thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
okay
gaming screen let's go
yeah
okay
[Music]
she just said like excitingly excitingly
that she has snacks
and I was like am I a joke to you
I was muted yeah yeah repeat that
hi
good I got snacks I have snacks I have
chocolate to eat our suffers
oh I uh I hope you're gonna have a good
time today go now
oh I'm gonna have a great time
yeah I'm a muted I'm a retweeted my
stream on Twitter um and she was like
kind of like hahaha
she should play the game too
yeah Watson play the game are you
watching this Watson
[Music]
big chicken well that's a day definitely
I am the chicken but
um
so I got a heart rate monitor for this
purpose and we tested it out before and
on when I played Alice it was like I was
mostly chill my chill heart rate was
like between 69 and like maximum 80. uh
I only only once I went up to
117 according to pulsoid and yeah nice
nice I know my heart rate is nice
um I was actually surprised because told
me that her heart rate even when resting
on the stream is already like around 100
that was that was I was nervous about
the stream yesterday though because of
the game so
I understand that I I get that I get
that feeling
um
well we're playing this today because
you have requested me to play this game
um but in exchange uh we we talked about
um you uh and me doing uh hadoke stream
together uh
afterwards right right yeah but I feel
like that's kind of like while Outlast
for me is a punishment
karaoke is for both of us I think more
of a reward
um so I need something better than that
I think
yeah do your work
ah wait I feel like I I got some
suggestions what how to
uh
chat Notch I cannot help oh and I have
them written down somewhere I think
actually
um
you guys and where are those ideas oh
[Music]
okay but yeah
about about the
about the Vengeance that I'm getting
uh yeah we will have to talk about that
again because I can't find my notes on
what to do with you
oh I'm reading the chat and I don't like
what they're saying
one of the ideas was
um for you to have uh for to have you
make a foot monument in Minecraft
foreign
[Music]
for the first time is that a thing
of the lucky but the lucky it can be oh
we can make it a thing oh okay okay okay
well
um I I want to say one more thing this
is some like I feel like the last horror
game that was supposedly the first one
that I played last year at Halloween the
Craven main or what's it called that can
almost not be considered a horror game
that was like really not that bad and
besides that the only other one I played
is phasmophobia so
uh please bear with me I'm not good with
this kind of genre I I have never even
seen a proper horror movie only maybe
seen glimpse of them glimpses of them
um so I'm quite sensitive when it comes
to the horror genre please be nice to me
chat and grew up especially you have to
be nice to me
of course I'm actually really proud and
very surprised that you decided to go
through with this all the way I don't
know why my heart rate is going up
already even though normally it's around
70. it always sounds like it's shaking
are you okay no I'm just not really
happy about this stream
um let's let's hope that the game will
be so great that I enjoy it very very
much and uh the being frightened of it
was all too still not necessary let's
let's hope it's that we will enjoy it
is very thankful that he is going to
bless them with your screams today
you have to consider that I I when I
played Minecraft in the early days I was
spooked out every time when my pickaxe
are so broke
oh that was a jump scare to me
I was like oh yeah oh every time
um so I am quite jumpy
um
yay yay that's a good perfect condition
to start with so I guess uh let's get
this [\h__\h] over with
um hello hi Callie
well uh yeah that's uh uh we'll get
through this and then I'll never ever
ever ever ever touch this game ever
again so
um well if you like it the new Outlast
that's coming out is actually
multiplayer so we can play it together
it's Co-op online
hey
I don't know good I don't know about
that I'll probably die today I mean okay
I guess that doesn't matter because I'm
a phoenix but uh please call uh one one
two if I die all of you all of you at
the same time call one one two uh
okay
it's the Audio I think the game audio
might be too low on the viewer's side is
that possible I want it to be pretty low
but okay I'll turn it up a little bit
and there we go it's a bit a bit higher
do I need it's right now it's just like
ah one one two is a European number
write it down write it write it down
guys uh is this is this okay guys sound
it's like right now it's just like Omnia
sounds or minions
sounds ominous ominous sounds I guess it
will be the worst later
um
uh let me erase
lower everything on my side on my
collection
oh
that's enough just checking if
everything's okay
I even had a phone call yesterday with
my mommy and and she gave me advice how
to get through the day but all of her
advice is I can't really use it because
it would be like me me spoiling myself
about the game and stuff and I was like
I can't do that you know because of my
that will not be a proper stream okay
anyway let's go uh this is a blind place
or going in blind huh yeah completely I
don't know what this [\h__\h] is about so
um I will read this uh text here
um you um
an investigative reporter whose ambition
is about to earn him an intimate tour of
Hell on Earth
that sounds about right uh always
willing to risk digging into the stories
know what a journalist would dare
investigate you will seek out the dark
secret at the heart of Mount massive
Asylum why
and stay alive
stay alive as long as you can record
everything I'm recording that's fine I'm
already recording uh you are not a
fighter oh [\h__\h] to navigate the horrors
of Mount massive and expose the truth
your only choices are to run hide or die
oh that's I mean actually a little bit
reassuring because I don't necessarily
want to play like I don't think I would
yet very far If This Were was about
fighting
running I'm quite good with
hiding
I don't know I was never good at hiding
once the ghost was like doing stuff okay
um um it's good practice then
um I
I don't know
[Music]
um
do I need to listen to this radio
and yeah what is he saying
camera okay I don't know how to ride a
car journalist that's fine it's an it's
in journalist mode it'll go by itself
okay uh wait sorry I have to move the
screen a little bit
[Music]
here alone that's such a stupid idea why
is this dude going here alone
journalism
Asylum
yeah I see
why are we here
to make history
wow is there someone in there that's
probably
up here
what is that the first jump scare over
there what am I doing I don't know maybe
I hate it when in cars the light is off
just always
okay
no no no that didn't scare me out it's
just like um
no no no no
uh you don't know me you have to make
this quick they might be monitoring I
did two weeks of software consult at
murkoff psychiat psychiatric systems
facilities in Mount massive all sorts of
neas I am very much breaking right now
but seriously [\h__\h] those guys yeah I
agree terrible things happening there
don't understand it don't believe half
the things I saw doctors talking about
dream therapy going too deep oh finding
something that had been waiting for them
in the mountain mountains are pretty
nice
um and very pretty aren't they
yeah people are being hurt and murkoff
is making money it needs to be exposed
okay I don't understand
batteries
and the camera
um
he's using people for content and we
must expose him oh will we always be in
this screen okay miles upstairs
subscribe
okay let's go wait you put down this
camera what was what what
cause you gotta switch in and out of
camera it looks like a witch's mansion
okay
containing your notes and and pick up
documents Jay do you remember those uh
oh my God
did it just close do you remember the
keys because I I don't I don't even okay
tab
does it matter does it even matter we
won't get far today hello
active what am I doing here
uh do I need to do something here I
don't know how these kind of games work
I don't understand I gotta get into the
big house okay
hello
[Music]
this is open
so open the door quickly press left
Mouse button to open the door slowly
what it was so fast what quickly why
would I open the door slowly why is
there two options
um and make sure you're quiet so you
don't alert the enemy oh but I didn't
read that wow how how how how do you do
slowly how do I don't know again I
actually don't know I always open it
really fast oh my God okay well that's
your camcorder yeah oh yeah why and you
can scroll with your mouse scroll wheel
and I'll zoom in and out yeah oh okay
nice um do I have to
um
recorded adding what what event I didn't
see anything
yeah when you use your camcorder you
will sometimes pick up notes when you
look through your camcorder screen
uh-huh yeah
wait press F oh there you go that's your
night vision that's night vision so you
can see in the dark
but also it drains your battery at the
top right you have two batteries and
whenever you uh switch in the night
vision mode it's gonna drain that oh God
oh God okay so I should generally not
use it continuously to hold down left
shift
oh we're going fast now
people Mount massive Asylum
hello
massive service
it's not open okay let's go home
oh no I guess we have to find another
way in no no no no no no no they don't
want me today I'm I'm gonna come another
day
that's that's unfortunate because the
gates are closed
oh no
all right left or right uh left the
joists
oh 100 100 BPM
oh baby
I know how to crouch I remember that
oh nice
I Don't Wanna Know
what what
I don't understand
why why why would anyone play horror
games like makes no sense to me usually
girls are crazy like you who played
those games with the camera zoom and
zoom out I have stuff
what it's exhilarating it's adrenaline
don't you like that is that does it look
terrifying
of course I'm terrified why would I not
be terrified I just looked over at you
and your face
I'm sorry I'm sorry yeah keep going with
me okay okay at least I have a nice
heart rate most of the time
asked you okay hello are they gonna like
come at me right away when I enter
no okay I'll warm you up to it don't
worry we'll kind of open it I thought it
was left ah there you go okay
okay
they don't want me go down
but they do
they're saving a special spot for you
with the asylum
for me yeah I have to play this game
I'll need it probably
oh wow what are they doing with the
music why are they doing that
jump
huh
High Court
do you hear the audio too good though
when I'm streaming Okay jump up first
transfer up up and down come on you
can't come on
can't jump that much
oh there you go yeah okay okay
so far so good
uh you're you said something about that
insane mode like when when you die then
you start over from all the beginning
where would I start when I die
oh you're gonna have Auto checkpoints as
you go so it's gonna be much nicer
[Music]
the light turned off the light turned
off
do I have a flashlight why do I have a
[\h__\h] flashlight
night vision
oh dear okay well that's a battery gone
that's fine
um one
one yeah you reloaded the batter it's
fine though
that's good
[Music]
okay
that's good wait what am I even looking
for
there you go
what what
like the meaning of this game why am I
here it makes no sense
you need people to know the truth about
the asylum
[Music]
come on the lights are on you're fine
it's a nice place
ah it's a nice place yeah
and books
when is it gonna happen girl when this
is when can you warn me one
you didn't warn me
I'm not supposed to worry about this
you're fine you're fine
it's so brave look at you're still going
I just wanted speed running
[Music]
papers what is it beeping I'll just do I
need to pick up the phone
oh who's the band blinking paper
like solve a riddle like actually use my
brain for this
okay
what
oh that's loud oh
[\h__\h]
foreign
up in the bank
I don't like eaters
do I go where the light is somewhere the
dark is yes that's the thing about this
game is it's gonna uh kind of let you
know where to go based on the light
always go towards the light oh really
okay yeah my hair done
yummy hurt something
okay
I guess I'm saving I saw someone running
I'm not alone
no
there's lots of friends in the Asylum
for you can you jump quieter
where where would I run where would I
hide when they run off
there's something there
it's a library it's always quiet in the
library
is
oh there's gonna be lockers you can jump
into okay
okay and you need to hide
[Applause]
myself
[Music]
you're fine
yeah that's a pretty bad one no that one
gets everybody
fine I'm not gonna sit here and feed you
when the jump scares are
unless you really want me to but
you good no
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
what do I look like go in there it's not
it's not like that
foreign
go in there
oh maybe nah you're fine
[\h__\h] is that light switch
no
foreign
[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h]
I think
there's somebody
hi you're good
he scripted he won't come after you that
one he went into his little room
he did it you made it to the library
[Music]
you okay
is
I will
yeah
what I said I will call an emergency
number if you need help
do I open this door I'm sweating oh my
God
this is okay this is a nice School
it's just a game it's just a game like
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
they're both weird
a possum a POS Apostle
a-p-o-s-t-l-e-ho okay yeah proclaim the
gospel new objectives Escape yes well
first you want to get in and now you
want to get out you stupid [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
idiot let's hold you you shouldn't go
into this building this is so stupid
like horror games are so stupid why
would you even go into a building like
this in the first place and alone it
just makes absolute no sense it's so
stupid that's why I don't play this kind
of games like jrpgs make much more sense
uh-huh but uh
I got something
the notes okay notes
he's dead so much for that
um okay
um where do I go we go where the light
is
yeah and there is a battery around here
I can tell you where it is I think
you're gonna need it um
if you're on your left side far left
corner our left corner of the entire
room I don't know where you're facing
anymore all right
straight yeah that way that way and then
there's a room on your left
you're good you're good I promise you
you're good
no you're fine you're fine
it's just right around
but it's in the toilet no no my little
blinky's hanging on the floor
ah yep nice it's covered in blood
that's fine feathers are used for the
infrared line what what I can't read
that quickly
I said do I have uh did I use two out of
10 batteries is that what it says to the
top right
uh well your your this one is dying but
um
[Music]
does it even open no okay we're going
this way we're going this way
let's go let's go oh girl I put you in
this chair and then I I will carry you
me it's over there
that's a friend
it's John he's alive
Hello friends but he's in the wheelchair
I'll be fine right he doesn't he can't
chase me that fast
yeah okay
I think
I think I got something in my throat
Library you haven't been there how
where's exit where is the exit
you shouldn't tell me that I don't want
to go any further do I go down or do I
go right and go down this hallway yeah
foreign
month wasn't it oh man
oh man
oh man witness oh is that gonna happen
to me cause I'm a witnesser
if you don't run fast enough then yeah
ah well I only have one um one speech to
Randall
this is like how you tell people
um to to hurry up when they're waiting
and they just want to wait faster
it doesn't work I can't run faster than
this
that this I mean
you know what I mean the logic behind I
think so
um there's another dead person there
security guard what this door is what
needs a key card okay I don't have one
oh
yeah
something coming here isn't there
maybe maybe Nan
okay
oh
I think you're safe in there I think
you'll be fine
are you a liar
I don't think so okay
okay because you said so I believe you I
just
I think do you choke on YouTube
it's just because I cried a little and
uh in the last jump scare and yeah
and when I cry I have no
stuff in my throat
hahaha and I feel bad now I didn't know
you were gonna cry
okay I got what I needed from that room
right there's no more
I feel like I picked something up
you picked up some notes or maybe try
the other door as well in here
okay
the one behind you hey I'm behind
it's on it's on your right hey
oh nice
what is this
I don't know I don't remember if this
really does or goes anywhere oh maybe it
was just okay exit
I bet you can't get out of it though all
right so I didn't go for that or uh
that's the last door I guess that's a a
choice right now for me
um
[Music]
for me
who are some people we didn't choose
this
all right let's find my key card okay
okay I think it's something it's the uh
other side of the okay
yeah okay
oh no actually I think we had to explore
the lobby a little bit more so yeah okay
okay
right I don't remember what it is maybe
that dude over there has the key card
maybe oh no yeah yeah you gotta go
through the uh computer room so I think
it's the one on the right I don't know
how much you want me to tell you though
on the right on the right uh over there
oh and you can go in there
wonderful oh there is a table right in
front of it okay
this is not good for the electricity
bill all the PCS around and no one's
using them
gonna be expensive isn't it
did they activate Windows though
haha
they must be sorry they must resist
activating Windows big big advice from
my side even have if you have a key
sneaky
oh real old batteries
oh was I even supposed to do that I
think I think I was dying okay
cool
okay uh
Island
I don't see much oh I don't see much
um
is there anything here a key card mostly
most
Mars
I don't have much battery
show yourself
it's not that dark you don't need your
flash in here yeah I don't see you Mr
Randall yeah no I didn't miss it I just
uh
okay
[Music]
jump scare hello
oh I see notes
confidential no not anymore
now it belonged to me
I feel a jump scare incoming I feel it I
feel it I feel it I feel it
oh stop breathing so loudly yep miles is
a loud mouth breather it scares me every
time
why is the game telling me now to pick
is there something to see ultimate
sneaky
we got to get that key card so you can
get to the security room and open the
door okay you're good it'll be fine but
if I close my eyes ah should I close
them wait I can always just close my
eyes right just close my eyes I mean
yeah you you yeah yeah
there's nothing there even if I peek
okay our wheelchair friend is here
that's it oh wait
wait a wheelchair
will he attacked me no
he's chilling oh hello
oh okay okay we're good
oh whatever time I say something like
that there there's a jump scare coming
every time
every time where I'm like oh let's go
why are we going to
five
he's chilling all
good
what do you want me to say am I just
supposed to walk past him yes bad idea
bad idea better oh
I'll get you some Burger King you look
like you need some food I'll go grab you
some Burger King if you show me where
the exit is I'm sure you know where the
exit is right I really recommend to you
the crispy chicken
um and the Oreo shake Oreo shake is
really good really good remember her
Shake
Oreo shake
oh my okay
oh [\h__\h] there's a lot of people here oh
ah our favorite Channel a white noise
with a little bit of a color a beautiful
color
watch in the Stream oh you gotta go
through there oh okay uh Hello nice to
meet you and
uh how's it going
um how's it going what's what's on TV
today
these guys are chill I promise you
oh he's got no fingers oh okay I feel
the tension is uh
[Music]
if I ever meet you
oh
okay okay door
that boy's got your key card now go get
it okay but he's dead
can you not open the door like that
oh my God hello
uh that is a nice painting I I was
thinking of getting more paintings for
my apartment like I need more decoration
or maybe I can bring that home that's
actually really calming yeah nice it's
very Serene beautiful
[Music]
good bye bye
uh where do we go do I have to walk the
whole way back
or will someone teleport me over there
nice no I would be ready okay
um
so this is gonna be the same work pack
right no nothing uh out of the ordinary
would happen
yeah these guys are busy watching the
stream they won't they won't bother you
all right
my mom said that when you watch the TV
for too long your eyes are gonna turn
into a uh into the square yeah
that's like when you make funny faces if
you make you just take your tongue out
like that it's gonna get stuck
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
he just wanted some help he was really
interested in your offer of crispy
chicken all right
that's it
she was really into that offer he said
yes Dental please
um yeah
uh on the right down the hallway yeah
you know whenever these things happen I
look over to you and you're just like
quietly laughing your ass off it's
yeah
is that is this this is so funny funny I
think this is funny I love this
wonderful and
that's funny and okay it's a little
funny hello
oh do I really want to see what's going
on there
day alive
without you well I I will take this time
to point out that there are lockers in
this room for a reason
okay
um I will already hide this
oh yeah at least good idea here we go
preemptively hide right it's not gonna
happen is it
as long as you know how to hide
okay
the next part is going to be scripted so
okay you gotta push the button which oh
I play hacker man
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't try to fight okay yeah that's a
good idea
um
is someone coming to pick me up mommy
please call me Mommy
him
oh my God he's so much
yeah what if I was trying to go out
instead of hiding in the locker he'll
rip your throat out
no no oh my God
oh
is that why is he not wearing pants is
that his uh
wrinkly big let's take a look if you
want
you guys helmet
oh nice I got some evidence
bye-bye
is it am I am I good
and here's his chain still
I think I'll wait a little bit
I think you're good now
what did he do
through the door
I said was he just looking for me
specifically
yeah he could smell you
the guy on the camera why I thought he
was somewhat nice
it's so dark now could I know the
monitors are off
um
where do I go well now now we have to
turn the lights back on so we gotta
restart the generator in the basement
basement here yes you're in the right
direction
you're doing so good I didn't think we
were gonna get this far but
wow it's really dark I'm gaming
I guess I gotta go down
yeah
oh they have a gaming and crying let's
go I have a leak here
and take a shower
oh
watch all that gamer sweat off
scared
nothing can get you here around this
area the basement yeah then uh in this
room specifically once you leave now you
are able to get grabbed so remember
where this little hole is because that's
that is your safety broom in there don't
pass past this point
yes once you get past this crevice okay
thank you for letting me know that I'm
about to die thank you it's good to know
I the first time I played this I died
many times here oh
okay
hmm
so this should be fun no okay
so Vault press space what's vaulting
moving towards waist high objects what
what what well it's parkour I didn't
read it what was the button face Pie
Face bar Facebook oh no that's just
jumping okay I know what I don't want
[Music]
hardcore back to this place is that what
you're telling me
oh God oh God oh God I know it's gonna
happen I know it's going to happen oh
yeah
who's there
I'm not here I'm not here why would you
tell them
we gotta go push some buttons we gotta
push buttons and then pull a lever this
will be fun cool lever push button pull
lever push button
until I do that probably thinking
logically
um
okay
good music music the music yes
for me
okay there's rooms along the right and
the left side that you need to push I
would start on the right side and work
your way around right right side right
side right side
ah
yeah
you're making me nervous now because I
don't know where he is
my batteries I don't have more batteries
go go inside here you're right you're
ready
wait wait wait wait wait okay you can
hide under the bed all right you see the
bend yeah you can hide under the bed
there okay
okay
else
you can
push that button you see that thing is
blinking yellow right there
behind you what's behind me
get out from under the bed no
yes that thing you see okay okay but
that's your first button when I push
that is
someone's gonna come
uh maybe probably okay under the bed and
I'm okay
okay
oh who's dark
Maureen
oh
[Music]
you got me no
oh now he's busting to the door
hello
hello oh I see something there
oh he's coming no I'm not here oh
I am not here okay I am not here
she says on the Mega Ball oh
I don't think you should find you he
might I don't know does he wiggle okay
we're fine
but he was gonna grab you
okay he's gone
my heart is Doki Doki in the game I'm am
I good to go out
I think I'm good to go I think so are
you wearing headphones yeah I am okay
because you gotta listen for him another
one
all right
your next problem is gonna be on your
left so we gotta go left side
it's not there anything oh my God
you might be able to sneak around if you
uh Crouch around I don't know how strong
his
I don't know how close you have to be
from since you
coming
she's coming
oh is this like a like a circle that
he's gonna be repeating all the time
like he like time wise like every let's
say every 20 seconds he's gonna make his
Circle or is it only when he sees me
like a little bit or when I act out
he's you're actually I think you're
right he's probably on a he's probably
on a circuit oh
[Music]
it's just a [\h__\h] game
that's the spirit but also Crouch don't
be scared to crouch your end
okay he's taking the other door in
what is he gonna open it for me
yeah
thank you can I go
you can peek out a little more and see
where he's going
wait what's up
[\h__\h] I don't see anything
it's dark
is he in there that's the next room you
want to go in on your left
is there a hiding
[Music]
foreign
I'm sorry it scares me too
[Laughter]
yeah you little chicken
um just a little bit
there is oh
okay
no no no no now there's a big lever we
have to find okay
where's um
you know I don't remember it's in one of
the rooms we haven't been in yet
yes
can he go away
he's walking away
oh yeah he's in the water now we're good
where do I go
I think it's
uh there on your far right did you see
where that light's coming from in there
yeah it was if you peek out
and then on your right the light source
that there
no right there
yep
well this piece there
how do I get up there do I have to go
like around
you can you can go around
do I have more batteries
no no
I don't yeah that's your last
okay that's fine
what what did I do and we're gonna die
at my destined to die
no you're good not yet but you're gonna
have to run uh I'll
are you ready to run no no
direction now
um
once you leave this room go straight
go straight yeah you'll be good oh good
you really remembered as well
I know I played this one a lot so I
forget I Leave the Room
is that is that is the exit the exit of
the road is like like here I think maybe
but
um
hey
go go
back
oh my cats are meowing because they're
so scared for me I'm okay
I said Mama
okay
um I still need to pull a leather right
yeah you gotta go back in
um but this is a safety room okay which
is good you bet you got a battery I
didn't even see that that's nice the
eyes
okay
all right okay where are you do you know
where the lever is yes
you were in the right wait I need Dr
Pepper okay
I just saw something blinking you know I
was like that's that's it that's it that
must be something to pick up
oh perfect okay okay okay where did we
go
yeah over there again back into the dark
room yes
[Music]
uh
yes
yeah okay I I think it's on I don't know
I'd have to see where the light we want
to go in the room that the light is
coming out of I don't know if that's on
your left you're right
where is he what the [\h__\h]
I think he's on your right he's on your
own
wait I wait until the sound is
um
silent it's sound but I think it just
stopped
to look around
yeah it's not moving I think
don't worry maybe he reset
take a peek
no
you can do it he's moving again
and that's the way you want to go over
there oh [\h__\h] yeah into that room
is there some stairs I see some stairs
okay yeah okay
well is there a hiding room
you're good
okay
go left left
oh
okay okay this is fine this is fine
Locker don't go oh wait there's another
way out of this there's a bed I need to
hide a little bit um hi
uh Doki Doki
oh this is his circle of walking around
uh include this room I wonder
um
I hear his footsteps yeah
look now he's in the water I see him
swimming again I hear him swim again is
there something in his room
I don't think so I think you
'll eat it I think you got it that was a
loud noise so what was that
what was that
I don't know
whatever
there's no leather in this room right so
no this is
you gotta go out okay into the hallway
and then go straight oh wait hold my the
one was uh not the water right
straight and then straight yeah hop over
that thingy
wait am I safe here again is he not
gonna follow me after here again again
anymore
uh I don't know
well there's another place to hide oh is
that a battery weight left oh
nice nice
although he did pull me out last time
right here
and then right right okay yeah
what
oh wait oh there we go oh God okay nice
level
okay what happens
better probably is there a closet I'm
scared okay now it's coming more Berry
I'm gaming
is there someone coming
you haven't died yet either that's
incredible oh my God oh my
oh my God
okay yeah I hear him he's gonna come in
and do his Loop his silly little NPC
Loop because you're cute
I'm cute yeah
there's a okay
so oh you know when you first entered
that big water room yeah there was that
stand with the big button in the middle
the red button yes that's the last
button you have to push oh to turn the
lights on okay okay yes and then uh he's
probably when I push that he's gonna
come after me again
even mine okay oh oh he's opening
up the heaven
he did he just open the closet or
something because it sounded like it
he's definitely here right now
are you leaving or what
I don't hear him anymore
I think he's
gone
oh yeah okay so when I go out of this
room
um I go
you know which direction
no I don't remember okay we have to go
out and over the table thingy and then
okay there might be a shortcut shortcut
yeah I think I saw a shirt
though hello
out the door
I think you can go straight
thank you
no I don't know why he was right there
is he coming oh God he's coming oh God
don't open don't open
I'm looking at the other one don't look
in the other one don't look don't don't
look lightning doesn't okay
he's leaving
wow wait I want Cali what
okay around the locker game time
it's go time baby
so close still though I think
is he
I heard
are those your footsteps or his
I don't see him now come on let's go
I'm on a mission
[Music]
okay okay
okay but he opened this one the last
time
oh no oh no oh god oh is this like he
always opens the one where you're not in
um
I have really bad luck with that because
he usually opens the one that I'm in um
he just wants to see you literally just
have to run around him
I say it might be smarter just to tank
the hit and then run past him push the
button and then get out
I think you can do that
fantastic if I
I feel like my direction sense will be
uh
um
I I can try and help
be spawn camping he is absolutely spunky
okay go down we're gonna run past him
time the game go let's go take that hit
baby I'm out of battery soon though
he's gonna smack you
but you're gonna push that button okay
[Applause]
tell us the way out
uh
you pushed all the buttons we didn't
restart you
huh
um
erase what do you mean what you mean I
have to do all this again
I don't have to push the buttons again
maybe you can speed run it all the
buttons I have to push all the buttons
again come on
let's push all the buttons again maybe
oh that's a little bit mean don't you
think
a little bit but now we know that you
know how to dodge him now for the most
part
push the button I don't know nice
okay
um
I don't know if I can be this careful
again I'm like I'm not I'm not there
did you stay running I don't know
where to start where to start
uh all right start on the right side we
go right the rear first room is on the
right first room on the right right he's
not he's not inside yet so it's good
okay
you should be fine I don't like this
sound all right
yeah
save to go hmm safe
yes this first room yes
he's not inside yet you're fine okay
okay okay I think he enters once you hit
the first button okay
um nice uh oh wasn't there real bad over
here too was that no different for him
I'll just where's the button here
okay
and blocker time
please don't open this one sir wait so
not open is he coming
is he gonna come yeah
he's gonna check out
what I did
you mind waiting to run by him maybe
oh
uh I can't water sounds
he coming oh oh God are you coming is
the game always making that sound
whenever oh yeah whenever I'm in a
dangerous situation
probably yeah how nice of the game to
let me know oh he opened one
I think he always only opens one
don't don't do this one are you leaving
okay
okay thank you
baby we're next
yes the next one
over there
no no no it's closer on your right side
holes on my right side here yeah uh-huh
you didn't see me
nice
are you still gonna do a left turn
I think he went into the room that you
want to go into okay
for a moment
well at least he's opening the door for
me like a gentleman because I suppose
before that it wasn't even open
hmm okay then we have it it's just a
gentleman boom
very kind of him I think he's
still inside
I hope he's gonna do a left turn after
that
hello sir when are you coming out
come on out buddy gentleman
oh yeah you're good there he is oh okay
here goes over there all right all right
all right all right
does he react to the sound if I just
walk normally for this water
I don't think so okay
he's preoccupied all right battery
battery
button button button button check
nice nice bed
chick all right baby
nothing can't hear me nothing can scare
me nothing gets scary come at me bro
[Music]
I'm here
showing my camera to before where you
said no more to the right yes okay now
the light the lighted room
he was that a shoehorn
or a bat
that I think it looks like a bad blood
he's carrying
go outside already
all right get out of here buddy actually
sometimes it looks like a katana to me
oh my God he had a katana where we get
one of those slice it's okay okay he's
gone
I'm leaving he's back in the water
and now now we move
oh God
I'm not gonna come here are you
come on
left left
[Music]
oh yes wait a second
okay that's fine is it fine
yes right choice it's good oh okay okay
okay
I lost my orientation
all right
okay
let's go back in at least at least we
didn't get caught did he hit me
yeah
but your heel back up oh really okay
okay uh we need another button right it
was not the under the lever okay now
we're on the lever
hello
[Music]
go back to where you came from [\h__\h]
get out of here get out of here
somebody said when you get scared they
hear a clucking sound like a chicken
good now I didn't say that somebody
I was getting a shark okay so be careful
what you say you were what I was
skinning a shark I was skinning bloop
alive
oh
what
what wait when were you doing that did
you not see my uh my pump did you not
see like the photos or anything from my
pumpkin carving screen
is it an actual shirt
I would never what the [\h__\h] no no no I
was skinning bloop
oh my God you scared me it's like a real
sharks
bloop enjoyed it he had a good time I
think hmm yeah shaving off his his
Summer Skin ready for winter you'll
you're definitely carved pumpkins before
didn't you yeah
[Applause]
he's not gonna come over to decide
unless he sees me right
um right I think
okay
um
good I'm scared
um so we go up and then we go to that
Lit Up room again
yes
oh that one that one yeah yeah
all right where is the guy now though
that's the problem
he might be in there
in the water
uh
oh I hear bees
he's
I think he's in one of the rooms
oh no he's not he's in the water oh
okay
oh I went where I want to go
yes okay after he comes out there I'm
gonna go
okay
is he gonna see me from here
no you shouldn't see it from here it'll
be fine he's opening a locker I'm not in
there buddy
you're like at the wrong place hey
come on
Phoenix in there come on how far how
long is this game go down how far am I
um
finish it is that six percent six seven
six percent yeah this game is long
yes
oh there he is so he's going that way oh
oh okay he's here in the middle
uh should we wait until he goes to the
right side over there
yeah okay
now would be a bad time
to move
is he still there I don't know
oh that was in the water
oh oh god oh
[Music]
snap but he's is he gonna notice me
got him oh okay now
I'll go
[Applause]
okay right right yeah let me go on left
hold on straight line
straight
no I was alive all right leave a battery
there though yeah
I'm scared
okay uh okay
I gotta hide
um
I feel like
it's coming soon
oh
and was that too early
you're good
is there a button in this room
no oh it's it's further down the hallway
okay um
he's in the water you can go out okay
yeah yeah
and then down the right
straight down the hallway
he always was like waiting for me wasn't
he okay
battery you get a battery is there a
button here no
I'm not further down
and then right okay yeah this is the
delivery room
[Music]
okay
we're back here this is the run baby
uh is he gonna come for me uh what which
one maybe this one
oh it's got it
a little bit
um what if he opens this one
uh run okay
okay great
but now since we took right to coming
into here now we should take a left okay
okay
oh maybe one left and one right
please no please no please no please no
please no
oh
Hallelujah ah
it keeps on opening the other one where
I'm not in
that's very lucky
oh
okay he's walking out
okay I think
we're good
okay um
now he'll be spawn camping it's just not
fair
we go out but here I go right and then I
go left
now you go straight and then you go left
okay
you gonna parkour and then he might be
there and just take the hit and then go
left
here left
okay
and then right okay
all right yeah
[Music]
surprise
ready
[Laughter]
okay that's fine
yeah
sure okay
[Music]
okay okay he was there he was there I
left okay now yes yes okay now go
all right I'm running a big big
one
yes this one this one this one this one
great and then left yes
okay stop
oh
hey
we did it good yeah
guys in this Asylum you must have been
here a lot
uh I don't know about it for whatever
reasons
oh wow we don't have to meet that guy
anymore Julie
um oh
all right um finally out of there though
that makes me happy
I still what's what's all right we want
to go out so
right what's next
um
tap um tab will tell you a return to the
security control ah unlock the main
doors secured
a security control is right here okay
well
I guess
we shall go there I haven't been here
before
Oh easy it's easy
um
oh have you saved your game do you want
to continue this game I don't know if
you're gonna oh saving it never mind it
auto saves you're good yeah never mind
I definitely saved up to the point where
I pulled uh to did the last
thing right and the blaster
okay we're hacking into the gate again
yes it's gonna
oh
[Music]
give you the waxing concoction
Sun not boy is this my father there's so
much
oh
um that's what I'm here for for
witnessing yeah oh
is that my friends
Believers what the hell
the gospel
wow wow sweet dreams tender okay
um
beautiful
uh I can't believe this is only like
seven percent of the game or ten percent
maybe something like that that's so
terrifying
why does it take him so long to get out
of here oh my God why am I in a prison
cell now that's not good I wanted to go
no
oh it's like a Kush
everyone well you can't hurt yourself
nice
time to stay in here no
yes quiet he did not kill his enemies
rest in peace thank you remember that
notes are only added to your notebook
when your camcorder is raised to record
events all
oh okay well oh my God
what he put me in there and now he lets
me out
he's at freed om your buddy lets you out
this is so [\h__\h] up Kuda
the guy's on the bottom floor friendly
they won't hurt you oh
maybe I might push you but that's it
take them together we would be stronger
you should just uh
oh yeah oh hello
we're gonna shake hands is this an idol
handshake event
oh my what an idol you are
beautiful
oh what did you
yeah
oh
what did you say she on
dude I feel like he said you shouldn't
have Shield what did she do
who's this
and they're naked by the way you're
naked yo hey can I show this on stream
uh I don't know I didn't see anything in
particular but those are a lot of naked
people so they have uh the the winner
worst not here do they have the one the
winner
how did anyone stream this game
um how do you do this
I think it's just dark enough that they
don't see too much oh great
great schools on the ground note
just naked too oh dear the the
bernardina the Vina versus
oh boy
that you can't oh that hurt oh he keeps
on doing that oh man that's messed up
you can't just walk against the wall if
you're not a ghost
okay
oh geez oh my
God oh good you even you were scared
that was that thing
is
at least he's wearing clothes
all right this room was open but am I
supposed to look for these rooms
uh I I I don't remember I know there's a
way out somehow I didn't we didn't see
anything it's too too pixely we don't
see anything we say no
no
wieners
what was that what was that look did you
touch me don't touch me
my opposed to you
I think there's a way to
parkour somehow
yeah I think that might be one of the
rooms who's that
can pick up pet bottom
parking lot B
uh
maybe one of the darker rooms there's a
darker rooms
oh nice
oh
oh that looks like I can go for it
um someone is like getting tortured or
something
ah no problem
um
what oh
okay I need my hands for that
sick
[Music]
she's having a nice conversation can I
go up um you're sick you're sick
all right
okay oh you're not here to attack me or
another naked guy oh
no all right oh I know that something
gotten it was good that I was recording
I guess I
am okay I'm nice
he called me friend and then he ran away
good uh I know do I look scary
no well
maybe a game you do
um I'm a cat what's scary about the cat
huh nothing
that's like cool I'm back in this room
I'm only oh yeah now I parkour
okay I saw a naked guy don't look at
naked guys get on the ledge just move
towards it okay no no no
no no no oh
come on
sorry Google
I fell down
oh how dare you
[Laughter]
um
no this time I'm not scared of you
not this time
nice try
okay don't look at me no no no no no I
don't wanna no no no no no no no no
no no no
no
please please don't don't
that's the biggest jump scare
hiding the yabs
wait until I finish
you what do you say for me to save some
some dessert
pasta tonight after the stream what kind
of pasta
oh just some simple really simple one
with like socks that I already have but
I'm in a
weird elevator
an alien room
I'm using the camera right so much maybe
but
that's okay I'm not oh battery I'm not
planning to finish this game anyway so
all right I'm just gonna use up all my
batteries now
so far
I'm here you're doing this so well I
okay I was not expecting us to get past
the uh the button room yeah that was
tough that was a bit tough you only died
once yeah how many times I died to that
the first time but you didn't have such
a great supporter as I have I guess
almost a drink
down the train
the train
you okay
wait no no I don't think he's okay I
wanted to switch there we go
this is uh interesting
drink this is right there should I go is
he telling me to go down the drain
maybe follow the blood
really oh yeah
this story is not accessible
okay down the train
down the drain
the train
oh there's an Open Door there
closing doors behind you will slow your
pursuers ah yeah I haven't really done
that until now why you
what
good I heard footsteps
are they yours no glad you're awfully
quiet
I don't remember what happens here
[Music]
I don't should I close that adorable
there where's the camera cool you can
um
uh you can go in time
maybe two doors Two Doors
left or right
oh it says Exit here but I don't trust
it
um
I guess maybe try this what the blood
leads over no well
there's these footsteps which are not
mine
and then move away from them go to the
right side then
failing
um
it's always
you remember this
kind of yeah now I can't remember
is someone's struggling we're gonna help
him
hello there's your locker over there oh
oh that's fleshy oh
oh
foreign
killed someone
maybe there's
if we need a key card for the elevator
or the the room right here this one I
don't I don't remember I'll try the
other way then yeah this way
[Music]
I smash
oh it's just a dark room
hello
oh sometimes like his own steps are kind
of delayed and it freaks me out
there's nothing here
no
stop yelling
audio stop oh hello
audio stock scream
is this this is bad for me to hide on
there later oh yeah it seems so remember
this bed I don't know if that will
really help me though can I huh it works
I mean we have our own rituals at kfp I
understand that it's understandable what
kind of rituals
#world hashtag yolk
what kind of stuff
which they follow which I make them
follow it
when necessary why is why is there
nothing in this room I don't understand
I I guess you have to go to the other
room then and then run here me I guess
yeah it's a good place to hide there
okay all right then oh I know what you
have to do I remember it's a hella
cracky mate
crikey why then challenge me I'll change
you use tackle Gouda
oh there's no one happened here oh hello
what up oh hi
I know
I just want to get by you buddy
stupid I'm here look at me
I think we want to get by him and then
there should be a uh
a room okay
oh
um he doesn't give a [\h__\h] he might not I
don't remember
I think it's at the end of that hallway
down there
ah
I just at the end of the hallway
um let's see your hand stays there
avoid contamination
no what
um I'm just gonna um
I think it's cool okay
oh oh nice boy he reminds me of the guy
in the water
yeah
I think he's chilling
oh yeah he's very chill I mean if we
just look past the point that he just
killed someone then then he's really
chill
I'm gonna be the next
yeah
yeah yeah yay
all right open the
security window Securities oh okay
[Music]
we wanna run you can't do anything to me
nice I'm sorry
somebody got under the bed as well
yeah
[Music]
um
all the way back go back to where it was
okay okay
there's a button oh yeah yellow button
on the table yeah
yeah yeah yeah
such a cooker I've been trying to be
nice to everyone
this is why this is fine this is
we did it oh
yeah I feel like I'm close to dying but
I'm safe
I think that other dude distracted him
thank you for not ratting me out is that
how you say that in English
where I am good good good good man good
man
okay so where are they now
I don't know but the button that you
pushed yeah uh it opened up the like the
weird uh golden foil room nice
elevator looking room so I should go
again
yes okay
should be right on this side
oh
all right what does he do to me
decontaminate oh
what no what did you say
oh I'll naked guys again
[Music]
I only like my witness with ketchup or I
don't know maybe some mustard but with
those yeah different yeah
please no please no um
you can't even look over there
and maybe you have to go by I don't
oh there's a window you have to get
up you can strafe left or right oh
straight straight what does that mean
yeah
um
I guess I'll go right well done
No One's Gonna
just grab my legs and pull me down and
eat me
maybe do I go all the way over here Ah
that's that's how I get past
nice oh they're gone
there's another elevator this one's
broken
okay
all right oh what I'm feeling confident
yeah very confident showers oh no this
is a key card
oh yeah
um I don't I don't I don't like this
this is a blood shower for a lot for all
I know
but first we need a key card
um also somebody asked how tencho's
doing I think she's doing really really
really really well yeah I didn't think I
would do so well either like the first
part was pretty tough but now I'm
getting a little bit used to it
in general I'm not really up for that uh
if you just
see that they ripped off his head he
tore it right off that that was the big
big big boy
that came out for me two ones it's
coming for you
don't worry I'll quit the game before he
can come for me oh
picked up the key card to access the
shower room is that really a smart idea
why is this this main character so
stupid huh
go off
huh I don't know why are you scared why
are you scared because I don't remember
what happens here
wait a second why is this uh
where's the okay I lost Direction since
we're just School
yeah it's out here and then
went to the showers
okay okay
um
um do you remember now
yes okay
should I well be uh yeah or should I
brace myself
no I think it's fine
shower room
don't stay in the shower oh
[Music]
oh I don't know how to help you
you know what they did say something
about closing doors to slow someone down
but like I I feel like I would slow
myself down too I'm gonna keep that one
but I guess that was about the other
room
um
makes it fruit what do you mean what do
you mean exit for the showers
what do you mean is this a shower
um I'm scared yeah
this one
oh look look at the windows
they look open
a lot of they could be used as exits
something's gonna happen
oh
man
[Music]
wow
what
um what
what happened
uh were they there
yeah
okay they were like right in front of
the window or what
I was supposed to wait until they're
done talking
um or was I just not supposed to go for
the window
um
ah
yes
okay
do I want to go down
pull this belly open you're talking and
throwing some nice dirty talk but
um
no in the really dirty way like uh
bloody dirty way murderous way yeah
so can I go today
yeah I think so I'm gonna just fall down
why can't we
can't wait upstairs
I don't know miles is very smart
I would take the broken uh legs broken
legs so I can take them to crawl crawl
outside
yes I still don't understand why I died
in that moment
uh the guys are probably right there oh
and they slit your belly open oh [\h__\h]
and they ate all your intestines oh [\h__\h]
okay nothing here
opened oh
yeah
[Music]
I
uh
it shows this way
oh
what's this
okay we're gonna die the headset just
died gonna do oh
no no no you gotta listen to this too
oh yeah
uh-huh security for this room again do I
want to go here hello
no
walkers
I don't I don't uh
I don't see a locker
a locker that's bad I don't know just
for hiding you know
yeah being aware of my surroundings is
there anything to pick up your button
button
[Music]
we
maybe we can go up up
Oh you mean up to the vent
maybe Follow The Line perhaps
smart move Buddha you're a smart cookie
or do we want to go oh
Papa
I don't know
no he can't fit he's too fake
do I drop down here yeah
really
I'm not
um
the showers
oh this part oh I would like throw the
camera out the window and then just
accept my face
it's really dark here
wait what the [\h__\h]
okay we gotta get up the stairs
um he's gonna walk past here
[Music]
it's another one of those
Circle guys
who walk around the whole time waiting
for me yeah
oh there he is
now you can go I don't know where
uh I'm opening stairs okay
yeah
you see
um
is he coming up too
okay guys okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
come on
I don't think I'm gonna die
you're mine
um
um uh
uh maybe maybe behind him maybe behind
him
yeah
you mean run around him
yeah because I think none of the dead
end am I not I think I'm maybe
okay that's okay that's okay
it's funny when a dead end really
becomes the place where you're you end
up dead
just a poetic if it fulfills the
prophecy I guess yeah
um
I forgot the controls girl
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
nice nice
okay nice
if I could
slap good slap
good good good good good stuff okay
um
I can't believe if I'm playing this game
for two hours almost
good job wow
I can't go into the shower so I guess
I'm going for here
I hate that one that one got me so bad
what is the matter with you sir
what is your problem I'm just just
trying to
what is this battle arena what Jose I
think this is the arena oh my god oh
yeah oh what
um
who wants to battle me oh okay
yeah
I think he's coming up on me
uh what's he gonna do though right bomb
India
what
I think this is more parkour time so I
let it go up okay up and around
can you stop following me I don't really
like uh being followed like that
okay he can't do that can he
says
nice
[Applause]
man
[Music]
oh
okay okay so jump from a little forward
and perspace
it's in here
nice I feel so sorry for these people
I'm so sorry we gotta go even higher
right or should I look what's up here oh
there's an I wouldn't remember this
probably do we need this Molina
I don't I don't know I don't think so
it's very calm right now okay
quiet nice
oh okay
yeah that's why yeah that's what is my
ways
yes
okay okay
[Music]
let me go let me go let me go
nice
isn't this a great place to be comfy and
cozy oh my God a big hurts
you okay bunny
yeah
we could just stay here I mean No One's
Gonna I think this is like the safest
place to be in this Asylum because it's
like so hard to enter Because yeah I
would say this game too
No One's Gonna
well maybe they'll come find you I don't
know
all right let's change the batteries
right now not that splitting we're gonna
get Chase when our batteries are
emptying again
all right do I go down here yeah oh are
you sure glad that's where the blood
goes to
follow the blind
I think so
you're one of those dance protagonists
aren't you what did you call me
thanks
people often call me dense
um
yeah no I'm pretty uh
okay I'll follow this yeah like what
what I mean but we don't have a choice
we try to solve the game the real dance
protagonist is this literal dense
protagonist
yeah it's not us we're just trying to
Zoom for a game oh no but that's a lot
of blood
um
that is what you call a blood bath
yummy but that's where the line is so I
suppose I gotta go there
yes
um
Walla Rider
who is
I hear footsteps
and they're yours maybe they are is that
a spine on the floor but what
is
kind of get that one replace my own
oh can I chew on it what is this it's a
pool
did you see that too
what was that oh the grabbing bug looks
like a shark though like a shark never
seen that before
[Music]
I go through here
why is it so dark
are these fire
like since when is there fire
okay you sound like you don't really
know what's happening at this point
anymore in the game no I don't I don't
remember like this way is that a door
next to you yeah maybe oh it's just
Locker
okay
they are streaming Sparks
thank you well well thanks to you guys
streaming Sparks you reached 2 million
thank you
okay this is dirty as hell
you you you you you
I don't like this screeching music
oh
oh I'm gonna regret laughing in the
moment I think maybe
stop stop oh is this another one of
those safe ones where I can run back to
it and they won't reach
I think so
all right hello finally
wow progress girl
oh
um
I disappeared
I can come back is that okay is it
because of uh
we know because of you
I'm gonna
I need my mental support Shack I need I
need hello oh wait I don't see you yet
in my back
no
no not yet
um
go around come back Mario girl
Mario
is it because of me it might be because
of me but you see me
uh no I don't see oh okay wait maybe one
second
one second the possible let me
find myself
uh let me
go now what's your favorite number
11. all right
wait let me uh
hold on
I'll do this oh
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
what did you do
we started ah
all right
[Music]
you know God I gotta say I was a little
bit worried about having you as my
support shock today
what why because I thought that uh
you're not gonna be much support
[Laughter]
but are you so far so
uh you've been extremely helpful
dang I don't know you were like I've
I've heard reports that you were getting
excited about me suffering today
yeah and I mean that doesn't sound like
someone who would want me who would want
to help me
oh wow it never really laugh that you
were
mislead you in a scary game
what was that he had like some stance
coming after him
stink stank or like fire maybe it wasn't
science
sir the spirit of the stinks tank is
coming after you
he went that way okay I'll go where the
light is
is follow the light
oh yeah excuse me
uh weird noises coming from there
there's not es but I have a bad feeling
pop around and blind really bad feeling
really bad feeling
ah really really not good oh there we go
we gotta go here I feel something so
filming
I'm In the Air Tonight
oh what is okay
oh wait wait a safe area again maybe
maybe yeah essentially potentially
potentially okay wow wow I can't believe
that that was an okay area lower
Junction Flash The Water by turning the
two valves
um
yay what why do I need to do that
maybe because that we got
because we gotta go down there and
there's too much water okay
oh
he's coming
again
time for Big Boy
how did you disappear so quickly
I don't know maybe he took a he went
down one of the hallways Maybe
but they still battle
me continue continuing on and on maybe
we have to follow the orange pipe and
the yellow pipe oh
it has a valve then we gotta turn okay
okay
follow this this yellow one
about the music is over
oh he was like nope
and he was like nope
I'm not gonna diet for this [\h__\h]
because that's what he said
I'm not gonna change myself for you I am
beautiful the way I am I don't need to
eat less Burgers now I agree with that
you eat what you want that's fine yeah
eat burger every day at least if they're
from KFC then then I support your choice
only best food that KFC what is this
place
that's the right way it's one of the
Bells okay okay can he go for here
yeah but he can't go through that okay
oh my god
oh that looks almost like it's light
from outside
oh nice nice
I know
okay okay
chill buddy okay
sorry for disturbing you sir
sorry
maybe we should try the orange pipe
because he seems to be guarding the
yellow one yeah why
I don't know all right I don't know
where's the orange
must be the smell of
you
yeah what was that
I smell like gravy I mean I get it
I understand he's hungry he hasn't had a
good Gravy Sauce in a long long time and
Thanksgiving 's coming up after
Halloween so we won't start crying
sweet Phoenix gravy nice
oh oh that's a dream oh
oh
one valve down is there like some secret
battery or so you know
really nothing oh but the lockers oh
wait is it gonna come is
he going to come I don't know he might
come because that's been the way it was
up until now those people are really
stupid though like they come after me to
check out what happened in the room but
they don't turn the these things back
the way they were before
Locker
um oh oh he's going for the other one
you shouldn't open
are you done
oh my god I've never seen him do that
though that's interesting he opened two
but not the one where I wasn't
oh boy
oh boy I'm so lucky
all right God this game destroys me oh
yeah
I'm
I'm a big chicken
uh
to be quite honest with you uh
I think I'm gonna have some troubles
going back though
well uh
you go back and then
he's right there
to the other side okay okay let's follow
him
stealth mission
hello oh sir
oh God I haven't had a bad feeling
oh don't go we just wait I just did he
go that way
we're back to the beginning
yes
okay
uh
like which I forgot which one is a
yellow play here uh
uh yeah yeah yeah
oh nice
quick quick go through that hole
right we're going for the hole right yes
but last time he was waiting on that
side I don't know see where he is
okay
I hear
him but I don't know shouldn't be too
close now he stopped
so you can slide to the hole on the
right
huh oh that one oh
oh okay
thank you Goda you're so smart what
would I do without you I would be dead
uh I don't know I don't know I would
have given up a long time ago I think I
think I wouldn't have been able to clear
the the first like the the the the the
button level in the water before I
wouldn't have done that without you
I don't wanna go out here he's gonna be
waiting
yeah
you have enough time to squeeze through
yeah he's not there
yeah I don't see [\h__\h] oh okay
[Music]
oh he's so mad oh he's like an ogre he's
so [\h__\h] older where's he going
this is he gonna come here
yeah
[Music]
can't come here
no what noise
and now you can go down the ladder
ladder oh that okay okay okay so first
we go through here again
see oh he he saw me
uh
oh no okay no he didn't but why did the
battle music suddenly turned on
uh the protagonist is about to have a
freaking heart attack
come on come on
[Music]
oh wow oh wow
[Applause]
I I thought I was safe
I did not know okay all I want to do is
uh go down the ladder and then I think
I'm done for today because we didn't get
a reset right the letter is right
it should be where am I right there
straight ahead right here yeah yeah yeah
yeah
uh ah oh my god oh thank God he actually
they brought me to a nice place because
I wanted to go back here very helpful
tactical disc
he ripped out my arm
your arm or your throat that it felt it
looked like it was my maybe it was my
throat oh my God that's more terrifying
that's very terrible oh my god that hurt
my head I didn't know he could pull you
off of a tube
well the more you know are you planning
on playing on this game again at some
point
um I don't know I want to play number
two though uh the second game sequel
yeah Outlast two yeah oh
ah well because I don't remember that
one at all I said I said um wait did you
ever play Outlast until the end in your
stream
oh last year I finished oh you finished
it properly nice could I respect wow
I've been for today we're gonna leave it
here I think I've proven myself two
hours and 17 minutes of horror game and
one of the most horrible horror games
there are apparently so I mean I think I
did pretty well wouldn't you say
yes you did so I was expecting a 45
minute Stream So the fact that you did
two hours
it's incredible after a while I kind of
got like used to it weirdly like it I
was I was immersed but in a way that I
could think logically and be like
this isn't even that scary I his name uh
when I played I think what the game like
blows out your adrenaline you get so
scared and then your brain kind of shuts
off and then you know and then you just
turn into Focus mode because you're so
numb from it you're like okay ah okay ah
okay
I guess it's also like uh
tires the body out to be like jump
scared a couple times yeah and you're
not even you don't even have the energy
anymore to be scared your brain is
screaming but your body's like blue yeah
thank you for being here with me
um thank you for like kind of like
pushing me to do again do something like
this I mean I mean I I I hope we can
play other
um games that are more cute and and
happy
but aren't you doing a fast mode after
this
I'm not sure I wanted to read a couple
super chats because I've been behind um
and I wanted to eat dinner and tomorrow
I think I'm kind of busy so I don't even
I don't even think I have time for fast
Mo okay yeah sorry you gotta hunt down
those ghosts on your own you're doing it
in VR right
I think Inna and I are gonna try it in
VR oh my God yeah well you kind of lost
yourself up here with Outlast support
yeah I gotta say I am playing all the
scary games day after day the past few
days is kind of really tired me out
Halloween week is quite tiring I chose
some games that are pretty kind at least
like Alice and tomorrow I'm playing
little nightmares have you played that
before uh no I haven't oh but I should
be good I watched it on my play a little
bit of number two so I heard it's so so
pretty scary even though or creepy even
though it doesn't like from what I've
seen it looks kind of cute but I'm not
sure
should I be scared to chant I hope it's
not gonna be I mean it can't be worth
in in case and scariness level than
Outlast right off all right father says
little nightmares is amazing and not too
scary there we go oh Father were you uh
watching me uh be a chicken with Gouda
thank you
we should all play Animal Crossing
together oh that's cute yeah what is it
is the the update is coming in beginning
of November or when was that November
5th oh so soon wait that's next week
and I should schedule Animal Crossing
for next week already haven't been on my
Island in a million years and my Island
looks like pretty basic what about you
good or do we have an island yeah mine's
also pretty Bare Bones wait did you
scream Animal Crossing before
no no
well it's about time
streaming Animal Crossing is if you get
some people over to your Island they're
gonna shower you in prison
I've got so many presents and money I
told them to bring me money to pay off
that stupid stupid loan from that Tanuki
you asked kfp to bring you money yeah
they were more than willing to do it
it's been a long time
don't pay my loan so I'm gonna have you
guys bring me some more items and money
next week then wait aren't you supposed
to pay them as their employer no good
you don't understand the system of kfp
there's a salary but the only person who
gets really paid is me like they they
pay me a salary
oh you must be new here could I uh yeah
sorry guys
I don't mean to question your ways I uh
huh that's why I also um I approve every
salary raise because it's basically a
salary raise for me
my [\h__\h] isn't it
I don't think I should ask too many
questions I think it could get me in
trouble here oh don't worry
you are allowed to ask questions the
employee is not so much they will be
brought to the usual room have you ever
seen my usual room
oh oh I want to show you one second I
don't know is it an animal crossing uh
no no no no it's here I don't know if
it's you gotta watch it on YouTube for
that one moment
um is it your office where you read the
super chats no no that's my office I
have a usual room
I don't know what it'll look like if we
jump over there right now though let's
see
[Music]
ah
oops what oops I made you too big
hi uh yeah you see this
I've never seen this before what
is this
well you see it for example on the right
hand side we have a stretching massage
table stretching in a good way of course
and uh
wait what if this looks like something
at a Resident Evil
the days this is
a brain massage uh a therapy uh object
the speakers all over the room are there
to remind you to watch only Kiara
there's a Lego pieces all over the floor
um so that you always step on Legos
there's a uh hear these massage chairs
are really nice um you can please ignore
that that little hand uh reaching out
and they're just uh
um enjoying the therapy there and on the
screens you will continuously have my
songs repeating and my streams repeating
and
I thought the usual room is a funny meme
I didn't know it was an actual girl you
gotta take those things seriously when
it when it's about kfb the snow joking
it's all serious
wow I am impressed and slightly
terrified
oh by the way everyone is uh there might
be like two seats there but uh it's
actually every usual room is
um like a you can only be there alone
this you see this kind of portal there
whenever I send someone to a usual room
there's like infinite amount of usual
rooms and you're gonna be sent to one
that's like
um kind of like I idealized to you like
like you the user room will recognize
what you're most scared of and then it
will implement it in the usual room to
give you the most accurate therapy
um so that will get the best effect out
of it and of course this is all just
basically like uh
um holiday a vacation torture no
vacation
let's go brainwash these kfp employees
to think this is a vacation I mean
there's a lot of volunteers every now
and then who just want to come here I
don't understand anymore but yeah anyway
there's no escape and I decide how long
they're going to be in here so they
better be good chickens my chickens why
am I doing
you wouldn't make me sitting here right
like that that would be you oh well if
you were you helped me out a lot today
so I guess you're
you're fine for now for now
for now oh it's it's if you ever feel
like you gotta be like alone and get
your mind off of work this is maybe a
good place to be
okay if you uh
if you forget
to collab with takanasi Kiara for too
long I will bring you here and remind
you to hashtag VOC hashtag yolk
hey do you still have the game audio
feeding through the screen right now
because this is oddly fitting and I'm
not really sure how I feel about it
yes yes I do it's a good vibe isn't it
hey you guys are weird over here
let's just know though this room doesn't
really exist though let's uh
um let me go over to my office
well oh thank you
my cats and my frog and all that kind of
stuff
this is nice I like this this is comfy
all right I can finally give you a tour
of my office here wait a second spooky I
wanna uh I would like you to take a look
at the bottom right
Casper
wait for it
wait for it waiting wait for it
oh it's gonna take a while wait for it
ah
YouTube delay
lady
they use the bottle right right yeah
did he do the thing you should have seen
it
say what
do you know you're watching on YouTube
right
bye that was a ghost did you not see the
ghost no oh
I don't see ghosts though maybe only icy
ghosts maybe maybe I see ghosts
now and maybe in three seconds one two
three now do you see it bottom right
the mouse
[Music]
oh dear
but I'm not even sure myself
uh I don't know if I'd like to be around
with these two kitties around and then
they might make you all
right
[Music]
I polarized her when she was in Japan
oh nobody's talking about that
nice feeling
different chocolates even though that's
toxic for me but it didn't kill me
unfortunate I see she tried to poison me
and she was
she was Emily but she wasn't able to
kill me
so now your spirit's gonna haunt her for
the rest of her life
[Music]
well Casper I just saw the usual room so
I think you're onto something here buddy
[Music]
oh dear
you are brainwashed
um and have a lot of fun with the
patients
[Laughter]
sorry
did you have a nice conversation with my
ghost pet
oh man I don't know I don't know what
kind of circus you're right in here
gaming with you though today yeah I'm
great thank you at least now people
can't annoy me anymore for a while about
playing horror games so thank you for
that but now you gave them a taste of it
and now they're probably gonna want even
more yeah not for now not not until next
year's Halloween
a new outlet it'll play Outlast two or
whatever next year then or three oh if
there's a is Aaron free already
it's coming oh well at least good eyes
happy about that I'm I'm fine without it
but oh thank you thank you thank you uh
to the audience for uh bearing with the
scaredy cat chicken that I am
it's fun you did really good if you're
not uh satisfied yet with spoopiness
feel free to watch the girls play fasmo
in a little bit I think it starts in
like one and a half hours
right yeah probably
yeah yeah I'm gonna read some super
chats now so I'm gonna say goodbye to
you good now thank you so
much okay thank you
oh Halloween collab
ah yes see you then no
no we want to say bye-bye
[Music]
have a nice day
yes oh God such a good turkey okay
I'm alone
bye bye oh there she goes all right I
got my my chair to myself again
ah Casper there's your spook my guest
Casper Matt Casper
you talk so much
just make sure to not tell her any
secrets company secrets about the usual
women's stuff uh-huh all right
hmm
let me close the game save and exit
and go yes
okay
okay all right that was that did you
guys enjoy that
I'm actually pretty feeling pretty
alright
um
I'm good
I'm fine it was uh
I was really not looking forward to this
stream slash game like I was I actually
took a nap before the stream sorry I did
it again but I
um
I woke up before the stream and I was
like I don't want to do this I don't
want to do this I don't want to do this
I was really so not looking forward to
this pretty pretty mad at myself for
even thinking about doing this
uh you did great really you did great at
the end yeah yeah I ended up being uh
quite chill around the end
um
everything turned out great well yeah
I think uh it was it was okay I mean
it was stressful now and then but yeah
at least at least the scary times will
always very short-lived moments that
ended pretty quickly
all the time yeah proud of you thank you
well at least I finally did you guys
really wanted me to play a horror game
for so long and I didn't really want to
do it
and yeah but I I guess I'm
um I'm okay with having it uh having
done it I hope I don't have to censor
anything of the stream though
there were a few uh -huh sausages there
not the not the yummy kind no
do you guys know that uh Vena is like a
specific type of sausage
you guys know that
I we
whenever I like talk to someone about
like the cuisine in Germany slash or
straight Australia
uh like especially when I talk to
Japanese people about it they're like ah
sausages and and uh and beer
and I mean yeah we have
good and a big variety of sausages but
that's not all that's that's by far not
all we have like and we don't I don't
even eat sausages like ever except when
I if if I were to grill with my family
or so then I would probably uh eat some
sausages but otherwise no celebrating
Oktoberfest
um
no
I I didn't even really realize that
something was going on I don't know when
exactly I think the thing about
Oktoberfest was that it's not actually
happening in October was that it so
either it's about to happen or it
already ended
or or it didn't happen at all I don't
know uh I'm sure there's a lot of
sausages at Oktoberfest
anyway so uh I don't know
I just wanted to this is a weird topic
because you guys make it so weird but I
just wanted to
um
never mind I'm just not gonna no
will you play Outlast again
um not particularly planning on it
anytime soon
uh
let me put on some bgm though
um why do we want to hear
what do you want to hear
oh I'm so hungry
what's this
[Music]
this app the Outlast It Feels So
relieving
so brightening oh
ain't it yeah
[Music]
well I I I hope you guys are proud of me
because I'm kind of proud of myself for
doing this
um playing this game
pretty proud of myself
initial
I'm really proud really thank you I know
a lot of you guys were really worried
for me and and and
um I was worried for myself too but it
it seems like I can take more than I
think I can
I can handle more than I I thought I
could apparently
that's good to know I guess but like I
ah I thought unfortunately I will have
to disappoint you I don't think I'm
gonna dab my dabble dab dab dabble much
more in this genre unless there's like a
specific good reason or like uh
event happening
yum no um
[Music]
let's read some super chats I
have to finish those member super chats
from some member stream right was it was
it among us
no it was a talking stream afterwards
right
there was this members only talking
stream
[Music]
and then uh I skipped a stream that I
already read I think oh my stomach just
said oh
what's cute
my cats when I scream did you hear that
meowing they were meowing so loud at
least this movie was
so cute how they were here about me
but it doesn't help much because they
don't know how to call uh 9-1-1 and even
if they did I don't even know even know
if 9-1-1 works so uh
and we stay they react to me suffering
so cute
Mama Mama are you okay they said Good
Girls movie yeah
so cute all right
um scrolling I'm scrolling we're gonna
try to read as many as possible but I
kind of have on Sunday after that music
video release of my song cover
a kind of pebble Super Chat reading
stream planned anyway so it's okay if we
don't get too far I think
hello scroll I'm scrolling can you load
in some more Super chats please
hello I know there must be uh
I'm sure yeah there you go that took you
a lot of time to load
next please
this is so slow thank you guys for all
the support today thank you
thank you
my cat checked on me when I was coughing
out water I drank the wrong way it came
right up and patted my land lagging me
out that's so cute
that's so cute oh that's adorable
I
I am surprisingly calm I kind of wanted
to participate in that phasmophobia
stream as well
um
kind of if I could but
um I don't want to uh
like stress myself out now and uh yeah
I'm kind of sick of phasmophobia
so I'm not gonna be part of that but I
did my part of
horror games today my share
yeah I need to
try to force myself to self to sleep
early today
somewhat early at least
I am still scrolling where is that
member stream where was that
where is that there it is okay I found
it
come on a bit more proud of you thank
you
gotta learn the game first to have fun I
guess so but like I wouldn't have time
to do the tutorial now anyway right
before that stream unless I stopped
immediately right now
and then ate something and did the
tutorial and all that
I mean I I was like I said that even if
I were to participate I was not gonna
stream it but just like because I don't
think we need like every point of view
again for fastbo I wouldn't have been
streaming it I would just be like in in
voice chat
[Music]
um
I don't know
I wonder if everyone else is
participating because there were some
other participants who were like up in
the air kind of
yeah
um
I think does it start at midnight for me
yeah yeah
it does start at midnight
laugh at them
you did feel great so it's understand
there's a new update oh yeah are they
gonna play the new update oh no are they
I'm not sure wait I mean you have to is
that like optional it's it's not is it
is that a difficulty
that you know fast moving what's up
is that an option
take a rest yeah my week is already so
packed I should take a rest
thank you
two scary games in one day well I mean
forgotten news
to the the way that the scariness of
fast smells so
it's really only scary in that one
moment when they
um first come after you and then catch
you and then
yeah strangle you
it's not really that scary
but
yeah it's definitely more scary in VR
actually
so we were discussing about you know
having dysphasma collab and and uh
someone originally suggested how about
we played in VR and uh Ahmad was like
nope nope nope nope nope nope nope I'm
not playing this in VR this is way too
scary I don't like it
and I was surprised with that because I
never saw Ahmed as a type of person to
be so such a chicken and so scared but
because I didn't think of her in that
way I thought that like VR fastball must
be so freaking insanely scary
if even AMA says no
um
but today I found out that uh uh good
dad told me before the stream that um
yeah she doesn't like horror games and
she hasn't played out last yet and she's
you know not really
open to it either
doesn't like horror I never knew that I
thought I was the only one in myth who
doesn't like horror games
yeah
I mean finally someone who I can relate
to
I thought I was the only one
Adam is a chicken too she's just hiding
it yeah
she's hiding it well
but has she played horror games besides
FastMail on her Channel
because I don't know I just had this
image that she doesn't mind horror games
but now that I think of it she played
what
which one
I'm is worse than you dead space Dead
Space ah
is that like an FPS horror game
[Music]
a little nightmares is little nightmares
really that scary is that really
considered horror game am I gonna be
scared on on tomorrow
is it no it's not
no it's traumatizing it's a little
creepy it's not that scary not at all
probably not much okay
okay
I'm really curious about little
nightmares
I really don't know what to expect but I
know a lot of people love it
more creepy than scary games
sounds like you'll be okay
yeah
okay well then
I'm gonna be reading the members only
super chats I don't really have a
thumbnail uh but afterwards I'll put up
a thumbnail to show you guys where I am
when I'm done with those members no
chance okay so let's go let's get at
least a couple ones done kitchen
[Music]
this motion here can you send me that
that uh on Twitter can you send me that
the thing again
um
that uh thing with the pure thing
nice very reliable
let's say little nightmares doesn't get
your blood pumping all right but should
I wear the heart rate monitor anyway
tomorrow
should I do it
oh God I'm so hungry
yeah she died okay oh hungry oh I'm so
hungry
thank you I'm gonna oh my God hungry oh
my God my stomach
shush shush
shush
be quiet will ya
okay
sash
go get a snack
no I'm good I'm good I'm good
I'm good thank you
[Music]
Korean one I think because uh
oh there it is 50 000. ah wait that's a
pinky then that's it thank you for the
yeah take good care of yourself if
you're sick I'll send you to the usual
room today I was a baby chicken
veg what what
I don't understand that part
but um please uh do not send me to the
usual room I'm not going to the usual
room
[Music]
cannot be sent to the usual room
no no no it doesn't work that way
thank you what's up
tell us my G1 thank you for the pinky
thank you for the amazing Among Us
collab it was a lot of fun to watch very
glad to have attention who is willing to
organize these big Ian collabs thank you
thank you
it was fun it was fun to organize and
um it was definitely something that
stays in people's memories when they
think about maybe this year of whole
life English maybe on the at the end of
the year if people look back if the
girls look back on on their memories of
this year maybe one of them will say ah
Among Us was nice wasn't it
I will definitely
um look back at it that way
yeah it's easy and thank you for the
pinky as well
I think about some orange chicken from
my cold Foxhole at night what
I I miss your stream bus but I'll be
back oh wait oh wait
my my tank person
wait you can use your huh
you can use your
phone or like you know you have access
to an internet
[Music]
follow the end
bonjour
he was in a hole what does that mean
[Music]
it's not here now though right so what
would you be mobile phone oh
yeah we have a tank commander Among Us
a bunker
is there a reception in the bunker
oh man I don't know I hope he's not too
lonely I don't know that sounds lonely
being in a you know Place lying down but
I hope you're not so lonely
it's probably not gonna hear this is he
maybe some nice chicken will will give
him the time stamp
um
waiting for you to come back you know
like how in those in those movies the
romantic moment when
her wife's husband I mean we're not
married or anything we're just my pony
but you know when they come back and oh
it's always so beautiful so romantic
hahaha
so you gotta come back
thank you for the recipe and the pinky
profile feeling leaving dunk
finally I can support my ocean again
let's go he hosted and organized a
freaking amazing collab Kiana kfb had so
much fun watching you girls and I don't
regret it at all for staying until
almost 6 a.m oh you
awake you stayed up with me oh you
didn't have to
you don't you have like like things to
do like during the day are you okay are
you uh you fine
because that must be really tough if you
don't get any sleep because of me
um
yeah at least 6 a.m at least you went
better at least you went to bed earlier
than me
[Music]
oh 6 a.m though that's tough but thank
you for suffering together with me I'm
so sorry for you EU European gang
um I chose that time because I had to
pay attention to you know the other
participants and
um since you know I'm the only one in
this 3D time zone
uh I'm the one to suffer it's it just
makes sense however
[Music]
um like there's some other big lab in
the talks right now and
um they were gonna happen at like they
suggested to have it at like four or
five a.m and I said nah you guys can do
it without me then don't worry about me
um I just don't wanna
do this at this time anymore but don't
worry about me just don't don't feel the
need to adjust it for me but it seems
like we might do it like
at the morning early morning time for me
now
maybe like 8 A.M or 9 A.M I said that
would be okay I will try my best to get
up early or sleep early that's at least
better than staying up or getting up uh
until or at four or five a.m to do a
stream at that time which will be
inevitable next week for
the sports festival but yeah uh
yeah we will see
um I don't even know what that other
maker lab is going to happen or even
helping it's gonna be I don't know I
don't know I don't know I don't know I
don't know anything I don't know
anything at all I am Jon Snow
um yeah but if it's like morning time
for me uh like let's say
and I think I might consider this more
after for the future depending on if I
manage to get up and feel somewhat well
uh
let's see
let's say 8 A.M
8 A.M and EST is 2 A.M oh that's also
pretty bad but PSD
PSD would be 11 P.M
and jst would be 3pm so that's also
pretty good
um
EST would get [\h__\h] here
what about CST
one o'clock well
[Music]
no matter what that's that's not true
11 pm is decent
that's not bad
especially let's say if it's on a
weekend then like on a Friday night or
Saturday night I know there's always
people who need to work at the weekend
as well but you gotta think of it this
way there's always gonna be people who
who don't care about staying up late
whoever [\h__\h] schedule like me or
people who have different shifts like
like a home afternoon shift like that
starts at like 3 P.M I used to have a
shift that starts at 3 P.M staying up
late was never an issue to me
um
yeah there's you can't even even if you
choose let's say a good time zone for n
a with a stream that starts at I don't
know 7 P.M there's still people even in
an a that work at 7 pm because they have
the late shift and some jump so it's
never gonna win for everyone
it's impossible hmm
Outlets is trending on Twitter
[Music]
is that because of me and gura playing
this this game right now
funny
I guess
[Music]
you gotta go into these games with a
different mindset how I'm gonna go into
it with like a ass
it's a mindset
um
and then it's not that bad
noise
for both you and the most viewers yeah I
do I do try to
um
obviously I need to like think about
where my biggest audience is uh it only
makes sense right so
[Music]
but but
uh I will try to
fix my sleep schedule
um for the sake of myself
yeah
some people like me got rotating shifts
as well so there's no way to make it
work for everyone exactly
all right guys we have an archive except
excellent people
like a freaking drama if they can't
catch it live there's always an archive
guys
and I personally I prefer our guys
because I can adjust it too whenever I
want to watch it and whenever I want to
stop it whenever I want to go to the
idol meeting whenever I want to stop to
get some food whenever I want to stop to
take a nap whatever
um
yeah
why the hell not hello Bob gang by the
way are you watching this hello
[Music]
hello
we want to interact with you as well I
get there you know I understand
but when it doesn't work then it doesn't
work out and it is what it is
anyway wait a second where was I uh one
of the best moments was when the hell
thank you at the end your blush and I
bet you are so damn proud at that moment
what you should definitely be you're
amazing and can't you're amazing piano
and definitely the club Queen out there
Viva La Kiana thank you
that was um
I almost felt uh um a little bit bad
because it seemed like peer pressure
once one person said uh thank you to
Kiara everyone else afterwards had to
say it too
um
is but
[Music]
um yeah it was uh it did make me happy
to hear that
so directly at me
yeah I did soak it up
um thank you
James McPhee dinosaurs
and you guys are trying to finish this
rainbow huh
[Music]
thank you
Jacob's monkey dangashion huddle 1475
spankenheim
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
here's another layer for your Rainbow
typing with one hand because big cat is
sleeping on my arm
thanks for hilarious calabriel today see
this is this is the type of person I can
relate to not being able to move and
accept that rather than just moving uh
because your cat is like being clumpy at
that moment and cats sleep all freaking
day and they're comfy all freaking day
but still if your cat is currently
sleeping next to you or on you or
whatever in a position that if you move
is gonna disturb it and wake it up you
are not allowed to move
foreign
yes it's against the rule but I often
when I when I lay in bed and I'm like
cuddling with my cat but I feel like now
I want to sleep but before I sleep I
kind of want to you know go to another
meeting first and
but my cat is sleeping with my arm like
with her wrapped around my arm like I
don't know what to do at these moments
because if I go to an idol meeting the
cat is gonna wake up and who knows if
she's gonna cuddle around my arm again
if I come back
I mean it's difficult difficult decision
most difficult decisions I've ever made
in my whole life
from hashtag relatable the ultimate
dilemma yeah no no no no no no chat no
nope nope
CD thank you for the pinky thanks for
the clubhouse
thank you for watching and supporting
thank you
one of my Great accomplishments I would
say James McPhee thank you also for the
pinky coordination among kfp
what do you oh
why are you coordinating are you trying
to
make it rainbow again but it doesn't
work at all like free pinkies in a row
isn't contributing to a rainbow guys
you guys are not good at this
Daisy making with a pinky too
miraculously spending money I shouldn't
for a rainbow contribution let's go
daisy daisy daisy
you are so bad at this
it went red pink pink pink the last pink
was you and then after that comes
casbakes with a two dollar which is what
color this is not how it works
they all came at once oh damn
you gotta I don't know get together
coordinate via voice chat or something
ah a ghost chicken thank you cute
[Music]
oh man
oh man spanking time thank you but at
least that's you know what this is this
is team thinking yeah good job at least
for trying
to be a team
um
[Music]
for the red super chat start over for
real this time man what was that about
start over
it was about I don't remember what this
was about
[Music]
oh the rainbow
oh you guys are playing in my projects
little children chicks
ah thank you foreign
[Music]
yeah kfp is definitely struggling
cuties for all our employees to improve
employees success in the restaurant
watching them fail like this is
excruciating
give them some time they're trying to
learn okay they got chicken brains and
there's not much we can teach them with
a tutor
um so I think we just gotta hope that
the evolution will help them get bigger
brains with more capacity
[Music]
monkey dance chin
thank you soon thank you thank you
doctor can speak Spanish
[Music]
You're ending your Rainbow oh it did
turn out to be a rainbow by your own
hand in the end just with a big break in
between thank you
Sally fundia
foreign
[Music]
I see a Korean name and I was about to
go find out what it says by translating
it but your avatar My Dear Mr Ken
your avatar
you should every time we change those
names you might want to change your
avatar otherwise yeah I see who you are
you can't fool me
so I assume that this is a Korean name
means something like I am a cheat
[Music]
for this now big brain Kiana oh
absolutely oh I see you I see
I know exactly what you're trying to do
no no no
[Music]
if only I could read this basic Korean
now then I wouldn't even have to
translate it anyway
[Music]
I'll tell you the favor and I'll
translate it translate Korean
matakiano
I am magic King that I freaking know it
I know it
oh yeah
[Music]
and thank you for the pinky but you know
what I do think it's inspiring how
you're still trying to come up with new
ideas and original ways to fool me
because this one is a new one
so typhen says the Among Us collab was
amazing and I can only imagine how much
work that was for you thanks for doing
it and all the other things you do to
make us smile we truly do have the best
the absolute best thing to help you feel
better soon thank you
um
you make it sound like it was like
insane amount of work it wasn't that bad
I mean it's definitely more work than
just doing solo streams and or doing
one-on-one collab streams and organizing
that or for people collapse rooms or
whatever it's definitely more work than
that but it's all right it's all right
it's just like no one really takes the
initiative
um besides me I guess in Hobo and
sometimes I'mma does but but it's more
like a most of the time it's more like a
Polo myth
limited
initiative that she takes
which is fine which is totally fine even
like we need we need Ahmed we need
people like Ahmed to do these kind of
High effort mythical ABS
the collab that's coming up what that's
uh on my schedule without a time but I
think on other people's schedules it is
with a time and that one is again
extremely high effort
it might
[Music]
um it might even
be more hyped and
uh let me say it was difficult to say
it's pretty damn good
it's gonna be pretty good
it's definitely comparable to the half
year anniversary so I'm I'm just
astonished by
Amelia's motivation
and she just said that she just enjoys
doing this kind of
streams and being creative and I really
respect that it's really cool I'm glad
we have Emilia
Amelia is like
one of the most important
Five Pillars of Hollow myth but we are
all the most important
oh I mean one year I never say not
healthier yeah yeah
I didn't link anything for saying it's
going to be amazing which it will be and
which should be a given anyway if you
think about the fact that Amma is
organizing it then you can already say
it's a given that it's gonna be amazing
it's just natural
[Music]
um
yeah you're welcome to raise your
expectations you're welcome do it oh
puzzle piece oh [\h__\h] I forgot I should
have showed you earlier I only have one
left maybe I'll just show it tomorrow
because I only have one left should I
show it today or tomorrow
now there's like uh most of the people
already left
I guess I'll pick it up somewhere if
they want and they'll look for it should
I show it tomorrow tomorrow might be
better I'll try to show it tomorrow
before the Super Chat reading if I do a
super chat reading tomorrow
remind me
it's so difficult to remind me I know
it would have to be everyone spamming in
the chat because one comment only
usually doesn't catch my attention that
often
okay free sticky notes show it now and
tomorrow
oh I guess that's some I mean that's an
option but it doesn't really doesn't
really
have the same impact
ah what if I just show it now
I'll just show it now
well let me go get it
[Music]
okay last time I showed that that pink
one right so now I have one that doesn't
really show much at all
it is uh it makes you think what is this
where do I put it here
there we go can you uh can you clip that
out
I'm not gonna work for you guys
could um
there you go
that should be easy to cut out I don't
what could this be I see uh oh what do
you call that a devil's uh Trident
what is that
a fork
that was Trident AKA a fork
foreign
[Music]
piece isn't it
looks like you should or are they no
they should be in the right uh like
angle already so I guess that's all
right right side piece
okay I'm gonna should I keep it here I'm
people I guess I'll keep it until the
end of the Stream
maybe I'll put it
here
I've seen uh did I say it on Twitter on
Reddit I've seen someone post
um
like how many puzzle pieces they have so
far and like showed it all together and
you can already see quite a lot but
Kiana's face still seems to be a little
bit of a mystery
at least by the time that I saw that
tweet Kiana face
seems to still be in secret
or have has anyone showed Kiana puzzle
piece with my face yet because I haven't
seen one
well may and Bae haven't given us any
yet have they forgotten
[Music]
um
maybe they only have one or so and
they're about to show it
no face yet no Kiana face
the worst case if they completely forget
it they're probably just gonna upload it
on Twitter afterwards so keep your eyes
peeled mm-hmm
[Music]
oh no
um
would be very bright on brand for a
moment
crony games one this is my third puzzle
piece all right then continuing uh
Albert school thank you for the painting
thank you for all the hard work times
you'll love the collab yesterday and the
whole talk of apple is cute yeah
collab of Aqua Senpai on her Channel
um
next week it's happening
so I'm glad to talk to her again
he
I'm I'm really surprised that we ended
up being like such a match
yeah flare as well yeah foreign
[Music]
thank you Albert
King Christopher
I want to congratulate you on homotalk
and the Among Us collab apple is feeling
clearly very well in your care and was
fun and lovely you too were great
together and Among Us was hilarious so
many so many funny moments lots of fun
and no drama
[Music]
um I mean yeah I I thought the the whole
uh good at bullying was a little bit of
a drama but
[Music]
in I guess the best way in a good way uh
when you look back on it we will laugh
about it hopefully could have a laugh
about it too
wow
oh welcome back thank you for coming
back
it worked out in the end yeah I'm very
happy with it once again thank you so
much for the support thank you for
watching the collab and and supporting
me in my Endeavors
I will try to do more stuff like this in
the future thank you
for the pinky oh
last year on this day I caught Ustream
live for the first time a manga's collab
with fifth gen I can't [\h__\h] believe
it that I accidentally
scheduled the
Among Us Ian collab on the same day one
year later after the Among Us collab
with 5th gen that we did one year ago
I don't know how I did that I am in a
Time Loop
that was crazy
thank you for being here with all of us
carefully because of you kfv is a big
family full of like-minded people
swimming for Phoenix yeah it's a great
place to be isn't it
yeah that's a cool coincidence yeah you
did it twice yeah I did that was not the
only time we went full circle yeah
maybe it's destined to happen
um
[Music]
will it be a tradition I feel like now
it needs to be a tradition yeah
let's do it next year too
if if we can make it happen if I don't
forget about it you guys gotta remind me
write it down can't be sticky notes
Black Version thank you for the pinkies
cookies can I have you ever considered
using melatonin to go to sleep I use
them like 40 minutes to an hour before I
want to sleep
and that's the thing you get from the
Sun
and it always makes me drowsy and I'm a
tall dude so I'm sure it will work for
you I also can't sleep when I need to
and I I don't is that something you can
get without a prescription
hmm
Elon in the sun melatonin oh
I used a no prescription oh
over the counter whoa
yeah no I didn't consider it I don't
know I also I don't wanna like if it's
like a one-time only thing I guess I'm
okay with it but I don't want stuff like
that to be a regular thing I want to
take as as little medications as
possible
um
oh for now I'm fine maybe I mean I I
might struggle next week falling asleep
for you know what we should do a ring
foot Adventure stream before I go to
sleep just kidding no no no most likely
not going to happen nope
but uh actually
he's gonna take the day off and
I don't know what I'll do maybe I'll go
meet up with my friend and tire myself
out like that way maybe go shopping or
whatever just going outside to go to a
cafe even that tires me
every little step I take
tires me out
we can feel Adventure don't don't get no
no no no no
the one thing then is um you know I
wanted to do that in wealthy but then I
had to consider the fact that
if I wanted to do that I would need to
wear that VR helmet and you can't really
do workout without VR helmet and also I
can't carry the the ring set Adventure
uh controller thingy when I'm carrying
the VR controllers yeah so I need I need
like different
um
I don't know is there a head tracker
that you can just put on your head like
that on your forehead or something I
suppose there might be a way where you
don't have to actually wear the VR
helmet
it's like normal trackers I
assume there is that something like that
other body trackers and for the hands
like a Tracker that goes on your palm or
something I don't know
um I gotta investigate
track IR does head tracking without a
helmet oh
track either IR jack IR
V
hand tracking for gaming
what is this
how's the work
where do you put that
foreign
[Music]
since you already have index though you
could probably use a Tracker
um I'm sure Ava knows what to do if I
ask her thank you though thank you
thank you
foreign
[Music]
the whole Cali incident with her not
like really not directly giving herself
away but finally still giving herself
away
is just genius
her slip-ups weren't even necessarily
slip-flops but they worked out well
to incriminate her
so good
morning for
ah
uh yes uh that is uh
that is a pinky I think yeah
a bit about your sleeping it might be it
might be destroyed but instead of fixing
you might try to look into dry fasting
sleep schedule adapt your needs two
units might help of collapse what is
that three three fast exercise is it
like sleeping three times a day I can do
that that sounds like something I can do
it's just instead of sleeping one time
per day like long time you just take
free free simple naps throughout the day
is that it don't just don't sounds
horrific free short sleep fairies but oh
it really is that oh
transitioning to it really sucks but
people swear by it what
hey there's people who do that for like
the whole their whole life
after getting into it
I've heard it works three times two
hours
that's only no I can't do that it has to
be more three times maybe it's a six
hour
[Applause]
or like five hours five hours I think
that would work three times per day five
hours of sleep how much would I have
left of the day nine hours
it's enough
yeah 15 hours of sleep
in the end I end up with more sleep than
a normal person yeah
[Music]
can't sleep even more than that I don't
think cats are awake for nine hours per
day at least not my cats
I feel like kind of sorry for my cats
because like I mean
I guess everyone who has cats and goes
to work would experience the same thing
but I'm at home so I feel like even more
guilty
um like they sleep
so much I feel like I don't like
do enough stuff with them because I am
always occupied my streams are somewhat
long I mean this week they're all fairly
short
but I feel a bit bad like I want I wanna
like play with them more
my cat seems to sleep 20 hours a day but
the rest they are making my day
miserable what do you mean what no way
how
I thought cat slept 18 hours a day
yeah
something like that did you finish Tesla
Verizon no but um
I think after Halloween is over I will
have time next week I'll definitely make
time for it this week I was just not
really able to take a second day off and
Monday was honestly just uh
a day of doing stuff again so next week
I'll have the time yeah those owls yeah
I gotta find those owls too
um
where would you even fit it this week
yeah I mean my streams were fairly short
this week but still like for the pumpkin
for example I had to prepare before and
after
afterwards I had to clean
um
and yeah yeah clean the pumpkin stuff
clean my setup put it away throw it away
[Music]
I'm interested like it looks like the
style looks like something I would play
you can't sleep a lot because your face
is dreamy
bad not that good
aha did you find any recipes for seeds I
didn't do it yet yesterday I put them in
the fridge uh I was gonna do it though
maybe I'll do it afterwards like uh I I
saw that like I want to do I Wanna Do
The Salty ones so you you put put butter
of it and then salt and then I want to
do the other half I want to do um
I want to do with cinnamon [\h__\h] I wanted
to buy cinnamon today
because I don't have cinnamon
[Music]
in the fridge you're not gonna go off
that quickly right
the pumpkin seeds
someone had that cinnamon idea idea and
I thought it was genius they should be
good basically forever really even
before I roast them
that should be fine
they should be good for a few days okay
mine was on the fridge for three months
what
food will tell you it has gone bad
not always not always
[Music]
we'll see we will see about
you never know well maybe maybe they
have maybe they changed their mind
Someday I'm not gonna
push it or anything I have other games
that I have my eye on right now anyway
butter and salt are great for seeds
someone I mean that seems like the way
to go for most people but someone showed
me a picture and told me that they've
been eating it with cinnamon and uh
brown sugar and I have brown sugar at
home so I'm I'm almost ready to do it
but I don't know that sounds really good
because it reminds me
um it reminded me of
um those Christmas markets roasted
almonds I hope it tastes a little bit
like that because that is one of my
favorite things to eat at the Christmas
Market or it is my top one favorite
thing to eat roast it
wasn't out wait no not almonds huh
no yes some almonds
yeah I think um roasted almonds with
like sugar roasted sugar almonds
I don't know if they sell that over
there and your guys's Christmas markets
but here it's like a normal thing
so good
yeah they're kind of caramelized and
they're like super super uh super
um hard
crack
not really I mean it's just really hard
the surface is really hard because of
all the camera
so yummy oh I'm excited for Christmas
markets oh I hope there's gonna be one
close to me because I want to go every
freaking day
I think you know in Australia and and
Germany we have a [\h__\h] ton of Christmas
markets um so
I'm excited
if they're open this year oh they are I
heard news actually that they are gonna
be open this year
yesterday or so I saw an article that
said Christmas markets will be open this
year
[Music]
bye
we see
oh oh top five foods at Christmas Market
I don't know if I can do top five but
and number one and roasted almonds
number two chocolate coated strawberries
and other fruits number three
um
is Australian dessert
uh that is surprisingly really really
fitting to eat outside in the cold as a
snack
uh number four maybe I don't know what
else do you like that's that's pretty
much all I eat at Christmas markets
there's way more things I think but
there's that's pretty much what I eat
glue that and it's not that's not that's
not food but okay
where do you get catchment on the
Christmas walk I've never seen it before
are you from Germany or where because in
an Australian uh Christmas markets it's
a must
I even just saw it like oh the other day
uh when I went outside
I actually went outside unbelievable uh
like randomly not in the Christmas
Market just randomly in the city
I saw a little stand that was selling
hot fresh kaisersman outside that was so
close to getting it
so close
in Germany yeah that's that's very
unfortunate for you guys you're missing
out on something have you guys even wear
the Germans are there Germans in the
chat where are you have you ever eaten
um
[Music]
uh
mm-hmm
there's this word let me teach you
non-german speaking folk says this is
word that we use in Australia all the
time uh which is Gaia but in even though
we speak the same language if you use
this word in Germany it means horny but
if you use it here in Australia it means
just like you know it can also mean
horny but it mostly is you being used as
like awesome like if I say oh that's so
awesome I say oh this is so Kyle
but if I use that word in Germany then
they sometimes they give me red looks
um
thinking like the southern part of
Germany they might still use it in the
same way as we know in Australia a lot
of a lot of things are very similar in
in that uh what's the English name again
for Bayern uh Bavaria Bavaria
Bavaria is like the southern part of
Germany and uh they are in so many ways
so similar to us
in Australia
I like the bavarians
I like them and I like Munich
Munich is one of my favorite cities in
Germany oh my god when have I read my
last Super shut up another tangent for a
million years now
foreign
[Music]
thank you
30 minutes
[Music]
thank you for the I think that's a pinky
hey it's my first superchar I love you
yeah
[Music]
foreign
hello Almighty Phoenix thanks for
keeping me awake when I worked during
the night
as much as I enjoy seeing you having fun
during your streams I hope you don't
forget to take care of yourself see you
again in phasmophobia and later cheers
thank you
ah I do I do try to take care of myself
like recently I've been improving that I
would say
[Music]
um
yeah next week I actually have a
physical therapy appointment
um because my the doctor prescribed me a
physical therapy I think it's 10 one
hour sessions
I think next week is uh number one
yeah and the the good
for seems to be a one-on-one session I
used to do physical therapy uh before uh
a long time ago and back then it was not
a one-on-one session
it was in a group at least like like
there were Parts like there was a part
where I look at like something on my
back like a
kind of like a
um what's it called something greeny
mushy weird stuff on my back to heat it
up it was really hot
and then there was a massage so
obviously that's like only alone but
then the the actual part of like
exercising is um
uh was in a group and only like the
really bad cases where I guess
one-on-one but this time I'm getting a
more than one session
stretches I didn't do that I'm gonna do
that I'm after the stream
um I think today I'm gonna try this one
one
[Music]
the physical therapist is going to be
able to focus on me
but I have to get up early for that one
somewhat early
somewhat
I have it which day was it
did I not put it oh wait no no no not
the next week the week after
the week after that yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
not next
week I'll go
okay that was the earliest appointment
they could give me but I was surprised
that was actually pretty early I guess
um it's fine
eight thank you for the pinky for
whenever you start organizing the Ian
Mario Kart stream please consider
inviting the first member of Homelife
English hot summer
oh don't worry I've I've been
considering it yes yes yes but good came
to me with a funny idea today that I
have to discuss with her
she suggested a specific lineup for
Mario Kart collab to me
[Music]
we'll have to discuss that
uh I am speaking Patrick
and I remember that one I deleted that
message
[Music]
that's it for the members only
did reread did I read Fastenal super
chats at some point
I feel like I read them
she talked
good I talked about it oh you guys gonna
know about it oh
oh then I can talk more about my opinion
on that
uh so you guys do know about it huh you
know what to talk about okay okay so my
thought was okay the first part I had
when she wrote that to me I was like
yeah that sounds fun but then I I took a
moment to think about it and I realized
wait
so let me see Team if this is really
gonna be in teams
UMC team consists of
acquis and by the best Mario Kart player
in uh live
gouda and Ina who also one of the best
ones in all of English extremely decent
Ina is the best one
and I don't know about Marine but she's
probably good too
that's against uh whole Birds mume I
don't know how she drives Maya Clark
she's probably not that good I assume uh
Elena is uh maybe one of the best ones
in ide but still not that good
nobody said but I'm not sure about her
skills and mine are just decent so I'm
seeing a little bit of a unbalanced here
if you know what I mean I didn't
go to thought about it that much but if
it's four versus four
[Music]
um or anyone even even if another team
joins I feel like damn a little bit of
an advantage there
[Music]
I am
an animal but still compare that to
that's freaking alkalescent by Aqua
would
destroy us with Ina and go down when
that one-on-one Mario Kart stream that I
did with her a while ago it was only it
wasn't the whole stream but she was
there for a couple of races and she
always won against me too
um I mean only the one versus one when
when you guys came into the match
it wasn't that easy to wear anymore but
still
balanced
pretty unbalanced don't you think if
what I do think would be fun is like
just doing it anyway but but like
everyone against everyone just having
these participants but still everyone
against everyone
um
no no but that seems okay I mean but
still I mean we would know Aqua step I
would win
against the first place
no no way anyone is gonna be able to
be a good rival too
[Music]
no no no
no ideas
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
though I really don't know she
definitely participated in Mario Kart
matches before but I don't know if she
was good
Chicago
[Music]
maybe uh maybe maybe
we could give a cousin but a handicap
but no like even if we were to say like
she starts five seconds later than us
she knows the exact uh strategies to win
even even when she's like at the last
place that that actually only helps her
that would only help her if we let her
play if we're gonna start five or ten
seconds later she's still gonna win
that's like helping her Maddie who's a
good player yeah I can imagine her being
good too
um
there's clips of her wrapping in
another's face
hey really
hold on
can't use items oh yeah that would be a
good handicap but almost a little bit
too much
nah I mean it's it's I guess we can do
it anyway because it's just about you
know having a fun time together it just
doesn't seem like anyone has any chance
against Oculus and [\h__\h]
all right so I did Fast Mo apparently
it's almost midnight I took too much
time
why is there a Outlast Super Chat in the
middle of phasmophobia
Hiroshi
thank you thank you soon
[Music]
Alice Alice I didn't read did I
no no I'm so fine I can read a couple
more but it's just gonna
overlap with Fastenal which is a bit
unfortunate
I didn't okay let's try to read some
Alice super chess next week we're gonna
have a giveaway
for Alice
I mean the giveaway the stuff that we're
giving away is not really Alice related
but
it's from the Creator merchandise from
the Creator and it's gonna be like
pretty cute
I wouldn't mind getting one of those
oh basketball was moved oh dude a whole
hour
oh do they need more time well then
there you go that's good then I
definitely can't take part in it if it's
delayed for one hour
foreign
[Music]
okay
anyway let's try to finish the other
super chats and then um out of here
thank you soon what a nice Super Chat to
start off with
oh I know he said your brief stinks but
after you fired him this channel the guy
he started having a mental breakdown I'm
worried maybe you should reconsider it
slow
oh this is where it all started
and is this one at a time where people
are still not sure where to call me
because you call me colonel in this one
I know there was a time where I was kind
of like you guys can call me colonel
if you wanna
maybe 10 show was not so much a thing
yet back then huh
jfp origin now
flashbacks that's so nostalgic
[Music]
what a throwback yeah Albedo
Patrick
and tiara is still missing Crow dancing
ah about the crow
uh when people are remembering my Crow I
feel like
um
kind of like you know with with my owl
for example my owl was absolutely
absolutely useless this time in this
whole mission
and I feel like it I mean it makes sense
like to like not have my out to be
overpowered because it would be like I'm
using two characters
um it's just so far in my owl hasn't
been uh
dad's uh helpful in the game and
therefore I think I'll just have my
crown Crow be uh
like I mean Cali didn't really mention
it either anymore and I feel like it
would be weird to like bring it up now
uh
and uh
I don't know I don't know how
first of all I don't know how to
integrate it anymore I guess and uh
second of all I think it's probably Fair
more fairer if I only have one pet
um
um uh yeah has been useful in that uh
mentioned before the vampire
Mansion there uh who was kind of useful
but
uh a lot of times just disappears
for example with the hedges as well I
couldn't find U-Haul anymore so
it's like every time I need is not
available
yeah I understand that it might be too
op
P
um I definitely get that
yeah it makes it makes sense because
it's just a a thing that can fly and
like it's an animal that I can easily
communicate to with my animal Ken
it's it's too op I guess yeah but now
like if I if I if if uhu doesn't show up
for this whole mission which is what
happened then it makes no sense for me
to have like this whole animal can thing
about me either the whole me being able
to speak to my owl
is because I wanted to speak to my owl
so wow
but then then I might as well reskill
get that skill change
uh roll
okay all the radio
walkie-talkie for my all
did I just read oh
I'm sorry no I don't
think
I just feel like I I it would be like
asking for too much if I had two birds
as much as I would like to be the
ultimate bird lady with a million Birds
surrounding me
it just feels like
um
asking for too much you know
[Music]
yeah I mean I didn't use ammo candle for
something else too but
yeah it's besides that one time with
vato it's only been used to communicate
with my owl
hmm
anyway I think there's only one Mission
left anyway
uh let's see if we can get
to join that one
because I mean that's what my character
is about
those owls and birds
it's kind of like cristori
hmm
all the birds and Tiara's apartment are
dead by now
perhaps yeah
if you're jealous that she's like a
Countryside Noble in the modern world
yeah
that that is true a true uh description
but how is that an issue
hmm
can get ufu to drop Bay in for help what
what
do you mean like bring a rat and just
drop it in the middle of a battlefield
and
have the rat fight with us
what an idea
she's classy but she also acts like
she's from another planet yeah but I
feel like recently I haven't been able
to embody that that much but like in the
last session there was just not that
much talking you know from the
character's point of view it wasn't much
dialogue anyway so I feel like I've been
lacking why did I went up go down to 81
chill chill
there just wasn't much opportunity for
my character to speak so I felt like I
didn't really play her well
hmm that was mostly just like trying to
figure out weird riddles
oh anyway circles I've forgotten MC for
his tank engine
sorry okay I could see one day just wait
for me Jacob 47 I'll thank you
oh thank you symbolic Super Chat
it's not symbolic it's it's an actual
proper Super Chat well
thank you I'm glad you enjoyed the game
and CD thank you for the red wait that's
a rainbow rainbow
[Music]
no no no rgd rgd I want to say RGB and
turn that into RTD I don't know why I
said r-n-gd
I mixed too many words
when will we make the next kfp value
meal we got a
re-do the home menu
no I'm gonna probably do that before
um I do that burger cooking stream with
you guys so Jeannie says what a
wonderful day to celebrate my birthday
Jenny what's your birthday
two Kiana's dreams in a day thank you
for always spoiling us
thank you for always supporting us with
content your tangents are Stella are
playing horror games for viewers and
collapsing you're kind of considerate
welcoming to everyone I couldn't ask for
a better Ocean than you
I'm proud of you for taking a weekend
getaway it's good to see other places
it's refreshing yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
wanna travel more
[Music]
our Phoenix I imagine you transform into
a badass Phoenix like in the YouTube
clip Hollow myth versus Ina fan right
Innovation see I didn't watch that yet I
think I'm the only one who hasn't
watched that yet I listen homeless
should I watch it now
shouldn't
waste too much time it's short yeah I
haven't watched it I was like I had it
on a different Tab and I was like I'm
gonna watch this later
I didn't it's only two minutes all right
I guess let's watch it people have been
uh talking so much about it uh wait what
happened
I just went on YouTube
and I look at the phone there what the
[\h__\h]
was there ever the real thumbnail
what
what what since when is it broken is it
in the sub box is fine
really
someone is
the real phone number let me reset it
again one second
let me try to fix it
well it is the right thumbnail Here
YouTube please uh please uh
okay let's see does that fix it
no
what is this
come on
family got scared after the usual room
visit
[Music]
apparently it wasn't only me happened to
Mommy as well
oh wait now it's fixed okay
[Music]
now okay so what am I supposed to happen
again a Hollow myth fan made animation
[Music]
uh oh Foundation myth Breakers or pee Oh
and then for wow one hour ago so new
yeah
okay we're gonna have a live reaction
isn't that nice wait which one do I
watch
is this one fake credits
there's a no credit version I know that
should I just watch the one of the
credits
wait a second I'm gonna watch this next
last music music video only version here
should I watch that one
well I'll give you guys a link in case
you haven't watched it
is
[Music]
okay but uh what is the music that plays
in this video is it something original
from home uh myth song Violet I think
I'm allowed to play her song
because I mean I would be allowed to
sing it in a karaoke as well I think I'm
fine
okay I'm just gonna play it three or two
a one I'll go
[Music]
cute
foreign
[Music]
oh
oh my God don't make me cry
[Music]
oh
you gave me tears in my eyes that's
pretty good
those are the moments when I'm gonna
watch look that at that again
[Music]
our first collapsed with her mad face
and oh me without my hats
chest my
oh Christmas
I don't know what Ah that's is that me
uh in my first stream with Cali where I
went to her uh when I was like in her
room
[Music]
oh cute
again
I didn't know why why didn't you guys
say this is a different one it's the one
with credits a different one
[Music]
it looks like the same
hey which one do you mean
hola myth versus Eno
I hit
it I don't think I've seen that do you
mean that one I've seen I'm pretty sure
I saw it on Twitter
there's like so many though
what is there like
yeah I've seen that one
it was really cool
extended uh 17 hours ago extended
I'll mute this one for you guys though
it blew yeah it blew up on Twitter
is this the same one the extended one or
is this is this the same one as on
Twitter I wonder
link
there you go
okay free
two
one
go
be careful she's lost it I'm gonna voice
this now
free voice over by takanashikiana
I will try to restrain her good on Kiana
YouTube protect Watson until she's ready
for the worst
listen
Nina
laughs
Callie
I'm okay I can reach it
well that's me
yeah
I got you back Cali
all right let's do this
together
[Applause]
oh
wow we are so cool
my God it's so intense
fighter Immortals of this world shall be
dealt with later Kiana
was that who was that
those two have such high hope for you
you must be the real problem here
human
please stop this Cena
your friend is not here
oh
holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
oh my God
come on
let me help freestyle oh that's it
as bit as a new one oh
Ah that's good stuff good stuff
I feel like all of Hollow myth would be
totally down for like subbing this for
real
I think we would all do it totally
oh this person is actually uh oh wait
this person it's not the one who made it
he just added music to this video I
guess it's actually only on Twitter the
original huh
hello
on Twitter so far
no we should dub it when it's done
he evil enough
so cool
they will upload it once it's completed
oh okay okay okay
gotta tell this person that I would be
willing to sub it
yourself
this is a [\h__\h] badass man can't
believe what the fans do these days
so so amazing so skilled holy [\h__\h] yeah
I mean I mean
this is the only time when an anime is
actually the best when they're in a dub
in English rather than anything else
just you know I would normally watch
animes of Subs
don't like English dubs but hey here
English would be the original language
and our true voices
[Music]
for the membership
random spider GT thank you for the
rainbow again
Anton
um
random spy dancer and again wait I think
one of the first one was a Pinky wasn't
it
or even a red one I was a red a red one
and and a pinky thank you random spine
audio stock and then you apologize for
interrupting the rainbow
I think it's okay it's okay I don't
think GD is mad at you
does it ruin anime a bit for you know in
Japanese
that would be a little weird because
Japanese people speak Japanese too and
they don't they don't dislike anime just
got here how was Outlast
um quite um
stressful in the beginning but after
like that part with uh that first part
in like how do I describe that the one
with the three buttons or two buttons
and the levers in the water
uh after that
I definitely calmed down a lot overall
the beginning was rough the basement
section was rough but after that
I was good
um
oh I missed the stream and wanted to
check the box well it's still worth it I
think if you if you were planning on it
then I think you should still do it
Kiana's forgotten Fire Emblem Ria wrote
who is this
sending these super chats about things
that I have supposedly forgotten
who is this
show yourself now
[Music]
I have a feeling I know who it is is it
different people more than one person
I'm sure I know at least one of the
people or two even I
know it's kind of kfp chickens do this
kind of stuff
oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah there's a few
suspects two to three suspects that I
was doing this
but I love it yeah Fire Emblem
um
I would love to
like get back to it and play the real
Roots like on my private time
um
uh Rogan Striker Duncan Andy Captain
looking forward to seeing you in Detroit
this weekend Daniel thank you me too are
you gonna be there that's noise
on Halloween an event on Halloween
that sounded so stressful that I almost
turned it down
um but yeah we're doing it we're
squeezing it in there in between
I'm gonna squeeze it in can I miss you
in New York
oh Mister can you change your name again
ah New York you mean uh
you mean this yomakon is that like like
it's Detroit
what
[Music]
ah that one okay it
back no no why would we do that ah yeah
that one is not only console I don't
know that I'm participating in that I
think there's like a whole whole myth or
whole life booth but the people who are
like participating for real though is
Council as far as I know
so you're not missing me because I'm not
really there
[Music]
they must be really excited because this
is the first event that they're gonna be
part of like this right
um
I'll be there to support them oh you're
gonna be there in person oh
I want to see like what the booth is
gonna look like aren't they like having
a booth or something like that I don't
understand I don't know any details
Twitter
I want to see like what it looks like is
there gonna be like a like a full-size
um paper
uh cut out takanasi Kiana
you guys can take pictures with it maybe
I have no idea
I don't know I really don't know I'm
just assuming
I'll be there in person too oh looking
forward to supporting Council but I wish
I could see myth in person too yeah
maybe um I mean there and there will be
other opportunities for us to be in New
York maybe next year who knows
who knows but it's cool that Council
gets to show their faces out there as
well
I'm taking too much time oh my God
uh spooky sorry
[Music]
as a fan of this game for more than 10
years oh I'm so happy that you decided
to play this it's just beautiful and had
a huge impact on my life so I hope
you'll enjoy it all for your home for me
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
let's see
um
[Music]
foreign
I like this I like this face
[Music]
thank you for the pinky when I first
started dating my girlfriend
around the decade ago I would read her
Alice in Wonderland over Skype every
night as she fell asleep over 100 times
oh this game came around then but I
never got to play it so I'm really
looking forward to this
[Music]
well good to know good to know
cute cute background sorry thank you for
letting me know
okay thank you glad you enjoyed it thank
you what is a board time to plant
yourself then servant come on thank you
and look at Severn Duncan
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
polite Super Chat it was thanking me in
the most polite ever way in the most
polite speech ever thanking me for doing
the the watch along for vatamus concert
and thanking you guys as well saying
that his heart was being struck and
struck by my kindness
and he couldn't help himself and is very
very
sorry but he had to send a Super Chat
[Music]
people like
instead
thank you thank you
[Music]
a good boy thank you I came here for the
first time at first to protect you
goodbye saying and it's very lovely I'm
not used to English so sorry so I'm
sorry if my sentences are strange I
still see people on Twitter
in Japanese tweeting about how much they
like my goodbye saying and I can't
believe it what the hell
[Applause]
I don't understand
what
um
[Music]
even though that was so like I wasn't
trying it trying like hoping for it like
I wasn't even trying to make it such a
good thing
I hope that the next one will be of your
liking too guys I I don't even expect it
to blow up as much
um because the Envy is like a simple
like just like lyric Envy
um uh but the song is kind of like it
has a similar vibe to it it's very
catchy and kind of fast-paced so I think
you guys will like it uh but I don't
think it's gonna blow up like that and
that's okay that's okay that's the thing
that happens when the algorithm really
catches on and I guess that happened
with goodbye singing so I'm really glad
for that but it's okay I'm I'm being
realistic if it if it's like gonna do
well then I'm happy about it but I don't
have any unrealistic um expectations but
I still help you guys uh listen to it a
lot
I I didn't originally want to ask you
now for a music video for this one
um as well but you know I was kind of
too busy so I ended up just going for
like a normal simple simple simple
simple simple simple music video but the
art is super cute though he yeah look
forward to it
Tony
[Music]
um
I did not do the art no I commissioned
one of my favorite uh fan artists from
kfb who have uh not yet worked for me
yet
um yeah
who I thought the style would be fitting
for this particular song cover
hi
hi hi hi and Jenny Jen froggy donkey or
Duncan our Trump's art room starstrada
Duncan now we're establishing about 9
000 hours thank you
oh yeah right the Animal Crossing Pilots
that dodo's trip too yeah
300 years ago humans found out that
dodos tasted delicious when cooked and
as they are unable to fly they were easy
to pray on top of that ah they can't fly
oh man
yeah I see how that would happen Panda
for the gaming dinosaur and Jet Luna
donation song Danke Schoen for the pinky
here's my idea attention during an
eating stream of the heart monitor no
thank you
no no no no especially because from what
I've heard
um if you have no real access to fresh
and good durian you gotta order it like
in this vacuumed
package and those are usually never good
from what I've heard so no thank you
I thought those were disgusting but we
ate them anyway
you say weak
are you
Australian
who was it again who ate all those
Doodles was it the Australians they were
apparently disgusting what
it was the right seasoning anything can
taste good nope
the Aussies I was lost no it was a Dutch
sorry Aussies
well at least at least they're still
alive in Animal Crossing and no one
really thinks about eating them
hopefully
drzilla 337
Years thank you thank you
speaking of flamingos I've heard that
red flamingos exist and they haven't
mistaken to be Phoenix sometimes
considering flamingos can stand in and
drink boiling water are they your
cousins what
their feet not feel hotness
flamingos can stand in and drink boiling
water
that is a fact that I've never heard
before
oh my God but like why would they be
standing in boiling water anyway
in what situation if you live in the
nature as a wild flamingo
in what situation would you be standing
in boiling water
okay do flamingos hang out around
volcanoes
[Music]
a hot spring but the hot spring is not
boiling either
it's very hot
[Music]
at least the hot springs that I've been
in are not boiling
foreign
[Music]
gorgeous is that a rare like version of
them
[Music]
that is beautiful how
why do we red flamingos exist
a weird question the pink or reddish
color of flamingos comes from
carotenoids in their diet of animal and
plant Plankton American flamingos are
brighter red color because of the better
carotene availability in their food
while the Lesser flamingos are paleo
pink due to ingesting a small amount
[Music]
it is that simple
they're gorgeous oh my
maybe one day we'll get a flamingo
Hollow bird member
huh I can imagine that it would be like
a very pink design very pink character
design I would welcome them
that would be cute I feel like that if
if we had a flamingo
Vito by would be a very pink design and
it would be a very long-legged character
a tall character with big Boba and a
very gentle face
I see that
yeah yeah I can imagine it can you guys
imagine I can totally imagine it I want
to design it right now
like similar to Dana but like more uh
girly
a little bit more girly designed than
old pink pink and white
uh where was I
passed it Crimson Phoenix
[Music]
Patrick moondock unit 13e dungeon n000
Patrick
skill page Danke Schoen Jim Tracy Duncan
series
here is one Outlast Super Chat mixed in
for whatever reason Jay cried for thank
you I'm just reading this in case it
won't be in my actual Outlast Super Chat
reading in case it won't be fixed and
included in that later
um
so I don't know if you're here but your
Super Chat has been red
[Music]
uh I am so hungry Chase look oh Chase
clock down
senior MC said
wait senior that was a red one thank you
no text for that though thank you
influx 27 thank you soon Patrick
[Music]
I'll leave the rest for Sunday or like
after little nightmares I'm gonna read
some I think after little nightmares and
then the rest and on the on Sunday
because we have more than enough time on
Sunday to read some super chattels
so next will be the Minecraft super
chats yeah thank you you guys are
clapping for me thank you
[Music]
thank you so on Sunday
um after the music video is out we will
have a chit chatting and feedback stream
and read the rest of the super chats and
just hang out and chill and and be happy
that the week is over because it was a
stressful week but it's already going by
so fast it's already the end of the week
yo
who is this oh
the amazing time to have a good one
thank you I I'm glad you guys enjoyed it
um
it won't be uh uh a thing that happens
too often at kfb horror streams but
every once in a while I'm okay with it I
guess every when I say every once in a
while I mean everyone once in a blue
moon half a year or so maybe
or as a as a punishment game
that would be okay I guess I love doing
good as interactions she was very um
helpful yeah I I didn't expect her to be
that helpful and she remembered the game
so well so that was really really good
she knew which directions and even
though it was so freaking dark and and
uh like in moments where I was running
away where it was really stressful like
she still knew where to go that really
impressed me
money
yeah she was just playing it yesterday
but she didn't get very far did she but
that was good I guess that she freshed
up her memory oh so really really huge
thanks to go down she's not listening
anymore I'm sure but I'm gonna write her
a little message afterwards because you
know she she um
um I mean I didn't like the idea of
playing this to begin with but
at least um like she made it into a much
better experience
then it could have been if I played it
alone
so yeah
all the things still go down I'm really
happy that she was there for me
yeah
and I didn't die I ended up being fine I
thought I would be much much worse but
uh
point my own like scare like
chicken-ness uh made me laugh and and
humor myself hi smoothie thank you for
being worried about me I'm all good
Mama's okay
[Music]
foreign
oh I should move my leg and it's it's a
cracked a a thingy yeah baby I just wake
up from a nap one of you hit me up did
you hear that
how did you know I was done even though
I didn't stop talking yet
how did you know
she's in she might be watching the
stream on the side
are you watching the stream in the other
room
you know I was gonna end it here
no more she always runs in when I stop
talking after the stream she always runs
in here
by the way I had like a two hour phone
call with my mom yesterday uh talked
about all kinds of things but she also
she
[Music]
praising raising so much she was so
proud about my the Minecraft
[Music]
[Applause]
oh man
she was praising me so much
[Music]
I did so well
Conquering the end uh and she said that
she was again impressed that I was so
lucky and for me it's not just a given I
don't even realize how lucky I am but my
mom said for her first for her first um
elytra you know playing alone on the
server where nothing's taken yet it took
her four hours
find her first Elijah and you know she
doesn't stream either so she's more
productive than someone like us who
streams
that's like more so I guess maybe Ina's
whole experience maybe is the default
experience and me just being so freaking
lucky is not the norm I thought that was
the norm
Phoenix like isn't her her I don't know
how to say that her right I know the
meaning I don't know how to pronounce
hereditary
maybe it isn't
it's not Phoenix luck it's just chaotic
huh
[Music]
you know
um
my luck works in extremes yeah also
today like with the lockers
why was I so lucky with the lockers like
he would never open the locker where I
was in
yeah the hiding place is today what
good I was like impressed because she
would always be unlucky with that
oh my God I thought it was normal I
thought it was like programmed that if
there's two lockers that he will always
open up the locker that you're not in
who felt like that to me
man gooda is just being bullied as
always why the hell everyone's bully is
good at I don't understand I will never
understand
I'm looking forward to the clips I I
hope that there will be some good Clips
uh you know we need some we need some
funny clips from Kiara not always those
serious Clips yeah I appreciate those
too but uh we need more game content
funny clips yeah and the stream okay
okay
yeah oh wait you're asking if it's
ending yes it is ending
um
I was watching a bunch of Clips
yesterday from pudding pudding pudding
gotta saying
um
you've improved a lot I think
Kiana approves
I would put the stamp on here right now
if I had a had it on the screen but I
don't have it
putting good job I like your clips
I liked the one
well the one way uh wait what was it
about
uh the one where I was talking about
going on the trip and like touching
grass and and walking uh walking on on
the ground into the animations that you
did we're so stupid I love this
show you guys
two hours ending tents no I'm really
adding I just want to give Big Ups to
pudding you guys should watch puddings
um clips
uh pudding makes a lot of Kiana clips
type in Pudding Channel there he is type
it in
give that uh Brit some love
sorry maybe you aren't even British but
I see those pants
maybe maybe pudding needs to make a clip
for my channel pudding you wanna work
for me
I was thinking about hiring a Clipper oh
I was thinking about it a little bit
gotta be honest like maybe like once
every two or three weeks
a clip of something maybe
I want shorter clips though I was
thinking for a moment maybe monthly like
compilation Clips but that would end up
being long again it should be like
shorter clips
I like highlights
so because like I I
see you see um I've seen people like
explain why they don't watch me you know
because I do such long streams that's I
I do yes but like I also do a lot of
shorts like decently
decent length streams as well especially
this week
so watch those I feel like a lot of
people just have this image of me and
don't even give them give a try to it's
a lot of skills yeah they don't even
give it a try
oh
I'm gonna try I've been doing a lot of
okay streams
five hour shorts too shut up
and hey you don't have to watch all of
it but like
Minecraft at least you don't have to
that's the point you don't have to watch
all of it you don't have to watch all
the previous Minecraft streams to
understand what's going on now
ah
um Kyle look around with one hour Clips
concordance Clips are really dope too
yeah yeah yeah yeah if maybe
I wonder who is Carl correct or she I
feel like I saw did I see I think I saw
my chicken icon on his Twitter profile
his or her I don't know
I feel like calculate might be a
chicken a kfb employee maybe should hire
a cow correct for like a one year
um
highlights compilation because that's
that's okay if it's longer I would say
and cowgirl seems to be like keeping up
with my streams not only my Minecraft
streams
he also did that Among Us compilation
but he doesn't dislike me does he
[Music]
gotta hire some peeps to make some
clipperinos I like the you know for for
example for pudding I really like that
that that the way like it doesn't always
do it but I like the way he um like uses
like stupid effects and stupid Graphics
if I were to hire him for a clip I
wonder how that would work because he
would have to be copyright three
um graphics and cut Heist movie I'm okay
I'm done she's telling me to stop she
keeps on robbing against my legs
I love you too baby you want those
cuddles helping me
but those always crack me up I want a
clip like that with me like uh doing
flips over the pavement I want that on
my channel
those shitty like Kusa editing
you know how there's crucial games so
this is Crystal editing in like the
finest way you will ever see it
yeah need someone who does stuff like
that I mean there's a lot of great
Clippers out there I've talked about
others before as well like Yuri gold
does great stuff as well definitely 100
all the all the kids be Clippers are
very talented and I love you guys you
guys are very talented and I'm I'm
watching you
there's this Korean Clipper or like a
couple a lot of Korean Clippers who clip
a lot of my stuff and actually like even
if you don't speak Korean you should
watch those clips because they're also
extremely well made
um
right this is I think it's been in
recommendations a lot as well
if you're a lot on YouTube
uh
I really like the the clipping style of
that one Korean Channel
um I like that too it's interesting to
see everyone's different clipping style
depending on what their editing skill is
and how much effort they put into it
what I personally feel like is that
adding subtitles even if the person
who's speaking is totally understandable
without subtitles I feel like adding
subtitles always adds like
I don't know something nice to it I see
that in in Japanese Clips always they
they always add jump taxes subtitles
because that's just the thing that is
normal in like Japanese TV and maybe
also in like other Sea TV but but like
in Japanese TV I've 100 noticed that
they focus a lot on subtitling and with
like really fancy fonts and really fancy
effects and that that's what makes
Japanese TV
um kind of really stand out a big reason
is the subtitles in my opinion and they
add so much that yeah it emphasizes so
much
um and when someone's angry though the
subtitles will be like on fire or when
someone's scared the subtitles will be
like
spoofy wiggling and gray stuff like that
you know and I I like saying that in
Clips as well I see overseas viewers
haven't been doing that much uh at all
uh but whenever I say it makes me happy
but nothing you guys should all do it I
guess it's so much [\h__\h] work I know
how much work it is to subtitle the
[\h__\h] video I hate it
totally get it is
[Music]
foreign
yeah my German fairy tale started
it was a painted yes and I didn't even
use like fancy uh effects for my or
different like looks and and fonts and
all that didn't even do that
um
I should end it here I'm gonna go grab
some food and then try to sleep early oh
my God and then I see you for a little
nightmares I guess I should probably I
need to make a a thumbnail now perhaps
okay so thank you for watching today and
enjoy when we say
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
[Music]
this movie is chilling on my guest bed
which is in the same room I have a guest
bed in the same room
she's sleeping on the like chilling on
the alpaca blanket
it's interesting how this movie doesn't
really attack it but chonkers does
[Music]
stop me stop me stop me someone
can stop me
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm alive
foreign
[Music]