[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
us ually
foreign
[Music]
let me raise it
whoa
this is
weird so I she did say something about
oh but Rose is any Above This should I
say it maybe that's what she was talking
about she said it will make something
some something
she said something about something
happening that was probably that so
we'll have to stay at this volume
because otherwise
[Music]
did you hear that oh [\h__\h]
but I can make the bgm quieter
how about this
how about this okay
[Music]
it's fine okay I heard rubber doll a
robot noise maybe a little ah
[Music]
I hear it a little bit so you hear it
what is this what is that that's this
she's using the same mic and same oh
make sure thingy as I do but oh my God
wait let me ask her she said you know
she's looking at her phone in case
something
happens uh
[Music]
ah I can't type with this keyboard I
think I know what you were talking about
about some kind of weird feedback with
the microphone now
uh is it
is there nowhere around it besides
making it quieter I don't think I
registered I thought f t h i n okay
registered
quite everything you told me
yeah I think she's busy though
um so the thing is I am I'm at Cali's
place right now I came over
oh two and a half hours ago first we had
we ate a little bit and chitchatted and
then she explained everything to me and
then she left and then I had to which
I'm still belong okay then I had to
record three songs
and
50 minutes that's why I was a bit late
several takes of free songs in 50
minutes something like that
and then I had to quickly set up
something that looks like a streaming
screen streaming yeah streaming screen
screening stream
ing screen because um Kelly normally
uses uh stream Labs so now your zombie
Ass
OBS is better
now look at this we tried
mama I mean I think I still hear a hint
of that weird
[Music]
oh nice but it's not so bad right
not so bad
it'll be a Supremacy yeah I mean
streamlabs you know it's just you know I
mean literally
um
wait what was the opposite of superior
we're Syria
inferior
wait what's are there Superior there's
inferior and then isn't there also
ulterior
what's that mean then
don't people say someone has an ulterior
motive
is that like inside
inferior is below superiors above
ulterior is inside maybe because they
have an inside
motive
yeah
another alternative
[Laughter]
oh well oh yeah and then there's into
here that's the well inside that that's
inside
oh well
um
anyway besides learning English
yeah I've been recording oh my God it
does bother me but I don't know how bad
it is for you guys because I think I'm
way louder in my own ears than I am in
your ears
is it does that sound okay do I sound
like I'm normally do in Austria no
because in favor it should be it's the
same microphone
uh
but it all sounds very weird to me
not picking it up on my headphones
oh okay
sounds good
okay
a bit different
okay still have robot voice and that's
what uh I mean I wouldn't say it's like
a full-on robot voice but
I do I don't hear like some
I sound American
I felt like a [\h__\h] yeah you [\h__\h] with
me now
and you should say not because I'm a
Cali's place
um
I forgot to
I forgot no I don't have snacks but I
forgot to put bring over my tissues
if legum is still part of my life yeah
time to read Kelly's wine counter oh she
doesn't have to worry about that because
I don't drink wine or any alcohol
so
the only thing I felt like writing was
she I saw in her kitchen she has you
know that Nutella snack with the sticks
she has all of those there we kind of
want to take it ah Kelly gets it you
know she also has a Nutella glass there
um like a normal one
um that's pretty rare in Japan I would
say
is this the temptation
she had one of those read the pantry
you know what I've noticed she has a lot
of Hollow myth merch around like there's
a lot of stance acrylic stands
on her table on her cabinets
everywhere
there's there everywhere
um
I was on record for not liking Nutella
what then why is it so openly on the
kitchen counter
this is a huge scoop
wasn't she wouldn't bother she wouldn't
mind if I would eat it right but like
it's a gift for me no way
Alaska renji's bag you know she left
um because she had something to do but
there's no problem you know I actually I
guess I feel more comfortable being
alone when I stream
um so actually you know if she would
have been here I would have offered to
do this together because we wanted to do
one of these together anyway
um but
uh yeah she comes back later she's got
something to do
well I'm really grateful that she trusts
me so much for leaving me all along here
oh
hi I'm alone
I'm alone
[Music]
it's really nice I don't think it's a
given not everyone just
blindly would give someone full access
on their home
but I mean we've been working together
for two and a half years or so
I also asked her for a shirt
I have I didn't change it right now I'm
still feeling okay but when I first
arrived I felt like super
overheated so I asked if she could
borrow me a shirt to wear for the stream
maybe I'll change later if I feel hotter
later
um
the house doesn't smell like anything
neutral
very neutral
I don't wanna I Wanna Give like you guys
so much information though but uh you
know
I mean so far the info I've been giving
you guys I don't think it has been uh
like two things posing right she's got
you know what's sweet I know this
remember remember that one drawing I did
of her ages ago uh of her in the winter
coat with some snow
I think I gave it to her in a frame Ryan
I don't think she did frame it herself
but the thing is still still around I
see it from here
it's visible
it's over there
so sweet she has it
it's right there
yeah
that's so sweet maybe I should draw her
again
ah
the bracelet I don't know why the
bracelet is
there's like so much stuff man our place
is uh
you know with all with all the
merchandise it's a little bit cluttered
in some spaces
some spaces you know where the merch is
it's got like some I think that those
are like Jojo
I think that's Jojo
I didn't watch JoJo but I think that's
like Jojo figures
oh oh
oh so it's like it's like 50 percent
um no it's 24 25 Jojo
then I see
let's see 10 maybe 10 of stuff that I
don't know
and then 15 thing and topangura nagan
and then 50 whole life merch
floor mass and you guessed right
but you know I love thing too so I'm
actually
excited to see that yo she's got a fake
and big what's her name Yoko I think it
was Yoko mmm
[Music]
good stuff good stuff
yeah already on the table she's got so
many myths of curl stands man
NY yeah
I really like
fascinated
this is I think this is the uh
third place of hers that I've I've seen
first one was a tiny tiny one
I saw
uh before debut
yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'm jealous though she's got like a Miku
monitor
occasion I should I should hold back on
this
yeah the infamous floor setup that was a
thing look at everything Kelly has well
there's a lot of familiar things though
like her huge ass TV I didn't know how
to turn it off so I I was only able to
turn down the volume
before she left she'd like
um turned on some Lo-Fi
I tried to turn it up turn the TV off
the remote was able to turn down the
volume but not turn off the TV
oh it's running it's pretty though this
is a pretty backdrop on the side
unplugged I was thinking maybe I should
do that but I don't want to unplug
Something Different by accident
no we're not
that didn't work
or whatever it's just gonna stay like
this
ah but you know this is nice because
um
I'm so happy it's at least somewhat
decent uh audio besides a little in my
ears
um compared to
the yeti mic that I've been using
recently since I came to
uh Japan
say Hey Google turn off TV hey I'm
scared of doing that
does she have that
she had this would you would you think
that reacts in her place did she ever
used that
hey hey Alexa
hey no no no no no let's not risk it
just gonna say
uh
yes Mrs Kawaii primori and we're all
gonna know oh [\h__\h] her real name is
kawaiiope
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
ah anyway I'm I have some Tommy horde
today so please forgive me if um I'm
gonna try to be good big energy anyway
um
but a little bit big tummy heart
Callie said I can have her painkillers
but I'm gonna be fine I'll try to
go with that
let me show you some water
oh it's water pump I don't know if she
has something like that
oh you know what you know Cali probably
won't be home until late but
um I asked her if I missed the last
couple trains
if I can stay at her place she said yeah
so maybe we're having a sleepover I
don't know
maybe her couch is coffee and beat maybe
a sleepover it's gonna be late you know
yeah no party sleeping
intentionally miss it
no I'm just done I wanna play with it
and then read Super Chat so I think the
stream should be decent length you know
I don't want to end it after like two
hours because I know you guys are
craving
craving for the Wawa
ah anyway I logged back into the account
here and we are
um back in the game it's Japan round
five of the five
foreign
[Music]
I kind of want that
it's not like I'm like super super
missing Austria's food right now not at
all I mean I haven't been I've only been
here for like a week or so
so I'm not like that desperate you know
but of course it would be nice to have a
Nutella oh you tell us a trap
tell for breakfast that doesn't make it
2020. I have been eating Nutella for
breakfast for my whole life
hmm
wait so we're gonna play some Geo guys
so we're currently still in Japan
uh what could this be let's let's start
walking anyway
yo welcome to the rice fields
[\h__\h]
[Music]
on this baseball stuff
what is that corn no it's not corn what
is that
oh
they rated
stream hi Ollie
thank you looks like we're on Twitch
thank you only
Lily only
[Music]
look at those sunflowers
oh oh I can't go no I can't go for her
why does it say x here
we're like in the middle of nowhere
I feel like it's in the middle of Japan
yeah
we can kind of see for the window it's
kind of cool but I want to be
I want to be that goes too far
it looks some kind of
hey is that someone's home
ah [\h__\h]
ah
I thought you know what's
what's Cali's setup is like really cool
and all but oh my God I had to turn down
her Mouse speed I don't know how the
[\h__\h] she works with this but her mouse
was like
absolutely uncontrollable even when I
was like you know right on top of
something let's say my mouse I was like
uh like really around here
I was trying to click something and even
though I was going really slowly with my
mouse it kept on going
I was shaking
so I had to turn it turn speed down how
the [\h__\h] does she like work with this
she didn't even know where to turn the
speed down she she's probably used to
the super speed but what the [\h__\h]
how
that's a nice house
was in the middle of nowhere
that's a cool house
I feel like overall it's pretty modern
not even so much Japan looking
except for like the
these
what do you call the the da da
nice air conditioner
okay we need to find like a main street
or something because this ain't helping
me at all
that way
ice let's go this way and wow
[Music]
that's so anime
like I can imagine here being like a
wooden platform over oh that's a little
bit over the actual ground
and they open up these windows in summer
and they sit right here
with ice cream and behind them they have
like a fan
and they just go like ah foreign
on that roof
oh beautiful beautiful
architecture get it
I feel like I'm sightseeing I I feel
like I don't understand how this game
works anymore but I know I know I know
I know oh they have a big this I feel
like this belongs together right
a big place
those Perfect Trim brushes yeah
damn bushes brushes push George Bush
Bush George Bush
bushes brushes bushes and push push push
push push big straight don't go
push push push push push
oh that looks like a decently big
straight let's go oh
um
okay they're selling red eggs what the
[\h__\h] are red eggs
doesn't help me though
hey can I not go further
both arrows show to the back
ah
[Music]
I thought you could go endlessly is that
really where it cuts me off
right eggs I don't know regional thing
yeah I didn't even go that far like what
the [\h__\h] how am I supposed to know what
is this there's no hand what maybe the
Sun
[Music]
no that doesn't help me
oh come on
[Music]
yeah but even if you call it to you
guess or like there's
you can't just say okay
here
[Music]
give you some kind of like hint wow
there's trees
oh that's like a noise Garden they got
there
you know
amen
okay where are the red eggs maybe if we
go to the Red X we'll find a sign now I
feel like I already missed
look at those roofs
I'm gonna prove inspector oh look at the
Gordon
I wonder what what kind of veggies
they're growing
[\h__\h] hell mate I tapped out again
okay look at the sky
whoa yo that's actually some sick clouds
though it's not just me that's just me
being fascinated right
sick
get it
tap down again oh wow
whoa
Birds
many birds
have that again
I should make it full window I don't
want to because her screen is so [\h__\h]
wide
and curved
where have I not been
the song this will help me but I'll go
here
take
I can't even go right but I see that
this no that's the eggs again
um
and I can't continue going that way
either no I can't okay okay
oh oh
yeah well cool house
no nothing even
I don't think this really so far has
been giving any clues
hey student maybe the school uniform can
give it away but he looks really young
he's so small
he should be like
uh junior hi
Junior High School
on the show
where are we
um
that's an anime product no he hadn't he
didn't have a slice of toast in his
mouth
wait maybe over there it looks like more
there we have a chance over there
there's a big sign big street sign over
there
if we can reach that oh but the traffic
is so bad right now
hey guys move move
[Music]
other people behind me yeah sorry guys
traffic kind of slow we'll have to wait
for the green sign okay here we go
here we go we're driving
[Music]
okay here we are ah
uh I gotta go over there gotta go there
gotta go there go go go this is my
chance
it's my chance
oh
yeah all of these places are unknown to
me
Japanese people might know though
um foreign
[Music]
Japanese people saying they can't read
it hi those are
you read it now
um
Pulliam again
[Music]
of it
five of it oh yeah
there's no way I'll find that
we're looking for oil
[Music]
is you know kanji Japanese for
um an island but I think it doesn't
necessarily have to be an island right
foreign
[Music]
what which one's the which one's the
full screen what was that to
oh
does that help ah it's hard to see huh
sorry to say it
wrote oh I guess I didn't look at the ah
it's got how did we get there
I took her here
Lana look at the road numbers yo that
was my strategy last time oh wait this
is a different one
it still says the same things though but
why is
whoa It's So saturated
look at that Queen
I love they have their own little Shrine
over there
wow scary
Mr Blue Sky
wow oh that's so beautiful here man I
can't focus okay two five two okay I'll
go get two five two
[Music]
um
easy let's look for two five two
five two two five two two five two
oopsie should be like a blue sign right
blue a blue two five two
[Music]
and these are also low numbers
nothing's free digits let's go down
what
maybe like okay 10 free
57 6.
um 9 53 on it
maybe oh oh oh oh okay hmm
oh
300 400. oh what's the system Behind
These huh
oh
258 does that mean that 252 is close
doesn't have any like meaning
two five six
maybe somewhat close
um
three six one four seven one
look for National Road Number Eight
first where did you see that I can't use
that hint if I if it wasn't given to me
in the game
no I don't want to cheat
last time this worked too
but the back then I had like a rough
idea of where the [\h__\h] I am
two nine free
five four
two five four
I'm looking for two five two right
[Music]
I'm not really asking
how Vegas canto
hey but the numbers you're looking
completely different again
four hundred two five three two five
three
two five three
where's two five
foreign
[Music]
don't lose it now okay okay okay two
five two
goes for nigata
uh
wait I lost it
good there it is
more left
what's the names of the places I'm
looking for again
uh
[Music]
where does
here we're just too fast to end
kind of here I think it ends kind of
because I don't see it
going out of this mess
two five two two five to mix this with
two nine one
and becomes 291
I think yeah this is where it disappears
Maybe oyama
totally dead
oh yeah oh yeah
it must be like around here though
all right
there's so much
to look at
there's
[Music]
um
where I lost my 252 on here
um let's go this way
after two five two let's follow two five
two
goes up here
according wait no I'm just uh was not
what we're looking for right
just because I read it before it sounds
familiar
two five two mixes with 17 year and
disappears
local Road
what do you mean local Road 252 is this
not the 252 that I'm looking for
look at the signs again huh
five six eight ah let me see the other
numbers
mean
huh
one five six eight
two five two
one five six eight two five two one five
six eight two five two one five six
eight
five two one five six eight two five two
one five six eight two five two one five
six three
eight eight eight eight
I'll say it's somewhere here
roughly whatever
guessing
huh
um
bruh
oh yeah
I see oh yeah
oh there's American land
there's a
um
a little bit
oh that's so funny what why why
are you telling why is 252 here too
there's no way it goes all the way
through until here does that
by the coastline or Subway
oh this is just what why is 252 there
there's multiple ones well what the [\h__\h]
what
[Music]
um
man
that's not fair okay let me hide this
one more because I don't know where it
will take me next
um like in terms of I'll go to the main
menu
okay
okay do we wanna try America
not that I I mean not that I would know
anything at all but
cute
I feel like Christians are living in
that house
oh
oh that looks like a rich family
cheers
where the [\h__\h] am I
I may be right oh
let me look at your house you also reach
these people are rich where do rich
people live in America
whoa
pretty house or maybe maybe it's in the
middle of nowhere and therefore it's not
that expensive to have a house like this
in America
what wait this looks like a
cult place
I feel like this is a neighborhood for
people of the same cult
because the houses all look kind of the
same
and they live so well only because
they're part of the cult no
[Laughter]
it
hmm
[Music]
oh they got a bouncy trampoline and then
the thingy to play with
so it's a nice cult because they they
play with their children more or less
okay
ah
which way should we go straight or left
where could we find more hints
[Music]
um
straight look at the van I was thinking
about that was just a security maybe a
bit more let me see is it still here
yeah
[Music]
I don't know it's very very blurry for
me then I can't read dad
well it's a bus
oh wait
oh
[Music]
they censor it
something company but maybe that's a
cold that the first numbers do they give
away what um like
state it is
like an area code yeah now if I would
play this alone I would look up 662. and
now you guys look it up for me and tell
me what that is Mississippi
okay where the [\h__\h] is Mississippi
um is Mississippi a state that is
Missouri
[Music]
uh
this Mississippi estate ah there it is
in Mississippi
Okay so
I'm very rough idea that's pretty good
I'm awesome UPS
okay
well the phone number was a smart one
now
cult in Mississippi oh there's a sign
cult cult invitation Cobblestone Village
that is so obviously a cult elegant
Styles underground utilities
to hide the bodies
one acre lots Caledonia schools call
Cali oh no wait her phone number is just
like there
wait
Cali Cali
Cali
caliope
Coldwell Banker West like Cobblestone I
mean I mean trying to find cobblestone
Village in the middle of here will be
too much of a challenge I don't think
that's
gonna happen
but
it would be nice if Michael
if I call them more
look for Caledonia Caledonia
oh
wait from where to where is Mississippi
where is the border
is it this squiggly
[Music]
is it this this is
yeah okay
uh wait oh my God where's what am I
looking at I don't [\h__\h] know let's
say here
nice
see nine kilometers from the correct
location
[Music]
good guess
Caledonia
Baptist Church there
wow not bad I mean look at how [\h__\h]
huge America is and how me with zero
knowledge gets that right next
sick oh
it's better
Ottawa
oh pretty flower
this is better because this will be
better this will be easier
where you guys probably already know
what that I thought we were in America
all right because Oliver sounds like uh
Canada
but we're in America
oh
there is oh
it looks like a big arena
van
Van Andel Arena okay some people
probably know that
this looks like a big city
look at the bus oh yeah wait wait wait
wait
oh uh code
area code
616 guys
West
Michigan Michigan
[Music]
foreign
wow that's
exact location what are those legs like
Michigan I've heard of that like
Superior is there an
inferior Lake
foreign
that's so cool this area that looks
really cool
those must be huge oh and that's why I
saw Ottawa place because the olive oil
is so close
okay well Michigan's
big cities are Detroit
and this place
Grand Rapids
so I would say it's one of those which
one has that big arena huh
hmm
I mean I feel like Detroit would be even
more impressive to look at no what are
those little what's going on here with
those millions of lakes
cheers I need to play this I I need to
see this place in person
crap let's say it's Grand why is it so
Square everything's so Square in America
okay City Center
would be I guess here
I'll say I'll say it's like somewhere
around here
[Music]
oh my God
wait you know what I actually want to do
uh give me a second before we continue
[Music]
okay getting myself
an American map of state borders but no
names because I'm gonna embarrass myself
right now on purpose I don't mind
okay
okay and we're gonna play now is you
guys give me a state name and I'll try
to guess where it is
how do I draw on OBS wasn't there a way
to draw an obs on the screen
could I did that before
does anyone know how that works
wait wait wait wait a second with the
names
someone know oh maybe it's just maybe
what she did was like have a green
screen paint screen or so on top
use pain okay yeah probably over there
paints
can I insert an image in paint
let's see oh yes okay cool Coolio
Coolio we're doing this now
and here it is
I know I know you guys are gonna be like
oh she does no [\h__\h] but yeah I'm doing
this on purpose I know I don't know [\h__\h]
and this is going to be good all right
someone said um Michigan is not what we
just had
was it the first one or the second one
uh the second one right
uh
uh Michigan is here right
Michigan
uh can I like type
that is like a joke okay
now I know what that is over there and
then before that we did Mississippi
right Mississippi was
somewhere here
I don't remember anymore
um
maybe maybe Mississippi was here I don't
want you guys to correct me I'm gonna
make my own Mississippi
oh Matt is it isn't this Texas
that looks like Texas I didn't realize
it was so down not the bottom though
okay next next
that's good okay the shape of Texas
gives it away
and I think
is this California
is it
I will not change it if you tell me it's
not
yeah okay good good good good good
um
okay this is where it gets difficult and
[Music]
Nevada well what the [\h__\h] why would I
know where Nevada is
um okay okay when I have absolutely no
[\h__\h] idea about something give me at
least like a trait uh like tell me it's
very desert tea or so
what what give me a trade for Nevada one
trade
Vegas is okay
so it's there's a tree right I heard
that the place where Las Vegas is all it
has is Las Vegas
and the rest is just
um
okay I think it's not over here
um oh yeah I've watched a video that
told me why most of the like population
in America is on this right side is
because that most of these here are
[\h__\h] hot and deserty which means that
Las Vegas and all that would be in this
area
because I know it's deserty so let's say
uh Nevada is here
at least that helps me a little bit
okay
New York is on the right side of America
I think
but what the [\h__\h] are those
when what's the state of New York is it
New York
state of New York I've heard that before
it's the state of New York isn't it a
city though
foreign
this [\h__\h] looks so weird
all of those look so weird
I said why are some of them so tiny
don't some of the tiny ones belong to
one of the others like they belong
together
I say I say this is New York
it's probably not
ah
I mean it was just roughly roughly put
places into places okay next place
um
next place Florida Washington
Florida
was Florida left or right
um it's Miami in Florida then it's on
the right side I think
because I know that
[Music]
let's say Florida is here
Flo Rida okay
next
maybe maybe Florida is more like down
here but what is this thing is that is
maybe this is Florida
and then I'll think about the other one
Alaska
it is Alaska this thing here
and
is Hawaii this year oh please tell me
yeah yeah both
let's go it would have been so
embarrassing if I got this too right
and okay okay there's still so many next
next
Tennessee
is it uh desert deserting or not
tell me at least that Tennessee
it doesn't sound tense uh deserty
the name the name doesn't sound so no
okay okay Tennessee is um can I see us
here tennis
I like to play tennis
um
lots of force and mountains oh that
sounds like it would be kind of North
East
maybe Alabama
desert or no desert
Alabama
[Music]
no no desert no lizard
Alabama
I have absolutely nothing to go
on to make this decision but Alabama is
here
[Music]
next
meal
uh
Kentucky
sounds like one on the left side
um
close I feel like they would be best
buddies with like Las Vegas
so Kentucky
next
South Dakota
um obviously there's North from South
Dakota
so one is more North and one is more
south
and they would be touching each other
right so maybe we have okay
okay
what happened I typed I pressed
something oh there we go okay South
Dakota
and and here we put
North Dakota
right I'm not far off let's go
I have to show this mess with Kelly when
she gets home and maybe maybe she gets
home when I'm still streaming and then
she can uh correct my homework
laughs
okay next is uh close but no New Mexico
wouldn't it be close to Mexico and
Mexico is under America
I say New Mexico is Mexico is here
uh next door
so close oh that's good that's good
though I forgive myself for that
Louisiana desert or no desert for
Louisiana
[Music]
swampland no desert
swamp means it's wet right oh and I saw
like a lot of like
weird stuff here
Maybe
maybe Louisiana is best parties with
Alabama
okay
okay next door
does saying this would help you locate
yeah
I know it's around here
do you even see the most now you see it
uh Connecticut
is here
Washington DC
foreign
that's where the president is right
here
it's really so wrong
[Laughter]
it's not on the map
about DC not being a state yeah yeah
yeah yeah
and then and then wanting to be a state
and then they're being like votes and so
on but you know they don't want them you
know political [\h__\h]
tiny okay okay let me redo that
um
I would try to remember maybe maybe
[Music]
I see something tiny there
watching
ton how about there
I can't see it
oh
hmm
well whatever if I can't see it then I
can't ride on the map next on
next door
give me give me enough something
Arizona oh that sounds very deserty
Arizona
[Music]
I feel like Arizona is more like
I'll look here
Arizona
okay next Massachusetts
so close yeah
yay
we're talking about Massachusetts right
close no no desert
um
I feel like I feel like Massachusetts
had a funny shape
but these don't look so funny anymore
put Massachusetts here
Massachusetts is there
Louisiana
sounds kind of like they're in the
middle
I put Lucy in here
I did that already
well hey my first guess wasn't that far
away
okay next up
next up
Oregon
hey Organo
that desert don't know desert
the [\h__\h] is working
huge trees
Forest oh
I would give it something morphine
Northeast
I'll give it this
might be more like on the right side but
and more particles okay
how about
you organ shall be
organ it will be this on the top right
this one on the top right
okay
West Coast oh wow oh my gosh down the
complete opposite
fair enough
Coast it's a coast
glad I got your state right Oh you mean
like California or something like that
all right next
[Music]
um
foreign
Wisconsin
hint
desert don't know desert
uh cold cheese [\h__\h] no desert
cold and cheese
Wisconsin is here
next
lots of cows not like I see any cows on
this map
yay
North Carolina okay so there's North and
South Carolina I would say they're like
in the desert area
oh how about
North Carolina here
uh South Carolina Scar and car scar how
about here
[Laughter]
well I made my decision I can't change
it anymore next
next next
West Virginia is there another Virginia
East Virginia
they began West Virginia Virginia is
there just one Virginia
and West Virginia
there's already no desert
tell me tell me
no desert
mama
[Music]
Take Me Home
West Virginia okay
Virginia here the owners oh [\h__\h]
you want to say for Russian
West Virginia
[Music]
this feels very wrong
oh oopsie
let me fix that
okay
next
go with
I'm going with the instinct
I have to trust my instinct Georgia
this looks like a Georgia to me
yeah
uh no desert
then this is Georgia
[Laughter]
sometimes sometimes I will let myself
make the change because I didn't know I
didn't know yet about the desert or no
desert
um
not far off
Oklahoma
[Music]
desert or no desert
close enough are you from there
uh what both oh both
[Music]
there you go that's where you are next
up
what's next what's next uh someone said
Ohio before
good morning to you too
Ohio desert don't know dessert you guys
gonna tell me that from the get-go I'm
not drinking I'm just not from America
no but it's not like everybody knows you
stupid map guys
not everybody knows
Farmland huh
so not so deserty
but big maybe very big
because farmers
Ohio I wasn't real
potatoes
Ohio Ohio is here
nah
Nana doesn't feel right
oh why it was here
which one was closer
oh
what it's all Ohio what what oh hi
what's that what second soda yeah
okay okay next the next one next next
next next next
what's next
by the way I was I was in LA before
right
where was LA California or of Florida
California right
was I on the West Coast
felt like I was on the East Coast
[Music]
okay okay
what's our next um
Pennsylvania oh
this fancy
Pennsylvania's here easy easy easy
that is an easy one mm-hmm
um thanks
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah Maine
Maine sounds small
here here tiny
main here next next next Wyoming Wyoming
Wyoming desert or no desert
close hey let's go
no desert what Wyoming no desert desert
yes desert no desert oh you guys are
confused about that
it's a grassland oh I will say
okay Wyoming
East Coast to you
okay okay and lots of messes no people
wait wait then Wyoming is here
land a thousand legs ten thousand legs
well then then Wyoming is here
laughs
[Music]
[Laughter]
that was closer before okay now let me
put it back here
next next
um Rhode Island
uh that must be this island here
it looks like an island
yeah maybe
Delaware Delaware desert or no desert
uh
nope
Rhode Island oh well
no desert for what which what was I was
what was I talking about
Delaware ah no desert Delaware okay
Delaware is like here
and then somebody said Arkansas and
Kansas
think I pronounced that correctly all
right then I will say
Arkansas is here
and
cancer is here although Kansas sounds
more like it would be in the middle of
America like somewhere here but I need
them to be close together because
they're like a pair
huh oh Arkansas I was really confident
in that one
I was so confident in that one
okay
Minnesota
[Music]
cold or cold
yeah Minnesota is like somewhere in
these small ones in Minnesota looks cold
up there
um next next mini suit
Montana Montana sounds
like it would be like close to Texas
because that's where Hannah Montana is
from and she's she seems like a
Countryside howdy girl
yeah
yeah okay next up
and Maryland
um
where
where Michael Jackson
has no
Trump
Michael Jackson or Trump have something
there
no I feel like I heard something about
that
I'm confused
well Maryland give me a hint about
Maryland oh that's my religion
[Laughter]
I mixed those too never landed marilago
become Maryland
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh man
look at me and give me a hint
um
amazing Seafood oh maybe cold City then
Maryland Maryland being here
Okay small okay this is pretty small too
yeah
crabs okay okay
Vermont state
uh Vermont
Vermont hint
there are two floridas
oh yeah
yeah true
didn't you know that
mountains skiing oh
Vermont is up here easy
okay okay how many more do we have
we can switch off Florida I don't know
what the hell this thing is down here
that used to be Florida I guess but man
I can still change it up I'm not sure
about Florida Utah
this this is
you that is Florida okay let's keep that
one then
the one I have right I gotta keep some
some of them
okay
floor Flores
Iowa
oh you want he was definitely this one
100 I'm sure
got relatives over there
oh
Idaho
Idaho is this one
next Indiana
you know these are all taken now so they
kind of all have to go to East Coast now
Indiana Indiana
wait was it Indiana
New Jersey
I love space for all these ones
is there old Jersey
Nebraska
Colorado
I have space for all of them Colorado
no Nebraska is like something over here
didn't I didn't I noticed in Nebraska so
this is where things get messed up it
doesn't seem right
oh Jesus
oh what did Delaware New Jersey
I don't have space for 50.
New Hampshire
New Hampshire somewhere
Mommy I need a new hamster my old
hamster's dead
um I don't know what I did
oh ah my tummy horned
um
what else what did I not do that
Illinois
it's probably bestest with besties with
Iowa Illinois yeah
oh wait I think I got a reply from Cali
no no no no no no
okay I don't know
oh okay okay
next Colorado I'm missing one well no I
promise you more now okay
that's right there
Washington
okay Washington is here on the this to
see that on the right it's hard to read
um Nebraska Nebraska
is that the only one I'm missing for
real then okay Nebraska will share
because I don't think it's anywhere here
Nebraska will share with
Parkinson's
nah yeah
there it is my map
of America
what Washington DC Washington State uh
Washington
the state is sharing with Massachusetts
now you got it
this is America and with that I think it
will be much easier for me to play
geocacher now
oh
big one somewhat right maybe
which ones are like completely off
which ones are like on the other side of
the globe here hmm
I upload this is Twitter so we can
actually oh go go go go okay
Washington
Vermont
well from Washington I did it at the end
I didn't have much choice you know
um Oregon where did I put Oregon oh my
God ah
okay
[Music]
this isn't looking so bad right
okay okay
good job man good job me
okay with big tummy horde I go back too
I'll go back to Geo guesser
oh
here we are again yo the last one was so
good why is it so big
oh
okay
oh that's kind of weird
oh well ah I guess I could
where we're going next
oh wow it's so pretty
that's nice
no idea though Where We Are
let's go on a trip oh
foreign
looks nice looks pretty oh look at those
trees
that could be more like North
North somewhere North
right I mean look at those
it doesn't look like it's freaking
scorching hot right
it's it's America it's definitely a
miracle
wow what is what they have
what they have um pretty
nice Garden
mmm nice decoration look at that
is that a
h
1805 1605
is that a grave Stone
nice Bush though
a landscaping very nice
here it looks kind of a little bit more
sad you guys need more green what's that
[Music]
oh an address address marker
stop stop
no [\h__\h] idea what that is fan pattern
we're in the middle of nowhere again
guys
[Music]
so guys I'm gonna go this way I'm gonna
go down the road
we are definitely an American Doll
because someone's got an American sign
up there and there we are as if you make
need to make it very clear to everyone
that you're in America as if you didn't
know as if you didn't know you're in the
middle of the [\h__\h] somewhere
Countryside in America and you think you
don't know where you are oh I must be in
Italy I'm surely in Italy oh yeah
because you get so many lost people who
think they're in Italy
you put up signs and let people know
very clearly you're in America son
oh yeah
[Laughter]
you guys really love your flags
was that the scribbles on the ground
here
what is this
oh look at all those cars
like we're at a car dealership on
another flag
okay we must be somewhere in the very
patriotic
um state
they really like their Flags here
uh
it's kind of cute though they play
basketball here
who's that
what's that structure oh they have a
deer too is it for uh
what uh uh Santa Claus
some muscle car no but like what wait is
it a muscle car
no it's not a muscle car but it's cute
it's an oldie
look at that
is a muscle car it looks kind of narrow
though
the classic cardio is kind of cute
foreign
[Music]
what is that TransAm
I love the color it's beautiful
uh so far I've absolutely no hint
where I am
except maybe the trees
but America's quite big you know as
we've seen
oh
and now this is like what McDonald's
McDonald's
is which way
you see that it said McDonald's
I had to actually
I have some McDonald's today and I
wanted to eat the teriyaki
Burger haven't had one in a long time I
only have it here so you know
it was good but I'm like so so confused
still I got reminded oh season change
got reminder that Japan doesn't really
do sauces for
on their potato fries
oh this is just like in GTA
it's like
[Music]
I'm playing with gangs
yeah yeah like they only have like two
sauces like barbecue and uh another one
but they're kind of like for chicken
nuggets they're not for the fries make
you can still get one but
I mean what I usually want is mayonnaise
and I don't have just normalized
mayonnaise it's confusing
I don't [\h__\h] know this one there's no
clues do you guys know where we are
I'll say I say North but like where
am I would probably know this right
yeah but I cheated oh you looked at the
street name or so that we saw
[Music]
try car you can't see those aren't they
censored they're censored you know
[Music]
um
only these are interesting street
markings
Keystone King's role hmm
cute
they built like a little Tower miniature
Tower
okay I found a big streak yo
relatively people
snow
and what
light
holy moly
what
never seen such a huge one that's not
snow
why the f are you [\h__\h] shut up of
course that is snow
look at the comparison to here
what do you think it's really really
really white Cobble or something
it's gravel
oh
I'm gonna go this way
because lights now
I think so too
America flag
let's find something useful American
flag whoopsie
oh
I'll say on this one
[Music]
I have no idea
[\h__\h] this
we are
Nebraska
oh we're good Washington
Maine
Massachusetts
Maryland Maryland
I think I was so far off of Maryland
anyway anyway
I'll say worms
Montana
oh
that's pretty bad
I mean at least I'm not on the East
Coast
oh
oh what
I'm back I think I'm back hello hello
hello what's up
you hear me
oh why is the graphic so bad here
that's really bad awesome is it because
the internet is still like dying
Graphics really bad here
I don't know why the internet died man
sorry about that
eh the graphics so bad here I thought
this was real live by the real life
Graphics so bad
how's that possible
[Music]
anyway let's just chat a little bit
while I'm trying to find where I am
so
I only wrote this on Twitter before so
let me just like say it here as well
at the end of the day I met
um for the first time we were in karaoke
with mermaids
Arena and Cali and me
well basically I oh I think I was like
hi guys I'm free tonight
anyone wanna hang
so I kind of organized it I guess
um
and
that was was that on the first I think
it was an on the first
January maybe
yeah
so Nathan was in Japan she happened to
be in Japan so that was perfect I feel
like we're we're on the big street and
now we're on the tiny Street what the
hell let me go back
I'm gonna go back
yeah eh how much craziest movement IRL
not crazy at all
she was kind of shy
um especially on that day I met her
again the other day
uh but on that day
she told me later that she thinks uh
karaoke and person isn't her thing
because yeah she was like sorry I was so
quiet
she didn't sing at all I wanted to see
her pretty singing voice but she didn't
sing it all
no
um but she was cute they were all kind
of cute and Bale's phone number may had
some matching stuff going on it was kind
of cute they had like the same matching
ribbons
[Music]
you know
um
and uh however me and Kelly and Nina
were pretty much
the only one singing Bale sang some
Disney songs
in like a low character voice
is exaggerated
low character voice I'm not finding
where the [\h__\h] I am again
need help from army
the pro but this country roads
take me home
I sang what did I sing ah me and Dana
sang some Japanese songs
we sang together a couple songs
it's nice this place looks nice
oh
wollenberg that's so German the back
uh we're saying lion together and the
honeyworks song and uh
good night borderline
[Music]
yeah cause I sat no Selena basically uh
I booked a really big room for us
big karaoke room I wanted to go eat
honey tell us there's a Kaioken
chain
called pasira in Japan that serves big
famous honey toast they don't taste like
honey but it's like big chunks of bread
loafs that have like all kinds of stuff
like ice cream and cream and fruit and
so on on top of it and it's really good
the loaf is warm and diced like inside
and the rest is like cool some nice
dessert but normally you can't finish it
alone normally you should eat it with
two or three people
so I was hoping they would eat it with
me but the cool thing is they have like
smaller versions so you can kind of
sample through
so I ordered the smaller ones
several of them but yeah Elena Elena and
um
Nina and Cali ate them with me because
turns out you know I was like Hey I want
to do this
um
sing and eat
um honey dolls anyone wants to come and
then you know they they were like oh
yeah we'll come we'll come uh but then
turns out
they told me like they were at the same
not the same like location but the same
kind of karaoke also passed it up the
day before also eating honey toast also
singing kanoka
so I was like why didn't you tell me we
could have done something else
science what signs I didn't see any
signs
that we could have done something else
because then they didn't they barely
sang and they didn't eat the honey toes
oh well Utica homemade pizza
I kind of wanted to
um melt them
beautiful
place a place I wanted to
to uh
show them this for the first time I
thought that it would be a first for
them but turns out it was not a first
for them at all
uh
I felt
I felt like a failure
Uptown New York
no that because you know that but I
don't know that but I guess you guys are
here to help me
upstate New York
oh they thought New York was only like
like huge buildings and packs and Tiny
Apartments
where's uptown
what's up dog
maybe here
looks very
you guys lied to me
you guys don't know [\h__\h] are you even
American
you got you guys don't know [\h__\h]
no [\h__\h] I think you guys have to
graduate from being American
every American instead in New York
graduate immediately
you are now European
it's more fun here don't worry
I wouldn't have known that at all though
so it's okay
[Music]
and well I wrote already for I'm gonna
be honest honestly when I wrote on
Twitter is pretty much all I can tell
you about that because not much happened
besides that
besides what I wrote
um
I feel like
it was well I wish I had some songs and
that's pretty much it we didn't really
have any particularly meaningful
conversation
these trees look like up north yeah yeah
oopsie don't go away
what does that say
Rockmart
found homes 706
wires 706 from guys
tell me tell me West Virginia
this is West Virginia
orange mountains
American yeah I know we are all the maps
are in America right now
Georgia
where did where did I say George was not
that that's gonna help us
foreign
[Music]
Georgia
um
I was better at this in Japan wasn't I
[Music]
look I was yeah Highway numbers I'm not
really I don't know what the [\h__\h]
I don't want to look at Highway numbers
here America's huge
[\h__\h]
oh where am I
[Music]
oh my god oh after the karaoke When
Callie left a little bit early
uh she had to go and then soon after we
left anyway
and then after karaoke we went into a
donkey Hotel because I needed something
and the girls mostly Bales needed
something ooh the quality's [\h__\h]
and then basically it was bye bye so
not much happened
sorry to disappoint you
I bought the hair iron that it works
with USB
I can't no that was another day
[Music]
no pillow fight no
ah tell me
oh tell me what what's this what's this
that looks like something helpful
finally what the [\h__\h]
look like on Easter card again what
[Music]
is that Atlanta Atlanta
Cartersville Calhoun Atlanta what
Atlanta is in Georgia
yes you can say as if it's that so so
much of a given
I don't see Georgia
Atlanta is in Georgia South East
out here hi
there I fall then it was a stick
okay it's close to Atlanta right and
what happens
Grace
oh oh
very good though
okay okay
[Music]
let me close that
a moment
so we did America we did
um
when did we do Japan let's try
let me see let me see what they have
they have UK Canada Spain France Japan
Australia Netherlands India Brazil
Poland Italy Germany we got the Germany
I feel like in Germany I maybe have a
chance do they not have Austria
it's not like I would know so much more
about Oscar than I would have known
about Germany though
[Music]
okay
oh oh
we're not on the main station we are at
I mean maybe like a station but um that
looks like
looks familiar
definitely familiar there's a station
see I know what stations and [\h__\h] look
like I mean okay I mean even besides the
train tracks though I mean this is a
station building so obviously in in
Austria
like a small and on the countryside oh
yeah oh but it's cargo
[Music]
I feel like now I actually have a chance
man yeah I have a feeling I have a
feeling I know where it is
even though I don't think I've ever been
there before
would they censor
oh let's tell them
it's time
[Music]
I totally know ah
I totally knows I mean I've heard about
them wait where the [\h__\h] is Austria here
let me look a little bit more
Google
yeah Google
let me finally hit but we were placed in
a really good place
like
oh I
[Music]
spoke
I had a feeling yeah yeah yeah so the
Earth's tala I must be Knuckles
yeah yeah okay easy well maybe I'll be
closer let's try to get to the main
station I don't think I've ever been an
ends book before
um but you know you just kind of you
just you just kind of know you just kind
of know
ah this is the main train station
finally I'm winning
finally
finally oh
that must isn't that
oh not Vienna
oh that's nice
it must be oh that's Vienna
can I can guess too
short tingling I don't know but
[Music]
um
wait was there uh was there a
Lake a river yeah that's a that's a
river
[Music]
it's not there
and it's somewhere here
I'm here here here shot tonight
let's go
oh
it is
um one of our
big girls it is
no
tram here
give me a moment
or maybe I wanted to try them here
[Music]
wait that's
huh
don't do I know this place
there's a tram what line is the tram
oh wait station name
[Laughter]
did they put us in Vienna again
somewhere close by come on come on
[Music]
come on put me somewhere else oh what is
that
okay no no no I don't know where I am
apparently but this looks [\h__\h] sick
okay
Juanita I need a hand you know we're
we're not in the capital anymore this
won't be so easy anymore but it looks
nice oh yeah that's a typically Austrian
building with the green green window
thing is the shape of that the yellow
and the green and the brown that's so
Austrian guys this is a mountains there
oh
that's also you see green window
thingies again very Austrian hi ladies
all right Google passing for you Google
Maps passing through stalking you
don't mind me
it's nice it's nice
but so far I don't know where I am I
know I'm in Austria
oh this is also yeah yeah Austrian
Austrian kind of old Austrian though
wait
um well that's cute
I'm a stock
[\h__\h] gotta go back maybe I can gonna go
here oh I should read that
no that doesn't help me it's just the
random street name but we are in a
little village you know
Countryside
I guess which could be anywhere we have
a lot of those in Austria I think
oh no sex nine nine
um thank you oh I've heard of that
before
is there a right way to play Geo guesser
like are you allowed to look up
something while you play it
that that
[Music]
no whoa
whoa
[\h__\h]
Ed out
what's pretty here
oh
wait that looks like a bigger Street
nice
okay what is that
foreign
it says um it's like a like a this is
this must be a factory where they make
um bread with wheat because it says uh
oh this is an a big place in Austria and
mail is flower flu or flower fluid
okay I'm wearing four eye bags
it is
[Laughter]
I can't say [\h__\h]
everything's so small
you won't no no no no no this is not
Germany Germany is like here from here
this is the Border
up until here it's all straight now you
see the Border
[Music]
wait wait do we have do we have a city
name though
for eye bag and wow it felt cute right
well I don't know where the [\h__\h] felt
cooking is
[Music]
wait where the [\h__\h] is for iPad again
eh I can't see it where is full album
uh here it's nice to be here I can't see
can't say I can't say it where's the big
letters
I can't say it
where is it
huh
shouldn't there be a big full album
right here
uh uh it's somewhere here because
there's eye bag here
there's a eye bag here
and then is
no [\h__\h] idea
let's see where the [\h__\h] I am
well I'll just say we're here what
it's pretty good that's pretty good it's
pretty good
oh that looks like a normal City again
interesting interesting interesting they
have a trap no wait that's a normal
train wait is it no train or trim
let me let me look around but this one
will be easier than the previous one
cities always a bit easier I would say
oh that looks like that's a train
that's a train that no no no no there's
another normal train tracks you guys are
saying Tremors more like a train track
to me
especially around here
okay
does this
foreign
why can't I go further
the solution is over there
[Music]
um
how about well let's see how far we come
we can go that way
oh oh there's snow but you know snow in
Austria can happen pretty much
everywhere
there's not in particular like North or
so
oh well I mean the address on this one
says Vienna but
I have that
I don't think right
well maybe I mean
maybe on like outskirts
because
in the distance that still looks like a
lot of City ahead of us
there's a concert oh no we must be
somewhere in Vienna because it says here
Vienna Concert Hall
Robin Hood
the musical
July 2022 this is pretty recent they had
a Robin Hood Musical
okay
[Music]
um
when where's oopsie where what
what what what what what here we're
somewhere somewhere
don't know where
um
I can't I can't guess this one so
exactly but oh
what
we were so Central
that's fascinating to me wow but I did
so good in this
um
I got a medal for Austria that means I'm
Australian
oh but most of them were in Vienna what
the [\h__\h] the only one here one here
could have given me a bit more variety
and I once again I want again
oh Austria the Alps are Cinema classical
music the inventions we all have Austria
and austrians to thank for the
inventions like the sewing machine
[Music]
I did not know about that
what
those composers like Mozart Titan
Schubert oh to name a few winter sports
and then particular albin's King is a
culture activity thanks for neighboring
Alps yep
what I don't know about the batteries
and the the sewing machine
[Music]
it's nice to actually like have a rough
idea of where the [\h__\h] you are though so
I enjoyed playing Wall Street what's
this Facebook parking only and they have
a little bit
oh wait a [\h__\h]
um
yeah we're uh we're somewhere
where don't ask me
let's see
ah they see me rolling
I want to Best Buy oh well
you know
maybe I should have at some point gotten
myself a license for one of those small
Vehicles what
because I still don't have a car license
but at least that would have been
helpful
[Music]
they are
um horse
uh
horse people hmm
sorry so yesterday I went uh okay with
Canada's Empire you know we actually
have uh
of collab set up
um I I've been planning one with her and
another member but the other day when we
did whole talk you know like we got so
excited and I couldn't hold back and I
needed to I needed to just get it out of
my system so I asked her to go to
karaoke with me first I wanted to hang
with someone you know and contact us if
I had time and we just need to get all
that help project out of her system oh
it's for horses
[Music]
I know by this thing
that this car passed by here around me
because this is a May Tree in Austria
on the 1st of May we put up a weird tree
like this
it's so nice finally I can show you an
example of uh this one I've been telling
you about
[Music]
Maple yeah and then they
um they try to get up their children and
adults and then you know you gotta go I
never did that before though and it's
more on the countryside so I don't know
exactly how the tradition goes but yeah
and then and then there's a tradition
where
um neighboring Villages I think they try
to steal other people's other villagers
Maples
yeah like how the [\h__\h] do you do that
though they're huge and I need some
strong bulky man to do that or lots of
horses are um around here I think
damn
definitely Countryside but where so far
I know
no luck in getting a hit oh this is a
better Street
okay
[Music]
I
wouldn't mind living here
oh foreign
which way should we go that way or the
other way
maybe this way
sweet what does it say yeah
Vena
Festival
don't tell me we're actually close to
the Capitol again
foreign
it doesn't look like it though
oh I guess maybe
[Music]
but I mean more and more it's starting
to look like ah okay
bamboozle
oh it wears
where is
oh
and I think it's like on the I mean look
look where we are it must be
on the outskirts
foreign
[Music]
let's
I'm so good I'm so good let's go
yo by the way guys I noticed for some
reason my monetization is off are you
guys able to send super chats though
checking because I don't know why the
monetization is off
chateau yeah again probably and yeah but
this is like random right
they're not set locations right
could be could be Vienna Gamble
same thing
yes we can okay okay okay
thank you
oh you guys are so fast with your tests
damn but are you is this making you guys
realize how pretty Austria is I I can
like show you around like this I wish it
would like bring us to like
um
I wish it would spawn us like more like
here I want to show you more pretty
places it's kind of lame
look I mean it's pretty here too but you
know it's just yeah there's pretty
places not much Street camera in Austria
oh is there not much Choice Maybe
foreign
[Music]
I feel like they have personalities I
like the green one actually that's a
pretty green
AI
I think I like the the this like beige
one too
hmm cute
all right all right what was I saying oh
yeah kind of the same time so oh that's
that must be a big hand what is that
oh for [\h__\h] sake it's Vienna again
as boring as [\h__\h]
no where exactly we are I'm just gonna
oh wait here's Obama
okay we're on the other side of the city
but whatever
come on that's Vienna guesser and it's
gonna be me and again no
I'm in Illinois it could also be
somewhere else in Austria really I mean
Austria looks like this everywhere
looking in the garden
beautiful garden
wow
privacy though privacy Sudoku
hey thank you for looking with me I feel
like I'm showing you around giving you a
tour it's kind of nice I want to play
this with Cal you know because she we
can probably like teach me a thing or
two about America
anyway anyway I want to say you know
yeah yeah yeah so kind of the same by me
yeah oh they have a pool
we didn't
talk much we were like in two and a half
hours we were just singing endlessly and
then fangirling over the music videos
because we were mostly chose choosing
songs that had music videos uh attached
to them like the proper ones because a
lot of the songs that are not so super
popular have just like random karaoke
footage you know
yeah weird weird Canoga footage
um yeah so we didn't talk much but every
time when the song was over like oh this
was nice wasn't it with someone's
thoughts like oh they were so young back
then oh
it's like reminiscing
foreign
property I can't read it oh [\h__\h] it
copy yeah I
Ikea Warehouse or can people actually
shop here
where's Sweden guys bamboozled
we're in Sweden hey y'all nice my first
time in Sweden
oh
that actually does not tell me where I
am
yet
whoa
I love it Ikea this is an Austria I
think
Obi and Ikea next to an OB
oh this is like
a big like shopping big things area
okay
okay we're in Vienna
our address said Vienna they need to
censor that
we're in Vienna
but it's not an Ikea where people Shop
Boys at the warehouse I'm not sure about
that
because it looked like you wouldn't be
able to shop there but maybe it's just
from that side
um
oh
Ikea Vienna North
okay so they can shop there okay
what the address
she doesn't even look so cool so closely
at the map though yo yo yo the answer is
small you know Austria is [\h__\h] small
yeah love it
wow oh there's a casino here
cool but why why does it always is it
really because I mean doesn't it just
have
doesn't just use the data from Google or
does Geo guesser
like
can they not use everything Google Maps
has
because why if if they have all of
Google
wouldn't they be able to throw me
somewhere else as well
I think every country in law is cool
yeah but Austria obviously does
apparently Germany as far as I know
actually not but still their choice and
and you guess right
it's weighted algorithm based on user
ratings and curation
I have no idea yeah I mean it wasn't
only Vienna so far but mostly
so that's weird not all other roads have
street views so like smaller like
yeah but we have more than one big city
in Austria
in the tunnel before I never see my
brother or my mom's buying them before I
hit him I want them back what oh my God
oh my God let me ask how long is the
center ah
terrible
stream along ew
ew it hurts my eyes
let me out I think I see the light on
the end of the tunnel
I think
um
come on come on
Let Me Out imagine we're at the end of
the tunnel of their site they say oh
this is as far as you can get you
already pressed so many buttons forward
the light
bye bye guys bye bye I said a light ah
it's beautiful whoa whoa whoa oh come on
this doesn't look like Vienna I think
who knows who knows
where are we
where are they
where can we be
[Music]
hopefully this one will be a bit more
challenging but wait I see some
cell
and a mountain Captain back never heard
of that one but I heard of Maria cell
before
I've heard of it
on a radio
it's a mountain but not a real
significant Mountain I think
[Music]
all roads lead to vehicle
was so sweet
you ordered me a taxi to go back to my
doctor tomorrow even though it was
really far I was gonna just go back with
the train but it was going to take a
long time and then kind of December was
like I'm gonna call you and text him
like
yeah because Senpai because I'm Senpai
with a nice Sapphire right
yeah
that was really comfy it was much faster
it was so much faster than going by
train thank god oh look at that we're
far from Vienna I think one how far is
138 kilometers I don't really have a
feeling for that I need to start driving
cars then I'll get a feeling for it well
but it's it's not so far that it
wouldn't be recommended to you on this
on the on the highway
so
is it how far is how two hours drive
[Music]
wait
okay let's go let's go let's go let's go
but we're not quite there yet right
we're on the way to it but very close
did we see let's try let's try to get
this close
did we see uh
there
a number
for the road
do they have numbers I don't see any
numbers for the road
where where would they be
I really closely already know where I am
though the mountain oh yeah do I see the
mountain here
oh
how would they
what color would the Mountain Bee
there's the mount this is all mountains
green
between these are all too big we're
looking for a small one huh
[Music]
something like cupping bag right
I should see it now no
huh
oh maybe it's not a mountain
maybe it's a okay yeah it could be a
city
like a village yeah
okay whatever
I'll say we're like
no I don't see it do you guys see it
we should be like around here
oh [\h__\h]
laughs
oh
a cup and Beyond
what then was wasn't Marietta really
close
wasn't it only like three kilometers or
so
it feels so far but yet relatively close
I mean it's not the worst yeah at least
we weren't in Vienna unlike now
again
skip
what does it say
Leo Port Museum
Museum
what's house
so comfortable
shoots house
oh wait wait
[Music]
um
too cold after schmelts no I don't know
what that is but it looks kind of
interesting what's that system
that's probably been again let's be real
oh man but where
Indiana
I mean it looks pretty like
City
not city city center Center but City
Center
all right all right all right all right
let's just get this over with
hey
oh [\h__\h] what what that was just a random
guess I was like on the red side again
[Laughter]
yeah
[Music]
can I get another medal
do we get another medal oh
okay I wish that maybe
should we go for a different one I won't
be so good at the other ones though
foreign
we'll do one more map
and then I read super chats
Germany
I can't do a mix of Europe you know I
have to be
um unfortunately kind of exact
thing
Canada well I don't I know nothing about
Canada though
UK would be safer
let's let's go to the UK
at least I've been there before
never been to Canada Oh Canada Oh Canada
oh
ish
how is it now why are they all the same
that's kind of lame but I do like the
design in general it's kind of funny
look at that
it's like round here they have a very
little little roof it's not really a
roof
[Music]
okay okay wait there's still something
here
oof
nothing new tells me I don't know I
don't know these places don't cast or
gainsboro ghoul what are those names
Glasgow you know what even though I have
no idea about UK when I saw this I was
also feeling a Glasgow I didn't want to
say it because I felt like it would be a
ridiculous guess like but I don't know
something about this even though I know
nothing about it it gives me Glasgow
feelings
I don't even know where Glasgow is
though
but
it just screams at me Glasgow
hello lady
you look so British
nice to meet you
wait did I write something down I really
don't think much happened in um in the
Canada same point oh yeah so we must
just sang I didn't um yeah we sang some
songs solo and then I wanted to sing
some songs together but you know I find
it kind of boring when you just sing
all lines together so we would like give
each other a sign like okay next two and
then next two and the next two to kind
of give each other parts as if it was a
concert you know what I mean it worked
out pretty well
um and actually it seems like I knew no
more songs
from Hello project oh by the way it was
a help project Only karaoke we said
we'll only sing karaoke from Hell
project
yeah Idol agency that I love
all the houses are the same
yeah and um uh I actually do more songs
I think I'm a
I'm sorry to say but I think I'm a
bigger fan
a little project in there I mean also
she's she had never has been to a
concert before which I wouldn't say that
that makes me a bigger fan but I mean
[Music]
no no no no she didn't go because
small you know what but still you know I
need more songs too
yeah and she's she's like mostly she was
into morning musume
the biggest group they have
and I mean I know some more muscle but
it wasn't my my biggest like interest
you know
[Music]
um
but yeah I sang I think mostly Betty
School Blue and cute and smiley songs
and then kind of
how does he sang a lot of songs but then
you know we sing together a lot of them
and
and a lot of oldies like usually all of
them were old songs
recent songs we both don't really know
so that's something we have in common
connected again uh
[Music]
hello
internet
what's going on
we're back
not as bad as yesterday
oh I mean yeah
obviously
what's that looks like a school
it looks like a school doesn't it
what the [\h__\h] is that
there's a job center
yeah it looks like a school to me yeah
job center okay but it didn't say any
city did it
[Music]
um
he's posing for the Google car
see it
nice reflex heart well chord is hard for
the city
does it belong to Ford
[\h__\h] people
[Laughter]
and
ah I said that
God was
oh man where are we ah I am I don't know
I don't know this place
um
are there any British people in my chat
right now
post office wow
a huge post office what the [\h__\h]
wow
train station
[Music]
I don't say a train station
oh from London hello ukfp report you
can't be no idea
yeah Grimsby where the [\h__\h] is that
though
uh okay let's see maybe it's actually
pretty big and we'll find it pretty
easily
is a clue any close at all to London or
uh
Cloud sister
oh
North
wow
Northeast
we're not in Grimsby though right green
greens grapes bridge is closed
right
nice though nice nice scun for I was
wondering too maybe we're here
because it looks like a relatively big
city I don't know
[Music]
it's pretty good it's pretty good guys
hell yeah
okay okay
go next
residence in my Marion that looks fancy
um
oh
wow Harry Potter
I like we're in Harry Potter
all right London
this London
who is this
who is she
oh oh oh
it's Scotland this is Scotland
oh [\h__\h] ship row Union Street
[Music]
there's a map here
foreign
Scotland
wow it's beautiful
holy [\h__\h] what a feel
oh this sounds like a well-known thing
Aberdeen
operating
wow this must be a pretty big well-known
City though
[Music]
wow that's beautiful
yo it looks so like oh like history
castle gate
whoa
oh yeah
cool
okay okay
wait where's Scotland up here all the
way up here I
wait so up here we have a Glasgow and
Adam blur
and but are we in those or
somewhere else
hey it looked pretty important
Aberdeen I don't say Aberdeen
is that where is that wow
wow wow wow
foreign
[Music]
but it's beautiful
okay it's castle gate
all right
oh me there's I think it that's the
closest we got before or was it 69
meters was I was that 69 kilometers or
69 meters before that I was like
far went far from something else
nice
[Music]
up there but um I will give some credit
to myself too oh one of the days
could be anywhere
I start walking
uh
so and I'm I'm gonna meet Canada Senpai
again soon so look forward to that next
up tomorrow I think isn't isn't my
tomorrow
I'm kind of having troubles like with
days
figuring out what day it is recently
yeah tomorrow evening
yeah judging by how shitty is that my
internet is at the hotel I'm I think I'm
since utano is in
is in uh Japan I'm gonna I think I'll go
over to her place to do it I still have
to make a PowerPoint though I'm gonna
make a PowerPoint presentation and we're
gonna do Platform presentations on him
project so you guys you should check it
out it's
um it's gonna be happening on Ophelia's
Channel I'm gonna tweet it out anyway so
just check my Twitter
[Music]
um
tomorrow
yeah I think actually the reservation is
already up so you could already find it
if you want to and turn on the
notification Bell
yeah so that's happening tomorrow
evening
um but during the day I have to like
practice and dance for Folk's sake
because I haven't been practicing at all
for [\h__\h] sake
and um I really need to for folks sake
and yeah but I've got all day I think
because
um collab is really late I think 10 p.m
jst or so or 9 p.m during stay
well
y'all might I hope you guys will be
there see you there
you know originally of course I wanted
to do stuff like this on my channel but
this way I have more freedom
got more freedom in terms of um
and what I can say
of course I'm gonna say pause the thanks
um but originally when I wanted to do
something like this on my channel I was
told I have to get everything checked
and I was like
um that kind of kills my motivation so
it will be in English we all speak
English
they're all English speaking
yeah
and then on Sunday I think of collab
with modern senpai
staying over at our place
and then Monday
clearness Empire of collab back to back
although Monday is going to be kind of
tough for me because like I wake up
early
I have to leave Molly and senpai's place
and then I have to do some studio
recordings
[Music]
uh uh and some other [\h__\h]
that will take up my whole day
and then I go to coronation boy
so
really stressful actually
but you know
that one will be on my channel I don't
know about the mindset by one on which
channel we do that one on but yeah you
know
keep an eye out I'm excited you know I
prefer these like one-on-one collabs
over big clubs
I know about you guys but that's just me
so I've been focusing on those I feel
like it's easier for me to bond with
them
focus on getting to know each other
with some one-on-one time yeah big ones
got chaotic yeah
and you know I mean free is still fine
for me free Payne's Castle no no go back
Payne's Castle
Brecken upper Hondo hey on why what are
these names
readers Retreat
[Music]
um
I think UK was a mistake
[Laughter]
it died
beautiful tree what happened no
no no no no no no no
go back to being pink
my mouse
ah look at this hey that was pretty
again
probably Vienna no it's not
no
like that here
cozy understanding
[\h__\h] what does it say elderly people
her node
what does that mean to the English
what are they doing with elderly people
you're speaking a different language
here
close the under canvas clamping bring
win Writing Center basketball arms new
church
Welsh
see that's that's a hint you know that
it didn't sound English to me
well should I say I say oh
very [\h__\h]
Hereford something lives Mr
I'm looking
at it those are cheap right oh they're
so cute
foreign
[Music]
I mean I saw some names of streets but
like nothing that I really see here
um
[Music]
all right
I'm not so bad
oh what's that poopy
whoa okay
we're in the middle of like tiny side
switch off and you're telling me you
couldn't Place me in more remote places
in Austria really
I'm really like [\h__\h] nowhere right
now but it's cute
where is this
oh cool Vienna no
that's cute
oh let's get out of here I need a big
street man
Chester United
what the [\h__\h] it was oh creepy
normal street
I need a normal street
put that here we go
here we go
don't hesitate
okay
so
day before yesterday guys
I met again with Mommy
and someone else
and
I I know I don't really want to tell you
anything about that yet until next
stream
because
yeah but we went to Arcade and then
played some marketing
with someone else and yeah so I can't
really
I'll tell you more about it soon okay
the Deets the Deets are following
I wrote it all down don't worry I got
the meats
nuts
[Music]
a graduated member and I should stay on
the this is yeah
yo it's more fun when I actually know
where I am
yeah thank you for driving carefully
okay so we're out of yelmed and if we go
that way wherever Yankton is
I'm not gonna give you any more details
I'm not I'm not supposed to
no make me
link me
I'm gonna get my butt slapped otherwise
yelped and knowing that place uh-huh yo
but this is cute look at that view it
goes down and then there's houses up
there again it's cute
looks like it rains a lot because the
streets are always wet definitely UK
shopping list all I tell you I'm not
even doesn't know that no that's
supposed to know them we shouldn't be
knowing them
you spoiling me
but it's not like I have any chance of
like figuring out where I am otherwise
to be honest
oh this is a nice cute straight
I don't [\h__\h] know man
here we have some oh bricks in Plymouth
I've heard of fly Mouse before and
Bricks nothing too
play mouth
all right all right all right all right
can we see a Brixton
um
how far does it say how far we are not
really
it says to get on the road to Plymouth
which could still be like really far
right
play mouth play play mouth please
whatever whatever
um wait a three seven nine yeah I mean
it really could be like I don't know
depending on how long the street is
could be really far right
hmm
I don't care I what
climb off
[Music]
just gone close then I thought it would
be further away because
yeah well okay okay
this is the last one the Royal orc oh
oak oak
Air Museum Roman Fort Wright and Gardens
oh cute building that is
not resonating going that way
oh that must be Vienna just kidding
um
London Road oh they surely have London
Road everywhere
that doesn't really mean anything
[Music]
oh my my top the top of my head is
starting to hurt from these headphones
oh
um
no no Road
London Road
take me home
to your rope
where I belong
ten foot what's your problem what was it
always about 10 foot 10 foot 10 foot 10
foot what does that mean
yo Scott why did I have the right hand
foot a million times on that
stupid graffiti I don't like graffiti I
mean if it's pretty and not like
disturbing like a nice building or so
okay but most of graffiti does [\h__\h] up
beautiful buildings in there I'm sorry
but I don't like it
um I'm sorry like I respect when people
make like really intricate beautiful art
with graffiti but if they just like slam
some shitty font on it and just write
like [\h__\h] you or some stupid [\h__\h] it's
like really like would you disrespect
these beautiful buildings that people
worked so hard on on putting up
and painting and you know
this is so sad
where are we what is that
is that straight Street markings zigzag
zigzag
tic-tock tick tock
um
who's weekly cars twinkly lines for
squiggly cars I was in cars that would
fit that here
on the street
definitely Austria drunk people
stop oh there's a there's some big
buildings over there
that might help us oh oh that's signed
that sign
Ring Road Ring Road jails more okay that
didn't really help me
[\h__\h] off [\h__\h] off mate
you know actually speaking of British
people and so on I've been watching
um I I kind of like was binge watching a
YouTube channel I think his name is Zach
you still used to be with another dude
but now his channel is solo no no no no
no but he makes really funny videos that
are like so well made
for example like he tried to hitchhike
to get um a free uh private jet flight
to anywhere out of the UK and and it
eventually worked after a lot of
a lot of [\h__\h]
and it was
so funny
[Music]
stuff like that like challenges
exactly set a c
um
and then and then and then what else did
they do uh he went to America to
um try to find Elon Musk and deliver a
leather personally never really not
meeting him but uh it was it was a funny
Adventure 2 because he tried to find
people who know him and actually a lot
of people had stories about him there
where the SpaceX uh stuff is
and he was trying to prove that we all
know someone threw like six connections
you know
Coventry Airport
rugby Warwick Whitley I don't know what
Coventry is but it has an airport so we
should be able to find it is it in
England
oh don't you love it when your eyes fall
exactly on what you're looking for
sometimes thank God
pretty good six steps of Separation
exactly exactly exactly now I can really
recommend that channel it's really good
okay yeah
give me that medal
in gold
here this one was way more scattered all
over
I didn't get a gold medal did I
didn't get a medal
[Music]
I got silver I should have gotten gold
I was so British you okay you were young
[Music]
um
but that was fun finally regressively do
you guys have properly yeah
thank you guys
but you guys want to read some pictures
now you're welcome to stay because like
you know you got you ain't got much of
me recently it's a solo stream and there
won't be many of them in the next days
at all next days are only collabs yum
thank you Karen no thank you
mm-hmm
what's so too yeah
[Applause]
thank you
yeah let's read some pictures I'm just
gonna stay on this
um screen because
um I
I don't have anything else
on Callie sobs
it's not even I can't even go to like
Cali's scenes because she doesn't use
OBS so there's nothing here really
um
on it
I wanna
here
let's just keep this open oh I'm reading
super chats
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
let's go
wow
earlier than I thought you would come
back oh she's gonna be so excited to see
my America map
okay I don't know if I can really focus
on reading super chats uh once she's
back so let's try let's try to be fast
uh
colonizer
guys where do I continue let's be speed
let's be speed let's be speed
foreign
[Music]
oh is tomorrow the Mario Kart tournament
huh
today tomorrow right
you see that the reason why I'm not
participating is just because I knew I
was going to travel in Japan at the time
and I could not like rely
on
like having stable streaming environment
and also I didn't know if maybe I would
have other things to do and then I
didn't want to be the one to cancel
it after saying I will participate
because I got suddenly something else to
do like more important and so on yeah I
didn't want to like stress myself over
having to stream something like that and
practice it in such a busy time yeah
so I'm not taking part in it
[Music]
um
yeah
it's okay no we wouldn't you wouldn't
want well you know with mummy and other
mysterious person the the when I was in
the arcades you know we played Mario
Kart
in the arcades
and I won it was so close though holy
[\h__\h] the whole time we were on each
other's butts
and then
I won yay
are you pretty good at the game no but
Mario Kart on in our cats is very
different from playing Mario Kart in
on switch very different
yeah who lost most oh we only play one
round
so I won that one
yeah
seems like they didn't feel like playing
again oh one thing I can tell you about
that day is
um there was a there was a like um you
know how there's a lot of those like uh
capsule capsule capsule catches
well you know kind of what you were
getting but there's like a five
different choices or so something yeah
and
um there was one weird gotcha uh and it
said that you could win a Nintendo light
you have to put in a thousand yen which
is like eight bucks or so and the
biggest thing you can win is a Nintendo
light switch light and other things were
like also pretty good when one was a
Splatoon switch game uh and I don't know
I don't know some other decent things
okay so I was like no way I'm getting a
light but let me try this it it showed
like six different samples or so of what
you could get from like good stuff but I
was like surely there's like some other
shitty really shitty rewards right
because all of this has more value than
eight bucks so there's no way yeah they
didn't show you what what are the shitty
things you can get I was like you know
what I'll try this
really I'm gonna try it so I put in the
thousand yen and what did I get
and USB capable
but honestly I kind of needed one and
it's a good one it it it's like USB
normal USB to USB C and whatever like
three different USB tabs one of them
being also an apple type so I was like
actually I kind of needed it and it's
not just a normal USB cable no I was
like oh this is kind of fancy it's like
uh red and and the cable looks feels
pretty like sturdy
so
I connected in my hotel room right and
and what happens is
it lights up and it lights up really
strongly in the lights it doesn't it
doesn't just like stable light up no it
it like moves you know the light moves
in the cable
[Music]
oh it's a game a cable
oh it's so cool I'm gonna show you a
video maybe when I'm back
it
looks so cool
but then the cool thing is you know when
it's not connected and when it's not
connecting properly and I've been having
that problem in my hotel room yeah yeah
I am my four thousand five thousand
dollar hotel room that sometimes
whenever I connect it's not connecting
it's not charging I notice it's not
charging but I don't really see a
particular like reason for it which
sometimes work sometimes it doesn't also
with different cables and with different
Outlets
huh
no I don't think it's the the fault of
my
cables or so Dough because sometimes
this super new cable would sometimes
work in the same outlet and sometimes
not
it was just randomly decide to work
hmm
I just got here how is this so wrong
have you not gotten the news
I'm president of the United States now
and I've changed your map a little bit
I've taken the Liberty to change it a
little bit
yeah so you better deal with it
I think this is way more fitting
I live in Utah and he's a little change
of pace hi portal so have I read those
uh super chats they're not many I'll go
through them let's see
uh Cruise
uh should I wait should I write this
down I should probably write this down
so you guys know what I'm reading uh
wait no I'll just I'll give you a little
I'll give you the thumbnail
foreign
good I still live in Michigan did I get
you right what no way
change of state
oh oh I still have two floridas oh oh I
didn't have to have everyone sharing huh
thanks for the membership
I did read that one okay
thank you for letting me know
oh you know I keep on having you know my
my screens and my home are like uh next
to one another sideways but Cali screens
are like on top of each other it's like
oh look up another down it's good for
the neck Maybe
good neck exercise
what about the Pokemon Scarlet finale
yondo I don't know
I did I did
oh all of this
oh okay
well a sock puppet I didn't read come on
I didn't read the sock puppets did I
okay
what a thumbnail
[Music]
yeah uh
here it is okay Pepsi language
[Music]
for the two pinkies give them girls
episode eight lower light passed up
Luke's coffee to go walk in the snow
crazy if someone gave you the choice of
fresh lasagna and walking in the
Maldives never mind it's the Maldives
yeah I mean fresh lasagna is awesome too
but poor little solid kiss oof don't
give up look wait who did she kiss
probably
um future
digging agreeing to go to Roy's dance
even though he's not a dance person was
sweet I don't think Dina off the first
two is nice bonding moment with Emily
and Laura and I until it blew up Tristan
is a deck
that needs to be true
Tristan yeah
Tristan is
I don't know how to describe it
he's like a like a Barbie boy but yeah
thinks he's so cool but actually uh
later in the story I think you noticed
that
um
a really strict father or so and you
kind of start feeling for him a little
bit for a moment there later
um but generally he's kind of a douche
yeah
possibly a [\h__\h] boy
oh but you know I think that makes
Gilmore Girls so great they have so many
different kinds of characters a lot of
like bullying characters too but
um a lot of the bully characters end up
being Rory's friends and so on and you
see you see how they have a big
character development going on there
it's really cool
foreign
puppetry
so I love this old school perspective
you know what you're kind of rhyme
you're kind of rhyme
tip
interesting sugar has together thanks
for the pinky yeah finally able to see
him live for a bit just wanted to say
that I went to a con and make more kfb
employees and some of them were kids
when you say kids how young do you mean
they saw me wear my homework submerged
and made me tear up
why did it make you tear up next gen one
loves quinoa at the next gen loves
quinoa
are you here how young are we talking
do I need to be worried
technically everyone's really quick yeah
are we all on triloquists
no no wait no because this is means no
no I'm not making like some things no no
no no no no no no
no that's not that that's kind of
breaking the fourth wall
yeah maybe I'm probably they probably
mean more like teenagers right
ultimate MK
203.
[Music]
the puppets have no clothes on oh yeah
you know if I had more time I did I did
consider like giving them like some more
details maybe not full on clothing but
for crony for example I wanted to give
her a big bow
um a big booba but I did feel like she
probably would not really appreciate
that
um but yeah I would have have had to do
that for everybody so I I just said okay
for now not if I have some more time at
the end I'll give them more clothes but
obviously uh of course
I did not have enough time at the end
maybe maybe for the future I can upgrade
them but I'm pretty happy with how they
are at the moment in cloves is kind of
like difficult next level
[Music]
um
would be cute but
yeah
[Music]
um
I like them the way they are now
I mean some of them are falling apart
I don't mean mostly good eyes falling
apart I wish I could redo Emma's teeth
oh
can we
[Music]
please can we go
are you doing
hello Kelly hello
um how's it going it's going well I'm
reading super chats I would like you to
inspect my homework
of my America map ooh okay here we go
uh to be honest with you I actually
don't know uh many of these but let me
see where's the wait okay Texas I got
right Texas you got correct
that is not Colorado of course
of course no this is Colorado North
Dakota and South Dakota should be over
here oh [\h__\h] to the right
um but I got Alaska right and then I put
a whole Hawaii here too yeah Hawaii and
I got California California that's
correct this is uh Washington they're
sharing they're sharing our Kansas and
Nebraska are sharing okay Florida first
I put it here but then I was like maybe
Florida is here and there it was correct
yes but I just kept the other one here
too so there's two floridas oh wow
you're really doing you're doing a great
job yeah uh New York I mean I got a lot
of them kind of clothes I heard they
told me not bad not bad uh West
Virginia's down here
I mean a lot of these to be honest yeah
I mean people in the midwest might
disagree they they may be offended but
but one thing I was I knew when I
thought was we were spoiled about that
is
um I know that this side is so populated
because this side is mostly desert right
uh yeah the desert the desert is not so
much in like the upper region oh yeah
maybe more like the middle right above
like Texas to the West yeah California
is not really a desert though yeah I I
know that like here is there some more
Mountains again which throw shade on on
that side Shadow on that side yeah so it
gets cooler again here but most of here
has like uh here has no mountains so
it's like hot as [\h__\h] and nobody lives
there well Colorado which is this area
definitely has mountains really yeah
it's very mountainous but I mean like
the desert's mostly right here and then
you have mountains here
there's like a big mountain range oh
yeah honestly for someone that you know
doesn't really live in America yeah
pretty good I mean I feel like [\h__\h] you
can't do much better than that so oh wow
nice job it's a compliment it sounds
mean but it's a compliment no no no well
I'm I'm
very well done
if not take off my shoes
yes uh these are really hard to take off
so excuse me they look still very clean
so yeah at least on the upper side
they're brand new I'm taking them off
and then
um I'm going to take a shower so you'll
hear some shower noises then I'm going
to bed so okay this is your area I'll
read until you're done showering take a
long shower will do yeah just do your
thing have fun
okay nice I'm gonna close this door sour
stream no one's invited though let's see
if she'll sing in the shower for him
oh and Kelly's man oh did she just say
that she's gonna go to sleep after that
then I have to
pick myself out maybe I should actually
you know what I really have to urgently
charge my phone though oh let me just
quickly get up and get the charging
cable
in case I'm going back
one
more
okay
is there and you always be Outlet
I can use
where are they use
it was being oh that looks like no no
that's not um
I have to crawl
under this
oh oh here's one this one here's one
second I'm just gonna try my phone here
it only has like nine percent
I gotta go home it's gonna be a long
ride so it's so it's so early enough to
go back I think for me like in terms of
trains
um
should I say it was my switch Yeah but
I'm like I don't know
[Music]
Nutella she's gone now she's showing
where was I uh okay child thank you for
the recipe
she came back a bit earlier than I
thought she would and then she that she
thought she would so it's Pro wise but I
want to still read as many as I can Jay
welcome I guess you and die of Windex I
guess you're engulging booming anime
food straps thank you and Jokers Mr
Helen Duncan Anonymous 247 section nerd
books
soon
[Music]
by the way I'm sorry guys that I'm um I
mean I'm still reading the ones that I
usually promise to read like Reds and
pinks but I'm sorry that I'm not reading
much besides that because um
once I'm kind of called up again you
know I'll go back to mixing in some
others again as well
[Music]
um
thank you for the pinky very funny
stream and Incredibly creative I want to
thank you for your hard work and
dedication and constant commitment to
your fans and thanks for putting
together the Advent calendar it melted
my cold Scrooge heart just in time of
Christmas oh man really I'm sure you
have a lovely warm big heart though
and yeah the stream was fun I mean it
could have been better it was actually
really exhausting for me I feel like the
the
members only one went much better and
was a bit more fun
um because of the perspective it was
less exhausting for me
I wanted to improve it in terms of like
I don't know
looks and cleanliness for the public
stream but it made it more difficult for
me
um
I I hope it still looked okay I tried my
best to
make the movement of the puppets look
exciting
oh but uh
it was so difficult
um
it overstated it's welcome a little bit
because I underestimated how long it
would be
oh but thank you so much glad you
enjoyed it
yeah my puppet show Queenie
also picked it up uh in her new show
[Music]
this was Peak online content
some puppets fighting over a love tank
mid lips in concert it's all downhill
from here just take my handle oh thank
you I don't think it went on for much
longer after that oh no I think it was
like two hours right
and then they dropped it they dropped my
cough drop man how dare you
had fun with them no also looking back
on some of them
cute
they were cute weren't they
sock puppets and members some people
said
I made them because
they were all gone and I needed friends
but that's not
that's not true it's not true thank you
[Music]
thank you
I'd love the show to start but didn't
expect it to be quite as entertaining as
it ended up being you put a lot of heart
into this and does it ever show Bravo
thank you bro oh thank you oh I'm really
glad I came up with the idea I hope I
can come up with more ideas like this
but you know these are like every once
in a while kind of creative ideas and
this one took a lot of effort I thought
it would be way faster and easier to
make the sock puppets but
after I made the first one you know I
also added more details
and I wanted them to really like look
like what who they supposed to be and I
put so much effort into like also dying
the wool
oops
with acrylic color
yeah dipping them into the water and
dying them and drying them and cutting
them and styling them
so much effort into it man
so
yeah being sick slowed you down
[Music]
yeah
not necessarily it's just um actually
being sick kept me from doing other
streams so I had a lot of time to do
sock puppets if I wasn't sick oh then I
don't think this would have been
possible
[Music]
um
oh her beep doesn't make a beep sound I
might and Jackson that worked didn't it
is
the worm Superior language shadow
[Music]
we will take the most out of even the
most depressing situation
sometimes sometimes
Shadow neighbor retention Slavic Channel
thanks for the pinky thank you for the
amazing concert no thank you for coming
I know what that around the time you
know I didn't stream much
so I know kfb must have been kind of
like
sad wasn't the best December for us but
you know oh thank you
and you get a really speedily you must
have ordered express delivery thank you
soon
thanks for being here today
yes
[Music]
and thank you for the pinky you may just
be a genius Andrew you absolutely killed
it this month between the Advent idea
how you got so creative in spite of the
illness was the puppets and collapse and
the genuine Joy of your whole talk with
Kanata big love for you thank you so
much
um
that whole talk man's really well too
yeah yeah even though I was ill
you think about it
I really respect myself man
of course maybe I should have also
rested more uncle that was definitely
not fully healthy but you know just for
one quick stream and then going back to
press to me that had really big priority
because I didn't want to do whole talk
from
Japan again I wouldn't know how stable
it would be so yeah
surprising went on so long being sick
long as I'm talking yeah
I had no way of stopping myself
hmm
thank you so much for as always well you
do too guys
yeah
takes great effort thank you yeah I lie
I didn't want to delay it anymore you
know because also kind of the same part
after all she also recorded the singing
with a Christmas outfit right so
if it was this was a uh the day before
Christmas if I had to delay it would be
after Christmas and then it would be
weird
yeah
it is so Iris a drama donation for the
pinky couldn't see the stream because of
work but I watched a lot later glad
you're backing out I'll have a belated
Christmas to you and gave hey
you
I hope by now you saw it I mean there
wasn't much else you could watch not
many kiwawa streams so I'm sure you
caught up by now thank you so much for
watching the Vlog even when you missed
something
yeah thank you sir and I appreciated all
the Vault watches out there thanks for
taking your time
soon foreign
[Music]
that's a lot of super chats but
finished them
always with you had
some super trucks
that's really fast right you didn't
expect me to be that fast huh
[Music]
always of you
oh I love you pretty song
pretty song all right I don't want to
ride yeah
Trevor Jean thank you very much my
channel and on the sponsored song cover
you're sending me a red thank you
comments on the sponsored song called
for Flappy New Year you have a ton of
fun in Japan with everyone okay hope if
you do a good group kind of okay you can
kind of like a roulette
what's that mean like roulette on who's
singing with who I rely on who what song
we would be saying and your ties on the
birthday Emoji blanket looks so pillowy
I had a bird brain idea kilometers neck
pill oh
but then
imagine there's like you know the neck
pillow
would would like the middle
be like a pen like panties though like
um
would you make me wear pants but then
it's not really recognizable that's me
how would you know it's me
I don't know about Dad
I don't know about that
sounds difficult to make you
recognizable if it's just legs
stockings
a neck pillow has merged always a good
idea though
it hasn't been done before I think
and oh no you know I like doing things
that haven't been done before
speaking of I wonder what Amy's birthday
merch is
I don't think I don't think I know
thank you travertine
come on we're supposed to pretend as
well thank you Happy New Year Happy New
Year to you too oh this was a bit early
though but I guess you you thought I
would read it later which you were right
with happy belated New Year moose
hopefully we will have a wonderful 2020
free I don't know what it has
uh in stock all right so how do I say in
in
but hopefully it will only be good
things for you and me and all of us in
store There It Is Well almost close
enough stores have things in stock so
thank you
and that's all thank you for the pinky
amazing camera boss great hammer named
crony oh and where's the Gilmore Girls
report thanks for delivering so many
bangers this year your voice is divine
thank you
[Music]
I appreciate it I I like singing this
one I know it's a sponsored thing and
it's a song that not many of you guys
know so it might not do as well as other
songs but
okay sir
a nice opportunity to approach a song
give it a chance give it a chance come
on
listen to it so that the sponsors will
be happy please
we want to make the sponsors happy
especially after you know what happens
please can your fee listen to the song
coming
in combination put it in a in a playlist
with pitani
yeah and then Loop it Direction
[Music]
Broken Man
I'm finally
I've been reborn let's go It's Been a
Good Year looking forward to my to the
next my Oshi will be supporting you
always
yum it happened too fast for me to be
honest and I'm very nervous about 2023
and I'm not sure if I can really
accomplish the things that I want to
this year
but there's still exciting things on the
horizon that I know about
and I think we will as kfp enjoy them I
think there will be
more 3D opportunities
that's for sure
but you know
kiwawa in-person real concert
uh that's not like at a convention or so
might be still very difficult I don't
know you may have heard
everybody's like been putting put on a
waiting list and I don't think I'm even
on the wait list
maybe I'm on the waitlist to be pulling
on the waitlist
um
um but I I I don't I don't know man
about that
but as long as I can still do some like
3D performing content I guess
that's somewhat okay
let's see it's kind of sad though
because
time is taking and
um
[Music]
I I like I wanna
do something big and wanna leave
something behind
[Music]
because I I never know like I can't know
what happens in the future and and like
how long I'll be here so
I want to make sure to use the time
smartly that I have here
to do the things I want to do you know
what I mean
oh it's stressing me out
um
wow
let's try our best shall we
fighter
GD thank you so much
I finished those as well
okay
yeah I wonder
Kelly after showering would just go
straight to bed
because I want to know
I wanna I wanna intrude too much
oh
how many did I make today versus how
many did I read someone does someone
know
text her
it's pretty early
yeah you probably won't sleep right away
right
I mean I mean
I already asked her like she doesn't
mind me staying over but
uh I did leave like I didn't prepare to
like stay over here like I don't have
the things that I would need to stay
over to be honest
I mean I'm not gonna like die but um
ideally I would go back
I read more than I got
yeah
why did that shock me so much
[Music]
I'm contemplating on what to do
are you going to sleep for real yeah
yeah I'm very tired but you can do
whatever you want
why
hmm
you can you know finish streaming and
leave or you can stay here
um
can I just ask why do you have so much
Nutella when you don't like Nutella
oh
she didn't know
because I was told you don't really like
Nutella oh it's fine I mean can I take
the Nutella with the sticks
yeah sure
love that
did you eat dinner yeah I did well
what I I just had food would give us the
food
together with you which is not oh oh Dad
that was your dinner yeah I don't like
to eat before I go to bed I guess that's
good for your body though I think I
always eat like so late and so giddy
gitty too sleepy time
okay I don't know I'll check later like
the trains okay well just if it looks
bad I'll just like sleep here yeah well
you can also wake me up too I just my
feet are very should I wake you up
before I go go yeah wake me up
so just okay just like knock Cali oh
okay I'll read a couple more Super chats
and then decide what I'll do okay enjoy
the rest
[Music]
I didn't ask I wasn't Nutella did you
not listen oh yeah
were gifts from Ina
she's she looked sleepy yo she's going
to bed at 10 P.M
wow good for her
that's good for her
juji
unbelievable
wow
yeah she was wearing pajamas
pajama can we
can't imagine being that responsible
that's usually my bedtime yeah
that's healthy well it depends on how
long you're sleeping still even if you
go sleep early
is this one a normal sleep schedule is I
wouldn't know
but
um
the schedule hasn't been that bad since
I came here
it's an invitation uh
no I think I'll go back
I feel uh you know like nervous about
staying here
let me check though
it go back with this little battery
which was three percent and like what
on Earth
let me just check train
[Music]
oh okay yeah we're still we're still
good
more or less
[Music]
um
I don't know
okay okay
don't worry about it safe
it's not about that but yeah I I I've
been having troubles charging my all my
like things
um
um epic seventh stream versus the newest
room since the news has more rights than
87 has
oh
oh okay yeah yeah yeah I'll get just off
the board yeah shall we
don't need to eat dinner too though I
mean wait at the same time but I feel
like that was my lunch
me and Kelly and at the same time but
for me that was more like my lunch
just need to get like some poof later
convenience store so
um
near as many super jets well of course
it did I'm very thankful thank you guys
for that
being so generous to me
okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
I couldn't thank you for free pinkies
with the exception of one very special
day 2022 was the most horrible and
depressing year for me and I realized I
need to take better care of myself
important that's my 2023 goal I consider
myself hyper loyal always here always
support and I'm very proud of my record
never missing a stream but I need to
take care better care of myself you're
the most beautiful and smart now in the
burp I know they say you're also reflex
fan base
so I need to reflect that I can't be
beautiful I'm not smart at all and I
have zero talents but I promise I was
trying my hardest to become a chicken
you can be proud of raising even if I
can't be here as much as before I
promise I'll always think about you and
still try to watch every day if possible
Happy New Year I love you all
well
um
I think that's important to for you to
take
time away
from
me I'll be honest so I wish you luck
with that
and
uh
um
[Music]
self-care is important yeah
you speak very negatively about yourself
but I think you can
um
I don't think you need to be so negative
about yourself
what I think is important is to not make
your life
uh what's the word reliant on me
yeah
and
open your hearts and eyes to more things
in the world
it's not all about me
yep
so
that's very important I think if you are
able to do that then your life will
approve improve a lot
don't give up
so easily on life
you know
there's
so much more to it than what you're
currently seeing
or Larry's mistake thank you and Harry
JC Duncan Alex GT for free Dr Shin Derek
Sito Dakshin Roto
little dungeon
foreign
Chad
[Music]
wordless Super Chat wait it says
wordless Super Chat it says wordless
super chat now it's not just empty
but that was added by Holland Liza right
they did not actually write
wordless Super Jet right
make it fairly clear
what's up why'd you have nothing to say
to me and you might want to talk to me
yeah because it's in blue actually it's
not a normal black font
yeah
brackets wordless Super Chat
make it extra clear
they're Chad
contact Mama
[Music]
kiss for you a wordless kiss then
Thai tea thanks for the pinky and all
the love you give me I hope that you
slid into 2023 nicely and that so far
it's going well
yeah I wish you all the best thanks for
still being here tattoo you're the best
Ultra new videos I don't know why but
this microphone reminds me of that view
you from two years ago you've grown so
much yeah
[Music]
does it really sound like it though I
don't think so it's just the the fact
that it's bad
quality more or less even though it
shouldn't be that bad
maybe I just set it up wrong but I feel
like a Yeti mic
should be someone decent but I don't
know
Maybe not maybe I expected too much from
it
it's not that bad it's not peeking
definitely better than the old mic oh
[\h__\h] I wouldn't say scuffed Mike's here
maybe it's the wrong way around yeah
I mean wrong wrong there's no way to
make it the wrong way around
this almost sounds like your usual setup
to be honest yeah yeah
um I'm at Cali's place and she has kind
of the same setup as me in terms of
microphone and mixer thingy
she has the sm7b go Explorer setup that
I use but I think hers is
um maybe it has some differences in in
terms of like
settings on
other things I don't know how to
describe it
you know ever since I came to Japan I've
been making doing my makeup like in the
past eight days or so I've done my
makeup more times
then I've done it
in all of 2022 I feel like
so
I feel like my my skin is not being very
thankful to me it's like what the [\h__\h]
are you doing to me what are you
Plastering on top of your skins like
[\h__\h] you
yeah
not very happy
I'm gonna do some skincare
actually
um skincare
never really did much for me
I had to take medicine
for my skin to improve
AKA hormones I guess
and I kind of stopped taking them
because I ran out and I didn't want to
go to the doctor to get new ones
this is annoying and they're quite
expensive
I stopped taking them like a couple
months ago and I I didn't notice that
much difference actually happily but now
that I'm putting on makeup again I've
been noticing differences again it's
pretty bad
I mean it's not that bad
not as bad as when I was going to school
hmm
it's still it's still
decent
no I was annoying me yeah I got one on
my on my chin
it's like I'm a teenager what the [\h__\h]
it hurts kind of hurts
it's like like inside
oh man it's too real it's too real
[\h__\h]
it's annoying as [\h__\h] I'm an adult
high five
just a sign of Youth when you think
about no
I'm not gonna open it with a needle
good things mascara thing I I love masks
for that
I had to um
not natural substance cosmetic
chocolate
I'm barely sweet and weightless sweets
than when I was younger compared to that
no anyway
[Music]
um thank you entrepreneur
I'm glad you think so
I'll come here and thunderstruck's life
as for sleep as danger soon
[Music]
I have a message for you I'm going to be
ready to be eaten by the customers this
game is you can plan play with four
player or three or two by yourself I
hear Reaper love these games
this one Epic seven well you mean the
one that you wrote In
in Brackets
River City girls
probably mean River City why did you
bring River City bring up Rose City
girls never played that before
yeah I think she likes it oh God that
map
oh I don't I don't I don't know about
playing that I don't know I'm not really
interested
at the moment
great game hmm can we play that
yesterday really
tonight Wednesday I'm I'm on her PC
tonight she couldn't have played it
tonight
or did she secretly stream from
somewhere else
did you mean Inna by the way no and I'm
really sad about it
there was some kind of plan and then it
didn't work out I guess
[Music]
oh son
no I did
um get
someone else to give her something
from me though
the mono wafers
or have free to turn nonetheless through
someone else
I was oh so sad
we were not able to meet up
wait can I still up wait a minute it's
10 P.M
and even if I was in Austria it would be
super early it would be
um 2PM I think
anyway thank you so much for the pinky
infection
epic seven female
is there another one
a quick one
with Super Chat reading super chats
oh wait a second
reading super chats has a lot
today no the last Geo guess the stream
Maybe
what's the same thumbnails I'm not gonna
show it I guess
yeah okay
oh it continues with all
with a red subject and a pinky oh no way
Reaper you're killing me I know Reaper's
job my Super Chat is useless
come on Al you got this you're the best
employee think other game you know what
boss like oh you're trying to get me to
like a game again I got one the Outlast
trials
hell yeah you know what I think I'm not
a good employee with Outlast trials is
not it's not never Outlast game
oh [\h__\h] no
[\h__\h] off
this is for all kfp thank you last time
I sent a silver chat twice
it is the [\h__\h] no
I did see kfp trying to let me know but
my English and typing skill sucks my
typing is slow if you feel hurt then
respond I'm sorry oh no I don't think
anyone minded so thank you Cave Spring
thank you for bringing the Super Chat
for me boss no problem of them you're
trying to regimenting games I'm sorry
that I'm turning you down but Outlast is
a big no
the ah the other one you still had
higher chances but this one
can't possibly think I would want to
play that
come on come on you're just [\h__\h] with
me now trying to troll me
you know I don't want to play that
good luck next time find a better game
to recommend to me that's good thanks
for the pinky
episode 12 I feel like I skipped some of
your reviews for now silky and Jackson
have a cute Dynamic but so much pain in
this episode Lane trying to get goofy
boy to dog
which one which one
ooh Jackson's cousin insulting Laurel ah
that episode insulting Lauren like all
night oof and we've gone out and
couldn't wait for the experience to end
probably
yeah that one Jackson's cousin
[Music]
ah that was a tough one to watch
so funny though poor little lime then
she
held up through the whole [\h__\h] so well
good good good good lady she is
hmm
what a douchebag man and he's not even
like the Tristan type of douchebag
he's just an oblivious
idiot douchebag who's salty
as hell and cynical and what an idiot
what an idiot but funny to watch not
nice to meet in person but funny to
watch in a TV show
for the pinky most importantly thank you
so much for being the sparta retail my
passion and dreams I got to meet so many
people cool people in this community
thanks to you also question is a Kpop
fan give me who is your lesser of him
and new jeans or she buys them
[Music]
and
say one hundred percent
million percent
she's
so cute she's saying so well
so pretty she dances so well she's hot
she has that slay Aura oh my God
and uh new jeans I'm not sure I don't
know actually I don't think I haven't
what's your bias they're all grain
I couldn't choose
now
you know but I love their songs like in
the beginning of first I was like
answer me but then I love them so much
now
and their visuals are like whoo Envy is
also really good the girls are so cute
it kind of freaks me out a little bit
they're so young it's like how can they
be so young
one of them is like 14 but they look
kind of older and
feels kind of weird to me
I don't know you're too young
they're like 14 15 16.
I think I think they're like two 16 year
olds maybe they're 17 by now no probably
still 16.
[Music]
the one that's 14 and she looks the
oldest to me though
turns out she's 14.
and they're babies and it's kind of
funny to me because in in in in in J-pop
the young girls look young
but in K-pop they made them look older
um fruit of fashion and makeup and just
it looks so stylish
and in J-pop they will look like like
kind of lame and yeah like really like
their young as hell
it's a different world
yeah yeah they probably won't have much
of a normal childhood but
I think
um a couple of them were like
training for this
and and
they've been in in the entertainment
business since they were yeah young
they're still young though
so
that's what they do that's what they do
tag team thank you for the pinky once
again had to always representing well
thank you you must be having an easier
time watching my streams now probably
because uh time zone
um maybe you're here right now
Maybe
faction thank you for the pinky sending
the Super Chat from the future yeah no
matter what you must not
what what
what what what what
[\h__\h] what happened did they did I take
him
is he gone
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] I will never know now I will
probably meet the same destiny
as you refaction
has anyone heard from reflection I mean
we guys are in the in the past
so I guess we haven't whatever you heard
is the past and
the fashion is in the future
unless someone else is from the future
we will never know
we lost them
thanks for the pinky minor 49ers
thanks for the pinky we got to hear
Mama's voice so the stream is still a
win thanks for trying so hard we
understand oh yeah this was yesterday
uh yeah I'm so sorry yesterday didn't
work out but here we are today worked
out and it was better audio than you
would have gotten in my hotel room
and I mean we still got the internet to
die two times interestingly but
generally
it was much better thank God I'm really
relieved at least one normal stream
squeezed in
got to play Geo guesser
is
[Music]
my throat is feeling very dry now anyway
so
oh
um
might be time for me to go
I think about what to do
still early enough for me to go back
thank you
yay
you have to enjoy the vlading a little
bit oh yeah yeah fun
hey everybody guys for coming I hope you
enjoyed today's stream
I have my phone 15 is
[\h__\h] at charging
poke
will this be the reason why I can't go
back
um 15 percent
uh I didn't bring a fast charger no
yeah [\h__\h]
no I haven't been using it no I haven't
it's just on the side with screen black
[Music]
and
I prefer just sleeping in the hotel
though because then I can sleep as long
as I want
versus here
when Cali wakes up equals when I wake up
you know
so I think I'll go back anyway
I'll be fine
I just don't like like being forced to
wake up because not even even if she
tries to be super quiet and not intrude
and all that it's her place like I don't
expect her to be quiet but
um I can't I wake up so so easily yeah
oh yeah you guys should make sure to
catch Emma's birthday stream it's in
like 12 hours reservation is up
I heard she prepared a really cool
stream for you guys
I should be awake to watch it too
um
I'll be putting the link of where I'll
be on my Twitter tomorrow so keep an eye
out for that and yeah
can I make a PowerPoint without having
PowerPoint
I have to make my PowerPoint
grading a stream
I don't know how it works
[Music]
Google Slides ah
can you export it as a PowerPoint
foreign
[Music]
okay cool all right all right then thank
you guys so much for this nice stream I
had fun making this map was fun too guys
take a screenshot and send it to me on
Twitter so that I can steal it and
upload it on live Twitter
here
or maybe with me
[Music]
got it
okay
I mean at least give credit what
oh no
no
it's my map
Callie gets some of my spit in her trash
foreign
I hope she'll appreciate it
kind of says I was born in Maryland live
in Florida and grew up in Colorado whoa
anything wrong with it what what you
don't feel like that's accurate
you've been wrong your whole life
I can't believe I live on the West Coast
it's nice over there I heard
yeah it's just kind of hard to catch my
streams in PST
I better move back to the east coast for
you
otherwise you'll have a hard time
catching my streams
go live in Arkansas Nebraska above it's
the same state
[Music]
so and the German Museum good night guys
wish me luck I'm getting home
bye bye bye bye love you guys
[Music]
thank you