[Music]
oh
a
[Music]
la o
la la
[Music]
n
la
[Music]
K
yippee oh my God I'm finally back kind
of not really not properly yet not
properly cuz I'm not in Austria yet but
I am back in
Japan yay hello hello
[Music]
half half welcome back half
Kiara yeah sorry it's early I um it's 7
a.m. or not even 7 a.m. I woke up at
4:00 a.m. but don't worry I slept I
don't know pretty early I think I slept
7 hours minimum yeah yeah no yeah
probably around 7
hours should should be should probably M
so I hope I'll make it for the day I
have like uh appointments and dance
lessons uh that I will have to leave for
which is why this stream is extra early
otherwise I would have done it a little
bit
later
[Music]
um like I don't know if I maybe to me
jetl is honestly just a
myth also jetl the game released a new
season uh a new Europe season I'm so
excited to watch
it but jetl to me is kind of a myth myth
match man two things that I love jet leg
and
myth um because like I feel like I don't
I don't even want to call it jet leg
because I don't know it's just
[Music]
that is that is it I don't know is it
really jat lag
when you just I mean I could have stayed
up
longer but I just like I don't know I
was just tired um but I don't think
that's necessarily jat lag that's just
because I didn't sleep enough in the
plane if I slept enough in the plane I
would have been maybe better but I don't
know like I don't know I I don't think
jet like exist I don't know I think jet
like is just a stupid excuse for
[\h__\h] sorry
what
um do you hear the bgm
[Laughter]
guys oh it's a skill issue
yeah oh it's okay I can I can swear um
the stream hasn't even officially
started yet so I can swear because
everybody nobody's here yet right
everybody will just join at 7:00 a.m. my
time
M circadian rhythm
HS what you're living in the circus or
you feeling the circus Rhythm or you
mean catas
what I'm feeling the circus
Rhythm yeah yeah I started early
welcome yeah jet leg is a scly shoe did
you fly first class of course not I I'm
personally hoping that maybe
for the next Ian
concert maybe cuz their budget seems to
be rising from uh last year to this year
uh perhaps next year they have budget to
fly Us in with business that would be
nice I don't need First Class A lot of
airlines don't even have first class
really but business would be nice
because honestly it was so painful and
my and my um seat was broken actually
yeah so I flew from Japan to New York if
I was in Europe at the time I could have
flown from Europe to New York and the
flight would have been actually quite a
bit shorter
man ah but you know timing timing
timing yeah yeah yeah
yeah my flight man so you know well well
we did fly premium we're getting
straight into it I guess we did fly
premium uh we you know we were on
different flights but I was with a few
girls I'm not going to say who I guess
but um I was on the same flight as a few
of them and
uh we all have premium economy I know
there's some girls like Ena I think who
like upgraded themselves to business but
I thought well I don't know I'm not
gonna do that like that's I'm not even I
wouldn't even get the miles from it
because I own like that this is not my
miles uh
territory like if it was an airline that
was part of the miles what was it miles
and mo where I'm getting miles from
which is usually like European
airlines then I could like consider it
because then if I upgrade it to business
then it's going to be uh you know added
to my miles count
[Music]
M yeah I'm sure her flight was super
expensive I think she kind of told me
and I was like no [\h__\h] no that's not
worth it I'm going to suffer for this
[\h__\h] flight and the good thing is
that the hotel all the beds I told you
guys that was like my best sleep in my
whole life and it was so comfortable and
I asked them I asked them and they're
going to hopefully send it I feel like
they forgot but they said they'll send
me an email um with the Deets about the
mattress and the pillows oh the pillows
oh my God so comfortable M yeah it's for
work like there's so many people like
who travel for work who get business
from their companies and I feel like
they generally earn you know less uh but
they still get business so what the
hell yeah it would be cool if next time
maybe we can get business because it was
really um rough uh pain because so my
seat was broken I told you
right so I was like in the front row of
the premium economy cabin so uh that
means that like apparent I didn't even
realize this until I flew back uh and
was in a uh road that was further behind
but so the footrest
normally is attached kind of to the the
chair in front of you the seat in front
of you so it's not the foot the footrest
isn't normally attached to the chair you
sitting on do you know what I mean so
it's kind of still a pretty flimsy
footrest well this depends on the
airline but in this case it was um a
pretty flimsy footrest that is attached
to the front so it's not like your seat
has like a like how to say like a
footrest pillow that you can lift no
it's just like there's air between if
even if you put your legs on the
footrest there will be air between your
feet and your knees do you know what I
mean does that make sense M I didn't
even realize that until later because on
the first flight I flew in the front row
so there was no seat in front of me does
the footrest was connected to the chair
it was part of the chair which would
have been cool more comfortable because
you can actually feel like your legs are
resting on
something but mine was broken the seat
next to me was taken by a stranger
uh and the stranger's footrest was
working mine was not working and I tried
everything uh to
like move it um didn't work and then I
called the cabin attendant and I'm sure
that they are 100% aware that their
airplanes footrests are often broken
because apparently um on the opposite
side of the other window seat I think
theirs was also
broken um and they're like oh they like
checked it for a moment they were like
nah I'm sorry it's not just not working
they didn't even they didn't even say
sorry they're not sorry they're not
sorry and then I looked up online if
like they like if the seat that you're
paying for has some things that don't
function if you are um if you get any
refunds and they said no you are not
entitled to any refunds so imagine okay
this is still a small thing even though
for me it was big because my legs are I
don't know what it is but
like my legs will have some weird ass
pain that I don't ever experience
outside of
airplanes uh if I don't get to lift them
a little
bit um I'm sure that a lot of airlines
if you complain enough they will give
you miles or something but I don't even
have a miles thing with them so I was
like mm but imagine you pay like 7,000
$8,000 $9,000 or whatever for business
class seat and then something doesn't
work there I've seen cases like that in
the feedback when I was Googling it uh
and then and then imagine it doesn't
work they don't owe you
anything
what say it's a medical necess well the
thing is though that it was fully booked
so they couldn't have moved me to any
other seat they they did tell me to like
oh well maybe you can ask uh someone
else to switch seats with you yo nobody
will want to switch seats to a a not
working seat also it seems like almost
everybody else on the plane was like uh
on the uh e premium economy cabin was
like traveling in couples so who the
[\h__\h] would want that yeah I think thank
you yeah I think it is probably
something yeah with my veins or whatever
I don't know take blood finess before
the plane takes off interesting maybe
I'll try that I I tried like wearing
those pressure socks before um and I
think they improved it a little bit but
not
really not really
[Music]
so I had to Rite something sorry sorry
sorry yeah it wasn't going to be a TI
what
what there's something like pressure
socks for half the body I don't need
half the body it's really just like
my around my knees a little bit up
upwards to the thigh and downwards
uh like down down and above and below
the
knee uh so yeah the footrest helps a
little bit but it's still like [\h__\h]
uncomfortable like my legs get cramps
and [\h__\h] um and I feel this like like
this pain that goes in the line upwards
and downwards my legs it just sucks it
just sucks I [\h__\h] hate it and I I
flew a few times like I've had the
pleasure to fly business a few times now
in the past year
uh and
now now that I know that I could fly
comfortably it's just so much more
[Music]
painful wait let me do one thing really
quickly
uh I think it's this
okay uh okay uh where was I sorry I'm ah
my brain so uh we'll talk about my whole
trip to New York including sight singing
and three concerts I well okay two but
like three days of concerts AKA breaking
dimensions and the world tour's first
ever stop which was in anime New York
City NYC is so stinky I I had so many of
you guys like warning me about like how
New York is going to be so bad and
everything it was honestly delightful
the only stinkiness that I have
perceived as a very sensitive uh
individual to these kind of things as I
am very straight edged is a lot of
[\h__\h] weed smell and I did see uh on
Time Square rocking around I did see one
uh person overdosing on heroin so um
that's maybe like you know that was a
little bit shocking but I was kind of
proud how I immediately recognized that
that person wasn't drunk but very much
uh overdosing on [\h__\h] so everybody don't
take drugs be straight edged like
me that was pretty typical I could tell
um yeah that's
concerning but besides that like a lots
of weed I'm sure it's like legal is it
legal in New York I'm sure it's legal
there but uh uh I I really hate the
smell so much I hate it I don't remember
if it was legal in Austria I think like
uh like medical like what do you call it
like if you use it like as meds and it's
legal I don't know if it's legal besides
that is it is it
legal it's legal in New York uh okay see
but I hate it I hate it so much so
disgusting um but anyway sorry to anyone
in the chat who likes to use weed uh
have fun I'm so sensitive to
it oh yeah that's the only thing that
bothered me besides that I saw no
rats uh except something similar that
was way cuter you'll be hearing about
[Music]
that um uh I so no rats and I saw I
don't know I didn't see anything
like I even used I even you'll hear
about that too but I even used the
underground Transportation method and it
was clean and not concerning even though
am warned me that I shouldn't step too
closely to the yellow line because
sometimes people push others over just
for fun into the tracks and then you
might die um that there's been incidents
like that uh apparently in the news
so yeah um so don't step too
close but yeah I went to the subway
anyway okay okay I'm I'm going too too
random here and there we should start um
from the very beginning a very nice
place to start so I had a few days in uh
New York and
um I I didn't have like an insane amount
of sightseeing time
uh but I knew I knew that I wouldn't so
I was actually the only only one more or
less
uh besides besides am only me and Amy
kind of extended our stays a little bit
um yeah so that was
fun me me and I'mma had quite a bit of
extra time
together which I I I was so happy
about so yeah there will be a lot of a I
think in what I'm telling
you but yeah so I was there
for here t uh World Tour this this is so
amazing I can't believe it this was a
World Tour first stop in uh New York
City anime NYC and I always like do you
see there's who is this which one of you
guys is this this one in the middle who
is this someone's wearing my happy who
is that please raise your
hand raise your hand now raise it who is
this is
that I feel like I feel like I might
know but kind of difficult this
one h no that's not Tre TR no Trevor
would would not wear a hat like
[Music]
that not you not you not you God damn it
well let me know oh oh on the left on
the left who's that who's that is that
two Kiwa happies or just one I'm not
sure that's hard to tell it might be two
it might be just one I think it might be
one or are these people who's who's this
one on the
[Music]
left let's see who else can I I see
narissa happy n happy GA happy these
happies are so nice like like one or two
years ago not two years ago it feels
like nobody were happy outside of Japan
one year ago it like started coming and
this year is like
wow so many happies the culture is
flooding over
[Music]
yeah cuz you guys have been like doing
fan happies and now I have an official
one so I hope next year I'll be seeing
the official ones the the fan happy is
so nice I love it so much you can see
how why is it standing out so much isn't
this one glowing it almost looks
photoshopped
in this one in the middle like it stands
out to me it's like she's staring at me
why is she looking at me
no this is not
photoshopped no it's
not I'm just like standing out it's not
even Orange it's not even that orange
like the Happy is not that orange people
always say that the orange stands out
but there not not that much of the
orange yeah perfectly positioned it's
not even in the middle of the picture
it's kind of like off off center but it
works thank you guys for the super chats
by the
way ah
she's like
enlightened she's so enlightened I can't
stop looking at
[Music]
her well well well well so this one okay
I got to say
like let's see what can I say this was
already so amazing like oh my God I was
already
so
adrenalin yeah who needs drugs when you
can get adrenaline through this kind of
stuff
man wah W God so excited this was so
fire right this people were I'm so happy
people were so hyped through this
concert already that people were already
saying like how can they top this with
breaking
Dimensions man but we were only we're
only a few only a couple of girls
here yeah so we had a really special
performance of do you my song and that
was with four girls yes yes yes B and me
and I will say like that was kind of
rough for
me I I remember like in dance lessons I
had to relearn do you haven't like
danced in a while at that point uh so it
had to come back to me and and so
basically like in that dance l i
remember babe was like learning it from
scratch and I I was like relearning it
but Bae is so good like she immediately
picked it up and and ah man I will say
that I felt like immediately under
insanely Under Pressure because it's my
own song and then people would
expect me to do a good good job at my
own song and oh man I I I I had some
breakdowns
man um but I tried my best and um
I'm so happy that my song was chosen uh
the set list for the world tour concerts
will all be different you
know so uh I mean there might be some
songs here and there like so to say
repeating but generally this set this
will all be different yeah so I don't
think you will see four person do you
again I don't think I need to like check
but
you want Blu-rays huh I know like yeah
people really thought it was hype I love
it I'm so happy I'm like even if you are
not a kfp it seems like do you you know
people know do you so it was like um
really easy for people to vibe to it um
people were screaming do you do you do
you do you say you do feel the same and
that just made me so proud and so happy
m
yeah I was really proud to have like
created a song that can capture people
like that and get them so hyped and
excited I'm so proud and I did sleep
talking
right right yeah yeah yeah yeah I did I
just I did sleeptalking for my solo I
don't want to get things confused
because uh for breaking Dimensions I did
pineapple so sleep talking was actually
a suggest suggestion from the staff like
hey K don't you want to do sleep talking
I'm like H okay because they they said
they want a song here in the set list
that like gets people hyped and I'm like
it sleep talking I
mean it's not a completely slow song but
it's also not like it doesn't go like as
crazy hard as like chimo or
so um but okay I was like okay if you
want sleep dogging I'll do sleep dogging
that's fine with me I mean sleep talking
I personally love the song
so
[Music]
yeah I think I I don't know if it really
got everybody so hyped as they wanted it
but I I think it did uh
[Music]
well yeah and then we had another chance
to show off me and kobo's uh eating hero
hero yeah
um good that we had that song in our
repertoire I guess because uh Kobo is
part of the world tour so uh a good
reason to bring out
that collaboration song of us again and
yeah I think it's really great it has
like these calls that repeat again and
again so I think they're really easy to
follow the su
su I okay yeah uh relatively easy even
though it's Japanese but
then I I thought I thought you guys
would be confused but not as confused I
thought you guys would be able to
somewhat do what I'm trying to do I
changed the call that's like in the
second half of the song there's like um
kobal goes first she goes like you know
this's is like break in instumental
break and everything and then KOB goes
like but she changed it she changed it
because we both changed it we wanted to
change it we thought how about we change
to something English at
least uh well even though she had some
japanes words in there so she was like
singing like Kat is not
Ki it's the same Rhythm and it's the
same like Melody so to say and uh
intonations but
um people were not able to pick it up at
all it seems did anybody like say it
successfully and then but then you would
think because Kobo goes first and then
you realize oh she's saying something
else that now is my turn K's turn you
guys would surely be ready for it
because you you may have failed at the
kobble
one but you wouldn't fail on mine
right what did I say um
K can make fried chicken out of me is
that so difficult is that so
difficult K can make fried chicken out
of me instead
[Music]
of kada can make fried chicken out of me
easy should be easy no okay I I get it
the sentence was a little bit
um complicated I tried to say it as
clearly as possible so that you guys
would pick it up as clearly as possible
was it
quiet the crowd was too loud really but
in that moment didn't you guys all go
kind of silent because you were like
what
what what did Kobo just
say I caught it
really I'm conf I'm happy you're
confident our bird brains but sorry well
now you know so if if you ever cuz this
is like in like the second half of the
song so you should be ready if we ever
perform the song again you know what's
coming now probably possibly although
I'm not sure because this really
intimidated me now I'm not sure if we
want to like try this
again if we try it again it might be a
different phrase or we go back to the
original I don't
[Music]
know I think one of the problem is also
maybe that the back vocals were still
[Music]
saying
maybe I don't
know I'm
icy but just yeah make sure guys now you
know now you know besides that it was
hype and people were following the calls
I think and uh chanting
along so yeah the first first concent we
did uh besides me singing sleep talking
and having two unit songs we also had of
course like full uh group songs um so
generally it will follow that kind of
pattern uh I think I think everybody
always gets one solo I think and there
will always be units and
stuff but just so you know we'll be
mixing it up yeah I really like the
setup too like all except for like you
know depending on on um the venue the
sizes of the area where we can dance
will be difficult and so when we were
practicing for this
one we were uh first we were practicing
in like a wide formation and then at
rehearsal pretty suddenly we were told
oh actually you only have this tiny
space here uh as you can see and I'm
like what [\h__\h] and then we went through
it a little bit and uh like I was
bumping a little bit my arms like
against the
others yeah it was uh difficult to
squeeze in in such a tiny space um I
think you noticed maybe if you were
there that especially with the group
songs um even with doyu though with four
people but also with the group songs
that we were really close to each other
but then because we literally can't
stand in one line I think there's like
always people standing in the back and
then people standing in the
front and yeah just difficult because
the motion capture area was very small
so yeah had to
adjust had to adjust like pretty
spontaneously bit difficult but still
had a lot of
fun I like the setup I liked it um I
think like the problem in this uh anime
NYC venue is that it's isn't there like
these pillars right these big pillars so
you can't really stand behind the pillar
people have to like keep all that space
empty more or less so there's some
wasted space but you see here on the
picture that's not all there's like a
little bit of like walking space uh here
at the bottom um but it the the crowd
continues behind that so it was pretty
packed I think right like quite quite a
big amount of people in there uh even
though it's kind of awkward with the
pillars and yeah everybody I guess
stands on the same level
so probably was hard to
see like the full body version in the
middle if you're not in a good seat like
but you know that's just an issue with
each of the convention venues whether or
not it will be better in the others I'm
not sure cuz I didn't really see the
others uh yeah I don't know how it will
be try to go in the middle guys try to
go in the middle in the front
ideally no there's chairs there's chairs
but people generally stand up so I can't
blame them because it's hype but when
people stand up you'll see even
less I was pretty fine in the back but I
could see a ride that's good to hear the
side screens just need some more
mid-range shots they were kind of zoomed
in most of the time oh okay I'll give
that feedback yeah I do like this like
contrast here very much I think it's
beautiful that that close-up shot of me
is just actually so coincidentally
beautiful I like the contrast but I
understand that if you stand on the very
left it might be difficult to see the
middle uh not we're not on the screen no
I'm really there the middle it's just
difficult to see the middle right so um
um I I I might share that feedback then
yeah yeah cuz I think I did see people
like like watching straight in to the
side screens because they couldn't see
the middle that
well the loud speakers had a bit too
much compression so it messed up the
audio quality interesting
[Music]
okay let me cl Cy paste I'm going to
bring your um
feedback
up
hello I got some more
feedback from people at the
[Music]
venue and so the other one uh was that
the
screens that the screen
on the
side should have showed a bit more
uh you know my is
typing show a bit uh should have showed
a bit more mid-range shots it was
usually
[Music]
only head shot so for people who can't
see the middle well m they can mostly
just see super close
up is watching my stream she want
B she's
watching
more hi Ana just right before I started
the stream I watched a video on Twitter
where a huge octopus is like trying to
to eat or swallow or
attack or hug a shark and then for a
while it looked like the shark was
getting captured and not being set
free but it eventually was able
to set itself free and swam away so what
the hell was that you saw that too why
do we always see the same things
man and do you think the do you think
octopus was trying to eat it and then
realized [\h__\h] I just can't get a bite
into the shark and then let it go
certainly it wasn't a t hug I don't
think octop [\h__\h] try to hug
sharks uh naturally it doesn't seem like
really natural
[Laughter]
behavior right anyway I think uh I I
don't I have limited time so I don't
know if should I it's hard to remember
at this point because like feels like
like these memories were overwritten by
breaking Dimensions memories but yeah I
think that's like mostly it was [\h__\h]
hype man was [\h__\h]
hype people people were like woohoo and
I said n my see what is up today yeah
yeah yeah yeah took you a moment too
though guys took you a
moment in the middle of the song you
know I like to um it's it's a bit
difficult with all my recent song songs
I feel like um to implement something
like that cuz like pineapple sleep
talking and also my upcoming song which
I'm working on right now they all so
busy they have so many overlapping
vocals and all that it feels like really
difficult to um fit in something like
like a
[Music]
crowd thing where I say something to you
guys yeah
uh what do you mean you wish it was Fire
and Ice we did Fire and Ice on day two
of breaking Dimensions but obviously not
here cuz cie is not in that
concert although I me we could have
maybe done it as a cover song where
somebody else would do C's part but I
don't know it feels wrong to
me
spoiler yeah miffin I think I said that
already last time like hey maybe for
next song can we like make add a bit
more instrumental like breathing space
breathing not just instrumental but just
like a moment where I can catch a breath
less overlapping vocals maybe but they
did it again for for the next one I I'll
say it for real like we need a bit more
like less overlapping vocal more in
breathing space
like this is so hard to like sing
live but
yeah nope no braving for you mm-m nuh-uh
you're not allowed to breathe
W well well well uh okay so um instead
of going to Breaking Dimensions I will
now do a little bit of side sing Talk do
you guys want to see side yes you want
yeah yeah yeah trust me you
want how about we talk about so there
there on on one of the days we did s
sing with
um can't
we yeah
[Music]
and yes but that was the group
right I missing someone I don't think
I'm missing
someone yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
a group that's a
group yeah interesting
combination I was I was surprised that
I'm would join our group I think think
she just likes me too
much I wasn't sure if she liked me but
she spent so much time with me this time
so I felt like you
[Music]
know yeah I met I met K
mhm yeah so hm where do I start I have
pictures and I actually have videos too
videos
n where's my
[Music]
oh where's my uh
here
T and with this group we went to first
of all we went to the this beautiful
Park that I think is quite
famous in New York there's this big
Central Park beak is so big I really
wanted to walk through it like a lot of
it we spent quite a bit of time here
um yeah it's really beautiful like this
was this was a beautiful view there's
this huge
Lake I know it surely has a name but
it's huge there's a bunch of lakes uh in
Central
Park yeah you need a lot of time to see
the whole thing right but we saw quite a
bit of it I would say and and and Amed
was like helping like Amed was legit our
tour guide
she was leading us through the whole
thing and she showed us uh like things
that otherwise we probably would have
not
[Music]
found and she did tell me this is okay
to say she did um grow up in some parts
of New York so that's how she was so
knowledgeable she told me actually not
on this day but she told me so many
crazy
stories about New York uh that like also
like like connections like not this
necessarily something that she experienc
but maybe family members experien and I
the whole time she's telling these
stories I'm like what the
[\h__\h] so typical amen it's so crazy her
her stories are so crazy and that was
like honestly the better than any tour
guide I could have
hired but yeah she led us pretty
confidently through um Central par Mark
and let's
see oh great no that's maybe a bit too
early no no no that's do you even know
what that was just
now a man I have I have so many tangents
let me
think I don't know I don't know I I have
I have like tangents all over the place
let's see okay so we walked through the
park for a while and there's like a lot
of of like wide big spaces and there's
people like picnicking and hanging out
and anywhere you look there's squirrels
there's freaking squirrels everywhere so
do you want to see a squirrel video
because we saw squirrels everywhere but
at some point we stopped in front of
like a fence because we saw a cute squir
wheel on a tree and then um we
were I was like oh my God so cute and
then Amy picked up a not
and was like seducing the squirrel to
come over I didn't yeah I was making
that joke actually nobody really
understood I think except maybe Cy but I
was making a joke that like I should
kick a squirrel like in Bower's
gate roll perception check and roll roll
a really bad
Dice and then kick the squirrel and then
I I just die maybe the squirrel kicks me
back or something I don't know I had to
think of that time in balers game
that was a great scene but yeah um here
and then um
enjoy um I think this should play wait
ah let me change that to
Monitor and output okay here I cut
something
together yeah I'll make it full screen
for you even though it looks not so nice
if it's full screen but okay
oh my God
so he's currently being seduced by our
local
detective oh
my oh my God I'm going to die me she
speaks to
animals checked it he didn't like it I
don't need your acorns your acorns got
hum on oh my oh he's eating something
look W he's destroying that destroying
that
Acorn oh is that good Wu is that good W
you like those
nuts I think it likes those nuts yeah Fu
was giggling her gigg giggle is so cute
um there's actually a moment where she
said but I cut it out because I I I I
wasn't sure like um I did confirm with
formac about the video but at this point
I wasn't sure yet if I would get their
confirmation in time so I just cut it
out but she was like
I I think maybe it has rabies and then
because of that I said because in that
moment the squirrel ran away like turned
around and ran away I thought like oh it
was insulted by you assuming it has
rabies but then it came back and it
wasn't because of that it was because of
a little cart was uh driving
by but it came literally I was obviously
trying so hard to not show anybody's
like hands or so but it came so close
like literally so close to am's hand it
it was going for Amy it was so going for
Amy it really liked Amy Amy can talk to
animals that was not the only time that
Amy talked to animals for
us
yeah
yeah it's cute everybody was
like happy about the
squirels so that was a squirel
video uh oh
so after seeing a lot of squirrels am
was leading us to and I feel like it
seems like a lot of people don't even
know this exists in Central
Park there's a turtle
pond there's a freaking turtle pond
guys this is a
turtle here let me close up do you see
it has a [\h__\h] carrot in its
mouth so there were there was a smaller
Pond actually for a pond it was pretty
big it feels like a small Lake but there
were so many turtles there like millions
of turtles I did not think there would
be so many turtles I thought maybe one
or two and you couldn't get too close to
them but no there were a million Turtles
and people were like like standing at
the shore of it more or less wasn't like
a Sandy Shore it was a stone Shore
thingy um people were standing there
sitting there watching the turtles and
the turtles were like literally sunbath
right there and you could touch them if
you wanted to people were feeding the
[\h__\h] out of them but don't worry they
were like just feeding like fruit
because there was a fruit stand right
next to
it yeah and we were watching them for a
while it was like so relaxing too and
then they the turtles were actually
sharing the whole Pond lake with Geese
they were a [\h__\h] ton of geese but the
turtles and the geese stayed in their
own groups and sometimes the geese would
like it would seem like they would come
over to us where the turtles were but
they St they stayed relatively far away
most of the time h
[Music]
eh we didn't feed them though we just
watched them although no sometimes we
Chuck like something some small things
that she found on the ground like small
pieces of a carrot or so like remains
would try to give it to the turtle and
they would be quite interested yeah
that's why they come so close because
they know that they're going to get food
from the tourists yeah they were giving
out so much
food and the turtles were eating so much
and they all looked like the same type
of turtle but they were all like really
cute and the more I looked at them like
I don't think I've ever seen turtles so
close up in so many of them um but like
they look like dinosaurs and crocodiles
to me yeah you watching them for a while
yeah they have orange lines in their
face
mhm do they stack the turtles no but I I
think we saw there was some Turtle
action going on like them like kind of
kind of fighting over fruit sometimes m
M yeah but no real like stacking
action uh yeah see like this just this
just kind of shows you like how many
freaking Turtles this is just a small
tiny part they're like you can get 10 P
10 turtles in one freaking
picture it's
crazy look how many and there's they
have little Tails I was like joking oh I
should pull I should pull her
tail small small Ted house small small
Ted
[Music]
house turtle turtle turle so this was
quite amazing that felt incredible so
thank you am for bringing us to the
turtles
no small small turtle footage I think I
took some videos yeah but I don't think
it was too interesting so I didn't uh
edit the any Turtle videos maybe maybe
afterwards I'll edit one and then put it
up just just small Cuts in case
anything's showing um but maybe I'll do
it afterwards and maybe I'll upload on
Twitter if I if you want to see the
turtles
moving but we were just chilling
there that was so fascinating and we
talked about
who was who was questioning it I feel
like maybe Fu was questioning I'm not
sure but one of one of the girls was
like questioning like when they're small
is the shell also small and they they
grow with it or do do they grow into a
huge shell or what how does it
work and I think am
was educating them on total growth I
don't know
yeah yeah it grows with them yeah yeah
yeah yeah for this one and then I think
we brought up that uh what was it t what
T what's this other there's a different
one right
that no I don't know the turtoise are
are they
different in that regard I'm not sure
[Music]
h no same does it work the same
way but they live in the desert wow so
good they have stubby feet ah right yeah
these ones have flippers cuz they're in
the water but right I never realized
that tur toes do have stubby feet yeah
which makes sense cuz they don't
swim
oh interesting interesting
cool yeah there were so many tourists
there and there were some a lot of
German speaking people too and Amma was
like do you understand them I'm like
yeah that's my language yeah I get it I
hear everything they're
saying and then and then we turn around
to go somewhere else and what do we
find oh that's another turtle that's
that's I think this one's eating what
Amy gave to the
turtle look at this Turtle this
fine fine Turtle wow it was looking at
us nice pick right you could get so many
pictures of
turtles from my
phone yeah but then we see a [\h__\h]
kitten and we all died especially I
think especially me and fuok
died uh I was too shy to ask at first I
didn't want to bother them somebody had
had their kitten out on a walk you know
um and fok went up first to them to ask
if they could pet the kitten and I I
felt too nervous I wouldn't have done it
but since they did it I felt more
confident to also join I don't want to
bother them cuz I'm sure they get
bothered all the time when when you
bring a [\h__\h] kitten out in the public
you I guess you have to expect that
people will want to pet your
kitten and you know I really I really
miss my kitten
C
so I I needed that moment but when when
I finally went to the kitten and and
wanted to give it some pets of course
with permission uh in that very moment
because the kitty the kitty was kind of
skidish too but in that very moment a
huge dog came over walked by or was
being walked by and then the kitten was
like distracted and like what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] so I didn't get too much
um touches on the kitten but it was so
cute it was so
cute look look oh my God we all died
looking at look at
oh oh my God oh my
God no it's literally
panning not peeing
panning oh my
God it's not fair it's not
fair oh my
go I
can't I can't that's so
cute so somewhere at some point uh no
wait now first I don't think I have
pictures of any any more of the Central
Park uh after that but we did like check
out a bit more like we went up to some
uh belad Castle I think that's what it
was called um there's so many beler
castles all over the world I noticed
um yeah we had a nice
view and I heard some people do like
music in the
park this and that yeah it's was really
nice did you meet more cats no this was
the only cat unfortunately but I was
surprised I didn't think I would we felt
like it was a [\h__\h] zoo I know there
is a zoo in Central Park too but this
already felt like a zoo to us we saw so
many squirrels like literally everywhere
we would look there was a [\h__\h] square
roll uh we saw Turtles we saw fishes we
saw Goose we saw this kitten we saw dogs
I saw a statue of uh a guy on a horse
who looked really funny and it's a huge
statue so when you stand right in front
of it and you look up to the Statue you
literally see the horse's
balls so I saw a horse too sorry I don't
know why I had to point that out but I
thought it was quite funny
that they modeled that part too in that
statue oh you know which one you know
which
one yes yes yes what's next in this
picture ah it's a sque oh my god there
were just so many of them like they're
so cute look at them I want to touch
their
tail oh oh I think I don't have it like
in this folder now but I I did take a
picture of I think this very squirrel
when it changed position and like sat on
the branch uh it was like we could only
see its butt so I have like this view of
a squirrel butt which was really cute no
I didn't touch them no I wanted to but
yeah I'm honestly also like very careful
like I I I do wonder if these animals
all have like illnesses if it's safe to
touch any of them you probably can't
tell so you probably shouldn't touch any
but they could have something but they
might not I don't know
M yeah shouldn't shouldn't touch them I
guess they could bite but I think
they're they they really friendly though
they went up to people and stuff
M well okay okay so oh my God oh my God
so
um I wonder like I was talking I was
mentioning this several times that all
these sitcoms and I watch
um yes oh s it com said I watch like
friends and Seinfeld and so on they all
like play in [\h__\h] New York and so I
was wondering like if I could see
anything that's like related to these
shows and Amma was like I don't know
because like they all like filming on
sets
right but yeah she found something for
me I did not know that this I didn't
have much time to look up things myself
where I wanted to go but yeah she found
out that there was not even that far
from the Central Park the the the
Seinfeld
soup and a that ey so excited no soup
for you I love that episode it's so
funny so oh my God we all got soup and I
didn't know there's so many different
choices of soups first of all and then
and then they they give you a piece of
bread a chunky piece of bread baguette
and an apple a big ass apple and a piece
of chocolate like uh I think it's mint
chocolate or peppermint or something
yeah um but there's also so many
different choices of soup yeah I got
butternut squash I think and me and cie
got broccoli cheese and I think fule got
uh I think they got the lobster Beast uh
cuz I think that's like the their most
um popular
one and this is like it looks I think it
looks pretty small of a container but
our especially our broccoli cheese soup
was so filling and we got the smallest
container and all of the stuff but the
soup alone was already so filling and
you can get all of this for
$5 yeah and they had some merch and
stuff and they had a
picture oh I think I oh no sh no the
order is
[Music]
wrong the order is wrong
no let me pull it up on its
own oh a where is it where is
it a
[Music]
here this is fine I checked it I checked
it
t here this is me holding my my lunch
bag they make you a little lunch bag
that's me holding it
uh and there's pictures of them on the
wall yeah and they had merch like little
cups that said no soup for you uh
displayed everywhere yeah I got so
excited man I got so excited and the
soup was actually good
um shut
up shut up it's not a yellow Wing no I
have hands okay no I didn't buy any of
the no no no no but I explained to
everybody cuz like foku didn't know it
at all and so I explained yeah you know
like Seinfeld there just like soup plays
this episode with the soup and it's so
funny because like elain just can't
decide like what soup she wants and they
get really mad because it's a really
busy soup Place really popular so if you
can't decide right away what you want
they're like [\h__\h] you no soup for you
get out of here and then she was so mad
because like [\h__\h] you right like give me
my [\h__\h] soup why you so
mean they're just really
mean yeah I I watch just the other day I
watch watch this whole
documentary uh so long of why how Elaine
became a pretty evil person throughout
the show I just watched
that it's such a classic I'm so glad
that this exists yeah it's obviously
it's kind of different from the show
because I think in the show it's like
it's not a restaurant where you can sit
down but it's at least like kind of
inside you walk into something this was
like open to the outside so
not quite the
same uh and I'm guessing they still
filmed it in a set so I'm not sure how
this is the one place but apparently it
is no anyway
anyway aren't you happy I have so many
pictures here for you guys to like show
you my story nobody else does it like me
nobody else does it like me tangents
that's my
[Music]
thing okay next a yeah so I don't know
this is really random but I was so happy
this is huge Banner thingy for rings of
power yeah reminded me that it's
starting soon the next season let's see
if it's better than the first one I'm
curious I we'll see isn't it showing
tomorrow is it
tomorrow oh my
[Music]
God yeah I know it's an ad duh what else
would it
be didn't you read the ad what do you
mean what what do you mean yeah yeah Oh
you mean like oh if I don't really yeah
well yeah see it says August something
behind the trees yeah let you said it
reminded me that it's
soon it's so big it was so big guys yeah
this was like uh close to Broadway so we
went we actually our our whole like
route was so good thank you
Amy like we started at Central Park we
walked through all of it we walked like
down
like I guess
south south of uh to the end South End
of Central Park I guess it's South I
don't know um and then from there we
could get the soup and we could then
walk oh kind of we found a little space
where we ate the soup and then we went
for here to like Broadway which brought
us to the
uh Time Square yeah Time
Square so this is funny um so Random I
don't know the store just kind of stood
out to
us apparently there's an M&M store and I
just didn't find that but everybody else
found that uh like like our managers and
stuff but this is a sardine
shop this is a [\h__\h] sardine shop
oh right at Time Square time
squirrel uh we walked into it because it
kind of gives like these Harry Potter
Vibes I don't know it's so detailed and
and the colors are really Harry Pottery
isn't it um but all it sells sardines
and like similar stuff in these um
little what do you call it again
conen you love sardines
really I don't think I like them uh
was
it where was it was it f or Amy or Cali
one of them
like maybe it was
F like I was like questioning if if this
was any good if this was something you
would actually want to eat and I think F
was saying like oh yeah they're they're
yummy yeah we eat them on bread and I'm
like
what
what yeah
um so that reassured me a little bit
because me and cie ended up buying some
of these cuz they had really interesting
versions like there was some millions of
different variations um I ended up
getting pretty normal sardines but with
a special date on them because there was
a whole section that had like it went
back I don't know [\h__\h] 100
years uh it had like one year on it
basically written and it doesn't mean
that the sardines are are from that year
they said that's basically just like a
joke it's just they're not that old the
sardines in there they just like as a
joke they put on the date there I don't
know
yeah you might think it is from then but
it's not it's not they said yeah so we
got a bunch of sardines as a souvenir
isn't that a nice souvenir to get from
New
York I think it's literally the only
souvenir I got
[Music]
I would not eat this though I don't
think I would like it e e disgusting
just the thought of it is disgusting e
okay h no that's something else
something else
okay that's Mexican food
um we're not there yet that's a
different day
spoilers so I think that was that yeah
that makes
sense makes sense basically so uh we
went to the Time Square I we didn't stay
very long at the Time Square it was kind
of
like underwhelming maybe it would have
probably been cooler if we went by night
and
also uh there was like this whole like I
think there was like this performance
like stage setup that kind of blocked a
lot of it which is kind of lame
M yeah oh and I did notice throughout my
whole trip I understood why people say
he I'm walking here in New York I
understand now why it's a famous phrase
here because it's literally so hard to
walk I have never experienced uh a
situation where more people are just
[\h__\h] in your path than in New
York I understand
now so many cars yeah
and then like so many cars parking in an
already extremely Narrow Street so it's
like really difficult for the cars to
get through here through
too yeah but anyway time scare was okay
like uh I think we were already pretty
exhausted walking so much so we didn't
stay too long and and we went into a few
stores here and there went went into a
store I really I really wanted to go
into a store um that had like new jeans
plastered all over it was I think um a
really cute store yeah Line Store here
and there you know we did some things
here and there yeah new jeans and I was
really considering buying stuff but like
I was like hey I don't know what I would
buy and I don't know I love new jeans
but I don't want to buy like merch stuff
cuz it clutters my home where do I even
put it I don't know yeah
crony also like um when we were were at
the Time Square there were like people
lining up uh at like like these like uh
Broadway shows tickets last minute
tickets offices and stuff and am was
like explaining it to me and then I was
like looking at the list of all the
shows they have and I was like oh my God
there's literally so many shows I would
want to watch but no time and nobody to
go with
me um but yeah there was a Great Gatsby
show that I was trying to like somehow
find time for but I I would have
probably had to go alone and
[Music]
yeah uh yeah great got me and they have
like shows for like uh like sitcoms
random sitcoms and stuff like the office
they have a the office musical what the
[\h__\h] so many random things and then
there was one thing that really confused
me it said yeah there's one group uh
that went to see Wicked we didn't no no
no what I didn't even they went I didn't
even know they were doing that we were
like separate separate groups and I
didn't know they were even doing
that but that wouldn't have been my
first choice of a
musical to
watch you could have been part yeah like
at some point my manager sent me a
picture of like the freaking Steven Co
Bear show those like like venue thing
and I'm like oh my God now you make me
realize I could have like if I organized
it better I could have maybe managed to
see one of the shows and be in the
audience I have to go again to New York
I have
to Mama Mia but yeah uh I was
considering getting into a show but uh
yeah didn't work out which is okay maybe
another time and then um after that we
went back after Time Square we went back
um I got this in Uber we drove back and
and then we like got ourselves ready for
dinner cie organized the dinner on that
night and um it was it was really nice
and I think at that point like our
groups merged and I sat in front
of s Senpai and SU and by sister
animi so animi was also in New York and
yeah I met her for the first
time and oh my God she's just so slay
like
gorgeous and fashionable I was shocked
and I I talked I was like shy and
intimidated honestly because Sude Amai
and animi together they had this whole
Aura this Superstar aura about around
them and and they were like both
fashionable and just gorgeous
slay intimidated me I was like really
nervous about sitting in front of them
cuz I felt like I had to be cool
um
so and then um when we're like starting
to like introduce each others and like
you know get into a little bit of a
chitchat suicide samai tries to like I
guess make this connection between me
and animi and tells me nicely that animi
was listening to listening to Kima the
whole time in the airplane and really
likes my music and I'm like
what what
what what and then that moment
I already decided I love you
animi so then I I chitch so much with
[Music]
her I'm so
excited actually listening to my music
actively and just recently in the
airplane listen to chimo what you for
real oh my
[Music]
God was so
honored it's nice to hear like when
somebody really listen to my
songs and it feels so
real and not just when it just literally
got released no it's been a few months
[Music]
now I'm the main source of cop style in
whole life yeah that's true it's is true
it is true
so I hope she will like my new song
too that was fun so we ate some stuff
and I just I I don't know I I I somehow
didn't have an appetite so um Cali
ordered so many freaking starters so I
just like kept on eating some of the
starters and and um taking little bites
from like others stuff like cie had some
chicken alfredo so I tried her chicken
alfredo
I just I just couldn't build an appetite
to order anything on my own kind of
weird I I think I just had this like
anxiety I I've been feeling more and
more um anxiety that I've never felt
before in my whole life
recently uh and I'm like oh is this
anxiety is this is this feeling
[Music]
anxiety yeah so but it's okay I still
like I I forced some food into
me yeah um it was a nice nice evening
and we chitchat we talked a lot some of
the girls had to leave because they had
to go um to their musical so then it was
down to you know less of us but we we
had a great
time
yeah it was good good stuff it was
really really early dinner
yeah yeah yeah cuz they went to the to
the musical and they're food was just
not arriving so we ended up just like
packing it they had like five bites and
then they had to run and we packed it up
for
[Laughter]
them stress from molting
season cat's musical I didn't see any
Cats musical on the list can you tell us
about drunk Iris drunk Iris I mostly
only noticed um on our like little after
party so I was going to get to that
later
[Music]
so yeah I think that's uh that's that
part of the story that's that
now uh let's talk a little bit about
breaking
Dimensions so this like if you compare
this setup with like big side
screens know like this is this was small
but I kind of liked these
um
horizontal what would you call it
vertical vertical vertical I kind of
like these vertical um screens I feel
like it's kind of unique and um for
close-ups it kind of works and not just
for close-ups like they would show uh
like full body shots and all that there
too right and if you're dancing alone on
the stage then it just works
perfectly I think they we
good so we performed at King's fater for
2 days in a row just this very last
weekend and it was our second whole life
English concert let me change the theme
down
[Music]
here our second Ian concert and I I
heard that you guys really enjoyed it um
I I noticed and you guys already gave so
much feedback that it was better than
the first one I think you know the first
one as because it was our first one we
went um with a really
simple um concept and pattern and like
the set list and everything is very um
tame and simple simplistic um which I
think was fine because it was the first
one but definitely a lot of our feedback
as um talents as well was that for the
next one we got to mix it up more and
yeah um I think there were a lot of
improvements there can always be
improvements and I already have a list
of like feedback again for the next one
but um yeah I think it was great
um I know you guys want the bigger
location at least the cool thing is that
because of the small venue the small
capacity they at least got it for two
days so the cool thing with that is
imagine we would have had like maybe a
9k 10K capacity venue we probably would
have only done one day but then we would
have had way less uh like performances
for
member the fact that we had 2 days I did
kind of tell you I couldn't like tell it
say it too clearly but I did tell you
that two days will be different um but
it was like kind of a more or less even
amount of appearances on each day I had
my solo and one unit song uh unless it
count myth as a un I guess so so I guess
two unit songs because we had myth and
the Ian birds and waa solo and of course
the big [\h__\h] songs but we're not going
to count them on the first day and the
second day I had my uh MC and and fire
night of c h so one one day would always
be like a little bit
more but generally you would see us all
on each day and that's not the case with
like the Japanese uh Fest concerts right
so like at that point with that many
members and several days if you want to
see the Waba it's just one specific day
right but in this case we had two days
but you could see all of us on both days
face and it was different different set
lists and
everything and it was really really
great really fun so I'm glad we had two
days because honestly if it was one day
even if it was a bigger venue we would
have had way less
appearances that's really cool
yeah
[Music]
yeah oh yeah yeah that was also a big
change that I think last time Japanese
and ID guests they were um like just
performing in their own groups so to say
but this time they were mixed in um with
the Ian
members why no Kima well Kima because I
literally just had performed it at Fest
in the same year I know Kima is really
hyp but if I get one solo I thought I
should give it to a song that has not
been performed in the same year on a
real stage yet um and pineapple was that
and also I did think even though
pineapple may have not been like the
biggest success out of all my songs um I
still think it would be a great life
song and I have proven that point
because everybody was singing along I'm
going one two one two three it tastes so
so so sweet when you go and kiss
me yeah everybody was singing
pineapple so
happy m yeah my choreographer she was
literally in the
crowd the lady of
ladies Kiana was in the crowd she
choreographed pineapple and hinoni and
so
on she was there on the right day she
wasn't there on day two and she also
sadly she wasn't at the uh the world
tour concert either I did sleep dogging
which was also her chore
but she did get to see day one which I
must say is lucky because if she went to
day two she wouldn't have seen pineapple
and stuff like day one was definitely
the better day for a kfp I think both
days were great but um as a kfp you got
more Wawa out of day one I
guess yeah so she
like she witnessed in the
crowd like how everybody was like
singing along to the song and how I was
dancing her C and all that I'm sure that
must have felt really special to
her I felt so
happy so yeah she lives in New
York which is why I ended up meeting up
with her and I'll tell you all about
that too um but yeah what else yeah so
there was so much like um waiting
time uh but also like rehearsals and
stuff and it was really cool like um
during
rehearsal like we could like you know as
long as it wasn't our part and we could
sit in the
seats and like watch
it yeah watch what the others were doing
and like hear it and all that and I
would I would look around at this venue
and like wow this going to be filled
with all the all the people all the fans
amazing and like we were I was like
checking out how it looked like for from
the other seats like to uh very left in
the back and so on okay the view wasn't
the best over there but it was really
good in the middle it looked so cool in
the
middle I was just
hype I thought it was really funny like
the transitions when the stage kind of
changed and the the the taxis would like
drive off and then there was like
[\h__\h] Transformers moment I was like
what the [\h__\h] is happening everybody was
like what the [\h__\h] is happening
what does this
mean but another thing I thought was
really cute those Transformer um the
Transformer set would like at the end of
the concert would like go down uh like
kind of like curtains but it's like
shutters closing from above going down
and we were like wave wave wave wave
that's cute that was
[Music]
cute represented hallway and perfectly
what the [\h__\h] taxi going to trans
Transformers n
how I thought it looked really cute
really really lovely um nice stage set
um I felt like it like it was
fascinating to me it really looked like
a real stage like obviously it was a
real stage right but like maybe
depending on The View you had not so
much but like it really looked like a I
mean I mean okay the taxis maybe not so
much but like so of it just looked so
real to me and
wow yeah the effect was so
cool
really and I was so happy like I wish
they would do the whole like showing
fans thing uh longer I wish they would
do it longer um because like I got so
excited
like it's always fun to watch and then
they show like they didn't even focus on
kfp in that moment but KF
um employee was standing on the side and
then people saw the kfp and and this
specific kfp was like super super hype
about being on camera and was really
proudly repping the
the the whole kfp attire and then people
saw that and started chanting kfp kfp
kfp and it made me cry already right in
the beginning before things even start
it
just made me so happy was that
you you and your
wife wow thank you if that was you wow
they showed kfp also on on like
different occasions but this one moment
really got me because it got everybody
to chant kfp and made me feel so
proud and then the other girls were like
wow kfp so loud and I'm like yeah we got
to you know we're not like the most like
here like we're not number one in terms
of numbers but we're really loud and
we've got to we got to be loud and thank
you so much for showing me so much
[Music]
love unfortunately now we are P
ofk um for that
MC
um you know already talked about it I
think and said you know I came up with
the
wave yeah behind the scenes I was like I
guess if we still do the wave you could
do the wave but you call it the W how
about that oh my God so [\h__\h] genius
and um I wanted to do this
like I feel kind of mad because like
maybe we should have focused on wave and
doing something else because in the end
every single MC on day two was doing
call and response once I don't know if
that was maybe too much was that too
much guys did it feel like too
much I'm sorry because I really wanted
to do call and response this time
because I thought of this thing like if
I make people shout uh letters then I
could mess them up and I could be like P
FK p p f f k f f k p and so on I wanted
to mess it up completely I wanted to go
like here and there and back and forth I
wanted to completely mix it up in the
end I only did it like once with pfk uh
because I I we were on time pressure and
I felt like I didn't want to hog it too
much but ideally I would have gone on
for a
while and then I I said I want to um I
if only you guys would have done it on
your own but of course why would you do
that so I had to initiate it but I
really wanted to have a wrap it up call
cuz we were already doing so many call
and response things right so might as
well because I had to think of the time
when I did um the MC with guda at Fest
and we were so overtime and staff was
like signing to us wrap it up wrap it up
in
[Music]
[Laughter]
Japanese yeah it was too fast next time
if I if I do uh nmc ever again feel free
to just after 5 minutes or so out of
nowhere just go for it just say wrap it
up no that's kind of difficult that's
difficult I feel like I have to initiate
it if I want to hear
that wrap it up wrap it up I I wish they
would just play some music like like uh
in the award shows I want them as a joke
to just like play music at the end of my
MC slowly and I'm like oh [\h__\h]
I
know that' be so funny but the idea was
pretty spontaneous and I don't even if
it wasn't spontaneous they probably
would not have accommodated my wish to
play some bgm randomly just for my
MC it would have been so funny
though yeah so uh I don't know I was
like spending a lot of time um like
waiting so during the waiting time cuz
we were there the whole day Mama
Mia so long we spent so much time there
uh so we basically ate breakfast lunch
and dinner there more or less um but in
the in the free time I like I was smart
I brought my birthday limited
edition uh poll Awards to sign
from Japan to America I brought them
with me so I was signing a bunch of
them uh while I was waiting behind the
scenes yeah being actually productive
and
efficient yeah and I don't know our our
room with all the girls in it it was fun
and and you know we had a lot of um
interesting moments um um mostly I was
just observing them like them screaming
their [\h__\h] lungs out when they were
playing cards
or I don't know if anybody mentioned a
certain
like
cringe
Dating Game phone game being played and
girls gathering around it and and
screaming like
I don't think anybody mentioned that one
[Music]
yet it was mentioned really they were
losing their minds over
it and then me and the ISA we were just
like sitting like across them like
thinking why why why and thinking to
ourselves like we said it to each other
like honestly like I don't care about
this if this was a if it was if it was a
girl I would be more interested
M and they was like yeah right I know
yeah give us the same game but with a
girl
maybe with a woman Mystic message yeah
it might have been it something like
that I'm sure yeah yeah yeah yeah I
don't know if that it was exactly that
but it was surely something
[Music]
similar and I left the room uh somewhere
during that and then staff uh like
manager and so on they were like what
are you girls all screaming about in
there we can hear you so loud and I'm
like oh don't worry about
[Music]
it they are just really
excited
[Music]
bruh did she that was cute and and
shocking but so cute
cute
yeah yeah now I don't know is there
something else um oh I stole some I I
found like you know they had so they had
so much good food and snacks so I took a
[\h__\h] ton of twixes because I saw so many
twixes so I took them with me and ate
them all in the airplane um
and
uh yeah the food was really good they
had so much food they had a lot of like
fruit and desserts and cakes and stuff
but also of course like proper like
dishes um D they had corn on the cob
they had corn on the cob I was so
excited about the corn I had so much
corn I I generally was like again not
really having an appetite so I didn't
eat with um all of the other girls I
like waited until the last moment and
then I was like I have to eat I guess
and I saw they had corn I was like okay
I can have corn
anytime
corn
yeah I'm glad America likes corn as much
as I
[Music]
do no way somebody was using corn cops
as glow sticks
what sometimes to our detriment I'm sure
mhm
[Music]
ah um okay um then
um I think think is wait let me check my
tangents want me saying something
[Music]
important ah I noticed like okay so one
more thing for my MC cuz I did you
notice how I I thanked the staff and all
that I had that planed since like Fest
because I realized real ized like after
Fest was over I was like H in all of
these MC's like nobody ever like thanks
a staff and all that and I was like
that's actually weird I I'm sure like
that we all are thankful for the staff
for putting everything together we all
are um but I think we're all like too
nervous to like mention anything and
also this the suggestions that they give
for what we talk about in the MC's don't
mention any of that so we just kind of
go off of what they suggest mostly um
and then nobody even ever thinks about
it but I was thinking like in other
concerts like they would often like have
a moment where they thank the band right
they're like give it up for the drums
and the KE and this and yeah um I just
thought like ever since F like literally
since what was it March I was like okay
for the Ian
concert if I get to do an MC I I need to
like G give a moment to the people who
are putting This Together Ollie Ollie
was crying I saw like a bunch of her
like reactions yeah a she's so sweet H
she kind of went very feral here and
there yeah yeah I also heard like
obviously I mean it had to um hear it uh
and feel it um on day one like we are
really we were really delayed because um
it took so much time to get people into
the venue
um probably because uh you guys like a
lot of you guys came from the convention
so you had so much like baggage to be
checked through and that took so much
time so yeah sorry about that on the
next day they um started earlier and
went through it kind of faster so thank
God there was only a 5 minute delay on
the second day m
yeah that's a bit difficult when it's
like on the same days as a convention
[Music]
sorry replying to a
message oh I'm not of sleep what the
hell why would why would I be
sleeping okay maybe because I'm up since
4:00 a.m.
[Music]
but sleep talking in my dreams I'm sleep
talking all these night is
you okay uh how's the after party should
I just jump straight to that I guess I
could okay uh so Callie Cy I have to say
like there was like this moment where um
okay we're all back right and we're like
waiting to go to the Afterparty and cie
realized is something behind the scenes
and notifies us that there's a problem
with our Afterparty venue
and and in that moment I
knew I talk to her about it later but I
knew oh Callie certainly
was how to describe I know her pretty
well by now and she always you know
wants to organize things for us and then
so often things will go like wrong for
her doesn't matter if it's like when
it's a stream that she planned and uh
either a solo or a collaboration and
things just don't go right or something
IRL you know like things always seem to
like kind of go wrong she's very cursed
in that sense so I knew that the moment
she wrote that uh like please wait like
something's wrong with our venue uh I
knew that she was probably like really
stressed and having a breakdown or
something or felt really bad about it
and I was just like later on I was like
Callie I know how you must have felt in
that moment don't worry about it okay
things turned out really
great and I'm sure you felt really
bad when it happened and I I know you
cie I know
you yeah just kind of trying to cheer
her up because she
M I feel bad like she how does she end
up in these situations all the time but
she shouldn't feel too bad about it like
the the fact that she like oh thanks for
the
raid hello we're chitchatting we're
tting a lot about New
York yeah welcome yeah the fact that she
always tries to put things together for
us uh you know she really she really
tries to please everybody but things
will go wrong sometimes and that's okay
but we're really I think all grateful
that somebody put something together in
the first place because um we were all
like so occupied with our minds and it's
actually incredible that she can do it
because she's already like one of the
busiest people among us and the fact
that she still takes time to do stuff
like that is
amazing yeah oh yeah let's change this
into after
party so after party
um yeah we ended up I guess they
somebody already mentioned uh rooftop we
ended up on a one of many of New York's
beautiful rooftops we were on a rooftop
and it was so beautiful can't believe
that this was the the emergency
Choice gorgeous it was such an amazing
view
I saw so many beautiful buildings up
there yes of course we were on top of
the Empire State Building
mhm and yeah I feel like you know we're
we're not really Party People we're
mostly like introverted people so um we
weren't like dancing or anything but
they were playing music and we got
drinks and we got food cie got us a huge
order of
canes which I think she says it's her
favorite
uh Chicken in
America I'm glad she um is the same as
me um when it comes to like bones so she
got no bone
chicken
and it's good but it's expensive oh the
sauce yeah the sauce was good we had
like no Cutlery so it was a bit
difficult to eat the
COA but yeah chicken tenders and lots of
fries and the is like she she ordered so
much more food um than we needed because
like we were mostly just like talents
and a few managers and she thought that
there would be so much more like staff
also coming she didn't give like a a
clear invitation to them so they ended
up you know going somewhere else but she
assumed that they would come so we had
like so much food holy
[\h__\h] yeah no plates either m
M but thank you for taking care of us
can
we apparently apparently we got like
Yago to pay for it in the end thank you
Yago cuz first it was like there was no
this all just happened because of Cali
like you know there was no like after
party or anything planned from the
management side so thank you
K thank you yo
for being convinced to pay for the
food yeah I just had like a mocktail but
some of the girls ordered
cocktails and yeah I you guys already
heard it but like Iris really stood out
to me crony too partially but crony and
Iris were like sticking together a lot
of the time
and there was like yeah crony and Iris
were sticking together Ena and Bae were
sticking together fuu obviously was
sticking together CI was just kind of
everywhere where um yeah an Mai and Su
obviously were sticking together I was
like kind of like sticking with
am most of the time but I noticed that
uh I noticed that Iris was I don't think
I ever saw her drunk before she gets
like so talkative of course but like
she's so smiley she just won't stop
smiling she's smiling so much when she's
drunk
and um it's so cute like she just
couldn't stop smiling with an open mouth
too like she was just
so and she talks so much and then she
uses her hands way more too like her
arms and her hands were flailing around
she was so excited to join
conversations so there was this one time
where um cuz like during the dating game
thing on the phone
uh Su Senpai did not like experience
that moment so I was like telling Su
Senpai about
it kind of like to have a fun talking
topic you know I thought that would be
funny to her and then the other girls
would get embarrassed and then everybody
would be like no that's yeah I thought
it would be a funny moment so I I told
about it and then she was she was like
Curious and so um I told the the culprit
I'm not going to say who but I told the
culprit who brought it up on their phone
in the first place to show it to Su
Senpai and she got very embarrassed of
course uh and then um eventually we
managed to show it to to Senpai and
there the whole thing basically just
repeated itself everybody got like all
over it again because there's like this
moment where you have to I guess um like
shave the guy's face
I was like cringing at it
man but everybody got
[Music]
[Laughter]
excited yeah that's very
interesting and then uh suicide Senpai
let's see I have a picture of this but I
think it's like out of it's not in the
right order so let me pull it up
separately what where is it
where is
it so s by got
us uh a cake a huge cake which again we
were like oh [\h__\h] we don't have Cutlery
how do we at least we managed to get a
knife at that
[Music]
point where the hell is that cake
picture I maybe I didn't save it
properly
oh it already exists
okay cake cake cake cake cake cake here
it
is red velvet
cake
whoa yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum oh my God you see it's kind of a
mess it's a little bit of a mess yeah it
it like was very very uh cheesecake is
red ret cake always like
cheesecake well that was kind of like
her Sashi eer Sashi eat it so to
say m nice dessert otherwise we would
have had no no
dessert so this was a great idea from
suicide
Senpai ah not usually oh okay then it
was like a red velvet cheesecake like
collaboration
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I usually
usually not
[Music]
always sounds
bomb thank you suici Senpai and then
suici Senpai like um eventually like you
know we would like go around and talk in
different groups and this and that but s
sampa eventually like went to me and and
and hit me up she was like Ki tell me
about the accent suit and I'm like oh
okay and she really liked my um what
I've done so far with the excellent suit
and I was like considering getting one
for herself um so I told her about it
and I I um got her into contact with
jenma or like her manager in contact
with my manager so that they could
figure it out because the compan is from
Europe they don't have like Japanese
communication and all that so um yeah
just like helping her out to get uh a
suit of her own she said that you know
it might be like convenient for her for
some
things yes yes what's that it's a motion
capture suit that you know I use when
I'm at home and I want to do stuffff
like record choreographies for music
video etc
[Music]
etc yeah yeah we talked a little bit
about like other methods and this and
that
but I was U yeah explaining her how it
works and
everything yeah she watched she watched
like the fever night workout stream
thing uh as well apparently like
probably should just watched a clip of
it but
yeah the booty yeah she must have seen
the booty oh my God I'm so
[Music]
embarrassed Mama Mia so maybe we'll get
a few more people wearing Accents in the
future and maybe maybe then the company
will like be able to um make our own uh
Whole Life Application more m
how to say compatible with accents in
general because currently it's not very
compatible as we have talked about
before yeah and then so you know H at
the venue like you know I got a massage
from crony right um and that was really
nice she's so good and I really needed a
massage as always I need a massage every
[\h__\h] day but I was praising her a lot
I was saying oh my God crony you're the
best you're so good yeah that's the spot
yeah yeah yeah up there maybe a little
bit more to the right oh yeah that's the
spot
crony and
um at the uh at the after party somehow
she decides to massage me again I was
like eh again really what you want to
massage me again no way and she's like
yeah lie down there cuz we had like
sofas
sofas so she's like really serious about
about it cuz she did say before like
when she first massaged me she was like
oh this is really bad like you should
lay down for this actually but yeah so I
laid down this time uh wow she's already
kind of like you know she had
alcohol uh in her body
[Music]
so maybe it came from that she was just
like in the
mood but so I lay down I'm I'm just like
I feel kind
[Music]
of she mustaches me and like happy
and it goes on for a while for a while
quite long she really like gets into it
you know
um then
after Cy don't watch
this after um a while um we kind of get
up and like she talks to someone
and um it seems to be the end of it
right but like she's talking to someone
and I feel like oh man she massaged me
so long and she massaged other people
too I feel like you know maybe maybe
somebody needs to massage crony for once
so I go behind her and like I suddenly
while she's talking to someone I
suddenly start massaging her shoulders
and she likes it cuz I get compliments
about my massages too you
know but she normally like she uses her
elbow only pretty much and I I don't
know I didn't really try that before I
normally just use my hands and go around
the shoulders a little bit I can't do
that much cuz I'm weak too but then I do
it for a while and she's enjoying it so
I really want to like continue longer
cuz she did my massage for so long but
then I notice I'm getting so weak and I
tell her like oh man now I know why you
go with the elbow because my fingers my
hands are dying but she she likes it so
I'm like okay well maybe you know that
maybe you can lie down I'll try my elbow
and she's like yeah okay and she teaches
me how to use the elbow you know this
and that and I'm like is this good here
is this good here cuz she's lying down
on the sofa and like
I was feeling
embarrassed but I I wanted to give her
something back you
know and that was improving my technique
so I massage her for a while and then
and then she tells me to you
know she massaged me again so we were in
this endless massage cycle and like give
and take you know pretty um wholesome um
[Music]
I was kind of flustered I'm so happy
about crony even approaching me yeah you
know like I don't know me and crony I
feel like we've been getting along
forever you know but like we it's not
like we have a million collabs and a
million interactions I just feel like
you know when we played Diablo and so on
like we did get along but then at the
same time you know I'm like she's this
cool type of person you know cool
personality Cool vibe you know what I
mean so I'm like I don't know if she
really likes me as a person or if this
is just business I don't
know so I'm like I'm sure and my brain
worms tell me that everybody hates me
you know so I'm not sure but then after
all this massaging like at the end of
the day or the evening like you know
when when we say goodbyes and good
nights to each other she's like let's
collab again sometime and I'm
like and I like try I I I try not to cry
because I'm kind of like feeling so
touched that like she wants to collab
with me
what trying to not cry really and and
she's like what's wrong and I'm like I
don't know like I'm just really happy
that you like me and she's like what do
you
mean like I don't I don't know like you
know I feel like I don't know maybe
there's no reason because we do get
along like the times when we did like
collab but I'm generally like I'm really
like not sure like sometimes if people
like me so when you ask me directly I'm
just so happy about
it cuz it felt genuine right when
somebody asks you cuz I'm always the one
asking you know so I'm not sure anymore
do you know at that point so likeon
asked me and I'm like oh my God C I love
you she was so sweet I'm going to cry
now you're so sweet I love
yeah so I'm going to uh I have I'll have
to think of
something I don't know what we could do
but I'll think of
[Music]
something yeah yeah she said so too like
she's bad at asking people she usually
doesn't ask people for collabs and she
just like waits for people to ask her
and I said yeah I mean a lot of people
are like that um so it's um I don't
know it's nice to be asked for
once all of you like that that's not
true I'm not like that for centuries I
have asked people for
collabs yeah yeah yeah yeah I love Cory
so yeah now we all had fun
um yeah we all felt like so
I feel I don't know this this whole
experience
um I feel like we all Bond it so much in
these few days it was really special
experience to us
and I don't know is it it's this special
feeling that is hard to describe and
hard to recreate and something that only
we
understand yeah we were all really moved
and yeah we grew closer as a branch and
we had a great time together also I
bonded a lot with Callie's mom
again Callie's mom was
there um and
I I talked so much cuz like we met
before right so um when when we like
reunited I was like oh my God Mama
Mory and she was happy to see a familiar
face too
and so I talked a lot with her I talked
about uh how cie was when she was a baby
I don't know like right next to Cali we
were right sitting right next to Cali
like getting uh transported away away
from the venue afterwards like we saw
you guys like outside of the venue we
were like when you watching oh my God
there's so many people like swarming out
of the venue and wearing their merch and
it goes on and on and on and on for
miles um but anyway like I was
sitting I was sitting next to um mommy
Mory and we like yeah I'm just making
small talk asking her how it was for her
and and and if she had fun and how was
Cali when she was a
baby and and then I don't know how we
got to this
topic did we get to this topic I don't
know uh but she told me she likes
Vikings the show and I'm like oh my God
I just finished watching Vikings valala
and watched Vikings like originally too
and and then we start talking like we
get so hyped we're like screaming at
each other like oh my God oh my God yeah
she's so great this and that and then I
was like oh but I really didn't like the
like the towards the end of the Vikings
show because like uh the sons when
they're all grown up there's this one
guy he's like so [\h__\h] up and it's like
so annoying how he's such a piece of
[\h__\h] like he's so unlikable it's a
character you know there's like evil
people and and but they're still like
kind of likable but this guy was really
unlikable she was like yeah yeah I get
it I understand you know this and that
and she's like I really love La gafa I
think that was her name and I'm like
yeah we told she's so cool right her
hair is so cool too and oh my God she's
such a badass and then we talk a
littleit about Vahala and this and that
and she's really likes Vikings you know
and and and and then I was like okay but
if you like Vikings what about Game of
Thrones and like House of the Dragon
she's like oh I didn't watch that yet
and I'm like oh my God you have to if
you like Vikings you're going to like
that too oh she also watched last
Kingdom yeah and you know I I I started
recommending all these shows to her that
she didn't watch yet and she recommends
me other shows and we go back and forth
and and I realized like oh my God this
woman she she has the same taste and
shows as me like she likes uh like
medieval and shows and and and fantasy
shows but also like when they're when
they're based on history even better so
I I told her like oh my God there's so
many shows on Amazon that you need to
watch that I already went for she's like
oh I only have a Netflix I'm like a you
got to get yourself the others like oh
my God these are so good blah blah blah
blah yeah so I said I'm going to write
you this whole list of shows that you
haven't seen yet that you need to get
into she was like yeah please do please
I'm waiting for it and she was going to
send me um
a was it a video or a book she told me
that there's either a video or a book
that she read or saw um about what you
things that you do that cats will not
like if you do it or so or something
like that I don't know I was like oh my
God I need to see that cuz it's actually
interesting so she's going to send me
that like uh through Cali but I think
like we have so many things to talk
about I might just have to like get in
contact directly with Callie's
mother we can't just go through uh cie
the whole time I have so much to talk
about with
her I got to get her
number yeah and she's so sweet she's
she's really
like so nice and and sweet and proud and
yeah we talked so much sweet
mama I was saying like ah man would be
nice if like one day my mom can also
like watch a concert in
person um I don't
know uh for that I feel like it would
have to be a concert in Europe at
[Music]
least would be nice if she could like
experience that with her own eyes in
person at least
once so
H let me
see tangent list
check yeah I don't know I wrote down
rooftop oh my god wow view is so
American I think what I was trying to
say is like this was not just uh in the
Afterparty I just generally noticed this
the moment I arrived D um until the very
end like this kind of view is so
American like I can't get this in
Austria obviously um but it's also kind
of different from
Japan Japan like Tokyo has a lot of
skyscrapers too but I feel like the New
York skyline and the buildings and
everything was very unique and really
beautiful and wow I like how I was so
excited cuz I felt like I was literally
in in GTA 4 when I was there um like the
brown
buildings there is some non- brown more
modern buildings too but I really like
the brown buildings it gave me the GTA 4
Vibe and I I just kind of like it
because Brown you may think Brown
buildings are ugly but no it it wasn't
ugly it just felt like kind of classic
and old and just had its own kind of
taste and uniqueness to it Liberty City
baby yeah
M it was really really nice to
see these buildings like I I actually
ended up not seeing the Empire State
Building up close I saw other other cool
buildings but I couldn't make it to the
Empire State Building but I saw it from
afar and honestly I felt like maybe it's
I don't need to go there and see it up
close or go up because I feel like I
I've been in a lot of like cities all
over the world already and I've been in
high buildings several times you know
high buildings where you go up and then
you look at the whole city and first of
all it kind of feels weird to be up
there and look at the whole city it just
doesn't feel real you know what I mean
can't quite take it in I feel like um
yeah far view is better like look at the
huge buildings from afar and see the
whole Skyline take it in I saw the
emperor stayed building several times
from afar and it's really gorgeous
during the daytime and during night time
it's
gorgeous yeah so I'm quite satisfied
with that
H there was one part one time in the uh
in the Afterparty where like I noticed
cie um separated herself from the
groups uh and set herself alone onto one
of the
sofas but like not in a sad way she like
sits down with this smile this this
content contempt
[Music]
content content just happy satisfied
smile see she sits down with her her
arms uh like spread over the the top of
the couch and the sofa and then her legs
also
spread and she just like leans back and
just smiles and I I I'm observing her
and I'm noticing I'm
like she's happy and I noticed though
that like she's she looks to me like
like you know one of these like Rich
rappers just like being cool so I go
over to her and I'm like you know you
look to me like one of those rappers I
felt like you needed a [\h__\h] on by your
side sit down next to her cuz she she's
like kind of
manspreading and her arms like you know
also spread like straight to the side
feels like she needs a lady around her
you know so I sat down I'm like I felt
like you needed a [\h__\h] by your side
and I wanted to lend her company she
didn't seem like sad about sitting alone
in that moment she chose to sit alone in
that moment and take it in but I felt
like you know I've been like bonding a
lot with cie and and I wanted to like uh
be by her side I was like
Callie can we let me sit next to you let
me be your
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] yeah she had a happy moment and we
were chilling there for a while together
talking
talking so like right she she really
loves canes and all that and she was
like um she also ordered a [\h__\h] ton of
like big containers filled with a few of
them were filled with lemonade and a few
of them were filled with the IC
tea uh that you get at canes and
now I have to criticize you guys America
I
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is in your ice
teas
like that tasted so disgustingly sweet
and I love sweet things how much [\h__\h]
sugar isn't that guys that was
disgusting kie said that it's really
good and she really um likes the the IES
from the canes and I'm like oh my God
like I took a whole ju because we had so
much left
over um so I took the whole
jog
uh and and I was like I guess I'll drink
this
tomorrow um but I tried it and it's
like not
good it's like I like uh sweet ice te
like Nest te or uh like whatever fuse
tea all these like sweet IES right H and
then I like the Japanese um that they
like when you order ice Su tea in the
cafes they give you not the typical Nest
tea or whatever they give you like a
normal tea but chilled right but that's
also different this is like an in
between thing and I noticed this not it
was not just the can's one I ordered a
an a sweetened icy on a separate
occasion too from some restaurant and
it's it tasted the same way way it was
ew like sweet but like the wrong
sweetness the different wrong
sweetness what is this it's bad like no
wonder like oh my God I hear the whole
time about how American food is just so
unhealthy um and so processed and this
and that like if this is how your eyes
te tastes I'm sorry but like
E Yeah High FR is that what it tastes
when you put like a lot of high fructose
corn syrup into drink oh my
God that's why you guys love it you guys
your taste buds took it into my veins oh
my God you guys are so messed
up I can't help you I can't save
you it just tasted so wrong
[Music]
um what does this
mean
[Music]
ah what does I think
yeah this is such a random tangent small
just a small moment but I thought you
guys might like it so CI was uh carrying
a backpack at some
point and like let's say you see imagine
CI wearing a backpack facing bi boo
small bi boo talking to each other then
Callie turns around because like we're
leaving the place that we're standing in
she turns around and because people is
so
small the backpack of cie smacks people
into her
face and she's like and CI doesn't even
know this and I just watched it happen
transpire and B was like ow she's like
oh
man the curse of being small
[Music]
yeah oh yeah did you guys notice in
Breaking Dimensions uh pineapple was
kind of sounding
different uh it had to be
remade apparently we lost the
stems
um even K didn't have the stems
anymore uh like we had the instrument as
a whole but not the single stems that
are needed to put it together and for
these like concerts we need the stems
separately uh not just like the
instrumental so it was remade by the
person who made like
sleeptalking that's why it sounded kind
of different M I was confused too but it
sounded
nice oh you know originally a long time
ago when breaking Dimensions was was
being
planned uh they were like giving us this
like stuff stuff to fill out and were
like uh how would you like to break
dimensions and I'm like
H they just wanted like General ideas
and this and that what we want to do and
so I'm thinking really hard about this
how can we actually break dimensions and
I brought up an idea that was not being
used in the
end did I tell this did I tell this
before but I I said I wrote please um we
as 3D girls we can never actually crowd
Surf and that's so sad but no giant
Idols that's my f feedback this is my
whole life English break Dimensions
feedback or pre not feedback feed four
feet feet before I said can you because
we can't crowd surf right but maybe we
can how about we break Dimensions by
putting uh like these
cutouts of ourselves cardboard cutouts
maybe during the MC or so I don't know
put it on the stage and
then let us like crowd surf with the
cardboard
cutos
please that way we would be breaking
Dimensions wouldn't we cuz we're like
leaving the screen and Crouch and I I
think I even said like let us leave like
walk off the screen so to say uh in the
moment where we put the cardboard
cutouts up and give it to the crowd to
crowd
surf um but I don't know why they would
not accept my idea I think it was a
great
idea but they did not go with it
evidently maybe another
time ah also like man I've met Shi on
several occasions by now but like I just
wanted to say like oh my God her
movements are so cute especially when
she's like actually like it it was it
was really interesting to watch um shodi
and uh narissa do their thing like cuz I
feel like narissa gets so into it and
she's like she raises her arms a lot
have you noticed like and she like she
goes into this power stance a lot and Sh
is very like bouncy and
like she's
like it's so cute they have like really
different Antics it's so
[Music]
cute that's what I noticed about their
MC all you think about is the kiss but
that was funny that was for real
funny yeah oh one more thing I I
apparently according to my tangents
wanted to talk about is how um I uh one
of my units that they put me in two was
uh basically Ian birds so narissa M and
me and U the song was chosen by me
because the girls just didn't make a
suggestion I keep on choosing songs for
these things like f also uh like
previously the unit song that I did with
who was it
Ena so on uh I chose that song that was
an idol song and then another time like
me my unit song with Chloe I chose that
song too
sometimes they just don't the others
don't make any suggestions or um they're
not sure and I just go with what I want
to
do yeah so in this case too nobody
really made suggestions so I made a
couple and then um we agreed that this
one would be a great choice because I
feel like um generally for a western
audience I feel like cool songs are more
um popular and fitting while when you're
performing in Japan um cutesy songs
cutesy Idol songs will be uh very well
received um cool songs as well but I
think on a western audience you might
want to bring out more cool songs than
cuty uh Idol songs even though I mean
I'm sure you guys would enjoy anything
but I thought if we want to do
something that leaves uh a great
impression then we should do a cool song
so that's why I suggested that one and
um I would suggest like English songs
but there's just really not much choice
in terms of English songs but it had a
few English words in there and the thing
is like narissa and M are such
incredible insane singers so I felt a
little bit nervous about joining in on
that um because they're just so good but
I hope I did not um like Stand Out
negatively next to them yeah but I think
we we had a really great performance
ments yeah and crowd went kind of crazy
over that one they went kind of crazy so
I F like oh yeah that was a good song
Choice a good
unit that's it's
[Music]
good oh yeah like I
actually you like those body rolls
they're uh by the courtesy of me
cuz like when we first got like a
choreography draft I was like
M this is not what I like and then I um
requested changes in especially like
that part uh in the chorus and kind of
asked for something pretty specific and
that's why it became that mhm
Body Rolls yeah let's go let's
go M and Fa that was that was funny that
was interesting I did not expect that at
all that was some quite
something their unit song I was like
what what is this that's really
unique it's not a
phase they should sing retrospective
yeah M and VA Where's my water
bottle I'm
dying oh as narissa would say I'm like
literally
dying oh my God I
[Music]
here I need to perform right disector
first h
[Music]
one day maybe but like gener I know it's
a it's really cool and it would do
really well um but in in cases where I
only get like one solo song per like
live
concert that's not really what I want
would want to perform because um I feel
like the reason also why you know some
people maybe do uh cover songs and I
always go for original songs of mine
first of all because I have plenty of
original songs and I feel like they
deserve to be performed cuz they're
great but also because I feel like like
this just like um at Fest and whole life
English concert and so on so many fans
of others are watching right um people
who not necessarily watch me um and so I
think it's like one of the biggest
exposure uh opportunities that I can
come across so that's why I would want
to perform an original song um to
represent myself as
myself
um and also well retrospective maybe an
original song but it's not really my
general direction in music so if I only
get one song to perform I feel like I
want it to be a song that uh represents
me the
best the way I am and what I usually
[Music]
do okay so
next next m
[Music]
want to do some bird
watching
that's yes I also hung out with Amy and
my
choreographer oh you've been watching
for 2 hours shut
up H that was really
special
yeah that's really special I somehow was
kind of twinning with my choreographer
for some reason we had like very similar
outfits for some
reason and um yeah Amma again being very
knowledgeable uh in New York was a great
tourist guide once again more than Kiana
my choreographer who lives in New
York for her whole life um wait where
did the bgm go what the
hell so she lives in New York her whole
life but like she did not like know much
uh and was lost and am was definitely
our tour guide um and so we went to some
places that I still had on my bucket
list so to
say
uh okay that's no that's something
else okay
and New York people might recognize some
stuff here a cube and uh some bony
structure uh yeah and the new World
Trade Center
[Music]
yippee but this thing on the left uh we
were inside of that too
[Music]
I think that's the same building yeah
it's crazy there's some train station
right
uh yeah and
so if you're in it you notice it more
but this when you're in it it definitely
100% feels like you're inside of the
body of a whale and I was pointing it
out and turns out that's really what
it's supposed to kind of
be when you get further like this this
is kind of supposed to be the rib cage
of it and when you get further to the
front uh I feel like I saw like really
like a
spine of it like I guess everything at
the top here in the middle is also spine
but there was a part that looked even
more like a
spine yeah I I I I don't know like is it
okay to stay I'm sure it's okay to stay
I guess but uh I did see because it's
really close to this obviously I did see
the memorial and it was so
beautiful it was so fascinating and
beautiful I stared at it for quite a
while
yeah all the like water fall it's like a
huge waterfall it goes down and then it
goes straight and then it goes down
again it's it's really beautiful it
felt yeah humbling yeah it felt really
M
special I don't think I've ever seen
something like that ever before
[Music]
yeah that was gorgeous so I'm glad I saw
that and there's like all the names of
the people who were inside of it like
written on the
fence yeah respect pay my
respects I wish I could have like
watched it for ages
because has such a special effect on me
I feel like
[Music]
so but in here I don't know if this is
this the next picture no damn it but
okay I I used I made use of the subway
of New York and it was not such a scary
I thought it would be scary I really
wanted to avoid it but I felt safe
because I was with am and Kiana my
somebody who lives their whole life in
New York and somebody who spent some
years in New York and both of them you
know I feel like they would protect me
um it wasn't dirty at all and uh orange
seats are very exciting I felt like it
was waa colored
so yeah um nothing weird happened I mean
I wasn't on it for very long and I I
only used it like once but it it felt
like everything was chill and
[Music]
cool wasn't crowded no
no I'm sure there's something weird
going on there quite a bit quite often
but it didn't happen in my
situation nothing weird happened so I'm
glad uh yeah I got pretzels from Auntie
ants like we came by the store and like
this smell imagine a smell because like
the smell was amazing and literally it's
so funny because like I was
being enticed by the smell and
ironically their advertisement says like
something like you can't resist the
smell or something like that and I
literally
couldn't I literally
couldn't so I got myself some of these
pretzel bites mhm and I shared them with
Kiana because um am obviously can't eat
it yeah but she was recommending it too
like she had it before I
think and oh yeah I'mma I also got a
drink so Amma recommended me the mango
Agogo so I got the mango Agogo was very
good strong mango uh taste very
good yeah I can't eat it so sad but I
shared it with Kiana they were really
good they were really fluffy and
buttery and I mean we pretzels are kind
of from the German speaking area
originally and so I would say oh my god
gigy Ra too
I would say that our pretzel are of
course even superior but these are
really good too these are really nice I
I was enjoying them a
lot hello hello welcome you want to see
something orange here I was in the New
York
subway so exciting let's
go a delicious bread yes yes was really
yummy the drink too we shared everything
and and yeah went to the Statue of
Liberty and with that I would like to
present to
you please everybody
stand for the national anthem of USA USA
USA wait
okay
[Music]
go I can see
thank you America we love you good
night am Miss sang for once a national
amam let's
go good night yeah I felt like a talk
show host in that
moment I was so emotionally moved by
am's beautiful uh rendition of the
anthem I was like I'mma sing sing now it
was still crowded so I feel like uh
nobody really she she sank pretty
quietly so I don't think anybody really
noticed like everybody was minding their
own business pretty much mhm never felt
more proud me too like I felt so
American in that
[Music]
moment
uh wait on the way though like uh I uh I
I took another video like I was like
bird
watching and I think this is in my
pictures too
though oh no this is something else oh
oh wait okay there's this whole story
but I saw Birds uh like pigeons that
really concerned me um I was like is
this normal pigeon Behavior are there
any pigeon experts because um these were
really like weird um like they were kind
of looking they were chilling like and
like kind of laying
sideways and they looked like they were
melting but not not really from the heat
they just felt like like they were
melting they were all like sitting and
it just felt so unusual sometimes they
would get up and like PE the floor and I
don't know it just weird it was weird
they do that really is it just New York
pigeons they did seem to have fun in
their little bird bath because here
um they were just so cute and fluffy
they're fatter than Austrian pigeons I
will say
that oh my God this is so
cute oh the
baby yeah a so many bird oh they're
drinking I like how they're doing it all
together like
[Music]
together they're so cute I was watching
them so long because they were so
fluffy and like into the water so cute
but then some of them W like just
melting on the floor and I felt like are
they okay what's wrong with them I I
guess it's probably fine right I just
wonder if they're okay but they're
probably fine um
so uh um I already showed you our
arrival so to say at the Statue of
Liberty
but it let me tell you a
story preach of ba no um let me tell you
a
story
uh yeah so
um
we we may have gotten
scammed
um so
basically we
walked um towards Battery Park and this
is so funny because previously I was
told by some of the girls who attempted
to go to the Statue of Liberty that
Battery Park was closed and they were
like really
aggressively
uh a what's the
word a a really aggressively
a uh a a what's the word of a
uh
[Music]
oh they people went up to them really
aggressively like hey go by uh trip to
Statue of
Liberty
um approached that's the what I was
looking for thank you very aggressively
approached um by all these like scammers
right and I was like huh okay good to
know cuz I'm still planning to go there
good to know I'll be careful of
that and I thought anyway I'm with Amy
who definitely can stand her ground
and I if anybody I would trust her to
save me from
this and then Kiana who was born and
raised lives her whole life in New York
like this not going to happen to
[Music]
me so we walk over and we like we're
kind of like
walking um from pretty far
away and then when we reach the point of
Battery Park we see that it's closed off
kind of partially like there's like some
construction going on and we walk over a
street and we see
we see lots of
people in blue
vests
um talking up people and the moment we
cross the street they
immediately come up to us and I like hey
you got a ticket and then am is like
yeah yeah which we don't but um I think
she did say that she said that because
uh she thought they were scammer at
first she's like yeah yeah yeah and
they're like they're like questioning it
um and like asking for which which fair
and this and that and then she's like I
lied yeah I got no ticket she's like say
saying she lied to them and then they're
like she's like I'm sorry I lied I got
no
ticket I don't know why but I think she
got intimidated by them cuz they were
questioning it and then they uh Speech
check failed she folded it yeah like
really fast
though and then and then they like okay
like we can get you a ticket we'll get
you a ticket and um and then they start
they start like selling us stuff like
attempting to sell us stuff I'm I was
not really participating in the
conversation cuz I thought oh those two
will handle
it and
then like I'm still kind of like trying
to make sure it's legit she just like
softly asks like is is this is this the
official you know and and then their
argument is well look at this vest that
we're wearing and look at this like idea
that we have hanging around our neck
that like if we weren't official the
police would get rid of us here and I'm
looking at their ID and I'm thinking to
myself I I was I was so close to saying
it out loud I was thinking like and
anybody can print out a [\h__\h] ID and
hang it around their neck this doesn't
even look like that proper
anyway um but I didn't say
it um but I I was like I mean they were
not like it they didn't seem as
aggressive as I would have expected from
what the other girls were telling me
about you know they weren't like that
aggressive um maybe because they didn't
have to because we were quite receptive
um so like they tell us uh the different
prices and the different like you know
like times like if we go on this one we
can spend like 4 hours there and we're
like What 4 hours we don't want to be 4
hours on the island just a shorter time
is okay and then they're like yeah okay
then there's this one way you can spend
an hour but it takes it takes half an
hour to get there then you're an hour
there and then another half an hour to
get back
um but yeah also you for this ticket you
can only be on the ground you're not
allowed to go up uh the Statue of
Liberty but you are going to be on the
like they literally said that you're
going to be on the
island uh because we confirmed that like
do we actually get to be on there
because like afterwards we also did so
much more research
but um that you you cannot Dock at the
Statue of Liberty Island unless you are
an official boat officially approved
boat which there's only like one fairy
that keeps on going back and forth there
only one thank you for the Super Chat
only one company is allowed to do that
but anyway um like I'm then checks the
official schedule because we already
checked it beforehand uh when the next
fairy would
be and like first he says like something
like a Time that just doesn't match the
schedule that we have and am double
checks it is
like and then he adjusts his time to the
one that we saw in the official schedule
which is already sus right um but yeah
hejust adjusts it to what uh we saw on
the official
schedule and then so he gives us the
prices and he says like some price like
what was it like
maybe maybe something like 30 bucks or
so I don't remember so well anymore um
but then he goes up with the
price and uh then am kind of questions
that and he was like oh yeah because
taxes and this and
that
um uh and then she tries like I'm I'm
saying like Okay I'll pay for me and
Kiana and EM pays for herself because
Kiana I felt like U she didn't even know
that we were going to do this so I
didn't want to like force her to pay
something so I was going to cover for
her so Amit tries to pay First with her
card but it doesn't work so I'm like
okay that's fine I'll just um cover all
of us for
now and his like card reader is still
printing out the slowly printing out the
like failed receipt of amus attempt to
buy it and I'm like looking at it and
like waiting for it to come out and and
and kind of studying it because I I
didn't realize it was the am receipt and
he keeps on telling me that's trash
that's trash like basically kind of
trying to keep me from looking at it and
I'm like I realized then later that oh
okay it's not not the right one okay
anyway I take it anyway and he's like
that's trash you don't need it throw it
away that's trash and I realized
afterwards why he didn't want me to look
at it because he raised the price
again um and I would have seen that I
kind of did see it I I actually I saw it
um what he was charging me when I ended
up paying um but I didn't question it
too much because he did say something
like taxes taxes that's why it's
more
so he ended up charging me 55 bucks per
person so I got charged 160 plus bucks
for all free of us I get the receipt and
he tells us now we didn't know this
before he didn't mention this before we
were literally like five walking minutes
away from the real dock but he tells us
to get into this bus it's like a Hop On
Hop off
[Music]
bus my card is a debit card not a credit
card so I can't do a charge
back so he tells us to get on this bus
and I'm
like I didn't question that too much
because I didn't realize how far we
[Music]
were or how close we were but the other
girls were questioning it because they
were more aware of how close we were
actually so we get into the bus there's
a few people already in it and I thought
we would because looking at the time the
fairy would leave in like 15 20 minutes
or so so looking at the time I thought
oh we won't be here so long so we first
we sit on the top cuz I wanted to feel
the
wind but the moment we enter the bus the
lady in the bus says oh tip me basically
and we're
like I'm personally like not feeling
happy to tip her because she didn't do
anything for me yet and we just don't
tip that much in Europe
up but I'm is like ah maybe later I
don't you know we're thinking we're
thinking about it you know so we we go
up and we
um um we sit up for a while and we know
this time is taking and somehow the B
the bus is just not moving when is this
bus going to
go and So
eventually I think Kiana goes uh down to
the bus lady and asks her like when are
we going and she's like
oh or or did she I don't know what she
asked her but like just confirming
something and then we're still waiting
longer and it's getting closer and in
this time I'm starting to look up uh
this company name on Google honestly why
did none of us do this beforehand we
just it would have taken a moment
because I look up the company's name on
Google and immediately everything says
scam scam scam scam scam scam scam and
it says like they make you wait on their
bus for ages uh like hours and they keep
on like delaying it and you either don't
get don't end up going at all um or you
maybe get to go but you
M you don't get on the actual Island
even though they say it even how dare
they say that they say you get on the
island on the actual Island cuz they
literally showed us like a map and
everything and a picture like you can't
go here but you can go
here oh my God so we're we're on this
bus for like maybe 15 minutes but I'm
getting a heat stroke so I'm like M
there's so much about this being a scam
um and then like we're being told that
first of all there's a delay uh we're
getting like on a different like later
Fairy like just as the scam people just
just like the reviews are saying on
Google um delays happening and we
realized that what they're probably
doing is they're trying to fill up the
bus uh they delay until they have a full
bus and the whole receipt even says like
no refund we have the freedom to change
the time or schedule of anything and
this and that no refs
and um yeah they're probably trying to
fill up the bus eventually after hours
after they made everybody wait for hours
they might actually go to their shitty
boat um which is not the official boat
and they can't dock on the island so
they're just going to like drive like
drive go around the island a little bit
and then that's
it no no we didn't stay like eventually
we were like [\h__\h] this uh we're probably
not leaving any time huh and so we left
the bus and while we were leaving I was
like I I said to the other tourists who
were sitting in the bus like hey this is
a scam probably so you know but they
didn't seem to understand me so oh well
I feel bad for them then we walk out of
the bus and they're like basically
telling everybody to get out of the bus
in that moment because uh they're making
everybody switch to the different bus
that just arrived why I don't [\h__\h]
know some another another like way of
making the tourists feel like they're
about to go but they're not going
anywhere I don't know we didn't move at
all so we walk past the guys and we're
like like why are we even and I think
what we were trying to do at this point
is like we were still like giving them
the benefit of the doubt and we were
like let's just walk up to the dock
because there's no need to be on this
bus
let's just walk over there there they
cuz they said they told us that it's a
40 minute walk we have to get on the bus
because it's a 40-minute walk otherwise
you know how long it took us 5 minutes
to walk over to the dock and then um so
I was saying like why are there no signs
telling people like if there's so many
scams like this why are there no signs
telling people about
this um right right there where the
scammers are and then we walk a little
bit past the scammers and they're like
hey why are you not on the bus why are
you leaving them and I'm like well it's
probably a scam you guys are scamming us
so you're never leaving anyway are you
and they're like what what do you mean
scam playing dumb we walk past and then
uh once we get like kind of into Battery
Park even though it was closed down you
can still kind of walk through it uh
that's where the signs start so where
the people are standing is like the the
the earliest point where like closest to
Battery Park where there's no signs yet
so if only they would put these signs
right there
man cuz they're getting so many people
with it I can't imagine how many people
per day they're
getting n and then I was saying to the
girls like while we were sitting in the
bus and like figuring this out I was
like you know what like
honestly if they were
official there would be no need for them
to go up to people and try to sell [\h__\h]
to them because Statue of Liberty is
literally one of the most famous tourist
attractions of the world they have no
need to get people to go somewhere you
go as a tourist you go to them you don't
like they go up to people and talk to
them and like hey you need a ticket you
need a ticket if they were official ones
there's no need for them to try to sell
anything
right I was getting all these
realizations while we were still trying
to confirm if it's a scam or not I was
getting all these logical realizations
like oh we should have just looked it up
for one second before we bought anything
and oh I was I was kind of like uh
making up like some crazy conspiracy
theories too because in the bus
everybody's Wi-Fi was kind of dead
everybody's interet was kind of dead on
the phone I saying like maybe they're
like cutting it off Somehow Here the
signal so that people can't look it
up and then also like um I was thinking
like uh this this was proven to be wrong
because Amy just didn't have enough
credit on her credit card apparently but
I was thinking like maybe her card
didn't work because credit cards are
easier to get your money back than debit
cards and they just don't let credit
cards
work um that's why my card worked but
hers didn't then this was proven to be
wrong but it would have been
funny
um yeah yeah yeah right there are Wi-Fi
jamas so it it could
be it honestly could be no but I I
really like fall oh man we were kind of
dumb to fall for this because it was
actually so obviously a scam and we were
even warned by the other girls
uh I was trying to contact my um like
24-hour emergency call thing from my
bank um I was trying several times on
that day but I somehow I couldn't get
through like something was wrong with my
phone signal so I didn't reach them now
I'm wondering like even if it's after
can I if if it's like a couple days
after and they already charged it
there's probably no chance for m M debit
cards for me to get my money back right
I don't know but it's officially a scam
like look at this [\h__\h] sign man and
then so we walk through Battery Park and
we find there's like a little castle
thingy where they have their official
office like these [\h__\h] were in their
blue vests and like they had a tiny desk
with an umbrella standing on the side of
the
road and um stop stop about cancel shut
up I don't need to cancel my card it's
okay it's okay I'm not getting anything
any weird charges um it's okay moving on
we were in there and there they have
this like little castle and they have a
proper desk but like a whole building
and they're not aggressive they're not
trying to sell us anything we're going
there to set to buy they're nice about
it and the only bad thing there was a
mosquito trying to suck my blood so so
[Music]
hard yeah and there's signs all over
like this right there and so we get our
ticket and you know what it wasn't 55
bucks and and there was no time
constrainted either it was 25 bucks per
person to get on the island with that
fairy no time constraints like they told
us like oh 1 hour max or so uh and and
so much cheaper so
oh yeah I ended up paying yeah the 25
bucks for all of
us and the 55 bucks for all of us so in
total I spent
um a lot of money to get to the Statue
of Liberty for all of
[Music]
us and I feel so stupid though I feel so
stupid but so prep person that means it
was kind of like 80 bucks um I must
say if somebody told me like if this was
legit that you need to pay 80 bucks to
get to the Statue of Liberty honestly I
feel like it's worth it um fair
price if I didn't know the reality of
it it was
beautiful and it was
nice um you can say there as long as you
want
[Music]
I don't know I I might still attempt but
I feel like I'm too late uh because it
didn't work on like the actual day um
like calling the
bank yeah I don't know ah copium no like
it's beautiful America has you know
beautiful moments here and
there 80 bucks is worth it mhm 80 bucks
is so worth it no really though like if
I if it was really 80 bucks I would pay
that yeah but like I felt so salty about
it the whole day um those [\h__\h] man I
can't believe it like I feel so bad too
when I think about how many people
they're scamming each
day cuz there were a lot of like like
adult really adult like
families with children in the bus like
tourists though that didn't seem to but
then again though it's there were a
million people a million more people
successfully taking the the official
route those those fairies were so packed
Island was so
packed it was a learning experience yeah
I I just want to say like to anybody
here who wants to go to New York in the
future let this be uh a lesson uh or
like a warning don't get scammed just
walk over to the official dock they have
an office there it's proper and there's
no no man trying to sell you
anything yeah hope it didn't deter you
from coming back no not at all that was
like the only negative experience I had
and I thought well at least it's a
stream
tangent uh this is the only negative
experience really
everything else was delightful and I do
want to come back because there's
Broadway shows that I want to watch and
um other like sitcom places there they
want to visit and and
[Music]
stuff Tax what tax seduc me getting
scammed if I can write it off my taxes I
don't know um Oh you mean oh because I
shared it on my stream oh I guess so
it's a topic now so I I don't know about
that
um I don't know maybe maybe I have some
time later today I I'll try calling I
guess
but yeah it's a national park officially
I saw a cute Ranger lady the cute Ranger
uniform that's that's that's why why you
can't go there unless your
official
um
[Music]
man
H well don't worry don't worry uh it is
what it is um here's a a cool video of
coins
can you tell like why is this all filled
with coins this was by the
dock
see as if it's like a wishing
[Music]
fountain
why why is all filled with
[Music]
coins yeah I saw I noticed that my
throat hurts I'm drinking too little
because I I ran out of water all I have
is ice
[Music]
tea but the good kind of ice tea not the
corn fructose syrup ice
[Music]
team blue vest guy [\h__\h]
you who is
that which one of you is that
which one of
[Music]
you Mama
Mia thank you I'll try
to get my money back but I doubt I can I
I don't think I will be able to get it
back it's okay thank you
aluda I did not make a wish because all
my wishes were already
fulfilled in that moment me hanging
out with girls like am and Keana in the
other days too like it was a really
happy weekend or okay it was more than a
weekend but was a a
really wholesome happy couple of
days
so I was a great time had great memories
uh you saw somewhere in
here oh I wanted to get uh Starbucks
because Starbucks is so American to me
free tickets to the moon what the hell
are you should I scam you you're getting
scammed right here right now I thought
Starbucks was kind of American so uh
after feeling very like hot uh uh after
walking for a while um I was like I got
to get something to drink drink and
there was a Starbucks so I felt like I
needed to check if they have any special
Frappuccino or so that I don't see in
Austria usually or in Japan even and I
think this one we don't have it was like
a caramel crunch thing you s so I
ordered the Frappuccino and then it
arrives and I taste it and I can already
smell it there's coffee in it so I asked
the girls like
girls in American Starbucks do they make
the Frappuccinos with coffee by default
because in Austria and in Japan when I
order um a frappucino it's not with
coffee by default you guys are like yes
yes of course
[Music]
yes what the [\h__\h] my PC was just like
shutting down I stopped it but it closed
some
[Music]
stuff what the [\h__\h] chat where are you I
closed all my my
windows
[Music]
bro what why are you suddenly trying to
restart [\h__\h] you I'm in the middle of a
tangent
H
[Music]
H hello
hello
hello are we back what the [\h__\h] yeah the
PC was just trying to restart against my
permission how dare
you damn thank God like sometimes
there's this warning that like oh you
still have these window opens open are
you sure that you want to restart and
that made me stop it otherwise it would
have just done it without my consent
what the [\h__\h]
man [\h__\h] Windows 11 PC scamming me
what was I saying ah Starbucks so you
guys all are like yes yes yes but that's
not like not the same in
Austria so I was like man I hate
coffee why is this forino with coffee
and I felt like I would not have um said
uh to like change it but am and Kiana
were both saying like oh you should you
should ask them to like remake it and
then they gladly remade it and you guys
are like what would it be that's exactly
what they were asking me like Amy and
Kiana were like what if there's no
coffee in there what would it be FR
Frappuccinos are very common without
coffee guys you don't get
it yeah there it's not like a milkshake
but maybe like I could compare it with
that if you guys are really confused
about it I'm I'm I might compare it with
that but that's not really what it is no
it's different from a
[Music]
smoothie yeah they don't make it with uh
coffee by default in
Austria only time I have that happen
sometimes is when I uh order like a
mocha Frappuccino or so but even that
like the like the chocolate mocha
whatever even that they by request they
can make it with out and then it's like
a
frozen I guess it's like something
between a slushy and a
milkshake yeah but usually if I order
any other like vanilla Frappuccino or so
it's never with
coffee yeah the mocha one I understand
the MAA one I
understand but the others no they don't
make them with that with coffee so
anyway God damn it oh did you even see
this picture this was also in Central
Park like we were observing these ducks
where one of them as you can see has a
fish in their mouth and the others were
like chasing the duck and the the duck
kept on like losing it because it was
trying to swallow it and it was too big
and it was like falling down into the
water and it kept on picking it up again
and the Ducks were always going for it
[Music]
yeah uh so I had the frappucino and then
another thing I want to show you here I
had this like Mex I just really wanted
to eat Mexican
food um cuz I felt like I had Italian a
lot on these days and fast food but like
I felt like oh I'm in America I need to
eat fat uh I need to eat uh What uh uh
uh Mexican
food yeah so I went with some managers
and um okay I went with a few managers
like jenma of
course HMA was also there HMA ordered
that green stuff like what was that
again enchiladas yeah HMA really wanted
to eat
enchiladas and we got like a beef tacos
pork tacos and chicken tacos I know that
Mexican food is generally like do you
have a you have a lot of spicy food but
I did not expect the tacos to just be
spicy by
default um so I bite
into chicken taco and then uh the first
bite was still okay but then I take more
bites and I'm like dying from the
spiciness they had some spicy stuff in
there and it was killing me H but it was
so yummy man I was
dying I was trying to like there you
don't see it on the picture but there
was like a white like sour cream kind of
sauce too so I was trying to like help
myself with that but even that didn't
help it's so sad so I was like man I
only ate one taco what do I do
um the enchiladas were not spicy but I
didn't like them very
much uh so I ordered another thing that
just really spoke to me even though I
hate raw
fish I just thought I had to try this um
what was it
called you guys maybe know um but this
is raw tuna a cish yeah
cish yeah it's a raw tuna
s so I don't know I thought even though
I never order raw fish because I don't
like it I I don't know this looked so
good on the Google review
pictures and I thought the serving would
be relatively
small and I I again I didn't have much
of an appetite in general so I thought
you know I'll be okay so I
tried is that the restaurant ano yes
ano yeah feel free to go there uh next
time you guys are in New York and and
think you're going to a place where Wawa
went now I I tried it and honestly uh
I'm glad I tried because I gave myself
an opportunity to try raw tuna which
I've never had before it's okay but it
was actually surprisingly fishy the
others also said when they tried that oh
yeah this is kind of fishy um I'm like
well it's less fishy when you eat it
with this like brown thing cracker thing
on the side
but yeah okay I would not order it again
it was not personally in my
thing I just wanted to experience
it a tostada uhuh
tostada not I see I see it's not
supposed to be too fishy yeah I feel
like the aftertaste was very fishy also
there was [\h__\h] jalapenos every
[\h__\h] where like on top of here and on
the
guacamole the guacamole had so many
jalapenos Mama Mia but generally really
good food and so I I made an a
realization I made this realization on
Broadway already when on the list of
musicals there was a musical called
Hell's Kitchen and I thought what the
[\h__\h] I mean I'm not surprised there's
like the office Musical and so on so I
guess you can make a musical about hell
kitchen with Gordon Ramsey then I looked
it up and it's not about Gordon Ramsey
at all okay but then there's also this
like Street I guess like this restaurant
has like Hell's Kitchen in its name and
I'm like so confused like what and now I
finally realized yeah it's a
neighborhood but I'm I'm still
confused what
what I'm still confused so why
H the Gordon Ramsey show is it called
Hell's Kitchen because a lot of the
restaurants are in this neighborhood I
don't
know it's where Daredevils hang
out
what what who wait I you talking about a
person or people who are just their
Devils
what superhero
[Music]
okay I'm more confused
again I'm more confused
now
ah
okay Google
him no I don't care
anymore okay so yeah it was yummy no I'm
glad I ate some Mexican
food m
[Music]
M let me
see let me see my tangents I think I'm
pretty much done and I got to go
anyway
[Music]
ah language problem one of these days I
uh Uber
Eed something from
McDonald's because I just wanted fries
and I know the fries from McDonald's are
good so I order um like a chicken
burger
um and like I see on the picture it has
lettuce it has tomato it has a chicken
patty and that's pretty much it like
some sauce okay not the Mec chicken a
different one that we don't have uh but
this pretty much could be a me chicken
if you just add
tomatoes m so I look at my order and
when I put in the the the the burger
like it says like it has this like
typical list of ingredients and you can
get rid of the tomatoes the lettuce and
so on you can add things I'm not adding
anything but I see a weird
thing um that was not apparent to me
when I looked at the picture of the
burger I did not see any potatoes like
sometimes there's like hash browns or so
inside of a burger right or like even
fries or so you know sometimes they have
that kind of stuff so but I didn't see
it in the picture of the burger but one
of the things it says tomato lettuce and
so on and then one of the things
say potato roll and I can check whether
or not I want the potato roll and so I'm
like what do you mean I don't see any
potatoes in the burger but I'm thinking
like well I mean in case I'm just not
seeing it in the picture I think I'm
fine with the burger without any like
hash browns cuz I just assumed they mean
like there's a hash brown secretly in
the burger so I remove it and then it
arrives and I'm not even sure it's my
real order because I don't recognize it
because it is not a burger anymore
potato roll apparently means the bun and
I removed it so I basically I went uh
gluten-free or whatever you call that
kind of diet when you don't eat the
bread and you just order the burger
without the bread and I was like [\h__\h]
this maybe I'll order the whole thing
again but no I ended up just eating it
like that so was like salad and the
freaking filet of a [\h__\h] chicken and
salad was like all over it was a hot
mess and the [\h__\h] Tomatoes all over
the place and the sauce all over the
place it was hot mess I'm telling you
[\h__\h] why is it potato roll the the bread
is not made out of potatoes like some
breads are like with potatoes but like
this bread like is the are the buns at
McDonald's made from potatoes I'm so
confused if they would have called it
bread roll I would have understood but
why is it potato
[Music]
[Laughter]
roll what it's so
confusing
[Music]
man I Uber e it so much like I Uber
eated my breakfast a lot I always got
some sweet like waffles with berries and
stuff and um pancakes and stuff I was
really happy there was so many so many
choices so many good
[Music]
choices oh here another tangent that I
wrote down is Pua playing Pikman the
whole time she's like constantly while
we're like going for Central Park she's
just constantly on her phone uh like I
thought she was like Pokmon going or
something but no she was
Pikmin uh was kind of cute and I was
like asking M you don't play Pikmin or
what and she's like nah no no no I don't
I'm like oh so like this is one of the
things you guys don't have in
common and it seems to be kind of the
same thing
basically oh you know one another man
there's so many Amit tensions I'm sorry
but like there was this one moment where
it was like um after dinner um or like
at the end of dinner and my phone died
and I kind of had to uh go a little bit
earlier than the others so I was like um
I'm I'm I guess I'm going to go back now
to the hotel and Amma looks at me like
she gives me this
really angry look I'm like what and
she's like you're not going alone I'm
like what
she's just like so insisting on me not
going along because I guess it's like
dangerous and
whatever so cute I'm like oh okay I well
if you do want to accompany me she's
like I'm going with
you also I'm a like she always brings
like little presents when she like meets
us wherever she she gave me a couple
presents she gave me a a frog
candle so
[Music]
cute I love
her I love
her
and and then uh you know Cron's on a
diet right she's been like talking about
dieting for a while now and like she's
she's definitely actively dieting and
then um there was this moment when we
were like just hanging out at dinner and
chilling and talking and um somehow
we're talking about how much weight uh
crony lost and where she wants to go and
I'm like
girl you've you've lost plenty of weight
like girl you can stop I think and like
there's like this issue that I think
you're having crony where you just like
this I think a lot of people they just
get lost in their diets and they always
think it's never enough It's never
enough and then they'll end up you know
losing too much weight but you just
don't realize it on your own and I'm
telling you you're fine and she's like
no no no I'm I still need to lose weight
and and I'm like well you're finner than
me at this point and she's like what no
no way that's not true and I'm like I'm
telling you like get up and
then we like um um compare each others
like tummies and all that I'm like you
you you're plenty thin now like don't
worry you're always wor but like girl
just stop you're fine you're
beautiful just like we're squeezing each
other's flesh and stuff comparing each
other yeah and then we're also like for
some reason standing back to back and
comparing our height which obviously
she's taller than
me but that made me go doie
doie yeah no she's
um she she she's got to stop she's
already
gorgeous you know cuz like I feel like I
I I feel bad I used to um have a lot of
like high school Japanese friends from
high like high school going Japanese
friends and like everybody I noticed
like teens and also girls in their 20s
in Japan everybody's like constantly on
a diet
and like that's their whole lifestyle
and and they always think they need to
be on a diet even though they're so
skinny already it's just like this
mindset like different standards too I
guess so I just feel bad for girls who
have a wrong image of themselves and
think they have to be thinner and
thinner and thinner and it's not true
they're already plenty thin they're
really thin like okay there's you might
like compliment someone who's like like
not like super fin but like medium Fin
and you're like oh you're so F just as a
compliment and stop maybe they could
still lose some pounds you know but I
mean it though like there's so many who
are really thin if you get any thinner
than that it's not healthy anymore but
they don't realize that because they see
themselves differently and that's sad so
I need to make sure that crony
knows she needs to know
yeah anyway I'm going to go now because
I got stuff to do I have to go dance
lessons and so on I'm kind of busy today
um but I'm so glad I got to talk to you
guys um I'm actually putting out a
schedule at the end of the day I'm still
waiting for something to be announced so
that I can uh put it on my
schedule um but I'm going to be
streaming every day for the rest of the
week um uh and then the coming days
actually I might be streaming like every
day until the end of next
week um
because yay why
not uh except actually uh I think
currently my
Saturday is like you know I might be on
a different Channel you know um but I
also have like dance lessons like every
[\h__\h] day I have dance lesson today I
have two dance lessons tomorrow I have
another dance lesson on Saturday I'm
like in the
last uh couple of days before my 3D
recording for my uh um like birthday SL
aniversary uh YouTube live um I'm
recording it next week so I'm like in
the last Spurt of dance lessons and I'm
dying I need to learn some like a couple
more
dances m
it's really stressful so um those two
days I won't be streaming the uh
recording days but every other day I'll
be streaming every day so you
know the last SP before I can finally go
home to
Austria and the last bit of work that I
have to do important work that I came
here for AKA my anniversary SLB birthday
live yeah yeah yay which will not be
streamed on my birthday which because
it's already over and also not be
streamed on my anniversary because it's
not going to make it in time for the
anniversary either but officially it's
more of an anniversary life than a
birthday life so uh I don't know what
we're going to call it
um but officially it's an anniversary
life because it's too late for a
birthday life even though it's
officially a birthday
life slot but you
know um yeah I thought I was going to be
able to um Read Super chats but I
already ran out of time I tangent it too
much but as I said I'll be streaming a
lot the coming days so there should be
time I think I'm going to play Blue
protocol
tomorrow in the evening jst I think cuz
I you know during the day I got dance
going on dance dance
dance yeah blue protocol is dead
officially dead they're going to shut
down the Japanese servers they announced
in
January uh they were going to La launch
the Western servers this year's summer
but that never happened and now we got
official news that the Western servers
are never going to happen and they're
shutting down the Japanese servers
that's [\h__\h] sad I waited for this
game like for 10 [\h__\h] years or so I
swear um so that's pretty much killing
my
morale but that's why we got to try to
check out the Japanese server before
it's completely
dead yeah I got the perm
for it so in German we say Al V and
thank you for joining me on my review of
USA and our concerts I really had a
great time in America I really like New
York I hope I can come again and uh
thank you so much for enjoying and
supporting our concert if you haven't
seen it yet um the archive is still
available I don't know for how long but
you can watch the stream like re-watch
it
if you get a ticket and as you should
because it was really
great
yeah I'll read in I'll talk to you
tomorrow thank you for listening to my
yap yap yap yap hope you enjoyed T the
tangents and the little
videos and yeah thanks for the super
chats I'll be reading super chats soon
and sorry by the way I'm aware that I
still didn't do the Polaroids for you
guys that um not the not the merch
Polaroids but our
Polaroids I don't have any access or
time for it I I swear I'll do it in the
first week when I'm home in
Austria I just don't have a um tablet
here with
me but I will still finish those don't
wor yeah thank you for your patience I
appreciate
it yeah I'm going to go dance bye-bye
[Music]