e e
[Music]
for
K everybody hello welcome to the
enigmatic recollection lunch
party
[Applause]
P look at them look at
[Music]
them
cute cute yeah before we get to the
intruction get there uh today we have
actually so many exciting things to
share with you guys so let's zo one by
one step by step first of all the
introductions I am Tak from Whole Life
English myth I am a phoenix I am youro
and if you are not nice in the chat then
you must go to the usual room somebody
who has never been to the usual room is
right
here good morning afternoon evening
this life English mid
hello and hiis it's Iris from H live
English promise with with this thing
next to me what this thing is um and I'm
so excited to be here with everybody
today in this wonderful beautiful
space and next up this thing
here thank you it's you this is Oro
crony from Hol live English promise and
I'm so excited to be here get out of the
way this is my
Spotlight and we have these lovely
people right here
I'm Nota I'm H I'm not hula I'm W
together
with this is our first time
[Music]
in and look at this cool place
friend just made for us for this
project oh my
[Applause]
wowo yeah well you know welcome to this
special episode to celebrate the launch
of enigmatic
recollection I hope you guys are as
excited as I
am in this special launch party we we
will play games together and get to know
more about enigmatic recollection with
all of you there are new info to be
revealed about the project so stay tuned
yeah oh by the way did anyone go to the
anime
NYC last year what about
[Applause]
2023 perform
well you know since they did perform you
as as it's probably pretty obvious by
now we did have a booth where we
displayed the images of the enigmatic
recollection at the
event we are certain domination over the
world did any of you get a chance to go
I hope you guys had a great time there
was so cool thank
you but at the event we also gave away
special b b is there anyone up there
that received them yes yes
yes very precious we'll show you the
special shopping bag later on this
stream but shall we first maybe start
talking about enigmatic Rec good idea Mo
Coco you're so
smart we should do that so can we maybe
see the beautiful key visual please
[Applause]
so head tilt yeah we look so
epic don't break your
neck did you break your neck during
that you're
so antic recollection is a new Hol life
English original content project but if
that is too long for you you can just
say
and
and nice that stays in your brain I'm
sure we have so many pictures that we
can show you so let's put them on in
monitors
bam everyone's
here there we go that is amazing
beautiful amazing so it is a collection
of stories in which US the members of
Hall of English play as the main
characters through streams animations
and original songs you can immerse
yourself in this new and fresh
project
interesting and actually this project is
going to be a longterm
project I mean who knows we'll find out
forever yeah but for the first
installment chapter one is going to
start this
time chapter one means there's going to
be more chapters maybe I'm a crazy W
good for chapter one of enigmatic
recollection in original realm was
crafted within a Sandbox game medium you
can watch as this new tail unfolds
shaped by the choices and deeds of all
of us all 19 whole life English
[Applause]
memberss of this overworking story will
evolve according to all of our choices
oo so make good choices good choic can
make bad
choices bad
choic yeah and the story takes place
in everyone's favorite
Minecraft it is a giant map that was
made especially for this project and
Recco we're so excited to travel in that
I'm sure right
w we can move around as we wish
Adventure into different places role
play and fight with
enemies PVP i' love
it this time we're role playing his
characters from this world with the same
name Kar Senpai is still playing the
character right
nice yeah well we actually don't know
what our characters Back stories are
going to be either like we're clueless
so we will be finding it out together as
we play more and you guys will find out
too get ready and the story so what's
the story you guys are curious too right
sure I'm sure well crony has prepared a
brief for us CR please take it away
well Once Upon a Time the girls are
summoned to the Myster Furious Kingdom
of lest unable to remember anything from
before their arrival they become
entangled in the Kingdom's conflicts the
girls are asked to defend the innocent
from looming danger and are thus
entrusted with the Kingdom's
fate ominous creatures enigmatic stories
lost within the kingdom what fate awaits
them at the end of it all expect a grand
tale of Adventure and Valor staring all
19 hollow life English
members that sounded so good can you
like retell me everything tonight like
so I can fall
asleep I want to hear it
again like a voice pack can you make me
a voice pack with that of course I'll
pay I'll pay what you want what you
deserve that sounded beautiful was like
a seren to my ears
yes it sounded very interesting I'm sure
must be a very interesting story and
there seems to be a lot of mysteries in
the story as well I think we're all very
curious
yes if we're that curious shall we dive
more into the world
[Music]
now this is the kingdom of leest and
that's where the best in live in this
town there various shops and
establishments from vendors such as
weapon shops the quest raised by
citizens and you know since it's an open
world soundbox game we could do a bunch
of things you know such as building our
own houses
even it looks so nice to be like
commission ID to build that because that
looks Next Level yeah only ID is capable
of something like
that wow oh my god this is my first time
seeing this
yeah that pretty nice well next up the
leest cloak a a cloak of Heroes hand it
down in the Kingdom of leesta leesta
yeah thank you leesta we will wear this
Leo cloak and begin our adventures isn't
it so cute you look
[Music]
so I thought it was the best
oh look it's me is it so cute why you
get that modeling job you know don't
worry about it so nice was right behind
you know too yeah and this will actually
be available for our live TRD models too
can use
it nice next please we mentioned it a
little bit earlier but the liest are
those who live in the Kingdom of liestal
can we adopt them it kind of look like
kfp yeah so they actually they consist
of four guilds and each with their own
unique approach to adventuring should we
like uh check it out every single one
I'll explain to you I'll explain you the
four guilds the four
guilds number one the red one up there
there yeah point point that is the
Scarlet wand
the Gil's characteristic is curiosity
and
knowledge smart people going be there
can ibly
be
candidates I don't know
honestly um we'll see and the leader is
a wizard-like leader so
who that's why a big hat yeah big hat
the next one the orange yellow looking
one is Amber coin and the Gil's
characteristic is glory and
ambition ambition to be rich
coin feels like they fit into
that
yeah is the cutest thing
ever yeah but this one the leader is a
merchant like leader stons am I right
St yes the next one the blue one is the
ceran cup and this one the guil
characteristic is philan philanthropy
and devotion yes so cute look at that
heart look like
a big
devotion
yeser the leader for this one is a
monkik leader yeah you want to be that
one
yeah you can be anything you want to be
in I'm sure so last one the green one is
the Jade sword the Gil's characteristic
is courage and grit and the leader is a
night like leader oo Spade I see a spade
sign there look cool yeah what do you
think about
this I
like she's a shield
hero all four of these yeah when the
heroes AK
o are summoned at the start of the story
there will be a ceremony to assign
everyone into their respective
group feel can be in all of them at
once that's
cheating that's
cheating yeah what does chat think where
where do you think we fit best
into the comments I think everything
everything where we that just means
you're not
dedicated I want to sell stuff you want
to you
want money she wants to be rich to
different
maybe and well we don't have just guilds
we have some enemies so let's take a
look at
them wow they're called stain and are an
enigmatic Collective of hostile beings
and these malicious creatures assail the
kingdom of Leal taking on various forms
like right over
here I like the small one but they kind
of scary and they look kind
of they have nothing to do with me okay
I mean they're they're kind of cute
though
no we're going to be fighting these
creatures so I hope you guys are
confident that you can
win we pretty
strong yeah
sure yeah sure yeah but that wraps up
the world introduction what are you guys
think so far I'm so excited to play all
together yeah Minecraft projectes are
always fun I think myth did one more go
right so I'm excited to do it this time
with all of us together we even more big
together in a while true I think we're
all really motivated to join this as
much as we
can well this is enigmatic recollection
the new H life English original content
project let we hear how excited you
are I'm so so excited
what you know we're all excited how long
are we going to have to stay like this
know you know I got a question does
anyone know IUN You Know It please
announce it announce it for okay well
enigmatic recollection chapter 1
starts maybe tomorrow
[Applause]
for details please check out X formerly
known as Twitter please stay tuned
everyone behind is so
cute is so cute what is
C everybody
listen okay now we heard so much text
too much to read tldr how about we move
our bodies a little bit come
on we already moving no no no we were
barely moving we were standing in the
same
time no we got to have on yeah let's go
let's switch over let's switch it up a
little bit because we're going to do
some fun things yeah we're going to do
something special you know it's kind of
new to see all six of us in 3D together
right I want to see what we can do let
do how about the game show right
yeah show we shall start the enigmatic
recollection game show today to we will
have two games together as a team yeah
team play each game is a mission and if
we work together and succeed in our
mission we get to release and only then
if we succeed then we get to release new
information
for yeah there's more and there's no way
we could fail
right if we fail then the stream is over
and you will never know
more so support us
we got to make
sure we need the energy
[Laughter]
right
it's excited you know that we're going
to do this
okay okay the first game that we are
playing is test your teamwork enigmatic
recollection pose matching
yes we maybe SE you've seen this kind of
game somewhere before maybe you know
more about it I guess we're going to be
tested on our teamwork
as guess could be could be I mean we
have known each other pretty well I
believe we should have any problems
we're on the same brain wavelength
right yeah it's probably kind of easy
for the twins don't
you but that will be helpful because our
points all go
together we're on the
same better you the team okay I want you
guys use your brain cells and connect
them okay so I'll explain the rules
everybody listen up number one keywords
related to enigmatic recollection will
be given to all of us yes
with that keyword we will think of a
pose that represents the keyword mhm mhm
got it number three on the count of free
everyone will strike the POS at the same
time we cannot cheat we have to have the
same P ideally but since we're six
members and that's maybe a little bit
too difficult we will make it a little
bit easier only four members out of the
six will have to have the same post if
there's two that's different that's okay
but if there's four minimum we will get
at one
point and you need to earn 10 points
minimum out of 15 possible earnable
points in order to succeed this
Mission did you get the you understood
the rules right easy easy then let's do
a couple of practice rounds first okay
we're aligned up so I think we're good
to
go okay yep I think we're good to go
yeah give us the pose
please
be okay all right there it's easy we got
this okay then let's count from three
and then we make a bear pose are you
guys
ready three two
one
oh my be ears might be different but we
got five out six people
Kara what happened I don't know really
same
bra guess we had a connection we'll see
if you get everything correct
Iris yeah no leave it to me leave it to
me do we have another one well yeah
let's do one more done give us one more
[Applause]
please yummy and all together three two
one
you want me to poke your your
Armond noodles are sort of
Wiggly but that's okay because it was
again five out of six right so we got
the point okay
well you may have gotten it very wrong
but do think it's hopefully we're good
to
[Applause]
go all right from here on out is the
real deal real deal we better do it
right yeah please give us the first
pose I got it I got it okay all right uh
we okay down 3 2 1 yeah three 2 1
um was
so we have the little I'm
helping are you serious yeah this is a
cat
so I adop I
adopt oh all right we got it next one
kind of hard well let's do the next one
I think it's going to get harder okay
yeah dog
oh easy okay are you ready okay 3 2
one I changed my
POS just you
know why why did this why did
get this is the dog this is dog this
feels more like
it's
really dog play just as F especially
when you're demon
dog yeah okay so we don't get that point
okay next one please
next
hero okay okay okay all right are you
ready yeah 3 2 1
[Music]
my I just slashed the
sword like
flying I was like pulling out a sword oh
I thought I was flying oh well let's not
talk about that yeah okay that didn't
work out next one next
one okay the
opposite think about it wait I don't
know what to do okay okay okay
okay okay okay are you ready ready 3 2
1 um okay I cannot mention oh this
beautiful
tuni what does the step
say thank you thank
you than
generous all right next one please is
Magic oh
Magic um what what would we do with
[Music]
magic honestly no idea I have no idea
spontanously yeah three two
one okay I mean I think we got
it except but that's good
we get it yeah yeah yeah we got it we
got
it good job good job guys good job guys
next
[Music]
adventure
okay got it guys yeah ready for real how
do you do this got it okay are you ready
okay good
3 two
one they're fing they're
fing every
time look every time
for
this
[Music]
maybe maybe they have like a connection
issue they got to be like
together okay next one please okay
D wait how do we do
that they want us to
lose think guys think okay okay okay a
dungeon is usually inside wink wonk win
got this okay 3 2
one oh oh we're kind of
[Music]
simar what are you guys
doing you I am the dungeon we're in the
dungeon in the dungeon we are the
D don't know man I don't know that's a
monster in the dungeon I'm looking for
in the dungeon that exploration it's
really rough I'm scared of whatever
shows up in the dungeon you
know makes sense is very adventurous and
brave yeah what were you doing I was the
monster that's just dog PS yeah that
is
forg no wonder
dragon dragon you would think that's
easy I got this got I got this can you
give me a hint
know uh Thor
s wings okay we got this okay you guys
ready all right three two
one please please stop us up please
please
that looks
like it worked out it worked out okay
okay how many more do we
have castle
castle castle you guys got this okay
this going to be similar to something I
already
did I know it I know it I have it okay
okay okay
ready that's cheating guys I didn't
really hear
it okay ready 3 2
[Applause]
your good job good job another one
perhaps
okay we got more
princess
princess over here everyone's princess
here we just got to do a normal most
basic pose right cuz we're all
princesses by default princess by heart
already okay all right let's go do it 2
[Music]
I miss eat a
me okay we
got
monster that feel like I already didn't
you already have
that okay we got this you guys ready
somebody here did a monster POS before
right when there was a
dunge maybe you
know you guys
ready 3 2 1
[Applause]
was the one time you needed to do the
same let us down but it's
okay
next
close this might be is there anyone here
that has a cloak on
already I have a
cave this is a cave
a when my do hair is done you go like
like don't you do
this when your job is how you do it
that's how I
want okay okay yeah let's do it all
right three two
[Music]
[Applause]
1 the same POS anymore I'm not going to
do it
okay good job good job okay we got the
next
oneir okay aren't I literally kind of a
fairy kind of got no fairy wi fair fair
yeah I don't know it's angel demon but
you know we could we could we can
compromise we can compromise a fairy I'm
a fairy okay okay so what a fairy do a
fairy um you know she flutters
around fluts around under the you know
the butterflies and the flowers just
like butterfli around us okay okay
everyone
ready three two
one all right do
[Music]
this
victory victory victory okay victory
that I might be similar to there is that
one thing you do with the ring I don't
know you
guys I know what you're talking about a
ring a ring and you you know perhaps run
with the ring and at the end of the road
I as long as four of us got
that okay okay are you ready ready 3 2 1
Victory I don't I don't know I don't
[Applause]
[Music]
know I think we got was our final score
yeah how many points you get do you know
you it was 11 points
[Applause]
[Music]
I can't believe we
made
sorry good job everybody I think that
means Mission
success nice music all right what's the
new info right I'm so excited
okay well I will give you the new info
on a silver platter we have
dungeon you did
dungeons I
dungeons well I guess we're going to
have dungeons that we can explore and
Conquer you're going to conquer us all
crony conquer me
if you want see know what the dungeons
like what's inside the
dungeon maybe
some may I haven't seen I haven't seen
the dungeons yet either we haven't seen
the D out yeah let's it all
together by
[Applause]
[Music]
the last one that's where we are right
now
right so cool yeah coolest part is that
these dungeons are based on Mid
members did you see Atlantis is
real fre
out that looks so quality yeah each
every single one of us Smith members are
getting a special dungeon yes and as he
conquered the dungeons we'll find pieces
of our character's old memories cuz
remember we we don't know after we get
bed forget
memories so are you going to forget
about all of us maybe we'll have but
isn't it nice like I think when we all
first met each other that was like a
special moment so we can relive the
first meeting
yeah yeah that were really cool they
were really cool those yeah I can't wait
to actually like be there and see it
yeah they were like
volcano are those because of fire is
that
like okay the lava is my territory all
right let's go
lava too like that yours also it looked
like your loading screen or your ending
screen or I built a pory gate before yes
it took a while and now that you have
like all there many of them have finger
I know yeah we saw the egg and
everything so awesome well since we saw
that let's move on to the next
game for the next game we will be
testing our physical strength um express
it will be called express your
excitement shake shake
shake and as for the r of the shake
shake shake um each member will get
pedometer strapped to their forehead
their hands and their feet um you have
60 seconds to shake your body to show
how excited you are for enigmatic
recollection um you must Shake huh can I
Twerk to shake I as long as the
pedometer counts it
right on the butt
yeah I wish we could not this time sadly
not this time yeah maybe next time by
the way note you must include two poses
from the pose matching game while
shaking I don't remember either there
were so many we did we did stuff we did
a lot of stuff yeah all the steps from
each pedometer will be added for
individual scores but in the end all six
member scores will all be added together
and we need 3,000 points in order to
succeed this Mission easy easy easy is
easy you better not slack off
yeah everyone do your
part so I think are we all ready for
this
everybody I might need the stretch for
this okay okay nice stretches okay we
will do it in two groups to avoid
accidents cuz this is going to be very
vigorous um the first group will be Ena
huh myself
and get ready get ready yeah can you
guys um the rest of you guys can you
guys talk about the project while we get
ready blue
ladies l oh here over my here oh there
we can still chill here I think yeah
we're the waiting gang we're going to be
second so we can look at their strategy
and their technique true true perfect
okay we got this we got this we got this
we got this
yeah we're going to beat them even
though we're all a big theme we're going
to beat them anyway beat because we can
yeah we got we're going be so
[Music]
[Applause]
good stuck on our
foreheads look like I can play games
with your
head I'm going to count 6 seconds for
you guys okay okay all right all right
out a bit ready three two one
[Applause]
go 50 seconds
seconds come on you can do better than
[Applause]
that 30
seconds
harder your feet your
feet
[Music]
20 put your mind into it let's go
don't up 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 one ding
ding
wow good job good job I think with this
we might already be over 3,000
yeah okay while you're so tired let me
check your numbers then okay
so uh it on the left hand 53 what yeah
that sounds good on the left leg we have
a w
186 on the right leg we have a
180 nice leg work oh on the right hand
we have a
107 more active Okay and on your head we
have 136 shakes
good job okay I'll continue
with on on her head we
have has
154 on her head you just you just gained
another point oh another one I'm like
cheating and then 32 on the right hand
and uh 53 no 35 on the left
hand I did I went so hard H the right
leg is 142 and the uh other leg is
104 good job now my dear did you work
hard did you run fast I did my best I
sure she did so Iris has oh you're still
gaining numbers 148 on the head uhhuh
um on the let's little left foot
128 wow on the right foot we have
189 and the hands let me see your hands
um I have 821 820 8,000 not 2,000 over
here 128 on her right
arm and 51,000 over here no no no no no
no that's 150 on the left hand
13 okay okay is that it written down
hopefully then it's all good job
girl I think now it's our
turn now we got to get set up I think
all right you
guys you entertain
[Music]
them oh my God that
was I think I did pretty
good I think I think all of us together
we're more than halfway so as long as
they do the
same what oh I had like I had like
51,000 right here oh yeah yeah 51,000
are easy so easy we pass it just F you
just flicked Your Hand p yeah Powers I
think oh they're ready all let's go how
does it
look beautiful beautiful I love
it so
much it fits it fits so
[Applause]
maybe we can sell them as
merchandise daily walks okay all right
okay I'll do my best I'm going to count
60 seconds for you guys okay ready okay
three two one
go can do it
[Music]
[Applause]
out
[Music]
yeah you can do
it you can do
it almost
almost 3 2
[Applause]
[Music]
1 good job guys how was that you guys
feel nice easy easy exercise well easy
let's let's count each of your guys'
numbers now shall we count yes yeah let
me count your leg first um on your left
leg we have huh what oh I accidentally
pressed a button oh shoot oh shoot it
was like it was like it was like 140 it
was 140 140 I didn't see 400 yeah yeah I
think I pressed something and then her
other leg has
162 yeah and then her arm has 81 oh
818 81 not 18 and what the what seven
and her her other arm has seven no no no
no no there's no way you saw my uh
handshake you saw it it's apparently
just seven strakes oh your head um your
head is
[Music]
118 your hands okay and then
croni head 161
leg
142 and the other leg has 149 oh five
five five yes 105 145 45 and then one
arm uh 94 the other arm is
74 you guys got a lot of legging yeah
never skip all righty then and then we
have I
no okay oh Oh you shook your head a lot
you have a 235 on your
head and then we have on your arms we
have uh 191 and oh
157 and then we have on one leg
132 and the other leg 61
we make it I wonder which team got more
I
think it was okay because we could take
a break right that was the deal right F
that's all that
matters well let's reveal the final
score then shall we we do it Dr
roll was 3,700
and
[Applause]
[Music]
we I'm going to take this off now I
think really
quickly well I guess like what's the new
information we can release
sow a new original song and release with
a music
video special song original song made
just for this project any magy
collection this one will be the first
original song just for chapter
one oh since you're announcing saying
that right now does that mean that
perhaps you are involved in that would
she be maybe
[Applause]
perhaps the singers for the first song
are Mori
K fabulous rap goddess Nissa
Raven
Beau and Elizabeth Rose blood
F beautiful fiery singing and and guess
what there's one more
person could it be perhaps me myself and
I
R we worked really hard in this you song
so I really hope that everyone will like
it it's really cool um the mvy will also
be available to watch on YouTube and it
will go live right after
this and after the show ends there's
going to be a link to redirect you to
the MB Premiere page so don't forget to
head over there don't depend on the
redirect though sometimes
it but there will be R if it doesn't
redirect there will be a link in the
description please do check it out we
got your cover don't miss it Y and that
wraps off the enigmatic recollection
game shop
all your and helping us succeed in the
mission all your energy coming through
to us thank you thank Youk you yeah I
had a lot of fun even though I'm a
little bit exhausted now but I hope you
guys we all and the people in the chat
we all had fun I hope so actually now I
have a little bit of a treat for us Tre
let me go bring it really quickly
[Applause]
what it's so fancy isn't it and I am not
the only one who has one of these
besides the chat of course now the girls
also have one look at
them let's
[Music]
yeah we got the shopping bag from anime
NYC we so cool I really like it we could
put all stuff in there right all kinds
of stuff oh yeah I wonder what we could
possibly put in a big bag like this
donut unexpected answer
donut dreams Dre hopes and
dreams put small in there okay everyone
everyone so what do we put in the bag
I'm
in yeah yeah
it's so we had enigmatic recollection
original merch made so let's check one
by one shall
[Music]
we because you're proud of
it all right I think I have the thir
very special special item to show you
number one is
jant the be
tapestry illustrated by Solani
Sensei it is the perfect size to be in
the center of attention when displayed
in a room or also great for enjoying the
the streams that we're doing while
you're in front of your computer so you
can have it right beside you so and
we'll be always reminded of this project
turn on the streams when you look at
this
T next is me with the acrylic
[Music]
stand Talent has their own acrylic stand
so there will be 19 of them each one has
their own cool poses so the fans can
display their favorites and their oneof
aind
Arrangement next who
YY what do you
got the cards the collection cards these
cards are also have the same
illustrations as theic stands and also
each town and every one of us here and
all of English we will have their own
cards the cards will also not be sold
randomly so you'll be able to pick
exactly whose card you want I want yours
yours yours
[Applause]
and each P will also have a face up the
back too
next yeah so next we have the collected
card holder right here yeah and you know
check out the special cool silver foil
finish and you can put all the
collection cards right in a snuggly and
makes the perfect pair just like us
sometimes
always so we have this pin badge right
here and we show the size and the design
gives the pen a little more subtle Vibe
making it easy for everyone to use and
you know what the silver finish it kind
of gives it a cool look
simple and up next we got Iris
and well last but not least we have the
metal charms yes these are also shiny
metal these metal charms feature the
motif of each weapon we have uh attach
them to the zip of your bags or pouches
for a subtle spice to your daily
life that that's a lot of merch yeah
let's
go as you mentioned at the beginning
this project is a longterm project story
will rely heavily on what choices we
make as we role play so it'll be a very
unique story that shows who we all are
at all live
English in addition we're excited for
how the project will evolve into more
music more merch and there might be you
know more exciting stuff down the
line all
events
gam Comics no the guy is the
living we'll reach it for sure okay wow
that was a lot to take in today did you
guys have
fun yeah I hope you guys are excited as
we
are and thank you so much for being here
with us today chat and everyone and I'm
so glad to share this special time with
you all thank
you and don't forget the MV for the
first original song will be premiering
right after this yeah so make sure you
click the link and head over to the
waiting room I'm so ready I'm so ready
toar
these it's going to be awesome you guys
are going to be mind blown so you know
make sure make sure to go to get blown
but yeah thank you so much everyone for
watching see you again next time and
don't forget to check out X formerly
known as Twitter for more details of
chapter one too all right byebye
[Music]
[Applause]
everyone e