[Music]
so
hello
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
chad is so fast holy [\h__\h]
your voice is
that's impossible
[Music]
oh
wait wait wait wait oh [\h__\h] i didn't do
the setup
let's go here
let's go straight here
[Music]
wait did that scare you guys it scared
me
um yeah that screen is like my
my setup for like chatting streams but
i realized i didn't i didn't fix it
since last stream
hello everyone it's been
for non-members it's been a while huh
it's been
i think my last stream that was not
for members only was on first day
right oh my god no medium there we go
you've missed me really
it's been
[Music]
it's been such a long time well as many
of you know
i moved and that's why i've uh
been gone a little while but
okay so i moved but then now i moved
uh again and
so i moved two times in the span of
three days
because uh after moving
and well i told you guys about this in
the members only stream but i had some
issues with the internet
because at the moment the only thing i
have is like a portable wi-fi
um yeah cause uh
the the date for getting the actual
real wi-fi it got delayed to quite a
while
and yeah there's been some troubles
and also there's other reasons why i'd
prefer to not be
in my new home right now
but anyway with that horrible
portable wi-fi i was able to stream
members only but
i could not move yeah that's why you
just saw that
huge uh face of me on the chatting
screen
um so i was thinking this is impossible
i cannot stream like this for a whole
week
because no one will watch it if i don't
move i mean okay some people might watch
it but yeah
i cannot be a cardboard cut out for a
whole week right
because it's gonna take over a week um
actually okay and now it's one week one
week until i get my
real internet set up and my new home
so until then i am now streaming
with manager pc and managing internet
yeah it was very stressful i have to say
because like
yesterday before the collab um
actually we realized this the day and
the night before the collab
oh welcome everyone to the membership by
the way welcome
so yeah yesterday uh no yes the day
before yesterday
i tried the membership zone membership
only stream and
the the portable wi-fi itself was stable
but yeah as i said i couldn't move so
we were like oh [\h__\h] what do we do
there's a collab tomorrow i don't want
to be
a cardboard cuddle again so yesterday
right before the collab
i i took my suitcase put my mic
my 700 million dollar microphone
in my suitcase my new one million
dollar mic arm put it also in my
suitcase
put all that [\h__\h] in my suitcase but of
course i couldn't bring my whole pc
yay but a manager son
has a good pc apparently we'll test it
out today
but um
so what i wasn't thinking of by the way
i brought my switch as well so we might
play switch games again tomorrow we'll
see i have to see
if the game capture card works but
what was i going to say and
what was i going to say oh yeah so
what i did not think about is because i
read
that if you bought minecraft once you
can just download it on another pc again
so that's all the information i had and
i came here and i downloaded minecraft
but then i realized that data is not
saved online
yay
yeah so i would have
needed to transfer or save the data
on my other pc online on my drive or
whatever
to bring it over here but i did not
don't know that and now it's too late
because uh the other pc is
somewhere else where i need a lot of
time to get to
but it's okay because then we got the
idea
right before the stream thanks guys in
the chat sometimes before the chat even
hours
sometimes before the stream even hours
before the stream i show up in the chat
to let you know what the hell i [\h__\h]
up
this time so i let
my friends in the chat know my ex that i
[\h__\h] up
by not saving the data and you guys had
the idea
that we do uh never
a ita yes
and i thought okay well that's that
sounds like fun
and like the only thing that would still
match the thumbnail
how many minecraft streams have i done
is this the third one or the fourth
one we're doing
another ita on the
third fourth oh mixed mixed opinions
three oh
fourth it what
okay where we mixed whatever let's say
three point four
five on the 3.5
stream minecraft stream what are you
doing
never rta and for the people who don't
know what that means it means i'm just
trying to speed run uh the game
so that i can get into the nether which
you see actually here in the background
this
red scary underground area where
probably kelly lives
we're trying to get there as fast as
possible with
a new world so since i don't have access
to my old world
and we're trying to get here
as fast as possible but i mean
i mean in the past dreams i've learned a
lot i would say
i learned a lot uh
and i know some things obviously i know
i know that i should not sleep in the
never
i know that i need a water bucket and
lava to make a
a gate i know that i need to wear
at least one piece of gold armor in the
never
to not be attacked by
the what whoever
so i know some things okay i know some
things
[Music]
that i know
yay okay so
i'll tell you one thing it's it's now
officially called
rta but we all know it's gonna take
hours
so i'm not even trying i'm not even
gonna try to be fast okay
because it's my third or fourth stream
on minecraft
i don't know how to do this [\h__\h]
but let's go my eggs let's go
i already i already did some options
like i turned off all the jump already
aren't you proud of me
i already did that let me pop out the
chat
and i'll i'll i'll use a timer just for
fun but
it will be a long timer a long timer
where is my timer
okay wait so we do this
put this here and then we
put this and then okay
um professional
never rta but i think we can leave the
difficulty on normal okay
so
each title
[Music]
if it's a shitty world we have the right
to restart
and i'm gonna say if this stream is
gonna take more
than six hours then i'll quit for me the
maximum i think today will be six hours
yeah i hope that's okay we'll see what
it shouldn't need to
take six hours right i'm not trying to
slay the ender
dragon i'm just trying to get into the
nether why i shouldn't take six hours
by the way you hear the vgm fine
let's see actually my manager is
supposed to have really good internet
so the streaming stability should be
fine too
i hope i hope it'll be fine why is it
hello faster
hello my comment stopped too speaking of
stable internet my comments stopped
everything just stopped for me
oh oh oh my god okay
i think minecraft is so much for a good
pc
is this potato fizzy
wait what the hell what oh my god
hello oh my god okay what the hell is
going on it's loading
and maybe we need to change some options
oh my god
i don't know if you guys my chat stopped
so i don't know if this
is working but
oh my
why else could we change off
you kind of like it i don't know seems
so
no no no it should not be
i managed to say it's a good pc
it's not moving
ah hello
oh it didn't calm down
oh my god okay now look at this
er
ah okay
call it call it okay is this a potato pc
is this a potato pc
even worse eh eh
manager lied to me managers
are lying to me it works fine now i
think it calmed down i think it calmed
down
what that's don't say it's a downgrade
[Music]
really it's a good one
it's fine oh yeah i
also my my chat is back and everything
seems smooth again it's just
minecraft for a second seemed to have
really challenged the pc
it's decent okay okay oopsie
uh look i need to get used to this
okay anyway we gotta hurry this is rta
this is rta we need to hurry
but probably shouldn't use this wood
let's use this wood
okay what is the first thing we want to
do
maybe make something like a cave
look at
chicken fishy what no it should be fine
now
get irons okay well first why am i
trying to um
see i don't know what to do turn off
fancy graphics isn't this shouldn't be
fancy anymore
nothing's fancy about this nothing ever
was fancy about
these graphics
okay yeah let's make pickaxe
blah blah blah all kinds of stuff
[Music]
and and let's try to not die
in the first night shall we
oh yeah we need meat we need food we
need food
maybe we can try to find the food source
okay okay okay okay maybe there's two
hey is it still on fancy graphics well i
thought i turned them off
[Music]
oh it is oh that's what you mean oh and
that okay yeah indeed
okay you know it's an rta so we gotta go
fast
and where are we by the way is there any
animals here
let's see
there's a fish
maybe we should get a fish um
what what i can't
did i turn off the i don't hear the
in-game audio do you guys hear the
in-game audio
like uh jumping sounds or whatever
no interesting
ah
no not that
and why
oh
my pc volume actually i did hear
my the minecraft sounds uh before i
started to stream
all right
oh i did turn off the other jump
but yeah all the all the audio
things in my obs are also turned on
just how i'm turned on when i see callie
eh eh
what what
what
what what do you mean stream die that's
impossible
what is the minecraft sounds maybe
one second do i
i want some music wait look music sounds
what if i turn this back on
oh i hear nothing
restart the game yeah okay
one second this is not fair
let me restart
[Music]
uh
hmm
[Music]
uh
uh okay i hear sounds
you guys hear it
um yeah
i don't know what is going on but seems
like the
pc is not handling minecraft very well
oh let me adjust the window size
whoop
well we'll try it anyway
uh but i i like wait but i want my i
want my
ah this music is too emotional
too emotional wait wait wait wait wait
uh wait no
okay now this should work and now i turn
my museum again
sorry okay
here we go again the same world i would
say
restart the clock it but no it doesn't
matter
it's going to take me hours anyway so
doesn't really matter
hello i'm back what the hell
uh okay okay okay okay
are we is it working
some lag again okay this is just the
beginning okay
it will calm down for sure
yes it has calmed down okay then
but possibly timer uh i turned it on
don't you see the timer
oh yeah it's there it's there it's there
lower fps what
okay oh yeah how about 30.
yo okay now we gotta hurry because like
i feel like the
night is oh my god the night is coming
soon
and i need food there's a lot of fishes
here
but actually first okay how do i make a
box again
is this how i make a box
no i forgot everything how do i make
that box again
wait wait how do i make the box again
[Music]
wait let's kill some fish first
wait are you guys seeing a lot of black
like i'm just seeing a little bit of lag
oh god they will never die without the
sword i'll need a sword
oh i got one fishing planks
oh okay okay okay okay
what's what's over there
what's that ink sack where did that ah
from that
from those um
from the squids no even more
lowering the rendering difference oh my
god
okay seven seven should be good right
oh dear this stream is already so
scuffed
okay okay okay make logs
into planks make a box out of the planks
there's so many trees here
oh okay okay oh
no okay i thought i saw something but i
didn't
how about we make a little
cave here okay okay
oh there we go there we go okay perfect
so out of this is this how you do it
yeah okay and then
you okay i made
probably too many sticks
okay
okay so we will make a sword
we will make oh no we don't need a
wooden hole
we need a shovel maybe we need an
x and we need a pickaxe
nice anything else
special no
what yeah i made too many sticks
don't mind me
i don't need to shovel really
okay okay
[Music]
and let's start doing some mining
making a cave so that i don't die
at night right and the good thing is we
have
i forgot what that was called but with
that we can make uh torches right
how much has kiana forgotten
over the span of how many days has it
been since my last minecraft stream
am i improving am i though
eat more chicken
raise fps to 16 no why would i do that
you just saw how
how laggy it was with 60 fps
why would i do that okay
now
[Music]
shape shape our secret
security cave a bit more
what
at least you know what to do i don't
know i'm not sure
do i know do i know
okay okay wait
how to make a cave
that's very unnecessary what i'm doing
right now
oops um where am i
ah that's it already oh my god okay okay
more stone please
yes what's your problem with my stone
pick pickaxe just started out give me a
break
we're making some stone things soon
can you show your face i'm showing my
face right now
this is my face this is how i look
this is just how i look
is it is this how i'm supposed to do it
okay okay okay so the cave is almost
done
here here wait so the box
is probably done in the way but oh well
here here
here okay beautiful
yo oh the sun is already going down i
need torches
okay
wait no i need a door too right
oops
okay okay
door cannot make dory god damn it made
too many sticks
quick quick i already hear some scary
sounds
it's not good
be nice ooh
i wonder if this oh my god i wonder if
this was
any good at all
thank you and can i already make
torches
oh wait how do i make torches again
how do i make torches again
what what are those crazy red super
chats
one second i made three doors again
oh yay okay perfect okay well at least
no one can come in here right no one's
gonna spawn here right
well we're gonna have to wait for the
night but
call stick wait let me get my box
is anyone here hello no okay
[Music]
this is how you get your box back yet
okay okay very small house but i'm used
to it this is just
how you live
oh okay wonderful one second let me read
that super chat at least
there is no need for a new pc this is
just uh
for the meantime and then the other pc
is also for the meantime and eventually
i'll have my old old old pc back which
is a really good one
you say aaron look like coco eh
iron iron that's just how you say it
it's the correct way of saying it thank
you so much for the super chat
i read it all again once we are
doing the super chat reading
but this this pc i will only use for a
week okay
only for one week can the nights be over
soon
please what are we going to do last
night how do i make a
torch again i don't don't i have
everything i need for a torch
is it not well how do you do it again
like
this no way do i need a furnace
did did i need a furnace for
ah oh well why did it not tell me this
in the
in in here okay awesome
hey nice
okay now let's make um stone sword
let's make uh stone axe storm stone
axe let's make a stone pickaxe
neat well that was just right the right
amount for that
awesome okay uh let's make a
box i just call
all of these things boxes everything
here is a box you this is a box
and uh this is a box
okay let's put in some sticks and uh
i don't know maybe okay so next problem
i i can't make it bad right now
and i don't have food
um
[Music]
i'm not taking the rta very seriously
ah oops no no just box
yeah for now the torches can go there
okay should we
already go mining
actually i should find a spot where
there is lava
right dig a staircase downwards
i'm just wondering if there's nothing
useful here
i'll probably never find my cave again
huh
find some sheep yeah doesn't it
doesn't really look like there's cheap
sheep where are you
whoop tastes like nothing
there's not even enemies here
oh creeper no i see nothing
okay one second let's get back
let's get some fish then let's get some
fish shall we
oh what a nice small pond with no fish
they're very lonely well peaceful i
guess yeah you'll get you could call it
peaceful
but we don't want it to be peaceful
why is there nothing is it just so like
not able to load anything
how do i swim fast again uh this
okay
no i don't have it set on peaceful mode
but
oh hey we can have sugar
[Music]
um
can you die please i need food thank you
where are all the enemies this is
too peaceful
nice it
peace is it peaceful it's not peaceful
noble what's happening where
where are the i see a skeleton there we
go
fishing i think we're going on a fish
diet
yeah where did the fish go weren't there
just fish here
oh there we go hello
nice nice thank you fishies
need air need air
you're gonna get lost oh that's right i
don't [\h__\h]
um it's okay we'll find home
i think it's somewhere over there
i hope you guys remember
i'm scared okay let's go back let's go
back uh
where is back god damn it
where where is my home i hope i'm going
the right direction no no
well i mean i i like it's lit up a
little bit so
oh my god there's a spider following me
[Applause]
oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god it exploded and the
spider almost killed me but i'm probably
running in the completely wrong
direction
okay okay don't worry it's all good you
don't diet you don't diet and it's
slowly becoming
day time again
no need to worry let's go up and try to
find my place
i should have made a tower
go away
okay where where is my house is it here
no
you have like a tiny little pond
in here no here no
oh god oh god
it shouldn't have been that far away
yes burn burn
maybe here no uh
hey why are you not burning anyone are
you a different one
oh my god i almost died that was so
dangerous why did i even try to kill
that oh my god oh my god
if i get fall damage now i'm gonna die
are you guys aware of that
hey i can eat zombie food if i wanted to
okay eat yeah what am i
oh can i eat raw fish
oh i can
oh i didn't know
does someone know where i came from
please heal me
i need healing
let's go down again don't die don't die
no flower lemons
oh there's a cave goddammit
is that a cat nickel oh no it's wolves
do they attack me oh god better stay
away
oh no no that is not
that is not where i came from
i'm lost
no all my fishes i wanted to grill them
god damn it
hey i'm already lost this is like too
fast
it did oh god damn it
i don't think we're gonna get so far
oh yeah maybe more fishies
like nope
yo i'm getting really good at hunting
fish huh
okay
i can make another yeah i guess so i
didn't really do much there huh
but no it has all my sticks and all my
torches
i need it god damn it okay okay
try to use your brain one time kiara
didn't you come from here yeah i must
have come from here
or maybe not oh no
is this where ah isn't this way yes
should i just make a new home follow the
river
and which direction
it's not this direction
i did not come from here but this
reminds me of my old home
of my old home with which i mean
the other server fish you have to
offer yourself to me thank you
let's get some more fish because what
else can i do
nice almost died
almost died wrong river
right
[Music]
okay let's get serious here
i know yesterday
[Music]
i'm just getting probably further and
further away from it at this point
oh no what
okay making new place a pig
there's a pig and some more fish
there's pigs and cows okay
forget the other place i had we didn't
do much
anyway eat oh i keep on forgetting to
eat
i want those pigs
hello yay so many cows
hello hello or don't run away
thank you for your offering
thank you for your offerings i'm gonna
make some nice burgers out of you
[Music]
yeah where are you going that's a
dangerous place
don't go there very dangerous oh my god
looks dangerous while i'm here
let me mind that thank you
those coordinates that i just saw in the
chat
where are those
i didn't really open my coordinates at
home i think
okay
what can we do why
yeah that's my spawn point right
but how much did i move from my spawn
point
didn't did i move a lot from there i
feel like i did kind of
you can make a new home yeah i think i'm
gonna make a new home
already
this is a great rta the greatest
of them all let me get that picked
though
where where are the pigs
where are there were some pigs here
where did they go
are they hiding from me there's no need
to hide
god damn it
getting lost rta hooray
this is how you do it if you've ever
wondered how to get lost
as fast as possible this is how you do
it
but maybe we can still find it i don't
know
[Music]
cooked food is better i know
enderman hello
my old roommate how lovely
okay i have decided to give up
let's get some some nice wood
what are we even trying to do
oh yeah okay
okay okay now
i don't know what to do
he's still angry because i kicked him
out yeah
why are you so angry why are you mad bro
there's no need to be angry just
we gotta love each other people are just
too angry about everything
there's no reason there's no need to be
so angry about everything
okay okay my friends you know what
is this how you do it yeah okay
we'll do it again
a box goes
here then we make
torches as many as possible
and let's keep those how to make a
fairness again
stone okay that's no problem i can get
stone uh uh
uh let's let's let's dig
stone yes this is never
rta
[Music]
very rtis aren't you seeing that i'm
trying to hurry
so are we gonna try to find lava
eventually
or are we trying to find diamonds guys
what do you think
make a shovel ah no need not now
i am winning not really at the moment
doesn't seem like it
i need a bucket yeah
diamonds first then lava but if i find
lava and water
then i can just make the
the the thing
okay then i can make the gate okay my
brain is not working very well what am i
doing
here okay fairness done
another box done wow
so quick world record
oh god it's getting dark again
eh okay
one second uh wait wait wait
here take take uh my meat
and take this and i'll go
i'll go digging
is that a good idea
i'll just i'll just go digging
it feels like the safest thing to do
right now
what is
why is there so much of that here
it's a good idea right we cannot waste
our time but there's
no stone here what the hell so we are
trying to find gold at least because we
need gold to survive in the nether
right we need gold to survive
oops
spring crafting table oh
we'll be fine i'll just go back
i can't get lost here oh i need a new
weapon though
oh you're going back going back
open up please
open up let me out
hello is it easier with the hand
should have brought one my pickaxe
here's a door i don't have a door
okay
hello
[Music]
make the night end please
hello don't come closer
don't go closer i'm calling my mom
well actually that's a safe spot for me
easy
why did that one have iron isn't that
iron
give me that iron
go away
thank you for the super chat make him go
away
rare drop nice okay he's leaving he's
leaving thank you why are you leaving
though
oops no
um okay we can do this i'll just kill
him
[Music]
hello am i safe now i'm like almost dead
but
i'm scared i'm scared the trees look
no no no no no no no no no no no no
oh my god oh my god
wait i can eat rotten flesh right oh my
god go away
i don't have [\h__\h] to eat can i eat a
sugar cane can i
oh god damn it
am i gonna die
am i gonna oh no okay i'm recovering
what what does it do what's the problem
with being eating rotten flash i don't
get it it recovers me anyway
go ahead and police hello
i wonder if there's somewhere there
i'm scared
they're gone
how long is this goddamn night
okay we cannot die here have my have my
coordinates
i just wanna
don't go away what do you mean i'm dead
what do you mean with that can i go away
for god's sake
oh my god so many let me think
let me think oops no
no okay here you go
um
new pickaxe where's the pickaxe here uh
no not that one this one
okay well then we'll just continue
mining
we'll just continue mining although the
night should be over soon
right it should be over soon
eat yeah but what am i supposed to eat
oh you guys say as if you say that as if
i had food that's like marie antoinette
that's literally like marie antoinette
say why don't they eat let them have
cake right yeah i did watch that video
by the way
they say why don't they just
eat it's not that
easy the rotten flesh
i refuse
yeah let them just have cake
i don't understand why are they not
eating
[Music]
again this is probably not should i just
continue
and ignore it act as if it didn't
show up just continue digging digging
digging speed run for cake oh
that sounds like a good rta making cake
in minecraft
how fast do we how look low do we go
over here real really high up there huh
did you forget your steak you might i
didn't forget it but i was too scared to
go outside
to pick it up
it should be day so
we should be able to get there
wow this is a good technique guys
wow this technique
[Music]
i just want to make some good stairs
here we go oh
give this to me
place a block i know i could have placed
a block but i just don't want to
do it that way
this is my style this is kiara style
accept it or don't
can never have enough coal right
i'm about to die okay let's go look at
that meat
get that meat now
hello first day
what a beautiful day
okay so now that this day we can try to
find more animals
maybe more fish fish is always good
oh we should eat
priorities right
keep on reminding me to eat please
because i will forget
after five seconds i will forget wait
uh let's only go straight how about that
let's let's only uh
let's only go straight and remember the
coordinates i just made five million
screenshots awesome
oops
eat oh yeah okay
hello i'm only going straight
i'm only going straight is there some
fish
there's pumpkins i can eat pumpkins
right i can eat them raw even
cabbage
wow
wow nice
oh my god yes
okay is there any fish
the sheep the sheep
hello friends
die thank you for your offering
to kfp you're becoming a phoenix burger
wait phoenix burgers with chicken i
think you're becoming a jungle burger
with say so sauce
nice don't don't run
why why are cows so chaotic oh
my sheep hey can you stop running away
please
yo
but i need them from the same color so
actually you're useless i'll just take
your meat thank you
will i even find back i feel like i
already got lost
i already got lost again
i know i shouldn't uh try to hit them so
many times
because the hit gets weaker but i just
get stressed out you know
anything else here
no well at least i took my coordinates
so
i see a sheep on my ship to make a bed
please please help this store manager
out
who lada lava guys
this is good we can make a gate this is
awesome
lava and sheep and my my sword is gone
god damn it
oh oh my god it's burning
what oh my god lag
please please give yourself to me please
come on please please please
okay should we remember this lava
it's not enough is it's not enough
thank you for the super chance wait what
i'm yeah i'm really not using much
german though but you're welcome
er i read them all again uh
slowly when the stream is over holy [\h__\h]
you're burning like everything down
please don't burn me down
okay how do we get back sheep
i'm sorry i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
no i'm not okay actually i
am i don't like killing animals it's not
nice
not very nice does someone know my
coordinates i'd like to go back
did someone know
i want to go back
[Music]
the whole pc freezes though
oh my god huh okay the whole
the whole pc froze for 10 seconds
oh oh nice coordinates
thank you thank you
where do i put them so i can see them
and why did i put them
here
okay and
72209 okay it should not be far away
uh two or nine
ah this way
okay goddammit i don't have a weapon
anymore
i don't need a new pc oh there's so many
cows oh
and i don't have a sword
could you maybe just uh not run oh nice
that was a good kill
nice oh the axe works well for cows
so below or higher
higher higher higher hi we're like
almost there
it's like somewhere here
aren't we like super close
what
now we're not so close anymore okay but
it should be
don't worry about why okay but so
two oh nine
[Music]
here here
here here here
yes okay okay okay
okay hello i'm back here's some meat
my offering thank you pumpkins i can eat
raw right
oh my god we found it can i eat them
okay i can place them
one second my my leg fell asleep
oh yeah make a bed oh good idea that's a
good idea so if i die i spawn here
oh my god nice neck crack how do i make
a bed again uh
my brain is not functioning so well
like this and then ah
[Music]
no
like this and then like this
yes oh bad
bed is done
what am i doing excuse me
no my brain is not working
i shall
okay okay um
[Music]
i can only eat pumpkin pie can i make
pumpkin pie
is that it oh
well i could make sugar at least
nice i got sugar
i want to make pumpkin pie but i need
eggs now
so close okay you have my leather my
rotten flesh my cobblestone
my sugar my ink sack
my dirt
my iron my pumpkin
my granite granite granite granite
there we go there we go
okay how far are you you're done awesome
here's more beef
okay what do we do next you need to lay
an egg yeah it's
i don't lay eggs okay let me sleep
good morning hello
okay wonderful you don't need more sugar
you're sweet enough on sweet
oh okay sword
thank you let's make some more pickaxes
oh oh no sticks
okay make more sticks make more sticks
these day i forgot how to make my sticks
okay there we go
lots of sticks awesome
and what's that stick i make more
pickaxes no those are one one that's
this one
one and two and
three okay uh can
we only have one iron right now right
okay
now then we shall go on
to try to find some iron
right
we need iron so we can get gold and we
need gold to get the armor
and then once we have that we
try to make the gate right
okay okay
eat oh yeah i guess we could eat
okay
shield it's okay we don't need it right
now
what's your problem with my iron
it's the correct way to say it
guys do should i tell you about
something exciting
collab bed is lifted in one
week right and
you would think the first person i would
ask is
piccola senpai but
i feel like we need to connect more
she's shy and all that and
i i feel like she might not be
comfortable enough yet
so yesterday i have
asked a certain senpai for a
collaboration
and she accepted
guess who guess who will be
my first senpai collaboration
the chat has some delay because uh i
loved all the lag on right now but let's
see
usually it doesn't have that much delay
yes i see correct answers
yes senpai
i i contacted subaru senpai yesterday
and right away she was like yes
[Music]
is most likely 100 i guess gonna be on
my channel
but uh it's also most likely going to be
mostly japanese
because well survivor senpai doesn't
really speak english
is that okay for you guys
i mean we're probably super senpai will
try to speak some english
every now and then some broken
broken english er
but i doubt that much is
much english knowledge is gonna come out
of that
so it's okay all righty
i just want to make sure the senpai feel
comfortable
i think i already have some ideas like
the first thing i wanted to do
with survival senpai was the the goose
game with
with two players but that's only local
apparently you can't do it online what
the hell
why wait i need an iron pickaxe for that
right
probably right is that bad where are we
we're already so low oh nice uh wait but
diamonds are like 10
11 right
we shouldn't have gone that low okay
where are we now six
what
yeah the untitled ghost game you have to
play it local
and which is not gonna happen for now at
least
talking so much i was suddenly at the
lowest point already funny
eleven okay we're at eleven so we'll
just
okay so i someone sent me something
oh i'm not gonna die here that's for
sure
and someone sent me something on how i
get diamonds quickly but our goal wait
our goal is gold
gold can be anywhere right
gold doesn't have to be on 11 right
oh god that's not good
strip mining is that how it's called
where you just make
a lot of tunnels in the on the same
level
steam has remote eh wait could i
actually play it with her
because it said you have to like play
locally
i went first what do you mean
get iron first or call this gold is with
diamond level
okay and where is iron i really just
feel like i saw it everywhere
branch mining
got that time lag in the chat what is
the yes floor
steam has remote play together and you
basically stream the game to the person
you're playing who
i can do it without being like next to
her in real life
then maybe i know what i want to play
wouldn't that be fun me and savannah
playing the
the goose game
need good internet well the internet
here is really good i don't know about
the pc here
but oh wait but at that point i would be
back in my house again
at that point i should be back to my
house again
okay i'm gonna make iron i'm gonna make
some iron i think but
wait so it's like like that
wait wait how do we do that
like this like this make it on the same
level
a yes hundred percent nice i'm glad you
guys agreed
i'm so happy that survivor senpai said
yes
i was thinking like okay but it might be
too early to ask pekla senpai but
who else should i ask and right right
away i was thinking
let's super the senpai kind of like we
had some
indirect communication
previously which always resulted in
misunderstandings maybe you guys have
seen some clips of that
there have been a lot of
misunderstandings between me and
civilization but
but still even for those indirect
communications
we have kind of
went along well is that how you say it
yeah bird brain excuse me what
how are you supposed to leave i'll just
make a stairs i'll just make stairs
your stairs yeah well i'll just make
stairs don't oh my god i make a tower or
something don't
don't worry
don't worry broken
oh they break so quickly uh
yeah kind of knew that that survivor
senpai
would say yes i kind of felt that so
yeah i was really happy i was like
uh
minecraft crap
game crashed
what happens did it get saved
oh my
oh my god oh my god everything's
crashing
[Music]
oh what's happening
i don't even i don't see the chat moving
i can't click on anything i don't know
if you guys see me but
i don't know if i'm moving for you guys
let's see on my phone oh yeah
oh yeah i see the chat on my phone
i'm trying
is it gone
did it save
but you guys aren't mad but i'm mad
[Music]
did it save that
okay not all of it
and okay whatever is so
good so good
maybe i should bring the pc
the potato pc which i normally use maybe
i should bring it over because i don't
know
apparently my potato pc is handling
stuff better than
this pc
i'm so annoyed cause of all the moving
oh god
it keeps on lagging i hate this
okay come on calm down
i don't know
oh my god
oh my god this
everything keeps on crashing
ah
what do you want from me
sorry guys um
i'm sorry
particles off what are what are those
even
anymore
there's no off decreased minimal maybe
minimal
okay oh do i do like
i complete i completely lost track of
what i was doing i was just mining
okay well let's get back up and make a
iron
[Music]
iron pickaxe
click on
oh my god it keeps on freezing
it's not even only minecraft is the
whole pc freezing
where am i what the hell oh this is so
confusing
what
i need to make stairs
actually i guess i could just uh
wait wait hi
hmm
optifine i'll check it out
i'll check it out
is it night please don't say tonight
please just say it's not night well i
wanna
make it more obvious
wait
um
do you have canned air what
that sounds like a souvenir
from from
helstadt they have
air and bottles
christa you want to die
huh you should not try to challenge
sad me said kiara is the most
dangerous kiara of them all you stupid
[\h__\h]
what [\h__\h] you off
i'm not in the mood right now i'm not in
the
mood are you so invincible stupid
oh my god
i am dangerous okay i am very dangerous
don't try to challenge me
can i sleep now thank you
everyone is always bullying me it's not
only like
you guys it's also the pc bullying me
it's it's the internet bullying me
everything is bullying me
unbelievable what am i doing again
oh god spider
wow what am i doing i'm making uh
i want to make iron oh yeah there we go
our first iron
oh yeah freeze yay
it i will kill you because i'm really
angry right now
i'm gonna kill you i'm gonna kill you
kill you
that's what you get for being close to
me
got it
don't get close to me don't even try
okay frustrated
angry chiara
is not something you want to see
belly full
because i'll just cry i just cry and cry
and
cry and cry and you'll get so sick of it
i should have a new title it should be
whining
crying kiara
cry baby kiara that's my name yeah
that's it
here we go here we go again mining
for iron and gold
to be able to survive
oh my god it keeps on freezing
it's all good it's so
good hello
okay it's all good
so good it's all good
it's all good
no please i want to keep oh i want to
keep my title of
i want to keep my potential title don't
change it to cry
we don't want to make it too obvious for
the new people
we will want to make it too obvious that
i'm crying baby let's just uh keep
potential title
thank you
oh my god it fails again
oh huh
what stream is ripped
what do you mean
oh my god oh my god
oh my god i don't think i can stream
this way
i don't think i can
do it
okay i think i'm giving up on the rta
this is not working
i keep on trying to make improvements
i keep on trying to make things work
but it's not working and i don't wanna
don't wanna
um
what do we do quit and do super chat
reading and then
i don't know what to do the rest of the
week
but this doesn't seem like um
restart pc with it
hmm
okay i think yeah i think for today a
little super chat
reading i'm very sorry i wanted to bring
you guys some entertainment but
it seems like god doesn't want me to
entertain you also don't be shocked i'm
changing screens and the other
screen is not cleaned up don't be
shocked don't be surprised
hey
he
okay i'm really sorry i'm really sorry i
i'm i'm
actually sorry for myself
for not being able to stream properly
for forever since like the beginning of
my time um
i'm very sorry but in order to not
destroy the mood anymore
i will read super chat now
do not
[Music]
a
um
if you want to stay you're welcome to
stay and i will
do some small talk in between
if you don't want to stay i totally
get it i'll see you hopefully
in the next stream but you will
hopefully
give me another one of the
500 chances that i've received until now
oh my god
actually can i do
can i do this in another stream because
later can i take a break for like one or
two hours and come back
i want to do it in the stream but no i
don't think i can
i don't think i can
stick
after i take a break i'll stop the
stream and i'll come back in a new one
like a couple hours later and read
everything
thank you guys for your patience
i don't know what to do maybe i'll go to
my old place and
get my pc from there which is
from the settings that you saw you guys
know more about pcs than me but
from the settings that you the the pc
specs that you saw in minecraft
didn't you say it's better than my my
own one
you guys said that right you said
this one is better at least
oh my god what the hell was that did you
guys hear that
oh my god okay i'll just end it here
this is impossible this is impossible
my mouse won't move though
yeah my other pc has more ram i guess
cpu is better gpu is worse interesting i
don't know [\h__\h] about pcs
okay okay i'll quit it here because this
is uh i can't bear this anymore i can't
i cannot bear the whole lagging anymore
uh yeah see you in a few hours
i'll i'll travel around the whole world
again to get
the other pc before the pc explodes
see you guys soon i hope
and in german we say
auf wiedersehen a financing
the hashtag why is it like that
what is it anyway
you