[Music]
what K
Ry
are you
there Mor I'm
my everybody's
everybody we' got we've gathered the
whole crew the whole crew is
here everyone's
here except oh wait are we dancing wait
can we hear everybody is there mic check
we get a mic check a mic check H might
be a good
idea yeah no G GA we can't I can't hear
GAA can you guys hear
G oh you can't hear GAA cuz oh that's
cuz Okay I that makes sense yeah um I
don't know how
to
should Discord stream yeah it's fine
guys just everybody in the chat go watch
somebody else's POV I'm sitting on the
first
so so so I can't hear GAA but I'm
haunting
her oh wait what if uh what if you watch
gura but also watch my Discord as well
does that work cuz I hear but will you
get double audio I'm not too
sure yeah triple audio all don't worry
about it I'll figure it out you guys you
know you're going to get fired you know
you have to make a we can we can also
use Discord audio but I guess I don't
know it's not as immersive coming to
kill
us this is fine this is a lot funner but
fig out it's just something that we're
gonna have to deal with I guess because
you I know a lot of people have been
mentioning mods we can't use those we
can't yes s's allowed yeah it's not
allowed it's it's not allowed guys so
we're going to do what we can with what
we have that's what we've always done
that's what we'll keep doing
dance
[Music]
well surely we can afford one soon
right well our we did just begin this
journey the is pretty small the first
day just got to pray we find the gold
bar accessing terminal enter favorite
animal be you know how to
use operation thingy there's a lot of
buttons
eater I want to press this
is help help moons moons come on time
mons
moons mons moons
experimentation
exr can find Compu so can you like hack
the system so it'll like pay
us that's above my bay grade oh no the
auto we are orbiting the moon o
Moon there are multiple ah exp your moon
or my moon experimentation
experimentation okay so you just
experimentation let's go we just
go going to Moon me I guess
captain go who's the captain I'm just an
intern Captain Captain CL am I the
captain yes you are you have now been
selected as Captain any deaths I see be
from your
paycheck big difference you know what
that's fine ladies I can lead the charge
here play a few times the only one who
hasn't played the game yet oh you
haven't played
yet uh is the only one
who I've consumed the content but I've
not played the
game well no we just we just go and T
off
scraps yeah main entrance is Right dead
ahead ladies just find a
ladder the lad no no
please to avoid the bees you have to
spin in the circle three times okay
three times real thing what happens if
you spin four times where's the ladder
it's real look the chat says it's real
right oh it's right here guys I got the
ladder guys follow me look it worked for
GAA it worked for her oh
really oh oh there's a ladder over
there where' she go oh there's a main
entrance there's another ladder over
there e what do you mean
no it's like Five Nights at Freddy's if
you're on the ship and you're looking at
the
cameras Oh okay um we have nothing we
have no flashlights just find metal
things and get out of
here only metal things o I found
something it is brave be brave be
[Music]
brave we are very brave I found the key
oh nice one I feel so safe we're jumping
ooh there's a deep door here you can do
it
gooda V type
engine I got an engine
nice one
nice kind of
dark I'm going to be a great asset to
the's
lock good I can't hear you by the way
nobody can hear you you're
alone Callie you need a key I do oh okay
we can open it hold on let me let me
drop this is this it oh it's upstairs
right up here upstairs ooh ke find all
right there would be right cuz like you
right cck got to right click that's how
you scan stuff you can see stuff in the
dark and it'll show you the value items
no it's okay I'm going to go too don't
leave
Meco
oh there's really nothing over there um
I'm going to guess that this is the
exit yeah
a there's steam what is this is this the
way out I don't know where girl came
from I don't really remember where we
came from I think this is it I feel it I
smell this place pretty big for like a
first area yeah I I have wait where wait
there's steam here okay we're fine where
is the
exit is that the exit found it it's the
exit it okay I'll leave this here it's
only 12 12:30
um no um I wonder where Kiara is you
think she's safe yeah I hear her are
those who footstep are those are those
your footstep that's me I don't have one
headphones anymore that's
me okay that's that's not me
let whose big me footsteps are those
that big meaty claw oh there's something
over there there's something I saw
something over there
go there's something over
[Music]
there you got jump five times that's how
you avoid it I don't know where I
am uhoh where is the
exit Okay I wouldn't mind dying
now get nobody can hear you you're ghost
help me yeah did you jump five times in
a row that's how you get away from this
one three four see I died you it hit me
once it's okay I'm alive let just I'm
just going to breath
this I'm like kind of like I see a
blurry vision yeah cuz you were we were
hit okay we
surv I've been good what
cost was eaten
just be careful speaking into the
void got to be careful there's no
dogs
hello dead ah how'd that
happen well there were footsteps
happened and then
death I mean I definitely wasn't there
you know I don't know you noticed but
I'm a big old
deserter only got one item no we got we
got three bottles yeah we got three oh
oh nice um I'm kind of hurt is
that yeah it's fine we're not going in
anymore are we are we are we are we
there wasn't anything else right someone
should stay behind regardless that is
true it's three my a button is I mean I
don't know if there was anything else
any other rooms um yeah I didn't see
anything it was hard to
see there we go fixed I don't know C
Callie do you want to get the Beast cie
bees be collect the be fast if I get
them yeah behive get him
kive you grab and run get the be they're
worth a lot I'm being G up on here grab
it and
run can you spectate CI so I can watch
don't thank you Cam C go speed look get
a penalty press on huh God
speed I can scan
maybe on the way there right I think I
could see yeah it's on the way or you
doofuses are going to tell me to go grab
the hive and not tell me where it is
it's like to your right from here yeah
it's coming it's like wait I'll leave
you over here basically please you have
to
help this way
yeah I think I oh oh there they
are did you grab it did you grab
it somebody need to distract them you
have to get pretty close and press
e no get a your in
timeout we can do
it probably going to die she's uh um she
she's
sparkling yeah she's probably um if you
can't get the H you should probably I
see her corpse oh you might can you
bring her a corpse back what she's
worth5
doll five yeah but her body is still
close to the
bees okay you could retrieve it you know
all right I'll give it a try your it's
kind of it's kind of getting
late I'm watching
you if you die don't die too far
away hey how are you guys doing hey guys
I tried to bring you back but I realized
just leave K just leave no don't need
the be okay she grabbed someone oh my
God the dogs why is it spooky why is it
spooky did she not know that at night
time she played this before this is like
that movie where you're going the wrong
way where's my's
myip behind you behind you which wait
the dies maybe death there you go Kara
there we go than she only chose one of
our bodies do I still have time to
bring
leave how do I even get this I'm hear
you tell me how do I pull the
L
the door
closes well the bees had to be
abandon I thought I could t a hit until
I realized I was already hit so was
probably not the
GRE the body
now yeah
just well I'll take
that
IV most Paran a lot of
sense game excuse me at least I surved
28 yeah thanks
foring dying you
killed oh we pretty much reached the
quot we just need like one more metal
scrap so let's try and save up to get to
those far away moons ladies oh honestly
we can sell like the clipboard and stuff
apparently it's worth something if
you're desperate but I think we can
definitely be
over over the the quota you know become
employee of the
month wait who here is anybody here a
part-timer or is everybody intern unpaid
intern intern I think I'm intern right
now interns get
paid um your intern you want to do some
it on your on your jack for
us confir who's oh
everyone I don't know do you think we
shes or flashlights I don't know where
we're going Part Time Warrior Yeah
March flashlight no there's lots of
stuff if you go to the computer and type
in shop yeah flashlight would be good
all right I got this leave it to
me stop one shovel confir we have to
okay store and then we'll do
Flashlight nice A little bit of money oh
I should do flashlights and then a
certain number
okay Bo I don't think we can afford
anything else no how many
flashlights just one okay single
flashlight and a dream we can get more
later though and a transporter and stuff
like that shall we go I can pick so much
with this
let's go land in the
ship got to remember to pick up the
flashlight before we
go floating
[Music]
SE we're in
March I believe we go to the right
hasard little H Fest time on
ready oh no time flies too fast guys
it's a go watch out
what what a yeah the
bridge someone almost went off the edge
I
saw I haven't done that
before you nether me
there
o very
scary did we get the flashlight there
goes somebody needs to hold her head we
need to put a leash on her wait is she
is she going to get the flashlight I
hear the
[Applause]
thing wait I'm
lost oh I heard
it
oh oh
W you bought a
shovel and a flashlight do you want it
no no no you take it my survival rate
is is
run do you want the flashlight oh I can
carry the flashlight and you can W
things all
right I'll be the bait you do the
bunk unless I fall off a
cliff that is unfortunate
ba ba
switch you guys forgot to grab the
flashlight and stuff I know oh she
didn't I thought you were for
real bait last time I recommenda
[Music]
be hey you want to go in
there wait where do you have the things
from did you pick it up from the
in there we picked it up from the the
present there's a present in the front
room are you
sure I a shovel can you beat him I I
have one piece of metal
that well you can bring that back for
now someone's got to be bait and it
might have to be me oh I heard oh she's
not coming out oh that's what got me
last time man double is you can hit it
hit
it pressure pressure
isy
fishy is we shall play with
[Music]
it it was on the right
more we should go all in
different take it we have a l
FAS where are you necessary there
nothing here
I we going to close the door can get
through the door if you guys just close
the door can you trap them in here just
close the door a door I think it's open
there's nothing the other way there's no
door it's just open no time for
baby yeah we can lead him into the other
room all right I'll have him follow me
and you guys look for
scrap he's gone he's gone hewn who's got
the flashlight I do where shall I go not
cowards gra protector it looks like a
Shar it's coming for me hit it hit
it h
it oh
no you got it there's a casualty
on oh I think gooda hit her by accident
it's all right girl you did what you had
to do no she did well flashlight in
herstead yeah take my flashlight my body
I did I got it yeah feels more noble
that way hey that was sick though got
the monster wonder if the monster worth
anything you can stay
here naap no don't leave
me
wait was that this room hello where's
Ena is Ena alive I'm
dead know I'm in the after the
flashlight I thought I saw a flashlight
yeah oh okay there's another flashlight
no that was my
flashlight was my
flashlight
anyway it's starting to get close to
it's getting dark in here so crab all
scraps in a big area I think
Good's lost a fish she found the fish
holy she found the fish that's amazing
it's meant to be wait does it do
anything like does it fake
swim try to fish this just really
heavy surely it's worth a
lot
fish okay okay hi hi yo let's
go remember me bring me home I got you
don't worry fireman's carry oh oh I'm
carried like a princess it seems like a
different door it's probably the same
door anyway let's get out of here before
the dogs
come friendly I think my I think my
brain's a
little bra my brain's shaking brain
shaking face it looks kind of
weird and then he puts you into it and
you hear a munchy
noise my brain where is it I don't know
it should be around here Chase
Dead's dead
dead I don't know actually I mean I'm
you're kind of carrying my body found
ship right again I mean am I alive I
don't
know it is GL for
punishment wait is that ena's body it is
my body's body it is indeed not mine
this is you was scary the whole time you
had killed the entire time I was bitten
by the but I quickly run away and
survive
somehow the monster stuck again every
time I go to the sh that way anyway I
got the kettle
Nicea really did do the uh switch of
Maru then sorry en rest in peace look I
found a fish Eternal bunk TST fish
that's a heavy boy oh plastic it's all
good got value by we I me the group Min
is it time yeah let's go everyone keep
your hands and feet on the ride what
I my
neck be inside when the door closes I my
neck one big fish I sustained the most
injuries I think Ena sustained the most
injuries cuz she died my neck
you didn't do anything I can't the the
shark looking
monster bit me said I'm a parttime
you're part-timer now I got
promoted why part it just means you take
the most risks in the next
Expedition lead the group do anything
until we sell all right uh let's see
access the terminal all
right it's
forever fine vow let's go to vow vow
inspect yeah wow free like vow with the
V or vow with
the what other bow bow sound
B Bow Bow Bow Bow don't think anybody
said that
sorry I'm just trying to entertain
myself cuz I know I'm going to be
interned forever and I'm just you know
entertain why I'm just forever intern
you know I'll just why are you why are
you intern forever a flashlights who's
turning off the lights you think you're
it's my second shift I've seen many many
other other same employees of the same
group um they they got promoted and um I
don't know hazard level C I'm just
always in oh you know we got to go oh
okay you can prove yourself now sure
surely this is the day all right
um a little now oh do we buy stuff nope
nope not this time okay okay I'm pretty
sure this one is either straight forward
or to the
right I see a
bird bird it flew away I think you'll
heard a s
what should I going to the right oh
there's a bridge there's a bridge it is
running off into the unknown into the
rning into unnown she'll find her way do
not do not sing the song they touch Polo
Marco Polo I had this dat chip before
screams
screams brige maybe I bet she'll find it
oh there's the main entrance
found oh I'm not a dark I knew it was
there is that before
Oh jumped is there fall damage in this
game kind of I heard there is if you
fall I'm not going to find out great
amount of time you
f oh that's a fake
door I don't like how dark it
is ooh bottles
nice you guys had a flashlight but it's
gone now oh where go Ana dropped it I
think so must last area Kelly picked it
up I don't know if she left it
though no no get hello you to grab the
core oh
no uh-oh uhoh
no
what I'm get
SC wait is this bad kind
of you're not going to believe what I
found does it
Glow it's a it's a light bulb a big
light bulb where is everybody where is
everyone I'm kind of scared to go
in hello wait why did the lights you
grabbed you grabbed the J
wait is that what that
was oh The Forbidden light bulb I don't
think so where's Calli and
Kiara probably dead probably dead that's
what to say should we go
back we can
go did you guys get any more loot maybe
we we we got some bottles and then the
generator so I mean I think you guys are
fine you guys already made the quota you
can go back you go back which one's more
expensive you grabed the light bulb
ridden light bulb question
marks question marks that means that
means special
prize stupid prize hopefully who oh ah I
don't
know
okay are you
alive there's another bridge to left can
you throw me a rope I have no rope I
have some beer you want some beer I I
think I think my leg is broken oh no
wait there's uh maybe you can climb
through there there's some bees there
though don't worry I'm Skyrim cheing
hold on nice oh
no I'm she's
gaming she
gaming I believe you didn't have to go
around I think trust
nice just
gameing
yes you can do it okay I'm going around
okay there's there's bees there be
careful the bees the bees let me just
put this at the ship oh oh oh you made
it so fast you know I thought I lost you
forever I just I just heard a scream and
turned around and you were
gone she was jumping on that thing like
she was jumping on a bed it was
bouncy I saw the I saw the plates shake
and I was like hm this looks like a run
angle you know I don't really hear
Calli and Karas I'm just going to take a
weal guess and see
they they didn't make it they
died maybe I wonder why I guess we can
check here huh
flashlight wait no they're alive oh
they're lost they're lost
inside oh oh she's left oh no it's oh no
it's a monster carrying it her
around oh call might be
alive oh she te's alive where is she she
make it out I think I think she's
alive I think I think Kiara didn't make
it maybe she's outside now do you go
pick her up is that the edge of the map
oh she be it out alive she's coming home
oh she's crossing the
bridge wait
what oh it's becoming dark yeah
well somebody has to go back for wait is
K you don't I think I think she's dead
the monsters are like oh look at this
new doll we
got oh she's making making back
Callie look at all my
trinkets o a
drot a drink kid okay stay here goba sh
oh K I'm here you guys are alive let's
go I thought you almost
[Music]
[Laughter]
died yeah we got the we got the
generator she bravely walked before me
and um and took a bug to the face we
evaded the Bracken I can't believe that
happened there wow we shouldn't be alive
after that okay let's go made it made it
you guys good work we were pretty
useless but I think I like to think we
lured the monsters away from you guys
maybe we were we were pretty shallow in
the uh when it happened I broke a bridge
oh yeah with her yeah that happens too
fish but yeah Big all there's to it but
too
massive you know thought the tungsten
fish was
massive stop jumping it turns out I'm
the tungsten face hey stop jumping
just are we leaving jump button isn't
even oh hold on sorry it's just my jump
button the door open open oh no no no no
no oh we're leaving
okay uh Goodbye Oh the bees almost came
come back inside before we leave the
atmosphere yeah nice you choke and die
you can die like that don't know yeah
it's like science
yeah
probably wait why am I the laziest
employee I brought stuff
back you're doing back to intern I went
back to intern because of that yeah if
you
die oh we got to we got to go hand it in
time to go be to the company all right
I'll take us
there to your scal ooh what do I
bring you bring the you can use theal
oh my hands are full we're on the
way well I think we all know I think we
all know what happens when somebody
rings the bell right so let's do we need
yeah
what you get a you get a sticker when
you ring the bell ring the they hit the
Bell like a bunch of times not just once
like a you get a lollipop
[Music]
H yeah something kind of new
happens all how do I hold
on
no why would leave it leave it just
leave
it
oh maybe the counter was kind of full
mhm give another sh she wasn't taken she
was not taken there you
go for a lot too and the fish the fish
no you're keeping the
fish no I didn't personal token we lost
it wait one more thing one more thing I
lost
it did it on its own I was that you
bringing it over my shoulder n myness
no okay oh what a deal what a deal
not the fish not the fish you're going
to lose the
fish can we can sell the PO oh no she's
ringing the bell and running
away I feel like she had so much more
money though more than 14 barely met the
quota we barely we barely when I scamed
it was like 240 something or another he
ripped
305 off
[Music]
no huh jely we can
no oh we have enough $300 went back into
the ocean oh
no she went home she went home wait fish
oh what this you throw them is
this yeah car might find the fish over
there oh I'll get the fish what is
this it's
lore she
actually I don't know I kind of forget
went home
sound behind the wall there was a log a
journal entry was it a
will that's not here I think I think she
went
home all right
well the shark turned to the
ocean well I got her
journal nice all right should we should
we buy some stuff
yeah that would be a good idea okay that
was okay Min is the Min is the
quota um probably
buy something should we poy takies
should
we switch members or should we
just I wonder if someone left would I be
able to invite someone again what are
you doing I don't think so I'm should
I'm should be able to play next
round is that how it works but then I
wonder if we have to
sculpure
re start a room it would be better not
if we did not do that we can't go the
away rooms I wonder can can we invite
apparently some you can make it saves an
orbit oh yeah that's right you can true
yeah like I have a save file so if we
quit out of it it saves your
progress so I'll quit out of it and
reinvite people okay okay okay is is
that going to
work yeah let's do that if one
person and then close lobby yeah we can
go orbit and then save okay go with the
[Music]
or monitoring big
fish all so who's going to out he's in
the deep deep darkness of the waters so
dark I can't see
anything G will sit out so watch no but
you're new to the game everybody else
has played
[Music]
it maybe I'll sit we even got overtime B
wait you can't cuz you're the you're the
host true maybe I sit last I don't mind
being the ghost of New Year's past
okay well I'll go ahead and quit out
then okay we're in orbit now
quit okay
okay oh me goach see how you guys can't
hear me or I can't hear you guys right
now it's okay I you
say how did you did you show the Discord
chair yes yeah I just had um like
somebody's main POV and then somebody
else cuz you can watch two streams at
once and then I had both audio playing
at the same time and it wasn't that bad
it's kind of echoey but it's not that
bad
okay wait am I not sitting this one out
I can sit out I don't mind I'm sitting
out W already been
made okay hold on uh stop streaming mine
[Music]
hello wow oh good what were you doing at
the
end kind of sweet uh can one more person
also stream their
game okay I can do it I can do it
important things okay cuz I think if I
do it like recently when I screen share
my my voice gets like correctly and
everything's crack uh
wait go chat now you guys can
hear I should buy one more walk maybe
two more walkies who taught you those
dances
huh don't want to spend too much
money have you cheated on me by going to
a different dance
teacher
T I don't know those dance moves they
look
I didn't teach you to it's okay it's
just your old age you're forgetting
things you've gone Cena that's
fine here and
there just a little bit and in good fun
B that's probably
it is stinking up the
ship no hold on I'm trying to get
this
Moon
Moon let's go to um moons the Moon moons
let's go Insurance
again that seems good off we go ladies
I'll follow your lead I want to see the
powerful skills of Amelia
Watson show
us Master TR
your tret I'll take that catch
me off we
go we something yeah we bought
stuff for Christmas cribo
[Music]
music you want this where is it keep
your eyes
the where is
it there it is not coming it's on it's
draining the
battery
Santa or else
itank it open there we
go what is it walk
[Music]
whoopsy doodle it's all good it's all
good
ladies all right where's the entrance
follow the
light two this is
Big Fish
over this is and over I'm looking for
the
entrance I'm staring right at it stupid
over I mean come back one two three
nerer main entrance
over breaker
breaker why didn't you call me a name
back oh wait this is's point of
view uh thank you over
this is
it I'm there entr SEC
over is it girl is it
Amit no this is
Amit
[Applause]
over this oh think this is
gur I'm
confused
what was
that this is like you farted into the
microphone I'm lost on a over that's
what happens when you don't believe in
yourself this is
[Music]
scus here it's a it okay now it's a it
okay okay
God what do you see on
Horizon the ship the ship are you guys
lost
me follow the light on
me follow the PS
maybe
yes that's be
this is guras this is
am are you at the ship
over where did you
go
over
okay yeah this is good right
now I see
you oh hello hello hello over
hello this way it's that way it's there
it's there it's there it's
there I found something
wa wa wait
what
log did you leave
it guys it's already 2:20 p.m. you
haven't entered the
building so all they found was
soda breaker breaker oh we the Super
Mario Brothers we're the super s
brothers oh wait wait wait hit me guys
there's a lot of stuff in there get get
it
really what's in the box you want it
what's in
[Music]
it a hair brush I
mean it's this
sucks they smack me with it I tried it
didn't let
me wait there's another one here open
this one O A gift wait
fish a waste wow a look's
[Music]
cooler activity detected let's get out
of here oh there's a noise oh botson all
right yeah you want to leave let's go
bet bet let's get out of here um someone
dropped her
walkie-talkie Ander
uh it's okay she's alive we should go
they're all
leaving what just happened did you guys
steal there she is she is wait what
she's
alive I thought you what was that
noise
I think I can get my title back right oh
there's
a there's a lot okay let's go let's go
let's go there's at least
two
yeah you guys see how carrying something
no is everyone
alive
yeah
okay actually survive that I'm I'm in
wow
wow I hear the it's a here doo doo
doo here boy
here get away from you
guys
dropped it's a good
boy there's many snacks here
oh hold on I haven't seen any dog so far
oh that get in
here is it a worm oh that's that's a
worm yep I made it I made it get inside
get inside oh everyone made it is the
worm I don't know see the giant red dot
on the
screen where' you find the
here it's important music is important
when you're lonely and onon a ship in
space what they F sing us a song You're
the piano
man
yeah uhoh I dropped
it laziest employ wait how can you be
lazy and profitable at the same
time I mean I'm again are you just
pushing your tasks to the other
employees yeah what problem no I I even
I literally saved Amy from Death a
monster was on her head and I killed it
the only reason
she's moment for Kiara big hero big
claps I on my own the no you did not my
is the proof strength of my will no my
is the TR Thank Me
Later does she not know do she not know
all right I'm sending us to the you're a
hero to me thank you let's go to Ren
okay or is it like French it's oh I've
never seen this green
before we're too poor we can't afford it
I'm
[Music]
there offense because we
are
off
School Friendly
Fire I Stay is someone twerking in the
corner over there what's going on are
you hitting me we have no what I'm not
twerk what are you talking about you
doing some some movements behind the
cabinet I wasn't sure you know if you
were uh right right yeah sure that was
me she's doing the Oinky
spy with the boom box yink spy I mean
someone could stay here in theory and
direct us with the walki
talkies why
is announcement from the company please
do not kill your other fellow
employees but the sign Square Off
I think I don't need walkie talkie so
I'll leave it here everyone's life
matters in this
company okay I'll stay here sounds good
let's go be assets though the great
assets they definitely value the great
assets more though what' you say to me
huh me no she did not call you an s a
great ass asset scary I said you're a
great asset the company wait you talking
wait wait wait wait wait wait yeah I
don't need it it's okay I don't I left
it on
purpose all right she doesn't want to
communicate with us all right Kiara I
see how it is all right me crying out to
you in Peril and you're not going to
hear me no no I will I will be around
when you need
me can she
promise I guess we go side there's a big
bird hat no they me sorry wrong Chann
untrue now you're just making up
fibs let's see oh maybe we can go up
here us
[Music]
right if we can jum this no I think
there's a different way we can
go we can just go around yeah I'll lead
you yeah yeah yeah
yeah you made
it
Sally gave up though before even trying
no I didn't I'm going to do it
now J she made it
coward crank with the
rest you know I just the other day
finished my first ever like um platform
of Mario game
a yeah all the
see yeah it was very nice to
me excellent
maneuvering that's all right they're
they're just haters ignore
it I'm going to leave your ass behind if
you much just
me all right I need I need some uh I
need some coms
here see
Divine Divine
Divine hello this is Morrison
speaking
hello can't pick up
anything what
are there was a treasure over
there what does the treasure look like
the the green dorit
oh I found
something yeah there's one behind you
in you keep a look out
for no it's a valve nothing good down
here maybe it's
below nothing good down here yeah
there's a green
oh green there's Lo in room if you go to
your
right oh did I see two eyes oh it's the
uh generator it's the
generator do not touch Until the
[Music]
End why is there no
items
oh oh sounds like a lights
saer
oh
ohed there's two
of I hear muffled the
screams
umist oh she's making a run for torted
out of there pretty quick though not
going to
lie where's did you guys go past the
monster
is
that I'll carry your body you can carry
the
core oh
what oh good idea gring the items very
nice wow what a
legend the clut you should wow
that's really admire that I'm a bit of a
coward though not going to lie hell did
I miss anything who's dead who is it a
bit of
a I am afraid to tell you that
oh did gar gumbus die someone has passed
away I
mean oh yeah her body away of they
not no sorry couldn't be a good asset
this time really was pretty baren I'm
not going to lie coming team ala
hello over over next
time he left us with a single and heed
out pieced out of
existence
uh wait oh oh no that just kidding it
must have been on the walkie see I knew
they'd be
useful I have uh Kiara's dead body but
what about Kiara's
sign dang it must have lost it in the
frame oh nice
MVP MVP what a legend all right let's Mo
on out of
here someone else can choose where we go
next leave it up to you
guys right on ahead
pick yeah
where does chat want to go this closes
on its own right yeah yeah thinkk you it
would be pretty funny if it didn't I
will say nice one um we have about one
day left for the quot I think we can we
can fill it how are you doing for the
quota so far
hi I'm alive
again Phoenix s it
yay profitable because I brought back a
body like a noble a noble Spaceman yeah
thank you for carrying me you're welcome
I got laziest but I was Button
Pusher I mean I could I pushed one
button oh wow Assurance really is the
only one that we can mess around on
huh please no violence on the ship qu no
violence on the ship
oh well in that case all out Battle
Royale
Doo number four is the best one n yeah
you got to charge it you got turn it off
no you know what I should also grab some
flashlights mine on I'm going to grab
some flashlights real quick and then we
can
go flashlight do three come
F ready now let's land
know make H yes please please speak up
har harassed by
what
listening excuse me there seems to
be
wait oh my God wa excuse me you have a
witness you just committed a crime I'm
here yeah I'm reporting you to the
company report has been made
please
karar I will kill myself though
Kiara you no step I do not I don't not
okay all right girl last day of the meet
the qua let's go you
me oh oh oh oh
oh um I do what just
[Music]
happened what just happened I can't I
can't hear El cuz she's dead I gain
my I'm so sorry it's because I just
realize you know you were hitting me
first anyway I can't go in there alone
it's okay two CL now oh yeah it was
supposed to be one for each of us we
playing changed clearly wait wait wait I
going drop this up yeah me
too how we going to explain to the
bosses that two of our team well one
committed a crime and the other one
killed himself anyone committed soku um
that's a great question um for now let's
not think so much about it I'm sure that
the company you know
understand I can't believe you've done
this take on the r that my it was for
love fellow employee was going love you
say
it's kind of different from the love I
know can I get that meal
ticket
yeah I'll take K steamed
potato oh steam potato sounds
yummy is
l i see that's what they all say
Kiara like I didn't mean it I didn't
think that was actually going to kill
her or like she started
[Laughter]
it it's like if someone else is going to
kill elit it's going to be me kind of
thing you
know it seems the made me shark has
missed her jump she
left I can't die here W's going to laugh
at me forever if I die here cuz she
literally told me you going die here
stupid and I I said n just jump jump do
it jump nice I'm good Yi I'll be there
shortly uh I had to fight off a dragon
sorry
Dragon but I
live I was going to make a plan but I
stopped myself is that a bird hostile
hostile hostile is it hostile hostile
hostile in the area hostile it's just a
bird hostile I'm scared
anyway yeah take
jump oh poison all right now all right
what she going to do with it what she
going to do oh oh oh mountain goat
strats hello oh she made it I'm alive
you made it before one oh present found
the present I can't open it for some
reason I pressed y but it didn't work
maybe you can open
it oh there are
pickles us need the quot
for we got
it we got
to nothing in here nothing
spotted full of
[Music]
nothing oh my God no way can you use
it find something good yeah dude what'
you find going believe
it okay all right uh I'm quitting the
game I've had enough of this I've had
enough come here come come here come
here come here come here come here come
here sit on it come
here yeah for the content C pick it up
pick it up pick it up pick it up
[Music]
really you know what you've made a
mistake G you're letting me hold this
now which means you'll never get it back
no it's only wor it's not even worth
anything times and yep can this Lage now
how
productive there's a turret be
careful te it that
way K you can use that you
know glass you can it says
glass flash it says flash my whoopy
cushion back or else yes yes it with
me find
her
I can't
[Music]
see I'm so proud of you you flashbang
the spider like no
tomorrow work did I do it did I flash it
you did you did
[Applause]
you I don't think that kills it though
just letting you know yeah
oh maybe it just got emotional damage
not
sure him and all his eight I don't know
which way should I
go I hear
no pleas oh no is that
Kiara
nodd R run
fortine this a creature
disgusting you made it though proud of
you it's very
slippery he's not happy is he
no
Mich over
M she not does she not hear
it
might have run out of
battery oh was
there
yeah left
me she
left turn your radio on you she's
leaving she's
leaving she she's leaving
she was oh is G still there oh what the
a that's what she gets for leaving
her behind
Miss she's farting the
Cs sorry about that
one you know on the bright side I got sa
cushion for you I'll have you know I was
fighting for my life in there well
that's fine you wouldn't have made it
back anyway the dogs were
prowling I did a
flavor now we have maybe
anot are we all getting fired or is
this we might beid from being fired
there has been some allegations of you
know members killing members so there's
that true employee
abuse h definitely going to hear about
this warm bodies that could increase the
you can actually use
it there's no bathroom in the ship just
to let you
know
it I figured she'd like
that that makes
sense so if we want to rotate someone
out we could this is a good time to do
it want to I can be the one before
before we die I can I can it's my
turn before we do the ah we're going by
the life order the oh I guess is that
how it
works all right I guess we're going to
the company
[Music]
now we got to sell everything we have no
days left on our
deadline I want some
pickles well you can check if you meet
the qu or not first
maybe yeah know I kind of did take a
look and I think if even if one of us
even if all three of us gave up our
bodies if three people gave up their
bodies it wouldn't matter we can give up
our bodies for points for
money yes and
no oh oh oh that's what you mean
oh yeah if we beat up each other right
we'll need something to beat each other
so maybe don't sell any we don't sell
the SOP sign yet I mean you can just
ring the bell a lot of times
yeah but oh sniper it's a laser
pointer where did you get
that I see the apparatus sells for a lot
that's
good yeah if we
sell
[Music]
[Laughter]
cushion we have to keep Spirits High
what about
the
no too bad oh is the Stu gone I
mean1 yeah you guys made
it you may keep the you can feel free to
keep your your whoopy cushion I guess he
was going to keep it anyway she's going
to keep
it but it okay okay all
right goodbye whoopy cush stilla
[Laughter]
baby
play get moving maybe we can go to some
better moves we're going to go into
orbit and then we'll switch out is
everyone
here I don't know is every I mean sorry
also didn't check again I'm not the this
seems to be a reoccurring thing Callie
all right now listen here hear about
this big apologies no no no no the
company doesn't need to hear about
anything anything of the sort quote is
going to start getting crazier though
from here on out um going to need to go
to further way moons with better
loot voice that everybody hears so maybe
lead give don't lead us but give us give
us give us useful hints yeah like a walk
talk you're like a GM now let's see what
we can buy
first see store I can spell store um so
we have quite a bit of money in fact we
can get a
transporter oh no what's the point if
the ship leaves before you can teleport
I mean Point too but we we actually
can't afford it so I'm going to grab
some shovels
two we need two fighters and then after
that organiz should be using should be
using the money Charing
everything M number one
employee will hear about
this that's really
expensive um all right what's the
cheapest Moon I wonder is it dyme by
chance we won't go there cuz it's
eclipsed but oh
no
is
R yeah maybe grenades would be
nice we're changing that's right correct
swapping out boss mhm see doodle okay
going to close out the room
now quit bullying
[Music]
girl going dancing into the wall
okay I guess I got a launch now
[Music]
huh oh I can un stream now in the
Discord
such intense
music it is
terrifying can you invite me again it
went through I'm excited thank you see
play Oh Ena needs another invite you
got okay no
problem for
now
know yes I guess we can go to a did you
see I I sent you a present on Steam did
you see I don't I didn't see anything
pop
up it's probably in your emails or so oh
I'll check my email notifications it'll
be in there double now you're double
can't go oh I received a
gift
oh accept gift I got it I hope you don't
have it yet you I don't I only have the
first
one please play it I want you to I want
to see you play it okay I will I'll be
the Artist Artist yeah I ended up giving
her something else guys than what I
originally said in the
Stream not Secret Surprise game o Secret
Surprise
4 yeah where are we let make sure we
grab our
stuff to
two I'll grab a doesn't okay who's
staying in the
ship you can stay in the ship such an
obvious pick guys not very good at
briefing I've learned that I'm just like
ooh pretty shapes oh right I have tell
them there's a monster is Double's
echoing for me oh sorry I forgot to mute
it's okay there we go
switch display
Mar hey how do I do it
again is the ship coming you got to look
at the
monitor you type in switch view monitor
yeah that's what it is hi guys make sure
you have a walkie-talkie are you staying
inside yes all right forward H here for
wait my delivery should be coming she's
a
murderer chicken chicken chicken
chick at
Freddy
two are just press the little plus
eyeball on
Discord oh dropped it oh my God right
thank you there you go now it's on this
is Shady call are we not receiving
anything from the
ship room Shady over this is HQ
calling in break a
record AFF Grim shady is enter is
waiting to enter the building but I'm
also waiting for my friends oh Grim
Shady
over Grim Shady over's
lost I have found the main entrance
over where's gaha Kiara can you hear me
over and out Grim Shady over and out
G
Shady it's pretty good right yeah she's
lost I see she she didn't take the
walkie-talkie with her like I told her
to ah there it is I'm not blind I can
see everything yeah is she going to be
fine are you going to be or is she going
to be fine
over looks like she's okay I think she
found a different
entrance okay tell her to jump on the
bridge jump on the bridge fun bouncy
woohoo
sorry another whoopy
cion oh she's
here the collection grows
[Applause]
larger
there should be two
items
AFF there's a monster downstairs
over I don't see any red dots right
now okay I'm fine I'm
fine completely
fine
[Applause]
there's monster right behind you yep
there is e it's like running away e e e
e
tell oh boy I saw that
happen
uh he's
gone you're gone I did see that
happen I saw that happen um I I don't
know what we could have
done SOA dead maybe can come in now
slime slime slime slime slime
slime I have to look at it to scare it I
see not messing with that look at it and
then look away okay can I hit what this
I can use this that was Ry shows up will
gotop them for me all right here's all
right so the enemy took this is where
the monster is Kar I'm going to go
for there I see
oh hi did someone just snaap their neck
what was that yep that was there was a
snap break
breaker it sounded just like when you
know like when you eating chicken wings
and you accidentally snaap
the that I think I can handle by myself
if you wouldn't mind coming to one of
them up to help me out I'll try to I'll
try to do both but
okay did you die by the same monster um
I don't think so M I got a I got a nice
hug and it was not a good hug oh yeah
okay my Go Chat is it this
way oh it was the same monster M the oh
okay apparently apparently I did I see
guess I found you after I follow me kind
of
dangerous
peace this way I did find like bottles
though that was kind of sad I was like
maybe I should bring it back no I'll go
back in and then I
died I'm going back they found each
other bringing the stuff back and going
in nice oh oh she she's walking back
with the B bottles all the beers the
bottles of water the
water that bridge looks way too sturdy
yeah this is the sturdy one the other
one on the other side I think the bridge
will break if you're too
heavy the one you're on the right again
that one
break
the I love bread
rolls
yummy what kind of bread rolls though
can you hear me like just the regular
kind yeah I think she can only hear if I
talk on the
radio Kell's not going in anymore I
thought they were picking up
bodies going to leave bottles and bodies
kind of sound the same over the
radio yeah maybe misunderstanding I
think my body body is kind of Farish in
the corner though so yours is a bit
closer no I was like near the
exit I'm
lost maybe press the right but right
click right click on me
scan scan way home you know how to scan
what is that oh she found it she found
home I hear big steppies
is she found a home oh big steppies is
that what is
that nice one nice one Watson let's
[Music]
go
partying they're mourning our death with
a
dance crating early
[Music]
amaz Z
serious the shame right two days left
the shame amount it's all right it's all
right no problem if we pull the same
amount again um a couple more times then
wait you can just step on
yeah I'm just an
oh you got deed no I can't get demoted
any
f it was never me to
be my coworkers are bullying
me she's mocking you
you're just an intern to you got
toed there will be no bullying on my
ship knock that right off Kara did it
she started
it you littleit you little I am done
being they fighting again never
again whatever want to get a couple
squirel they're like gross
roing
nice that was actually pretty good where
are we
going so we're going to land and we
should look listen look listen for the
delivery I got flashlights for you guys
oh thank you I owe you my
life
you don't
worry
where's the Christmas tree should be
coming Christmas
tree oh nice is that the
sun yeah why are we all looking into the
Sun at the same time guess bad for your
the sun o oh nice oh there it
is I just got flashlights for you guys
it's prise the
sun oh main entrance is over
there oh there's the it's coming up it's
coming up it's coming
up Sun's moving real
fast
bless I got a key hope there we got lots
and speed
running okay nothing here Grim shady is
there anybody at over now I have no wiie
toi a dead
end dead end just like my career in this
company
M we're coming to get
you is that a
bomb what is
this oh it's a
pipe I fixed it you fixed it it's so
broken no I fixed it you can't see I
didn't bring my flashlight there's
nothing here
watch gri Are You detecting any hosti I
fixed it not at the
moment oh stuff there's like nothing
here oh there's a key pretty
Barren got to meet the quota
though need to keep the walkie talkie on
for watchs and updates
key
oh nothing
here let get
it okay maybe really isn't anything over
there where must we go maybe
here I think it was a dead
end funny
items huh
way what is that
e
what what is sound familiar why is that
[Music]
the I thought she was asking for I
thought you were the
ship
[Music]
I don't know
there's funny I I only have one item but
I might as well bring it back I only
have a
key where's the fire SM like an air horn
we didn't find anything what you say I
have this it doesn't sound like an air
horn it sounds like something
[Music]
else you take that back oh there's a
fire exit maybe there's something
there guys guys there's a fire exit if
you want to
check I have a feeling I'm going to die
but it's okay I'm an intern
anyway jiggle jiggle
over what is that e e oh my
God what was
that I don't want to I don't want to go
home without bringing
anything please be a
whoopy it's a bug Mafia give him my
key take
it
ena's yeah yeah
well well take my
offering
I don't like the sound of
it okay there's something else there's
something else this was a mistake this
was a mistake where is the exit where is
thank you thank you friend
oh my God oh my
God I just lost the key she's insane
Ana's insane am I
insane I didn't get anything I just lost
my key
and I'm just going to go home Nextbook
Serpentine
maneuver just going to go
home is there anything by the door I
need to carry oh you need
help I have a emotional damage to look
for you too oh no I'm fine I just went
to check the fire exit don't check the
fire exit let's just go home let's just
go home okay if you say it's been a long
day let's just go home without you my
friend
are
you
[Music]
bra we have we're going to have a m
field of whoopy cushion yeah I don't see
anything wrong with
that we know we're selling first if
we're low on
qu Jesus should be
enough we got more stuff than I thought
no credit to
me
monsters it's okay Mom one
of wait ear horn is worth
52 actually a lot a
lot nice one yes no notes is better than
being called
lazy great a great a
nice one day left one day left rber you
guys want me to buy oh cute um I could I
could use a walkie I didn't have one
okay I don't have one either oh really I
thought for sure we had four definitely
bought I mean I kind of died when they
killed yeah all right
two does someone need to go to the
bathroom or
what guess not I imagine ping in space
well can you just FL out there forever I
mean maybe just going to March toilet I
mean gravity helps
right how would you even get it out
anyway all right all right where's our
next destination
March yeah all right let's go March time
oh team go March in isn't that
right you want stay in
behind oh there's a there's a hive
nearby be
careful that's
[Music]
level you don't really need a flashlight
technically oh it's not re charged no no
you can just go into the darkness and
it's Fine's
entrance oh that was quick easy one sec
I'm just where's the Christmas
[Music]
tree
anytime
now is that it no that's oh that is
it
yay she's going
by yay nice is that it I think
so Boston if you enter the
building swag over wait where is the a
building
oh
um yeah I think for March I
think
yippe I saw it from the ship so I'm
guessing
oh I trust your direction sense better
please don't trud my direction
sense especially in video games might be
might be a bad
combo go TP go t go straight away oh
yeah it's this way it's this way
straight away we're we're on our way
over all right all right all right all
right all right all right okay okay okay
okay okay okay
wow how getting hungry do you think a
company has stuff meals probably just
like space meals and stuff like like
umat
solidified oh one of those
food oh hello guess we're here I'll go
this way oh there's a
key
uh oh I didn't mean to drop that there's
a mine over there there's a
mine mine oh my God good
find be nice if we can bring the mine
back you
know oh
who oh that's a yeah that's a she's got
the God
damn how do we deal with that oh get out
get out get out get
out we going do
is got this I felt
something we don't have a shovel though
I'm pretty good running away oh uh it's
okay we going through like the fire exit
or something uh they're going in they're
going
in yeah oh
um we can find the fire exit here yeah
different exit different entrance I
don't know where it is but we'll just
walk around and oh
careful
oh o bravery I don't know if there is a
fire exit actually seems like H Kong
Hong
Hong uhoh no
[Music]
k
no okay you got the
body oh oh here come here
come run
Oh I thought I could grab it I thought I
could grab it I thought I could
grab this is not looking
good
where's the
ship you're going to have to toss Oh no
you're not you
just
H I'm going back you're going
back something weird is happening what
what is happening
feeling anything I can just grab from
outside another
Hive anywhere
nope
unfortunately I I thought I could grab
the hive but I mean we could have some
Allure and then grab the
hive there's a lot of them
around
here left of the ship is the fire exit
which
left this oh my
God oh my
God sorry I'm sorry you got this girl
you go girl what's happening you better
you
better
oh I found the fire exit
over I'm
[Music]
coming oh God en's in there
now that's to
what just happened time it's 500 p.m. oh
boy K you I went through the fire exit I
found the I found the horn and then I
[Music]
died what is that was it a coil head
pretty must have been a coil
head he's why is he just standing would
have made us
succeed talking to herself thinks I
don't hear her but I hear
her surely he
can't around the mountain what are we
seeing a monster is it B on the
outside I am dead no I am
dead yeah n you darn
it some we all went to after that
alive chilling yeah oh that's her being
dead okay okay dang it ah and the other
dot is some uh so maybe
yeah going back is that K Buton just a
giant here right no
doggies um I think they're could be
doggies I'm not sure
but or she going to the exit oh wait I
could ask if there's anyone who can get
around them it's definitely Watson
uh hi guys are you coming back yeah
she's she's
here nice wait so is dead in the in the
thing yes I am dead
hello go it was a noble sacrifice though
I tried to get the arrows this our last
day yeah but we made a lot of money
before I think on the previous day did
we did we I don't know I see okay it's
okay we have I I just that air horn
could have saved
us don't sell the whoes have to sell our
whoopy cushions
[Music]
sorry oh great a not
bad we're going have to the who cushions
playing a song for you guys
everything away with this away with all
of it maybe they'll forgive us I don't
know I think we're going to have enough
we're going to make
it I believe
somebody okay I mean as long as one of
us is
alive we can just ring the bell a lot of
and get the uh tentacle need buy a the
spirit I'll buy aov have a shovel oh
yeah you could buy a shovel wait but if
we buy shovel will we have enough no it
won't affect the money don't affect the
money I'm sorry I'm not really good at
math all good well I guess we can
land
question Yeah question after this should
we maybe just like chatchat a little bit
and do the like talk about the things
we're supposed to talk about yes oh oh
yeah we're supposed to be uhok do we're
supposed to do something that's true I
forgot about that I think another round
would take too
long okay I want to play Moon can
play
L yeah I mean let's get a let's get a
mod let's get mod perms yeah I want to I
want to play okay I need to ask what
else is there anything else we can sell
where's the clipboard s the clipboard
all right now the shovel should be
coming that's so omous the shovel sh
should
be yeah valuable to the
company I think even selling our bodies
isn't going to work you know what what
the didn't know it was coming just
never know
okay oh all the
toys got to sell you Ena
no we couldn't Ed that body they spit it
out oh oh no ena's dead
what real what was walk oh I I don't
think I can
[Music]
any I just wanted to sell the item
before I died
shoot oh is it I
did get away from there he's got a he
can't take it back it's okay whatever
it's okay pretty
aggravated patient huh he
okay take there we
go oh I guess I'm dead right come
on yeah we'll be fine oh think
so that's now right did we hit it didn't
we yeah we
did we did
no we didn't no we didn't we
didn't how much are we short I can't see
true enough do it okay although it is a
good ending although it is a good ending
it is a good ending isn't it when if we
get sent to space that's a nice ending I
mean that is
true but I could still where are you
where you could but you wouldn't we're
just all going to go there together
right we'll always be together right
anyway need a more convincing
argument uh uh takam
[Music]
takam this the
argument all right
okay for now for
now for
now yeah you know
what should beat up
I'm should be both of us yeah that's her
dream no the way around wait did she
jump into the water did she go after G
oh she's not dead cuz she's not talking
to me she's still alive she on on an
adventure though
maybe she
hiding I hear her I think I hear little
sounds where is it is that GAA
GA I know you're like only in disc but
say
something
t wait leave her C hiding somewhere
leave her behind
leave it's too late now what else can
Survivor guess we'll go I'm
leaving Amelia
Watson
oh no check the camera check the camera
o good idea oh it's just like the black
wow I don't know where'd she go we're in
the ship she's she she's coming back
what's she doing messing around
[Music]
silia hi where were
you hey hi yo are
you hey
hey I didn't close the door on you that
was I think
I'm fingers at the end of the
day no man left behind she did she no no
okay wait something's burning she bought
something she bought something you can
buy something
here stop don't tell me she bought the
thing I think I think you mean mine she
want to kill us
she I knew it get her I took your weapon
I you
[Music]
shovel you not the end of me but there's
two go go
[Music]
go start the
ship do this
stop the
ship
open no she opened
it I mean I was going to show
Mur could have taken off on the ship
yeah I was like I'm going to take off
take the
ship should we s her first witness a
cold blooded murder I was going to get
another
a
plan oh my God at the end of the day
there's only room for one sheriff in
this now make the quota
Kell
the's back there's only room for one
Captain it's like the ending of a bad
Space Opera I was killing you I was
trying to save you by getting a
a just doing what has to be done to
satisfy the
company look at that face the face of a
murderer we're still twitching and she's
selling us while we're still
twitching any whoopy
cushions everything wants to selles want
things what are you doing
my did he take the ball
bodes why aren't you
hungry yeah he'll take
them here we go the reaper is
reaping there you go eat
up eat
up she she's like the antagonist at the
end of the movie that like actually took
over the world and just like well time
for a glass of wine sits back what's the
world
not still in the boom box that's for
sure um with that being
said it's
over there's only one one
remains is like a movie he has the boom
box oh we back you are a little you
are
25 look you are I was just doing what
needed to be done wait we were so
close
you we were so
close I don't want to
die
Eed all right girls
fired was nice was
nice can't believe I got fired again oh
suddenly double I leave the
game okay I'll do this
[Music]
W this is your very own autopilot ship
where you will eat and sleep you girls
okay ready to talk I'm ready to
talk unmute C
unmute cie unmute pretty good was okay
Callie yeah Callie cute herself is
she in
TR she's still she's still feeling the
end of the
movie why are you crying
mate crying you look like you're sad
about your actions like you're
regretting what you have done don't you
feel you know guilt regret shame I feel
remorse I do okay I do feel that for
sure for sure for sure what you
believe yeah I a little bit I think your
you don't want to show it but you're s
so deep in your heart you have
remorse okay well yeah I would say I
mean that's apt that's about right maybe
a little bit I just had to do what
needed to be done you know for the sake
of the company and H we were never
meeting that quote but you know I should
I had the opportunity to take the ship
and leave you guys and kill you I should
have taken
it I wasn't going to kill kiar until she
killed you so what were you up toh I saw
you hit
her she doing my job
everybody everybody
everybody first of all happy New Year
from myth Happy New Year
h
may24 a year it's a new year it's 20124
oh my
God I don't know do we want to um do we
want to say like what what we should say
yeah what I don't even know talk about I
don't either okay I have some pictures
prepared I don't have the pictures no
it's just like you know the usual uh the
small my stuff right we are here to
advertise the small small myth stuff
that is still on sale
until oh my God no cute cute a little
while longer um I don't know when it
ends it doesn't say here you guys can go
look at's channel for the Imes I don't
it will be gone soon description Hing
them yeah there's a lot of stuff there's
uh the t-shirts where we're where we're
poking out of the the pockets then
there's the small metal charms there's
also random stickers and the plushies of
course again are also still on sale so
I'm going to put the link in my chat if
you guys I'm waiting on my Shed
Corporation Hey where's my small stuff
this most hang all of them on my my
backpack but then just keep it in my
house so say you go out with that stuff
no no no no no no I just look at it I
put in like a a glass case and I'm like
yeah cool also can't forget the
plushies my Bas plushies give me all of
these line them up on my bed so oh they
a regular restocked item oh they're
regular restocked item oh there is dead
oh nice so I don't know whenever you
want them okay gra them nice well well
well mhm so that was just a reminder and
then there's uh I guess a re
announcement that we have yeah kind of a
a re oh wait hold on a sec first did we
mention the figures we've already talked
about the little figures
right the
boxes yeah they're part of that I guess
part of it they're random you mean those
random ones right yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah they're part of that yeah okie
dokie well then there's another thing
you guys that other thing being we
announced something a little while ago
which is a brand new song right can we
show it a picture yeah I showed a
picture we showed it during the when we
announced
it guys we finally have a release
[Music]
date guys but the song will be released
uh a music video for it will be released
on Janu son of a you would think that I
would
J no January 11th January 11th
2024 12 a.m. jst so when the clock turns
to January 11th hooray hurrah the song
will release on the official Hol live
English Channel so make sure that you
guys check it out I'm probably going to
do a little unarchive karaoke beforehand
to lead into it
so those hands check out our new song
can you play it am on that ukulele yeah
play
it play it am
whoa the you showed
up I'm ready she's nervous wait that can
you can we can do that now yeah we can
do it now it shows up in the groups
cool let's go ready to party so
cute it's I hope you guys will enjoy
it you guys like it it's so cute oops
changed exciting soon TM
soon get flashbacks more flashbacks
every time someone
says being
targeted anyway that's that's really
about it and then we also kind of wanted
to play some lethal company today
together because you know it only seems
fitting funny we all join the fry
together that was that was a good time
someday we got to get on those more
expensive moons we'll we'll be able to
do it
since this is the first myth collab of
2024 do we want to say something nice I
don't know goals or so together down the
line um give a not a speech just say
something I don't know just a short
comment this know I should start I
should start you know what put the
pressure on myy um because I'll be the
example okay cuz I was today's captain
and I did I did betray my entire
ship go ahead and take the punishment
that is starting off um so let's see
2024 since the number four is included
in the year I've decided that this year
I'm going to go um 5 million per um hard
and so I hope you guys will support me
going hard real hard um next month a
bunch of things are happening there's um
a special stream on valent
um that's going to be um about love but
not romantic love it's going to be love
bonic love love of there's going to be a
charity stream on Valentine's
Day for like 12 hours so look forward to
that um I'm not going to announce the
charity or anything like that for a
little bit but that's the plan right now
so look forward to that and then I'm
announcing something big next month um
two big things one is significantly
bigger than the other um it's it's the
it's the big it's the big thing um and
so I'll be doing a 24-hour stream before
that
so yeah yeah so look forward to that I'm
going to work really really hard this
year um and I love I love Holo and all
my friends and um I'm having a lot of
fun thanks to you guys and I think this
year is going to be amazing aming let's
keep having tons of fun together and um
[Music]
yeah that's all I wanted to say
anyway next
up yeah let's go by the
line uh well well well we have Rec it
looks so
stupid perfect we have
recently we have recently expanded
gotten a new gen
Generation Um who are doing their best
working hard U but I'm I you know I hope
that as myth we can still do a lot of
fun things together it's a new year so
let's let's do some cool stuff myth my
cutest gen mates thank you for a
wonderful year 2023 and on to another
one with more power than ever more
energy than ever let's be strong
go go home
[Music]
baby let's not lose to the new energetic
girls all right we're still young and py
py we have it in our nerves and in our
jeans we we are we are the strongest
let's go I'm not wearing go let's next
to you supp to wearing pants go I I want
to I want to actually get the mush guy
for a second mush mushy gushy I
apologize um I just want to I want to
say a genuine thank you to not only my
Miss girlies but also to uh everybody
watching right now for your patience
with me as I uh get my personal life and
all of all of its things together and
the time that I've been away I I really
do appreciate it all of your sweet
messages uh that they do make it back to
me and your fan mail makes it back to me
and my myth girls who are patient with
me and they check in on me and they they
say hi and they they invite me to do
things and they wish me happy holidays
and all of that stuff I want to say
thank you I appreciate it very much and
I hope to be strong for my myth girls in
2024 because I do I do want this to be I
want this to be a happy fun strong year
um with with Miss and Hol life so thank
you everybody
Mina happy happy New Year everybody
Happy New Year
nice nice nice good well said
Kuba said you guys said a lot of things
now you want to say something too you
guys already said a lot of the things I
wanted to say but I hope that this wait
am I muted what hello no no hello hear
you you're here oh oh I muted her cuz
like she was doubling in the game and
here wow she
m you were double at some
point I can't believe you're saying
things so far damn it I was please
repeat everything for
me no I just wanted to say you know um
it's been a wonderful wonderful time
with you guys with chat with everyone um
I hope 2024 is filled with more fun
things and exciting things and let's
let's let's all do our best let's have
fun thank you always everyone to you
guys love you love you
too love right back at
you I guess it's my turn your
turn detective yeah it's been really you
know the time has gone by so fast it's
still crazy to me approaching our fourth
year pretty
much
crazy you know we've been holding strong
we've been we've been doing so much
everybody's always so busy so um I hope
this year we get to have more fun
together and also get you know some a
little bit of time to relax and and
chill but also do the stuff that we
enjoy cuz you know that's what we're
here for cuz we enjoy it
y y
yay and also I will be having my
birthday stream tomorrow
this
is Studio 3D special happy
[Music]
birthday I can't believe we're only five
days into the year what the
hell six days crazy excit I'm my
birthday everybody make sure to mark it
on your calendar if you haven't already
tomorrow 5:00 p.m. PST 8 p.m.
EST
tomorrow I'll be awake I'll be there
[Music]
can't miss out on that it's going to be
exciting I got some
stuff well after this you guys may have
seen But Advent kimono reveals have been
delayed they're after this they start in
50 minutes right oh
exciting W they'll be matching with us
yeah their first outfit so cool I wonder
how they I want to see yeah they're
probably nervous it's true remember our
first reveals we were just like oh God
why am I more nervous than
the I realized something recently now
it's my turn to get like a little mushy
gushy I
guess in the beginning we like we really
didn't know we were doing like at all it
was just five of us you know like kind
of fumbling around in the dark and
trying to figure out like what what kind
of identity is Holo Yen going to have
and now that it's gotten so big right
the group has gotten so big I don't know
it is kind of like a family to be honest
I didn't like saying that before but I
do kind of get that feeling you know
it's it's expanded our our little Holan
family has expanded quite a bit and I
really appreciate all of you guys being
here beside beside me and and all the
fans of myth to kind of like grow along
with us and grow together and I don't
know I'm just I'm really thankful you
know to you guys fans and I hope I hope
we can still keep having a great time
together you know and and just thanks
for supporting us for so long thank
thank you
you thank you myth fans my fans the best
thank you we love you thank you for
supporting us for such a long time
yeah been here from the bearish star
from
the from the yeah
it's okay you're stilling on our hearts
yeah yeah
oh it I can't seem to send everybody to
shiori's stream but I wish I could just
go there just first she first I believe
shor's First
yeah all right guys you know take lots
of screenshot give give them lots of
support I'm sure they're very very
nervous right now need your support so
good watch birthday then yeah so please
look forward to it and um yeah thank you
for watching today everybody thank you
everyone hope you guys have a wonderful
rest of the morning afternoon evening I
guess we can say
ultimate okay 3 2 1
ultimate thank you bye Everybody byebye
by bye bye bye bye
byebye
by bye bye-bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
bye
for