[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
uh
yay hello
hello
i missed you did you miss me
yes
hello
oh my god
they're loud okay
[Music]
actually my voice
oh my god
pong are you already back home
[Music]
hello
okay
i can't say anything but hello
[Music]
i
have to admit i'm a bit you know
[Music]
tired but
um
looking at this week i felt like i kind
of have to stream today
uh you will understand eventually
maybe tomorrow i have a recording and
then on the other day
that i have off i should record a lot of
things too
if possible
so tomorrow
oh my god
yeah
um
and then on the other days i'm busy too
and then you know i need to prepare a
lot of things blah blah blah blah blah
subscribe subscribe
i came back from
the german
neighbor country today
today
and
i think uh some of the cave people
who went to germany
also already came back and some of them
are currently traveling
on their way back and some of them are
not even on their way back yet because
some are staying longer which is great
yeah
i think that's good i'm glad some of you
guys are able to use
yeah spend a bit more time there and use
it as a
as an opportunity to travel
yeah that's really really
nice to hear because i was really
worried anyway about whether or not i
can make it worth your while guys
you know it's just a one day concert
yeah
but
we'll talk about that
[Music]
talk about how the
whole convention was for me from my
point of view
and
and then and then
um i don't know maybe we'll read super
tests i'm not sure
cause i'm tired
but i kind of need to read them because
in the next streams i might not be
reading them
uh what's iris there no no iris did it
like from home but i traveled there i
didn't need to
uh but i went there last year as well
and dokomi is like one of my favorite
conventions
so
you know i
i wanted to also because all my friends
are going to usually to document my
friends are going usually so i wanted to
you know
have fun with them too
go with them because i like conventions
i like going to conventions
or at least i used to
you only got 96 super chats from
previous streams
i don't know if that's a lot or not
i don't know if that's much
but i did i did write in the waiting
room stream that i'm
not going to read those uh out loud but
i'm going to read them previously and i
already know this right now like also
the whole day like when i was talking to
genma doing breakfast and all that and
yesterday night as well
uh
i've i've had a really uh
course course course course
rough
throughout
uh
yeah my my throat
feels
i'm trying to keep it up you
should not be too noticeable but my
fruit feels
sore
and i think it's partially
not only partially but maybe a hundred
percent
because of the concert and me spending
um
how many hours was it
ten
more than ten it was more than ten
ten eleven
[Music]
eleven and a half hours or so
on saturday
in the room
that was
the air conditioning was really strong
and i was doing meet and greets for
hours and the concert and yeah i think
yeah even though
i was
like
constantly drinking tea
i think
it up my throat
yeah
i still feel it
[Laughter]
there was a meeting i was about to like
be like how the did you not know
but then i read your name and i'm like
you're just around
you were
there or was that of
was that my imagination was that a fata
morgana
how do you say that in english
how do you say that
so i just realized
i fixed my
i fixed this
but like i said it oh
doesn't sound very english
um i just came home like
like two hours or so ago
[Music]
so i didn't unpack yet except i got out
my equipment and put it all back in
place where it was because i brought my
own equipment this time
so i'll put it all in the in the usual
spot again
and besides that what did i do i
immediately got uh to work by making a
thumbnail making the schedule putting up
the members
uh
wallpaper
and filling out some documents for some
private stuff
scanning it and sending it for email and
all that
oh
and then i spent 30 minutes cuddling
with my cats because i was tired and
that was right before the stream i did
not fall asleep
but i wish i did
i wish i did
and then yeah it's just i'm
uh i was i was dreading this whole
current
um past week and this week and the
following week actually the whole month
for
being a very busy busy time for me
more like behind the scenes which sucks
because then you guys don't see a lot of
it and you guys don't quite understand
why i say i'm busy unless i like
constantly explain it to you
um but let me just tell you how i'm busy
[Laughter]
um
i wanted to stream today though because
i missed talking to you guys
and
because it's also going to be difficult
in the coming days and weeks
so and also because i
am still like you know as long as my
brain
remembers
what happened the past three days
i want to share it
you know what we could even
with the exciting things that have
transpired i have gained some new cute
photos that i could put on this this
this
what's that board called in english
corkboard
cork right
i was thinking doesn't that sound weird
yeah ah okay amazing so i wrote i tried
to write everything down on my phone
again so i don't forget because my brain
is a thief as you guys know
but then for example on saturday
i was so
swamped
that i did not really
write down anything so i wrote it down
like two days later i hope
i hope i got everything important
down
and um i'm gonna maybe try to show you
some pictures so you can
see
have some visuals and maybe use some
pictures from the kfp at docomi 2022 or
22 hashtag i keep on changing it um so i
hope you guys don't mind i don't i'm not
gonna use the ones where like your faces
are like on like really blatantly okay
don't worry about that
but i want to use some
oh that's cute what the
oh there's some new pictures that i
haven't seen yet
oh man okay let me scroll all the way
down to the beginning and then we can
start talking about it
this girl's gone
don't kill your frog let's already kill
where was you when potential throat was
killed
oh no
no
yes
scrolling
i'll probably um
you guys should maybe start counting my
yarns cause it's gonna be a good number
at the end
it's not a cute pgm i just picked it up
before the stream
will resurrect that's a good question i
would like to know that too
yes okay i think
no that's not
huh
twitter doesn't load anymore even though
that's definitely not the end of the
hashtag
oh because i'm at the top tweet so
i'm not even late as i'm in top okay
sorry
samia sorry one more time
wait what the
my twitter
oh you stupid blue bird
cooperate with me
sorry i really
really i mean i could have uh cancelled
the cuddling with my cats but did i
really have a choice
did i really have a choice
no
no i missed my cats man
i missed him
yeah blue bird
bbb
[Music]
only for calling the class but also
because i needed a moment
a moment of just
chilling in my bed
just silence and
yes serenity
to orange verb yes i was
i think i was using twitter a lot this
weekend
uh but now
now the bluebird we're back here on
the
red
play button thingy all right so
um no these are good oh this is good
this is good this is good because that
has me on it
so it started out here i'm using this
picture from salubrious beats
so no you know what it actually didn't
start out like that i guess there's no
real photos from friday huh maybe i
should
i'll keep this up though
let me start with my friday notes
or my first day notes actually
[Music]
okay okay so number one
it's just gonna go for my that's not my
hand it's a lubricant sorry doc's your
hand
ah
i will just i will just like go through
my notes okay
so the first thing says
oh yeah yeah
so i flew in on the first day
uh
i have a throat candy here
already died
i have these old ones maybe these are
still
good
hello
fruit gummies
pizza's right next to me is so cute
you're still together
[Music]
i'm so cute okay so
following thing
the following things have transpired
during dukami 2022
i flew on
[Music]
thursday
how many times am i going to lose
my
[Music]
train of thought
part of train train the foot
um yeah on the first day oh sometime
oh yeah i didn't i have a
oh yeah
i have a stream do you guys remember i
had a stream on first day
cause like um
[Music]
before that week
at the end of the week i was like okay
so i gotta i gotta
do the iris collab at some point next
week before dokomi
um in the document week
and so i message her like on sunday and
that's like right after she already
pulled out her own schedule
for a couple days
and then i'm like okay well let's see
where we can squeeze it in
and
yeah we had some
issues so it didn't really fit in
anywhere else besides that so we had to
do it
um
on the morning
on this day when i was about to leave
um to go to dokomi to go to dusseldorf
yeah
uh
and and the whole week i was also so so
busy but i tried my best to prepare and
and teach her some things
uh prepare some useful phrases that she
did actually end up using wonderful
um honestly i did put that
that one phrase in as a joke i wanted to
be like haha as if she would use that
just like i wanted to give her useful
phrases and then that one was the punch
line like
no way she's gonna use that
keyword can you actually give her
something useful
and then surprise surprise she ended up
using it
damn it
um
and she made a
you know and she didn't just say
the sentence no she made a whole bit
about it she stayed on that topic for
quite some time
um
so
i felt
very guilty
what have i done
but anyway so on the first day after the
stream
with iris i had to pack i had to speed
pack that's why i ended it so abruptly
and um
yeah i actually
i was really stressed out i didn't
really have much time i had to pack in
like
i think i had like two hours
uh
and i thought i thought two hours is
enough
but i didn't only have to pack i also
had to kind of like low-key at least
like
shallowly superficially clean my
apartment and do some other stuff that i
already forgot
yeah
packing rta holy i underestimated
the amount of things i had to find and
put together and put in my suitcase
i did not forget anything though no no
no no i don't think i forgot anything
and everything went well i'm glad i
brought my equipment i mean
forgot not really forgot i i
purposefully didn't pack some certain
things that were prepared for me then at
and document thankfully
oh
yeah oh yeah oh yeah you know the night
before
um
the iris
german collab i was like on up until
like 2 a.m 3 a.m
recording those vr videos trying to
figure out like
um
you know
i had some issues i was i told emma like
i think i can do it alone don't worry
about it i'm just recording something on
green screen but then i did have some
issues like uh i didn't realize that i
was in the wrong version of our world so
like some buttons weren't there and i'm
like am i am i blind how stupid
am i i can't message her to ask where
that so obvious probably so obviously
place button is and kept on looking
looking and i also i you know i i did
try to practice
the ulta game moves a few times to
figure out what fits the best
um and have some variation you know like
the towel thing for example i did do
that on the night before as well
no no on that night i guess yeah
um for like one or two hours
um and it's still
it's
hard it was hard to remember when i was
actually recording it
eventually i figured everything out and
i was able to record it on my own i feel
so grown up now my first arrand
had
[Music]
first time i recorded something on my
own the first time i you i went into the
our vr world on my own i usually always
we usually always get invites from amit
but this time i was like i mean i don't
want to disturb you maybe
maybe i can enter the world on my own
and try to do it myself record it on obs
and all that
and some of you may have wondered why
did i use eggiara
what's the problem of using eggiara
first of all but
uh
i thought you know i don't know i think
it
embodies the spirit more
and fits quite well and kind of embodies
you guys too
um you know
yeah i thought it made sense
i was like
what outfit should i use and i was like
scrolling through the vr outfit so i
have so far and then i'm like oh
you're right i have that egg model
oh i forgot about that
i was like oh could be funny if i use
that
hmm yeah so i did that but then i
realized i really really really really
don't
even have time
to cut it and overlay the music and all
that because i was also going to use it
at the concert
um and in order to sync it up with the
instrumental i needed to
you know edit it so that uh it's a video
that i play on obs
the green screen video i played on obs
and use it as an instrumental for those
four songs
while legit had no time
so
um i want to say thank you
to cow carrot
for um helping me out with that
really quickly
glad you had time
and kyle carrot wasn't the only person
who helped me out
in my times of emergency need
yeah
which i'll talk about too
are coming in in the clutch yeah
[Music]
tascada really
and yeah
so i got those videos and then i
uh
on the first day um
after the collab i flew this is gonna
take a while i'm already transiting so
much
i flew to
germany and the thing is
that
i think already when i was
um
boarding the plane i noticed a few
obvious very obvious
convention goers document visitors
are already at
at the airport you don't want to know
why i noticed because they were wearing
lolita fashion
stood out so much
very obvious i'm like
this flag is going to dusseldorf you're
wearing lolita fashion i know where
you're going
yeah already on thursday um
yeah they were lolita too
in the plane
that is dedication yeah
not only them i noticed some other
people too because
there was like
there were like people i've seen at
conventions
before
but i didn't talk to them because don't
really have a connection with them
but yeah that was interesting so i
boarded the plane and you know what okay
this this is for a while we're not even
gonna reach the convention part
thank you guys for the member thingies
so
i checked myself in to a seat
um
that once again i would like to share
with you my seat hacks my travel hacks
but it's not much of a heck i guess
actually it's not really a hack at all i
guess
um
i
this time for the first time in my
lifetime
i got myself
a seat at the emergency room without
knowing
yeah
without rowing i was like oh this this
road still has a window seat i guess
i'll take that one
it's completely empty i'll take that one
i did end up having a seat next to me
open
but yeah i was actually excited about
sitting in an emergency room excited and
also scared
at the check-in calendar they told me oh
you're in the emergency room are you
prepared to take
that kind of
um
pressure
they ask me like if i'm okay with the
what's the word not obligation though
[Music]
what's the word
the
the duty the responsibility as a
responsibility and i'm like oh
yeah yes
question mark and then the lady at the
counter was like you know at the very
unlikely case and i'm like yeah yeah i
guess so yeah yeah
[Music]
if you say it's unlikely okay let's do
it
so then when i was boarding the plane
uh the lady oh and yeah that's the thing
at this okay never mind it is a it is a
travel hack because this is the thing i
was excited about
it got me like priority boarding
among the ones with the with the babies
i was the first to board
even before the ones who had actual
priority
[Music]
on their tickets
emergency seats go before them
[Music]
emergency
exit
no no not before the babies kind of like
after the with the babies yeah
yeah yeah yeah and then
yeah i got in very early smoothly
it waited for everybody else to bullet
and then they were like yo are you are
you okay um are you okay with like
lifting because you're on the window
are you girl are you okay with the
responsibility
of opening and
lifting this 15 kilogram door
in case of an emergency and i'm like
yes
at that moment when i realized wait what
15 kilograms
eh
but i just said yes
sure because i didn't want to lose my
window seat
yeah there was like a british sounding
guy
uh like not quite next to me but like
there was a seat between us open
but he was like on the on the aisle
and
was looking at me and like laughing and
he said some kind of joke or something
uh and i'm like maybe you should be
sitting here you look stronger than me
but now i want my windows seen
so i was actually i really felt the
responsibility
and even though i'm normally like not
that worried about
um
you know
planes crashing and all that i don't
really worry about that i've fluent so
much by now that i don't really
i don't really
worry about it so
but in this situation
i felt so
responsible
i felt this duty this pressure
that i looked at the
i think i was the only one in my row
that really seriously looked through the
instructions when the flight attendant
told us
to look at the instructions because
we're in the emergency room and they're
they're just like
and i'm like i was studying them
pretty seriously
because i'm like sid
life depends on me
holy it's time for me to be a hero
let's go
i'm responsible
you never know
what if it happens and i up because
i didn't read it properly and people are
gonna be like chihuahua dot dot dot
huh
i wanna be dr daughter
what's the pronunciation
so um
fortunately
nothing happened and i did not get to
lift the 15 kilogram door
um and
but
another reason
another thing
that proves that i was really
responsible i was kind of tired and like
thinking about
dozing off but then i was like i can't
doze off
i can't
i have a responsibility
i need to be awake at all times during
this flight
it was a short flight anyway but if i
wasn't in the emergency room i would
have probably closed my eyes but then
before this
i was like
for the whole
for the whole flight
i was like
i'm awake i'm awake i'm ready to rescue
you guys i am responsible
leave it to me everybody in the airplane
i will i will lift this 15 kilogram door
and i will lead you to safety if i must
yes i think i took it very seriously
so
i think i'm ready to
take on the duty of emergency row a few
more times again
i'm a hero
full-time hero part-time warrior
no i'm serious what the
i'm serious wouldn't you want someone
like me to sit in the emergency room
wouldn't you want someone like me huh
huh
i took it so seriously
you guys suck hey
oh man hey there's no one else that
takes it more seriously than me honestly
the other people didn't give a
you want them to sit in the emergency
room alone without someone who takes
your wow
wow
wow okay
no trust after all this time you don't
trust me
amazing
but 15k look
well i mean
yeah
never mind so anyway
uh that was nice
unfortunately i was not able to leave
the plane first
how i entered it first
that was sad
and nobody gave me an applause at the
end of the flight either
[Music]
i wonder why
i saved their life in theory
like in some in some alternative
timeline
i saved their life
and yet they did not
applaud me at the end of the flight
it's kind of rude
but okay
maybe they applauded in an alternative
timeline too
well
so yeah they didn't appreciate my
heroism no no they didn't i did not
um
so i arrived and i
made my way to the
hotel
and
my managers were not there yet uh
so anyway i took a shower
and then i waited for my friends to be
ready
who were also already there on thursday
to go have dinner
yeah
and on thursday i went of course
immediately straight to tonkatsu
gonta
the one i told you about before
uh i saw some of you guys eating there
today for lunch
i mean i saw you on twitter i didn't see
you in person
some of you guys posted you guys eating
in a group there then sweet
yeah good job i'm glad you guys went
there that is a must-go restaurant
last year it wasn't open during dokomi
because dokomi was during a different
time last year
and they were closed on vacation i was
like what the
what the actual
talk about the place was so good
i'm glad you liked it oh man i know
watching you right now together
[Music]
i heard a lot of you guys went on friday
yeah yeah
yeah so i went on first day
and
oh yeah i actually made a reservation so
i didn't have to wait in line
i'll do
if i remember correctly
on first day there wasn't even a line
but i made a reservation just in case
anyway
thanks for the plus
yeah and we got uh we got some yummy
katsu um
the friends however
dad i went with on thursday
for
a weird reason
this usually doesn't happen
i didn't meet them anymore
until
and i thought i wouldn't meet them at
all anymore i met them
at the very very very last moment when i
jumped into my uber
with my
suitcase
uh i'll tell you more about that later
maybe
but i was really in time stress i
couldn't even like hug them or anything
but i only saw them on first day and
then sunday for one second i was like hi
bye hello i'm about to miss my flight
bye-bye
so
yes i jumped into my uber yes
yes
so that was funny um i didn't see them
anymore i had i saw a lot of friends but
i didn't see them anymore they were like
in a complete completely different
part of the convention most of the time
apparently and on saturday i i was
i was just the whole
day from morning till night in the same
spot like
imprisoned anyway
so i didn't see a single person
basically besides genma
yeah
but anyway
so i had some leftover katsu
um because i didn't finish but i wanted
to eat it like a little bit later i have
a small tummy i wanted to eat it like a
little bit later so i i took it
to the hotel
and after the dinner i greeted um
oh janma and henna and my also came and
one more uh cover stuff i greeted them
in the lobby
and they actually coincidentally
also
um
arrived with some
guests that i also greeted some special
guests from the convention that was nice
seeing them mm-hmm
who's hannah i am his manager
i'm his manager yes
don't ask me why
henry in particular came but
yeah
and i was there gemma was there
henma helped out
a lot the other cover stuff as well
um but with me mostly was gemma did you
shout and run to the gym when i was like
sitting inside and then i saw from the
outside i saw outside the genma and him
and so on were coming in and like
i stood up i didn't run against them
because in front of them where like
those other people
so i was like
standing but jumping like
i was something like this
and laughing and
and then
once genma saw me she
had a big smile on her face
and then finally when there was space
i ran at her and she ran at me too this
time
so cute
i gave each other a big hug
i was so happy
yeah the other people they just all like
walked into the hotel so chill it was
late and
and yeah it was late and dark and
everybody was just fairly quiet and then
there was just me and gemma like
bouncing and jumping and hugging and
like yeah yeah
we have some some special bond okay
[Music]
cute indeed
and then
yeah they arrived really late
so anyway
um
i waited for gemma to check in
to the room
and
then genma kind of started exploring
um
her room and and she was looking for
like hot water
because she brought
and
she brought cup noodles and she wanted
to eat dinner because like everything
was closed outside
and there was no nothing
around in there
though
and then i i was like damn i still have
leftover katsu gemma i still have
leftover cutter you can have it you can
have it if you want you can have it if
you want and for a while she kept on
turning it down but eventually she was
so desperate for food she said she was
so hungry
yeah there was no kettle in the room i'm
like we were like what the
i think there was like hot water
somewhere like in the lobby
but
i don't know for some reason
she didn't end up using that
so
she said in the end that my leftover
tonkatsu
was
a life savior
so here i go i finally you know get the
what's the word confirmation
the recognition that i am a hero in the
plane they didn't give a for me
being their hero
pajama cared yeah i got my hero moment
i'm like i'm i'm so glad i got this
leftover katsu
i'm so glad i didn't leave it at the
restaurant
i'm so glad i brought it to the hotel
and had it ready for gemma to eat
oh yeah by the way i also gave genma and
hannah and the other cover stuff i gave
them
uh some souvenirs
i gave them i gave hemma the same
chocolate cakes i gave to reina
and i gave genma some
fancy austrian
tea
from the famous sakura hotel
where also the cake is from
and i also gave the gave genma
some sand
yes gave her some sand from the maldives
because i i bought like several tiny
bottles
of
maldives sand
in tiny bottles it's cute and it's like
the
the bobble cap
has like um
a cute small maldivian shell on it and
an inside is also like
a
golden accessory shell is like dangling
inside
it's cute it's pocket sand yeah
yeah
they sell that in souvenir stores
um
i guess i could have bottled it up
myself but whatever
i bought it
i have more of those i was thinking of
giving it to like myth members or so i
don't know
uh
yes so i gave that to her
and henry also gave like a
mozart of chocolate i think
i think i did no
yes i was giving um presents
away
yeah and
so that's that so we exchanged exchange
to no i no exchanging
only chihuahua giving gifts and i was
very happy to give gifts what did i just
do very cool
yeah
um
oh yeah
and then uh we did exchange something
because genma gave me
about um 200 cards from
to sign autograph cards and it was
already like 11 pm or something
and i'm like okay
okay
leave it to me
uh
but i think
what it
i didn't sign them on thursday because
it was already so late and i wanted to
sleep i think
i think you assigned them
friday night
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah a lot of cars yeah
so anyway on
friday
uh
after sleeping a night
oh yeah i got family to see i got some
yeah yeah some family that's partially
from like christmas
i got one of them thank you really i'm
glad
good to hear
not a signature stamp no no handwritten
that's why it looks so
you generally you only get family when
you see them well i mean i think the
other members get it sent to them via
mail
uh
like once
i don't know once a year or twice a year
maybe
uh but i
i don't know we we meet
at dokomi usually so
that's our thing now so genma just
brings it to me whenever
we see each other yeah
sometimes it gets sent to me together
um with like other things that cover
sends me like for example when there's
like new merchandise
um from like events from whole life or
whatever then
um they sent me some samples so that i
can have some of it
and then they often
put in some of the fan mail
if i send you a letter now you'll read
it in a year no i think i would rate it
earlier
um
earlier than that i think definitely
yeah yeah
this year i'm seeing more occasions
to receive fan mail yeah
i need to move on holy i'm talking
so much
uh oh yeah oh yeah what i did on
thursday night before going to sleep i
uploaded those videos and i premiered
them all
and you guys were like
what the why are you making it into
instant premieres why oh my god there's
more oh wait there's more
yeah yeah bamboozle
i just did instant premieres because it
didn't matter
i just i originally just wanted to do it
without the premiere but then i added
premiere because i felt like you know
seeing you guys in the chat would be fun
yeah
so then you saw my cringe
but cute
uh
instructions
yeah i wanted to upload them as early as
possible so you guys still have some
time to
get it into your system
[Music]
that's what i did on friday
it was thursday and on friday i woke up
early had breakfast with grandma
and then i did some stuff with friends
for me
donkey wonky
there's some stuff with friends
uh
uh yeah uh before
before
later in the day
on friday i started i think the
microphone is kind of not not perfectly
uh situated
oh maybe that's better
later in the day of friday
uh
i had
rehearsal
and
uh rehearsal
[Music]
what
was
uh kind sorry i'm just answering my cat
was kind of
difficult
yeah
let's just say things were not perfect
um
oh my god what are you doing
uh
i reserved for us
um dinner in a restaurant
uh because i wanted
to have some fancy dinner with my
management
meow before everything starts getting
stressful
um
and i booked it kind of like i reserved
it kind of like
half an hour
after the approximate ending of the
rehearsal
was like planned to be like an hour wow
and the problem was
uh i'm gonna be too exact i guess
but
um
let's just say i didn't get to rehearse
at all
because things were not
properly
ready
and uh
yeah we spent most of the time setting
up and trying to
make things work
uh
so that was a problem
but i kept on like
saying like i don't want
to be late for dinner
i don't want to be late for dinner
[Music]
so i i ended up not being able to really
rehearse for my
uh concert i just like
sang the songs after dinner on my own
like actually so what i did
we went to dinner and that was funny for
many reasons
but
um
i was like we have to we can't stay for
too long yeah because i have to go back
into the room where i was doing
everything
um
and rehearse because i was basically
just like wasting my time and was just
on standby figuring things out during
the actual rehearsal
so i didn't get to do anything
so around like 10 p.m or so
uh i think we left dinner
went back and me and genma went back to
do work
gemma was like
sitting next to me working and i was
just singing and practicing and
preparing my
my stage on obs my settings preparing
the green screen syncing it up writing
the mc
everything
um
and then
the thing is there was another staff
there like kind of keeping the room open
for us and waiting for me to end it too
they said it's no problem but i kind of
felt bad about going too long and then i
also was like obviously getting very
tired too
so at some point i was like telling
myself okay i need to i need to finish
up at midnight
yeah um so i was just singing singing
singing practicing because i still
needed to practice some strider's song
and prison melody a little bit more and
viva happy
because i wasn't perfect with those
songs yet
i practiced them to sing them for the
first time at the concert
yeah so it was i was practicing until
midnight and was really busy and
tired and so tired
it's at midnight we leave the room
finally
um
and yeah say good night
and then oh
yeah yeah that's the thing i wasn't done
because
we left the room at midnight but then i
had to sign the meet and greet cards
um so that they would be ready at least
for for the meet and greet people
um
and they started signing
and i
didn't realize that with writing names
of the participants because i had like
about 50 participants
it takes a lot of time for each
signature so i wrote 50 signatures in
like what
one and a half hours or so
i think it took about
that amount of time and it took me
longer than it should have probably
because i
[Music]
um
i was uh
i was really tired
i was i was chilling with you guys in
pre-chat on the side right i had
pre-chat open to communicate with you
guys because i felt like lonely maybe
too
and um
i had that open i updated you guys how
it was going and i'm like i'm so
tired
and then at some point i realized i
can't do them all i can only do these 50
for now
uh
and then maybe after the concert between
the concert ending
and the
first meet-and-greet
group i had a one-hour time window so i
was like in that one hour i'm gonna
write the remaining autographs which was
like
i think like a hundred more
because i said
this wasn't even necessary this was me
just saying i want to give something to
everybody who applied for the meet and
greet to
have
so that they're not sad about not making
it into the meet and greet
i want to give something to everybody
so
it was
my decision
because i won't so i can't really
complain but i'm just saying it took a
lot of time
so at 2 00 a.m i think i finally stopped
writing the autographs and
uh genma of course was also still awake
and like genma
gemma hi i'm i'm done with these
autographs
do you want them
good night
and then i fall dead into bed
and i wake up around like i woke up at
like
8 30 or something
i had breakfast
then
um
we went to the room again and had like a
last text check because my concert was
although i might have maybe i woke up at
night or something what it doesn't
matter but i had another tech check and
then i practiced some more
and the problem
was
the line was so long ah
were you there too
nice happy were you
there with so many of you guys
so many
up i know
we're in land by 7 40. i'm so glad you
guys were there so early i was like holy
really scared that you guys wouldn't
like make it in time
in hindsight missed the first few
minutes ah that's nothing compared to
like you know
some others who missed it completely i'm
glad you got in
got in early
yeah the thing is like
um
they were still letting people in at the
when when my concert was happening there
was still a two kilometer
line to enter the convention
and they were slow
because not everybody wanted to go to my
concert but there were definitely people
who wanted to go
um
and they couldn't
yeah they were there before the opening
yes or no like around the opening time
which was i think 10.
and then
yeah they didn't make it in time made it
in at 11 40. oh man
[Music]
yeah but anyway i um
i tried my best at the concert
and
in case you didn't watch it
it was amazing you can still watch the
the archive on twitch right now
and i'm hoping to upload the free songs
where i had dancers
on my channel
i asked them if i can do that because
that was something that i prepared
for my performance out of my pocket i
wanted to make it more special so i
wanted to be on my channel because it's
really hyped i really really am
proud of that
um
so
[Music]
let me tell you my set list here it is
so i started a stardust song
i think it was surprising to you guys
you probably didn't expect me to sing
stardust song
uh that was a bit difficult to learn but
very very fun to sing
and then i did a fever night and i did
hinotonii
then i did journey like a thousand years
and i did sparks
then
um
then i brought in the dances during
arena circulation
we continued on with viva happy
and then we
took a picture with everybody
which i will show you
and then
uh we did hi challenger they learned my
challenger choreo i'm so glad i was able
to
uh
show you guys the choreo a little bit
early
through not my own body but someone
else's body nicer
yeah and and you know i thought of the
idea to
have you guys
rotate talos during that and you guys
did so great it looked so fun on the
stream as well
and then i ended it with prison melody
without the dancers hmm
let me get a picture
from my twitter you probably saw it
this is not the whole haul because the
it was taken with with a phone
and
it wasn't wide angle enough to capture
the sides
but there were uh more rows on the left
side and on the right side but the most
scared people
were i think very motivated and
therefore all went into the middle you
see a lot of orange in the middle
yeah the more shy people the ones who
wanted to just sit and just watch where
on the sides or at the top
i'm hidden
in this photo but there was another
photo where most of you guys were
visible
oh
so the thing is
that i personally have some regrets
about
gonna be honest is that
yes i know this is not completely full
but it could have been
if the entrance would have been
faster or earlier
or if my performance wouldn't been at
eleven o'clock like the first act in the
day i'm gonna be
honest when i saw the time schedule
i asked uh can i not be later in the day
why am i the first i have bad feelings
about this
i don't really want to be the first act
i feel like usually at conventions the
first act that's kind of the shittiest
time slot you get usually
because
usually the hall will be super empty
but yeah it wasn't changed and i was the
first one and
people in making it in time
made me sad but
they've fixed it for the following day
giving an early entrance two hours early
they started letting people in at eight
a.m
which i wish they would have done for me
i wish they would have done that for me
too
it's like you know i was uh on the first
day
so mistakes are made on the first day
and then
it gets fixed on the second day
that's kind of sad 8 a.m for both days
and it did let people in
but it was still two kilometer line at
like 10 a.m or something i think they
just kind of did it differently on the
on the second day i heard
like how they let people in
oh because i don't think the line was so
bad on the second day
um
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah the thing is a
lot of people came early on sunday while
on saturday most people came kind of
like
later
uh
like they came i heard a lot of people
came like at ten
hmm
yeah yeah and then from learning from
the mistake obviously people also came
earlier on sunday from hearing oh
didn't make it to the
to the concert guys i guess i gotta be
earlier on sunday
yeah
so that's sad um but still very full and
still good turnout and you and you guys
were so passionate
all the pen lights were so great to see
unfortunately i saw everything with um
approximately a 5 to 10 second delay
because
i actually
it was a bit different last year but
this year my only feedback was
twitch
so
and and because it would be confusing to
hear myself double
i did not even have
audio feedback i just saw your hands
cheering
and
guessed
when you would be cheering how long you
would probably be cheering
and try to adjust it just by my sheer
imagination
yes
i did not have time to watch it yet
i want to watch the whole archive
yeah i will
but i didn't have time yet i will watch
the whole archive so i can actually hear
everything properly i did hear like some
clips on twitter from like recordings
not from twitch but like from people who
were actually there
um i heard uh i saw and heard
you guys there and that made me happy i
was like really really surprised you
guys were actually that loud like
oh
[Music]
hotel
but
i
once again don't have
time currently if you guys wouldn't mind
waiting until next week then we can do
it next week
we can't do it next week
maybe next monday
i want to do that too actually
yeah nice okay
sounds fun
yeah
[Music]
okay so
where was i oh yeah so concert um
[Music]
the dances they were so great how
surprised were you guys when they came
out you didn't expect it i think i told
you guys i prepared something special
for it
uh but nobody expected this i think i
was shook i want to hear the the
surprise from everybody when they first
came out
i want to hear the audio from that i
wonder if people were like oh
did you go guys go like oh
was it audible
caught me off guard very surprised
shook
we did like whoa really
i did too surprised to speak
no more like oh aha fauna style
yes yes
yeah
um
i post here on this photo in 3d but
um i i did uh want to document 3d
but
not possible
so
um i was like okay um
3d not possible
the
food court not possible
and then a whole live move also
we couldn't do a whole live move
so i'm like
i actually made the decision to add the
guests
pretty late
one month i think they had to learn
the songs
and at the same time they told me
they were studying for finals
and i think one or both of them also got
sick
and other things happened so they had a
lot of troubles
but
they still managed to do so well yeah
they nailed it and those songs
especially heart challenger they said
that was one that was the most difficult
one
they said that the songs were pretty
difficult to learn i can imagine
um
so i really respect them for doing so
great and by the way uh we have here on
the left we have nate and on the right
we have hanako
they're from like um
like a dancing
uh
cosplaying dancing group for that
performs at conventions
uh called stellaria they do it while um
cosplaying as love live characters and
they perform love live songs and all
that at german conventions
and yeah and like a month ago
i actually
i met them
um
[Music]
somewhere and i'm like
like we talked and we got into talking
and
i was like hmm
what do you think about me dancing at my
concert
and they're like that would be so cool
yes i'm like okay
let's do it
and then we started planning
um
yeah
and i was thinking
uh about what what to have them to dance
and i thought you know
vocaloid songs that have good choreos
and ordinary circulation has a very
famous choreo
we did get them permission from the
choreography creators
that we could perform it on stage
gotta be proper with everything
yeah and uh yeah and i thought um
it would be too difficult for them to
learn all of my original songs choreos
so i just went for heart challenger
and then i wanted to align it in the
setlist so that it would be around the
end so that it would be extra hype
and then even more hive i thought you
know i understand that heart challenger
is not everybody's favorite song of mine
but i thought it was amazing to um hype
up at the end of a concert
so i think you guys felt that
especially with the dancers
one day i will dance that choreo myself
i'm gonna be honest i don't know the
choreo yet
but i have to learn it for
future purposes
oh by the way i also want to say thank
you to dakuma for
um
making that
uh waiting room
graphic for me
dakuma was another person who came to
the rescue for me because i asked i was
like it was in the middle of the night
when i think when i was signing
meeting great cards i think i was like
come on can you help me i don't have
photoshop on my laptop and i'm getting
oh desperate please help me and tagama
was like yes about it immediately
[Music]
getting help from you guys really saved
my butt cow carrot and dakuma
and of course the fan booth we got to
talk about that too
but yeah was there anything else i
wanted to say
uh
i had a delay
that that was why the whole like taking
a photo
section was so awkward and the times in
between when the dancers put on like
their knee protectors
i didn't know when they were done
because my video feed was 10 seconds
delayed i had no audio feedback
uh
so
it was really awkward
oh so awkward i am
especially the photo part because i was
trying to communicate to them that i
wanted to take one alone and one with
them and so on
uh and apparently they told me later on
that they barely heard me on stage
i
think i know what they mean like um
there's like
uh
there's there's speakers on the stage
towards the
performer
but even then if you don't have an ear
monitor
it's so hard to hear on the
stage for some reason the acoustics
are weird
and ear monitors usually are only
prepared at like big professional big
beak concerts
not much
not often prepared at smaller events
like this even though it was still kind
of large scale
it's really hard to hear
very different from what you guys hear
on the other side yeah
so they didn't really hear me
they didn't hear you about the photo
they knew it beforehand what i was gonna
do and i think they roughly heard the
kiwa voice roughly
well it was difficult um
yeah yeah
so that was that let me look at my notes
[Music]
ah
you know what i'll keep that for
a wind waker
um
[Music]
i wouldn't wake a attention
okay
[Music]
oh yeah after the concert
um while doing tech check for the meet
and greet
for one hour like i was on standby in
front of my laptop i was like giving
feedback yes i hear you yes i can see
you
yeah this is fine ah now i have now i
hear my own voice double i was doing
that while i was signing about a hundred
extra autograph cards and this time i
was not tired as so i at least made
it in time
i exactly took one hour to finish them
that's why
that's why they
might have arrived kind of late at the
booth
i'm sorry i wanted to do it earlier but
it was impossible
it was so much work
yeah i underestimated it uh so that's
why they came kind of late but yeah it's
made my story
yeah i was like i kept on signing it and
uh in order to dr dry it i always gave
it to gemma who was sitting right next
to me and she would line up the cards
and have them dry
and then i kept on asking gemma how many
more and then no it just didn't get any
less i'm like what the
so then at one o'clock we were supposed
to have the first
meet and greet group
i was gonna have it half and half
one before the panel 20 like around 25
people before the panel and around 25
people after the panel approximately
giving each meet and greet about one and
a half hours plus
time slot
so after the one hour standby with tech
check and writing meet and greets at one
o'clock i was ready i was sitting in
front of my laptop and it was just not
starting nothing was happening i'm like
[Music]
oh yeah
what's what's the problem what's the
problem
yeah
so then after like 20 minutes of me
waiting we figured out
that
outside of the meet and greet room not
many people were waiting it was actually
they told me there's three people and
i'm like
i mean there's three people
what what do you mean and then i started
panicking
because
this means that
we have to add them
onto
the second group
and
[Music]
um
that means that i would have to do meet
and greets about three to four hours
with no break
continuously and even go over
time into the night uh after the
convention ends
so and at that point when we realized
what the problem was is that documents
send emails without stating the time
when it actually is happening they told
them
in the email group one group two your
group run your group two
but as far as i know the email was like
uh it only stayed at one time and that
one time was for the group 2 time
so around 20 minutes in to the meet and
greet like i was waiting to let in the
free people i didn't want to let them in
just yet because uh
i wanted more people to to join but at
some point it was like okay well i guess
we'll just do the three people that are
standing outside and hope that more are
coming while we're doing these meet and
greets here
and i tweeted out people please come to
the meet and greet there's a mistake
please come now
but unfortunately only one more person
joined
the news didn't make it in time
uh so in one hour i did four meet and
greets and that was
a big problem for us
yeah
we
had a time slot and a very busy schedule
and could not make use of it and that
was really bad
really bad yeah
i'll say that it was really bad
yeah
so um and then and then
after the meet and greet
uh
we had a little break for
lunch i think
and then oh
[Music]
what i'm not moving you guys hear me
i think my yeah my camera crashed sorry
[Music]
perfect face that's a brain head empty
face
i'm back in a second
uh
yeah then we had a little break for
lunch
um
i got some bento
but
bento came
a little bit late
so
and i was like i don't know
not not quite feeling
the act of eating food at that moment so
i didn't eat much and i'm so glad i
didn't
because i really needed my
my bantu leftovers for later in the day
so
uh we had a little break and then we
went back uh
we sat in the room the whole time
actually me and janma forever forever
together
and then the panel started the german it
was german but uh you guys were still
watching thank you
on twitch and
in the real audience
let me try to get a picture of that
[Music]
yeah here it is
so we actually did this last year as
well
we did do this last year
last year the topic was different
uh it was like these these three people
on the stage they're like organizers of
doklami
and they always do like a panel and they
asked me if i want to be a guest again
and i was like yeah sure why not i guess
uh yeah it wasn't german though and oh
[Music]
and um
it was about childhood heroes
and i was like
childhood here i don't really have a
childhood hero and i even asked you guys
in the in the waiting room guys did i
ever mention childhood heroes did i ever
say
something about that because i really
can't remember anything especially like
it was supposed to be travel heroes from
animes but
i didn't really feel like i had
something like that so i was trying to
brainstorm and the few things that i
came up with was like paramore i did
mention that
uh and which the italian comic i did
also mention that
um and then i did my best to tangent off
of that and throw in some
points to contribute to the
conversation somehow
although i did feel it
partially awkward
i don't know this this kind of like
podcast style i think that's what
they're
they were trying to do because it was
supposed to be a podcast um
where
you know in podcasts
people usually talk kind of calmly right
like in a radio show
and i get that but being part of it
myself when i'm used to being a streamer
who tries to
be energetic during my streams
and
like
never have like
any silence and all that i don't know i
felt it was a very very very different
style
of
conversation and it felt to me just so
unusual that i felt like it was awkward
but i guess that's just podcast style i
don't know
um
and i tried my best to kind of like
think of things that are somewhat
somewhat related to the topic and like
go far far far
dimension
yeah i threw in some
some topics
yeah when they asked like they asked
like uh what do you think
um
who do you think the
future childhood heroes will be if in
the past it was like anime characters or
whatever
or musicians who do you think it will be
in the in the
in the future and i already knew by
their faces
that
this was gonna be a hmm
thinking moment for them so i just i
just threw it out there i said take
tick tock people famous satan people
and then that was actually good because
that i think really um brought up a good
a good somewhat at least a topic a topic
because then we started tangent thing
off of tick tock
and i think it's not even that far off
maybe not necessarily childhood
they're hopefully not necessarily going
to be childhood heroes
um
but tick tock has definitely been taking
over uh and making a lot of people
famous and then those people who became
famous i see them like there was like
was it a nest like show or something
else maybe not netflix but i saw like a
review
i didn't saw the show itself but i was i
watched a review a very serious
um deep review of uh a show a survival
show not really survival i guess i
didn't get kicked out but like a contest
show
with tick tock tick tock tick tockers a
bunch of teenage tick talkers like half
of them were boys half of them were
girls
and they had like daily challenges to
make tick tocks it was like reality tv
and and like the reviewer he was also
like literally who are these people but
um
it was so funny
and then they had this one uber
tick-tocker that were like it was their
moderator and the person they listen to
and the person they always got advice
from
and
they would like as a reward for winning
a challenge they would be able to have a
conversation with that person through a
screen and
again literally who
i have no idea i don't even have the app
on my phone
um
but
it was funny how they tried to make a
reality tv show with tick tockers when
this is the thing like i i don't mind
like tick tock being a thing and all
that but the thing is
that if you were like famous on tick
tock i know that it's really hard to
like
bring that audience into other social
media channels of yours
they usually stay within tiktok and
usually they don't really care for
anything else you do i mean of course
there are exceptions but you know if you
start out and blow up on tiktok then
it's hard to
channel them to your other social medias
but anyway
that was funny so we talked a bit about
tik tok
uh the pound was okay
um i just felt the
awkward throughout the whole thing
i don't know i felt like i couldn't
really
that was that was just not my topic
it was just not not my topic
and the last year topic was better for
me going to conventions the topic was
conventions i think last year
and this year it was childhood heroes
from animes and i just don't have one so
yeah
but you guys are still sitting in the
audience and nodding
even though most of you didn't even
understand german i said that in the
beginning of the panel because i wanted
to warn these guys on stage i wanted
to warn them
if they're gonna like say a joke or
something and don't hear the audience
laughing that much that the reason is
probably because they didn't understand
your joke so i told him in the beginning
everybody raise your hands who is
who is um
not german speaking in the audience
right now and see i didn't see how many
hands were raised but by the moderators
reactions
i had the feeling that many hands were
up in the air
so if you were watching for twitch it
was probably easier to follow the
conversation because you had live
translators in the chat and i know some
of you guys had even live translators
next to you sitting in the seat
uh but not everybody i think would have
been easier to follow it in the chat um
yeah but it was definitely a lot of
non-speaking german people in the
audience so
that also maybe made it a little bit
awkward too
but i just told you to nod and smile not
and smile
thank you for doing that
and thanks to all the german speaking
people for being there and listening as
well i'm glad you guys understood me
maybe my awkwardness came across i hope
it didn't come across too much
i tried to fit in
i tried
don't think i did so well
[Music]
so
no
where am i in my notes
you have school to take a foot in duncan
you're fine i i think it wasn't that
disaster good to know
that's good
yeah yeah yeah
and they talked about digging one and
you understood nothing yeah i'm honestly
dead all three of them were really
ecstatic about digimon or digimon they
said diggy monk cause we're speaking in
german
and in german we say digimon
uh but yeah i don't know about the
one that's not no no no no no no no no
no no no
no
sorry to disappoint i did not watch
dragon ball i did not watch digimon i
did not really watch
any of those shows when i was younger um
maybe a little bit of pokemon
i'm i was watching some things like john
dark something like that
something like that
uh not even sailor moon i did not watch
sailor moon actually
that and
even though
when i was watching it when i was
younger i always felt like it's too loud
for me to watch i shouldn't be watching
this
yeah
not jump dog jumping
[Music]
hey anyway
i am maybe a little bit of detective
conan a little bit
[Music]
lazy
like talk about this also i mean the day
started with you guys sending me
these pictures of you guys in front of
the venue
uh all in orange clothes and you posted
it in that hashtag and i was like
oh my god it's really happening
these people
are really so serious
about this and wearing
like my merchandise the omo cat stuff
and all that
yeah the aprons so many people in aprons
so cute now i want to make more
merchandise that's like wearable at
concerts too
in the future
so you guys have more to choose from
although i feel like with the omo cat
merchandise you guys were already pretty
well covered
[Music]
some of you are wearing the first ever
whole uh live english merchandise the
shirt that i drew
that was released at
one month anniversary right what
was that one no no
wait was that one for
no christmas oh yeah it felt early but
it was not six months it was christmas
that was like maybe four months in or
something
or three months or something like that
yeah that was a shirt that i drew and
not many people have it because it's
from the very beginning
but
some of you guys are worrying that
long time ago
yeah
but
more the more and more tweets i was
seeing
the more and more photos i was seeing
i was just more and more realizing how
many of you guys
came
like
i am i i'm of course happy about all the
ones who came from germany and austria
and wherever but i'm like so surprised
like i never expected
so many of you
to go on such a long trip
from like australia
america
several countries in
and so on
i think there was no one from canada
though not that i knew of no one told me
that they came from canada
what's up with that
huh
what's up with that we had like
everybody but no no no canada
yeah korea
couldn't go what what what canada isn't
real
you don't like me
why was i the only british you were not
the only british guy
i remember at least
another one
which was me just kidding no i
remember at least one more
who had
who maybe didn't have such a strong
british accent
[Music]
but that was um anyway the panel and
then later right after the panel i think
i think pretty much right after the
panel
we started
the meet and greet
and um
this was
it started it's at 5 00 pm
oh hello
kiwawa
why don't you stop moving
[Music]
kiwawa
hey yo
why did i die again
no this time my camera didn't freeze but
i'll open it up again
[Music]
thank you guys for all coming to that
holy
so many of you applied and
it was it was crazy like
i wish i wish i could have talked more
and more and more of you guys and i know
that you know just the fact that it was
only two minutes must have already been
so stressful to you guys like how
how you guys were nervous too so many of
you guys were really nervous and shy and
and um like
thinking about what to say and all that
uh
yeah
i forgot to say so much oh man i didn't
even think about what to say
i remember
one person that really stood out to me
it really confused me
like they came in
and you know you know when there's like
shy people i'm like i tried to help them
because i i pretty quickly noticed oh
they're they're the shy type of person
and they don't know
what to say so i'm gonna help them out
i'm gonna throw some questions at them
and i'm like are you nervous are you shy
and like no
i'm like okay
do you want to ask me something and
they're like
[Music]
like they didn't really have any
questions for me
and but then i'm like confused because i
kind of expected you to ask me more and
i don't know you make use of the time
yeah it seemed very soon that it had to
me
uh
i was so confused after that one
[Music]
starstruck no they played it so cool i
remember that they they they played it
so cool
it felt so similar
yeah hmm
oh oh i think i think i even asked like
do you want to take a picture and they
were like no
and like in
because i think that was the only person
that didn't take a picture
[Music]
yeah
i'm like are you sure
but i have a brain verb
birth brain
to be honest i already forgot like who
exactly that was i have like memories of
like how certain conversations went
and how certain people looked like
and
which certain people came but they're
all like separate memories like a puzzle
they're the pieces are disconnected
already in my brain
and that sucks
yeah
so
but i think he was nervous even though
he said no i think he was very nervous
yeah
which is okay i told him you'll get that
i totally get that some of you guys ah i
wanted to give you guys more time
because i i knew the time was stressing
you guys out but i tried my best to like
still help you to make the most out of
it i kept asking questions and then at
some point you know hannah kept on like
i think you guys didn't even notice but
hannah
uh would continuously like walk
around the camera behind you guys and
give me signs uh at certain
time
um
points of time
uh to
show me how much more time there is
yeah and
um
yeah so i tried to like
keep it up and then
yeah leads leads to an end of
conversation and then leads to the
picture and all that
but i already have experience with these
meet and greets at this point
uh so i think it went well
um
[Music]
i don't need
it
[Music]
yeah you know i asked hannah if it's
okay to say hemma said
okay that that i could say hema was
there
hello worked so hard gemma worked so
hard everybody worked so hard
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah henry's actually really funny
yeah
emma would like make a lot of jokes
ah sometimes they
bombed and weren't funny
yeah especially during dinner himmler
kept on repeating the same joke the
first
for a few times it was funny but then at
some point i said hannah's not funny
anymore
your bombing is not funny anymore
sounds like kiana huh excuse me i'm
always funny
i'm always funny
so continuing um meet and greet was
amazing i want to do more but to be
honest i was very happy when it ended
around like i'm sorry if for the last
five or last ten
i think for the last time i could still
keep it up but for the last five
i think it must have been noticeable
that i was
not at my best
uh that was like
for we were doing it for four hours i
think because it started at five we
ended around nine pm
that's four hours
and
yeah managers kept on telling me it's
okay to take a break if you need a break
and i'm like no the venue already closed
venue is already closed and and we can't
do this forever i need to finish this
so the oh i took one break in four hours
to go to an idol meeting
and then then there was one not really
break when
my my tech just suddenly all
died on me
so we had to like restart everything but
that was not really a break
it was just before i added the idle
meeting
yeah i am
i powered through
and
it was tough
but also i was very happy to see you
guys and
i want to do more of that it was so
special to see your faces and hear your
thoughts and you guys were so sweet
[Music]
what
you were the one that was supposed to
come after that one crash of my tech
interesting
it happened right at the end of um
one person
like i think right after we took the
picture and i was like about to say
elvida's in and then like everything
crashed and they were like they i think
they were like taking out um
presents and were telling me about what
presents they they brought for me and
i'm like yeah yeah thank you but the
thing is my my whole system just crashed
so i'm sorry but thank you so much and
then the german selfie that's in they
still heard me my whole screens weren't
black but they still hurt me apparently
but it didn't go come back so i had to i
had to
like restart everything
but it was in theory it was good timing
because it ended it was at the end of
the conversation not in the middle of
the conversation
yeah weird i don't know why i would like
to know what happened because that was
with my alienware laptop
it was not blue screen
it was black screen suddenly
what could that be because like uh my pc
was still running
but there was no way to like get it back
uh except on a forced restart
overheat
but i was only running like obs and
if that overheats i'm very disappointed
gpu crush
what the man
never happened before though
graphics card though
oh man what the
actually i don't think the laptop got
that hot though
sometimes it gets really hot like
actually always if i put it like on my
bed which i try to never do
usually it's never on my bed but i
noticed before that if when it was on
like fabric it would overheat insanely
but if it's on a table it's fine
anyway oh um but besides that um
yeah we got through it and i'm so glad i
chose
more originally it was supposed to be
like i don't know around
25 or 30 people they suggested
me to do about that amount because then
it would be like about one session for
one and a half hours or something
approximately
and i'm like no i am aware that so many
people are traveling from far away
so many people looked uh even even the
ones who came from europe they looked
forward to this opportunity for so long
they bought tickets ahead of time so
long
and um
everyone just wants to meet kiwala
so i said i don't i don't care how long
it takes i'm doing mom
cause i also have fun doing it yeah
dude oh you heard
i'm sorry i really have back pain and
it's really bad at the moment
should they hurt them
[Music]
i want to mute
it's really bad i really need a massage
i swear the past few days i've been in
so much pain
it's been so bad
[Music]
thank you for understanding
oh
that was a good crack though
[Music]
i want to record the session but i
didn't get to record it because
um i was using like virtual camera on
obs and the moment i wanted to record
i realized oh
i
can't
i wanted to use it i want to i wanted to
record it for obs but then i would have
to like you know
i don't know how to explain it but
on the screen of obs it was me so i can
share my face to you guys
uh
but
i couldn't
oh my god thank you guys
i'm actually getting a massage this week
a fancy
fancy massage
so thank you guys i'll get that
definitely
yeah what
i wanted to record for personal news
cause like i i regret it so much not
recording it last year because i have a
bird brain and then i forget
what you guys look like
and anyway it all ended up being so
scuffed that i couldn't record it i
thought about it too late and
there was no recording button in the
thingy that we were using either to
connect to you guys
so
ah
my voice
a sound
if you want i can send a screenshot
screenshot of what of your face what
you mean a screenshot
screenshot you mean a photo of your face
what
well
[Music]
no you guys are welcome to send me um
photos of your faces from the meet and
greet i already saw a lot of you guys
you were posting the meet and greet
pictures now i will have to archive all
of those so i can always look back on
them like five months later i'm like i
wonder i wonder what that person look
like
or before the next meet and greet if i
want to fresh up
and and try to remember some if there
are some repeaters
i would like to
not be like who are you and then you
guys are going to be like so
disappointed you know
ah she doesn't remember me oh no
hey
i only saw you for like two minutes
excuse me so so many people in four
hours
i can't remember i'm sorry i wish i i
want to i want to you have to come more
often and then i'll remember
yeah please send your pictures to me and
i'll save them yeah yeah please please
otherwise please don't be mad if i
forget it next time okay
please don't be mad and sometimes you
know people in the meet and greet they
would like i would ask them what's your
name what what what do i know you by
and some of them said their names but i
didn't understand it even though i
should have
because their name is familiar to me
but the way they pronounced it just
sounded so
so unfairly unfamiliar to me because
like in my head when i read you guys
names
in my head they sound different
and if i don't see the letters you know
because i always just read your names
uh
in text or in my own voice
and when you guys say it some of you
guys pronounce it so differently
but i just didn't right away get it i'm
sorry about that but once i see it and
in the chat again i'm like oh yeah this
person you know what i mean
well you know
yeah
well never track me bro what's that man
have been employed yeah actually uh i
think almost everyone was wearing those
name plates
at the meet and greet and uh i used it
to you know read their minds when they
came in and sat down sometimes i would
be like oh you're that person aren't you
before they would even say it themselves
because even though it was pretty low
quality
um i saw i saw the name written on the
nameplates
and like here that first night and
they're like oh yes
yes i am
that's right
hmm
yeah some of you i just didn't get man
but then yeah you guys write in the chat
again and now that i see the letters in
the chat it's like it looks so it looks
so familiar
i wonder if you guys understand what i
mean man
i didn't want to ask too often like what
what who who because i didn't want you
guys to feel like i don't know you
unless like some some of them were like
oh
yeah yeah you don't know me because i
don't really use the chat i don't really
i'm a lurker and i'm like
why are you lurking you should write
more in the chat then promise me there
were actually quite a few of those
there was a good mix of like
lurkers who i don't really like
didn't really know about yet because
they're not in the chat
and then there was a lot of people who
are always in the chat which made me
very happy to to get a face to add on to
that
so thank you guys so much yeah lurking
is okay hi lurker lurkers lurking is
okay but
um
you know if you write more comments i
can like talk to you and remember you
i can try to remember you
do you recognize people from chat if
they use regularly but don't super chat
yeah i think so um i think if it's
combined with like people people there's
some people who like tweet at me a lot
and that's something i definitely
remember
the tweeters
that stays in my memory
yeah
tweets replies to me
oh my god all the lurkers
[Music]
watching while working that's okay
okay since i only hear you at work so
many of the lurkers i guess always
listen to me at work yeah
[Music]
and much more often on the kia about
shifts ah
i have watches too hi vlog watchers
hi
you never tricked me into talking in
chat good try though
gotcha
who got you
[Music]
i'm getting tired
get tired so early like a baby
thank you guys
so uh okay so i'd like
let's continue
at like
what was it 9pm we finally finished
and
it was very different from last year for
some reason i'm gonna be honest here at
the end of the day
i feel like we should have had the
concert at the end and then i would have
felt differently
but at the end of the day i felt
drained
and
kind of empty inside
it was so weird
i i know i should have been like super
over the moon and happy
like you guys were
after the meet and greet
but
i just felt so drained because there was
a lot of trouble during the day
and then it was also really exhausting
so much work and then it was just like i
don't know
the exhaustion and partially like i feel
like things could have gone better
definitely
um but i was so happy
it's just like that the happiness
um
was more like it had a little bit of a
delay
it came
on sunday i think
on sunday when i was not so exhausted
anymore
when i got my sleep
yeah
so after that the thing is though that
because we ended so late at 9 00 pm then
we had to like
um get like we had to
me and gemma had to clean up the whole
room that we were using like we put away
all the equipment
and then um
sort it all out
i still had to sign
a few more things i think
and yeah we cleaned it all up and then
it was so
late that
uh
i
my dinner was
the rest of the bento box that i had
left over
which is
kind of unfortunate because i wanted to
eat some good
fresh food for dinner during the whole
stay in in dusseldorf because they have
really great restaurants
yeah
but i also at the same time there were
still some places that were open most
places were closed there were some
places that were open but at this point
i was so drained i was just like
this i'm gonna eat this bento
and then just
disappear in bed
yeah but all in all like i might have
felt so drained and empty at the end of
the day
but i saw you guys had such a great time
and
looking at it objectively
the meet and greet and the panel and the
concert especially
was all a big success
yes so
i am happy with it
i am happy with especially in hindsight
now
let me talk a little bit about the booth
i think i have some
how cute i think i might i might have
some
i think i was sent some pictures
[Music]
oh
from the booth
oh yeah
yeah cute
so
unfortunately there was no whole live
booth and no kfp food truck or so
but
oh the fans came through
wow
with a pretty big fan booth
made by fans organized by fans but i
contributed some things to it too
[Music]
yeah and it was such a i mean i didn't
see it in person and i regret it so much
and i couldn't see it i was so mad
i really wanted to see them first i only
saw it in pictures and that's just not
the same thing
but um
there was so much there they organized
like a stamp rally
yeah there was a lottery
and there was charity
and then there was that flower stand
yeah let me show you that one
so a while ago i said
i mentioned
that in japan
when
there's like big concerts or big
openings of companies
people like to send these big flower
arrangements and you guys took my
obvious very obvious hints
that i wanted one
and
then you guys organized one and it looks
so cute about the chicken in the middle
oh my god the flowers are so pretty
flower power jimmy let's go
now
[Music]
you guys are so sweet for doing that
yeah and the thing is i was so sad that
i could not see that in person
and
i wanted to
i really wanted to see that in person
so
after
saturday
i woke up on sunday and i was like
i will
look at these flowers
no matter what
so i woke up
and you know genma henma and so on they
were gonna go to the venue
and do the whole shenanigans over again
with um iris although
uh it was i think much easier for them
on that day
then
you know less problems less chaos
so they it seems like it was better on
sunday overall that's good i'm happy
that they didn't have too much
problems uh
but i was like a german gem my gems are
back in japanese can i join you guys and
go to the venue with you guys
i really want to go and see those
flowers and i heard that they're
backstage now
i want to see them
just the flowers because the thing is
the boov was transformed into an iris
main booth on the following day so the
flower stand wasn't anymore at the booth
it was backstage and i was like that's
actually my chance that's my chance
so
the following picture is taken by me
with a timer
i put up a camera on a tripod and took
this picture together with the flowers
now
there might be an optical illusion going
on for people who saw the flowers in
real life you may not remember it being
that big
um
that's an optical illusion
but look at these
[Music]
yay
cute
[Music]
is this cute one
one more and one more
derp
derp face
it's a perspective trick
or i'm just that small after all
yeah but the thing is when i walked into
that backstage room and saw
like
i
i saw the flowers
separated on the ground
and
i
i was very emotional
and was about to
cry
i was about to start crying i was like
they took it apart you threw things away
oh my god i can't believe it
and
then
a few moments later we realized that
you could just put it back together and
no one took anything away
so i put it together and i'm like oh man
it's fine it's okay
this is fine it's all it's all good
so i sat there i took a picture i sat in
front of it i smelled the flowers i was
like
[Music]
ah now i'm happy
they smell so good janma they smell so
good
[Music]
and then i picked one flower
out of there because obviously i can't
take the whole thing out with me but i
picked one flower an orange one
[Music]
and then i took that
and
i went back to my hotel
i was satisfied because i got my look at
the
[Music]
thank you guys so much
big thanks to the organizers of the fan
booth
um i know um there's probably more but
the
the more more people who are behind it
but um the main organizer as far as i
know was dominique k so thank you so
much
that's so sweet
without this i would have been so
disappointed yeah if there wasn't
something like this i would have been so
sad and it served as like a hot spot i
guess
for the kfp people
during that day
and people would like me there and i
heard that people like some kfb
would lead the other kfb to the concert
hall or would lead them to the
to the
meet and greet place and all that and
they were doing a stamp rally which i
think is so cool because i i feel like
uh
that motivated a lot of you guys to walk
around the convention more
so people were like going to the to the
artist booths
and found the the ones who were making
whole life or chihuahua merchandise
and then bought that and then went back
to the main booth apparently and then
they got something what did you guys get
after finishing the stamp rally
was there like a reward because i don't
know what what the result of that was
[Music]
what was it
another lottery item art or batch oh the
katja pool oh
cool
[Music]
how many people have a person for yes
please for tell a big packaging because
i'm sure there's like you know many
people behind it
you know
also for for this thing
uh i know that originally size
drew some art for it and that was
supposed to be implemented into the
thingy but it wasn't quite it didn't go
well or anything something happened but
i still appreciate it sighs
it turned out so beautiful
yeah
and yeah unfortunately i didn't see the
boof in person but she saw pictures but
it seems like it was a big success
and also you guys helped us out because
that's where we um had people pick up
the meet and greet card so thank you for
taking up on that work
thank you very much
i'm sure it was a lot of work
but
i hope it was fun
for the ones who are organizing it
anyway
and
yeah
amazing can't be so powerful
the whole booth was
was organized by kf people
i'm so impressed
so impressed man
it's so sweet
yeah i'm just glad you also got to watch
the concert though because i was worried
about that you know working so hard
making that booth a reality
and then not getting to see the concert
oh no but no i think they did because i
think i saw them on the picture
a few people took turns holding the meet
and greet information sign
nice
you guys are all just like ah so titty
everyone was so
respectful and kind
and polite
and cooperative
everyone was helping another and i saw
so many of you guys were like bonding
by like going to dinner together in
groups you guys we even went to karaoke
together apparently
i heard you guys went to karaoke in like
a 30 person group or something like that
something around 30 people
like separated into two rooms
so nice
i love that
even though at the meet and greet which
was at the end of the day
almost every single one of you came into
the room and you were like
oh i only slept like two hours three
hours four hours for this i'm so tired
yeah
and then i'm like oh they surely after
the meet and greet will all immediately
fall into bed right
turns out after the meet and greet they
all went to go to karaoke together
even though they were already
tired
i did not have that energy anymore
but i am you know i at a concert and all
that so
oh it's so sweet i love that because
when i um
um
when i used to go to idle concerts in
japan
i would also like together with um other
fans
i would sometimes go to have like dinner
together after after dinner or like
karaoke as well and we would sing hello
project songs you know songs from that
idol group
and it would just be so high because
everybody would cheer as if they were in
the concert they would be like
ah it's just so much fun
[Music]
um
ah this is uh
it breaks my heart a little bit because
i see you guys like bonding and having
fun
and
eating dinner and lunch and all that um
exploring the city together and all that
in groups and i'm like ah
i wish i could just like be part of that
too like
i wanna
want to be on that side too i want to be
on both sides i wanted to also look at
the fab move you know i wanted to i
wanted to be on both sides it was it
felt a bit lonely to
yeah not be able to
be part of that
gotta be honest
because i know how much fun that is
because i experienced it myself
in the past
and
uh
you guys gave me so much love so it
might also be like
a selfish part of me
wishing
to get
as much love as possible from you guys
so yeah it's just me wanting more and
more and more love
um
because you know you guys are so sweet
to me and always flatter me and
compliment me and praise me
so maybe i just wanted more of that
maybe i thought if i was in at the
karaoke with you guys it would turn into
another concert
part two
where i would be singing and everybody
would be like chihuahua so cute kiwawa
you sing so well kiwamo let's go love
kiwawa
and
yeah
so sulking that it's over
yeah it's sad that's after convention
depression yeah
yeah it's so sad
i can't be part of it
[Music]
oh man
yeah
man
sad really sad really sad
but but i'm happy that you guys were
getting along and i want to thank you
guys for
oh oh
oh crap in my leg
okay okay stretch stretch out that foot
yes yes stretch stretch
okay
yes
i wanna thank you guys no no no no egg
no no no no no
no
thank you guys for
being
such almost my phone of being such an
amazing
amazing community um
this just proves once again how amazing
kfp is
like you were helping each other
you were creating that booth together
you were organizing these flowers
together
i think kfb helped a lot with the whole
iris booth i think
i don't really know
how everything went down behind the
scenes but
i think kfp was like
um helping
the irish democrats
with their stuff a lot hmm you worked as
a team that's wonderful
that just makes me so proud to have you
guys
okay if we funded the flowers oh yeah
yeah i heard you guys were like funding
them
collecting
donations for it
so sweet
[Music]
let's do more like this
and and and please
continue being this awesome community
who respects one another is polite to
one another
is open
for newcomers
and supports one another is helpful to
one another
let's set an example
to be a good community
okay
it's i know it's difficult with like
it must be difficult with big big big
big communities
to like
you literally can't control
everything
you can't control like there might be
some
some people who don't even want to be
part of the community and just want to
be like in the shadows
don't want to be
with those people
uh like much more than a lurker and
that's okay too but the ones that are
like
openly like connecting with one another
and are mostly like
the outside of that what you see
of the community i hope we can set a
good example
and you know
yeah continue being so lovely yeah i
love you guys i love you guys you're
beautiful
beautiful glowing chimpanz
psycho
[Music]
um
thank you
about that race no no what the why
are you bringing it up now
[Music]
yeah
okay
what else
what else did i want to talk about i
actually have to get up early so i
probably shouldn't attention too much
more
uh
so on sunday i had my private dookumi
day
uh like last year
i like to have my private day at dokomi
because i love tokumi
and that was fun less pressure it was
rainy it was really shitty rainy
but it was okay like uh i feel like i
made the most out of it and um
like
the weather report was
very scary but it wasn't it wasn't that
bad there was like at some point it
rained like later in the day it rained
so strong
uh and that's when we were like okay we
should go to dinner
we probably should go to dinner
now
so yeah after a really fun private day
we went to dinner with my friends
we went however we went to
tonkatsu
again was like and where do you guys
want to go
have you been to the tonkatsu place yet
i already went on thursday but i
wouldn't mind going a second time and
they said yeah we didn't go yet so
we want to go to tonkatsu place i'm like
perfect marvelous i want to eat tonkatsu
twice
i did not eat ramen or anything there's
so many choices you can eat okonomiyaki
you can eat shabu-shabu you can eat
sukiyaki you can eat yakiniku you can
eat all that kind of stuff but i want to
go tonkat twice
i want to go to tonkatsu twice so on
sunday night uh me and my friends we
went we stood in line i think for an
hour
it was cold i was tired
but yeah we made it in
we had a nice yummy dinner
uh
oh it was actually my bff
and lentil boyfriend furendo
which who is the boyfriend of my
bienvent and another friend yeah had
some nice dinner
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
ah so good at this time i on the first
day on first day on the first day first
day i had hirakatsu
uh taishoku which is basically just uh
the hirakatsu
uh with the rice but not like on top of
the rice the rice is like a side
and uh
yeah it's like uh like a set
with some salad too and the miso soup
and all that and you put the
um the sauce on top
and then just eat like that
but um
that's my that's my to-go order but on
on sunday i was like you know what i'm
going to order something else and i
ordered hiracast
holy hallelujah
wow amazing i mean way too much for me
dessert the serving was way too big
um and it was a little bit spicy it was
very hot so my nose was running
uh i wanted to make the curry to feel
better about itself of course uh well
yeah that was tough but it was so um
[Music]
and
actually the friends that went with me
it was also their first time at the
tonkatsu place
which i seem to continuously
um
keep up a tradition
of introducing and bringing people into
the tonkatsu place for the first time
last time it was uh also like that like
i brought
another group of friends to tonkatsu
place before and they were also like
over the moon about it it was their
first time in tonkatsu and they were
like holy
this is so good
yeah dragging them down the tonkatsu
addiction aka and the tonkatsu rabbit
hole the tonkatsu whole
we got us to go to yes i got so many of
you guys to go
yeah you should have told them
we came here because of chakanashi
kiwawa let it be known let it be known
i wish their restaurant was a bit bigger
though it was pretty small so they don't
fit so many people so you gotta wait in
line a lot but it's actually not as
overrun as all the ramen places
surprisingly even though there's so many
choices for ramen places in in
dusseldorf
i think people don't quite realize that
tonkatsu is the best thing ever
and that's where you should go but
that's good don't tell them don't tell
them
don't tell the others
i'm not sure
this year i had to try how can you go
for the first time
that's good um i hope you went to the
the one that i recommended before
because there's other like like 14 for
example korean barbecue and all that and
that's good too but that's not the same
as japanese yakiniku
it's very uh different i think it tastes
very different
i hope you went to that one
[Music]
oh you know what one more thing about
the meet and greet um
i don't know what i'll keep that no no i
mean it's just a small thing i noticed
but i write that down and talk about it
on wind waker day
[Music]
i i should have kept more
more intentions for
the weekend
[Music]
so did i forget something
on sunday i found the flower location
dramatic went back to hotel had
breakfast and had a private day rain all
day
and didn't care anymore very happy then
i decided to go
no regrets
[Music]
you guys took goodbye videos
apparently
i saw some of your guys's goodbye videos
where you were like sneaking leaving on
an airplane and then it transitioned
into never gonna give you up
you little
heads
little shits
if you're wondering what we're talking
about i think it's on the kfb dokomi 22
hashtag
i know maybe it isn't uh
that one was a reply to me
i think it was quote retweeted with the
hashtag maybe
[Music]
well that was funny
okay
i'll keep that one
i'll keep that one for
another tangent
and
maybe that one too
yeah i'll keep that one
i'll keep this too
okay it's like my my treasure chest of
tangents
thank you i talk sadly
even though i live in germany oh no
that sucks
now this was the second time of me at
dokomi and in between we also had me
being a digikami
once um
what i don't want to say is like it's
not normal
to have repeating guests at conventions
like that
so
i know a lot of you guys
even booked a dokomi ticket this year
before i even announced anything
and that might have been partial because
i was hinting at it but some of you guys
even like bought them before i hinted at
everything
now
i
i already thought two times in a row was
unlikely
i think three times in a row is even
more unlikely i mean it still depends on
like
so many factors but i just want you guys
to
not
uh like book anything too early for the
next year okay
okay
because
i don't know
if we can really do it three years in a
row okay
maybe something else
next time
uh a different european convention or
whatever
maybe it will happen at dokomi again i
don't know
but i just don't want you guys like i
cannot tell you
like if it will happen again next year
and i just generally looking at how
conventions usually operate i feel like
it's unrealistic maybe they invite other
whole life girls who knows or whatever
maybe they don't invite any at all um
but
yeah
i might also want to try to go to other
places perhaps
um
but we will see
we'll see i just don't want you guys to
be too fast okay
don't already book your flight to
germany
for next year
okay
if something's happening you know i
might i might give some early hints
again to help you guys book early and i
might try to
hint at something
but
um
if i don't hint at anything
don't book anything
okay
otherwise you're going to regret it
[Music]
okay
my goal was
for this year
to be
better
and more special
than last year
now didn't wasn't quite able to do
everything i wanted to do
or that we wanted to do
um but i think in general
i mean the fan booth was new
um we had more meet and greets we had
more visitors from kf from out outside
more more cave people more than before
out the outcome
was bigger
[Music]
so yes i would say it did
uh expand somehow
um
yeah
and i hope you guys made like some
connections and friendships and all that
all the people who went there
i feel like you know
meeting people who you only know over
the internet for the first time
it must be so special to you guys
because that's how
uh
we also feel when we meet like another
whole life member for the first time
like especially the ones who live far
apart you know
yeah
and yeah
no
[Music]
hey you're falling in love with one
another
and it'll make me jealous
thank you for a membership welcome
plenty of new friends
it was super fun i got to meet over 40
new kfp family members oh
it's been such a busy but super
amazingly fun weekend
just landed it was a special a lot of
ways so great to mean the rest of kfp
love is such a strong word
hey everybody wants to be with pudding
everybody's in love and wants to marry
pudding
uh
[Music]
hey
hey listen
over me
what about me
you know did you not fall in love with
me
[Music]
why are you falling in love with one
another what about me we're not falling
in love with me
[Music]
the female females are like well i guess
i guess i'll take you then
i guess
or if nobody else wants you then
i guess i'll have to do it
[Music]
huh
i'm still in love as i didn't go
oh no
i'm scrolling for the comments
reading it one by one
too orange
excuse me
wow
what's what's wrong with orange
i can marry you cats no you can't
leave
don't you want to hear that
[Music]
i'm getting tired
i love oranges me too
i want to marry jenna
[Music]
i'm too tired for this
i'm too tired for this no
oh
we'll end it here because i have to when
the is my recording
i i wake up so early recently anyway i
really have no problem waking up early
oh but
6 a.m
all right
um
wait i have to wake up really early
okay guys
uh super chat writing another time my
recording isn't like six and a half
hours oh
um
that was document 2022.
it was a very very special experience
i'm sad it's over
really sad the realization is saddening
thanks guys for the membership thanks
for the super chattels
um i want to go through them i hope i
hope some of the ones who were
uh there wrote me some nice messages
about their experience because i want to
hear from you guys
how it was for you
i'll upload these on twitter
and then i'll go to sleep i'm really
tired
um
i just want to say thank you so much for
everything and i love you guys
and the next week's may be
very busy and and know exhausting for me
but i'm working hard
to
yeah
create something great again for you
guys
so please wait for it
[Music]
and hopefully we can do more conventions
like this
and i wanna i wanna see you guys again
see you again sometime
in my heart
[Music]
my throat hurts
hope you guys enjoyed the concert and
everything
um i know i spoke so directly to the
ones who were actually there most of the
time but also thank you everybody who
watched it on twitch who couldn't come
even though you wanted to come
no regrets there will be more times more
opportunities okay no regrets just
happiness okay
okay
[Music]
oh oh and
new outfit reveal on sunday
on saturday
you you have to be there
i announced that talk to me
and on twitter
and on the youtube community board i
hope you're already new
on sunday
yeah
so i'll uh i'll see you guys there or
before that probably before that um
thank you everybody for watching and
enjoy when we say i'll be there in the
second time bye-bye
[Music]
do
you