[Music]
do
me
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
it looks like everyone absolutely
enjoyed that song cover mm-hmm
wonderful to see that wow wonderful
wonderful
oh uh for all the taco duchies i put out
here the cookie
taco that's if uh so that you get your
cookies even on a different channel
you know whatever
anyway so do you guys mind if you're
floating in the air
you need to fill this you can put them
on top of my head and some of the
cookies from my head oh okay i'll get
good good it happens
are the is the size
uh accurate is it as big as your head as
your face um
kakodachi is they can be all kinds of
different shapes and sizes oh yeah i
heard you say that very recently and
where did i hit it was that a clip or
was that just
you uh recently maybe in the q a i'm not
sure i think i'm pretty sure what's the
q and a
they come in small sizes and big sizes
oh wait i need to turn on bgm uh here's
some
christmas cafe music
how how is that do you guys hear that
you probably don't even hear that much
do you
here turning it up a little bit
turn it up
push once
[Music]
unfortunately doesn't hear it so she
doesn't she's not able to vibe with it
[Music]
oh
you do like christmas though do you
do i
do you
do i do you
do i
hey come on you don't seem like the type
of person to dislike christmas
you know
[Music]
i like christmas of course you do
what of course why do you seem like
you're being brainwashed
i love christmas christmas is the best
holiday of the year
best time of the year yes it is yes it
is enough of course it is christmas yes
of course
are you okay
[Music]
am i ever okay what christmas done to
you to make you act like dad
i'm like what has christmas not done to
you oh my god i'm worried about you
what has christmas not done to me
thank you okay of course i like chris
okay okay good good good
well everybody um in case you
somehow
missed it uh we just released a new song
cover
on my
like whatever whatever whatever and it's
a song by nero and z5 i don't know if
that's the way it's supposed to be
pronounced but yes
and
it's a vocabulary song originally and uh
i hope you guys like it because it's
kind of like um
uh
it's i chose it for several reasons
uh yeah for you know it's a really funky
tune um and for the reason that it's
like a uh two people couples oh she's
bringing out her colors already yeah
yeah yeah
yeah two people couple song i thought it
was you know suitable for us
and uh and and also the lyrics i think
are very special i mean i i i wouldn't
necessarily say that we both hundred
percent relate to the lyrics but i mean
i think it's very very interesting and
um
i mean yeah every everyone is a little
bit depressed so espresso every once in
a while right you know
oh i don't relate to
i relate to 120 percent
oh man
yeah this i makes me worry about you
again
the breath of twerking the breath of
twerking
[Music]
yeah so today we'll um draw a little bit
um maybe i was thinking to have us draw
each other in these outfits um
and since we're using a drawing program
where only this uh aspect is
um possible so i thought we could do
something like a japanese style shikishi
and for the people who don't know what
that is that's it's like kind of like an
autograph
thick uh cardboard board
fine board yeah yeah yeah yeah and
japanese artists all kinds of artists or
like famous people whatever not famous
people anyone really uh uses these to
write autographs or whatever just some
memories whatever
and
yeah but we're gonna we're gonna use uh
this in order to make something similar
to that maybe to memorize this memorable
day
oh yeah now and i have figured something
out i can put this at the top here okay
nice nice
perfect okay
[Music]
yeah so um
i guess uh
when so so so i draw you you draw me
okay
hey this is my way of getting according
[Music]
well if you need cute art from yourself
you can always just draw it yourself
can't choose
easy easy kara you know i i'll try it
anytime oh no no no no no no no
you're busy busy ladies
no no no cannot do it i mean i doodled
and randomly sent you a sketch before i
was like here chiara
[Music]
what that was a while ago though
you forgot nothing too it's okay though
how do i make the how do i make it how
do i make the the the thing bigger
one bigger oh yeah
yeah up there okay i was i was asking
for inaudible
[Music]
she was very worried i mean she's always
worried
i was kind of thinking
maybe
like um oh my god my leg
oh no one
part here one part kind of here
and then here we can fill it with some
messages or so
okay
sounds good
i'll take the bottom i'll pick the
bottom
okay you want to draw on the um
you want to use both layers or do you
want to have one layer let's use both
definitely
yeah oh wait wait yeah yeah there's a oh
two layers for okay we would be drawing
on the same layer
um we can use layer like the bottom
layer for the rough sketch and then like
the top one for the lidar and then we
can erase the sketch and then use that
to color good idea okay okay
i'll be drawing
chibi or something more realistic
like i mean realistically
not realistic
what do you feel comfortable
how about
not chibi because the whole music video
is in chibi style
uh
by the way
oh there's a ring
[Music]
style for this um
i was that i was so lucky like oh and um
i should i should be talking while while
drawing you know you should maybe
already start okay okay i i i draw you
can you can yeah i'll try um
i was saying um i was saying i was
saying uh but where's my mouse
[Music]
i can't do these two things at once you
know i'm not used to this
[Music]
is this opacity yes i think it is okay
um
so
for the people who already um
uh
um
[Music]
you can look here you can do it uh for
all the people who already checked out
the song beforehand because i let you
guys know a little bit earlier what the
song is this time um
you uh
uh you probably saw uh uh what kind of
uh
song
it is already and what the music video
looks like and all that right right yeah
yeah yeah and yeah what's it must be
what uh
[Music]
no problem
um
yeah yeah so so you would have you would
have noticed oh yeah piana you're so
right the the the the art style of the
original music video is kind of like
similar to akashima's drawing style yeah
yeah
yeah yeah am i right am i right
so uh um
and also akashiba's specialty i would
almost say is oh my god you're so good
at this
um
you're so good at drawing
why do they care they touch things
after all animation like these little
small animations
oh wait look can i put one on the screen
i think i download one you can totally
like put some like all over the screen
yeah
where did i save that one
a jingle bell i love the one where we're
like on the floor and we're like just
like looking
down the feet oh so cute i want you guys
to tell me on twitter which one is your
favorite please um not not don't don't
have to do it right now but i want to
eventually know
uh do i have it here no i don't okay
i'll give it one more try is it in this
is it
is it in
this folder
no
no it is oh it is so does this work if i
put this on my screen here yeah look ah
this is us right now
we're drawing on the screen this is
perfect where do i put that now damn it
uh i'm over here
yeah
we got so many cute animations now
yay i think i
can is it possible to like select an
area and move it upwards or no
probably not in this goddammit
damn it i started too low okay i guess
that's that's how it is that's how it is
um
okay i'm drawing ina right yeah yeah
yeah i'm drawing
yeah i feel like i haven't drawn five
million years
me me too like
i didn't think you haven't drawn in five
million years and i haven't drawn in 10
million years or even more than that
it's a long time
yes it's been 84 years
that one is your favorite guy it's the
one where we draw where she's drawing on
me it's so cute isn't it i like also the
one
[Music]
you dance so well oh thank you um
i am a professional twerker yes oh
yes
oh
yes one must be able to twerk when
putting out songs like sparks
it's true
true
a twerk full song
oh my god the art is too cute i can't i
can't even compare
damn don't compare just draw
i'm trying to draw
wait do you do yeah you do have yours
you have like
pointy ears yeah
yeah okay
oh yeah yeah um uh
so
uh
when i are you okay when i planned out
like the whole uh music video i sent
like a big list of like ideas of
what kind of
poses what kind of animations i want
um a few ones akashibasang came up with
himself but uh most of the concepts i
think came from me like i want you to
draw us in a disco
[Music]
um
so uh i hope you guys enjoyed them
they're they are so cute i love every
single one of them
was so fast like
oh yeah exactly
the hour was finished like
before everything else
way before it was so fast i thought he
would need more time but then he was
speed
[Music]
oh my god stop being so quick please
maybe you can talk some more
what do i talk about oh yeah actually
include like uh for the harmonies and
stuff i include like totally different
what should i say
like i i sang like one one um high and
one
yeah
i think the higher one worked a lot
better
yeah
i agree i like the higher ones but but
you know you know like like like like
because this part that i think is lens
part and lens
range is much much lower sometimes than
what i can
manage so
but i think the amelo was mostly fine it
wasn't even
that low but but then that one part
[Music]
but you did well i i really like how our
voices sound
together
[Music]
yeah definitely definitely
for me this was kind of like part of a
project you know you might have noticed
that i um
kind of
i'm doing song covers with all the holo
myth members
mm-hmm you only have i mean left but you
already were you already said you're
working on some right uh no i already
have an idea of like what i wanna
what i want it to be
but i haven't quite uh started yet step
by step gotta do it
one at a time one at a time yeah it's
too much going on at the moment so we
don't you know we let our managers get
some sleep
what you don't get sleep
no because if you work on so many things
at the same time then um
your son will be like oh
[Music]
yes yes that's true too
manage your son kawaii so
i'm sorry manager son for uh putting so
many things on on you
she does a wonderful job every single
time so yes
[Music]
cute glasses
are they like that yeah they're kind of
kind of like that super cool party
people glasses
yeah
honestly those gloves are hard to draw
okay i don't really think that you would
be the
like
realistically speaking i don't really
think you'd have to wear those but in
this situation for this music video it's
perfect that you're working
[Music]
her darkness of reality
and then you got long no no okay okay
okay ah no we kind of didn't
i your clothes don't really show much in
because i only have like a headshot of
you damn it
okay
damn it
anyway i want to ask you something in
yeah
okay
when you
joined
whole life did you think that or did you
want did you hope for
um like doing a lot of
singing activities or is this something
that just kind of happened and you
weren't quite like this this wasn't
really your goal when you joined or
how how do you feel about it
we are a idle
entertainment company um
so you weren't expecting good luck
[Music]
but yeah i just wasn't like as well
versed in
it
i was like i'll do it if it comes down
to it but you know it's a learning
process
it is indeed yes
yes yes
it's been a lot of fun all the ones that
we've worked on so far have you had like
any experience in like singing before
that or just like hobby
hobbies things just singing
my show
in the show yeah that that totally comes
that is a professional singing career in
the shower
well i don't think i've ever really like
saying
like
seriously before
so now that you kind of do do you
do you
um do you and enjoy it a lot or
yeah i do
okay
that's good
i sometimes just sing like a 3am in the
morning
sing unravel three am in the morning
hope that my family doesn't wake up
are you still you sing more than you
used to before like in your free time
i mean like before i used to only sing
when like no one was home and stuff but
nowadays i'm just like
dude
[Music]
is not so rough sketch
is that the offline
yeah it's gonna be the outline
oh damn she's too fast be slower please
okay i'll talk oh yeah for my first
karaoke stream like after i debuted and
i had to bribe my family to go like out
during the stream oh
cause i was like so embarrassed oh no i
totally get that
yeah but nowadays i'm just like
yep
when i uh moved back from japan to um
to australia wink
and
i
uh like i went back to the like uh like
a roommate thingy that i had before i
went to japan so i lived with my
roommate again and she was like totally
understandable and like super
understanding and super supportive of
what i was doing but i still felt like
kind of embarrassed though because like
when i was streaming i also always had
my room door open because of my cats i
didn't want them to
they couldn't enter so
rmt would usually like hide in in the
living room or in her own room and and
watch netflix and all that and she would
be like just do what you want you can be
as loud as you want for how long you
want doesn't matter but i still feel
like
i was holding back and all that so i
ended up like eventually saying okay i i
i'm sorry i love you but i need to move
out in order to be able to really open
up again on my stream yeah
[Music]
so i get that feeling but i guess uh
you're not
you are you planning to
move out one
when is one day after her life or during
her life
probably during but i'm not telling
people what exactly it is oh so you will
you will
transition
into the living alone situation without
letting people know
yeah probably though
so it will be
people will maybe see someday but
not sure if i like to face it can you
can i flip the canvas here
no
i need to lift the canvas how about wait
i can do it at least wait i can do it on
bs one second
you're saying the pandas flipped in obs
then
modern problems require modern solutions
yes
okay transform
and then uh flip horizontally nice
okay let's take a look uh okay the
balance is
decent
oh my god oops
that's really helpful thank you obs
[Music]
oh now i can look at your streaming and
see
mine too okay
see i don't draw much but this is a
technique that i used to use a lot like
all the other artists when i was drawing
more often um just automobiles right
what
[Laughter]
maybe i should i should add a hand
should i have a hand i want
i want to add a hand so i'm not like
running away from my obligations but
you shouldn't run away here don't run
away i want to do like a piece above the
head
tell me if that looks uh weird
does that that works doesn't it
i think that works as long as like you
draw the arm kind of like
it going up um
there's no space for that oh maybe oh
okay maybe uh
yeah yeah the shoulder will go okay
oh
[Music]
peace peace
now that i'm not i'm not the one
streaming i can listen listen to the
cover and loop
oh you're listening to the cover how
about the audience are you guys doing
the same
yeah you should yes doing it too oh huh
what what did i just do that did you did
you
what's happening
oh i'm doing that
[Music]
oh okay okay okay okay when you're doing
the liner you can you can lower it but
right now you're drawing on this i
didn't
okay now i'm gonna go to the other layer
i'm gonna go up here i'm gonna also do
some
outlining now because i guess it's fine
it's all right
i feel um
i don't feel comfortable drawing on
stream and
not even outside of the stream because
it's really
my times as an artist are long
over
it's never over yeah
yeah i do wish i do wish to like kind of
like
start drawing it again but
i don't know i
missing too important doesn't have to be
like finished pieces at the start as
long as you know you learn to start
enjoying it again i think that's what
that's what counts
well i do want to
when i'm like an old grandma or grandma
tori
um
okay maybe not as far as grandma but i
don't want to when i'm too old for doing
this
i want to
do art on the side maybe
[Music]
so that at least maybe
i have some sort of
if if i can make income from it i would
like to make some income from that but i
don't know if that will work just
at least to not go crazy uh by
not doing anything
um yeah
yes
yes that's the only thing like favorite
things about drawing is that like
if you want to make like a
career out of it you can whenever
you know whatever you i feel like i
guess so but i suppose it's not easy to
actually
make a career out of it
i mean even if it's just like pocket
money you know
i used to when i was drawing more
actively i used to
get some small like in
from from individual people some
commissions
yeah that was pretty cool i was pretty
proud of that
yeah
[Music]
you already have experience you're ready
yeah but it's been just
gotta
you know de-rust a little bit you know
maybe i can put some
butter or so on my body will that help
oh
oh yeah
not that or unsalted
i guess maybe salt it
oh
yeah
let's see
gamer girl butter
put in your order now
[Music]
yum yum i really want chicken now oh
i can't help you with that you are in
the middle of a lot of cafe chickens but
i can't help you with that
no no no no unless there is some
volunteers to want to be eaten by you
know
any volunteers volunteers
usually don't want to be eaten by me but
i think there could be some volunteers
[Music]
oh yeah that's a lot of volunteers
oh my god
speaking of love chicken for the whole
year mmm indeed
speaking of food i um
i was cooking before the stream i tried
to cool
and i made
i made
a decent
risotto
oh i love risotto that's my first time
getting it done somewhat decently i
think
yeah you become like such a good cook
over her
that is true whole life is the thing
that's pushing me to cook more i think
for like streams yeah like also for
because i don't want to like order too
much food and all that and i don't have
a mommy that's cooking for me
it's not my choice i had runner
not your choice
you could say no not me i will cook for
myself you think my mom will let me too
she's like the guardian deity of the
kitchen no permission to cook in the
kitchen without
well then bring the her to your room
isn't that what you're doing anyways
that's gonna be tomorrow yeah exactly
with one with one hot plate there's so
many things you can do
yeah
[Music]
oh my god she saw like my hot plate she
was like oh my god we can use this to
have hot pot together i'm just like
it's first dream wow
cute
yeah i was i was making a
uh zucchini risotto
oh and i used like a
a recipe that's apparently from jamie
oliver i think
oh not gordon ramsay
no not gordon ramsay
go with that guy just kidding he was
pretty sure i was running around
he's okay i mean
he was very nice to me the other day
well you guys don't know who's that who
that is he said he's like an
english-speaking woman you know people
don't know jamie oliver you know jamie
oliver right i know jamie oliver some
people in the audience don't know him
he's pretty out in our country in the
german speaking realm he's even well
known
more well known than gordon ramsay to be
honest
it was actually a funny story um i think
like someone asked gordy ramsey's
daughter how it feels like to be the
daughter of the best chef in the world
and she replied with my dad's not
dreaming
[Music]
oh
sick bird holy [\h__\h]
i love so hard
i love i love how savage that is
i mean it effective like you know a
quarterback
i guess
that is really funny
that was really funny huh
nice nice one
i wonder how old she was when she said
that depending on the age it could get
even more savage
[Music]
you've got some fire in her veins
i would expect it after dealing with uh
carter
[Music]
although he's surely um
like to his family to his children and
so on he's surely
[Music]
um by the way with the with the cheese
risotto i made some uh
a garlic baguette wee-wee bucket yes
you like garlic spaghetti gummy bread i
love okay
what do you love garlic baguette
yes okay good
welcome
welcome to the no welcome to the garlic
forget church
[Music]
get your chicken bucket yeah
but i want your spooky hair wow okay
no my my baguette although i do have one
more in the fridge
yes she on bacon you left it in the
middle i'll be right there
[Music]
taco eats eating food from food i could
use some help right now in my apartment
anyway there's some things to do that i
can't handle alone
oh like what
like
cleaning
although i've been i've been cleaning
like um like a maniac
today and the other past days because my
family is coming over
on the 24th
oh
and i ordered like a million things from
amazon which comes with a million
cardboard boxes so that'll be
destroying a million of cardboard boxes
of course flattening them properly
before
i saw the
i saw the pile of cardboard boxes that
piled up the last week because i was
ordering stuff for the uh cheesecake
stream and stuff too right so
it's ridiculous
it is it does get ridiculous
okay
i kind of caught up with you a little
bit
yeah you're doing very well kiara what's
your name
oh hi
no no no no
i want to draw like
you more often
no
no but i did promise my viewers to do a
drawing stream sometime soon
good good you better keep
keep the promise
don't let her go easy chad
[Music]
don't let her go easy
attention does what potential wants a
chimpkin cannot control attention
unless unless there is no unless
a net
no no no no
unless no no no
no
um it's okay though because i already do
um
i already do what jenkins wants a lot of
the time
exactly yes therefore you shall draw
yeah
[Laughter]
team
well drawing so hard in yeah
yes next topic actually i wrote down
some topics that's why oh good that's
how i keep on talking i i was like i
can't focus on both
entertaining and throwing so i gotta
write down some topics beforehand
as as always kiara is prepared recently
i always uh uh call you inya right yeah
it's fine
i feel special
[Music]
yeah
yeah but um
i do have to say i did not choose the
song because of your name but it is very
fitting isn't it
you could change the lyrics and sing
[Music]
and i really like the song like way
before hallow live you did
yeah
so long
how surprised
when we started talking about what to
cover i sent her like a lot of different
songs but then i was like
like every second i was like no forget
well how about this one how about this
one how about
when i came up with this one but wait
wait no forget all of these i think we
should do this one
yeah yeah
and thankfully you agreed
[Music]
yeah i like nano sound songs a lot yes i
i'm not enough vocaloid case
i didn't like i i i didn't know his uh
songs to be honest before that even
though i am like i'm quite um
knowledgeable when it comes to vocaloid
i somehow missed out on his songs but
now i'm going to count them and and i
listen to the other songs and i really
like them they are very special
[Music]
they have a special sound to them
you guys should check them out too
nervous songs really really good stuff
there
i wonder if you'll somehow listen to our
cover
maybe i'll be really happy if they
listen to
i think there's always something special
when you cover something and like the
original like artist
yes like
listens to it yes
they're like oh look they covered it
yeah
that's how maybe that's how like the
other way around when people cover like
my songs for example
i i wanna
take the time to listen to their covers
uh and recognize them or remixes or so
because i know how much it can mean to
someone to be recognized by the original
artist
yeah
it can make one's whole day or one's
whole existence like
i i remember
like before whole life
long time ago
um i did something and then i was
recognized by the
whoever the original
artist or soul was and then i was like
i felt like my self-worth
was
multiplied by a hundred i felt so much
better about myself and so like oh i was
so proud and so excited about it
yeah there's something special about
being like recognized by
like some people you admire
oh my god where did the cameras go where
did the cameras go
oh there it is
i kinda flipped
it's so pretty no but i should probably
flip for uh the people
in obs i hadn't flipped for a while
you guys you guys see obviously that i'm
not drawing myself
not that good you're already starting
with colors
oh i'm just cleaning up the lines of it
okay
let me switch it
horizontal there we go
i'm zooming into your drawing for me
i enjoy watching you
so a
question
yes
and christmas is coming up soon
do you and your family celebrate
christmas or not really or just slightly
oh probably more on the slightly side
we do have a lot of like gifts under the
christmas tree this year we usually
don't do the christmas uh gift opening
because
we were like oh let's just skip the uh
wrapping presents up and stuff and just
start using your gifts
yeah edition i like that idea
yeah but this year like i think mamani's
really wants to do the gift opening and
stuff so
yeah we have gifts this time
that's nice
yeah
[Music]
there's no undo button is there
there is
from what i know
they are torturing artists to this pro
with this program
and just know that if you if you master
this program you got the basics down a
lot you know you don't need no
undo
i guess so
push um
okay so so you guys are
doing the proper christmas
uh traditions things like
putting a tree up and
and opening presents and all that
i guess so we always do the christmas
tree but then like
yeah i guess this year has been a while
since we last did like a christmas gift
opening
ceremony thing nice
what about you
um
the well last year yeah last year since
i was in japan i couldn't celebrate with
them with my family
but this year since i'm back we are
going to celebrate together and they're
all coming to my place
yes
normally normally my mom would cook for
all of us but i said this year
mommy you have cooked for me for um
eternal years
so
um as much as i love being
like love eating your cooking um this
year i am going to bring you all to uh
um a fancy
fairly fancy restaurant not too fast a
decently fancy restaurant yeah for like
a course
dinner
thingy
and i looked at i looked at several
restaurants that do that for christmas
the christmas dinner and i gotta be
honest i don't really like
their menus because it's like too fancy
almost like a lot of them apparently
it's normal to eat fish for christmas
it's a traditional thing
yeah i don't really like fish that much
but fish is on all of the menus so i was
like okay i guess whatever it's it's
about you know
taking the time to just lean back and
being being served for once rather than
having my mom cook for all of us in a
stressful situation yeah
so yeah that's what we're gonna be doing
and i do have a tree but we're not gonna
really
there's a we have a we have a no
no presence policy
[Music]
i've actually had that for i think a
couple
couple years now
so no presents understandable okay
that's okay
that is fun
how about you chet are you celebrating
christmas
i celebrate this fish is very very
traditional yes yes yes
salmon for christmas no it's not salmon
it was something else but yes yes yes
of course they are uh
odd
cod
i'm not sure i don't remember anymore
hmm
i only know like two types of fishes
almond and cod maybe tuna
aren't you like kind of from the ocean
shouldn't you no more than two
i am very much human
i know as much as humans do
starting my coloring process sound
[Music]
aha
i should all know the fingers oh no two
no that's oh no my new bail base
has uh on it
oh there we go inya has thinner fingers
and that i think i'll
[Music]
sorry guys i'm really close to the
microphone
[Music]
i didn't you know you did asm
did you do any proper asmr before i know
you did that cleaning stream the other
day or no
proper probably closer to no are you
planning to do it eventually
i don't like doing like only asmr i
guess i'd rather be
doing something i should say
while doing it
like i'll be making food or
okay singing or
[Music]
yeah
i feel like more fun things could be
done at least on stream
agreed nice you know nice
i mean nothing against people who like
asmr but uh it's not my thing it's not
my thing
it's kind of like watching
some more videos though you like
watching them
like just the cooking videos but they
don't have music behind it and it's just
like them oh that's that's something i
can get behind but like you know stuff
like like ear triggers all that like
like ear cleaning i can't listen to that
it's like it gives me like i really like
tingling yeah
i get shivers when i listen to something
like that
it's like too close to my ear i don't
like it
there's one video i listened to like a
really long time ago that's like
like the first first asmr video ever so
it's like the barbershop one
where they
have like a surround sound viral
sound that you have to use your
headphone too interesting listen to and
i really feel like you're there in the
barber shop
but
yeah i don't i i personally don't listen
to it like
regularly i guess i just like watching
cooking videos with no music
you know what what you do like when you
draw it's kind of like asmr too like
just hearing the pin strokes
and that's again something that i i
think is nice like as a background to
your normal talking and all that like
hearing that kind of like pen asmr
mixing that i like it
that sounds nice to me i don't know if
that's even considered asmr in that case
i think chad will say about just about
anything his ears
oh yeah it's like art it's like anything
can be art and everything can be asmr i
guess
yeah
yeah yeah yeah no hate sorry guys no
hate of course it's just you know
i mean people have different preferences
yeah
i respect it yeah
for sure
and cool
okay
i have another topic you know this is
gonna be like a mini mini mini hot foot
like holiday edition
i mean i i answer the questions too so
yeah
and next topic
is uh mario kart
oh mario kart because it is coming up
uh
next in early next year so that sounds
like it's far away but it's not anymore
yeah
we're in the same group cara we are
which um kind of
you know what
see
i hope i like i
yeah i mean i'm not gonna do it on
purpose but i hope i don't make it to
the next round
[Music]
because i want to go back to sleep it's
at a horrible time for me absolutely
horrible oh no
so i i know like i mean looking at our
team there are several people that are
definitely better than me so i'm gonna
do my best and i'm gonna practice as
well but i know that i won't make it
around and that's good that's good for
me because i can go back to sleep so you
know you're probably also gonna be
better than me and i appreciate that so
you're gonna tell me the reason why i
can go back to sleep soon
but what if we make it to the zucko cub
cup as far as i know there is no taco
club this year there is knuckle club
what
i thought that was no taco cup only to
you
by the way it's for the people who are
bad at the game i guess
wait let me yeah let me see
where was it where was that
where was that info
this one oh
no there's a taco crop no wait so i
can't do it
okay wait is there like
is there a middle ground where i won't
be in any other house
or will i definitely be in one of those
cups wait only the three the three uh
oh wait
huh
wait who makes it into the
finals are the good people right
and zucko zuckercup is something else
i guess yeah yeah tacocar is something
separate i think
how many people may get into the tackle
club everyone who's like
probably like the last or like two last
places i'm guessing so if i'm like for
example fifth place in my cup
could it be that i don't have to go
anywhere
possibly
like aim for a specific
[Music]
specific placement
well that's the real gaming though if i
am able to
get a specific
place
that was like pro gamer skills yeah
that's you know usually like anime and
stuff like when when like a main
character hides their power
they like you know they like rick the
rankings because they can just like
adjust their skills like a certain level
uh
that's the real strength you know i
believe tara is anime protagonist i
always was i always have been always
happy
[Music]
okay i i'm not so happy with my art but
i'm gonna go to i love this it
soon as well oh i need to do these uh i
need garage take your time
i can spend more time with you
ah
oh yeah
oh yeah oh
yeah oh yeah oh yeah
yeah guys if you have only listened to
the music video but not really taking a
look at the lyrics you should
you should take a look
very interesting lyrics
this looks kind of weird
anyway so how is your how confident are
you about the
about the about our d cup
[Music]
um
you're good
i just mean that you're part of the
teacup
that's all i mean hi hi hi of course of
course
[Music]
honestly i haven't played that much
mario kart after the enid tournament so
i'm kind of
kind of worried we have some strong
players and uh who is strong
buddying senpai is pretty strong she's
in our she's in d cup
yeah oh then we're already [\h__\h] okay
good
[Music]
oh who else is in the let me show it
super senpai and
lena was
[Music]
one of them will win win for ian right
not me i'm actually pretty excited to
see there's four hollow birds in our um
[Music]
yeah there's only one
yeah even even the new burp in town is
in the cup wait i don't know if they did
that on purpose they didn't right
it was random right
weren't you they're random
um
yesterday or earlier today i guess for
me was today uh what did you do
yeah you just call in
i got to choose like which uh placement
and the and the ladder thing
everyone was put in
and then
uh you know the ladder thing like where
you like go down the ladder and it uses
like a placement for you
oh
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
you didn't decide who gets into the d
team right
no no no it was it was random like
uh what what is it actually called the
latter thing
i'm sure there's a vocabulary for it but
but yeah um
but yeah like i i chose where people
will be placed in the top and then like
you go down the ladder it's like
kind of like a it's like kind of drawing
the straw thing
yeah yeah
normally the bracket ladder game
something like that yeah
so
it's thanks to me randy
what is that song and not indeed
i kind of feel bad for girl though
um why oh because she's with aqua sample
for
it was funny because uh when i was when
it wasn't but i was like oh you can
choose like where everyone's placed like
on the top before or before the group
like placement source shown was like oh
should i put myself in the middle part
nah i'll put girl then that was the
beast
well i think you know glitter
was a good driver too and
i think she'll take this one
very seriously and practice a lot as
well
i um i woke up this morning i got a
message
oh she'll look sweet for me
i was like i'm sorry
[Music]
and she should be happy she can
communicate and hang out with aqua silva
and stuff
it's like yeah
[Music]
indeed
oh that was not on purpose but nice
definitely not intended but accepted
i'll take it
how are you doing
yes
[Music]
i didn't hear the preview until like
right before it was posted you didn't
choose that line though right it was
assigned to you
kind of i chose it actually i also tried
something else i think but i was like
because i i forgot the songs i didn't
know the five golden rings was the five
golden
i was like wait i have golden ring on my
head i can't beat the golden rings ah
just yesterday i think in my stream i
was like wait a second why
what five colonies is it because of her
golden ring no way and i was like
wondering if that was on purpose or
so it is important
oh
[Music]
i wasn't sure i didn't i didn't get that
reference from the beginning
took me a while
yeah i don't choose my i don't put my
rings on that often i don't actually i
don't think i have my ring with this
outfit
but yeah
oh
but it's just one golden ring not five
golden rings and i order five onion
rings or order four onion rings to make
up for the one golden ring in total
golden rings
simple math
math
okay once again what's three times three
and what
three times three
yeah nine
okay she's back guys she's back
i thought the first question was three
plus three i heard four players three
times he had a break i heard three plus
three not three times three your brain
was a little occupied okay she's that
guy she's back
i would have known the ques the answer
the first time already
i didn't hear it correctly oh man
i have
[Music]
multiplication or multiplied by occasion
the multiplication thing was no my
strong suit that was like i was
sometimes in school like in math class i
don't know maybe the teacher did the
same for you but they would be like okay
i'm gonna randomly pick people in the
class and i'm gonna be like three times
four or six times nine or whatever and
you're gonna give me the answer and i
was always like i was shaking and
shivering because
well
it was really bad at least like the
later ones like you know
did you have that kind of like thing too
in class
where she would call you out and be like
what's this and this five times six or
okay five times six is easy but um
eight times six what's 8 times 9
probably yeah yeah
yeah it could could very well mean
yes yes yes okay
panic
okay okay
i was right chestnut 72 okay
yeah there's a few that like confuses me
like seven times eight
um
i don't want to think about it
the good thing is i am not in school
anymore let's go
i don't feel guilty about not knowing
these things unless i would clash
i just wanted to ask uh siri if i'm
confused oh you have serious that's how
technology has changed you know you have
siri
yeah just get a relaxing hey siri what's
five times siri talks to you
yeah siri is like from
from iphone right from apple
right yeah well
siri doesn't talk to me on my iphone
it's not that i want to talk to her but
do you need to like set her up or
oh yeah i think there's an option where
it responds to hey siri but i usually
have it turn off for my iphone because
stream
but for my for my ipad and stuff i still
have it on oh
i never have
yeah
it's a different accent did you see that
um the crony theme of cortana cortana
what the [\h__\h] was going on there
really didn't like does she have like a
virus or something
no i'm pretty sure
um
it's just it's just windows being
windows huh
that was crazy
yeah
it was so scary
i was like
overlapping with
[Music]
just like another
yeah
oh my god but it was so funny
it was
so funny man
like one of those things but you don't
want it to happen to you but then when
it happens to someone else
yep i mean i made for a pretty good
stream moment gotta say it did yeah
cause like i legit like i saw a clip of
it and i was like this can't be true so
i went to the archive and checked it out
so she must she must have gotten some
archive views from that
people being like oh the legendary the
legend can't be true
it must be a myth but no
i just can't
[Music]
oh man
okay uh i ran out of the topics ina
oh you throw me one
uh
how's the
how's the weather
how's the weather well i mean
it's been uh
snowing every now and then but uh
currently it's not so i guess there is
no white christmas after all probably i
mean there's no chance i guess but
um
no that's okay i haven't had white
christmas in in a long time
[Music]
oh any any plans for the new year
because pretty soon
um
uh not
not exactly
um
i am not sure
what
to do at the moment like part of me
wants to stream
and then part of me was is like i
probably should be social and do
something with real people but i don't
really want to be honest
but my chat was like
keanu like we really would be happy to
spend time with you but then the other
people are like oh but kiana you should
go out and be social
and i'm like oh no i don't want to go
and i want to spend time with you guys i
don't want to be social also you got to
push i spend time outside um uh looking
at the fireworks or whatever it's gonna
be cold as well it's just gonna be
painful i know already i'm gonna freeze
my [\h__\h] butt up and i'm gonna be like
why did i go outside
true
[Music]
have you still been playing animal
crossing
not much but last year i did my uh
i did my
new year's countdown on animal frosting
oh wait so what are you oh oh damn i'm
not done ah there's no [\h__\h]
[Music]
she is not yoga
you must understand this program that
we're using has no undo button
and i just deleted my outlines big part
of it that i was struggling with the
[\h__\h] windows from those glasses i was
struggling with those
[Music]
okay if you did it once you can do it
again kiara believe it
[Music]
i don't even know what is so behind you
i'll just stop for a bit
let you catch up yeah okay
oh my god
[Applause]
okay
let's talk about uh
gingerbread
gingerbread yes so i i went to the
supermarket
i went to i went to a million
supermarkets looking for already
finished gingerbread dough but i
couldn't find it today i went to another
one where it said online that they have
it but they didn't actually have it
and then the
guy from the supermarket he was like
gingerbread don't
know
that has been so loud since ages girl
and i'm like oh i can imagine
okay i guess i'll make it myself so i
bought like all the ingredients to make
it myself i have the
kitchen aids to make it myself and i
bought all the all the decorations like
um
like you know
like so smarties and whatever
smarties um
do you guys have smarties over there
okay
um
uh so i have everything i guess i'm
making it myself but to be honest i'm
it sounds like so much work because i
gotta do the dough and i gotta do the
the sugar
coating or whatever it is the sticky one
to stick it together icing yeah
ice cream is pretty easy but i have
actually never made gingerbread from
scratch before i think the closest thing
is probably like snickerdoodles do you
know what snickerdoodle oh i heard of
them
like the the
molasses cinnamon
cinnamony no ginger oh
something like that yeah
those are pretty
no apparently it's really not that
difficult and i mean
i don't have to really eat it i'm just
making it to build it so it doesn't even
have to taste good that's a good thing i
guess you don't need your gingerbread
house
um
i i mean i've heard from people's
experiences that those are usually
disgusting
all right i guess
you'll be fair i guess because a lot of
him like you touch the cookies a lot
when you're decorating him yeah and you
won't either right away what would you
build it for if you eat it right away
normally you build it and then you have
it standing around for a couple days and
then eating it afterwards is kind of
like ill
i don't think so i don't think they're
made for eating they're just made for
looking at them and having fun with
building them i know actually ikea had
like uh i don't know if they still had
it but they had a gingerbread like set
oh
ikea you tell me that now i've been
looking for ages
[Music]
i don't know if they still have it in
stock but i mean i've seen like
there's pieces to just glue them
together yeah like like walls and like
windows and everything are you for real
those now wait let me let me look
for real cells
i don't know if they still have it
because it was a couple years ago i saw
them in the house
they [\h__\h] do
because this there's one
there's one like food uh youtube channel
i've been watching for years
it costs only four euro
[Music]
and and they did a video a couple of
years ago with building the the
gingerbread house and it was i was like
oh i didn't look
oh my god but who knows if they have it
in stock that's the thing like that they
don't have it in stock but aqui is
pretty good with stockings oh my god
if only i would have talked to you one
day before and i would still have time
to buy it
yeah my stream is tomorrow
[Music]
[Applause]
look here one day one day i've been
off collab we still cooking stream
together
[Music]
um
i mean as long as i have a recipe i can
basically cook almost done okay yeah we
can learn by doing
yeah but like every time i ask you like
about cooking you say oh i can only make
cup noodles so
[Music]
yeah i can make cup noodles that is
wow but it's not the kind of cup noodles
that people think about i make some
premium cup noodles
add stuff to it
okay what do you add
i really like okay there's like a when
it's like spicy
i see your noodles with soup in it i
like to add a lot some some veggies like
bok choy and like some
some uh
the green onions sometimes if you have
some ginger lying around you can it's
the very small thin
then strip so ginger you can add those
into
yeah
not too much just like a little bit
a little bit
you can add in some garlic garlic
okay wow
yeah okay people think eating cup
noodles is like you know last resort
thing but no it can be
good a meal it can be first
yeah i resorts
know okay i didn't think you would like
really uh
like uh accessorize your cupboard i'm
serious about my cup noodles
oh by the way chad how often am i
stopping moving i hope not too often
because when i look at the screen i
probably often stop moving i'm sorry
chad
sorry about that oh you should add soft
boiled egg inya to your cup noodles
oh the thing about softball thing okay
so when you cook like actually like
putting water in the cup noodle there
are things you can add to it um some
things that you add into it you have to
do it afterwards because it lowers the
temperature of
the cooking water
yeah so stuff like eggs and stuff kind
of want to make sure that you don't add
it until later otherwise the water
temperature is going to go down and your
noodles aren't going to cook properly
oh [\h__\h] she sounds like a scientist
i'm very serious about my top noodles
[Music]
oh by the way speaking of scientists
here there we go new new topic let's go
kiwawa whoa
new topic today i talked to a scientist
oh
called coyote
new members
she was doing a call in totsumachi
stream
um
um by chance but by by accident no but i
was i was
randomly in front of my pc at that time
uh
and was gonna record something but then
i saw harry streaming and i was like
oh i'm gonna talk to her because like
she really impressed me in her debut
stream
i really like yeah
so i wish i could talk like
machine gun talk
yeah i can't like i can't speak fast
actually recording for el was kind of
hard at some parts
ah yeah there are some
parts yeah a dripped over my words a lot
so when there's something possible
oh i get it i get it
[Music]
i've juggled the lot with the
muji
[Music]
okay that's the thing
if there's no challenges in life you
you tell you what
if there's no challenges in your life
you're only comfort and you'll never
improve you know
yes so it was a good experience i liked
it true
i hope i pulled it off
but so who who in
when hollow x speaks to you who would
you be interested in doing a collab with
yes
with the important questions
oh i don't know anyone who reaches out
to
what
you're going to reach for yourself the
japanese girls they are always like they
don't really
they kind of lowkey know that some of us
speak japanese but they still feel like
too shy to talk to us and ask us for a
collab so you we have to ask them ina
but but if you could ask someone who
would you ask if you were to collab with
someone yeah
[Music]
actually i heard that uh
louis
is good with puns that's at it oh and
she's also the best one in her janet
english
[Music]
um
right right yeah right yeah i think
yeah she's
a lot of uh what's what what's with like
hollow birds speaking yeah language it's
a great coincidence because that makes
it even like it makes it even easier to
collab with one another
yeah
i was like let's
[Music]
like pretty good with like english too
she was like uh was this was it canada
she said that she was
i think in canada for a little bit
um not that it really like
still has that much effect on her but
but when we played wars together i yeah
i kind of had her speak a lot of
english and she really did a great job
at it so
um not not not much of a deal like she's
really good at english and then dana of
course also speaks uh three languages i
speak three languages uh super decent
movie is the only one i think who
doesn't who's not quite able to
communicate in two different languages
but but it's okay that it works we can
she probably knew and then for a bar
she probably knew in them for car
that could very well be yes yes
well yeah i was thinking that too when
when uh the new burb arrived and she
said oh i can speak english uh i was
like
oh perfect thank you that makes it a
whole lot easier
okay i think i finished the
the outlines again in the second half
see when you talk and draw at the same
time you just you just look back at the
canvas and stuff is finished
yeah
yeah yeah
yeah it happens it happens
uh
wait what was it i think i was going
somewhere else oh yeah wait so you say
you want to also collaborate
um
oh and conveniently she's in group
[Music]
stream is gonna be like we're gonna be i
guess when we're racing we're gonna be
on our own like not together in voice
chat i think
it'll be fun to be in voice chat to
scream yeah i think i think it would be
too distracting almost
true
i want to focus on on the
race
so you can get fifth
exactly to aim for an exact spot i'm not
sure which one yet but
[Music]
um
i believe
what
i believe in you thank you you believe
in me getting the the placement that i
want yes
i believe in it too because i i need to
believe otherwise it won't happen
i gotta believe
okay what if you like coincidentally get
first you know now that i never know
absolutely not happening let's stay
realistic here
i mean you call yourself your
protagonist that's how things work in
that world but but madden is also
protagonist we're all protagonists of
our own youtube channels
that's not gonna work like that when
there's 20 protagonists and no one is
the protagonist
i wonder if there's like a a series like
that where
everyone's like oh are you okay
yeah don't die
don't take here
we need you
oh
we lost her
it's my stream now
[Music]
um
hello chat
kiara carr will be back
she'll be okay
she's moving again is he alive
where's my keyboard
okay
are you okay i'm crying
tears coming from us
like crying are you okay
[Music]
breathe
[Laughter]
[Music]
in
i feel like you have so many of these
moments
oh this is a different one this is a
different one i i
i i
the water that i drank it went into the
breathing place
[Music]
the breathing place this is a different
situation
last time i was actually so worried when
you got the i think it was like leg
cramp
i thought you were actually like dying i
was like oh my god
yeah
i was dying indeed you were right with
that assumption
wait
when i was running away from the pc i
further i threw the pen to the ground i
threw it to the ground
oh now
[Music]
you could help me with base colors okay
can you help me fill in some colors
okay
breathe in
[Music]
everything is gonna be okay
excuse me
i threw it to the ground oh my god ah
you'll be okay it's so hot though wait
can i change it to something else
and i need more water oh my god
[Music]
um hi
is this you and me again
[Music]
kara is changing in the back
please don't look
[Music]
um
how's the weather today chad
wait i'm in i'm in kfp territory
i can look into your secret faults
for the secret recipe
full of
nutritious
chicken
it's cold it's cold but it's colder than
my heart
[Laughter]
it's cloudy okay i'm back
oh you're playing because don't tell her
what what's happening what what
are you asking for a secret recipe
no
uh-huh
well you know i do have to say um
for my um
uh for tight glue
um
for your what my fatigue
my defense
a phoenix oh it must always be close to
death um
it is my natural state
it's my natural habitat close to death
oh
yes yes
maybe i'm a phoenix
[Music]
oh okay this is nothing you got a long
way to go
you do
um um
okay i'm
sorry
[Music]
it's it's um i'm back i'm back come back
to the back
[Music]
stuck in my throat in a help
oh no
i just imagine like people like when
chickens swallowed stuff and then like
they have to take like they go to the
vets like
try to take it out
and they have to like open up the
chicken to see the throat
you know what exactly made you think of
a chicken now i do not understand the
connection
you have something on your head that
reminds me
that's a phoenix verb
[Music]
that is
oh man
are you okay you need a minute
i need to drink more water
i'm gonna drink more water yes yes
cheaper water
[Music]
a little louder on the gulf please a
little closer to the microphone
i don't have a cold
thank you for worrying it's just
normal
[Laughter]
wow let's uh let's fill in colors um
colors i love your cell shading that the
way you drew this oh my god it looks so
nice it has like this kind of sketchy
look to it because of the outlines
oh thank you i like it very nice so um
if you if you got some hands on your
time on your hands
[Music]
if you have no hands on time
um
then i don't know you could maybe fill
in the skin color also
[Music]
yeah i mean i could put my hand on time
but i'm not sure
[Music]
it's already a good color in the on the
color picker how come so nice nice
ena hair color
okay now choose the
right layer ah
okay um i chose it
and now
and now now be careful don't delete it
all at once careful okay this is the
right one okay good hallelujah i'm
guessing there is no filling tool either
nope wonderful
wonderful paul manuel
back to the band that's
[Music]
okay
okay got rid of that
i mean some parts look off to me but
it's been a damn good while since i last
drew something so forgive me forgive me
it's so cute
actually if you look like especially
like on um
what's it
on obs like your lines look like almost
drawn by pens
oh very nice i mean
i mean it's a pencil too
there's a pencil too i mean it's only
pen i mean that's a pencil no pen is
short for pencil no
no
what
[Music]
it is of course it is
what are you talking about ina you have
no idea
you don't know a thing about artina
[Music]
you
out of all people
don't know a thing about
sick
burn oh
yeah i have a lot to learn for here
yes you do young padawan yes yes oh
please teach me
i will teach you young jenny
master
i will teach you if i if i uh find you
worthy
of the teacher oh i see i see
oh no
i'm on the wrong leg
i knew it
[Music]
elementary money
it's conflict elementary
mistake
that's confusing
[Music]
this is okay this is fine
okay
now maybe the color should have been
brighter though you know is this a good
color for your hair
yeah looks pretty
okay time to fill in colors
um i could draw on top of them
and then draw on top of that
okay serious business guys
there is business
[Music]
oh i could also draw on top of that if
the skin is gonna be on top of that
big fake opposite big thinking guys
big brain strategy i could make the
whole box in this color now
[Music]
nice effect i don't know how i did that
i don't know either what did i do
oh
i might have turned the opacity down no
no did i i think they might be the
opacity of the
actually it might be
i turned it back up yeah probably the
opacity setting huh
in yeah
it's me you know what i will do after
the stream
sleep no i think i'll take a bath
because i got myself
um
you know i got myself a table for my
bathtub with like an ipad slot yeah and
and i even got myself a pillow now it's
gonna be so comfy
waterproof pillow not i mean not
waterproof but it's like one that you
can put on your bathtub
[Music]
it gets wet kind of but it's it's okay
to get wet
hell yeah i'm so excited
[Music]
dear kf people
there is part of your feet that is
thinking even though i already have all
ingredients
i i i don't feel
i don't feel quite
comfortable about doing that stream
tomorrow there's a slight chance that
i'll change it to mario kart
um
uh and
would you be very mad at me
oh they say they're so sweet they are so
sweet they already got a cooking stream
for me a few days ago so i guess that's
okay but i'm not 100
yet but i'm just i'm just really really
you know these streams are so so
stressful somehow i mean you know i know
you're gonna make cheesecake without a
without a hand camera
but with the camera it's it's very very
stress-induced yeah
especially when the setup is very um
[\h__\h]
shitty
very amateur setup
understandable understandable
but i already have everything
oh man i mean why don't you just do one
without because i love the camera no
when i do something i do it like
for real those and and like my people
already
know my cooking streams are with a
camera i feel like i can't just go like
a few levels back i have to stay on this
level you know
i can't go back anymore
i'm sure i'm sure as long as they get to
spend time with you they appreciate it
no but i i want no if i do a cooking
stream it has to be with a camera oh i
mean like whatever you do if you change
it or not oh yes yes perhaps my my
chicken
enjoy any time they spend with me
hopefully hopefully
hopefully
it's just like i made i'm making this uh
christmas week way more stressful for
myself than it needs to be perhaps
all these is about chilling you know not
only limited to the viewers
it's what i think
there was more space down here oh
it might be
but
i mean maybe for the people who don't
have to go oopsie to work but
this is this is work
gotta work work work hard work hard
thank you guys
doesn't mean that work has to be you
know always stressful
[Music]
i suppose so
sure you can have fun at work you can
relax at work oh i always have fun at
work i always have
but when it comes to relaxing
i
i feel like
i'm
i am relaxed sometimes in certain
streams but most of the time i'm like
always like oh my god oh my god oh my
god need to
need to entertain
my voice
[Music]
i feel like there's an outline missing
here
that is way too fast yeah
i don't know i think you always work
hard yeah i was throwing on the wrong
layer again
again
it's okay it's
it's okay
[Music]
we all work hard in her life
am i on the right layer yes okay
i don't know what the hell happened with
my throat
you're coughing quite a bit
i want to be surprised if it
i was i was hoping for you to if it was
gonna get any worse to call an ambulance
oh
i already have my phone ready
let me know yes problem is you don't
know where i live
ah
only baby baby baby baby baby every baby
roughly that's true
actually no man i mean actually actually
oh wait yeah
i did give you my answers
i just realized i do oh yeah yeah what
happened with that huh
um i've i've been shopping i just i'm
really bad at mailing out stuff on this
data inaudible's gonna send me some some
stuff
uh-huh
yeah it's okay i kind of
i kind of low-key don't worry i haven't
forgotten i have still has a sticky note
with everything written on it oh okay
okay okay okay yeah
why wasn't i gonna send you something in
exchange too
think so i don't have your address you
didn't give me your address yet
i said you can write it here
right here
my address okay hold on
[Music]
everybody close your eyes this is
private please close your eyes
private information
you guys know where the line is right
you guys know
this is not for your eyes chimpkins
they know they have manners
your eyes
[Music]
oh
stop
[Music]
turn
left
[Music]
something that really exists
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
i bet i had chat when i wrote the number
they're like oh you know
no
no they know you wouldn't
you're a more big brain than that
no yeah oh yeah
[Music]
um
oh wait
how there's there's only i can only do
cell shading here can i well like i mean
you can lower the opacity of your brush
but it it takes a little bit of uh yeah
yeah
well
let me see let me try well first of all
you your
your
tentacle thingy color
maybe somewhere around here
[Music]
then like how do i should i just like
cell shade it like it can fall shaded i
usually celebrate it for like the chibis
i draw
yeah damn it no i'm out of the border
again
are you finished
uh
you seem finished i don't see your hands
moving
i'm moving i'm moving
[Music]
i'm moving if you want you can do your
skin color i would have i would
appreciate it
okay give me a moment i need to uh
add in more more shading onto your hat
hey
jingle bells jingle bells jingle all the
what's your favorite christmas song
uh
i don't have a favorite there's one that
came up recently it's cover
uh-huh
what could that be
it's uh 12 days of christmas i think
like never heard 11 girls covered at
once eleven goes who which eleven goes
um
have you heard of paul
[Music]
what you cut off there
all alive have you heard about what the
hell is that
law of english
it's like they're like virtual youtubers
it sounds lame do they stream
they're pretty nice check them out let's
check them out um
they released this uh
this uh cover of 12 piece of christmas
on the official whole live english
channel oh no although you're saying
that everyone in the audience right now
should check that out
yeah okay but not not before they check
out the
[Music]
okay okay yeah yeah i'll definitely
check that out and that one is like
absolutely amazing
oh really yeah
here what's your favorite part about it
[Music]
the beat the bait is off the hook or
something like that
the beat i see the beat the beat
i want to listen to it like endlessly
and dance to eat
[Music]
lots of spain
what about
what about other christmas songs what
about last christmas i feel like that is
kind of like a the rick roll of
christmas
wham's last christmas is like a rick
well don't you think
yes
oh look it's it has a comparable effect
what do you say chat
yes it is yes thank you i was thinking
about that
because like people are like oh freak no
not that song again
every time i christmas
i mean i like it but it still has kind
of that
that effect of being like obnoxious
mommy at the same time sure there's
people out there who actually like
the rick roll
yeah i mean i think we all like we all
do
it's just a meme that like people are
like oh no this song again
you got me you got me again
[Music]
in the chat
oh
what did she say scroll scroll to school
school school school ice cream oh this
isn't going wrong
oh no it stopped
oh there it is
[Music]
oh i thought she was singing
but then it's more like i don't want a
lot for christmas or is she combining
the songs
for christmas
he's speaking in riddles to me
i was challenging your rick world
christmas song
[Music]
i see
guna and cali are putting out an
original song by the way yeah i heard
that it's gonna be like an animated
yes
i mean in some way out i was saying our
music video is
technically
it is it is i'm very very proud of it
[Music]
i don't know how i did it it was it was
a really weird coincidence like
yesterday
i was um
it was like 2 or 3 a.m for me
and
i was uh finishing up things
and then i was like okay okay let's
upload the thing now and then go to
sleep and i put up the the reservation
and i made it public and then i wrote
out my tweet and i tweeted and at that
same moment
at the very same exact minute callie and
gooda's tweet for the queue
went up and i was like how how what
quick
and i was like wait should i delete mine
i i i
the coincidence
it was a coincidence what the hell
[Music]
that was a weird coincidence that was
not planned no it was so weird
i didn't even know that their
announcement was coming like at that
time or even that day i didn't realize
that i was too
occupied with my own
things
didn't really it happens
hard to keep track of what everyone else
is doing because everyone else is doing
so many so many things at once too
i think i slept like 12 hours once and
then when i woke up like five different
things were announced i was like
oh
is it still 2021.
never gets boring at uh hello live or
hello live english or whole life in
general yes it goes by so fast
um
yeah
yes hard working or hardly working no no
definitely
always working yes always break ain't
never heard of it
[Music]
even at this moment at this very moment
we are all also working on things that
you guys will know about eventually
always always something in the future
one day
yeah
oh cool
all right
how's it looking inya how are you doing
kenyara um
what's okay i'm not deleting things
anymore by accident so i'm feeling
really good
i'm trying to
get some shading into the hair
doing very well
this kind of motivates me to
draw in a proper drawing program
where there's more possibilities
i am motivated
to do she's not even
[Music]
i don't know why i don't know why my
audience gets so excited about the
possibility the prospect of me doing a
drawing stream
they love seeing you draw i don't know
why
they know
they know that you like drawings they
want you to pursue it more maybe
they want the best for you
yeah
cute
your tentacles here look like
some kind of candy
jelly beans
especially when they're like cell shaded
like that
you know they're detachable
are they
[Music]
i don't know
i happen to
maybe i have heard of such a thing but
not that i have ever seen such a thing
[Music]
oh there is that song you know
is going over what's three times three
nine
what three plus six or three times six
nothing it again you gotta guess
what three three ten three plus six is
uh nine
and three times six is eighteen
she's still here guys she's still here i
like how your chest is full of nine nine
nine nine nine
i was hoping for that
last one
[Music]
highlights into the hair now but we're
here
i'm working my neck
how's your body doing like
health-wise
oh
it's alive
nothing
[Music]
my answer would be suffering as always
it's alive yeah
are you taking care of your health inya
[Music]
um
you better be maybe your mom is watching
this right now if you say no that she'll
force you to take care of your health
you think your mom is watching us right
now
probably not
she does she only watch things on your
channel
oh no she watches other channels too and
clips but i think she said she was gonna
go out oh
i'm not sure
mama is out there somewhere gotta go
probably shopping for christmas junior
nice i hope you get lots of
nice presents
um
yeah what what is this i don't know what
are you wishing for
what i don't know because usually
like my family always tells me it's so
hard to get gifts for me because
whenever i need something i just buy it
myself
my friend said the same to me
i'm just like because i'm the one with
like the access to our family amazon
account or my
amazon account that like my family uses
sometimes too right so
if they want to get something from
amazon they have to go through me it's
already
ruins the element of something is in
control
yeah because they don't want to pay for
amazon prime
understandable one one account per house
household is yeah i mean that's not
reasonable
yeah
so they're like do you need anything i'm
just like
no
and get me food
get me a box of cup noodles that's all i
need
[Music]
premium cup noodles please exactly
almost like cup noodles of all different
kinds
it's the best because
i like to just like you know eat on the
fly
a lot
so cup noodles is good because i can
like technically quote-unquote cookie
like
very quickly right and just have the
meal done and i'll be just back to
working and stuff
you know for me like cup noodles is like
the very last resort
the way you cook
it's for me it's like how i eat frozen
pizza
frozen pizza takes too
no it just long like a maximum six
minutes meal like like okay let's say
you're like super super busy and you
just need to eat right
i guess it's rather cup noodles or
ubereats and you can't really uber eats
every single day yeah without feeling a
little bit of guilt yeah they always
bring too much food kind of yeah usually
when i order like takeout it's like
meal for like the entire day
yeah same same same i can't eat
[Music]
okay yes can you help me
okay
can you like maybe do the glasses for
example the glass is looking yeah
okay yeah it's like an orange color um
is there a color because yes there is
there it is yes taking a similar color
from you
you can just cheat
you can cheat
not really cheating it's difficult to
i find when when picking colors i find
picking skin colors
um
a little bit difficult
always like like either to yellow or too
pink
[Music]
really love the color thank you guys
please listen to it a lot
it's my my uh
uh my third holo myth
colabo cover
next one will be amelia
[Music]
looking forward to it yeah i'm planning
to have it out like maybe on valentine's
day
and so far i've been having
really special music videos for each uh
and every single one of them
and for the coming one
this the coming one might be the most um
how to say the most expensive one
oh wow
wait inna
oh
you're already fixing it while i'm doing
this
oh i'm drawing over your glasses
just to get my skin color oh yeah
[Music]
okay i'll go back over wait i have to go
there again sorry okay go ahead i have
to make it darker because of the shadow
actually it has to be even darker
[Music]
oh wait that's that looks too yellow now
wait chateau mata that is also what is
going on
uh
oh no that's too bright oopsie
you can just you can just
just cheat just take the color from the
left uh your color
yeah we don't have the same skin color
but yeah yeah yeah
uh
[Music]
that one's good oh yeah
that's the color i wanted how did you
know
oh i know everything
nice
teamwork teamwork thank you i'm gonna
wear it to this side too you can fix the
right side
my assistant
oopsie oops i drew into the haircut
we're getting closer to
[Music]
am i free to go over it oh yes yes
please do okay
oh that's too young
that's too yummy
that's that's okay
maybe that's also too yellow
i don't know what the hell i'm doing
here
yeah yeah how are the taco dutches
enjoying it a good question they must be
enjoying it because they're getting
cookies
that's what they want how many cookies
have i eaten so far quite a lot
many cookies yes
i made
inya i want to send you my christmas
cookies that i made
will they be okay i don't know cookies
usually have a long expiry date right if
they're packed properly i think if i
would have sent them on the day i made
them they would probably be fine but now
it's already been a couple of days so
i'm not sure
i'll just print it out on on paper and
use that or you could use my recipe and
make the same ones because i actually
posted a recipe
oh didn't you like just buy the
well yeah but i did post a recipe for
how to make the dough
oh
yes yes yes look into it i do like
baking stuff on during the holidays
it's a it's a typical
austrian christmas cookie called vanilla
kipvan repeat after me vanilla keypad
vanilla
what
[Music]
close enough vanilla
[Laughter]
i need to teach you some german huh
yes please
i want to learn german
i could put apples on top of your head
like i did with gouda
you get a green apple
oh if you want you prefer green apples
i like all apples
[Music]
yeah good i got the red apples but
a dessert that i can really
i mean i think that it exists probably
in other countries as well but for me
it's very austrian um that that
i like to eat it's with apples
it's like um
no
that one as well that one is austrian
but uh fried apple rings right out the
rings
five apple rings
for fr fried dough dough fried i have
fried fries no fried five fried
[Music]
fried apple rings
they're so good i love eating those so
much but i i rarely get to eat them
because
usually my mom my mom was the one to
make them and
you know i don't know how to make them
myself even though it's probably pretty
easy i should teach myself how to make
them
but fried food is usually hard to make
like on your own
oil stuff
yeah it's not so much oil i don't like
doing stuff like that because needs so
much oil it feels like such a waste
same
i need uh
professional air fryer oh oh
yeah i heard of that
do you not need oil for an air fryer
you just put oil but like
it's basically closer to like a
convection oven than an actual
oh
it is useful you can just drench stuff
in not really drench but you can just
sprinkle stuff with oil but
um it's not like the same as deep fried
but i think it's still pretty
very crispy
don't even need oil very little oil
but i already bought so many kitchen uh
appliances i don't even have any space
anymore in my airfryers are very
versatile
okay okay
would you like to sell me one
i mean okay think about i feel like i'm
like
selling you like
before air fryers but air fryer's
basically i still working on the
because if not you could like scribble
something here
oh okay
okay hell's gonna sell you some air from
do you think i think you can get away
from drawing here no no no no no
[Music]
okay
what is the left straw
what
you know like
[Music]
something like that
um
would you say you have uh
purple eyes or blue eyes or purple blue
eyes
purple blue lines
they're mostly blue
i feel like they're only blue at the
bottom
it's a mix of extra mix of
they're mostly blue
i'm gonna do your eyes now
blue she said blue
oh
nice calligraphy skills in yeah
i don't know what i'm doing
it looks like you do
yes
everybody listen to a new song cover
your ear whatever whatever whatever do
you have a day today where you feel like
whatever
whatever listen to this song it's made
for you
it's made from my everyday
[Music]
it's our
our uh anthem
yeah i said i was the anthem of my life
damn girl
[Music]
oh i'm getting so close to finishing it
we're almost there
[Music]
i forgot this hand here let me do that
i feel like that finger oh my god i drew
it really well it looks nice
nice i'm proud of that finger
[Music]
especially in that that left one
good finger
always gonna be proud of the ububs you
draw because you'll be user is one of
the most difficult things to draw
yes
true facts
[Music]
so you recently put out a solo sound
cover as well
uh-huh and now this collab with me
any any plans already for something new
or not yet
[Music]
i don't know i'm looking for a song like
i have like i had a lot of lit
but you got you got kind of you you have
a lot of old
i had a lot of like songs that i want to
cover hey but i don't know which one
oh
i don't know which one
i'm going to do next
like the one the songs that i've sang
like in karaoke i don't wanna
put out like an actual cover for them
because people already heard it right
it has to be something surprising really
i agree the songs that show
did i choose for my song covers i
usually don't sing them in karaoke
because like
then
why make a song cover out of it you
could just clip it and listen to it like
that
so i get that logic i do
[Music]
yet because i'm waiting for her live
english to eventually in a million years
put out ocha makino
so i'm hoping for it it must happen
right
one day here one day
i really like that song that's the
problem i know it by heart i've known it
since way before her life i even know
the dance to it because it's like so
addicting
[Music]
i just want to sing it for you guys
i can't stop myself anymore i've been
recently kind of like a cappella singing
uh a little bit on my streams
it is an acting song yeah
i love it
okay whatever whatever whatever nice
okay and then a gray hoodie
green
gray who did
very on brand akashibasan did uh some
very cute clothes for us i told him that
it should be some kind of like rough
clothing similar to the original um
music video so nothing yeah too crazy uh
you know
also since he does animations it should
be something that's easy to draw
obviously oh that's so true yes
but um
i like what he came up with i like the
turquoise heads that he gave me a pair
yeah
when i uh when i put out the
the um the blurred version of the
thumbnail
on my schedule people thought i was
getting cat ears but
i mean you do have caddies yeah they
could be hidden underneath i wonder
what's underneath that hat
i wonder
my cat ears are usually a bit bigger
than that so it's kind of sus
although there are heavies like that
that just have that shape with nothing
underneath yeah
it's a cute head
i like seeing us in that kind of
um
comfortable style of clothing yeah right
i know we already got like
like normal like everyday clothes yeah i
wouldn't mind seeing like pajamas yeah
oh
i have english and pajamas one day
yeah we can do like satsang and
like comfy streams in it that's true
that's true
but we literally just got our new party
dresses so i think that will be
something in the far far of our
future
yeah but foreign
[Music]
that looks really cute i like the
corona senpai she has that that had a
like
the hair
back i like that i use that too when i
wash my face so when i do my makeup
mine has cat ears on it
dude my nose has candles on it
yeah girls talk
nice
well enough what foundation do you use
do you use foundation let's talk about
makeup
chad will be like what the hell are they
talking about
i don't even remember the problem
[Music]
i don't go out that often anymore so i
was using foundation and a lot of makeup
from this korean brand uh a lot although
recently i've been barely going outside
so i've been barely putting on makeup
makeup but what was it again um
what's it called again uh
[Music]
what's that where's the korean makeup
brand again chad do you know
maybe there is a lot
i feel gory
my brain is in a lot
house dancing
house
in the house when you become a princess
every time you enter the store
do you become a princess every time
i don't know
well uh
yeah i oopsie i really like the makeup
from them it's like affordable and
really um
like they have for example really nice
lip tints well you guys probably don't
know what a lip tint is but
[Music]
i do like their makeup like i used to
i used to buy it their makeup because
like in my country i couldn't find the
foundation in in my skin tone
[Music]
wow girls talk oh my god
oh my god
[Music]
i'm not sure if we can actually do any
uh review streams or anything
[Music]
okay why not this is my real face what
do you mean i can totally put up makeup
put on makeup on my face
i mean it's not yeah but people won't be
able to see it like of course they will
yeah imagination
imagination
[Music]
live 2d makeup stream question mark
let me be the girl the youtube girl that
i always wanted to be
did you ever watch like youtube uh like
makeup gurus i i had a time where maybe
i watched like a few of them but i never
really got too deep into it they have so
much drama
you don't know many
no
if anything i watch captain
cat videos yeah yeah
lots of cat content i also
i know what what it is with uh uh all
these korean channels that i watch but
there's this korean uh uh channel that
is called a milky bokitan i think they
have uh one two cats and one big samoyed
dog and i really like their channel
you know what
no they got some but they like i do like
toggles and cats
and cats yes me too
mostly cat person but uh i don't like i
mean i like all animals but if i had to
choose like one to you know
put in my house uh-huh or raised and
i'll be
probably a cat who would be a cat
yeah
if you're actually looking at a lot of
adoption sites recently oh
you said that eventually someday someday
someday you're going to move
along are you planning to get a cat at
that time
yeah oh let's go
i'm so good but but i've never really
like had pets before somebody
if you need advice you can always ask me
yes if you're getting a need
um i would i would recommend you to get
two cats though
or two cats um the more cats the more
fluff but also just you know so that
they can entertain themselves when
you're busy when you're not at home and
all that
[Music]
i don't know because like sometimes in
like the adoption sites they're just
like this cats need to be alone
oh if you're crying like older cancer so
yeah that that is the case sometimes so
yeah that's true i thought you were
maybe like just getting kittens or so
but yeah i mean it really depends yeah i
mean if possible i want to get some from
like a shelter or something because i
don't know i really like hmm
get a cheese
geez she's a cat geezer
[Music]
he's a cat
i mean an old geezer do you say geez or
not geezer oh damn it is it it's a
geezer
i thought it was easy okay and then why
did why is it oh geez though
oh geez
some people say oh geez
this is the whole gift jeff thing again
i don't want no
no no
don't you say gift for jeffy now
yes yes okay
she doesn't want to
start a whole
thing now
this is the whole thing the same thing
with like the uh you know the japanese
[Music]
it's basically the same thing where
people have two options and then i was
like oh one's better than the other
it's all the same
[Music]
stop fighting
oh you made a lot of progress
you just notice where were you looking
at
your face i want to i want to
do something similar to what you did
like uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
now this one this one i dodged on
purpose
[Music]
you don't need to flirt with me like
that i love you
you don't i want to go
we don't even need to flirt to kind of
you know to like you know you know you
know we our hearts are already connected
it's not necessary
really yeah
i mean
yes look look at us here drawing a tt
image and having a tt sun cover out
there
okay
[Music]
okay okay where am i
trying to make it like blending they
could at least have given us a blending
tool
at least
but okay i guess not a bastard does not
need no blending
[Music]
okay
almost there almost
oh you're doing it you're so cute that
works actually oh my god i'm having fun
you know
yeah
you're finding your
joy of painting again yes
yeah
oh [\h__\h]
i don't know what i was doing there it
only took five seconds five seconds to
hurt the screen
i don't know what i was trying to
accomplish there
anyway no that's okay
and now uh mouth
inside of mouth color
do your reference
no no oh
oh yeah you have pretty uh
my mouth is much darker than your mouth
oh
jingle thank you
thank you
guys
[Music]
i love this image
also guys did you notice it on twitter
we have matching twitter icons right now
yeah
it's so cute
let's see who it is this is like you
know did you see how marine and i am a
senpai they had matching icons for like
quite some time
oh yeah
i think it was was it i am a senpai it
wasn't mindset but who first uh got rid
of it and yeah i was like oh my god
she took it out
[Music]
i barely remember it but i think she was
like a little bit sad yeah
because they had it up for so long
kusa they did it
because they didn't like the one collab
together right and that's what
changed uh
the icon
is it gonna be like this with us you
know oh maybe i did tell you i didn't
tell you uh you can take it down in like
maybe one or two days if you want but
but i wouldn't mind having it up a
little bit longer yeah
if anything i feel like you're gonna be
first to change it because i rarely oh
okay okay how about we keep it
we should maybe like put up like a like
a like a disclaimer that it's okay to
change it no one will be salty after a
certain amount of time
do you really need the disclaimer
yes
also not only for us but also for the
fans who will be like oh my gosh you
changed it first and the other girl she
still hasn't oh my god did they fight oh
this is so sad to look at okay okay
let's change it on the same if we end up
changing stuff we'll change it on the
same day people don't
don't start okay what if i keep it up
there forever and ever
are you sure you're gonna do that no
because i i mean i commissioned
specifically like you know my girl and
my uh
[Music]
my secret
oh
[Music]
how about we keep it up until the end of
and maybe a bit longer and 2021
a little bit
at least at least until the end of 2021
okay okay okay
deal
hey
i think i'm i might did i miss something
i'm like that i could still like
do some more i guess yeah did i miss
something
[Laughter]
i think i'm done
i like it i eat this what a deal
let me i gotta i gotta
i gotta flip the canvas though and then
i'll i will hate it i'm gonna tell you
it's gonna be fine my eyes tell me it's
gonna be fine
let me
let me flip that canvas
and see lift it we are both happy with
it
flip it i dare you
i flipped it i like yours yours looks
perfect
mine
could be worse
oh it looks green here what are you
talking about looks cranky cranky anna
oh it doesn't
yeah it's okay it's pretty it's pretty
good
you know what i'm gonna give us though i
wanna um although that will be very neat
it needs to be done by a calm hand i
wanna give us like a funky outline
like oh like like a like a thicker
outline yeah maybe like a but not in
black with just like a neon color or
something like that maybe
okay
pink pink i think pink will work on both
of us yeah is this color good
oh my brush is kind of small yes yes
good color yes good i can i can take the
same color and do it and and we can do
it together
okay
flip it again
[Music]
i was actually
i wanted to do a an art collab like a
proper one with you for quite some time
but to be honest i never felt like
comfortable enough we no we cannot add a
layer underneath there's only two layers
in this program yeah and we already used
it anyway i was saying yeah i i i felt
like i i didn't feel ready
for it you know and this this situation
kind of forced me into it now and
now i have it behind me my shoulders
feel so relieved yes
yeah
i'm glad i'm glad we could do it
don't count because that that's like
not proper drawing i would say
the little one yeah the hoodles that was
fun too but we didn't have to draw
humans so i think that's different
what's what's your brush size right now
like 30. i have pen printers though me
too okay i'll put it up a bit
okay
yeah but i'm glad we we did this
yeah very happy have a lot of fun
why did i do these hairs here oh no what
a pain
[Music]
story of every
drawing need a steady hand here
[Music]
damn it
you're doing it don't worry
[Music]
german want to add a little bit of white
at the end
why does the front need a little bit of
white to differentiate between the
pattern
oh
nice yeah
yeah it's getting so
much better i mean it always looked
great but now wow it's a masterpiece
[Music]
i feel like i'm in the inner stream
surprise you're on your own stream
it's my channel but it feels like i am
inna
do your best email impressions
[Music]
no matter what size
can you say something and i'll try to
recreate it
[Music]
really i
i i love emma
yeah
you just want me to say i love inna i
would say that any time i love you yeah
[Music]
that was not necessary
[Laughter]
[Music]
i know
you make me you make me happy
yay
you're so sweet enough
oh i'm so glad you speak because you're
telling live english
thank you for all y'all
thank you for joining me thank you for
joining
thank you
[Music]
i am on the bottom layer why mm-hmm
yes you're on top
[Music]
looks like you're trying oh never mind
oh i just yeah that is also on the
bottom layer so i have to be
very i didn't do that on the outline
later happening
no the regrets now
it's okay
regrets this means you did something
rather than not doing something
true the regret is about not doing
something yes but indeed in this case in
this case you know
it's all right
do you want to do the white around my
pink outline oh yeah
thank you
[Music]
drawing inside the line is overrated
sometimes
you know i really admire artists to
draw like
i like that the art art technique of
like drawing a sketch and then you know
without doing other layers just just
like
working on top of the sketch the whole
time you know what i mean
[Music]
um
rather than doing like what i or i think
you mostly also do like doing a sketch
and doing the outline on top of it and
doing the color underneath it you know
like very clean art
i i really admired the messiness
of the other art techniques
yeah but it still uses a little more
like that before but efficiency wise i
just didn't
felt like it took too long for me to
get a finished product and like my id on
paper when my brain is already thinking
about like what to draw next
yeah
meow
did you hear her
[Music]
is ending yeah
she always
she really
knows she really knows like when i
stream the moment i like switch from
this screen to my ending screen and stop
talking she will come into my room every
time now she came a little bit check
that she's super chat or something you
should watch me
she knows that the the time of when i
continuously talk
uh that she
you know just
should be somewhere else snapping not
that i kicked her out anything she
decided to be somewhere else because i'm
so noisy
yeah but the moment i stopped talking
she was coming to my room she's so well
behaved by both of my kids actually um
we're almost done just in here
[Music]
oh good so much
kids are so cute i love them so you know
what what fan art i want to see i'm sure
that you know you have i feel like you
have the most
um artists in your fan base so maybe
someone will listen to this and do it
but i want to see um the the new outfits
that we got the party dresses i want to
see an outfit swap
oh
i would like to wear your outfit or or
ammo's outfit or so because yours and
amazon i think my favorites i think
yeah i like everyone's everyone's outfit
which one would you like to wear which
one do you think you you would maybe
even look uh good in
[Music]
i mean
a dress like callies would not really
work so well on you
um
that it's just i mean it would work if
it's adjusted but it still wouldn't
maybe look that good on you but um
um
good good stress would definitely work
for you
yeah i don't like girls often maybe
maybe good
outfit but then change the the blue
elements into like your purple
to like you know have like a super smash
brothers thing going on where you can
change the colors
yeah yeah yeah
and then i mean there is a super slash
bros character that's similar clothes
kind of
to ah is it the one with the wings
yeah pit oh
maybe there's actually like a black
version of the clothes too actually
i never played super smash brothers on
my channel i really want to play it oh
you know let's play sometime let's play
let's smash i'm really bad but let's
play
what
never mind uh we're finished with the
art i think
[Applause]
[Music]
thanks for inviting me to the cover and
have
yeah of course thank you for taking the
invitation
yeah and for uh going with mostly the
things that i mostly decided
wow i
[Music]
how do we save this i don't want to lose
it
oh we have to screenshot it
no there is there is a safe option i
just have to find it again
somewhere i don't see it
well thank you
yeah we'll figure it out i hope you guys
are
enjoying the song cover uh please listen
to it every day put it into your
playlist so so
share it with your friends yeah yeah
spread the word um and yeah thank you
everybody for supporting
my music i will continue to put out some
music thanks to your support and yeah
thank you
thank you thank you
you were a great collab partner for
singing
of course
thank you for spending your precious
time with me on my channel it was fun
i almost died but that's just normal
that's okay yeah yeah whatever what
happened
[Music]
we say
a prep right here let's put this in the
middle and then let me let me put in
your hair and
here oh my hands
my hands
oh no my arms
or her arms i'm a kiara and kiara
everybody take a screenshot
yay
[Music]
thank you for watching this movie she
can't hold it anymore she wants to
cuddle
okay okay i got it i got it okay
bye-bye
i'm gonna go for everybody's comments on
youtube now to see what your opinion was
of the sound color
okay me too
eat them for hours wow
didn't you just eat cup noodles
bye-bye
[Music]
do