[Music]
uh
[Applause]
so how was your first day so far
what do you mean it's perfectly safe
i've only been here for 30 minutes
that's a relatively safe day here for us
fine you really want to know why
just look at her look at her
[Music]
what's wrong with you
look at that tummy the legs
[Music]
right yes and you don't think this is a
problem listen here you little
being able to see kiara and that outfit
is worth everything okay
[Music]
[Applause]
how's it going my fellow chimpkin you
seem to be doing very well you haven't
got promoted to the supervised after
only like three months
what's wrong
what do you mean getting worse
production is the highest it has ever
been suffering
from them
yeah and then their package is sold to
our customers it's perfect the circle of
lives
it is our queen quinoa commands
she's the one true queen
she's our savior she will guide us to
true happiness
[Music]
it is very dangerous to the wreckers the
concert says that the work is supposed
to be dangerous though
what do you mean um
why would i pay the insurance they're
supposed to pay me
you'll pay me so that you're allowed to
work for me so this is why i haven't
been receiving any paychecks over the
last few months and stuff someone keeps
taking money from my bank account don't
worry the money is put to the
[Music]
i am being serious smoothie and
chocolates are my life and soul
we can always recruit more that's
exactly what we have been doing but this
isn't a long-term solution
fine don't worry you propose since you
think you're so smart
[Music]
like what a bunny suit
i don't think you know what it means i
will hurt you
okay fine basically something that shows
less skin right is that what you're
saying
[Music]
um the tuxedo
how about those standard office clothing
that you see the ladies wearing at work
let's go