[Music]
he
yeah
[Music]
hello
hello everything's normal now I think
this the stream is kind of a little bit
I have a lagging
problem really let's hope better now
yeah okay so this is the first time that
I am uh asking uh some Ian member Kon
Kiara and FAA to join the uh Age of
Empire 2 uh but we also have Ana and
rainy to play
[Music]
again so uh this time this time um we
put it into a team um since me Ana and
rainy already playing this game before
so we put I think it's wisely to put uh
two versus two versus kind of thing
yes um every team have I and
ID International Teams let's go yeah
yeah yeah yay
yeah like a like a game setting with a
right map a noral six player and the
location actually right now is randomly
choose Coastal but I actually have no
idea about
it I don't have any idea about the maps
yeah I don't have any idea about the
[Music]
map are you sure it's random Mrs Mauna
who's playing Vikings are you sure that
was not on purpose cuz you're playing
Vikings I I put like game modes and
random M and they put the
Coastal okay
okay should I should I I Coastal is fine
right it doesn't really mean that the
whole map is covered with ocean right
it's just that there is a coast
[Music]
right
c yeah that there you can just choose
like 10 or 15 maps that you want to be
in the pool oh so you can choose
everything that looks good to you for a
big
match okay mostly oh maybe I just choose
the one that have like maybe six with
mostly they yeah people
M choose Arena too Arena and black
forest in the uh in the top uh two top
top two row Black Forest yummy black
forest and AR Black Forest yummy black
forest cake
oh
cherries which one again H in the top
row there should be black forest and
Arena it's alphabetic anyway Black
Forest yeah I heard that I never played
it but it's very popular I think for big
matches and then what do you want to
request ER Arena I don't know I up to
you anything's fine
it'll be fine oh you chose so many how
bad can it be all right you chose
so oh my God no no no no the one that is
on arum black
forest um which one but
there oh look at that V MAA pahit Empire
oh my God wait can I sh a costum map
Pool oh I can oh I can maps are there
there's so many oh wait is standard
there where's the big
mapish they have like a many Maps
there's a map called Mega random like is
it is there really like a question mark
shaved water on
it Mega random is just super random
interesting
unpredictable going to be heavily sty
list like everything is going to be
random it's not always going to be the
same I'm looking at four people yeah but
like the thing is I can't select see
like I I can't see the six people maps
how do I see the six people Maps four
people m mostly they're
four how
mostly how I mean it's just a map size
maps and these are just map Styles right
there 83 maps in the
game automatically adjusted it says oh
look at this oh now this is huge adjust
it ah you went to real world Indonesia
oh my God so much water in Indonesia not
real world not real world in real world
so much water in the real world go back
to
random random black forest
it's
fine black
forest um no no I put it on random black
for Black Forest Arena and Empire that's
the three random that I choose oh okay
black forest here but I guess when you
get to the game it's going to be
randomized yeah I
guess we'll see hey it's not bad if we
go eat cake
right cake is good let them have cake
let them have
cake okay um well I think it's time to
start okay guys ready are you going to
kick us out good luck good luck everyone
good
luck us have
mercy EAS okay bye
bye
let
hello
so I I I almost have no experience with
this game oh me too it's been a long
time since I played oh God you practice
I did not
practice but I watched one
video how to start the game for like 30
minutes I think yeah that didn't do
anything I think we got
this hopefully we
do so do we need to like team up first
in game or like we're already in one
team right
yes how does teaming work in this game
um I don't know are we oh we can see
each other's
Maps oh I
see oh yeah I can see I can see your
village
mhm so I think we just build yeah we
just
built next to each other or something
mhm okay
cool um and I think
we we get
sheep this is what I learned from the
video I watched uh-huh
is to good oh wait this is Indonesia
wait what oh are we in Indonesia we're
in
Indonesia yeah cuz I see the
flag I see the red and white flag oh
wait there's a Wonder right
outside our
walls there's a goat uh how do how do I
go here where you going hey there you go
where's this villager
going
I'm going to your village as we speak
right now wait where am I Scout I see
it yeah there you
go
um wait I need to make more V so little
materials there's so little materials
wait wa yeah are there
like trees I guess these are the trees
trees I don't see any Tree in my yeah I
see bamboo wood but no
trees do you see any trees no but I
think the bamboo is is okay wood yeah
should be
good it's still
W oh Stone wait let me
build Lumber
Camp here the um what what do you think
I should build first oh who's
scouting Kara is scouting in my house
oh I see a blue that's crony I also see
crony at your place they're scouting
okay why is everyone
here I think it's good to build a lumber
cam um okay we'll
do and
kill the Sheep the poor
sheep and
then eventually you want to
get uh Hey
aloom mhm do we have money I guess how
do
I how do I how do I choose
buildings I'm pressing nothing
working oh uhoh someone is scouting here
oh it's
MAA so scary I know it is scary they're
probably like so
scary
uh I'll build a mill
okay and I'm just making a lot of
villagers Lumber
Camp
here and
then mining camp
will be
good oh I'm my Scout is going
somewhere I haven't played this game in
a really long time but I did play it a
lot back in the
day oh oh I have many
ERS I don't know I'd have to check how
many hours I have although I feel like I
didn't even play the Ste
version back
then MAA Senpai is not leaving my
place please I'm just a little guy I
know I'm just a little guy don't do this
to
me oh oh she
left
um
okay
anyways
um you good I think I'm good
I don't know what I'm doing I watched a
guide to the first making the first
villagers what you should do with them
and I already forgot
[Laughter]
everything it's okay I don't remember a
single thing too mhm
YOLO all
right it's still early things can't be
so bad just yet I know
right I'm spamming Farms wait I should
probably build another house yeah cuz I
need more people that would be a good
idea yeah
uh all right oh research Loom right
that's a
thing yes I did do that whe
bar who is this
kiar Kar is here is there like a a truce
at the start of the game where we can't
fight each
other I I don't think
so I don't think so so we can fight at
the very
start well you can try well I don't
really want
to yeah what if they what if they tried
to find oh that's
you I was about to say fight Muna Senai
cuz she's nearby but maybe that's that's
not a good idea I don't have any
military units
yet yeah maybe I don't think anyone has
any in
unless
um make a farm okay I should make more
houses
yeah military
building I guess I will build a
barracks
oh I also have no idea where to put
anything I'm just me too I'm just it
puts wherever it
seems yeah may we should we should try
building
like no
okay I'm going lots of I
guess I'm spamming far right now for
food I guess we should try to advance
our to the age
ASAP oh MAA Senai
place just SC thing don't mind me oh God
I feel like she so
[Music]
dramatic feel like she's going to attack
me any time now oh
no she scouting
somewhere you
oh you
oh uh go
here excuse you thank
you is this C there's one minute left in
the
treey uhoh oh
uhoh wait how do you increase your
Villages again oh oh you just built
houses you and you need food and then
how do I make them work like the the
people who are not working uh you can
push period to find them and
then uh right click on whatever you want
them to
do
okay what am I where am I where am I
where am
I
um archers are archers good what they
did say we're allowed to accept back
seaing from
chat oh yeah which could save
us how do we get archers oh we need an
archery
range
um why can I
not buy
this it cost
175 oh
oh oh we have to upgrade Advance the age
I'm almost to the feudal age oh crony
just made it to the feudal
age okay yellow vill at the
top oh
nice
oh make bunch of villagers I probably
should make more houses
or maybe make archers I don't know what
I'm doing me neither
really I'm just hoping for the best hot
key H I know we were talking about hot
Keys before the stream and I was like
wait you guys use hot
keys I don't have hot keys I don't use
hot keys I don't know how
to me
neither oh I'm going to build a market
that seems
good what were we doing again right I
should
build more houses more houses maybe just
because okay there you go oh my city is
looking so
ugly I don't think mine is any better
either
are archers
good they should be but I don't know if
the The Meta or not I don't know
either what is scary music for theer one
oh I'm going Zen one attacking your
place
no okay I don't think
so there is scary
music
scary music is
normal Calvary is good for my S maybe
here maybe here and then oh there you
go 10 rude I love this
game I know I'm happy to be playing I
love this game too I haven't played in
so
long me too I have AR we collap this but
that was like a year
ago was it already a year ago I have so
many little
Meats
yeah oh who is
this wait wait wait wait wait I have a
lot of far away
found
yes K is AFK in my place if you want to
come and attack should
we is it bad start a war I should go
back where is she her Scout she's like
should I kill herting but she's not
moving okay she's not moving at all
guess we teach her a
lesson uhoh is this does this start a
war I mean why
not why not I don't know she's still not
moving she she's still not moving are
you fighting her
I am heading back to my place
I to my
Scout my Scout
what did they kill our
Scout
wait what does that
mean I might be Stu
huh
help are you okay
um my Scout is not okay I think mine
might be dead I'm killing kiar Scout
with my
archers should I get rid of the
roots is that what I should do get rid
of
what right I'm stuck like in the middle
roots oh you might have to like chop
them down yeah oh oh oh oh they're
attacking they're attacking me oh
there's
another dead you're a scout my Scout is
dead oh no I couldn't get
out I'm just a little guy I know oh oh K
left I killed her her Scout oh I wonder
if she
noticed
we're all just little guys out here yeah
we're just little guys okay God trying
our
best how do you get more Scouts again do
you need to like build the military
buildings yes I don't know which one let
you get a scout though
oh
um oh God more wots please I'm building
many
archers okay that's enough gold that
should be enough gold
right
um create the villager oh not enough
food okay cool I have a lot of food can
I give you food oh wait did you build a
tree is that
possible the what I'm sorry did you
build a Trade Center
yet um no not yet I'm trying to work on
it let me know when you build build one
okay going very
slowly need more
houses research wheel
Barrel Town watch do that that seems
good
O
A oh yeah we need
foodom
oh oh I could get a monastery I'm going
to build a
monastery so I can grab this Relic here
unless you get mugs you can get relics
and it generates gold you can win in
some mode with it but I don't know if
you can win in this mode that's amazing
oh
okay
[Music]
oh
fine hand card yeah re I'm just going to
research
everything
and hope for the best a oh hi bi
boo welcome welcome oh hello
bioo um we're playing Age of Vampires
and we we might be the underdog
team but I Believe in
Us
yeah who knows what will happen I want
both of them to fight and then we oh try
to take everything from behind that
would be good you know that would be
cool
um oh my Scout I'll be able to make more
people build a
castle do I want a
castle why not you know
um I don't see why not to build a
castle my monk go get
this my civilization can have
[Music]
elephants and I'm mostly excited to get
elephants can do that yeah that's why I
be so
cool the Persians get elephants you know
what I kind of just picked mine
randomly go home also
Fair more wood do I need more
wood I have a lot quite a lot of
food I have 23 food 23 can I can I
donate to
you I should build a Trade Center
wait I have like 1,00 th gold oh yeah
build a trade center and we can
trade
[Music]
mhm um I think it it's still locked for
me okay I'm going to build the farm
first oh there's a lot of relics around
wa who is
this muna's scout is here can I convert
her
Scout can I wo her
Scout I could
try she killed me so you have to take
revenge for me will I'm going to go
below
her hopefully ter what does it mean w
it's the sound that the monks make
whenever they convert a unit oh they
go
oh that is interesting to know
I'm going to make a million
elephants I will load
her
nice now I have two what we doing
here does it consume the monk when you w
low I have no idea Chad might know yeah
oh everyone is idle okay hold on more
more more lumber
Camp over
here Monk Is Not cons where did my monk
go what's he
doing oh oops
oopsies whe battle sound
watch why are
you why are you
idle we need
food we need
food okay there we
goom
card
H oh here's my
monk oh cool okay wait I want to can you
follow this
one and
then I wish to go collect these relics
oh um no no no no
no my elephants are
here I'm on
[Music]
patrol they huge
do you see them they huge
yeah that's actually so
cool Elite war
elephants
a grab
this oh there you go no no no no
no and go
back I Advance oh
need a lot more
gold um Lumber Camp do I have more
humans I have a
m not sure I'm very afraid if anyone
starts attacking
us MAA senile already
dead but she didn't send my Village but
she yeah she got my Scout no I have yeah
if we get
invaded
yeah
well when it happens it happens I guess
that's
true um did you build a Trade
Center not yet okay wait where do you
find it
again I think it might be l wait how do
I oh you need to advance your age yeah
Advance how do I ADV Town
Center say
Advance um I don't see it so I guess I
shoot um on your town
center
uh-huh oh yeah I need more Meats
yes can I donate food to
you no idea can we trade
um
a
diplomacy
um oh you need the Trade Center to trade
that actually makes a lot of
sense you guys did somebody die
no
[Music]
I shouldn't have done that right well
then
um I think I have a lot of stuff I don't
know what to build
though we Town centers is that
good
is that the
meta I thought you only do that if
you're
dying where
elephants upgrade my troops
okay cross
Bowman okay there you
go should I advance to the cual age why
not more
elephants oh
no what's up what's up no are you okay I
I messed up my clicking and now
it's no it's kind of messed up is it
okay no but you need to see my
farm
oh I see don't worry mine look way
crazier I just Place mine wherever they
go it's not symmetrical now okay I I'll
live with
[Music]
it do I what do I have
once where is M here too hi
M hi Ms
this is wait crony started building a
Wonder wait does she win if she does
that I think so do we need to kill her
Let Them Fight Let them fight each other
fight are they going to let fight each
other oh I see her
wonder how long does it
take I have no idea I think it takes
pretty long like 15 to 13 minutes or
even long
[Music]
long
oh oh
gosh moo will take care of it they're on
the same
team they're on the same team it's
over
uh how do we it's okay they will fight
each other will
they they they will definitely fight
each
other I don't know
I don't
know do we need to go we go there we
go
um release the elephants is what what
unit should I do to wait do I need to
build a Siege
Workshop uh do
you
maybe I guess you just attack them what
do you need for a Siege
Workshop build a
blacksmith you have plenty of
time wait is the blacksmith a regular
one oh it
is everybody go
help treuchet plus elephants look at my
elephants maybe I should more elephants
H wait no Castle also make oh Trevor
shes okay
okay
uh oh what do I want all right here we
go
everything
oh I get everything
more
villagers are we at the highest
level there you
go
Farm 800
huh more elephants
no
oh um blacksmith
Market at
least
good where's Trade
Center oh this
[Music]
mhm I'm going to have this I don't know
here must be packed to move unpacked to
attack What will what will un do my
Treet
Castle
okay there we
[Music]
go I'll try to get the castle up oh I
have our
elephants do I want to
skirmisher how do I get those
elephants uh elephants are from my
civilization only
oh but you also have a unique
unit some unque unit I
see that's actually super
[Music]
cool okay there we
go
H okay research
P Watch is that
good oh do I need to send the
treets to the to the
Wonder Elite elephant and blacksmith
upgrades are there more blacksmith
upgrades did I not get all of
these all right oh there's
more let's see
[Music]
is an
elephant a Calvary
Calvary I think we need the elite war
elephants more castles equal more
elephants okay I like the way you think
but do we have enough
stone is it worth it
why
[Music]
not I forgot how fun this game is
although maybe it's only fun cuz we're
not being attacked
yet I mean that she'll be one of the fun
Parts too it's
true oh I want to get my Elite war
elephants and then I'll send them
over
start The
Siege but maybe I should leave some
units at home to defend just in
case all
right Lucky
Sevens
cool um oh wait I don't have nearly
enough gold for the elite War elepants
we might just have to
go
oh yeah how is the wonder how is Cron's
wonder I don't know but I'm going to go
I think I'm going oh you're going to go
and
see yep I'm going to send in I say if
they're fighting each other leave them
be that's true but what if nobody
is
yeah yeah I think it will be a good idea
to
check um um I can sell wood at the
market
K what the heck is this stuff oh this is
the
University oh
gosh murder
holes
oops
oh okay there we go why you can't sell
wood wait I have so much
wood I have a lot of
wood research
everything uh all right I shall research
too pwn
watch I don't know how good that is food
oh
no hurry
I need more
Farms more Farms
everyone work I build more
too oh is it
them there go oh you can send your trade
card to my Trade Center to get
gold
oh I think I have enough gold I still
have
like almost 2,000 oh but you should send
it anyway cuz that's how I think that's
just what it should be doing it'll go
back and forth ah how do you do that um
do I just go to your yeah just go to my
trade mark it and then click on it with
your with your
unit
okay which one is trademark at G uh mine
is
next to my castle
University oh this
one oh I'm out of
[Music]
stone do I just click
my fure to go
okay I'm going to go attack her and hope
for the best select my trade
card
oh which one is that again oh here there
we
go Cody is already in shambles is
she or will she be what happening I
don't know I'm about to attack
her careful of Mauna
Senpai oh yes it's not going to be a
good idea to meet her
halfway I'm going to hope for the
best and I'm going to build more more
elephants I'm being attacked by wild
animals that should be
no no trouble right we are the wild
animals oh no my treor shades are
unpacking to fight the wild
animals are they going all
right there we go you guys
[Music]
going
a
hry town
center a university will be
[Music]
nice maybe more TR
CS
okay my units are going this one is the
fake out she's going to think it's okay
cuz there's just one and then these guys
roll up
ooh oh they're fighting they're fighting
they're why then let's go they're
fighting let them
be this is the Wonder wait is the Wonder
already
dead I think so wonder I'm being
attacked by
K oh is this her Tower her
castle I
see don't walk by the cast closing
anyways these
monks I don't see I don't see any of
Muna senpai's people so oh never mind
the elephants are out we should be fine
I
think oh we're fighting oh gosh I
see those elephants
man the elephants are
going oh
nice wait
the
castle you destroyed her
castle but is is Kiara's
Castle I guess she's sping me
too oh
gosh how's everything at home maybe we
be careful be
careful k k k going in oh my trets are
dead oh well you guys are that's fine
you guys are attacking
crony yeah my elephants are on the war
path maybe I should send them home
though yeah cuz you destroyed her castle
and one more
building I'll send them home
a
okay it's time everyone go
[Music]
home okay you know what I need more Farm
we have a tactical
Retreat now we
defend all right bre the New Castle is
this just
mean I feel like I'm going to make
enemies
here I think that's kind of the point of
game yeah kind point of the
game there's no friendship oh no
I guess it's
not oh no her castle got
built Oh My Elephants aren't that good
against the
castle wait how do you build military
stuffs more
buildings yeah I see it
wait palite
gate
Watchtower more
trebet do the research a workshop spies
you know what I should have this
first oh and
you
trade
um I want more trade how much gold do
they get
that's a good
question oh my monk can heal the
elepant oh no moon is attacking me where
where is she I don't
know I don't know
where your village seems fine
though yeah it does seem
fine is it really fine
I hope
so yeah oh oh oh my Scout is in her my
elephant is in her Camp why is my
elephant
here why there's a lone elephant here me
what are you doing my
elephant get out of
here that's a lot of elephants whatever
the
elephant will just he sacrificed Hey
where's the
people he's just a little
guy I have a lot of elephants oh wait
the monk can heal
these
oo please heal
these sh spend these resources I should
but where do I spend them
on
okay research
everything oh I spend like all my
gold that may have been
bad
oh oh
okay I just
want
money I can cancel the
resources
maybe I should what's everyone
doing is he
feeling is he doing
it sell the
wood oh wait we have a lot of this quite
hot
wait oh my wood economy is in shambles
though look at
this Okie doie how much do
I oh
gosh oh wait I have a lot of idol
villagers I need more
food always need more food
research
foring oh I should
create oh you need houses okay you know
what that makes sense that makes sense
that makes sense SI work bu work
what there you
go
oh house did I build this
no this placement is kind of but
okay I not have a stable
either what's happening oh okay
everything is good for now is everything
good for now for now it's
good oh no right I just want more
money more gold money will solve all of
the problems
right yeah how do you how do I give you
my gold oh you don't need to give me
your gold it's okay oh if you need
anything do that in game I think you
can
o I guess there is a gold
mine salom a
nice wait so I'll build a mining C
Mia
man oh you can
upgrade
cool that's
expensive is it worth it
though what are you looking at oh
oh um I'm seeing at the archery
upgrades oh
yeah okay I'm going to do this too for
now and then Camel
Rider um um so let's
see I'm researching
[Music]
everything Siege Tower I shall do that
too oh
nice camels counter
Calvary crossbow
[Music]
men I farm
oh I should get this I should have got
that a long time AG there's so
many UPG you good
[Music]
yeah rang units oh
no like
this click unit to
C oh yeah you do that
right
going to research
everything if we just get a million
units we can never lose
right can never have enough find
out I'd love to find
out who's
Idol
Farms
oo now what she'll make
[Music]
more guard
Tower I shall make even
more I should make even
more
okay
oh oh I don't know what I'm doing
me
too I feel like the others are probably
like doing a
lot yeah they're fighting they're
probably doing good
things and I'm
not is fight then considered a good
thing I guess
not okay wait what
oh
cool
okay aggressive
stands if you let them build it's going
to be worse that's true stand stand
ground should I try to fight
somebody Raine maybe my next door
neighbor
how's she
doing I don't
know oh yeah I could Scout that's
probably smart mhm do I even have Scouts
anymore I do what happened to your scout
no they're just hanging
out
a
I have a lot of elephants that's for
sure not enough
units what are good units to
have I'm going to research
stuffs oh I need more
gold I see
elephants rain is attacking me oh no my
Scout did my Scout
die I think so there's a castle right
here
[Music]
H Castle the castle
more
upgrade I'm not
afraid I've got
elephants and
trebuchet I sh Scout too and
horses I saw someone said that my
civilization is the horse girl
civilization I'm not I'm not a horse
girl
maybe I am
though you you kind of you kind of are I
I have a lot of horses oh what are these
what the heck are
these what you find wa wasn't I building
I was building camels
though uhoh uhoh oh I'm getting I'm
getting
[Music]
attacked oh no more is starting
elephants do you need do you need
assistance oh they're pretty op oh no no
no I'm good it was just my one Scout oh
gosh it was just my one Scout oh shoot
let's
go oh gosh I'm going I'm
fighting oh she's got Trevor Shades
too uh-oh
oh you good I think I'm
winning
oh
nice
maybe a roll out
elephants
[Music]
research
H what shall I
research murder
holes murder holes sounds good yeah
sounds kind of spicy I'm going to
research
it
okay okay that was a good start I'm
building more
houses um how do I heal these guys does
my monk have to do
it is he good at
it oh no
no all right there you go
houses cross Bowman more elephants more
Treet more
elephants with
villagers I may attacked by rainy where
we looking
fine
oh you
good is she building again oh
no she may regret this
decision
uhoh monkey get out of here get out of
here monkey go back
home five
okay
oh
uh-oh elephants
fight where you guys fight then I'm
fighting oh I found you oh
shoot W let's
go
okay elephants go
those elephants yo I I will be so
frustrated yeah that will be so
frustrated I need
more
houses more houses for more
elephants
more all right more more
people
a okay I need to build more
houses there's not enough houses more
houses
a okay that's a
lot
more houses more
elephants and everything will be
good more houses maybe more
Farms okay cool I have a lot of
resources do you need
anything um maybe
gold
okay can
I how do I trade with
you I have no
idea I also have no
idea
umy
[Music]
tab I see hey
tribute wait researching coinage all
right okay I'm going to research stuff
first so I can get a better
deal
um tribute is not a good
idea oh a
a
sorry is more more castles are more
castles really
good oh yeah I need to build more
buildings more buildings more
[Music]
elephants that is that is
right more
units time to have this
uh more
units more elephants more units more
elephants more houses all
right there we
go 200 elephants no no more
TRS what are other good units I should
the camel Riders seem
good what's strong against
[Music]
archers
houses
[Music]
skirmishers elephants
horses do we just need more elephants
not beating the horse girl allegation
I
know I have several
units here I don't even know what all of
these are oh you can go un finished
buildings I
see okay my elephants are getting healed
very
slowly oo I'm getting
rich oh good I guess not for Stones I
need more
Stones all
right this guying
here oh you think I can fight rain oh
no apparently those two seem to be
fighting so you can
try I should Scout first I guess I don't
do I even have that would be a good
idea why is there a random house here I
guess I buil it
there
nice I should research quite a lot of
food I have a lot of
research a lot of resources
[Music]
explosives are you guys all I
don't
uh-oh
uh-oh you good I'm
good upgrade my
balls
build stone
wall all
right I have enough
Stone can I upgrade my walls I'm running
out of stones
too Persians can't upgrade
walls or monks for more
healers
[Music]
Library
no defend only
attack we're just wait why does it look
so ugly like
this I'm just doing the attack on Tian
strategy where I have multiple layers of
walls
oh yeah that's the
plan that would actually be kind of
smart
strategy I don't know if I have enough
stone for this your place looks so clean
oh thank you my place this wait who is
this who is
here somebody's there do you need help
this who's building a castle oh my God
they're building a castle we have to we
have to fight
them what is
it oh goodness
it's Kiara she's here she's right
outside build a castle she's not ready
for my
elephant I'm going to send help she's
not
ready
uhoh are you sending I'm sending in
elepant
and the Trevor shets oh
God oh
God it's a
massacre you cannot Escape
me they're trying to run but they
can't oh there's another
Castle
whose Castle is it everybody pack it
up this this one pack my
Tre she's got another
Castle where's my oh there you
[Music]
go but I'm ready I more Mony don't go in
alone
uh my elephant is aning
upgrate who are these guys do they
fight oh they fight they're a little
FY no you're elephant it's
okay I need to send everybody else
in that's right pack it up pack it
up get out of
here
who walls are these yeah there's walls
over
there you know what let's
go I think I'm going to attack
rain oh my monk has
almost
okay look at my why do my walls look
like
this also what does even have happening
here I'm going to destroy those
walls
oh why do my walls look like this what
is
this was this the mining
[Music]
cam
bring villagers how do I how do I get
the
villagers separated uh-oh uhoh wait wait
wait wait why are my treets here why are
my calvaries
here I've gotten too far wait maybe they
should be
here are they in shambles um you guys go
here uhoh they're
strong
uhoh
uh-oh they're fighting each
other oh no they're actually figh the
my okay pack it up and
leave oh they're getting
close what is happening my trade
cards okay they left
uhoh you
guys
build a
gate I can't see what's happening here
what is this is a guard
Tower and mining camp need to go out for
more
stones I have so many
trets forget wall you need
units how many
units which units
elephants probably elephants
[Music]
okay more elephants always more
elephants
um H archery to who are who are these
people oh I can research something for
the elephants you can going to research
this I don't know if you get the effect
to like you you should
right does f also receive this
effect B elephants receive plus one
normal uh-oh I'm getting attacked ah
uh-oh oh
gosh my my
Army I only have
trebuchets oh they're really they have
wait they have a lot of units this is a
lot of units uh-oh oh oh they're double
teaming me oh no I'm sending in My
Elephants oh no no I'm getting distra
I'm sending in My
[Music]
Elephants uhoh everybody
uhoh
fight
uh-oh
more oh it's over it's over it's over
wait are they
living are they living no they're not
leaving
uh-oh it's
over oh no you can build a town center
in my city if you want if you send a
villager and we can live
together
uh-oh
fight there's more people
inside no my poor
villagers
uh-oh double click elephant to select
all of them
oh everybody go are they retreating
uh-oh maybe not oh
no oh
[Music]
gosh
no who are all you
[Music]
guys my TRS are my TRS working
no well there's a castle
uh-oh my poor villagers
up
uh-oh I'm trying to send in the
reinforcements wait that's
you
oh
gosh four un
go more everything more
elephants more
elephants cast is alive for some
reason that's a lot of is a lot of
elephant
uhoh
no it's okay we can
rebuild we just need more
elephants uh-oh my game is lagging okay
they're leaving I
think oh that's my game is is is dead
maybe uhoh I'm lagging out you
okay
oh I think we're okay maybe yeah we
should be okay we should be good thank
you are you okay yes it's very much
lagging but oh my gosh me me and my
little
filler my castle is still here though
good some stuff I guess
oh my
God this little guy just casually
farming
okay I'm going to try to attack rain
now pack up my
trebuchet everybody can I build stuff in
your
place I think you
can no I don't need h where am I being
attacked
blacksmith should have one
here
oh oh my gosh my
elephants I have so many
[Music]
elephants what is this
oh I
[Music]
see more
everything okay okay
team
um you guys over here too oh my
gosh
me um you can focus on rebuilding I
think yeah I'm doing it right
now thank God I have enough
materials
um you
all
right um what do we
need good question Stone and
then all right roll out
everybody you guys
what I'm being attacked are
you where
oh
[Music]
it's well that's
fine
uhoh elephants go for it do your best
[Music]
elephants
pack it
up
uhoh is everything good I don't
[Music]
know can I get in you have to bust the
door
down are you attacking I
am I'm busting the door
down oh shoot
let's freaking
go that's
so the kids are
open that's a lot of elepant pack it
up
is this the Town
Center all
right your best
elephants more
people who's
this I don't know how to how to kill
someone how to wipe somebody out a scout
AFK in my
place oh this is
Rus um let me see destroy
[Music]
everything I'll
try oh
gosh I need more
units I need more
elephants I could have infinite cross
Bowman cuz they only cost
wood a don't
leave what's happening over there oh my
goodness I'm
a
uh more
[Music]
elephants more more
everything oh that's pretty
amazing oh God okay what do I do with
this people
again a here upgrades are there upgrades
to
get for these Siege units but I haven't
been using
them
um okay
oh I need
more
okay how much do they they cost the game
oh I see
oh we attack
by
[Music]
where
everybody pack it
up
and get
ready oh my rider in her base why are
you
there that's fine you WIP the entire
place I'm sorry I'm sorry
R El sleep oh W wo w w this is actually
satisfying to
see she has a castle here
uhoh elephants roll
out everybody roll
out
elephants
going to do this for
now then more
houses how do you quue the houses wait
no all
right
uhoh pack it
up
[Music]
she's on the Rampage I am on the
Rampage I did lose a lot of units
though what's moai and crony up to I
don't know but we should probably be
afraid
yeah
true
um let's see
you
everybody roll out here can I repair
this oh there you go okay okay okay more
elephants more
trebuchets more
[Music]
crossbowmen pack it
up
all right
everybody everybody group
up and get ready to roll out my
elephants are
gone my elephants wait why are they here
why are my elephants
here oh
no I still see them why are they
here already he roll
out oh
no they rolled out too
much how do I control
them they cannot be
controlled okay
no the
rumbling oh goodness is attacking
me
where I have no
idea
uh-oh
um My
[Music]
Elephants my
archers is this enough no one building
to go
fight oh they're woing my
elephants they can't do that how dare
they
Faron this more than enough let's just
get these guys to come as well I like
how they March in
formation oh wait they got a lot of
castles oh gosh
uh
right all right get ready for the
castles I don't know if there's any
units ignore
it is it a red
hering the
castles I
see
H more
elephants
more
Castle more
crossbowmen more
[Music]
houses
stable heal my units but I don't know
how it's
hard all right pack it
upal massive elephants there could
always be more elephants get to
it all right I'm going to roll out get
to it
[Music]
everyone yeah to ready
everyone can we go in through here how
they off you
cron and Mauna I don't know maybe we
should be
afraid
yeah way to
suspicious way to suspicious that I
don't see
them
oh
what uh-oh
all
right my oh God I need any
more My Elephants can't
[Music]
pathfind are they woing okay kill
them oh good okay time for St
send in more
[Music]
elephants more
elephants what more
archers
more
oh I see how I get rid of this no
okay okay elephant good
job the elephants are rampaging okay
okay you know what okay okay I
understand I understand the gate is open
all
right okay fine oops pack it
up
is this the Town
Center how many people do I have now
we're on the war
path
no please do your best
elephants oh
gosh there's more elephants down
here
okay there you
go oh you're making a nice Army here
yeah I know right it's good
defense because they probably start
coming for us
eventually I'm forming them thank
you all right the elephants are really
moving
out
attack the
civilians have no mercy
um going do this for
now
uh-oh more trade
okay I'm running low on by me oh looking
like oh
no what what
happened my arm is
trapped oh
no can they not go through the
gate what
happened stal oh
no they could be the
defense unlock the gates wait can I open
the gate oh I'll open the
gate
I think the
gate oh wait it should be
unlocked
maybe are they stuck in the
corner the game might be dying can I
destroy your wall
sure oh I I don't even know if they're
capable of doing it oh oh then they
should
be
okay everybody I'm trying oh I can't
never mind they're not doing
anything oh
okay pack it up oh
wait this
one well the game is dying for
me uh-oh oh wait delet delet my
wall I delet
it I it's fine it's only two armies
anyways okay it's only two people I may
have made too
many wait is
it too many oh I can make more people
right I need more
houses
all
[Music]
right there too many
elephants oh gosh it is like the
rumbling oh no here sign oh
no have I got too
far oh no wait what happened I might
have trampled
everything all right
everybody crony is up
next pack it up and roll
out
everybody if you need help call me any
time okay I might have enough I don't
know if I have enough units anymore I do
have
units we'll send those for
backup who send these guys I'm
forming I'm forming a nice group of
alleys right
here oh is this Castle I'm
sorry so many military units I
know
okay elephants rolling I have it
here I going we got to make more No it
should
be all
right oh goodness the elephants don't
know how to pass
on oh
good oh my
God okay the elephants have infil
I'm oh this is oh okay I
see it up R that's
cool all
right my archers have arrived come this
way
uh-oh
roll out
everybody more
military yeah maybe I should build a
Wonder but then I need to defend
it oh no that's what they get for
attacking me
yeah
I can help you are you good sending the
rumbling but I might need to
build build a Wonder oh you you're doing
good it's too late for I I need to
upgrade more
stuff upgrade them and then maybe we
should be going this
way you want to go from Luna s by next I
think
so
yeah I can send in some guys okay send
in everything you
got
okay
well maybe we should I mean we should
Scout but I'm just going to send
everything in and hope for the best I
think
let me know if you're
staring I think I'm going to I'm just
going to go for
houses okay hold
on you're going to Mauna senis right
yes oh the wall is already
open
[Music]
is it here yeah it
is I'm sending them in okay I'm sending
them where are they
hiding did I send them yeah I am it's
going to take a
while but they're heading there oh they
got
walls
ooh they have many walls it is like
Attack on Titan
[Music]
uhoh the calvary is here uh-oh that's a
lot it is a
[Music]
lot I'm sending backup
troops
[Music]
uhoh on more
archers all
right heading
there me too oo you
broken oh
gosh I don't even know what's
happening
okay more crossbowmen oh oh I need more
houses oh no go go everyone
uhoh I
hope I hope they're doing
well wherever they
are uhoh oh that's you I'm
sorry I got scared I saw another
color
I think we're doing good I think so
too
yeah I'm going to try to break
down the
doors oh I need more houses cool
too okay the gate is
open let's go
let's freaking go everybody in can they
have more
gates open the flood
gate you have so many units
too I'm sending out almost all of mine
oh yeah me
[Music]
too we need a buster here
too Haack it
up and roll
out oh yeah they have more stuffs there
yeah
a all right good luck
elephants go
go
go do your
best I'm coming
in oh you did it oh one more there's one
more there one
more where's all this stuff
is this their
stuff I have no idea
maybe
oo all right roll out all right
go go in
[Music]
everybody
this is so crazy this
unit it is no
mercy no
mercy oh
no all
right
oh crony resigned do is this it is it
just Mo
[Music]
left we
won let's go Anya I didn't do anything I
didn't you did you had so many units TOS
goes to you no thank you for the car I
think you you shielded me you were the
tank you tanked the
oh yeah I guess I kind of distracted
them I guess that's something yeah you
distracted them while I built a million
elephants do you want to move to the
yeah yeah let's go yeah let's
[Laughter]
go
still that was really
nice I enjoy that that was fine I'm to
play scared k at first like K put Castle
everywhere yo I was minding my own
business and was like yo yo yo yoa can
you send some help I'm gonna attack Crow
and I'm like what dude I was minding my
own business and I was minding my own
business too sound like everyone was
minding their own
business damn Kiara was over
blind I mean I was just trying to get
the game the ball rolling well I guess
so yeah before someone rolls it on me
yeah I guess otherwise you know people
would be just like build like me like me
peace well me and Ana I feel like we're
playing like a farming simulator me that
was me that was me before Kiara was like
yo help me out I'm like huh what oh yeah
yeah actually the reason I attacked
crony was because she was building the
wand and I build the Wonder you target
for everybody yeah she building the
wonder she was building a Wonder yeah
and that gives you automatic win if you
keep it for a very long time and as we
see this game was going to go on for a
long time so the Wonder could have won
yeah that would have been a good Strat
found I was about to attack but then I
was like if they're fighting each other
then let them be
I just did elephant strategy just build
a million elephants and hope for the
best wait can we see the I think Mauna
has to maybe somebody has to press
something so we can see the the the
stats or something oh yeah that's
already here um oh sorry I understand is
it quit current game yeah do you do you
click to M A there we go
nice wait where do you see it oh my
Society hi
Society living in the society I clicked
return to map a
lot Society a
lot
yeah cool cool cool cool cool a very
nice oh when come back to economy I sent
a lot to
[Music]
oh you were
trading t t trading oh I had 11 castles
it was good it was good I killed 196
people yay oh
no very cool oh our numbers are actually
not bad yeah nice food collected
yummy wood collected very
oh
oh very nice if you look at timeline you
see like the graph of how things are
changing
ooh I see I
see oh my god wow just like going up
yeah the
Taps all about the
elephants
yeah let me see I want to see not
attacking first was a good strategy
though cuz like we could
focus chilling at the
start I was like if if they're fighting
each other then let them
be yeah I mean why not that's probably
what you should do true but sometimes
the intrusive thoughts it's true yeah I
them
to in intrusive thoughts I just yeah I
understand in my chat people say like
nobody stands in that
way what whatever we do natur Alis
wi uh well normally I would have liked
to play defensive too but I don't know I
had to kill the Wonder and then from the
Wonder everything was just like rolling
and I it just happened yeah feel like
aggression is good it adds the spice you
know yeah I think I underestimated you
guys honestly I thought maybe you guys
didn't practice enough so maybe you get
a sneaky Wonder out
yo I was a couple how do I build the
[Music]
Barrack was constantly asking yeah don't
remember almost a single how do I do
this how do I do that why are people
unemployed um if if I want to ask for
rematch again would you want to do it
but not now yeah yeah not now but I'm
totally down another time will be nice
yeah this game is really fun maybe this
time it's uh we we make it pretty pretty
easy because we have a cheating seat in
in our live chat but the next time how
about no Che yet no yes
sure if you can really control that we
could we could randomize the Cs so that
everybody gets something unexpected from
it's not months from now cuz by then I I
forget about the game
[Laughter]
already we Su just the date immediately
before we forgot how to play
again I'm
saying what I'm
saying
maybe after this I will put another date
yeah but overall this this seems fun
like like I I'm pretty pretty I think I
underestimate a lot of you guys yeah oh
my God that is crazy I need to play I
was scared of you MAA I was so scared of
you I I told you I'm not really good at
this game you didn't believe me just
because I play this game doesn't mean
that I'm good at it
you good you are good it's just that you
were trying to save me and I'm
sorry I think everyone need a practice
them after
all
no but yeah thank you so much everyone
for playing this game with me uh it's
been F thank you for
organizing yeah than you I'm glad it
happened finally it was was super fun
thank you thank you it's been we almost
doing this like for like 2 hours
actually yeah I know it flew by that was
a long just like I expected the game is
going to be two
hours perfect perfect
timing yeah well um for this one
actually I have a lot of uh strategy
game
um uh Age of Empire is like one of the
while the others there is another game
called
Starcraft interested on Starcraft it's
another building game another starting
game if you guys interested I would love
to make another one try it yeah I'd love
to but I need to learn about the game
yeah I need to learn too yeah
yeah more more learning more go
go my brain is going to
explode
oh what it is what it is thank you so
much um I think we need to end guys have
any uh maybe information for the
viewers I don't know I'm good no no I
just want to say thank you thank you way
for being a great
teammate thank you Kwa for bringing out
the aggressor in me let's go
for being a really good like we we
actually working good together yeah next
time I won't build the
Wonder I should not have
underestimated you need to build a
wonder you just have to figure out when
you're building the Wonder is your
military already finished also we you
building it like at least when I arrived
you only had one person working on the
Wonder but the Wonder takes like so much
more time than other buildings you need
like people at once yeah need you need a
lot of people and make sure that your
military is ready to you
know
take the Wonder I wanted to build one
too someday someday someday
[Music]
someday that's all everyone thank you so
much I'm going to end sh then you
[Applause]
let's play
again thank you awesome bye
[Music]
lat