the team member record room oh this is
easy this is okay this is nothing let me
try the computer and yeah I don't know
why I thought I'd be on uh oh hang
on what is this man they really need to
improve their security around here here
we go kfp un
03 why this file warm that's strange
something's not right about these IDs
there's a class h and a Class C and I
don't think anyone's here at this time
of the night I I need to take a look
I've heard some rumors about how they
fire people around here these Department
listings food preparation versus
preparation of food that's a weird
distinction to make why would they feel
the need to do that it's like the more I
read the less things make
sense maybe maybe this other file expl
more this feels so familiar but remember
don't learn their names oh no there
wasn't supposed to be anyone here I'm
not getting sent to the usual room over
this done with me wait something's not
right how do I know the usual room I
still have some time before they get
here I don't know what's going on this
this doesn't feel right there there's
got to be something in these records
that can explain what's going on they're
close I got to get going but
protoc clearly why is it so hot no I
don't have time to think about it you
know exactly what I'm talking about I'm
uploading these files to you now I think
there's something there we got to get to
the bottom of this um we close I got to
leave