foreign
hiya Darlings this is Hello Life English
advents devilish Diva the one and only
narissa ravencroft here today with the
number one Phoenix Phoenix Beethoven
takanashikiana are there any others I
don't think so
yay hello I am your Senpai and I will
treat you well whether you like it or
not thank you
this is my first one-on-one collab and
I'm very happy to spend it with kiwawa
Senpai uh we we had talked about it and
she's like you have to you have to let
me since I'm your since I'm your OC you
have to
and I was like of course I'd rather I
wouldn't I wouldn't want it any other
way so
I thought so
but I was trying to think of what would
be a good idea for a first stream and I
realized a lot of people seem to think
our connection kiwawa is a bit too good
to be true have you noticed um
so I thought it would be nice to start
out with a combative compatibility not
compatibility did I miss your
pronunciation up because I said it wrong
[Music]
compatibility yes compatibility quiz
we're going to be
yes so basically I'm gonna have to do
math at some point which might be a
mistake
um just let chat do it yeah yeah yeah so
I'm I'm gonna be keeping a tally of
everything so we should uh oops uh we
should be able to combat time
round one point
I mean
wow it would be funny that way we'll
have to do that in like super smash or
something when the smash all right
I'm really bad at it but yeah do you
okay wait no I I can't ask you about too
many other things we have so many
questions yeah
so why don't we some of these things we
have already talked about but some of
these things are also things that we
haven't talked about
um
so let's let's get started shall we all
right oh let's go bring it on so first
one Lord of the Rings how do you feel
kiawa I mean can you guess like I've I
went so far to spend like over a
thousand bucks to fly to London to watch
the first day of the Lord of the Rings
musical in London uh so I kind of like
it yeah yeah what about you uh I love
the Lord of the Rings I have to be
honest so I'm gonna I'm gonna give you
the run-on I've never run I've never
read the books
oh my God
thank you for not reading the books but
I like
oh I I want to read them because I think
they're gonna be fantastic and I need to
know who the hell Tom Bombadil or
whatever his name is
he showed up in the musical too and
everybody was like oh that's cool that
he's there and I'm like when who is he
but but that's that's maybe also the
reason why we both tolerate and kind of
appreciate rings of power because we
didn't read the books yeah
um but I I only recently a few years ago
actually got it was able to watch Lord
of the Rings and I was smitten so I
always had a crush on like a list
um because he's just so cute but say
when like Liz the yeah but but then you
know upon watching it oh I can
never remember his name the really hot
guy the really hot guy our gun yeah or I
always want to call him Aragorn
yeah he's totally my time
for the moment I was I was thinking that
we might even match on favorite
characters Galadriel is my favorite
character oh she scares the out of
me man at least in Lord of the Rings in
rings of power I quite like her yeah
she's so scary a lot of the Rings yeah
well wait who are your favorite Lord of
the Rings characters I would say samboy
yeah so someone is a good guy he's a
good boy because like he's the real hero
of the show you know he is because if if
it wasn't for Sam if further was walking
up that path alone then Gollum would
have corrupted and killed him probably
yeah how would he have gotten away from
the spider you know mm-hmm and I just
you know my favorite scene in all of the
Lord of the Rings movies is the scene
where Frodo tries to separate himself
from the group gets on that boat that
little boat and leaves and then Sam even
though he can't swim he jumps into the
water and he's like Mr phone
although in German
[Music]
it turns on the Water Works yeah I love
one of the things I loved when I was
watching Lord of the Rings most was was
that connection that uh Sam and Frodo
have because like I love I love shows
that like have a big emphasis on like
friendship and like bonds and connection
and like boys love exactly not quite
this guy's love between two guys wait
all those musicals do you like the
scrubs musical the one episode I have
scraps I do know scrubs I haven't seen
scrubs the musical episode I think I've
seen one song from it but show it to me
the musical episode is so fun anyway
sorry back to Lord of the Rings so I was
so happy when you told me because like
you know I I've watched rings of power
mostly on my own just the last episode I
think I watched uh with my fans together
and you know I stand that you know it's
not perfect and all that but I I still
kind of liked it a lot I appreciate
anything that comes out of the Lord of
the Rings Universe should we move on to
the next question before we get into
this oh is it is it rings of power it is
rings
[Laughter]
so yeah yeah our I don't know it's fine
to me same so here's here's my issue I
understand why people dislike it and I
can't I can't say I have no gripe why
did they dislike it again I forgot why
they disliked it well here's here's the
one thing I disliked about it okay when
when I watched the movies with Galadriel
I expected her and not that I didn't
think that she was a super powerful
fighter right I imagine her to be more
Magic based I guess yeah my mom my mom
uh kind of got really angry about how I
guess they made her not powerful enough
because at that time she could already
apparently use like mind control and
that kind of stuff yeah yeah yeah
um it felt like they didn't know her
like magic ability to make her like a
really strong guy and I again I didn't
mind that but like it it felt like
it to me it didn't feel the same as
movie Galadriel but she's hot so I guess
one big like reason also that I happily
agree was the cast the choice of cast
like I did feel like some people just
didn't look like um they would be in
this world like medieval fantasy kind of
world they didn't quite fit into my idea
of it
um
that makes it look like they know what a
cell phone is yeah
[Laughter]
explain that but some of them just look
very modern like they could be in modern
shows but their face just looks so
modern yeah not their fault not their
fault at all but um
thank you you get it you just get it you
just get it but no I I liked
rings of power because I agree like for
me after after I finish the Lord of the
Rings I was like I need more of this
like yeah right and I was just I was so
then I I watched the The Hobbit I really
like The Hobbit too
um I know some people thought it dragged
on but I didn't mind because I was just
so happy to be watching more of Lord of
the Rings did you think it was dragging
on when the drag on was
yeah I can't even finish that because
to say that part
I thought it was fine I I I still can't
get over the Benedict Cumberbatch uh the
recording of him in the book happens
what
wait no did I see that I probably got it
I promise not it's just so he was a
mocap for doing playing the dragon right
he just is making the most amazing
facial expressions and like moving
around like an animal and it's I'm I I
don't know how much of it they were
actually able to use because obviously
he is not a drink oh I gotta watch that
yeah
reminds me there was some something I
discovered
um a while ago that I wanted to like
binge watch with my viewers it was like
you know I also always look for new
things that are related to a lot of
drugs I may not read the books but I
watched a lot of Lord of the Rings like
lore explore explanation videos you know
from the famous Channel yeah but I found
um a channel that
um shows behind the scenes
uh like from the actual like who was it
from the actual team
um
um at the at the Lord of the Rings set
and it's so cute because you see the
actors too and all this yeah so you know
the more the merrier isn't it right
exactly yeah well wait now now I have to
ask you about sunflower in the future
what if we went to hobbiton together
because I would love to go it exists you
can go yeah yeah that was one of the
things I learned in those behind the
scenes videos that like originally
um you know they they didn't like they
were just like four looks but they have
at least one that you can actually go
inside and check out inside yeah the
little okay I think I think the door
just opens for for the main house but
all the rest of them they still have
like a lot of like details yeah yeah I
watch someone walk through but I'm like
I need to go there but it's in New
Zealand right yeah I I want to go but
it's just from Austria it's really
far and hard to reach yeah I
think it's but it's worth it I guess
it's beautiful we should go yeah until
next year okay sounds good
okay we should we should move on too
much Lord of the Rings about Lord of the
Rings all day yeah but I just want to
say uh
the haters
no for real it's fine if you don't like
if you don't like rings of power it
doesn't have to be your cup of tea but
like yeah don't be mad at other people
for liking it you know we're allowed to
like things that might be shitty
potentially
controversial oh my God okay okay we
will force you to watch the second
season with us yes guys exactly
okay and next one Idol Masters so I'm
one of my questions I'm a big big Idol
Master fan I love I love it what about
you
yes so I think you you you generally
like a lot of these like Idol Animes in
general right yes for me I I guess I
like like macros for example if you can
call it someone of an idol to me yeah
Master is my favorite uh like anime and
game and music source and all that and
we discovered that we have the same Idol
Master Oshi
not even in one series but two yeah can
you believe it yeah
is the goat she's the best and then yeah
you want to say the next one no you go
Shiki Ichi no say from Del Este is
so cute
yeah the first one is the white hair
girl that's right yeah she has the white
wavy long hair and chicken is the one
that kind of looks like Iris
that's one of the reasons I was so drawn
to Iris when I first saw her because I
was like she
she looks so cheeky
[Laughter]
the visuals are gonna steal you from me
no it's okay
um I've I've loved you for longer than
you're allowed to know
[Laughter]
yeah but yeah we were like sending each
other you know all kinds of like
songs and stuff Also regarding to Toho
there was this one evening where we were
nerding out about alamaster and tohu
songs yeah
um we're winning yeah it's it's because
the fact that
girls in Idol master and the two that we
both say we like the most are the same
guys it's crazy because like let me say
with the original idol master I feel
like it's understandable to meet people
with the same Oshi because there's only
like what 11 12 girls you know like it's
a pretty small pool but Dennis day I
need you guys to understand there's like
almost I think there's almost 200 Idols
in dentist so like there's a lot and
they're all really really good like so
like there's like riamu is really good
to bring Shibuya is fantastic there's so
many so many amazing girls but the fact
that of that many we we like the exact
same one the best
yeah I think it's like uh it may not be
the same with YouTubers but with like uh
this kind of like with Idols in general
real life Idols too I think I'm drawn to
the more mature ones and I'm I really
appreciate shared an idol with a great
singing voice me too so that's I think
what drew me to those two girls good
exactly yeah I think the feather flock
together exactly
okay
I don't Master we get a point for that
though
this is a Chiara question yes
it's more like not not so much a do you
slurping rules more like can you like
slurp your ramen noodles
can you do you I I've tried and I've
tried to learn but
um I I usually tend to slurp up a little
bit that but I have a tiny mouth so then
when my mouth is full because I know
some people just like swallow the
noodles whole
which is crazy to me yeah I've met
people who like apparently they'll like
slurp it and they'll just directly
swallow it and I I can't imagine what
the how can you not choke from that
right are you sure yeah it scares me but
so I talk about ramen noodles though
um I don't actually eat a lot of udon
but Ramen I try to slurp it but I
usually end up especially when the
noodles are like really really long like
cutting it with my teeth like halfway
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah my problem
for me is like I first of all I'm very
very sensitive to hot food so I need to
blow on it and if you just eat it the
normal way like
it's you can't really like you would
have to take the the whole pack of
noodles that you're gonna you know take
in with your with your chopsticks and
pull it all the way up to the top into
the sky then blow the whole Noodle from
the top to the bottom like how are you
gonna do that so I eat them very
specially in a specific way like I
usually when you get Ramen it's served
with a with a spoon right yeah sometimes
it's a bit of a weird spoon but I still
do it so I put the noodles like a chunk
of noodles on there I put like some some
spring onions and whatever else is there
on the spoon I put some soup on there
and then I just you know take in the
whole spoon because I can't slurp the
noodles and and it takes too much time
me trying and when I tried and it like
splatters all over so I just do it this
way okay yeah if we're talking about
actually eating Ramen in Japan I I do
think that's the best way have you seen
uh kage Osama Love is War
no okay there's a character named Tikka
and there there's this one episode where
she goes she goes to a Ramen Shop and
basically what she does in the spoon is
just makes every bite like a mini bit of
the ramen yeah
I saw that and when when I was in Japan
I did that too because it was uh in you
know where I live there's not really any
wrongs
what
what she does she's supposed to be
Japanese right in the anime yeah
oh my God I thought this is I thought
what I was doing was illegal no like I
think they're literally going on about
how she is eating it perfectly too like
because there's a guy and he was like
this youngster she's not gonna be able
to eat ramen in the masterful way and
then he's like she's adding garlic or
he's like huh she ordered her noodles
this certain this certain way doesn't
she know that like this is gonna like
and then like if she's doing everything
right though and he's like no she's
getting me she really is a master but I
don't think that's the right way to like
the most common way to eat it though I
don't think you never see someone eat it
I think it's the right way you eat it
like that too yeah when I was in Japan
that's how I did it because I was like
here here there's barely any toppings
and it's so expensive that I don't I
don't get Ramen where I am and usually
the ramen sucks too so like being able
to actually like because I mean it's a
that's a fun of like having all the
different Toppings is like having a
mouthful with everything yeah right
because if I just slurp it how am I get
how am I gonna get like all these
ingredients into my mouth as well the
talks about do you slap your noodles but
I can't believe that this is also your
preferred way of eating it yeah nobody
else does this yeah I again I don't I
don't get to have that kind of ramen
often usually I'm eating instant Ramen
in which there is no toppings to be
considered and which of them is another
story yeah then I try to slurp it but
yeah if we're talking actual like real
real bowls of ramen yeah that's I agree
that's the superior way to do it you
know because I do it like that like it
does take quite a lot of time to always
get everything on the spoon and I I take
more time to finish a Ramen Bowl than
other people
um so I'm kind of embarrassed to go to
normal ramen restaurants in Japan uh if
anything I just go to ichiran because
nobody can see yeah how I'm eating it
and how long I'm taking nobody can like
be bothered by it so if you also eat it
that way we could both be the stupid
gaijins oh my god let's do it
who take an hour to eat a Ramen at the
ramen restaurant we can go to all these
places without feeling shame because
we're together and and then it's not
shameful anymore exactly I have no shame
anyway so
happy
[Music]
I mean I need to leave I'm too happy
no you can't leave you can't leave we
have to talk about K-pop
I'm so happy
oh my God okay K-pop yes yes we like
K-pop but your K-pop likes are quite old
compared to well do you like BTS
no I like girl groups only Larissa I'm
so disappointed in you you don't like
super junior or or BTS no I don't care I
mean some of their songs like because
they get pretty viral so I hear them too
sometimes but not I only like girl
groups I like so many girl groups in
from K-pop because they're so pretty and
I love their songs I just prefer hearing
female voices too in general I think
no I and the ones that you mentioned
were pretty old Like Girls Generation
yeah well
do you like red elements yeah red
velvet's really good I feel like it's
hard because I usually uh and not the
kind to listen to like a whole
discography of something unless I really
really am discography discograph so I'll
listen to like I'll listen to like a few
songs or maybe like one or two so it
takes a lot to actually like pull me in
as a viewer uh I I'm very I'm very hard
to please I guess but I did introduce
new jeans to you the other day and you
like it I sent you so many songs I like
them I I keep I keep I finally figured
out what was happening in the video of
ETA and I was like oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah what do you mean why
did you not get it the first time I I
don't know I didn't I didn't understand
I was confused and now then I was like
wait a minute wait a minute
yeah
yeah I think my favorites are well twice
I love twice too yeah wait what's your
favorite twice
are there so many so many I love so many
you can't ask me that but you know from
the currently active groups I like twice
and the seraphim and new jeans and
I feel like there's some that I'm not
thinking of right now but those are my
my big
yeah favorites okay I love talking uh it
see but it's here somehow they just
recently released some new stuff but
they're not they haven't been that
active for a little bit but yeah I do
like Etsy and mamamoo but also mamamoo I
don't hear much from Mama mood these
days yeah yeah
yeah those are like kind of my favorites
and and izone when izone was active
before they disbanded I loved izone I
just won
um yeah so now you're into new jeans
yeah I will uh I will poison you with
the love
as well oh do you like Luna
ah
haven't really been that much attention
I only know one Luna song and it's one
of these the solo songs by one of them
because I heard it and it was Eclipse I
buy a Kim lipberton
oh this is not her name I'm so sorry
um but it's I I liked that one but like
I I just couldn't I couldn't really get
into them hardcore there's so many K-pop
fans yeah they're going off
nice nice nice
yeah so we may not agree with the groups
in general so much but we do both love
kpop yeah so I say this is a win that's
the point yeah that's the point we both
like K-pop because sometimes I've met
people who don't like K-pop at all
so I think and the thing is I might not
listen to as many groups in my free time
like current ones but when I hear it's
just because Kiara
and YouTubers I can't learn all these
Idols names I will get two into it you
don't have to learn their names
no you don't understand I fall in love
and I'm like I need to know everything
about that
is that you know they're really
accessible for foreigners because they
it's like the first K-pop group somehow
that has all of them speaking fluent
English and they all have New Zealand
and Aussie accents and sounds so funny
and they're like they're just like 14 15
16 and still they're like really great
singers they really raise dances they
make really original fresh music they're
so talented like oh my God this is like
holy macaroni the greatest group it's
gonna one day God forbid went twice
after their long long long long
successful journey is gonna maybe
um you know Fade Out fade away I think
new jeans
be the most popular Idol group out there
and they have so much time they're so so
young their average age is six okay I
should shut up I'm too too fan girls
okay we'll move on we'll move on before
we keep tangenting Sports
oh I I
like oh yeah
[Music]
well yeah that was something I brought
up yeah so I what do you mean
do you do any sports no so I never
really
I I like
I really like if I get the opportunity
to play a sport I like to be competitive
so I I actually I really wanted to play
baseball but I was told no
um and I really wanted to do wrestling
but I was told no who's telling you no
oh my parents why why because you can
hurt yourself they didn't want to
encourage my dreams I guess and then uh
what yeah I I couldn't so I was like I'm
gonna become a professional baseball
player a demon someday
no I I actually I mean you can tell I'm
pretty tall right um I I believe it or
not now I I stay inside and play games
all day as per my job but when I was
younger I actually would go on
adventures uh in the Underworld like all
the time uh I would I was always outside
I was always doing something I was I was
pretty fit child you know um a child
demon and then um yeah
them but I don't know what happened I
found anime and then suddenly suddenly I
didn't go outside ever again from
outdoorsy type to indoorsy time suddenly
yeah but I I do like sports if I get the
opportunity to play them so like if we
if me and you went to like the park and
there was a soccer field or like a
dodgeball or something I would have fun
doing that but I won't go out of my way
to play yeah I mean neither I mean I'm
currently the only Sports uh sport that
I'm doing I guess is you could say
swimming but I'm all I'm not doing it
because I want to do Sports because I'm
doing it because
yeah no no I'm not even doing it to lose
weight or anything or I just wanna I
have I have chronic like shoulder and
and back problems and I'm just trying to
help myself with that right now so it's
like a health thing that I'm trying to
improve
um and I do like dance every now and
then but I don't quite see it as a sport
either
um you know but you know I prefer to not
move my body at all well okay I just
want to be a sloth I'll tell you a
secret about me I have back problems too
so that is actually one of the reasons
yeah I I can't do I can't actually do a
lot of things because because of my
specific back problems
[Music]
okay so I feel like this is kind of an
agreement yeah
um yeah you may be more open to do
Sports than I am because it is a 0.5 how
about that because what a point but
we'll give it do you want a full point
or a half Point yes why are you trying
to manipulate our relationship
yeah I will I will never force you to
play a sport take it yeah let's take the
win okay I believe we're on we've got
six points I did enjoy sports in uh
Minecraft though a lot yeah I mean uh
who doesn't like I like parkour and
Minecraft I'm not good at it but popcorn
is always rough though parkour is always
the most difficult I feel like
um okay yeah yeah that's the point it's
a point next one
vote Game of Thrones and this is
included in a house of the Dragon the
the whole conglomerate uh wait have you
read the book heck no I don't read
also uh nothing against George RR Martin
but I simply if I do decide to read a
book series it has to be done I have to
read all of it
um because I you know I I have
occasionally read books and I like to
read the whole series of of it you know
so you know he is slow knowing that it's
not done I just like I'm interested
because of uh how Game of Thrones ended
I really want to read and see how the
books end but the books aren't over
yeah well so obviously we both like Game
of Thrones and whatever belongs to it
but the fact that shocked me even more
is that our Game of Thrones or she is
the theme and it's not it's even
kind of like a minor character because
she's not alive for too long
you don't even understand so I am so
obsessed with Marjorie Tyrell I would go
on like hand handmade uh website stuff
right and I looked for perfume based on
her character and I it was my signature
because I was like I want to smell like
Margarita even though I don't that's the
most ridiculous thing the most
ridiculous thing ever so I would buy I
would buy perfumes that were based
around her character theming so it would
be like roses because you know it was a
Tyrell sigil and then like uh
strawberries because she's so fresh and
there was uh did you ever buy any
perfumes that are inspired by me no I
don't think I've ever found Giada
inspired perfume but I also after they
discontinued that one it was
discontinued it was actually my
signature scent but then they they got
rid of it
um because you know custom custom made
in and they just kind of stopped doing
stuff which is fine but it hurt me it
hurt me so bad but I ended up um finding
a signature perfume so I actually only
wear one scent and I don't um there's a
Marjorie Tyrell signature profile no no
no my signature scent uh now is just a
regular perfume you can get up like that
it's like a French French perfume so
it's pretty and the other one you just
made up yourself like
mix things together that you thought
would fit no I bought I bought I bought
from someone who knew how to make
perfume oh okay okay yeah that's that is
so wow that's quite nerdy and still
girl-like like wow yeah I'm I'm kind of
but she's what made you like her though
she's hot
like all all of the girls are hot but I
really liking a character when someone
um she makes me think very vaguely of
Rouge the Bat from Sonic and I mean that
in the best way possible she's beautiful
she's feminine unapologetically she's
self-interested but she's not a bad
person so as to where like Cersei is
about I said that without bringing up
Sonic
as to her like Cersei is self-interested
but she also is too self-interested to
the point where I feel like she ruins
things for everyone you know um like
it's very much just about her her
interest and you you know I understand
why for her character and I still really
like Cersei as for a character for what
she is and her actress is phenomenal so
it's amazing but
I love characters who have that kindness
to them too and like that overall our
overarching kindness with their scheming
you know so I was like uh Marjorie
you're what I needed
I agree with all those points like you
know her personality being fascinating
and and her being hot and all that but I
actually I think I'm me liking her is
very much influenced by her being my
favorite yeah yeah yeah and I told you
that but and and then and then I told
you about how I first saw her in the
tutors and I fell in love with her and
watched a lot of things that she acts in
and then we got to the topic of you
liking the tutors and that there's a
to this musical that I even
walked past and when I was in London and
didn't realize it was a freaking cutest
musical because it looks so modern and
like Kiss inspired by The Outfits I'm
here but you are the reason why I now
need to go back to London well it's okay
we can just go together it's fine
I really stay away from the wobbly water
though wobbly water there's wobbly water
in London stay away from it okay anyway
yeah we agree on the same character but
we have I I'm very influenced by other
things I think that's okay though
because at the end of the day oh
foreign because
um like who who else apart from Marjorie
do you also uh Kenny in in Game of
Thrones
[Music]
I think I just have to say Daenerys
so when when what happened at the end
happened I was like I'll support you my
queen wherever you go but Jesus you make
it hard
wait a second in
okay I don't remember names right now
but who is your favorite in uh house of
the Dragon
oh that's hard I don't remember their
names either
um not not uh not the mother not the one
that keeps on making babies no with her
no relatives me neither I I I I I really
liked the strength of the young the
young actress for for the uh the the
girl the the turkey that marries the
King
which one I'm talking about uh not so
Alice Alice is a is the the brown haired
one uh we're talking about
um I'm talking about what's her name
yeah Queen Allison Allison not
Alice yeah Allison so I'm talking about
raniera renera so yeah I I really like
raniera because she's she's the main one
she's just I like her confidence I do
agree that she is also self-interested
and in a bad way but I also think
Allison I feel the most bad for her
um I'm interested to see how next season
goes but I can't support her when
especially after the time skip because
um Allison is just so like the way she
twists everything to be about her and
her son she
said she just has her epic you know
understanding you say no no no no it's
just you know because runera is uh kind
of
especially as an adult kind of selfish
oh yeah who keeps on going back to
incest and
you know
um elephant has her standards and her
ethics that she will follow and I
respect that and I I understand
why she's becoming very desperate I
totally understand it I I have a
solution actually to what I think would
make the show better if Damon left and
if instead Alison and renera would sort
their differences and then they would
Rule the Kingdom together I think that
would actually wonderful be the optimal
ending because I love their friendship
as kids and it made me yeah so sad to
see it disintegrate and like become like
this like especially like right before
the king you know X died uh I was so sad
because it seemed like things were
finally going to be you know
um sorted and like the differences and
maybe they could have you know started
to become friends again and maybe renira
would have stopped being such a such a
yeah I liked it also when they
were besties so I I hate seeing girls
fight I'm like please Queens you're both
bad you don't need to fight
hahaha
yeah yeah I I just but you know elephant
kind of in in how she's playing things
and how she's using her position and all
that don't doesn't it remind you a
little bit of Marjorie Tyrell to me
personally it makes me think more of
she's a nicer Cersei
it could be yeah and granted I feel like
they both kind of are like Cersei
because they're both ranera wants a
throne and she wants her uncle guy weird
weird
um but like she like for example when
when the thing happened with the kids
right uh and one of Allison's kids stole
the dragon right after yeah one of the
deaths and then
um they tried to fight back and he got
his what happened to him is I got taken
out I am I'm sorry that kid was in the
wrong that Dragon was not his to take
yeah sure they bonded or whatever and it
claimed him or whatever but like it
wasn't his to take he just went for the
opportunity right when I don't think
that the kid who was trying to defend a
dragon that he wasn't trying to take
either should have then also gotten
punished but Allison right away was like
okay uh an eye for an eye let me take it
and Rainer was like no what the
like
well I'm biased right now so oh do you
think do you think that it should have
been an eye for an eye do you think
uh I think you know we're in there and
it just has to be kind of like brought
back to the ground of reality and off of
her high horse High Dragon you know so
yeah it's not a disagreement
it's an extended discussion but we love
Game of Thrones and we love we have the
same ocean Game of Thrones okay that
comes for a lot yeah well I'm looking
forward to seeing then how because I I
haven't read the book so I don't know
what happens going forward so then I'm
curious because obviously things changed
like I knew from the beginning that I
liked Daenerys when I met her and then I
knew from the beginning and I feel like
that also gives me bias towards Venera
because she's also a Targaryen and so
I'm like let's go Queen a fight you know
um because I'm like oh my God it's like
Daenerys 2.0 but like they they do have
a lot of differences
um but uh so I think
I think I'm curious again to see how
it's going to change especially with
like a lot of the things that are going
to be coming I need it now I need it now
it's it's still taking ages I think when
the season ended it said that it will
take like two years until the next
season and I don't I don't remember
anymore when it ended but I was like
what the two years they hate us is
what it is but maybe uh is it gonna be
in 2024
are we gonna be lucky maybe end of 2024
that would be great but maybe not
oh but some people do say 24. oh yeah
let's go let's go I want it now okay
Mom this is an agreement though yeah and
I think we agree on Game of Thrones we
weren't technically House of the Dragon
isn't listed here
[Music]
in the very beginning Game of Thrones
end and how's it you said that but let's
say let's act as if we didn't say well
we still both like House of the dragon
and I still like Alex I like it yes I I
don't I don't dislike her I don't I
don't dislike if anything you know
Kristin Cole the the guy
um I I shipped him in renera when he
left I felt my heart shatter a little
bit and went to uh Alice inside I was
like no my king yeah it was so hot
please yeah
but yeah so we still agree that we both
like it technically this question was
not regarding oh she's like we like the
show so I say it's a full point if if it
was about games yeah exactly exactly the
game of birds
okay raw food now this is your question
I'm gonna answer first because I don't
know what what exactly you mean I I
presume if you're just asking do you
mean like if we're talking raw
vegetables sometimes if we're talking
like sushi I Love Sushi if we're talking
like tartar I can do a good like salmon
or like beef tartare occasionally
but but I don't go out of my way to eat
like raw meat um but I do go out of my
way to eat sushi and I don't mind
vegetables cooked or raw so no please
elaborate it wasn't really on vegetables
but I do know that there's some people
out there who just don't like a lot of
raw vegetables which I don't understand
they're yummy they're fresh right I love
a good cherry tomato same yeah
um but it was more about yeah a raw fish
and raw um beef for example uh obviously
no raw chicken or anything like that
um but I agree with you on the like beef
beef tata for example like I can eat it
but I would never really like order it
like if it's there because somebody else
orders it also then okay I'll eat a
little bit because it's actually I think
it's mostly like a brain thing like in
my mind I feel like I'm not supposed to
like eat something like this and I
should Grill this but uh when I put it
on a little baguette yeah it's quite
good yeah
but I I remember this in Japan too we
went to Big Yakiniku with some Japanese
and en members and me and Ahmed were
sitting next to each other and the
Japanese members they ordered I think
yuke and it has raw uh beef uh and and
me and Emma were both like but I already
knew this dish and so I just I just
stayed away from it but I'm like took a
little bit and just grilled it even
though you're not supposed
yeah
um but so I could do my best with that
the thing is with raw fish I I
I think I've I'm I'm just
I have I haven't tried a lot of it I
will admit
but yeah I have this big like I don't
know block
in my head that I don't want to eat it
no so do you eat any sushi for example
no so I mean if it's a non non-fish
Sushi
or if it's I think I could still do like
a like a tuna sushi or something like
maybe so no so here's here's my thing
with sushi too when I eat sushi I'll eat
anything I've got a black hole for uh
you know a stomach so I'll just kind of
eat and I'm always willing to try
anything right I actually don't like
fish in general so usually Sushi is the
only time I eat fish and recently I like
eel and eel Sushi is always cooked they
never give you just raw oil and I like
it yeah and the eel sauce makes it Sushi
is always cooked oh then I should eat
that yeah but then uh then uh I've tried
a lot of other ones like I don't really
like this is maybe an opinion people
will be mad about I don't like salmon
sushi I don't like salmon I'll eat
salmon but I don't like salmon
um oh yeah cooked or raw and it just has
a flavor to me that like it's just weird
but cooked too yeah no cooked I I don't
like it wow I well I feel like um I I
got to a point where do you use an air
fryer
I I clearly own an air fryer but I
clearly don't use it much
I I love my air fryer and I used to have
a different one and I I it was perfect
at cooking salmon perfectly I was able
to perfectly cook salmon but we got a
new one it sucks okay it it's never
consistent but you're telling me that
you liked it when it was perfectly
cooked by your airfryer yeah but now and
it's just a matter of how you cook it
then yeah exactly because I just feel
like I feel like I'm eating cat food
when I'm eating salmon because of the
way that it Flakes and like the sound it
makes when you're chewing it and like it
gets to me I I can see that it's it it's
used for cat food too after all yeah so
I'm not I don't really like them but I
like tuna a lot and tuna sushi is my
favorite
so I I especially uh sometimes when they
when it has like the spicy spicy mayo
but I can eat it without you
uh but but specifically do you know
Otoro
yeah that that is the kind of sushi I
like the best
it's a very very fatty part of the tuna
it's so expensive okay we'll find it in
America
oh I I want to challenge myself to eat
at least a couple to try a couple of
sushis like the more simple ones to me
that are not like like the crazy stuff
yeah too crazy stuff but the thing is I
also don't really like seaweed that much
yeah that's also a problem
understandable I I like seaweed
um but only with rice
I will admit we don't agree on this
topic yeah we agree on the beef one but
not only the important Sushi one fish so
I'll give us I'll give us a one point
gone this is a problem for me because a
lot of my friends also within Hollow
Love Sushi and when we go when we're
like in Japan like oh should we eat like
a lot of them often want to go eat
seafood or sushi and I'm like uh I
really don't like it well I here's the
thing ah I have a really good sushi
place near me and I've had sushi in
Japan and I've got to be honest I didn't
think it was that terribly different
it's apart from fish freshness so when I
when I go to Japan I'm actually more
interested in eating like the not Sushi
because I also I don't like seafood much
either with with a few again like uh
what's the word with a few exceptions
but so if we get to go to Japan together
I'll go wherever you want just take me
to a cute cafe or something all right
I do like a lot of other you know
Japanese food when I say other looks
like sushi to people in Europe a lot of
the time the reply I will get is hey but
then what do you eat in Japan I'm like
dude there's so much more than sushi in
Japan Japanese Kitchen come on yeah well
if it makes you feel any better I don't
like ketchup
so
why would you don't like fish I don't
like ketchup so and Everyone likes
ketchup so whenever is it what if it's
like mixed into rice like omudaisu no no
interesting I mean there's plenty of
food without ketchup oh but you know the
tonkatsu sauce there's like kind of
ketchup in there too it has
Worcestershire sauce in it so you can't
taste the ketchup too much okay okay I
have I have a story but it's too gross
so I'll tell it to you privately I don't
want to share it on stream about why I
don't
okay okay yeah okay that's fine then you
can I feel like you can get like stay
away from ketchup in Japan easily it's
just no Alma rice for me
sorry but but uh it's got a lot in
American food I guess like in hot dogs
and burgers they often put ketchup
inside right like I'll I'll still eat
ketchup I don't like it though I do you
know about this Japanese pasta
they make it with ketchup you don't like
it huh I've never had it but the idea of
just putting ketchup on noodles like I
used to just make butter noodles where
you literally just cook the noodles and
then put butter and like parmesan on
them and I think that's pretty great but
I I also come from a place where butter
is King you know so like I'll when I was
very young I literally took a stick of
butter and just took a bite out of it
because I didn't that's disgusting but
yeah okay I was I was very I was very
little I was like a newborn demon but
for the people in the chat who are
confused it's not just like plain
ketchup and noodles the that Neapolitan
Napoli it's called politan Japanese yeah
ketchup noodles it's not just ketchup
it's it tastes like more than just
ketchup yeah yeah it's pretty good to me
I want to try it because I've heard it's
good but I just need to not think about
that oh you haven't tried it before okay
I've just seen it yeah and I'm like
ketchup yeah or maybe give it a try if
you don't like it I'll finish it for you
okay it sounds like but that'll be our
that'll be our one disagree so far for
now I am
Naruto I don't understand why you put
Naruto in here girl don't you want us to
agree on things what do you think about
Naruto
I don't give a
you just ruined my life
Naruto is one of my favorite anime
you don't give a like you don't
like it or like you've just never seen
it like I I don't like this kind of
anime
I need you to explain to me I need you
to break it down for me
genre and the topic and the endlessness
of it like yeah and the characters I
don't like the characters much either
wait not either broccoli
what
there's some cool songs though oh in one
of my karaoke's I sang that song before
what was it like Naruto
he's really cute
yeah that one yeah that's hilarious
I don't know you know when I was younger
um on on German Austrian TV there's this
one TV channel that sometimes played
some really mainstream anime so only
like Naruto and Sailor Moon and stuff
like that uh and it just never spoke to
me at all well we'll we'll give a minus
point because clearly we disagree but I
feel like yeah I guess I don't like
Shonen I I have to defend my honor too
real quick I actually don't really like
Shonen but for Naruto I make an
exception so I agree with you Naruto is
too freaking long I will not watch
boruto and I actually haven't watched
most of Shippuden because I looked at it
and I was like 500 episodes what the
because then you have the original
Naruto which is the first before the
time skip that is my when I say I like
Naruto that is what I'm talking about so
it's just like Dragon Ball uh I used to
watch Dragon Ball Z uh but I don't
really I don't follow it anymore Dragon
Ball's not for me Naruto Naruto the
reason it's special to me is again I'm
talking solely about the first I think
it's technically the first one like 150
episodes
um but technically it's 200 episodes but
after a point after Sasuke leaves the
village they just were like we need to
pad so they started doing filler and
that's where they realized oh we can
just do filler and people will watch it
um but I uh I I skipped the filler um so
I just watched like again I think it's
like 150-ish episodes which is still a
lot don't get me wrong but yeah
um Naruto is an amazing story
I I don't like it
SO waiting out hear me out you yeah
you gotta get to the point where first
you get to uh there's a village with I
forget all their names but there's this
guy uh Haku and this is this is what
kind of got me in his Naruto I was like
oh yeah he's this little kind of
kid and then he's got that stupid
dark character Sasuke and then
there's a little annoying girl Sakura
who I loved to death for some reason
um but you know they start out as
kids oh Zabuza yeah Zabuza but
then uh they eventually get to go on one
of their uh first kind of like big
missions right and they end up going to
this village where like things are
really up and they're they're
supposed to take down uh zabuzan Haku
and Zabuza is kind of like this scary
guy Haku looks like a girl is a very
effeminate uh looking guy and um is not
a bad guy despite being the bad guy and
it's the first kind of one that like
makes the characters like question
themselves a bit a bit I guess I don't
know how to describe it so it kind of
it's and it's very emotional like it
wasn't what I was expecting when I was
going into it even like really like when
I was younger because I was like oh this
is probably gonna be like uh just
whatever you know just like boys
fighting you know like uh or whatever
but then or like Dragon Ball Z because I
I watched it but I wasn't a fan but like
Naruto for me got really emotional and
deeper and then like same with like
there were Stakes people would
die
um uh my other favorite Arc is when my
favorite character my my boy Rock Lee is
introduced
Rock Lee is I need you to look up a
picture
wait I need you I need you to look up a
picture of broccoli I'm gonna tell you
why I love him no Rock like a like Bijou
a rock Rock Lee yeah Rock Lee
ah I need you to look at him broccoli I
got him I've seen him okay yeah he he he
is the best character in the whole
series and not only is he cute as hell
because of his big eyebrows and his
little eyes he is so cute but okay I
guess you might look at him and be like
what the hell's wrong with him he he
he is the best because he has no magical
ninja ability
so he only does taijutsu so it's all
physical movement right so the first
time you meet him he confesses his love
to Sakura and it's kind of it's kind of
like the first time I met you and he was
like I'll protect you with my life and
she's like yeah what's wrong with you
get away from me
um but then they they get through how it
was between us yeah you were nicer to me
but I was I was a little I was a little
creepy no but um they end up going to
the tuning exams which is where they met
and they get thrown into this really uh
hard course where they have to collect
these Scrolls and like people will kill
you like you will die here potentially
so it's like really difficult and um
Sakura Sasuke and Naruto uh Sasuke is
like knocked out and I think Naruto is
too so it's just Sakura and she's
low-key kind of weak okay she's alone
and there's a big bad is here uh he's
snuck in because he wants Sasuke okay so
stay with me stay with me
broccoli broccoli comes in and tries to
save her okay
and it's it's he barely knows her but
he's like no I said I'll protect you so
I will and he doesn't expect anything he
never comes back and he's like you have
to you know like
but then then leave your endlessly fancy
even though I am not very receptive but
you just keep going
I love the passion and the determination
really I love it I'm gonna I'm gonna
force you to watch just just one Arc
with me okay
I think I have like like one or two
exceptions
um of like anime that are Shonen that I
actually do like so it uh I can't
remember right now but I I think there
are because even like my fans were like
what you like this one I thought you
didn't like Shonen uh but I did like
some and so I feel like if if Naruto was
maybe in like a really like
compact shorter anime it was like one
two three seasons yeah then maybe I
could get into it well but yeah let me
to let me look at you and see how long
because I'm pretty sure tuning exam art
comes in pretty quick and like I think I
think I need to look it up but um
the I love that is that Shonen huh
the sins the The Deadly Sins one is also
Shonen I think I like that one
so you know I do like a lot so a couple
of children
look you gotta trust me trust me on this
because I I don't like showing it I you
just got it you just gotta give it a
chance just for we can watch the German
version I don't know actually it turns
out I like a couple of Shonen yeah
um
but we'll move on because I could talk
about yeah all day but I don't want to
hear anymore
okay this one cat's the musical
I need I need you to tell me why you
like cats has has kfp told you to put
this in here no but I saw people saying
about it and I have never heard you talk
about cats so I need
I need to know so
um I did a watch along with my members
for this no wait no we did a public one
wasn't in the public one with Ina and
I I like everybody was like so overly
dramatic about how it was so so so bad
and oh my God this is unbearable this is
the worst thing I've ever watched and I
wouldn't say it's like the best thing
I've ever watched at all but I wouldn't
also exaggerate and be like holy
this is the worst thing ever like it was
fine it had some fun songs too are you
talking about the movie
yes so have you ever seen the musical no
okay so I can tell you why people don't
like cats the movie versus Cats the
musical
do you want to know
I am I I I I heard that the musical is
better and all that but I'm not even
sure if all these haters for the movie
really wants the musical though I can
tell you the real hatred for it
um
for me the reason I don't like Cats the
musical and won't watch it is because
it's made by the same people who made
the live action version of Les Mis
and no I don't know that okay that's
okay the way that they did the recording
do you know how they recorded everything
oh you know how when you go to a musical
there's a band in in mocha not green no
green screen I mean I mean the vocals
the vocals do you know you know how it
usually goes for like uh movies right
they'll go in and for singing vocals
they'll pre-record the song and then act
to it right so it's it's like perfectly
in tune they didn't do that for this
movie they actually did it backwards so
they'd have a few different tracks that
they could switch switch through and
they'd basically just let the performers
go in and do whatever and change the the
tempo and stuff so that the singing was
Live recorded which you might think oh
that's really cool but the issue is what
they did is then they would make the
orchestra come back in
and then have to record
with and match the singer's vocals
instead of having the singers work with
the orchestra so for example I'll use
Les Mis as an example there's um there's
a part in the music and I don't know Les
Mis much either but where the musical
stings where it's supposed to be like
dude
like the beat is supposed to be with
each tear of paper and it's very
specific the music is written that way
for the emphasis I know I put it on
order but for the emphasis it's supposed
to be there right
um but instead uh Hugh Jackman just kind
of tore it up however he wanted to
um and the music was literally not able
to follow it because he didn't tear it
to any beat so there was no way or in in
cats too and Cats the musical you can
see Parts where like or like here Parts
where if you have a really Keen ear for
music you notice that the orchestra
sounds weird and it's because they're
not they're not following an actual
Tempo the only ones that sound really
good oddly enough are the ones that were
recorded by dancers because to dance and
cats is all about dancing it's um you
need a really consistent beat right so
like you know that too because you dance
like the BPM can change here and there
but like otherwise like you needed to be
pretty pretty like pretty much the same
or else it's gonna throw things off
right if the BPM is just kind of jumping
around it makes it makes music really
really really hard to record if the BPM
changes
um from a musical standpoint and it
makes it harder to dance to it makes it
harder to play instruments too but they
just let the singers go in and change
the BPM the beats per minute uh the
tempo like really weird and I feel like
that is not at all what most people
disliked about well people will just
like yeah they'll go off and they'll be
like I thought it was cringe uh cats
okay if we're talking genuinely is cats
cringe no because it's a musical
musicals are I thought it was a bit
cringe but a new life can't be cringe
musical it's musicals they're literally
like musicals but like the the way they
look oh I mean yeah the that's the real
issue of it is that um
the CG the CG wasn't very good which so
I can understand why people hate it from
that perspective the CG is bad CG which
is broken by the way
I see your heart still chat I see them
the heart they'll fix themselves it'll
yeah it'll come around and we'll come
back
yeah but I think you you broke him with
your oh they're back you broken with all
the like informative talk about music
you you you're you're quite the music
nerd aren't you yeah I I I I I can't I
can't do a lot because my parents didn't
let me play the piano growing up so I
can't read music very well or play an
instrument but I'm really passionate
about music and uh there's definitely
certain things but so for me pants if
we're talking about the original cats
everything I've seen it seems pretty
delightful I mean it's a typical Andrew
Lloyd Webber you know musical right like
I mean it's it's not quite Phantom of
the Opera but it's pretty you look lost
I'm so sorry are you okay no but what
about the movie though I haven't you
don't you don't like the movie but I I
will not watch anything with James
Gordon in it
um I I don't know if I should say it on
stream but I do I don't like him I don't
appreciate him I I saw one he ruined my
favorite musical movie
he was in Into the Woods and it's my
favorite Sondheim show or it's one of my
favorite Sondheim shows it doesn't beat
out Sweeney Todd but it's one of my
favorite Sondheim shows and he was the
lead and I hated looking at his face I
he's just I was so angry every time he
opened his mouth I was so mad I was like
he's become a little bit of a
controversial Persian like person I
guess I I did like him like before like
I love his like car car cut out yeah
that was fun stuff I don't think he
should be in my movie musicals I think
okay I I can see that uh yeah so I won't
watch it and same with like there are
just so many people in that movie which
I'm like why are you here like
Taylor Swift though I liked that I was
like oh that made me kind of want to
watch it just for that because I was
like oh well I'll enjoy a little tea
Swifty sometimes but um she's very
talented so I was like well that's and
Jennifer Hudson too I was like that's a
good cast good casting yeah you know I
I'm not gonna I we keep on kfp it keeps
on joking with me about this they make
fun of me but it's not like I'm gonna
put this on my favorite uh movies list
you know I like it but I also don't
think it's like the like one of the
worst movies out there so that's that's
you know my opinion I'm just like you
know neutral about it I see
oh yeah I'm pretty neutral too just
because I haven't actually seen it like
I've seen numbers but I've never
actually seen the musical or the movie
and I've watched in-depth things about
it like talking wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait you haven't
watched a musical order movie nope I've
only how can we even agree about
anything here
because I I I you I knew you were
talking about the movie and I have
opinions on the movie because
I'm making you watched it then huh
you've been talking so much about this
stuff like as if you you know just
because you found out about how they
recorded stuff
I can't look at his face Tiana
no we are going to watch it
whatever you like you'll have to strap
me down to a chair and use one of those
things to pry my eyes open to get me to
watch him
[Music]
girl you can't you can't hate on it if
you never watched it I'm not hating on
it I'm hating on the way that the music
was recording
this is you you
it's like you like you you you listen to
like music tracks musical tracks and all
that without watching the musical well a
lot of musicals really aren't accessible
for a lot of people you know like
Hamilton is a special case where like
the musical is is on like
um
you know but um like a lot of musicals
you can't actually watch anything unless
you go out to see them so like I I've
like I've been out to see like the sound
of music or like uh The Nutcracker
ballet in like theater like at a real
theater
um like live and I really I really love
being able to do that but like
um you know sometimes there's just not a
lot of opportunities if the show is
never near you and if you well we have
to we have to go watch the tutors Muse
and not the Kudos but the like you know
whatever it's called the
say
the six yeah six six the musical it's
about The Six Wives of Henry they're
they're pointing out they're pointing
out but you hate Naruto without watching
it no but I I said it was on the on our
TV and sometimes I would like you know
zap through and see a little bit of it
and just immediately you know okay I
don't like this you're so funny okay
because I love musicals but yeah it was
if it was shorter I might even give it a
chance but endless filler animes no
thank you look I will I will I will I
will curate a Naruto episode list and we
were we're just going to watch up to the
tuning exams past that and then and then
if you still feel that way we seems like
we have a lot of work ahead of us
hey look we only have three disagrees
three disagrees and seven agrees and
we've got a lot to bring on the next one
girl Final Fantasy VII era 135 do you
have an opinion I do not understand why
you bring this up but the only Final
Fantasy game I've played is 14. this
this can be this can be just based on
looks this doesn't this doesn't have to
be based on you playing the game because
I knew it was difficult I knew the
moment I looked at aerith that she was
for me
who based on design I I can tell you
General things about them and you can
say who you think appeals to you better
do would you like that
I uh it's like it's plainly from the
Aesthetics point of view I
I do not like arif's hairstyle
I do not like it
um well and from like that
from there
from their like outfits I like both but
it's like two different spectrums and I
just can't I I
um it's difficult to make a choice it's
like depending on the mood I I do want
to you know play a lot of Final Fantasy
games from now on though like until now
you know it was just that when I when I
grew up it wasn't accessible because I
didn't have PlayStation and so on so I
was more of a Nintendo game me too
player yeah but now we just got perms
for a couple of Final Fantasy games to
finally play them so I want to get into
it and then maybe we can get back to
this topic what do you think about that
okay so what what should we should we
strike the question then Strike It
Strike it I can't make a superficial
opinion okay we'll we'll put it down
then we'll we will leave it we'll leave
it and which one are they what do you
mean and which one which game are they
in seven seven is the best one I think
we have perms for seven now well we're
gonna have to get into it so you're
gonna have to play all the Remake games
only one is out now but you can if we
have the perms for the original it is
still fun despite the fact that it is
aged
if you like if you like old games wait
wasn't there a remake yeah the Remake is
still coming out though they only
they're only on part one part two I
think is coming out end of this year
like beginning of next
yeah you have a final fantasy seven
I think do we have a Crisis Core
what's Crisis crisis 24 is
um
no because it's it's like a a spin off
about like a it's like a prequel
I don't see a crisis I don't I see it
this car isn't here hell yeah oh okay
yeah recently we got some beautiful
beautiful fresh prince
I'm gonna get into Final Fantasy let's
get into seven please for me for me I
beg of you I need someone to freak out
about it with I'm just gonna start with
the newest one first now and okay that's
fine I understand yeah
but after that go back go back and do so
okay uh do Crisis Core last
uh after after the Remake games it's
good but like it spoils a lot
okay we'll move on though move on yes
Peach Girl now I'm gonna give you this
is one of my favorite shows I'm gonna
give you the rundown because I know you
like things that are similar you just
have to tell me if you think that sounds
like or if you think that sounds
like an anime you might watch
this girl is a Shojo anime uh love
triangle it is about this girl named
Momo which you know why that's Peach
Girl so funny um yeah
she is a normal girl going to school she
is tan and her hair is bleached because
she's on the swim team okay
um so she gets bullied a lot for looking
you know kind of uh yaru you know and um
so people people make bad assumptions
about her but in reality she's really
actually like sweet nice girl but people
are always basing uh misconceptions
putting misconceptions on her she has
one friend at school her name Sai
kashiwagi she's your typical uh
beautiful uh very pale skin uh you know
like uh ideal like everything Momo feels
like she is not basically
um small cute small bone you know very
pretty apparently uh she though is
secretly an evil mastermind okay evil
mastermind she wants even though they're
friends she wants to see Momo uh suffer
basically so Momo is constantly bullied
by her one friend and she has a crush at
school who's like a childhood friend
whom she loves named toji okay and then
uh she knows psy psy takes everything
that she likes right and she's still
friends with her because she's so nice
but she's like I can't let's say I know
that I like told you or she'll try to
date him so I can't tell her but she
knows I like someone so she lies and
points out uh this really popular guy
Kyrie okay and um then the love triangle
starts so Kyrie notices Momo and he's
kind of a is the best way I can put
it and then uh it's everything is
misunderstandings and drama so it's
constantly like going between the two
guys and not knowing who's the right one
and it's like will they won't they kind
of thing but then Psy is also trying to
get in the way just because she wants to
see Momo fail you know that's the kind
of plot it it's really dramatic because
it's from the 90s I think it's really
really dramatic so everything is
overplayed to the max I am going to tell
you that when like
the problem is I kind of stopped
watching anime
a couple years ago
um I would only like probably go back
into it on my own well if a new Baka
monogatari anime season comes out
um but yeah so because of that just like
like generally I don't even watch anime
anymore so I um
and and and I feel like my even if I
watch anime now my standards and
expectations are very different from me
like 10 years ago maybe 10 years ago or
15. I would have liked this I don't know
if I would like it now because I am not
so much anymore until like love triangle
drama I think I like maybe more
um
fantasy and and maybe serious I don't
know I don't know honestly I don't I
don't know it's hard to tell
maybe past while I would have liked it a
lot but current Wawa I honestly can't
tell it's it's honestly I I have to
watch it once a summer because it is
just so it's one of those shows that
like is fun to watch because it is so
comically banned
ah it's bad it's bad in a good way
in what way because it's all you you uh
this is this is my opinion I actually
really don't like misunderstanding like
as a plot Point
um I think it's hell daddy you can't
watch Moka mornings
I mean like an anime right like when
when there's something that could easily
be like figured out if they just talked
but for some reason it becomes like 20
episodes of anime and I'm like what the
yeah that's unnecessary this girl
doesn't necessarily do it that bad like
because it's only 24 episodes so it's
pretty short
um
but so it's I I don't really like
misunderstanding anime I can't I can't
do it you know but this one is special
because it's written in the most
dramatic way possible that like you can
see these characters being that stupid
that like you can't help but be like God
like you you love to hate him it's one
of those shows it's not one where you
watch them you're like wow the masterful
animation the masterful storytelling and
World building you know um because yeah
I agree I actually don't watch a lot of
anime these days I tend to prefer old
shows but I don't really go out of my
way to like go and watch like a lot of
new stuff unless it's really I'm really
interested but yeah yeah so that's okay
I'll I'll take I'll take the minus point
hey it's not you can't even the thing is
I never watched it so like you honestly
you can't even count this either you
can't
kiwawa keeps striking my questions yeah
but this is too specific it's too
specific
okay well yeah well I'll cut it I'll cut
it but I got to tell you about it so at
least there's that
I I am happy that you got to tell the
whole world about your love for peach
girl thank you for giving me the maybe
you made some people in the chat put it
on there you need to watch list
okay you haven't seen this one either
but rather than talking just about the
musical Austria
I was happy when you told me that you
like it because it's Austria related
very much so and that just because you
tell you say it's your favorite music
it's my favorite musical out of all
my favorite my favorite historical
figure
favorite one
what do you think Empress Elizabeth
she's I mean great I guess I mean just a
little bit maybe overhyped in my country
but
I can't believe you'd say that
no she's fine and I mean you know I went
to her Museum here and yeah she had some
nice dresses and interesting history you
know depression Arc and this and that
um yeah no no she's an inspiring figure
I guess
um interesting stuff I'm just really
um flattered that you like her real so
much it's so specific
I I've convinced actually both mume and
Ali to watch this musical with me oh
yeah so yeah excuse me
hello why are you not calling me because
obviously we're going to I I'm literally
why are you watching it with them like
privately together uh privately I I sent
them a scene from it and Ollie was like
excuse me what is this I need I
need to know what's going on and I was
like kill me anytime
immediately the date and then moon May 2
was like wait I haven't been into
musicals for forever but I want to know
what's going on so bad and I'll stream
it for you you know
I'm trying to find good talking points
but no uh I feel like the the thing is
Kiara and me are gonna have to watch the
German version
oh and I'll live translate for you what
yeah well there's yeah yeah yeah you can
pay me I know a little German not well
but uh I I sang it before
I don't sound good
[Music]
oh yeah
um you are
you're such an interesting lady in
Arizona
you bring up the most Niche specific
things
[Laughter]
you get so passionate about it yeah this
counts as a point because we both like
Elizabeth
she's Austrian yeah I mean I have to I
have to like it you have to like it so
this is this was a free point because I
knew you would like Elizabeth and then
of course now we're going to watch the
Musical together I guess so
I wonder if they ever like still play it
live here I'm pretty sure they do I mean
if they're performing it's still in
Japan I'm pretty sure Austria the place
that actually wrote and created the
musical is still performing it too oh
I'll check it out I'll see if I find it
if it is tell me I'll I'll come over
oh I'll be on my way I mean you already
have so many reasons to come over yeah
yeah and I I already know what beat for
beat story-wise so I don't even need I
don't I I don't need the translation
it's fine
yeah
yeah yes point and now cats or dogs I
hate cats I have yeah
I I love dogs but let's see if we agree
on why so cats I think are cuter but
they're also less maintenance in terms
of like I don't have to take them for a
walk I don't have to like wash them as
often because they don't roll around in
mud
um you don't have to have to wash them
yeah yeah exactly
um like I mean you have to brush them
but that's different um so it's like you
have to brush dogs you have to wash them
you have to take them on walkies every
day like and then you have to feed them
and then sometimes they don't want to
eat their food and they just beg at the
table all day I've never had any cats
ever beg me for food ever Nina what I
don't like about dogs specifically I
think is how they
um
it's cute but when I look at it I guess
but they're so aggressive of their love
like they will jump on you and yeah Pew
and lick you and there's so much so much
slime I don't like dogs ever I I
actually uh I have I have a an expensive
handbag and I went to visit a friend and
she has two huskies and one jumped up on
me and I was uh it scratched with its
nails my
very expensive bag is uh my friend
didn't warn me that their dogs were
going to attack me
otherwise I would have brought a cheap
purse here
what did she say I think she likes dogs
more by the way oh yeah
sorry for amoko too
I like um some some dog species uh like
visually very much and I do want to get
a dog for myself someday um but I just I
I hate how they're so like
clicky
stop stop licking so much do you find
having a dog if I lived a more active
lifestyle you know
but I don't have time to go out all the
time like you know I'm busy I work and I
need to be on you know my computer 24 7.
so it's like there's not a lot of time
to be like let's go to the park for like
three hours today you know yeah but I
still do like dogs but cats and there's
so much maintenance like yeah I would
love to have like a Samoyed for example
the big fluffy white dogs
um but there's so much maintenance like
oh my God so much fur and they shed so
much and you have to wash them all the
time but when you wash the whole ordeal
to like wash and then dry and then brush
a sandwich it takes like four hours if
not more yeah thanks no thanks dogs
deserve love but it's just too much for
us to give so I'd say that's a that's a
very hard agree
yeah yeah
I'm gonna say that's good it's good yes
poor
[Laughter]
oh thank you please no no you don't like
horror movies or horror games I would
not go out of my way to play a horror
game unless it's like Halloween the day
where I can't escape it
um or when gura and AMA ask me to play
with them at least it was if it's not
such a bad one that's okay I guess like
phasmophobia levels that's fine but
especially horror movies like I will no
you can't you can't make me go watch a
horror movie no no I love horror I like
I like to be scared sometimes I knew
this was one we'd disagree on but I you
know we have to show that we have some
some things we don't agree on yeah I I
do horror games every Saturday
yeah and I will never watch them that's
okay I understand or is not for
everybody and that's okay
why you need why do you need to like
suffer why do you make yourself suffer I
don't see it as suffering so uh here's
the kind of horror I hate is uh
problematic maybe I actually don't like
Five Nights at Freddy's
um games games that are just to me jump
jump scares I really dislike I don't
think jump scares are like good horror I
think you like lore I like lore or like
and don't get me wrong like I'll play
some stuff with jump scares because
sometimes with a lot of games like
that's kind of like how they do it you
know but um you know like for example I
consider uh re or Resident Evil games to
be horror games right
um but they're not I think a lot of
people wouldn't consider them to be
Horror in like the same way as like
oh Five Nights at Freddy's right a
psychological horror yeah or like a
perfect blue have you seen perfect blue
no oh it's no way I have wait ah do you
like it wait no wait a second have I
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait you
brought it up before then too
perfect blue why wait no I've seen
paprika that looks very similar well
it's a psychological horror it doesn't
have any jump scares it's very
introspective we should watch it
together
no trust me trust me you won't be scared
in the same way you are at like
scary games it's not that kind of it's
horror but it's not that kind of scary
okay maybe then yeah we'll think about
it but I do I do
um like uh your idea of what you like of
her about her like the lore like like I
I would say like just horror games that
are just basically jump scares it's kind
of lazy um
and I like games with more effort in
like even with like you know not horror
games I prefer games that have lore in
general so
so we are both lore based people I think
yes even if it's sometimes in different
ways
but yeah we'll move on because you're so
sad talking about horror I can't stand
this special on your face
I Don't Wanna Hurt Myself
we won't we won't let you hurt yourself
we'll talk about pizza instead
I know
yeah so wait what are you what is
your favorite topping combination
ah
pineapple and there's I have two
favorites even
um tuna tono which a lot of every time I
say it my n a viewers are like what the
but it's very normal in Italy and in
Europe in general so I like tono pizza
with um like red onions
um and ideally I would add corn to
everything so also to this one but it's
fine without and then a pineapple on
days where I want something a little a
little bit more refreshing tasting than
I want pineapple with either ham or
bacon or whatever
and maybe even corn who knows corn on
Pizza is actually a really big thing in
Korea but I know a lot of people in the
states too are usually like that's so
weird why would you put corn on pizza
and it's like they don't understand corn
is so good we literally have corn in
everything that we eat like why would
you be like corn so we're topping up
corn is in everything there's literally
corn syrup
do you know of that corn Pizza stream
that I did yeah I do that that was
something that was a little
I I took a joke from what company was
that the corn cup the company that
advertised their corn Club Pizza yeah
but it wasn't even real
why would you troll me like that like
Little Caesars yeah and I was like okay
I'll make it a reality and I put like
shavings of you know the corn cob all
over the the sides the crust of the
pizza and all over the middle of course
as well it was marvelous it was great it
was genius I want I wanted I wanted to
try
I see you had an oopsie there sorry
cute wallpaper you got there yeah yeah
so pineapple is great you also like corn
that's even greater yeah have you tried
Tuna on Pizza though no that's not a
thing here but I look I'm down to try
anything would you would you'll come to
understand about me is I I have Foods I
dislike but I will always try anything
so especially it because American Pizza
is very different from like actual Pizza
in like Europe and stuff I've never
gotten to have like true European pizza
but I've we have some places that are
sort of similar and make it that in that
style and it's really it's really really
different so I think probably even in
Europe though when you go to a random
place to have pizza if it's not Italy
you can still get like pretty mid Pizza
yeah uh there's places that make meat
pizza and then there's places that make
authentic pizza yeah well if you take me
to an authentic place
um I'll try anything because the only
thing I probably won't try on a pizza is
anchovies
ah yeah I don't really like them much
either perfect
okay
[Music]
this is everything all 80s 80s music
City pop 80s Idols the 80s sound you
love it I like it of course Japanese or
non-japanese Japanese Japanese or
non-japanese bring it on it's all
amazing so Jazzy the bases the guitars I
don't like it what the oh it's my
favorite no oh I feel like I want to
send you
um some that you might not even know
send me lots I will every every time uh
fomoko 2 is sending me 80s songs and
being like listen to this and I was like
holy you're making my life so much
better
it's easy easy agree honestly so I
really like and I feel like you would
like fever night then I did I did when
it came out I was like oh hell yeah
she's doing she's doing the 80s
80s synthwave that's good for my heart
I hope you make an 80s uh like original
someday I hope so too like
um
yeah I'm wondering what kind of music
will be best for my original stuff you
should try plenty of genres yeah we'll
see
but okay that's easy easy easy but now
uh past workplaces
yeah I've brought this up because
we have
also a matching similarity here yeah
well where have we both worked before
hotels hotels yeah
[Laughter]
matching
yeah so this is what part what part of
the hotel did you work I I was front
desk so I was a receptionist so I took
all the calls me too mainly but more
like everything I was trained for
everything uh like for three years I did
like a apprenticeship like Germany and
Austria have this like apprenticeship
system where you go to like a specific
school for whatever job you were
choosing for two months in a year and
then the rest is uh the workplace but
you get paid
um but yeah a lot of people do this
instead of high school
um and you can do it even when you're an
adult though I did that and then I uh
worked in also in a hotel after that
before I joined Hollow me too oh my God
I can't I couldn't believe that because
I I didn't know that you worked at a
hotel before so I was like oh
I honestly I think I really liked it I
mean there were of course like some days
that you know where the guests really
pissed you off yeah when they have like
especially in like expensive hotels and
you get like guests who have really high
standards and they think there's
something better than you and also when
they come from different cultures
they're just by standard think they're
better than you so you know you gotta
deal with that and yeah yeah it was
fun though I still liked it I loved my
colleagues too
yeah it's amazing the people you didn't
like your colleagues did you well I
actually loved my colleagues but my
situation is a bit different so I
actually my hotel sucked and I would be
the only person there
ever like when smaller type hotel and so
no no no no cleaners no one to do
laundry so I would be doing all the
receptionist stuff as well as like if a
room had to be cleaned I had to go do it
yeah yeah we're small hotels there's a
risk that you get yourself in such a
position
so I I left but I I would really like to
someday in like the Far Far Future after
after you know everything I think it'd
be fun to work in like a really high-end
hotel and like a really nice city you
know yeah because like yeah think about
it it'd just be so fun
yeah yeah I mean I don't I for me it's
like hard to imagine to ever go back to
normal job again
after three years of doing this uh but
yeah if I really need to I would
probably go back to working in hotels
because that's just what I what I can do
yeah
let's hope we don't have to ever do that
again I mean yeah that would still be
optimal I I wouldn't I wouldn't want to
willingly willingly go back into any
kind of work that isn't this but you
know because of my hotel experience and
me just being able to work in like
touristic uh jobs because of my the
training that I did and the languages
that I speak I I don't know if you know
this but I once signed up for Lufthansa
I went to Lufthansa auditions so the
German airline and I made it in and I
was about to become a cabin attendant
I was about to start my training I even
canceled my apartment and everything and
and found an apartment in Munich because
that was going to be my base
and it was gonna happen but then I said
something in my in my health exam that
me over oh no it was all canceled
yeah well at least you're here now
yeah yeah I was just sad
I was really excited to do it but
honestly it's it's a really rough job
with
um like lots of drama between the
co-workers it's kind of toxic
environment no matter what airline and
really stressful on your health so it's
probably good that I didn't do it but at
least for one year it would have been
fun I feel like yeah no I wanted to I
wanted to be a stewardess once too but
um I never I never went for it
if you know like some languages I feel
like it's pretty easy to get at least in
Europe they they really value their
stewardesses to speak lots of languages
yeah so it was quite easy
lucky you you you you you try language
becoming becoming Korean language uh
jozu as well I don't know how to say
good in Korean but
I will forever cherish that one memory
picture that I have because I went to an
open audition which was like they had
this venue where you know they did a
whole day of auditions and I passed and
then at the end I would take pictures
with like a picture with the Lufthansa
cabin attendance next to me and I've
ever cherish that picture yeah that was
almost almost in Lufthansa well
that's what you get for being too honest
yeah lie next time yeah don't be too
honest guys no okay it's it's good to be
honest um no health health is definitely
very important to be honest about in
when when it comes to you know these
flying jobs yeah yeah
um but for me it was something that
didn't matter but I still was too honest
about it and they kind of misunderstood
it and yeah that's why they canceled me
yeah I can't believe they canceled you
they canceled me
[Laughter]
move on to the next question next time
okay I made I this one I actually made
Kiara listen to a little bit so we'll
get through this one because you put up
a specific one again and I'm like I
don't know this so I listened to it
before the Stream So what do you I love
this myths they're my favorite I like
them too I generally I do like
um like uh British artists with British
accents I do like that a lot and I
listen to a song before the stream I
liked the vibe and it was fine yeah I
could listen to it again
I'm gonna I'm gonna get you into them
I'm Gonna Get You Into The Smiths
gee I think she listened to Heaven Knows
I'm Miserable now so yeah we'll get some
This Charming Man and dude he was
dancing funny well the the great thing
is I found out that uh basically every
Smith song is good uh for an archived
karaoke streams
so you know if you end up liking them
and learning them it'll give you more
cutout case box you can see all right
I'll I'll look into a few more songs and
see if I wanna I'll give you I'll give
you the funny ones
I definitely like the vibe and and
overall like genre and all that but yeah
so moving on that one's your favorite
band yeah it's my favorite band I found
I found them later and I actually
um I've had many different favorite
bands like first first I'd say when uh
Panic Fall Out Boy and MCR were all kind
of king
um was my favorite I love them all
pretty close but MCR was my favorite and
for a long time
um after they kind of just disbanded I
didn't really have a new favorite
because Fall Out Boy was still around
but they they changed a lot
my dog's being loud sorry and then
and then uh like Panic 2 is not the same
as when it started and the music isn't
the same even though Brendon Urie stayed
a really really good uh musician
um but you know uh so I didn't really
have anything and the great thing about
the Smiths is they disbanded early uh
pretty early in their careers because
they all the great thing about them okay
hear me out they released a lot of music
right so I think they have like 80 songs
um so there's still a lot but they're
all it's fairly consistent that they
never became like a parody of themselves
is the best way I can describe it I
guess you mean they never had the chance
to like change too much yeah compared to
their Beginnings because they ended
early yeah and then uh Morris Day still
makes music and oddly I mean it doesn't
have the Smith sound because like a lot
of it came from uh the guitarist uh as
well like uh very prominently but like
his music lyrically is still exactly the
same as this
yeah they're they're my favorite band
thumb I I do enjoy uh I do enjoy some
some more if they're your favorite I
wanna listen a bit more today okay
you I'll get you the good songs then
okay okay all right moving on we got a
free point uh sitcoms this was asked by
you
I love sitcoms many many sitcoms I love
Seinfeld I love full everything I've
watched somebody
okay
what really and it's also really good oh
my God yeah so I like a lot of sitcoms
you said you don't watch them anymore
because you don't have cable but they're
all over Netflix and then what did you
say when I said that I don't uh I don't
really I don't really use Netflix no no
you said you don't know how to
like what get into or yeah yeah I know
how I don't know how to Netflix what do
you mean you don't know how you make an
account you make a subscription you
watch Netflix I don't have money Wawa
oh okay we're changing that soon don't
worry but yeah yeah no I don't I don't
know Netflix
um
I I
don't know how to do it on a TV and I
didn't know it was something you could
do on the computer
so whenever whenever I was watching
Netflix I would need to have like my
family set it up for me she kind of
sounds right now like you're a boomer
but like I I don't know how to use a TV
I will be completely honest I have no
idea how to use a TV I can't figure it
out it's just very you need um you know
you need like a on Amazon you can find
things like smart TV sticks thingies
um I don't know what they're called but
I I had to get one of those too it's
like a USB thingy that you put into your
TV and then it can like receive all
those things I think a fire stick yeah a
fire stick oh yeah yeah
yeah and then then you can watch that I
mean you need a subscription too of
course but yeah yeah so but you likes it
comes generally I do so yeah I watched
oh gosh I my my mom and my grandma's
love sitcoms so or I guess soap operas
but I I consider them to be pretty much
the same
um basically there's differences but uh
I will I will go and some Netflix ones
this girl she needs Netflix so badly
like I can't believe it like what
how do you not Netflix I I don't know
you're missing so much and oh my God
since you have access to it because like
I me in Austria I literally I'm
incapable of getting Hulu but you have
to get Hulu yeah when you have to
transfer it my sister has Hulu so I make
her I make her I watch Hulu with her oh
my god do you know the handmaid's tale I
haven't seen it but I want to it is like
you like horror right and it's not
horror horror but it's like terrifyingly
painful like traumatizing to watch it
and it's on Hulu and it's like so well
made it's like um dystopian uh like
America a dystopian America I think yeah
where
um
it's just it's very terrifying
but it's kind of using bits of our
current reality to show you that this
this could possibly be a thing and that
makes it even more terrifying yeah
that's scary I I that that does interest
me I might have to look into it if
you're recommending it to me I I
recommend it if you want to suffer like
I cried so much and after a lot of
episodes I like many episodes made me so
traumatized I needed a break before
watching the next one oh my God I
haven't had a I forget I had a show like
that too but I don't remember what it is
right now
um I love that though it's kind of a fun
it's kind of a fun but okay we both like
sitcoms it's generally I prefer to watch
light-hearted things like yeah no same I
I really I really liked uh the office
it's it's probably the most recent one I
thought the off even as a like kind of
like went down a bit I still loved it
yeah
mm-hmm
okay it's like it's like you know Game
of Thrones like at the end becoming
unlikable to a lot of people because of
changes being made but but for the
office I feel like you know it's still
very much likeable even even though they
made changes yeah yeah so that's a point
it's funny you know Parks and Rec I've
seen a few episodes of parks and rec but
I haven't seen it it's true completion
but everything I've seen I like
and
um what's it called the anus tart show
um what's that have you seen It's Always
Sunny in Philadelphia
no not that one but I haven't watched
that one actually me neither
aggressive development Arrested
Development I haven't seen it
it's also Netflix once you get Netflix
you will have to binge watch so many
shows but then but Chihuahua when I work
you are my background noise I can't
cheat on you with sitcoms I'll give you
um a leaf for unpaid leave for a month
to catch you won't you won't send me to
the room right
nah nah you have to watch those shows
you have to okay I'll thank you
you're using your Senpai Senpai bullying
no it's good for you I just want the
best for you I see I see okay moving on
from sitcoms
he uses another you question
I don't know what you want from me with
this so I'll answer first and then you
can reveal so that way people I need
people I need you too to stop accusing
me of copying you
um mushrooms I answered this in my debut
yeah I don't really like to eat any
except anoki mushroom Enoki mushroom are
the best mushroom I'll still eat
mushrooms but I don't like how they
taste okay I will eat um but admittedly
uh I didn't grow up with it so there's
certain kinds of like fried tofu I think
is the best but like I actually
when I'm eating a soup I don't really
like the texture of tofu in it so like I
love miso but usually I like kind of
ignore the tofu me too spinach I love
uh spicy food I can handle I like spicy
food but I don't necessarily go out of
my way to eat it I feel like I usually
prefer for there to be a bit of a kick
but not too much like uh for example I
have a sweet tooth so usually sweet I'm
gonna go for so even like Curry
um I will
eat the like hot curry but the hot curry
that they sell I don't feel like is hot
at all like the mild one though I'll
also eat and it's very sweet yeah the
golden the Golden Curry yeah
yeah so I'll always get hot because it's
not that hot
um at least the one that they sell in
the states I don't know if it's
different
um because I know sometimes and switch
things up you know depending on where
it's being sold but otherwise I'd I'd
usually tend to prefer a little sweet
stuff if I can but I can handle spice
Seafood uh I love crab and lobster but
as you said not fish I'm not really a
fish fan anyway but crab crab is a pain
to eat though so I don't I don't usually
get it a lot because it's such a
freaking pain in the ass
what about what about like clams
I like clam chowder but I've never like
gotten to have like glamor like oysters
on its own I want to try them but I'm
kind of scared because oysters
especially raw oysters they they they
look to me a bit scary and intimidating
what about shrimps
I don't like shrimp oh okay let's go I
actually really don't like shrimp at all
like crab crab I think the the thing is
the reason I like crab is because I eat
it with butter and lemon
and I I doused it in butter and lemon
and I like butter and lemon and then I
can't like I wouldn't eat raw I mean raw
as in like um not dipped cooked crab
same with lobster I baste it in butter
yeah I think that's how you supposed to
eat it what about fish eggs
[Music]
um
no no just say no no I there's the the
small ones don't bug me as much but the
really big ones something about the
texture and like knowing what it is gets
to me I'm not a big fan of eggs in
general so like anything that I know is
an egg kind of like you know it kind of
like gives it like a weird feeling okay
okay so I this is all things that I
don't like
oh my God I hate mushrooms I don't
really like tofu I can only tolerate
spinach when it's so hidden in the food
that I don't see it
and like maybe like pure pureed into a
sauce like Ahmed did it for me I don't
like spice I'm very sensitive about
spicy food so often spicy food that's
not spicy to others is very very spicy
to me and seafood I also don't eat like
at all I think
um so yeah you agree on some of these
but others not so maybe we'll get a 0.5
yeah we'll do it we'll do a half Point
somehow I feel like my numbers are wrong
what did I miss
maybe Chad is also still but they they
they didn't want to give us certain
points yeah what's our count what's our
count wait do we do we have more
questions we do okay wait we're not done
yet a few more maybe okay I think this
is the last one though so I feel like
I'm still missing one
question uh in my count I did something
wrong
because we got rid of one or two uh yeah
well I I minus them I'll double check
real quick before while I'm calculating
the score okay but okay wait no we have
two more so roller coasters oh okay you
have roller coasters I asked this
because I honestly I I go on them when
I'm with a group where let's say we have
we're four people group and three of
them love roller coasters and if I don't
go then I'm the one ruining the fun so I
might join if it's not too bad but I I
you have to like open My Dead Body will
I go on a roller coaster knowingly that
has a loop
yeah so I I actually due to one of my uh
my my back problem I'm not supposed to
really ride roller coasters
um okay I will still ride them if I'm in
the same situation you were saying like
if I'm if I'm with someone who I know
really wants to like ride rides or like
what if I'm with like a group of friends
and they like want to go do everything
together I'll still go on them but the
issue for me is actually um because of
because of it I I get whipped around and
I can actually I can actually die if I
ride roller coasters so uh yeah and I'll
I'll tell you more later but okay it's
silly it's silly but um yeah it's really
dangerous for me actually so um I will
ride ones but especially if they're like
wooden and like old uh if they if they
uh Shake too much I can't do it I can't
do it at all or else it's a risk to my
life oh okay okay so we can enjoy the
more baby ones together so if we go
together then you can you can have an
excuse to not go on them be I'm sorry I
have to take care of narissa because
she'll die
that's good you know for
um even even like pretty
mid roller coasters and not too crazy
like
when there's a drop I I first for the
first two seconds or so I will scream
the out of my body and then I go
into a state of I'm dying where I
look down I kind of like become a little
ball and I I am incapable physically
incapable of screaming anymore and I'm
just like kind of holding my breath
somehow and just waiting for it to be
over because I'm like really dying
inside
every every time every time the pictures
uh happen after a roller coaster I look
like like my eyes are scrunched closed
and like I look like I'm the most
uncomfortable person like everyone's
like screaming like hands up and I just
look like yeah me too me too yeah yeah
baby again uh I I personally prefer
Ferris wheels uh oh yeah I love Ferris
wheels because you get a really good
view or like unless you have to pay
freaking what was it it's of 50 bucks
for Ryan like the London Eye what the
yeah 50
50. let's go on Ferris wheel together
kiwawa Senpai okay there's some various
whales out there where you can have like
dinner in them really
it's really romantic yeah
um then I guess we'll have to do it
together yeah
well okay I'll count that as a win I'd
say we agree
hey we do we do we do we definitely do
yes true crime is also from me I love
true crime videos
you make
that because like I I binge watched a
lot of them and at some point it got me
like kind of traumatized where I'm like
why am I actually actually why am I
watching
traumatizing but it's so interesting too
and I guess for someone like you who was
in prison
um
it didn't really help you did it huh no
um well I yeah I tend to I tend to get
actually uh I love True Crime but like
so I'll watch it and then I'll like
afterwards I'll be thinking about it and
I'll be like
I'm gonna get murdered yeah yeah yeah
yeah it makes it very
um
so I'm always one one thing I know
thanks to these videos if I ever get
into a situation wherever I'm guilty or
not not is that a question I will ask
for a lawyer immediately oh yeah I'm
like these idiots who let themselves to
be interviewed until they go into prison
forever without asking for a lawyer once
it's so stupid stop talking about me
like that
why did you not ask for a lawyer the
gods punished me they saw they were
there for it that's not
they didn't they didn't even give me a
trial they just stole my horn and threw
me in jail what the they should
still give you the benefit of the doubt
maybe you were maybe you weren't like I
was delicious I didn't know I didn't
know that was gonna happen
maybe it wasn't like you were controlled
by something else yeah it wasn't
actually you yeah maybe we could say we
could say that right if they come out
the voices in your head told you to do
it
not not fit not fit yeah yeah why did
they not consider that that is kind of
up I must say good question very
good question uh maybe we should sue
them whoever the gods are I'm gonna find
them but yeah uh dude do you have a
favorite person you like to watch
specifically or should we not talk about
that I don't know I'm not I'm not fine
but I can't remember the channel names
there's like a few famous ones I think
that I watch I like Stephanie Sue she's
just like mukbang and talks about horror
with like her yeah yeah I love her so
much she's so I like her too but I
generally prefer to watch the ones where
I can see the interview by myself I like
those ones too where it's like in in the
in the police room I don't have any
channels specifics with those ones too
but I also love those ones because it's
like it's so interesting actually like
watching and like having like someone
explain
like what's going on like yeah and being
like you can see kind of here like do do
the body language yeah tell me more tell
me more tell me more what I need to be
careful about next time
but yeah she she's
um very good at telling those stories
yeah but I I wonder like does she also
not just get traumatized like all her
channel does is tell up these like
up stories like how can you even
what function this is your whole Channel
content I know I know she she stops
sometimes and will not talk about True
Crime but she'll actually talk about
like uh other stuff like uh k-dramas and
like horror movies instead so that way
she's talking about something that's not
so real
um where she'll talk about stuff that
like is still just disturbing and like
you know but not not as like True Crime
as like murderous or like traumatizing
um I mean the stuff I saw from her was
all pretty up like now I'm
thinking back on it oh god oh man yeah
there's one I can't stomach that I every
time I think yeah
when it comes to my stomach hurt
it's really rough I don't know what
compels a human to watch these videos
but maybe at least
after watching something like that you
can at least feel like relieved that you
are not ever gonna be doing like
that you're never gonna
stoop to that point solo yeah yeah it's
the better personality I think it gets
too morbid curiosity that's so weird
humans are so weird honestly
oh man it's rough it's rough yeah
YouTube was I think something was gone
for a moment there
that was just a short moment
I even had a small lag and and Discord
oh no that's not good my internet
no no well I don't know what it is we
need to fight over this last one because
oh do you like Crocs
um
Kiara no you you don't I think they are
acceptable I don't wear them
Oh I thought you put this on here
because you liked them and I was about
to yell at you I think it's only
acceptable if you wear them at home or
in your garden or on your back or so
yeah going outside with them
with them they're ugly they're expensive
I I don't understand the fashion of
Crocs either expensive why the are
they I don't know but you can get like I
don't know Crocs are just the worst
things I've ever looked at ever yeah
like okay yeah like if you're Watering
your garden with your Crocs on shoes
yeah sure or you go to if your
Supermarket is or a convenience stores
like five steps away and you go there
okay yeah but any further than that
outside please please
I'm begging you for me
oh thank God we agree on this oh I was
so I was like when you told me that I
was like she likes Crocs
maybe I'm gonna have to change ooshies
no no no I will not be made to work I'm
so glad I was scared yeah Crocs I'd I'd
much rather wear like boot like
someone in the chat said Birkenstock
Birkenstock is where it's at birken
Birkenstocks are pretty I mean it's an
instant style right now here I don't own
any because I think they're expensive
here too I don't know I guess they're
fine like Cali was wearing some the
other day it was like Kelly Birkenstocks
what's going on is this style in uh
here but I don't know how I feel I I
will unironically because it's a style I
will just wear my socks and put on
regular sandals and then go to the
supermarket because I'm like what are
they gonna do it's in style with the
with the Zoomers nowadays
okay but um that's only some people are
shocked that what I just said about Cali
because she normally wears always like
very like
fans not fancy like but like
um Stand Out tea
uh crazy shoes
uh and then like a while ago when we
went somewhere together she had these
dad sandals on and I'm like Kelly is
this like a face
yeah she's she it's fine though like I
mean it was just a shock compared to her
normal self at least she wasn't wearing
Crocs so yeah yeah uh I can forgive
anything but not Crocs
is the point for us okay okay then I
think
the results are in
um oh I need I need to calculate it real
quick so just give me okay you'll
calculate and then I'm gonna because I
have to calculate it I actually have to
turn the screen off for you guys that's
fine
um build up the anticipation a little
bit
um well oh none of us here can count so
we are already into all really
anticipating the results none of us
could ever guess how this will go I
can't count for one so but I think maybe
there's a slight chance that we are over
all overly compatible yeah yeah as we've
already known it because we get we got
surprised so many times when we're
talking to each other in the past days
yeah and then every time a new thing
comes up I'm like what
what
so yeah I'll give the stats first and
then I'll give I'll give the the
percentage or rather
um chat give your percentage guesses
first I'll give you a minute so we we
did pretty well we struck two questions
so technically I'm not I'm not I'm not
gonna add those two disagreements onto
it so we will only go with the questions
that we agreed to not any of them that
were stricken
with the 69s
oh some 80s Maybe 75s
some 70s some 80s all right let's go
ahead and show them then shall we the
results what happens oh
we did well I don't like this ah
should have been a hundred I know
for at least 90. well we had 22
questions all in all we agreed on 17.5
questions which is really good we only
just we hate each other ah I don't are
you okay
this is quite a shock to me honestly wow
is it I guess we're not meant to be in
don't say that to me
too bad I guess I'll never collab again
[Laughter]
unfortunate man guys help you can't let
her do this to me I love you what a
waste of potential
she's breaking my heart into little
pieces right on my own channel well I'm
just accepting reality man somebody
knows this is so good just kidding just
kidding everything that's pretty good
look I I I we agreed on most things
which is is surprising yeah and it's not
like it's it's not like most of them
even were like kind of half agreeances
anyway
[Music]
there will be even more agreements in
the future exactly this was this was
just a short you know you you all know
if you're going to actually do something
you have to really go through and
actually do proper
testing so we'll have to we'll just have
to do more of these again in private
with do you feel like we should add um
five percent
um because the fact that we are both
Birds is also making us compatible
I agree okay you know then yeah the
final number is technically 79 plus five
four left
[Music]
well technically and then I'd also give
us another another 11 points for how how
well we banter together
yeah but like even even offstream uh you
call me and I'm I think you call me more
than my Jennings
yeah you do oh so I think I know you're
always around when I need you which is
so weird and then I feel like I'm I feel
like I really am welcome to call you and
then you will always appreciate me
reaching out and then you will always
want to make time for me you know so it
makes me happy okay
[Music]
I'm looking forward to many many collabs
from now on yeah me too
but for now I I'm I don't know what time
where what time is it in
um midnight I want to let kiwawa get to
bed no are you sure
yes
because it feels like even if we're in
the Stream we're gonna continue to talk
for well that's quite exactly it's the
long goodbye but if we if we keep this
dream going then we'll we'll still have
the long talk after school you know you
know I'm even considering starting
Terraria just for you because I don't I
don't want to miss out on lots of
nerissa actions
you know I wanna make you happy Kyla is
going to join too and the collab ends up
so but are you gonna play Minecraft
though of course I'm gonna play
Minecraft
because I was thinking since you're like
always awake kind of when I'm streaming
that maybe there's hope that when I play
Minecraft you'll join me so I'm not
always so alone anymore no I mean as
long as I'm not because usually I'm
working when I'm watching you but uh now
this is my job so if you're if you're in
a call and you're sitting there and
waiting I can't guarantee you I'll be
any good or any help at Minecraft but I
will happily join you if you'll have me
yeah even if you just join the VC
without even being in the game that
would also make me happy yeah yeah I
would love to but yeah no I I like
Terraria and Minecraft but I like
different things about them you know so
for me like they they're they're
different appeals but I like them both
so yeah I'm don't worry about me playing
Terraria I'm still gonna play Minecraft
and play Minecraft with you
you beta I I will
because you're gonna bring some new life
to the en server maybe yeah Advent as a
whole unless unless I've been plans to
just never go to the en side and just
stay in the Japanese service
I'll ask you about it off stream but I'm
kind of confused about the different
servers I thought the en server was
deleted
no no the answer is still there but it's
kind of like merged now like
nah I I would still say it's kind of
like separate but
um ever since the new server was created
uh all the en members like made
themselves uh houses in the new one so
Japanese members also had to build
everything from scratch again so the
other ID and emm is I guess took it as
an opportunity to start from scratch 2
there and now en is just like kind of
like abandoned yeah
yeah I thought I thought they were just
merging and that they nuked the rest of
the servers so that it was more easy for
everyone to play together but I guess
that makes I guess that makes sense
yeah and I enjoy playing with them
together too but also on the other hand
I want to have something that you know
belongs to Ian you know something that
we build together yeah
um our own world our own memories
because like the EM World side I feel
like you know there's a lot of like
funny history uh interesting buildings
that have I want to show you around I
mean you may already know a lot of them
like no show me myself dreams okay you
know like there's so much lore there
like myth floor and so on like the
tunnel that we built in our first
Minecraft collab for hours and hours
because gooda forced us to
[Laughter]
yeah and the PPP and and my or Phoenix
stand and this and that yeah I feel like
it would be such a waste to just leave
all of that behind just because there's
a new Fresh empty server you know that's
that's how I feel but most people don't
feel like that I guess yeah
oh there's a famous hole you don't even
know what the famous hole show me the
famous hole I think it's filled up now
oh
but I want to show you the the whole
video the compilation of the whole lore
to do it I'll watch it
that's so good
yeah so
um when are you when are you girls gonna
join the Minecraft server um I don't
know I think uh they want to plan
something specific so I don't think I
should talk about it because I don't
know and they haven't told us anything
but just to be safe I also don't wanna I
don't want to bring it up till until
they get it fine but I guess so you
girls are planning on a specific date
yeah I think all of us whenever we do
join will be introd all at the same time
so it'll probably be a collab with all
of Advent
I'm personally hoping for it to be next
week
we'll see we'll see but we'll see I am
right because I guess she only is in the
round maybe yeah
but yeah I I need to bring it up to them
though because I know uh I mean the club
ends up pretty soon I imagine it'll be
once a collab the big collab in is up
yeah so probably around then whenever
that is okay if if you need a personal
en server tour let me know be my guide
I'd be so happy it will it will it has
been a while since I've done the tour
but I am I'm a good tour guide trust me
I believe it you don't have to convince
me Kyla is also waiting for for all of
you ah my microphone Kyla's also waiting
for all of you to join Minecraft I know
she's crazy
she's everywhere well I hope you will
join for Terraria because uh I I think
uh my manager uh she was like you should
you should uh actually make a different
server just for you to like mine stuff
to like make equipment for everyone
oh wait can you if you do it on a
different server can you bring it over
to the other one yeah so even Kyla she
was like I've never played it before and
uh I was like uh you you can you can
move characters between so even Kyla was
like oh I might start then and get get a
hang of the game and then join so um
yeah you can you can make someone and
you can go into any different world with
that same character and you keep
everything you keep everything that's on
your person so oh that's cool yeah it's
hard for me not to just like bring in my
good equipment and just start
immediately being a digging a digging
guy
uh but
you know sometimes it's good to start
from scratch yeah exactly so but I hope
you'll join too especially since uh
Kelly popped in I feel like that would
be fun and since
even out of pure jealousy not wanting
you to be too much with other people
without me but
thank you
yeah I'll consider it just for you
you're happy to hear it fomo fomo
the fomo indeed well but for now we
should call it quit
I need to send you to bed I like you too
much I won't allow you to stay up late
anymore now that I'm here I still have
to cook though I'm not going to bed uh
you eat this late at night
don't you know me I I know you do but I
often I can't yeah I often end my
streams at like midnight and then I cook
and then yeah I but currently my sleep
schedule is really messed up anyway but
I went from going to sleep at 10 A.M two
days ago to going to sleep at 6am last
night so today I will go to sleep back
at my normal time 4 00 am well
good luck
thank you thank you
I'll fix it yeah I'll cook for you too
please I love it do you like cooking I
love cooking see we should have added
that to a couple no why didn't why
didn't we
see yeah another another additional
Point see we just keep going up yeah
cooking cooking cooking we should do
cooking collab someday I don't know I
wanna when you sleep over at my place
yeah I really I actually want to make
that part of my content someday I want
to do mukbang and cooking content
I think it's interesting yeah I just
don't know how to have to work yet but
someday yeah yeah you need to need to
build a setup
but we need Kiara to cook now
okay
thank you for joining me and for being
my first collab with this
and then you joined like I can't say it
enough honestly like it's it's really
nice to have someone who understands and
appreciates me so much me specifically
makes me feel special makes me feel
loved and and you're so sweet and so
talented so it's like even more like
special to be liked by someone who's so
who's so talented you know and also so
sweet so yeah and we even share so many
interests so it's not even like one side
that's I think we'll be great friends
and yes
um I think you're kind of like
you know I I I I've been through some
rough times and it will be nice to have
someone like you uh and in those rough
times you know when I'm feeling stressed
out or lonely
thank you guys
[Music]
kfp we'll see you
bye
[Music]
thank you
foreign