foreign
oh
man
[Music]
oh
yeah
it was smoothie meowing in the back and
junkers
purring
oh
yeah
okay
ah I'm sorry for being late but you know
I mean you heard you heard the prayers
you know what that means
uh okay
step by step cut hair in my mouth nice
um
copy
starting now
um
okay bad news I didn't uh really I mean
I did get myself into the game but it
looked very glitchy uh the textures were
really off and so
um besides that Steph was like please
please wait kiwawa don't do it yet
please so now I'm waiting and we'll do
it another time because I mean I don't
think we'll finish the game this episode
I mean we could probably but let's
purposefully not do it
um
foreign
[Music]
quite far with
the game that's what I feel like at
least but who knows maybe there's much
much more to it
oh oh my God thanks for the pinky
eh did you hear chunky wonky purines
you're so happy
she was just lying in front of my
keyboard and gonna pop
the whole time yeah and she's so cute
she's like as long as I look at her or
touch her she purrs
constantly it's so adorable man
it's just joke Yahoo
uh
Bob calm down Bob horny bunk
and
let's see I forgot how to stream
um bgm first of all let's get some bgm
going
is it
shots
I don't have the schedule up yet you
know I arrived today
[Laughter]
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I I I I I
I I I I I I I I
I wanted to throw them into VLC uh but I
threw them into BS I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry
ah I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
like confused
um and then what I'm doing
hey some aren't you should have already
turned it down anyway
in preparation
oh man I'm sorry confusion uh
all right
there you go okay okay hi that's what
that lucky up ah I'm sorry I am such a
sassy Baka oh no okay let's let's get a
hold of ourselves and not make any more
mistakes
um
there we go there we go there's that
okay okay
sorry
yeah you hear
some very soft pajam right
soft right yeah
[Music]
okay
you can't hear me over all the ringing
oh no
ah oopsie little yeah it's harmonica
right
okay
ringing in your ears
what'd you say boss app
I could hear the PGM
I can only read your lips now too bad I
don't have lips
God damn it what
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah what what BTS no no I don't listen to
BTS I mean BTM
what about the idiom eh you wanna hear
ADM for the BTM
the burger machine is all good boss well
I mean that's good to know
okay okay okay okay okay okay
um
[Music]
uh
uh I'm back so after the stream I'll
make a schedule I mean I already have it
kind of in my Google Calendar
um but just gonna make it into a
schedule
uh for now we'll just play this because
I thought you know you guys probably
missed me right
so I suppose
that's a possible play a game
and it's a Buckeyes no no it was a
holiday on vacation it's a holiday day
today
um did you know it's the first oh first
of Maya
okay tablet is tablet is in front of me
ready to draw
hey yeah I saw like people driving a
with several cars and so on driving a
huge really long tree for the city not
where I am but where I was yesterday
uh
which is a May tree
[Music]
um
a big long
asparagus looking tree
yeah maypole I guess
yeah I would actually do say a tree in
Germany in German
it's golden week in Japan oh
um
[Music]
mayday mayday
okay so sorry my brain is just not
starting
we're gonna figure out what to do right
away
[Music]
tell me do you want something from me
Bobby from Bull Street
has a new interesting product coming I
read in office supplies Harold
this is like a newspaper so that Bobby
is developing a new sturdy machine
if you happen to see him maybe there's a
job for you over at Bull Street Bull
Street I'm a car
yeah um So eventually I will hopefully
be able to run around in this game with
my with my own body
um for this stream it was kind of
spontaneous of me to decide
what to stream today
so unfortunately
unfortunately it couldn't happen so
spontaneously
we're looking for Bobby right
it's Christmas excuse me
is this Bobby no we're looking for Bobby
[Music]
yeah I think I should be able to put 3D
wow into the game I was like I already
did it but it was kind of glitching
you're an artist that people are
chattering about I got a job for you
okay Mommy gave me a small loan to start
a business I got just a disrupting idea
that will take this town by storm
t-shirts with prints oh that is genius
I've never heard of such a thing you
might be an entrepreneur
but not just any Prince fancy I just
prints that's where you come in
design a cool t-shirt for me and I'll
make it worth your time okay good
t-shirt
too can I turn this one around as well
like the other one
oh yeah I can the people
the pizzas I think
regret the OG myth shirt oh good idea
wait
OT miffshirt
let me look it up
phone
helped me out here
you guys remember the OG mixture engine
oh yeah speaking of t-shirts
and by Elena's dream
um
whole life
shirt
oh there's like a lot of fake ones ah no
I found the right one
okay
oh let's see let's see this should be
your recreatable so first we start with
uh painting the whole thing black
because it was only available in Black
also I want to tell you Stars today
so
let's see how that goes oh you can paint
the inside of the sleeve too
[Music]
you know putting paint
like this
straight onto the T-shirt is probably
gonna make the T-shirt
a little bit hard to put on and move in
around with but
oh don't forget the the
under the arm
Waki
Okay pink I think we got it it's all
black now where was front where was the
back
I think this is
my be back right yeah yeah yeah this is
front
this front
lucky
no Rocky has to be covered up
okay now
um
[Music]
let's make the big writing in the back
is anyone here who doesn't know the good
old
first ever
uh myth or like whole life English
t-shirt
[Music]
I designed it I drill it
I very much remember
I have one wow
that is a treasure
restock please
but that would make it lose its
exclusivity
you treasure mine as you should
as you should my friend
[Music]
are you still going
to round yet well that's what makes the
shirt so special that if you have it it
probably means that you've been around
beginning
so
but maybe you even if you don't have it
you maybe have at least seen it anyway
so it was like this
and then on top of it was like
the girls
and I asked them back then like yo I'm
not good with like graphic design can
you please like do something about the
background
so this is just like replace this
replace this with something cool under
the characters that I drew okay and then
they did nothing I just
can't do like this
oh man
okay this is really tiny though like I
don't know how I'm supposed to draw all
these cute characters on top of it
um
it's gonna be a bit scuffed
[Music]
it was Cali up here
we have a skin colors yeah I got the
skin colors with me
oh
so how you guys doing today huh
I got a lot of sleep
so I'm I'm quite
happy with that
but I'm still always tired it's just my
General State hold up more shipping yeah
people already receive it
I caught up with follow what's nice
doing pretty damn good awesome good
chilling with family nice
better than yesterday
oh is it because of me
[Music]
you might be because you mean
okay I cannot
I cannot do too many details it's huge
Mall
[Music]
come on
it's very pixely
what I don't even see what I'm drawing
okay that's fine
oh no I actually I gave her her veil and
stuff actually oh
[Music]
a perfect replica you know what we may
not resell
um
this ever who knows but here here is a
tutorial on how to make your own okay
good luck
just follow every stroke and every step
what I'm doing
good
[Music]
so over the weekend I was gone
thanks for waiting for me patiently
everybody bootleg move shirt but again
made by me
um
I was at
a convention convention
having some fun with my friends
[Music]
I can't zoom in
well okay it's got a little bit of a
smug look
did you have fun I had fun yeah I mean
um
it was a bit exhausting but
I did have my fun met a lot of friends
again uh for the first time in a long
time so
that was very noise
some time to catch up with them
some time to bond with them
wait let me try to
ship first
[Music]
mm-hmm
yeah and uh
it was in Germany so I drove or I didn't
drive I was in the car
and my friends with my friends like two
of my friends
I was first Wheeling them
but they probably appreciated it because
uh that way they didn't have to pay as
much
uh
gasoline
yeah it's always nice to have another
person to split it with
I was sitting in the back of the car
the whole ride and
I feel like
this this really says something about us
but we we did not even turn on music
until like the very end of the ride most
of the time we were just talking
all kinds of things
[Music]
hmm
yeah no music just just chit chatting we
were making our own podcast basically
and oh yeah that's nice yeah you know in
the beginning I remember I was actually
feeling kind of sick this was on on
Friday uh early I think it was like 10
a.m or so that we started driving I
think
maybe and I was feeling kind of sick for
some reason I
did I even have breakfast I think I
didn't
[Music]
I didn't have breakfast and I noticed
that oh I was feeling very sick
even when I was looking out the window
it like ran away in the beginning of the
red normally I can take a few hours
um without food
and feel all right
but this time
yeah
looking kind of PN
[Music]
should I draw a body too difficult
I can't break up my mind
um
let me
let me try the fingers I drew on black
then
what the [\h__\h] am I doing
oh it's really really sick even though I
was looking out the window all the time
and not on my phone because that makes
me really sick and so I was feeling sick
so we uh we weren't even planning to
take a break
because my friend uh the driver he's
really good at just driving through for
hours and hours and hours there's no
break and that was the plan because
the other friend she wanted to arrive at
the convention really early
even though it wasn't gonna really be
much going on
because it was the first day of the
convention and it was bad weather and we
already saw like the previous year that
there wouldn't be really anything going
on at this time like when we would
arrive like no the whole day really not
that worth it
but she wanted to and you do so we tried
but
any minute counted no breaks welcome but
we ended up you know taking a little
break for me to grab something to eat
and then everybody ended up getting
something to eat too and then afterwards
I felt better yeah
yeah thank God normally I don't get
carsick
only you know
if you make the mistake of looking at
your phone
just
then
obviously my own fault
I didn't I didn't I was nice of them
yeah we got some yummy food at uh like a
in the middle of nowhere a resting place
and then after that we zoomed zoom zoom
zoom zoom zoom through the country over
to Germany
um
it's a nice it was a nice little
roach trip
I always enjoyed doing these in the past
with me and my friends we most of the
time we would go to conventions by car
even if they were like I don't know 12
no maybe not 12. yeah I don't know that
may have been 12 hour car rides but like
10 hours 10 hour car rides were were
pretty common
with us it was always fun and our driver
usually oh it was always him usually
he's very very good at driving forever
he's he's the type of person who just
enjoys
uh driving
endlessly
so no need to worry
long drives yeah
can't relate oh he doesn't only need no
breaks he also drives usually pretty
fast
so we get to the conventions really
quickly usually
um
so this time uh uh yeah it was just us
free there was another friend who was
supposed to come
but kind of canceled on us again that's
so sad like please come but nope it was
just us free small group but I was
hoping to meet some more friends at the
convention then instead
oh
which thankfully happened but after we
arrived you know I was really tired
because
I didn't get that much sleep
and
um
no I was just tired so I we checked into
the hotel we were in the same Hotel
and
I was basically waiting for a friend to
bring me some stuff that I ordered and I
had to send to my friend because can't
send it to Austria anymore
for reasons
Austria being very very
annoying and particular with uh Parcels
or literally anything coming from China
um
which is really inconvenient
can you recognize gouda already she has
no hair yet
it's gonna be a fabulous t-shirt they
better appreciate the hell out of it
[Music]
yeah
she doesn't even not only have a hair
but she also just doesn't have the top
part of her skull
all right you shall receive it now
yeah I was waiting for my friend and I
checked out a German Supermarket called
rebe
r-e-w-e and I was like yo this
Supermarket is really cool because they
have a huge salad bar with fresh salads
like
like 15 different types of salads to
choose from
or more maybe 20.
our supermarkets in Austria
like a big salad bar
yeah awesome so I got a lot of salads so
if I wanted to I wanted to try them all
and I just sat down in my hotel room
alone eating sampling all the salads and
watching some shitty uh German TV
and like poziben tough Taft tough tough
tough was the program I used to watch it
a lot when I was uh younger
is like one of the better TV channels I
would say
but
still like some of the things they show
they're they're you know some of the
things I report on in that program are
kind of cringe
no it isn't it
oh you guys think don't think so I think
it's one of the better ones I mean look
at RTL
rtl2
then I would say impossible is one of
the better ones like what what is one of
the better ones then
if if posi made it then I don't know
which one is it
[Music]
um
RTL is
[\h__\h]
I never watched those they never had
anything interesting to me
if
[Music]
okay
okay all you do you wow your box ah that
was a thing box I think back in the day
was showing Charmed or so I think
box oh I haven't heard that in a long
time does that still exist
pink box was good for some good shows oh
oh yeah
oh because old days I wasn't trying on
cover and I don't know
Charmed Trump was even voxo I think
um
so I was just chilling and then my
friend came eventually brought me the
stuff that I ordered
and oh I was I was you know
just chilling and then I went to sleep
relatively early but you know what
happened in the morning
I
you guys I worked at a hotel before so I
kind of
know how things work and when
housekeeping usually starts doing their
thing and what they do first and all
that
um and I I didn't expect
this uh I didn't put out a do not
disturb sign so it's partially of course
my fault but but listen
[Music]
at 7am I was in deep Slumber and
somebody knocked on my door and oh no no
no wait that's the problem they didn't
knock on my door even they just opened
it immediately and walked in a little
bit and then I guess they looked and saw
that I'm sleeping and then they uh went
out again I couldn't see who it was so
then I was like confused like what the
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] early normally when uh you're in
a hotel housekeeping will start working
at that time yeah yeah usually but what
they do first is
they normally they have like a list
uh that they print out first things in
the morning and to see who's already
checked out because usually okay there
are some early checkouts like six seven
a.m maybe most checkouts are more like
nine from nine a.m 10 a.m to like the
actual checkout time
uh but yeah 7am is kind of early a lot
of people are not checked out yet but
whoever's checked out already they would
first go to those rooms
um and then the stairs usually don't
wake up that early
usually I mean some do but most
statistically don't
so
what they wouldn't normally they they
wouldn't just like walk at least they
they would maybe at least knock and see
but but normally they don't go for it
that early
in my case they did and they woke me up
with it and then I just couldn't fall
asleep anymore I was so tired but I was
lying in my bed after that for two hours
with my eyes closed
until I finally fell asleep again at 9
00 am for like 10 minutes because then I
had to wake up anyway
then I had to link up that was the final
time where I had to wake up to get some
breakfast before breakfast would close
yeah
so they sell two hours from me
I was so mad I'm so mad because once
once I'm awake even when I'm [\h__\h]
tired if you wake me up it's so hard for
me to fall asleep again
so that was kind of rude
and not a good start for me in my day
that was a Saturday morning yeah
but anyway The Show Must Go On
do I have no I have no oranges all right
we must go
we must go and grab an orange
going back home
looking at my pallet stair so
I woke up I got some quick breakfast it
was like I walked into the breakfast
Hall with my eyes half open kind of like
wobbling like a Pangolin
but my friends were there which made me
happy they were already at the breakfast
area
ah
I said
[Music]
zombie basically zombie
take the summer fun for now I think that
has orange
oh yeah there's orange
[Music]
yeah uh I had to me I'm in breakfast the
breakfast was pretty good then I went
back into my room and I started getting
ready thank you Jackson
[Music]
I started getting ready for the day
and I was in the bathroom you know doing
my makeup
I'm just you know
trying to be quick
and I know this I had my phone lying
there and I noticed that I I I've been
like getting calls
but I didn't recognize the number
but the calls they wouldn't stop coming
and I don't stop coming and they don't
stop coming and they don't stop coming
they really didn't stop coming and I was
like what the [\h__\h] is going on I didn't
pick up because I didn't recognize the
number
they would even like call with
uh
an unrecognizable number or with a
private number
so I thought I don't know I didn't I
didn't feel like picking up a number
that I didn't know
if I didn't have to
so I ignored it for quite some time
until
at some point you know after 10 minutes
10 minutes they were still calling me
so I was like okay
I guess
I'll I'll pick up I guess
so
but I pick up the phone really carefully
and I saw that it was a number from
Austria
uh I pick up really carefully like
not wanting to say my name so just say
hello really carefully
and
what what I didn't hear is somebody
asking like a like a mature male voice
serious sounding voice asks me
are you Mrs takanasi piano
and I'm like
uh yeah
and that that
him asking me that
okay they didn't ask you know they
didn't say takanasi yeah
they asked if I'm
well you know
well you know you know you know what I
mean uh
um
then that was really concerned because
Maguire you're asking if I am this
person this is weird I normally don't
get calls like this it's very sus
oh my God
oh at least it doesn't look so bad that
it's so tiny oh I can't do much better
Pian
so I said yeah and then the guy on the
phone says
uh okay uh I am so-and-so from the
police in
this AKA your city the city on this
street
and I'm like
foreign
and my mind immediately like this is
like freaking out like what the [\h__\h] did
I do what what did I do what did I do
what could I what could I have done and
what excuse shall I make why why would
they call me what what reason
what
why are they calling me I'm scared I was
scared I was so scared what did I do did
I do something illegal I was trying to
remember if I did something illegal that
they would know of
but I I couldn't think of anything
so
[Music]
very concerning very concerning this now
um yeah
so well he tells me that this he's from
this Police Department
next he asked me
Miss takanashi where are you and I I say
oh I'm I'm in I'm in Germany
and he has since when
are you in Germany I say since I was
yesterday
that's gonna get one more work why
you are looking for me are you trying to
arrest me should I never come back home
again
um and and then and so I I'm like yeah
I'm worried and he's like okay don't
worry calm down Mrs takanashi it's not
so not so bad you know
uh so I'm like okay okay um
please explain
and
he tells me
[Music]
um or like I think
I think he first asked me like
if if somebody has like access to my
homework so and I'm like hey why
and I said yeah well I guess my brother
is taking care of my cats right now
um while I'm gone
uh
yeah bro sorry what
uh and he says
that that my neighbor uh reported
that my door my entrance door was
completely open and my cats were running
around
um and that I should if my brother is
taking care of my home that he should
learn how to properly close the door
kind of blaming it on my brother
immediately but
um he doesn't know how intelligence
movie is
uh now the thing is my door you know it
it closes like automatically you can
still you can't open it from the outside
but you can from the inside without you
know
but I don't know they were worried and
and instead of just putting the cats
back in and closing the door
uh what I suppose happened is the
neighbor went in and was like hello
anybody there didn't see anyone didn't
hear anyone so they were worried and
called the police and maybe I don't know
what they thought was worth it calling
the police over but maybe because
maybe it looked like I got kidnapped or
so cause the door was but the door
didn't obviously didn't look like it was
broken into the lock wasn't broken or
anything but I don't know maybe they
assumed I was being kidnapped because
there was no sign of me like I don't
know huh
it's not weird it was the door my
brother told me later on it wasn't even
that long that he was gone he was gone
for an hour
and yeah it was just gone for an hour
but they were like super worried
apparently and they tried calling me for
a while and I didn't pick up and I said
sorry well you know I don't I don't like
picking up calls that I don't recognize
the number of
um
and yeah they explained well
everything's fine now the cats they put
them back and actually it was mostly one
cat and the other one was hiding in the
very back of my closet which tells me
they went through my whole apartment
like they saw it all and that makes you
feel that very uncomfortable I don't
know if the neighbors saw everything or
just the police but it feels like kind
of uh
very uncomfortable for me because it
wasn't perfectly clean and and and you
know there's like stuff like
my my YouTube play button somewhere and
I hope they didn't see it like what the
[\h__\h] like who expects the police still
suddenly break into my home huh I can't
prepare for that
I don't know
but I feel like the the YouTube play
buttons are in a place that
kind of like
you know it's not the first thing you
would see when you walk around in my
apartment normally I think but yeah I
felt like very invaded uh yeah very
uncomfortable about Cameron and the
funny thing to me is
um
police guy he said
it was difficult to catch smoothie and I
was just oh oh so you guys your job is
to to catch criminals and you don't have
a problem with that but you struggle
with catching a cat
imagine a police guy running after this
movie and just struggling with catching
her but every every little every single
day you know they catch criminals
so she's
sashies though
oh
officer officer
hey it's her
yeah I think my brother like the officer
asked if I could give him my brother's
number and he would call him and explain
[\h__\h] to him
um maybe scold him man and I gave him my
brother's number and I think
um
my brother told him probably that it
wasn't really him it was my cat
who was able to open doors
and
I don't know if he believed that
but yeah
this movie is capable of such things oh
[\h__\h]
and that was a really exciting way way
to start my day
they said in the end that no problem
we're putting your cats back in
everything's okay and then from then on
I didn't really hear anything more I I
called my brother afterwards I'm like
what the [\h__\h] rotary didn't you learn
from when this happened previously and
he said yeah I forgot
I I will ever close the door double from
now on sorry but this I also didn't
expect this to happen again because
after I came back from Japan this movie
never did this while I was here
weirdly it only happens when I'm gone so
that means movie really misses me isn't
that so cute if you think about it
[Music]
no she's going out to look for me she
only attempts this when when I'm gone
for like but this time she did
immediately like after the first night
we didn't want to be alone she's so
she's so sweet
[Music]
now
it's movie
don't do it anymore but she really
doesn't do it with me
thankfully
[Music]
yeah that was a thing that happened
I don't think I ever got a call from the
police before
isn't that exciting I merely went over
to my friend's room and I told them what
happened
I'm like you know what the [\h__\h] just
happened the police called me they're
like what
nice nice story to tell thank you for
giving me a tangent police
thank you
much appreciated
[Music]
okay
I think the t-shirt is finished
why did it take me so long again
wait huh
[Music]
with you
always in need of a good tangent I am
yes yes yes yes
okay here is the T-shirt they better
make everyone wear it wait I can't type
on my keyboard hello myth first
anniversary
shirt this was a half year anniversary
t-shirt that I drew
and we sold for the half anniversary
our very first merchandise yep drowned
by me
I still have yours oh thank you
eh wait okay no I'm I'm wrong it was
it was Christmas what it was Christmas
merchandise
okay it was Christmas merchandise
sorry but it was close to half year
that's why my mind is so foggy always
mess it up
since
how about you think
okay this is he always says this
hopefully interesting I don't know if
this will work but let's give it a shot
you've done your part
wait how much did you 500 okay okay oh
that's a good decent price
time to show mommy what I'm made of so
who's gonna wear it
with
I want to see people wearing it
immediately
well we're not see it right away because
before like the car I think we saw
pretty quickly let me walk around
see if I find someone wearing it
I mean 500 not not for purchasing this
one t-shirt but for those the rights to
sell it is I think uh actually cheap if
you think about it
yo anybody wearing my t-shirt
what are you saying
I have Bobby it's so about Bobby I
really love you know Bobby is developing
if you happen to see him maybe there is
a job for you over upholstery but I was
there and there was no Bobby
that's weird
flag is awesome really
that's I don't know I was just trying to
make it flaggy
but I don't know if it's really flaggy
that's hairy hmm
hmm
but that's our first piece of the day
foreign
[Music]
but Bobby it's not supposed to be here
as Lance London whatever
[Music]
else
wait especially from this fall when it's
on somebody's body it really looks like
the teacher doesn't it
[Music]
I don't know
you know this good I think this design
is something special my fathers will
totally recognize me now
yay thank you for wearing it yeah
that's so noise
they get it
then get it it's gonna make everyone
wear it I want more people to wear it
anybody else
mmm
[Music]
okay nothing in the trash can
all the word t-shirt will be spared from
the coming Champion uprising
you better wear it
and then I spare it
spare you
you oh
look there's a big advertisement of my
t-shirts
oh I wish I could look at it like from
the front but blazers be cool look good
I love how this game puts your art
everywhere it's so cute
all right I still don't see a Bobby
that's kind of weird maybe it's a bug
even the quest is
a bug and I already did it or I don't
know
[Music]
okay let me check Benjamin maybe
Benjamin has something for me
ah okay now this just Masterpiece I
don't know what you're doing but we just
keep doing it thank you
oh people asking for the tools I'm using
I'm inspiring
oh
okay we gotta get a quest I feel like I
probably uh accepted one
already that I don't remember see daddy
he's still he's still going on about the
stuff
I mean I guess I could ask him to repair
my
broken shelf but
but
do I need that too
move on in the story I wonder because
I I don't draw like that fast to make
use of all of the shelves yeah I got a
[\h__\h] ton of money I know but like I
don't use all the shelves
you have nothing for me
he's just going on about Bobby
let me find real quickly did you ask me
to do something
the person so fast I could never catch
them
you know what maybe Champions are the
way to go for you because chickens there
they are nuts they can't fly away that
fast at least
think
so you should play with chickens I have
a lot
one of them
I'm sure they would be
I play with you
this one really sold the starving artist
idea
you think so how
wait didn't did you want something too
no okay
wait let me go
to you guys Maggie you got something
[Music]
hope
and Punk's appear 42 I never got it
there is no meaning
let's party to the answer to everything
I think so
okay but no Quest
he's gotta watch the movie
no Quest okay how about maybe I'm ready
for you
the equity
oh the apparel said lie ahead one must
possess bigger virtue and some 2000s
see to their name list their hope is to
be late crushed by the countryside I
have
what is this the humble Squier shot law
is here to the to hear the appointments
polite
eh that's me is it wait who
oh is that the Lord find me
Shakespeare's skull viciously stolen by
the villain what
this is the part where you say of course
what is this the humble Squire shut the
law is here to hear the poor man's ploid
that's me
I guess of course
such kindness such or courage now the
heroes aspirant makes his way to the
place of solitude wearing lives alone
Sage there he will train and gain wisdom
in the garden of Tranquility Gardner
yes go to the Garden of twinkle little
can I I don't know can I enter this
house no
Garden
what's he talking about are we in Zelda
game now hmm that's it I was just wait
maybe it's this Garden down here and
yeah there's suddenly an NPC
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
do your Sage order
oh it's just shut the low I see
oh shut the law it has been too long for
I have known you since you were small
runt playing in these gentle Woods
so the low ever since I found you after
that Fateful Encounter With The Forest
fairies I knew you were to return one
day
I remember
and now that your village was rated and
you lost so so much you have finally
come to me
you were once chosen by the spirits now
it is time for you to train
yes train you must Master the mystical
lots of
inscription yes I see you have still
have your late father's wands
are you ready to begin
yes
already you are not already not yet but
you will be this training will test
yourself and it includes a 250 your
service charge eh
didn't you just say I'm not ready
okay we're getting ready for the for the
test by doing a training okay
now your face your final test
take this out of heroism inscribe it
with all your mystical might enchanted
with you a mystical brush perform your
most awe-inspiring inscription
what is that what did you give me
the hilt
what the [\h__\h] is a health
what is this
you like my French accent ah thanks guys
merci beaucoup
oh
um
the sword thingy thanks for the
membership gift
foreign
[Music]
so this will be stuck onto my brush I
guess
not a sword
and I'm supposed to write something onto
it does it really matter
what is this anyway is this like a side
quest
what is this
[Music]
you know
now maybe I'm really designing a sword
but he talked about my me having the
wands still from my grandfather so I'm
thinking it's uh
[Music]
um
he's talking about
my brushes
that's what I'm thinking
I don't know what I'm doing guys I'm
just trying to make it look like gold
wait
see I could do this
no no no
I take it back
I'll take a bite I'll take it back
although that looks very shiny but
[Music]
um
then I have to do all of it like that
because it looks so fuzzy on the edges
[Music]
not sure what I'm doing
sounds I oh yeah should we put like a
nice sparkling
um
that was the perfect shape for an eye
huh I didn't even see it
ironically I
I
ironically I didn't even see it
ironically
oh [\h__\h]
the pun game is so strong
Mamma Mia
[Music]
so let's do
it's kind of scary but
you gotta do what you gotta do
[Music]
not necessarily trying to make it look
like a siren's eye but maybe it does
it looks magical though I think
yeah
I'm not inscribing anything but who
cares
they won't know
[Music]
there we go
the hilt has been finished
the enchantment easy done enchanting
let me see your look oh Marvel lost the
power already it's ah we did it such
power I have not witnessed since
your journey has now begun
the endless scouted by the Lady of the
Lake
you must now travel to the forest lands
in the Southeast finder among the Sandy
Dunes
and the beach and pray she is benevolent
okay okay okay I know where to go
I wonder if that little girl is playing
around alone actually if she's playing
along with this little game
she could
be a costume she's just a girl
oh no okay wait
um
sassy looking mermaid there with a lot
of chests here but I mean who who says a
mermaid can't have a chest hair on
Mustangs right yeah
Lady of the Lake
[Music]
behold to learn you have to look very
much the same who blessed kingpandora
Gone With The Sword of Excalibur
know what you seek but
the lady of Select them and sacrifice
for that is the book of a tour hero
throw your offering into the lake eh
I have a choice between 250 and 500.
I'll go for the expensive one but I
wonder if I would get the same [\h__\h]
hmm
go big
scam
I do have the money let's do it
such a selfless act to stare the heart
and deaths below
the only angle
oh
ah then the other thing is part is the
other part of the sword
Boone from the lake
Excalibur
oh that it was lost in the trenches of
Mariana now in the Far Western the
concrete jungle you'll find a legendary
blacksmith she can add with your blade
the West
over here maybe
no
oh no no no no
taking part in this little theater
are you innocent oh I see someone
you don't look like a black
[Music]
he just turned his head around
completely
foreign
[Music]
are you good how are you doing doing
that you're very flexible huh
me I'm just a regular pumpkin needs
nothing's just about that for sure and
the Smith of Aladdin's box Oh no you're
using an actual person for that
she can make the blood no sweat
Sparks who is spicy on you no
yeah yeah
okay I thought it would just be him
again
I have a quest oh blade you say oh I'd I
got a script for this m I am the
legendary blacksmith you see your
questions most honorable and I sure like
you I shot the law need a blade of
silver to defeat the villain oh wait
that was your line anyways I shall
crafted with faced but materials don't
come cheap they're taking out all my
money from me but okay
I need one thousand zero for this
endeavor oh sweet I get paid 1000 for
this sorry but you heard the script
well done shut alone now it says that I
shall cast the blade that's kind of
stupid now whack it with hammer sure and
it's done not really how a blade is made
to be honest
eh the blade of birkengoth concrets
that's all the paper I got said so this
was weird thanks eh
okay I think I'm really supposed to draw
on top of all of this
am I but what the [\h__\h] am I making what
am I making
her
here's some blood splattered onto my
blade
from all the enemies that I have fought
in the past and will fight in the future
yeah that's all it needs
and then
the handle
should just be a continuation
I suppose this is the handle
[Music]
I want to draw animal girls you keeping
me from doing my important work
what the hell
hmm
[Music]
how will you make up for it huh
I don't know what I'm doing I am so
planless I hope this looks good when
stuck together
[Music]
ah it looks beautiful it does look like
gold I think
[Music]
some kind of shiny structure right
I can flip it over
yeah like just like that not the back
side
okay I got the handle
what are we gonna do now
inconspicuous Punk
I don't know what you want for me a
regular Punk maybe you should eat to the
sage fella okay
foreign
please stick the cardboard and I mean
the the the fancy Metals together for me
excellent the sort of eras is almost
ready it is now up to you to embolden
the blade with a final Enchanted more
make the blade as powerful as you able
[Music]
uh you mean in case I didn't draw on it
yet I did I did
okay
are you certain the inscription is as
strong as you can make it
this will be the it was only chance
chance oh let me guess in their Glory I
dare not touch you vote on yourself ah
yes I did thank you
it's a dangerous blade it must only be
wielded by The Chosen One aka me so be
careful do not touch it on this on the
on the blade part it will hurt you it
will make you
lose explosion and fly away like 150
meters
it has a big impact
[Music]
only painted one side no no no no no no
I mean you couldn't turn around but I
guess you're right
I show you some magic of my own to forge
the parts together I wonder when
Splendor the sort of arrows is complete
now it's a hero
he's fighting Barefoot as we speak in
the criminals of great to zeist
[Music]
is
is she gonna fight
what exactly is he gonna be fighting ah
before
yeah yeah yeah that that store was
called that and the guy too
Goliath hero
of course some actual armor on you wow
Looking ready to fight oh you're gonna
use my sword it's supposed to be for me
travesty
the sort of the heroes now I shall
easily defeat you Belfort oh God ah come
on it's your line now
ah the plot
my immersion is broken the plot isn't
using Rambles such a pointless epic
without the climax
he's carrying
camera
and that's it
what
oh uh a hero will always answer the call
for it perhaps the West stage can guide
you yet again
do I need to make him a shield or so
maybe maybe
it's kind of weird I'm just like
helping him with his stupid games
so into it though oh the champion is
lost
I'm sure you're here for a good cause
now return to the hero where the battle
must commence
but what what did me coming to you help
me now
I Need a Hero
you gotta be strong
help
no that's the same
am I am I bugged
you're saying the same thing
[Music]
hmm
you're saying go back to the stage right
[\h__\h] it's a sage
who's guiding us
huh that's a rich guy
okay okay
a villain the villain
what did he do besides being rich
[Music]
ah
I have no idea what this lunatic is
talking about he just gave me a note and
yelled action
rumors that spark lady got paid in
Frozen just for reading off a paper is
it true no no no 500 or is that so I'll
take your word for it but you better not
be tricking me
yes no no I'm not gonna spend a thousand
bucks for some Child's Play anyway I'm
not one for turning down money but I
better be the one who gets paid the most
ah okay then 501 Euro should do the
trick
very well I'm ready to read my lines
could you let the sorry sobbing Knight
over there no
he's right there he knows now I think
so Travis d uh so now knife
well he pretends not to be a true what
but true with the end of walnuts we have
revealed his true nature oh God
the villain stands in shock in the face
of the sword of the heroes now waste my
final plow taste Blues nah villain is
brought low and now I hold the skull
sufficiently stolen but what is this
about for drugs for my side I too will
perish here at this the hands of Belfort
come closer closer the day it has been
won by my ends but do not Fork it I
could not have done it without the help
of dear shuttle and now Texas is called
return it to the rightful owner and let
all know what came to pass this day now
go shut the law
I go I shall go with the skull in my
hand
to share and spread the message of what
happened on this Holy Land
well who am I going back to not the sage
right
and what
well I think I was going up
oh no to you
you have been successful wondrous news I
never doubted your abilities for one
beat now hurry up the witches must have
their Justice oh okay
he gave me a nice comment on it but I
think I'm going up
to him
lunch land core
[Music]
ah
oh my skull that I would have never seen
my school once more thank you it's a
hero visual grief from this day to the
end of days
got this virtual performance has been
astounding success not only did it
manage to grip the minds and odds of its
Spectators but it also made the viewer
into paying a participant into a paying
participant yeah me and you guys
without them ever realizing it a blah
blah blah blah
well believe it's time for me to finally
move all these non-necessary items
now we can pass
for me to be or wherever not be here at
you
but
what is here for me to see
a stage cute
only the station May flick the switch
what with the stagehand
are you gonna like play some place for
me up here Le pretty Globe cute
I am making full pot to play as the
leading actor naturally
I am me but not always I am sometimes
the soonest the villain that's called it
villain sometimes both Universe
yet one that's the common Mantra Among
Us classical trained
I don't know what the hell you're
talking about but
is there anything I can do up here
oh it goes even higher
Charles this is Charles
are you related to the royal family oh
my God who is this
it tastes like
still so much more to see and this is
what
is this
shop
what tools
expensive too
Michelangelo's metal point
the legend goes that Michelangelo use
did this in many of his sketches but it
looks basically like the sponge
okay the trees look kind of cool but
now this is just
I've seen exactly the same
pattern on a cheaper tool down in the
other shop of Benjamin
I'm Margaret that well this this is a
graveyard Stone
ancient squirrel but maybe if I use
these they will have extra value gold
and silk
really really golden silk
um
[Music]
interesting very valuable in itself I
wonder if I purchased this and then just
sell it without painting on it would I
be able to get some more out of it would
I be able to win something
oh
but yeah maybe I should paint my
masterpiece on one of these
I say we pop we buy the golden silk
canvas I wonder how big it is
paint on but this but this is [\h__\h]
but ah Rob boss
Rob boss's favorite accident Mark ah
the happy tree stump okay I mean
it does Rob boss really use this for his
trees does he use a tree shaped sponge
that's actually a genius
that's a genius thing to do if he does
that
so no yeah he doesn't does he but bullet
would be it looks like it could work
pretty well
I don't know when I'll be drawing trees
but I got I got money
send home
does this work oh I could switch it out
we got a new tool
wow really expensive shop in here let me
talk to Adrianne
oh it's your shop have you visited my
luxury luxurious Art Shop yet my
collection is most impressive if I may
still say so myself
I see that the finest art supplies find
their way into the most delicate
Artisans and so my family has done for
centuries even before we left our
homeland of Pennsylvania
exactly how I would pronounce it when I
read
Pennsylvania
you funny one
to imagine wait there's even more
oh my God
what is
Hillcrest well it's really muddy here
oh the car is so stuck what the [\h__\h]
it looks like it could go even further
though possibly
wowzers
wow
what is this magical fancy land
what a beautiful garden can we buy this
place oh I wonder that would be crazy
can we Chantelle does it come with you
I had lunch with Picasso once he said he
loved my macarons
oh I am just your standard lover of art
living in my humble Chateau you live in
here some colors the elite and well they
wouldn't be wrong
keep most of our art collection in the
museum wouldn't wanted to get devalued
by gawking eyes
foreign
I feel like eventually there should be
quests here
but maybe I'm not ready to progress
yet
to receive such quests
but very interesting well it's so far I
need a bicycle or so to
get through this place at this point
faster because he's really slow
my dude is really slow
there is a bicycle
are you gonna give this to me actually
[Music]
look at this that is that is uh the
meatball the Swedish Swedish meatballs
with lingamberry Jam you get it yo I
want to eat that right now
[Music]
you need to address me as Prince after
all I am Swedish royalty
I am Prince of Sweden I love the Deep
gem London forest and Elks and other
things you'd expect from a man of my
stature
Angie named
is that it that's all you're gonna tell
me and I don't want to give me quests
yet
[Music]
yo
it's cool though we got a new area big
ass new area
okay let's see who can give us a job
actually wait
how do we get in here
Museum okay
who goes there
[Music]
oh yeah so how do we get a ticket we get
well we can buy it no you don't of
course not
of course not I am again my job is to
keep you outside and I'll tell you how
to get inside don't you have any allies
you can ask
no I don't remember what
yeah I learned how to pronounce it
properly I guess like at least how to
pronounce it in Swedish
but in in German we do say cut Bola to
it
the plans for the park
you I hope you have nothing to do with
that accusation objective
okay no Quest
did I break the game they used to like
throw so many quests at me
and now
what about you you still haven't really
given me a quest to help you
[Music]
um
it's all tax write-off okay I heard that
before
has anyone finished this game before
oh wait this guy ever talked to him
now I find you it's like
one looks there and you look so
unnoticeable that's so sad actually
Bobby I was looking for you
oh perhaps you were the talent I need
time for old Bobby to embark on a new
Venture I'm sure I have a safe bet going
I just need a good product designer
seems like you've done a good job so far
if you're helping me I can pay you 750
okay for what
make an appealing design for this paper
shredder X
we keep on having to paint on things
that are not normal canvases now
wait what did he say in the end
too small to see him yeah he's pretty
small
paper shredder
why why
I'm gonna draw the paper shredder
it's cute though look how it's stuck on
my over here on my I a lion weasel
I'm not really in the mood
all right
okay okay okay okay okay
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I paint the top too
oh you can even paint the ah
[Music]
awesome
um
okay first
we painted all white
foreign
to work with
I think we got it covered now what do we
do with this
what do I do with this
[Music]
um
turn it into the house a mini cave
yeah you guys genius
surround I want to try and tell this on
my on my stickers
sticker
[Music]
can I find it
I stuck it onto my fridge so I can't see
it from here
I found it okay this will be inspiration
more or less
um
first of all
let's paint the top
hmm
okay
and oh
kfb like outside of the store
really stands out a lot doesn't it
it's such a bright red color
[Music]
we kind of stand out because
we are boldly
trying to place ourselves at the number
one spot for
fast food restaurants in this world you
gotta be bold we gotta be bright like
ketchup yeah I guess so
okay I was hoping that this wouldn't
happen but okay
[Music]
um
okay
it's it's difficult it's kind of messy
all right all right
and where is the front I want these look
like Windows huh this could be the
entrance Door
did you guys see while I was gone
yesterday I uploaded the
K of B101 usual room episode
I saw your guys's feedback
I wasn't able to be there for the
premiere but I hope you guys made it at
least some of you
I saw you guys really enjoyed it right
[Music]
asked me to like record in a Gladys
voice like try to copy what she says but
he also put like a effect a voice effect
on my voice on top of it I feel like I
sound exactly like Gladys is like pretty
much
pretty much non-recognizable does it
sound like me
smile it sounded exactly like Gladys
which is a good thing
um
you did great thank you it was great
pretty close you sound a lot like her
right very close to the glass right
yo
hey
I'm very very happy to hear that thank
you
it was it was fun impersonating Gladys
and cow carrot put so much work into the
editing again Sasuke
yo I
I actually wait as a merchandise I would
totally want this Shredder
no like in my home
not even us like selling it to everybody
but just for my personal use just for me
special edition
wouldn't that be so cute
yo
you need
kfp pencil sharpener
that could also be that yeah or just a
normal trash can
could be anything with this design
anything that's like box shaped
hell yeah
[Music]
I'm gonna make this orange for some
reason
because it stands out to me
I'm glad
a door
[Music]
it's totally a door
totally
and there's me waiting behind it
waiting to hire you
welcome to kfp
[Music]
kpf what is that
sorry I made a mistake I forgot what our
place was called
kpf kfp
iano's pretty friends
camping
[Music]
what else what else what else ah
what else what did I write uh
could happen on the first day ah the
carving oh Mama Mia
Mamma Mia
on the first day of Christmas
my true love sent to me
uh
when the like convention day was over
the day was pretty nice but it was
pretty sunny so very enjoyable
um I was basically just you know
chilling at the convention uh grounds
all day just talking to friends really
not doing much
uh but it was really a lot of fun no no
nonetheless
and then uh at the end of the day we
were gonna go uh
find some more friends in a restaurant
they made a reservation so uh we were
gonna go find them there and have dinner
together in the evening
so
me and my friends my driver friend we
went to the car and the thing is they
were like parking spots on a huge field
of grass yeah
um
and you could see like the the kind of
the entrance AKA exit of it was
extremely muddy had like this huge like
wobbly mud rides at the hill
that was quite Troublesome to drive over
my friend's car is like a little bit
lower than other cars just slightly
lower
um so that's already a little bit of a
problem
um but it's really only like a stretch
of like
five meters or so where it's like really
bad and the rest is just really tall
grass
uh but the the muddy part is like super
wobbly and rumbly
I don't remember what it says on this
poster but I will write
what I think it says wait or
hiring
cute
and then the other poster there
yeah so uh when we first parked it we
kind of had to park there because there
there was like a million parking spaces
there and the other ones which were like
on normal pavement were all taken and we
arrived like pretty late so yeah there
was no way for us to get a normal
parking space we had to join the the
grass parking space
and so when we first parked there in
like the noon time when we arrived it
was already very muddy oh but we like
drove really carefully on the side of it
where it looked a little bit more
um straight straightened out
so
it was somewhat okay but like we already
had experience with it and we knew to be
careful there or our drivers supposedly
knew it
now on the evening our driver was like
in a really good mood
um because I guess it was just a nice
day so when he's in a good mood he gets
like really excited and
just a little bit I have to say ahead of
himself
and so he starts driving out the field
and he goes on to the muddy part and
instead of just driving on the side of
it where it's a bit more straightened
out he recklessly goes diagonally
through it while people around the car
are like yelling at him like ah you
should you should go to the side you
should go to the side it's super wobbly
be careful be careful
and he just I don't know he's like
laughing and thinking it's all fun and
games yeah
so
then he ends up getting stuck in it
um
so there's like a few bystanders who run
over to us
uh and then like kind of push him uh to
drive back they pushed the car and we
drive back a little bit and then they
push it from the other side and then you
know they keep on pushing us Instant
Karma yeah wow wow wow
[Music]
um
it's really nice of them to push us it
was like Free People
uh then eventually we were able to drive
out of it after they kept on pushing us
and we drove up the little Hill a couple
of meters and then after
that I think there was yeah some normal
street like a little bit of a Pavement
and immediately we noticed that the car
was making some really concerning noises
um
like
rattling noises
and I don't know much about cars
but
um the driver he immediately recognized
it as a very concerning sound
and so he's like starting to freak out
like oh my God I broke my car it's over
we cannot drive anywhere we can't drive
to dinner we can't drive back to the
hotel we can't drive maybe back to
Austria either I don't know what to do
like I need to have my car repaired but
but oh no I don't I don't have money for
it I don't even know like what we're in
Germany what am I supposed to do like
he's freaking out okay and I'm like I
don't know [\h__\h] about cars like is it
really that bad and [\h__\h] but I had
another friend with a car
um
who actually just like like walked us
over to our car and then left to say
goodbye like for the day and I called my
other friend like please come back we
reveal car maybe possibly because our
car apparently just broke down and we
don't know if we can you know go
anywhere so it would be nice if you were
there and you could like maybe get us
back to our hotel at least or so yeah
um
okay I'll leave it at this
oh cute very cute
I think you'll like it so the friend
comes back and but the fascinating thing
oh he likes it
he made a billboard a huge ad noise
I just need you to make it pop I'll hang
tight here with your payments it's
complete
go and make it pop what do you mean
let me go and make it pop and then I'll
get my payment
oh it's there heavy duty Shredder
[Music]
oh oh man
yeah hi chunky monkey
I have to do this too
can I
I can't draw on top of the Shredder okay
you want to eat the pan
she likes the pen she really likes my
pen
kfp Ed oh I also can't draw on top of
the writing huh okay
foreign
okay pop a donkey monkey you're on my
table you want to drink out of my glass
no no you're not allowed to no no
no hi baby
hi baby pen pineapple Apple pen those
are good aren't they
[Music]
oh she's so cute why are you here I'm
streaming
now she's in front of my camera
ah there you go she's past it she's
behind my tablet she's wandering around
actually let me turn on the light really
quickly it's getting dark
[Music]
um
oh wait
my headphones are completely Tangled in
the chair what are you doing huh
she's cuddling she really likes this
plastic bag with some chocolate in it
like the edge of the plastic bag she
likes to rub her face on it
because it's kind of
Sharp
what are you doing
hey you want to lay down I'm streaming
normally you don't like that oh she's
showing me her belly is asking for belly
rubs
and purring loudly
oh she's right in front of my monitor
cute
yeah
oh she's like
shaped like a castle
rap belly okay well while I'm doing this
let me tell you the rest of the story
so my my friend is freaking out I am
trying to be the calm one okay sorry she
did that
and I had this thing selected
um
yeah
my friend is freaking out I'm calling my
other friend just in case we can't go
anywhere because the people are waiting
for us already in the restaurant
and so on and like yeah they're freaking
out he's freaking out and um the thing
is one of the people who pushed our car
uh he runs over to us notices that
something's going on he's like what's
what's your real Cardinal and yeah my
friend
tells them I can't drive it anymore
it's broken
and he panicly describes to him what
happened what what's his hearing and all
that and then he's do you know what the
guy one of the people who pushed our car
said
oh
um I can take a look at it if you want
I'm I'm actually a mechanic a car
mechanic
[Music]
is it that the one person who is there
is a car mechanic [\h__\h] odds right I
was like freaking out about that that's
like some freaking Miracle what
what are the odds
so he's like just wait a moment let me
change my shirt really quickly because
he was actually also you know he had the
parking space there too and he was
changing out of Cosplay I guess and then
um changing into some clean clothes and
all that to then leave as well but then
he changes really quickly because he was
gonna get under the car and he said oh
let me check what I have with me in my
car and and and and yeah then he comes
back in a minute no half a minute later
to our car and he just really like a car
mechanic
crawls under our car
and takes a look at it and she spends
like maybe two minutes maximum under it
Meanwhile my other friend
um came back card with MVP for real in
the month no at this point we're out of
the mud but I mean still the ground
dirty
um my other friend came back she's
looking at it I'm explaining my other
friend what's going on that I don't know
if the car is gonna work again but we'll
see I guess stop chunkers stop pushing
buttons on my keyboard [\h__\h]
yeah it's crazy so he looks at the car
he comes out of the bottom of the car
and he says I fixed it
he tells us he explains this everything
well mostly to my friends to the driver
because it doesn't really matter to me
but so if I understand correctly let me
try to re-re
Yeah so basically car yeah
undercut
chunky monkey I need to draw something
let me
let me play this game
there you go
um he said that under the car there's
something
that's kind of some kind of plate that's
kind of u-shaped probably like this and
that there's like several screws
holding it onto the car and this plate
is supposed to hold like
um the Heat
inside the car or so uh and keeps it
like from burning or so
and so while the car was being like
pushed around in the u-shaped get me
Shaped
well it was being pushed around in the
mud
um a heat shield yeah
some screws got ripped out completely
and then the the plate yeah on the car
it just curled and that's what we were
hearing on the ground
making noises
and keeping that open of course is
dangerous but since it was only a fruit
screws he was able to like bunk bunk
bunk push it back into its original
straight uh
shape
and said that even without these couple
of screws you will be fine for now
you should be able to drive normally and
um
you may not really need to go to a
mechanic proper mechanic either he
offered us to you know go to his thingy
but you know there's a vacation another
another
um
holidays today and it was weekend and
you know we couldn't have time wise we
couldn't have we had to get home anyway
but you said it's fine we can drive
normally even high speeds and explained
everything and we were really really uh
relieved to hear that we're so really
pretty odds that is so
so fascinating I was like I was going
crazy over the fact that this just
happened so I um I I was like you guys
you you too you need to like exchange
contact numbers and all that because
what just happened is a miracle and that
was extremely kind of this chat to do
this for free
and just helped so nicely with such a
sweet attitude this is a miracle you
have to be connected for Life yeah
because without him we would have been
[\h__\h] so I I pushed them to exchange uh
like contact information and and
um
uh
then we went away and we were pretty
late to the dinner but uh it was all
right we arrived and we had a fun story
to tell
yeah
quite crazy the car really was fine but
even afterwards it was still like making
some noises like when we were
um breaking using the break for example
but drivers driver [\h__\h] said that is
probably just the rest of the dirt stuck
in the brakes and that shouldn't be an
issue
um
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] what
just
what
you
need
[Music]
right
I would agree with that it looks so
sparkly
making it pop
um
we did end up getting back home to
Austria safely even after a long hour
ride so
dad was such a big save I feel like if
we if this guy wasn't there in that
moment thanks for the memberships thank
you thank you 20. thank you if this guy
wasn't around that moment
we would have been like
Bamboozled like what the hell do we do
like I wouldn't know he was panicking
too I thought maybe there must be like
um with his car insurance maybe it's
like maybe it should also work in in
Germany I don't know I don't know but
there must have been some way of finding
a solution but still we were like
freaking out so
especially him and I was also worried
can I can I get back oh yeah I I
probably
weren't the only austrians at the
convention I knew some other austrians
who went to the convention with the car
and they probably would have still had a
space in their car for me but what about
my friends
I would take it home
yeah that was they surely would have
been something but yeah as he also said
that he didn't have
um
the funds for it really
because it could cost a lot and who
knows how fast they would be able to fix
it maybe it would have taken them some
time and yeah
so it was such a miracle and I met this
I saw this person again
exactly yeah that's crazy I saw this
person again the next day yeah
at the convention and I just threw a lot
of chocolate on him I was like thank you
so much again for saving us the other
day everything went fine afterwards yeah
I know I know what's what's what what
what
um
as thank you thank you for everything
you're our savior
yeah I threw chocolate at him look
there's like
me
me for my things
hey
it's definitely popping now
chunky monkey
it's done I think it should sell
a sturdy message for all to feel
comforted by well done
[Music]
so now finally hopefully we can progress
you guys got anything new for me
probably not
they have speech bubbles
um popping up when
[Music]
when there's something new
can I actually go in here no
oh I went in there a little bit
but yeah crazy right like
what
I still can't get over how crazy that is
what a freaking miracle
tonight
and so sweet to like offer your help and
now it's just like look the other way
and just mind your own business
because I feel like a lot of people
even even when they're in a position
where they could maybe help someone most
of the time
what happens is that they ignore
their surroundings and just think about
themselves
just kind of shut
I'll off everything around them
wait a second
my my cat did something is it F12 to fix
it
f11 she she full windowed my OBS there
we go
I'll fix it
true true
or they do it expecting something to
change exactly yeah this guy didn't even
expect anything but I felt so bad I I
mean it wasn't my car that was fixed so
I I but I still wanted to you know
show my appreciation so
I gave some
some um
chocolate
this is so sweet such a
kind-hearted gesture
okay maybe now because nobody is like
trying to give me a quest here maybe now
if we go up
we get a quest Maybe
[Music]
um
or we talk to Benjamin again I don't
know
let's see maybe fix the Shelf I wonder
if we have to do that in order to
um proceed in the story
I might just do that I guess
and then Charles isn't talking to me
okay
not because of cute cosplay girls in the
car I was looking so cute anymore
I was looking like a mess after a long
day at the convention
there were no such cute girls
in the car
oh well well well
doing the right thing is its own reward
the poor surface and
I've been good so we shall do more good
all right George help me repairs
it's my broken shelf how much was it
2050 okay
I have I have so much [\h__\h] money
[Laughter]
screwed in a good and professional way
would you look at that it seems to be it
seems that everything is ah everything
is repaired
if you have to travel on the road
Perhaps it is tension she'll give you
chocolates
yeah I had some uh Kit Kats from Japan
like I bought a lot of uh uh I love
kitkats from like different fancy
flavors while I was in Japan
thinking that I would surely give it to
someone
there it is fixed
I would surely give it to someone
as like a souvenir but I didn't really
give it to anyone and I didn't want to
eat it on my own so
I brought it them all to the convention
and just gave it to a lot of people
what's the landlord is so
pothole Quest
even what if I were to paint
nothing happens
is my game bugged forever
[Music]
then him just talking about this but
this has been fixed for like forever
okay let me walk around again see what
happens
otherwise we'll just paint something on
our own
and I'll figure out if my game is bugged
or like if this is it and I did it all
but how do we get the ticket
did you see any whole live cosplayers in
the convention
um
on Saturday or Sunday no one on Sunday I
saw
a very tall lanky uh male lapless
yeah that was funny
that's all I saw though sadly
yeah Yamada
Yamada that's right your mother
I saw um I said two of my friends not
one of my one of my friends
that's so close really more of an
acquaintance she with her friend
together cosplayed like uh niji sanjido
like gender bender uh uh two of the guys
from Ninja Sanji
but like a female version
yeah
actually
uh one of the people who were
you know with me driving in the car
the girlfriend
she I think she said she watches very
rarely
did you send you guys
I think what she said
doesn't watch me though
my friends will watch me actually I'll
be
uh watches
some stuff with me sometimes I think
I think and BFF also a little bit
but this other my other couple friends
those two they don't really watch what I
do which is totally fine I mean I stream
so much like but I may have completely
changed the opinion of you know whether
or not they should be watching my my
streams or not because
um
on the drive back it was a long long
many hour drive through the night
and
uh the girlfriend she's fell asleep
immediately
I was also really really tired but I
know you gotta keep the driver awake and
he was worried about getting tired too
and he said we would probably have to
take some breaks during this drive
because
um well we're all tired and it's late so
we're gonna get home even later because
of that
and I was hoping for that not to happen
but I was okay with it I mean if it
happens it happens
but the thing is like my brother was
waiting for me at home
uh until
I came home because I needed someone to
open the door for me because he had my
keys he was taking care of the kitty
cats remember
okay we're gonna draw something on our
own now
so what's giving me a quest
that is
um so and then because of that and me
being the only one there to entertain
the driver even though I was really
tired I was like oh yes okay I'm gonna
do that slapping my cheeks trying to get
myself awake
I took two sips of of uh his Monster
Energy drink
only two because I knew that would be
enough and then I started talking like a
freaking waterfall
I was Unstoppable
we talked about everything we talked
about
um thought about my job a little bit we
talked about uh you know struggles of a
streamer we talked about my family my
mom and all that we talked about uh
Investments we talked about possibly
buying uh uh apartment or house from me
you know I I wanted to do that I talked
about that talked about tears who talked
about ttrpgs the Dungeons and Dragons
talked about movies talked about talked
about Charmed and killer girls
and found out that he liked it because
and remembered a lot of it because he
has a sister and kind of came from that
talked about so much I and and he
and he happy and fascinated and praised
me so much that I was so good at
endlessly tangenting and tangenting and
keeping him awake and entertained so
much that in a
45 hours right he didn't need a single
break
and was constantly awake and happy and
entertained yeah and engaged
and I was like well it's my it's
literally my job this is what I do I
extreme and talk for hours and hours it
is my specialty after all
oh
maybe we have to paint the must be let
me one second I'll just talk to Benjamin
for a second
just one second let's see what he has to
say
um
yeah so thanks to me check the building
to the left you mean this one
I want to give him the Masterpiece yet
though because I worry that it means
that the game ends
when you put the Masterpiece into the
into the museum but I don't even have a
ticket yet
I always gotta start watching the
streams yeah that's what I'm thinking
like now he's kind of convinced he also
loves Dungeons and Dragons so um I told
him that we actually uh have this ttrpg
and we're gonna continue it this week
um so he was really interested in that
too he was like oh maybe I'll watch you
stream for once
because he's uh interested in that yeah
told him we're just ending it but yeah
you gotta start from the beginning
wait so does anyone have an idea should
I really just go for the Masterpiece
does the game not end when I do that
oh yeah this week I mean I'm gonna put
out my schedule and Kelly should be
putting it out too
so
it will be on there
I think it's on Friday
Friday 10 p.m my time
Benjamin gives you a ticket after given
Masterpiece
um okay
okay then I I guess I'll just
no no shut up
if I agree I'll give you a ticket to the
men's Museum to meet the curator okay I
just don't want the game to end yet
what's with all the stuff up there that
we just discovered are they not like
can we is that after we get the
Masterpiece and all that afterwards
that's supposed to be done afterwards
hmm
can save it for next time no no I'll
draw something now wow I wish it was a
big canvas but okay it's like a medium
size
Cali we've had we'll have a stable
connection from her parents home so no
worries ah
I saw she has like a lot of troubles
with her internet Tuesdays
so
she found the solution for that for
tooth fairy RPG at least
okay
okay well done
um
I think for the Masterpiece I know what
to draw
I think I know
to her parents but okay okay
well
the Masterpiece hey but is it is it easy
to cut the masterpiece
um
let me exchange romantic
I think as long as I have a lot of hours
in it
a lot of minutes I guess
um should be okay
okay
[Music]
actually what do I want
um
whatever I don't know
actually it didn't matter that much
[Music]
salad no no no
no no no
Look Away guys look away you shouldn't
be seeing a masterpiece before its final
State it's basically you know like
seeing a bride before the wedding
[Music]
but wait the thing is with the Spokane
is if you draw
over it you can't there's no eraser
so I should plan ahead how much of the
cameras I want to cover because I want
to keep some of the gold obviously
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] that's already small
can you recognize ah
this shape
oh
I think it is
already clear as they
so how you say it probably not
[Music]
coming
oh the cutest of them all
that is her I'm just gonna like
have her bounce prawns
foreign
over the
whole
family my brother was still awake when I
finally got
back
and I was so tired man
I was just so tired all that
excitement and very much exhaustion
wasn't exhausting I almost wanted to
take today off too you know
almost
but I felt like I
couldn't
you guys would be
too disappointed what the [\h__\h] is with
you white face kiwawa
why is your face so wide
your eyes not supposed to be that far
away
[Music]
to
I was uh actually kind of surprised
this year
um this is my first convention this year
I think
last year I uh
uh the last three years I guess or no
last two years or so
I've conventions in Germany and Austria
and so on
well I saw mostly in terms of Cosplay
was a game of the initials GI
right
everywhere everywhere and I think that's
not only in Europe like that
um
[Music]
and and this convention actually I think
uh it like went down a little bit
I I was surprised to see actually
a couple of actually a group of Arc
Knights cosplayers and I got really
excited
and besides that it was like
an interesting mix oh no I mean I also
didn't walk around that much
um
to see that much
but
it felt like to me at least things were
getting like a little bit more mixed now
I like to see variety at conventions
um
thank you
she's coming for your croissants
hide them
it's gonna pounce on your kung fu
oh yeah even even I even taught the
croissant meme to my driver during those
hours in the night
oh yeah and
that was you also didn't even turn on
the music and there was no need for
music
my tangents were plenty entertaining
I'm like a podcast that you can turn on
in the car
laughs
but I also enjoyed just not having music
on Just Just
in car rides like okay I wasn't enjoying
like during the day if it's the day
time ride just singing along to music
loudly but in the night
yo you need to have an actual
conversation to not fall asleep
um
yeah
tangento
and until music is nice to vibe to what
you talk to yeah yeah when you when you
have confidence in staying awake I guess
yeah
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
oh
one thousand six of what
50 hours one what
where from
[Music]
what what what
are you not from Germany
you probably told me before but are you
not what are you not from Germany
why would you drive
where did you drive
50 hours to
huh wait you you got you got me really
curious now North Germany to West they
are together
ah to South and back
ah nerve to West to South and then back
oh you basically visited Old Germany in
one go
hmm
oh my pen my pen
all right my pen
[Music]
you
know
here we go now that's a bit better
ooVoo
and
froaki Wawa just so happens to have the
same eye color as me that doesn't mean
that she's me
not at all no no no no no no no no no
even though a lot of my friends were
you know not coming with us and missing
from our group
I was I had I had a lot of fun I met
plenty of other people at the cone
and friends I haven't seen in a long
time again and all that
so
I'm really glad
that I went
and the weather was good too
there was no rain I experienced no rain
really nice
a good
kickstart
to the convention season
[Music]
I'm glad you enjoyed it so much yeah
me too me too thank you guys for letting
me have some off time you know
it's not quite a vacation at all because
I got uh I was pretty exhausted from it
I also got a big sunburn
it wasn't even like hot but you know I
underestimated the sun I suppose
I got a strong burn it's burning it's
pretty and it's not it's
I guess I got it like
a little bit but where I have it it's
pretty strong
[Music]
I don't know where I have my aftergone
do I have ultrason
[Music]
run out
of exploration probably but
when is it
[Music]
um try not for a long time I wonder if I
still have it
sunscreen does don't know about
afternoon
[Music]
because mine if I still have it it
should be a couple of years old
from from before Holo
to buy a new one
okay let's make you green froggy Wawa
is that the red green
um
maybe we should be a bit more bright
green she's green
[Music]
I also was thinking about which
conventions to go to
with my friends
for the rest of the year and I got some
ideas
I've got some ideas
unfortunately I can't go to docomo this
year as you guys know
because I will be in Japan
at the time
yeah
too bad
because I always like docomo
Carefree who has been there will know
but they have like this huge Garden huge
Park area that you can chill in
and you meet so many people it's just so
much fun
[Music]
this year
this year it's not happening for me hmm
[Music]
it do be like that sometimes
gotta make sacrifices
I'm ready to make sacrifices for this
job
[Music]
honestly I mean
it's worth it so
that kfp will attend a new Stead
alright you better have a lot of fun
for me
oh wait Frankie Wallace thingy doesn't
look like that
actually
it's just like this
[Music]
totally convincing eyes the ones down
there are fake
don't trust him
just because they look somewhat cute
trust him
[Music]
she's trying to deceive you
cute
oopsie
I want a frog
s frogs are cute
do we have a lighter pink no
hmm
wait
I'll get some pink for her cheeks in the
moment
um
[Music]
and frog
yeah I forgive her for the crimes
probably that's why the police has an
eye on me because of the crimes that she
has committed
I'm on their Raider because of her they
think I'm her
it's okay I will cover for you for now
but you better be nice to me in exchange
and not try to overtake
again
we wish you
sounds like fun I wish I was kfp
I wish I wish I was kfp and could be
part of the fun
oh man
[Music]
wait I just realized I'm drawing my
masterpiece
this is my masterpiece
[Music]
this is my this is my masterpiece
I'm taking this game seriously totally
I'm taking very seriously
[Music]
don't misunderstand
okay
speaking of art it seems like my new art
hashtag has pretty much fixed the
problem that we had
so
you don't have to look at endless
amounts of spam anymore when going for
the art hashtag
we have repels the evil guys we've done
it
at least for now
for sure what color was the ribbon
turquoise right because my ribbon nose
with turquoise
[Music]
ah the description I I got rid of it for
one stream but I guess yeah because I
copy pasted this one
I have it in there again
I am it
oh well oh wow
okay
[Music]
okay let me get something with a pink
color I'll get rid of this one oh my God
this one I've been pretty pastel
should be
have something
yeah okay just gonna give her a little
bit of a blush
[Music]
okay
but is this really okay to put as my
masterpiece
hmm
[Music]
I feel
I feel like I'm messing with them
I've drawn some amazing things but yeah
it's a masterpiece really you think so
you really think so
how much would you pay for this then
because the Masterpiece you know it
should motivate people to pay incredible
amounts of money
[Music]
I don't know if this really
if it makes you feel like that
[Music]
it's a gun
not her pink one
this is a real one
[Music]
I'm gonna make it worth more
by drawing money on it
hopefully this will inspire you
pay more for it or like yeah
are they gonna try to buy my masterpiece
I wonder
[Music]
this is what money looks like right
yeah I think so not exactly what Euros
look like and the problem is we are in a
setting where euros
is what we're paying with but oh well
that should be good enough though all
right I shall title this
my masterpiece
will he accept it
is there any criteria
maybe a bit more tools like how about
how about I use a little bit of my spray
can
here and a little bit here oh
it messes with the gold
[Music]
Chow butter sponge this sponge can get
pretty small
oh
the [\h__\h]
[Music]
what [\h__\h] well
I didn't expect the brush to do that
[Music]
okay it's ready I deciding fitting for
the Masterpiece at 107 on the end
but you're donating in Europe none of
this makes sense
you're saying you're building in Yen
you're actually bidding in Euro I know
the painting there's a US dollar hmm
getting mixed signals here
all right it's time
to offer this as my masterpiece I guess
I mean the criteria should be met I
think I spent time on it I spent
good materials on it
I'm done
oh monkey
what a I can't you just so beautiful
here's the ticket to the museum
when you meet the cute wait could I have
literally given him
a [\h__\h] scribble
would he have taking it
don't look him in the eyes many have
made that mistake promise you'll find me
later and tell me how it all went down
[Music]
Museum time
yeah
probably but let's not ruin the moment
it will just be so satisfying to see my
painting in the museum right it'll feel
extra special
who goes there
it doesn't make you a thousand dollars
for a painting of a bucket of kfp thank
you
I keep ticket it's an older ticket but
it checks out okay
why'd you have to say that
cool Gates we're walking up the stairs
to our
faithful
place
oh
the stairs they're not quite golden but
they have some golden elements on it
very fancy is that the curator
oh this place is big
I like the way they make grass look in
this game
it's very properly trimmed
unlike my deck
[Music]
Natalie Dormer resemble in oh damn it I
missed my opportunity I can still do it
though it might just not be in the
museum afterwards
a
oh my God what
they have all the real famous ones and
mine is gonna be there
I can just put it there
the final empty slot in the Museum of
the masses oh no I can't
okay
he's looking at me just don't look don't
look back don't look back
well only available for a few
you sure if you show me something I
wanted to be
expectations
is that what you got
yeah your soul should be reflected in
this piece of art
it should breathe blood and sweat and
tears
I have shed Blood and Tears
and sweats because of Fergie Wawa
don't know if it's reflected in the
painting but there is the history
it does
and show me you better not waste my time
heck
yeah
okay
take it
Moment of Truth
a very nice printing worth about
no
568 it will be guaranteed to spot that
he's gonna say and like the trash can
also I don't know
[Music]
what an insult to froggy wow wait is
this scripted is this scream that's
I mean okay
all right
that's fine I guess I shall draw Natalie
Dormer after all or me as and Berlin who
knows we'll see
the local flea market good luck with
that uh true Waters here in my museum I
loved by the most prestigious critics
you can find did you really think except
just any drugs simply because it's like
by one man of a struggling art supply
shop
my art is plastered all over the city
first of all so it's not liked just by
one guy and also let me just say
Benjamin do not underestimate Benjamin
yet his opinion is worth so much more
and in the end what makes your opinion
so much more with Benjamin's opinion ah
tell it to me tell it to me straight to
my face and then let's see actually you
know what don't tell Tomatoes sell to
Benjamin yeah do you have the courage to
say it's a Benjamin
did we get one guy did Benjamin one guy
me into making me think that my painting
is enough when even I was doubting it
lovable now if you don't mind I have a
museum to create wait did you just look
me in your eyes
guess I did because [\h__\h] you
yeah okay so it doesn't just end there I
thought it was end there that's why I
never like
went for it
but I wonder if it's scripted though
if there was no other way
if you have to fail at once
oh sorry you look like me I wasn't
confusing
Benjamin Benjamin
milk me I
had more out man
must be our new Superstar tell me did he
love your painting
ah that's fantastic it is
oh you didn't like it I'm so sorry
possible though I don't know how to help
you anymore that's why I want to watch
movie my critics what
you [\h__\h] the critics
not to help you anymore I'm just a
simple shopkeeper what do I do no but do
I know about realizing dreams who am I
pulling no Benjamin don't be sad I'm so
happy you believe in me
hmm unless unless
it might be a foolish idea but no no no
we shouldn't I just realized I haven't
had the sound of the game on huh
for the whole time oh well
okay okay this can really go sideways
but it could be your only chance there's
this lady up at Hillcrest called Adrian
I already met her I think yep she runs
an exclusive action yeah
yeah oh wait maybe you need to use at
least one of the canvases at least one
of the tools in your painting
and I use the canvas but not one of the
tools well I did it too early
and you only have to use one of them
more so but
too much
am I golden
canvas wasted
she knows everyone important in the art
community and is quite influential cut
Adrian to talk to like you and she could
get you into the museum okay well it
truly hope so there's some old crutch
between her and grandma and my grandpa
from from a long time ago I've always
had the feeling she's up to something be
careful don't be
don't pee
okay okay okay okay okay let's talk to
Adrian
and now we get the quests on the upper
side all right
yeah I see I see I see
Charles though
Charles doesn't seem to have anything
yet but Adrian
yes there we go
out of our element oh wait
oh another content for the final
Museum's thought
or should I show it that's not important
right now before I even consider what
you ask you must prove you're up to
stuff you get the endorsement of my
inner circle and we can discuss more all
Chantelle and Charles and of course lens
is that her child or so
how do you say that someone get it
so now we'll be doing Quests for them
for them to say they like me okay
yeah the skull guy
the ones that a little bit crazy
[Music]
talk talk
okay
some favors are we
endorse them all my daughter once speak
to me it brings great distress and shame
maybe you can help me make my dearest
Hyacinth return she's been lost for far
too long what is the expression of favor
for a favor I'm arranging a concert
concerto here at my estate and I shall
perform Brahms Violin Concerto and D
major it was highest and favorite
growing up we even had to build another
Concert Hall Just for her
[Music]
but first preparations are in order all
the Great violinists have spectacular
headwear make this hat into something
High sinful adore her favorite color has
always been blue
blue
my hat's also blue what a coincidence
okay
I love it are we gonna draw over the
ribbon too
you should do
is this blue
yeah a nice
oh no it doesn't go over the ribbon
what if I just really just painted blue
and leave it at that
[Music]
recycling they have so money it's so
money so much money and yet
they recycle an old hat
paint over it really
so cheap I guess
you don't get rich
if you waste your money on a [\h__\h] ton of
things but I mean still isn't that I
mean they buy designer clothes and stuff
so
oh wow
I will
um put like a nice border
[Music]
at least to give it a bit more detail
wait she's gonna wear it right
mmm
do I like that no
boom boom
[Music]
don't
what even if I want to become rich I
would not waste my money on name brand
really really
maybe just like one item to treat
yourself with how about that
still a no
found some spots I didn't paint
[Music]
I'm gonna give it some hearts
make a bit girly since it's her daughter
[Music]
what else happened at the convention
that I wanted to tell you about
[Music]
you know my friend uh one of my friends
who I always meet at this convention
um
she like completely upgraded her
convention chill equipment it's so funny
I was like so impressed
when I saw you know I was like I'm
wearing a blank blanket
Chill on but
she went Next Level she brought like a a
blow up couch and a tent
so we were
spending time around that oh this is so
chill
that's like next level she wasn't the
only one though
there were some other people who also
had a camping attire like a lot of
camping chairs and Tents
so over the top I know like a lot of
American conventions are like inside
Hotel buildings so I think that's not
really something you see much yeah but
it's really just convention veterans who
go that far to bring such equipment
but in in Germany Austria or Europe
there's like a lot of garden like Park
conventions
so you know
it's worth bringing
stuff like that because it's really
comfy you cannot bring like grilling
equipment though of course that would go
too far you can't start like grilling
there
but it's really nice because if you have
like all this like chill stuff to chill
around
and do you like headquarters all your
friends will like gather around it and
they will stay there and you don't have
to go anywhere to see your friends no
because they will all come to you
it's like uh the light and the flies fly
to the light
um
here's a third shade of blue
I think the algorithm wants me to do
that hmm
I don't want to overdo the design but
okay
maybe on the inside
a nice inner lining
[Music]
maybe I'll do the whole back
mm-hmm I actually I like this hat
I think it's cute
and not like unfashionable
a ribbon with a hat honestly it makes
everything
a million times better anyway look at
that I like it I know what the [\h__\h]
happened I didn't do that no
that went through the pain went through
staining
will it now go through on the other side
as well
again
hopefully not
oh no
oh that was the wrong one I think
let me see the moment of truth
no okay now it stayed
okay the hat is done it's really nice
look at it
we Asian also bring like pillow or even
have a mini tan too oh really
I mean I I never saw something like that
in Japanese commercials Japanese
conventions are like you know completely
different
there it's like nobody chills the
cosplay area is really like contained in
one area and then
yeah there's no like chill area
a comicat there's like cosplay area and
the the area with all the you know
little little stands so there is no
place to chill you're not supposed to
chill anywhere people are busy there's
the time of the convention is really
short too so you go in you really have
to hurry to get what you want to buy if
that's your goal
stand in line get that maybe go to the
next one Etc yeah and you don't really
go there for meeting friends I think I
mean surely you you might meet friends
if you have friends but that's not
really the first goal of conventions in
Japan I feel like at least not for
comicat Comic market and Tokyo game show
is a bit different because
yeah there there's like stands and all
that for like official
game companies and all that you can test
them out sometimes or like they give
something away and so on so that's a bit
different
um
but yeah there's like it's very
different it's very very different
what's the name exactly I like Tokyo
game show though
I really like Tokyo game show
hmm definitely prefer it over comicat
like in terms of the vibe and the
atmosphere
what a lovely hack you've made your
tracks although she's ringing oh here's
simple being off such a lovely hat well
you look good in it too
anyway so the violin in Focus we need to
make sure it's a real centerpiece take
the violin that I will be using and make
it the violent no I'm painting on the
violin
details should be something that makes
Hyacinth gazen up
okay I'm just gonna like speed around
that okay
oh but the pink with the blue the blue
Shades that I chose is gorgeous
all right violin Sun you know what I
think is fancy white violin
it's just Elegance isn't it
but
maybe I should just make it orange
though
yeah that was pretty
foreign
silver shiny Violet wow it is so shiny I
have white paint but it's turning out
silver
yeah I mean look at that wow wow it's so
shiny
but I don't think it really fits the
image that they are going for
yeah
imagine
[Music]
what was she like asking for anyway
what was her wishes for it just
something the centerpiece that catches
the eye right
well
wow well then how about a red violet nah
that doesn't look so special
again how about a blue one okay blue
looks kind of special to me I feel like
I've seen red violence before because
the red is very similar to Brown which
is the shade you see the most but the
blue one matches with the hat
and it's something I haven't seen
yeah
blue is elegant what about this shade
like a darker one
[Music]
yeah here I totally put a lot of thought
into it I mean I did but I didn't put
detail into it once you still like it I
don't really care anymore
take it
oh
okay okay there you go now you see that
don't just take anything
okay I will make it match your hat
um
I won't make it match your hat and it
will look beautiful
[Music]
that is definitely already an upgrade
violence are so pretty
sounds so pretty
backside
[Music]
maybe this side
let me make it really interesting all
right I hope this doesn't
um
go on to the sites that I don't want it
to go to
[Music]
problem
ah what the [\h__\h] the color doesn't go
there
I guess not
Raiders there's a raid hello raid who's
rating me sorry I was I was focused
who is writing me
[Music]
apparently I'm not the only one ah hello
welcome to the Stream
hmm
rage Shadow Legends just sponsored by
rage Lego legends
I used to really not know any YouTubers
out of outside of whole life but
nowadays like I
I know like I don't know them personally
but and I don't watch everyone
I don't watch really anyone but at least
I know of their existence
[Music]
it's nice to see that they know of mine
too
welcome
welcome all right the back
hmm
looks like I'm drawing a cat face
oh I saw this doggo at the convention
who had it was like one missing eye and
the other one was blind and he was
wearing like a blind jacket self-made
one
but but he was so cute it was like a
Corgi mix uh yeah a poor doggo but
everyone was giving him love and pets
and he was like moving really really
slowly because he didn't see [\h__\h] and he
apparently it was also deaf as well so
his only sense was well uh uh like
smelling things and I guess you know
being touched and petted a lot so
I don't know I I'm sure you know doggos
they're just so sweet so surely he's
like happy and loved and all that but I
felt like so
pien
when I saw the dog go and I I spent a
lot of time with him too
but you know whenever he would walk
around kind of aimlessly he was walking
so slowly and wobbling and and it was it
just looked kind of sad he like
constantly had this like low-key sad
look on his face
but I I want to say that you know a dog
will cannot be sad when as long as he
has like you know an owner who loves him
he surely is happy and the owner seemed
very very sweet and nice and caring
but still
cruel why right like why why make a
doggle suffer so much such a sweet baby
it made me feel oh
hmm this world is a cruel place why make
someone suffer like that a dog who
cannot you know that Dogo deserves to
see the world and the treat those
um and here all the oh good who's a good
boy
good boy he should be hearing that right
that's so sad I was so sad but like he
he was loved by everyone like everyone
who saw the dog who gave him pets was he
old I don't know he doesn't look like
super old
um
I don't know if he was born like that or
if he had an accident
but at least he has
an owner who loves them and he's not
just like rotting in the shelter because
no one wants him because that is just
the saddest thought I could ever think
of man
that's the saddest fault ever isn't it
[Music]
how do you draw
what I want to do in the back like
anything
[Music]
hmm
don't make me think of that I don't even
know it's sad
oh
for flowers verbs or verbs flowers
oh guys did you hear the new let's
seraphim song
I know you guys know a lot of you don't
really listen to K-pop
but unless seraphim put out a new song
okay
[Music]
it's really good
it just came out
who who
La seraphim
maybe it just came out so maybe it will
come into your recommendations today
and then you will not enjoy it probably
because you don't a lot of you guys
don't care for Kpop huh
well well how do you spell that l e and
then a space and then
was it double double it how do you write
it s e r a f f i m I think
foreign
[Music]
look at that double rose
it's a a song from izone retired uh Idol
group
the title is French phrase La Vie En
Rose or so
it's so pretty
okay you better take it there's lots of
details on there now plenty
[Music]
is it a song Unforgiven yeah that's the
new uh La seraphim song
[Music]
what the what does
it
well if if I we give it any more details
I feel like I'm like
gonna overdo it though girl
maybe she wants what what the [\h__\h] does
she want
front is blank it's not it's not blank
God damn it
[Music]
[\h__\h]
so demanding customer is always right
[Music]
this is how you draw roses effectively
by the way
keep on drawing the petals onto it in a
circle motion motion motion
the expectations of the kingdom is
coming out that's when we'll start a new
series oh
also I just realized tomorrow I'm going
to a doctor well I didn't realize
suddenly I got a reminder for mine for
my for my appointment that I made like
two months ago because that was the
earliest appointment I could get
so
[Music]
cannot
oversleep
[Music]
I'm going to a dermatologist
just checking you know because I haven't
been so long and hmm
10 years or so
and I just wanna you know I just felt
like checking my uh my uh
what do you call it birthmarks
just just in case because right you
should check them every once in a while
right
yeah
just check this is the birthmarks yeah
and I guess I guess so maybe she'll give
me something for my uh sunburn
hmm
[Music]
eh you just remember you had you had a
minute you missed it
motion
might help a lot with a small program
problems with my pimples and still work
in progress
um I mean I've always good to check out
as time goes on simple yeah exactly
should get checked just uh like can I
have every single one checked do I have
to get naked
sure
[Music]
finally she likes it wonderful
extraordinary this is truly a majestic
focal point for the Concerta
I can see how it Sims child draw as I
perform now for the Final Touch our
carpet isn't red any honored guest must
arrive on the red carpet well do you
really only want it to be red or wait
can I ah a draw straight on it or do you
want anything extra too why did I
disappear
oopsie
does it really only have to be red I
didn't even bring red [\h__\h]
it's so far home is so far can I
[Music]
um
all right I have to I have to go back
to get my red color
or could I make it Orange
[Laughter]
fast travel book for real like now I
would appreciate it but okay
oh good one good one
red with some golden patterns yeah okay
you have a quest you guys are crazy
what's going on why do you no no you're
just talking randomly normally you don't
do that
ah you have one Gabrielle
um you're constantly talking to herself
she's right over there
hmm
oh okay painter yeah that's me
hi I've made some life-changing
calculations
here's my conclusion if I continue to
help my father with his fishery I will
never leave this town but if I instead
aim to become a successful influencer
the world will be mine within a year you
could help me out there's this contest a
social media thing called well
narcissize me
second place when student 50 and the
stupid print of post of the post with
the most likes but that's irrelevant
we're aiming for first place 500 and
most important loads of media exposure
to win I have to be the most liked
participant by the end of the challenge
an easy win how well my research reveals
that one of the most running things
right now is to post a square drawing of
your current mood using only crayons eh
a cray moo stupid yes I am not a painter
can you help let's do a 50 50 deal
okay
what's a good first step uh
your mood
I don't have a moody personality but my
research shows that the feeling people
tend to like the most is love
pathetic but apparently a winning
concept do you need anything else Square
canvas
thank you
and the Crayons if I don't have them yet
okay since you say you don't have them I
probably already have them
filled with love okay
easy enough
straw hard
or
but sorry to 10 P.M
I've been focusing on the quests for
this stream so we didn't draw like much
crazy [\h__\h] but
at least we drove very well should I
just sell froggy wama now or what what I
do with her you guys said they said it's
not oh I don't have a crane they said
it's not
a
Masterpiece which I think is
ridiculous
absolutely ridiculous and insulting
I don't know how to deal with that but
hmm
I'll take the crayon
crayon
[Music]
what my purchase made me a little bit
more well-known
[Music]
drawing of janma
that's right
ah Square cameras okay I'm really
quickly
[Music]
um
she said only crayons
[\h__\h]
next
uh ah I didn't switch it up uh cancel
cancel cancel abort mission
I'll do it there
maybe the problem is that the true
matches your fragile can't be captured
in a painting yeah it can only be
captured in a glass bowl
here there we go
this one
take the crayon
and we'll
paint it all oh that's the biggest it
can get also I still have a brush in my
hand I just realized it doesn't actually
change the tools
I'm painting with a brush still even
though supposedly it's a little crayon
lies
all lies my immersion is broken
[Music]
who would have known that immersion is
so important
[Music]
now I wonder if I put too many other
colors in it is it gonna you know not be
considered lovey-dovey anymore so I will
just
I I'm not gonna draw Jade empty but I'm
gonna
I'm gonna just write it
[Music]
there we go
and then we'll go up to the carpet and
we'll fix the carpet and then we'll end
it and then I read quickly some super
chats
there's a Korean street food place
around me called GMT
just JMT
interesting
Gabrielle what's up
I'm in second place now I only need to
pass it Australian guy how are you
already in second place I thought you
needed this thing here
I got it I got it take it
only crying I can see the love in this
it's all around it everywhere I look yes
this is it snap post I told you so just
look at it go one of the four likes to
the 99 likes 5 level 45
another one nine four nine seven nine
ten
we're going to win this I am not
surprised no wait what that's really
cool
no click I need to post a sick or sicko
I need more help here's a new Square
canvas what sickle
a sick pick as in wild and weird as in
over the top something that makes you go
dude that's sick if you're mine
hmm
okay maybe next time
negotiating okay I'll give you all the
money if you help me I just need the
likes so use whatever tools you prefer
just create the sickest painting please
what if I gave her froggy Wawa I guess I
can't it's not Square either okay
um
[Music]
I think yeah froggy mama would be pretty
sick like color-wise she would also
probably like it because it's green
green is pretty sick
especially when you're sick on the floor
would that be Han Solo no
that's the sickest sickle it kind of
sounds negative though
I mean
if it's only sick I can see it being
positive but it's sick is sicko that
sounds negative
[Music]
okay this thing doesn't look so good
here this red is better
airbrush
paint
it kind of works
no
I'm gonna pay for go go go go do your
thing
foreign
I'll finish it with my brush my trusted
we love it brush
there we go it's red now but she
probably is not satisfied with that so
[Music]
I mean red carpets usually really are
only red
what
I'll I'll ask her I'll ask her if this
is good enough we'll see
not then I'll try
oh
I can see her walking on the carpet
already
marvelous oh we're done everything is
set and imitations have been sent out I
made sure to invite all their new
friends as well they should arrive at
any minute in the meantime let's get
this concert tour started
she doesn't have the stick to playing
rip
here she comes my dear oh
that's that oh yeah right that's her why
are you friends another Gemini at first
I thought we were past this
ah oh dear Harrison why do you have to
be so dramatic
goes from a rich family huh oh
she's changed her name
ah simv it's not safe just sent all my
dear Hyacinth oh she's breaking all
connection with me I'm not feeling too
well did I eat too many oysters oh no I
don't like this feeling at all I don't
want to let her go I want her back but
the more I try the fertile part we grow
I guess I'll just have to regroup and
try harder some other time you that's
probably your violin that failed to
impress
you're making it my fault now
I put a lot of work into that because
you were so unsatisfied with it so many
times
what's your remained loyal as a woman of
Honor I have to endorse that
uh-huh wow you left a really bad
aftertaste
in my mouth with your [\h__\h] lady
I kind of like you now and now I don't
now I'm kind of pissed
you're not appreciating all the work I
put into it blaming me for it
no wonder
[Music]
all right ah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
shall we sell froggy Wawa
and then
then we'll end it will call it a day
oh
wait what if I sell it up there are they
gonna come to buy it
We're not gonna come anyway to my store
even though it's so far away
but I wouldn't mind them
although wait did are they gonna
appreciate it they already didn't
we'll see we'll
what colors and so on do they like ah
this isn't like it and underwhelming
realization of weakness it's on
the converse even though it looks really
green right now
it's on the goal
[Music]
s
how do you not like it it's like
screaming it's yelling money
well I don't need you to buy it anyway
foreign
I don't know my other boys down there
they also pay me plenty of money
I don't need your dirty money that you
got through scamming people
with your stupid tools that are the same
as Benjamins
and honestly your golden canvas I didn't
want to say it but it honestly just
looks like you painted it with golden
color with that tool that I have as well
that makes everything shiny
I didn't want to say it but let's face
it it looks exactly like that
it looks suspiciously shiny
think about it
so here
my masterpiece
let's see what they pay for my
masterpiece exposed
I don't need one stupid Museum
telling me
that my masterpiece is a masterpiece I
know my masterpieces are masterpieces
come on George you know it too
oh now it too ah
that's what that's already incredibly
good
hmm
I don't think it'll get better than this
but I I would like to hear some other
opinions
worst guys will just reset it by putting
it back up then George should come again
I think I want to hear our opinions
though
I think what's what's the most money
I've earned with a painting before
also also didn't they say this is worth
500 something
but George is already offering like more
than double
more than triple
uh-huh okay but wait the the one of the
rich guys is coming
like it green is The Color of Money
George again
he went up
oh almost 2 000 wait George I want to
see what this guy is what was his name
what's his name come on offer me
something dude
there we go he's coming and George is
still not giving up either
George is Rich yeah oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
he's looking at it from all angles no
he's kind of bugging out to be honest
now he can go
practice the Benjamin's shop would be he
hates it
[\h__\h] off
[\h__\h] off bring me back George
excuse me
wow rude rude awakening
there's more people coming but I doubt
she would like it
[Music]
um
maybe this game's unpopular color is
green
instead of pink
oh one thousand three hundred all right
I mean that's not bad
all right you gotta
get higher than George for me to
take the offer
oh I got so many people in here right
now this hairy guy I think he also
offered quite a bit of money often or
was it a cook the cook also offers money
quite a bit
it's not cheap as these people are go
go away you're blocking this person for
making an offer although I don't even
want to hear it it's just yeah it's just
insulting what and you made Harry leave
too because you took up all the space
Harry couldn't even make an offer
because you intimidated him
[\h__\h] off go away
bring me back George
at once I don't want to hear what you
[\h__\h] you you're a mess
your life's a mess you suck
go away cool you guys are such froggy
wobble haters it's unbelievable go away
go away no I don't
I don't want you want you here
oh
[Music]
bring me a bag George please I'm sorry
for doubting you George you're always
the one who pays the most I should know
better
more punks are coming thanks for saying
it's dope but I I need the money more
money because I didn't I pay 1 900 or so
for the canvas how much was it again
I don't remember it was a lot though
I think oh a thousand if that's better
because you come from a rich family
George
[Music]
please
at least I don't insult it
um
oh Postman is coming
he's got some George vibes
but his job probably doesn't pay so well
please please
wait Charles is also coming I'm curious
what he would say but I'm not turning
this down anymore
wait oh oh the rich [\h__\h] are finally
arriving but
ah
okay I'm taking it
whoa ten thousand again let's go hey
thanks guys for coming I I wish I could
you know offer you something
um
damn it I have I have this Red Canvas
but okay bye bye
bye bye I had lunch with Picasso once I
know I know you keep on flexing about
that makes me doubt if it's even true
at least she's still carrying everything
I gave her
nice
okay
that was good
we
um made good progress in the game we
maybe didn't draw you know a lot of like
whole life members
but we make good progress in the next
time
uh who knows how far we'll get but I
will try my best it should be possible
to implement my character I got pretty
close to doing it I just need the
confirmation from
staff that I am allowed to do it and
then I shall really do it I thought that
I didn't need it because money said but
I already did it but
apparently I do so sorry guys for
getting your hopes up but next time next
week I'll stream it again and hopefully
we can draw also some more whole life
members or I might just do it in my off
time hey
um
now let's read some super chattels where
did I leave off last time do you guys
remember
let's go to my office also I'm gonna
move back to monitor because it's very
frontal
stuck
sure okay
we had tangents that's the real swim
yeah you guys we're served with a lot of
tangents at least yeah from my little
trip
um
police
car crashes
actually uh I mean that wasn't the crash
but it almost broke down and during the
ride this never happened to me before
because I guess I'm not much in the car
but when we were on the Autobahn the
highway
you know there were barely any cars most
of the time and we were like almost
alone but at some point uh in one moment
there was a big truck on the right lane
and we were on the left lane over
like passing it and then uh
suddenly
suddenly really close like to us we were
like zooming right and really close
right in front of us we noticed like
really really late but there was
like a huge deer already dead on the
ground
uh on the left side like on our lane but
like not in the middle of it kind of on
the left side
uh just lying there and I screamed but
better and and and and I think my driver
saw it too but he said me like you know
being there definitely helped otherwise
otherwise we would have gotten into a
huge [\h__\h] crash and
may have been very very hurt because it
was like really big he said that would
have been like a total crazy crash yeah
um
we just we just barely right in front of
it managed to
go a little bit around like swoosh but
right next to us on the right side was
the big truck so we couldn't even like
go too much
yeah but it was pretty [\h__\h] bad it
was shocking I didn't even see clearly
what it was from the back seat but uh
who is a deer and just leaves it on the
road that's almost a month of food well
you're not allowed you're not allowed
right to like take home your own
roadkill when I was joking we should
have taken it home because that's a [\h__\h]
ton of meat
and that's apparently good
um
[Music]
I guess
English
who
I hope no one else had an accident there
because that is really dangerous
suddenly German hmm
sorry it was just disgusting because the
the the the walls on the
Highway
we're pretty low I mean there were some
walls but
pretty low so a deer could jump over it
and I was thinking like Wyatt why don't
we make the highways was like really
high walls all the time
so that this doesn't happen
wouldn't that be like super useful but I
guess yeah those are against sound
and this part of the highway was in the
middle of nowhere with no houses
anywhere inside so you don't need the
isolation from the sound
the noises you don't need it
um
but I mean you don't have to even put up
a wall you could just put up like a a
wire net
that's as tall as a wall
that would be much cheaper
but lining every Highway with that of
course is
like
cold I get that
but wouldn't it be okay well for mayor I
was saying that's like you know what I
want I will become a mayor so that this
doesn't happen and I will build all the
highways with fences and walls now and
my friends because finally uh the girl
also woke up at that point they were
laughing at me
like you gotta be a bit more than just a
mayor in order to make something like
that happen I want to build a wall
at every Highway
we'll have our votes well then first you
will have to become Austrian I guess
register yourself in Austria
deers pay
knowing I feel so bad for them man oh
and then you know like just a couple of
minutes later
that it was like a bunny or something
really quickly zooming over the streets
over the highway
almost drove over that one too but that
one was still alive at least
oh but the deal was already dead so sad
um
yeah I think I think it was a bunny
because it was like really small but
fast it looked like a bunny or a cat or
something why would a cat be there so I
think it's a bunny oh
okay it's spring yeah they're all coming
out now saying hello please
please get the [\h__\h] out of here I don't
want to kill you guys I don't want to be
in charge of that I don't know I don't
want it to be my fault I don't want to
take any lives
except of chickens
just kidding I love you guys
whistle I'm gonna go to my office
oh God damn it yeah
I guess I just said I was doing that so
I said I'm kidding
sorry Steve
oh man the chat is also bugging out
bug
why why is it bugging
ew mine's not showing up
croninia had the same problem
come on
chat
[Music]
um
what if I do this no
it won't work
I am turning it off and on let me go
here no [\h__\h]
sorry Marcus I'm gonna get you back
really quickly after the Stream
just wait
wait oh man chat no the chat stuff is
broken all right we gotta
um
no chat I guess
no chat
it's okay it's broken
oh wait no oh
foreign
[Music]
no
I had something weird with the chat
before and just fixed it by changing the
size but it's not working this time
hmm
sorry guys you guys have to look at the
live chat of the VOD I guess if you want
to see it
but the weird thing is it worked in the
gaming screen
shall we read it there is it still there
okay now we'll read it here
tonight
that's so weird that's really weird
that's really strange
Michael
[Music]
no
can you copy the chat from here and
participation in the office it's like
the same it's it's actually the same but
let me
[Music]
oh
chicken chicken friend why why why must
this happen to you
uh it doesn't show up
um
copy pasted it but it doesn't show up is
it still here or did I broke it did I
break it I broke it
I'll get rid of it here
on Romeo
it's gone forever here now too I [\h__\h]
it up
maybe I can find it elsewhere
how about
can I find it here
[Music]
I'm not even here what about here
wait there's no chat here at all
like I'm thinking existing chats made hi
existing chats may not be bugging out is
what I thought
um
hello I'm Sarah Gutenberg
[Music]
right
oh wait I mean no this hello
I replace the URL but it's not showing
up
well
foreign
[Music]
which one is this one
um
also broken
Kento help
even though it's supposed to be way
bigger than that it cuts off down there
ah
I can't
fix it
[Music]
wow
nice corn cup Pizza though
nice Pizza
the Multiverse of koala scenes
um
what about here
time to check the usual room is that
where I put the chat
no
there's no chat here
I shouldn't have changed the the gaming
one that one was fine
what about you
what a weird place to be in
um oh
no no
over here
ah a chat was there for him yeah it's
kind of there but it really isn't
it I was kind of there
thank you
okay I can't make it better bigger even
when I make it bigger it always cuts off
on the very bottom I give up I give up I
give up
I give up let's go here
[Applause]
Timothy
today I'm sending so many of them
accidentally God damn it
for one foot for what
foreign
[Laughter]
okay I'll let it go
I let it go we read super chat anymore
flying for the Kiana cinematic
Multiverse
okay
um
how do I there
Super Chat oh
what do I read guys
this one shows oh this is
that is incredibly weird
that one goes all the way up it's so
broken
I think crony had the same problem
[Music]
um
ah
[Music]
okay whatever I don't have time for this
you know
did I read Minecraft superchats when did
I stop I don't know Scrolls girls
[Music]
cute did I read kill
did I really kill
Faith simulator first one thank you
thanks for filling up the chat guys
for trying to at least
in that case I can make it smaller again
there we go
ah it doesn't feel so empty
cool
yeah that seems to be the only way of
getting yourself onto the TV if you want
to be like Mommy look I'm on TV this is
the only way right now
foreign
[Music]
thanks guys I love you
let's see
I'm still scrolling guys
those are not new is those they're just
using their
okay I have reached the first I think
fifth simulator stream
[Music]
nails
there it is
yes you're on TV congratulations
here we go take this monkey thank you
and Jacob 47 I'll thank you Jeff the
Phoenix
[Music]
Sun oh no
oh holy one can you hear our prayers we
sense the great evil arrives then
immediately ran Chris even after all
this time we're grateful you continue to
grant our village Your Divine protection
Chef I love you thank you for still
showing up oh man I'm sorry that I'm not
showing up
makes me feel bad I should go to Phoenix
Sun again
oh man
yeah we didn't you didn't even really
wake up from it right yeah it was a
night you guys were sleeping you were
maybe feeling oh
a little bit a little bit of a ramble
oh that must have been nothing and just
went back to sleep that's how quickly we
vanquished the evil
um
and so I'm gonna use it recently uh
I saw Anna like fixed something and she
was able to play I'm I'm explaining it
I'm just able to play I'll make it I was
able to
um play Minecraft again is that when she
went to Phoenix soon
[Music]
um
oh
why why Sean Mendes I'm actually like
surprised they just didn't they didn't
just go to fauna's place she just has
mending too doesn't she
and hers is easier to find I mean I'm
very happy they would go to my place but
Emma doesn't know where fauna Farm is oh
that's interesting because it's like so
close to her PPP
oh see I still have my reputation and uh
yeah the the the
I'm just Phoenix I made it famous so
people still know where it is I still
have that advantage
ethically produced mending yeah it's
Superior
hmm I see
I see it's good to know Shawn Mendes is
still alive too
that's good
thanks for the pinky 911 help I've been
robbed this orange ruin has stolen my
heart
and you're are you complaining about it
I think
you wanted me to steal your heart anyway
and you're happy with it now so
just hang up the phone
hang up the phone
do it
thanks for the pinky and the camera
Creed thank you thank you thanks for the
pinky nine eleven oh no they're getting
so many calls I think I just saw a cute
orange bird sneaking out of navid's
place I think she had a croissant on her
mouth you need a description she's cute
and amazing uh artist hard working sweet
a Divine singer and Dancer funny lovable
oh can I stop
that could what's wrong
you're reporting for someone else
but what about you are you sure you got
everything
on you still
while you were making that a call
I may have sneaked into your house
and sneaked behind you
to take your heart as well
and your underwear
yeah yeah
oh oh sorry oh nine one one sorry
confusing
um
don't steal his underwear just one just
one
it's only one
empty right
we don't need all of them right
surely you don't need all of them you
can spare me one
did you see the picture of uh Yanko
with the uh uh what do you call a box of
shorts
merchandise around his arms
and I think we were all disappointed
that he wasn't actually wearing them
on top of his pants right
squeeze into it you don't have to be you
know just wearing the the panties
but okay yeah on his head too oh
cracked into the candy
altar said tempo's management asked him
to wear it but legal said no legal said
no
would Yago have been okay to do it
because shouldn't Yago be the one who
has the last words the the final say in
it
or are we just using legal said it as an
excuse because Yago also didn't
necessarily want to do it hmm
yeah go back the legal to say no see
that's what I think
he was like you you girls and guys
you're making me wear the weirdest
things and have the weirdest things in
my hands for a long time now making me
take all these embarrassing pictures but
this is as far as it will go I will not
make you take pictures of being
underwear you thought you had me you
thought you were but we're gonna
bamboozle me and you're gonna take the
most embarrassing pictures of Me by
making boxer shorts panties your
merchandise
because you knew I was gonna take a
picture for it but no no you cannot make
me do anything I have boundaries
this is where they are this is where it
ends it's over
yeah I mean understandable I guess
is is that the line is that the line
[Music]
so also no no bras right
what about swimsuits I mean
people show themselves in swimsuits
like normally in public
what about swimsuits
or socks
oh yeah socks
would he give us sock picks
I wonder would he just hold those up to
hmm
I guess we must try like there's no
other way around it the only way to find
out is to make him do it and then see
what he says
[Music]
[Laughter]
socks should be fine I think I mean I
also feel like there's a chance for
socks I think there's a chance for socks
an innocent piece of clothing item
right I think bottom had socks before
really
um
the problem is like with socks you could
have the excuse of saying you know that
it's difficult to take a full body
picture or so
so that's why he's holding it up
so you see them better or so I don't
know
it doesn't
I feel like crying
uses them with sock puppets
I mean yeah okay that could be one way
of doing it
and and honestly
that's how I used socks before so I
can't even complain about it
do I hear this and meowing no there
shouldn't be any
cumin actually
[Music]
thank you for two pinkies question if
the Hamburglar burgles hamburgers from
McDonald's and what is the name of the
one who steals from kfp
answer the clap cluck to Maniac sounds a
little bit like a dinosaur
you hear it in this video sometimes too
really
hmm
Club I don't like the pee in there she
got rid of I guess but it's silent huh
clock to main is silent huh to be sound
clactomaniac
good it does sound like clap clap what's
it actually collect what what I forgot
good one good one
[Applause]
you faction that is a good one
clap domain okay but there it's not
silent
but I can see it becoming silent in this
situation
maniac
[Music]
Sky dinosaur for the pinky Chihuahua
there are two important things I want to
tell you first thing is you Aya your
YouTube sisters are still using old Art
Attack second thing is you are so lovely
thank you I think I saw that Super Chat
and then I changed it but yeah it's back
again
thank you though I don't think anyone
would look there anyway who looks at my
description
looks at that it's always the same
usually
I'll try and remember but
it might happen many many times again
thank you skydo for reminding me soon
uh Black Version thanks for the pinky I
think waking up to a Kiara's dream is
the best way to start my birthday hope
you have a ton of fun lala thank you for
another awesome year glad to be spending
it here with you on kfp you're the best
you cute dark love the tinking life
it was your birthday
oh I'm so sorry I'm so late
I'm so sad I'm so late Black Friday now
you're here are you a hero I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm so late
did you have a good time
fashionably like you
oh man I hope you had a good time
congratulations on your birthday
hell yeah oh you're so sweet I love you
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday black fake John the
best chicken in the world because you're
so cute I love you but everybody's the
best you can I'm just saying yeah but
you're pretty awesome I love you you're
the best say to say the way you are and
don't change ever you're great awesome
super cute
[Applause]
stay healthy and happy
it was part of the official Happy
Birthday song did you not know
did you not know
you're so sweet thank you so much for
being part of kfp still and I hope we
can spend many more birthdays together
um
Sky Junction 177
wait some of these are passed part two
super jets
hmm
Patsy Duncan breakfast uh
yeah I saw that stupid [\h__\h] I told
management I don't know if they were
able to take care of it yet
canister
thank you for the pinky no right now I'm
not using a whole laser
right now I'm not
thank you for the pink sticker Jeffy
really appreciated thank you soon
Santiago Martin thank you for the recipe
chat dear Faith Kiana please give back
my heart you stole it for me two years
ago although surely you're taking good
care of it I wish you the best Santi P.S
ignore the cringe of the Super Chat
don't worry it's weird though why am I
getting all these complaints now
I stole them ages ago and you're now
complaining about it I mean it's too
late
it's too late now
I pawned it
you're not getting it back I I
disassembled it like jewelry
and I sold it
no just kidding I still have it but
you're not like entitled to get it back
no refunds that late you had uh one year
time
and even then it would have been
questionable because you needed a good
reason
to take it back so
not happening thank you Sandy I'll keep
it
foreign
at The Sweet Spot the closer you are to
it the further the lock will turn
so if the correct pin position is three
o'clock and you have the pin at two
o'clock it will turn most of the way
then stop yeah thanks for trying to
explain I probably wouldn't have
understood with your explanation either
but I ended up understanding and now I'm
pretty good at it so no problem anymore
thanks for trying though I'm sorry I
didn't even read it I didn't see it at
the time
sorry for making you suffer
but you'd have to actually like show me
an action I think for me to understand
thank you Jesus
Sean Tyler km2
Santi I'll go again thanks for the
recipe chat
he says which
you know what's gonna happen now
Santiago you may have sent me a red
Super Chat
but
that is
that is a very dangerous thing to do
to the usual room you go for trying to
report your boss to the police
in front of my face too
and frighten my face
bye bye Santiago
you are gonna stay there for five months
um
it's actually like a pretty low sentence
for the crime that you did
but I'm going easy because I don't I and
recently I've been sending too many
people to the usual room by accident
it's getting a little bit busy to to
keep on keeping up with the maintenance
so
yeah
I have to take care of that
um
Riley dirt charm Duncan kitchen
brisket man thank you
uh spanking time thank you for the red
super chat I'll just leave this here I
hope nobody steals it
[Music]
up
I'll take these red super chatos and put
it into my pocket
[Music]
he surely didn't know this right he
won't be missing his
red super chat right I'll take it
thank you foreign
into my pocket
Pink Panther on membership where can I
even Watch Pink Panther
pamper pencil pen pencil one of weird
that's so weird to say panther
I really can't pronounce that pants
pants Panther
s
Pink Panther in German
let's just go with that
Panther
ah
th I hate you
no I have no trouble with th whatsoever
your th sometimes sound like d and Panda
but listen that's a pink panda kinda
cute
oh
Transformer Pink Panther
I didn't say Pink Panther
I'm better at it than I used some really
really
I don't doubt it
okay I'm gonna read whole talk super
chattel
uh
[Music]
foreign
on my shoulder I think
[Music]
cute baby
hey guys
why water in the fire why exported my
UVU as you fish to have confidence that
I'm diving you forever
no confidence but dog is icon welcome
wow
hello happy face happy dog
um
uh what what what what what is what is
the meaning behind this soup chat
small smooth and love the turtle house
one
making fun of the small turtles so mean
good Corner impression strategy
yeah all the well-known memes yeah but
look you left out the
[Music]
I also Olive boy
there's so many good ones
yeah it was so smug
small small turtle half that don't have
small
excuse me Turtle house owner be like
excuse me what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
so mean
so funny yeah
she's just like Rambles in English
she just froze out whatever she can
possibly think of
but
I think she's really good at it like
she has
some vocabulary it kind of works yeah
yeah very creative with her limited
English
so I like listening to it too
thank you Trevor G for the reminders of
the cute coroness Empires many famous
words
can you stand thank you soon
or cumin
there's a j there now in the
pronunciation thingy so I'm not sure
anymore
thank you thank you
um
Super Snake Mario thanks for the rest of
the chat
hot dog with coroner let's go I'm so
excited I've been looking forward to
this for so long Corona has a special
place in my heart as she was the first
whole life member I discovered I don't
know if I'd be here today if not for her
so thank you Kiara I love you both
thank you and you're welcome oh I'm
happy to hear that yeah senpai
was one of the members who really like
were able to create a lot of
entertaining viral clips
so
all the respect and love to her and to
you super snake Mario thank you so much
for the support of whole life
and for being here still today
very glad you made your way to kfp after
being introduced your whole life through
Colony Senpai hmm
it's my honor thank you soon and a kiss
for you catch it open your hand or or
show me your you kissable mouth
um
thank you
for the support
Corona was a Gateway for a lot of people
yeah
thank God
I think Corona is a great representation
of whole life
Mr Blue
chat thanks so great to see The Return
of whole talk thank you for finding out
the sense of my UB you're the best
you're sincerely you're welcome well
actually you say return of Hall talk it
wasn't like supposed to be gone
was an accidental break again
oh now I should
I haven't like asked for for the next
guest yet but I should get to it
who should I go for next where we did uh
we did we didn't
we didn't buy yet right so two hours
senpai
right
didn't do any of them I think
otherwise I would be blanking really
badly right now
yeah pickle and I already did what are
you talking about I already did pickled
have you forgotten
too yeah yeah but that's already the
Next Generation
yeah I've only done Canada's input um
[Music]
okay
I don't know who I should reach out to
First
you will see soon
I got chicken brain what a coincidence
me too
ah so chunky chunk hopefully the next
whole talk won't be too far away thank
you for watching and supporting
um
[Music]
foreign
okay oh four to nine Junction
[Music]
one two three nine eight seven Nations
that was a fantastic episode it was so
cool to learn more about one of the
girls who pulled me down the rabbit hole
originally so much fun to watch YouTube
chat the memes were great and the clips
brought back memories thank you glad you
enjoyed it thanks for the sweet feedback
Lego is a really good episode I was
really satisfied with the corona episode
because I know it was shorter than the
previous ones but I mean actually this
is the intended length
I never wanted this hotel to become that
long I wanted it to be more bite-sized
so I think it's good if I'm able to
bring it back a little bit to 1 hour 30.
yeah it's supposed to be like compact
size so I know longer is nice too but
yeah
it shouldn't be so long
it'll be different for each member yeah
yeah I always will but the interesting
thing is like I felt like I was talking
to colonist Empire for two hours or more
but it was pretty short
fee
the big red super chat I might not read
it now but another time another Super
Chat reading
did I read the member super chats I
think yeah I did I did I did okay next
would be cute but I'll leave it at that
because I have to cook something now
um
I I was defying the chicken I wonder if
it's default now
I had it outside the fridge for four
hours hmm
[Music]
I wonder in what state it is let me cook
you need to let me cook otherwise I'll
just throw it like the way it is into
the frying pan and let it do its thing
oh
I mean defrosting I guess oh
someone need somebody damned me
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
yes but
you know
[Music]
a mermaid wrote To Me
why am I laughing like this
it's not like there's something going on
behind the scenes where it makes sense
to love like that
[Music]
foreign
I was like yeah really intensely
they are clearly cooking what are they
plotting we're really not plotting
anything
hmm
[Music]
okay okay sorry sorry sorry sorry
um so my plan is tomorrow
uh to probably not stream
um
and then maybe on Wednesday
um but I've put up a schedule at least
tomorrow by the latest
um
my plan I think was
having
member stream on Wednesday possibly in
the evening
and then
but I might still move things around but
I also want to play
um 12 minutes this week because it's a
game that's on the shortest side and I
haven't played it yet
could be interesting I thought and then
just like as cardi uh not fixed but just
because I didn't know what else to play
I put Planet zoo into my calendar for
now 12 minutes was gonna be Saturday and
then on Sunday in at 8pm jst
AKA 1pm my time during the daytime I
want to do a rebroadcast of my karaoke
but then in the evening I would want to
play like Planet zoo
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah because I had it for
a while and
and why not play it for a one-off stream
not necessarily planning to be fifing
around this week I still uh I'm looking
I guess at maybe one more fellow stream
but I'm not sure because actually so
first day no Friday night for me is myth
Breakers that'll be on Kelly's Channel
and I might be the only stream that day
and first day
in the late evening for me
is
um collaboration with iron Mouse on her
Channel
on Twitch I'm being interviewed isn't
that nice yeah that's on Thursday night
the devil
yeah but since that's two days in a row
with no stream on my channel and the day
before being members and the day before
being a day off
uh that's kind of weird for my channel
so
hmm
and I will maybe do something during the
daytime on one of these days
um
you're offering me Mario 64 is a filler
game
yeah what why in a second I don't care
uh I I have a health about it about
something else not that one
um I'll squeeze something in during the
day something shorter I guess I wasn't
sure about playing Minecraft this week
because now I'm worried again that
nobody will be online when I am so I
would prefer to just plan something out
I think
um
yeah I don't know I don't know I'm I
I'll figure it out
but
yeah this is roughly how it will be
roughly
64 is on the switch now
wait they just added it what about what
about I just checked the other day what
about
my snowboarding though is my
snowboarding on yet
it's
it's my
it's my snowboarding
is is snowboarding there though
that's more important no
why
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
is doing so bad right now it's actually
such a good coincidence on going to the
dermatologist tomorrow
but I don't know if she can really do
much because
when I made my appointment I had to
choose between like what kind of
appointment I would want it to be and
it's the first time appointment so
I don't know how much she can do we'll
see I guess hmm
yeah Zelda is next week so until then we
still have days that we can fill with
little short games
um
yeah
I will filled with something
maybe I'll just put a TBD
there for now hero truck simulator
bought that a month ago I'm sorry they
said it doesn't happen now and I right
it's confusing
so confusing
they confuse me
girls talk when girls talk is so popular
yeah girls talk I have nothing scheduled
for now and now that week already
started so it's kind of difficult to
schedule for this week uh
because it's so fun
yo guys like listening into girls talk
huh
it's almost as if you're stalking girls
while they're doing girls talk
don't make it sound weird well
I'm just doing a play with words we
learned it from watching you
[Music]
it's in the name it is it is all right
guys I'm gonna go now
thanks for watching today I'm glad to be
back home and let's have a fun week
together I will upload the members
wallpaper
if I don't forget after the Stream
and it's amazing it's amazing
so keep an eye Oh eye and eye open on
the community board and um
is Kelly streaming
is Cali streaming
yeah
she just started
what is she streaming
Kawaii pomori
uh doesn't show that she's dreaming to
me ah she's just starting now you mean
choo choo Charles ew it's like a horror
game I hate it
but sure I'll do it for Cali
nobody's ever rating me but sure I'll do
it I mean I mean I mean people raid me
but not my own members
sure I love a Cali
[Music]
I'm always a Raider
wait I might sorry my YouTube's slow
YouTube [\h__\h] slow
[\h__\h] hell
let me set it up I know how to do it
[Music]
I go here
great kiwawa Legends
for some reason the whole ID doesn't
right it feels like something they would
enjoy doing
because we've streamed before everyone
in Ian that's not always the case
there's times mostly yes but there's
times where some of them could raid me
but they don't because I guess they just
don't think about it which I mean I also
normally wouldn't think about it because
it's just not quite our culture here
um
get rid of that get rid of that show me
show me what there we go
there we go okay uh I think I said it
now
we shall go
it's powerful for stats what do you mean
YouTube algorithm likes it or what
council's been doing it more
maybe they stream more back to back
Cali wanted to figure it out
she must learn it soon
all right here we've got one in Germany
we say avidas then are we sure she's
ready to stream uh that's a good
question but
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah she's ready to stream starting
[Laughter]
okay bye bye