[Music]
n
PA
[Music]
oh K KY key K KY key K KY key I'm going
to steal your
key
hello
welcome you're already seeing the first
car hello everybody how you doing we are
the car enthusiasts or The Drifters of
the future drifting into the future in
our dreams but soon in reality my name
is takanashi Kiara I I have opened my
eyes for cars ever since I played GTA 5
um and and now now I'm I'm a you know
I'm looking for cars everywhere I go and
yeah what about you narissa Raven coft
what's your connection with cars ah hi
Darlings this is hello live English
Advent devilish Diva the one and only
nerissa ravencraft and I have to be
honest I don't know [\h__\h] about cars
but I really like to go to round ones
and play Wong gun midnight and uh
Initial D oh that doesn't mean I know
anything about cars but I just I like to
look at cars I like to play racing games
so nice yeah me too racing games Mario
Kart yeah yeah yeah and and who doesn't
appreciate a cool car let's be so for
real absolutely like oh my God I I I was
having this discussion um on Twitter a
while ago uh I think it was when I was
in Japan I want to know how you feel
about this u a lot of people said they
understand it a lot a lot of other
people said just I don't know what the
[\h__\h] you're talking about but I was
saying that when I see like a really
really flexy car like a Lamborghini or
something like that uh I I feel like I
don't want to inflate their ego even
more so I try to not look at it and just
like
peek but not give them the impression
that I actually care about their car or
find it like cool you know I don't want
them to feel better than they already
are because I'm a I'm a pathetic peasant
and you know how do you feel about this
do you have this this this Phenom
phenomenon no I'm quite the opposite I
will go up to cool as long as no one's
in them I will take a picture with a
cool car um if I see one you will take a
picture with the cool car yeah I will I
will take a picture with me I won't like
post it or anything because like it's
just for me it's just for like my
personal collection of nerissa Raven
coft with cool cars weirdo you're such a
weirdo
even when when a person is in the car no
no no no no if they're in the car I'm
not going anywhere near it okay but um
occasionally if if it's one of my
favorite kind of cars I might be like
cool car car bro let's go you
know okay so you're you're quite the
opposite of me but recently I've been
I've been opening up a bit more and
giving the cars you know the ego boost
that they so desperately need um by
secretly taking pictures of them um but
still I'm still trying to like hide it
kind of um I understand by the way guys
uh so I opened this hashtag is this a
muscle car uh for you guys to submit
your cars uh 24 hours ago roughly and I
did not think we would get so many good
great submissions holy [\h__\h] right there
is to help me go through them and yeah I
think I'm not 100% sure but I noticed
that a lot of submissions are also from
people who don't follow me and don't
look really like a whole life fan
account and all that which gave me the
suspicion that maybe some people yeah
cuz it trended some people found the the
hashtag and saw a lot of cars being
posted and just thought oh I'll throw
mine in I don't what this is for I want
to flex my car so I did check quite
often is this person following me and it
was partially a criteria cuz I didn't
want to throw in like random people's
cars so you know just so you know and
also I could barely feature all of the
amazing cars um maybe we got to do a
part
two yeah damn there's so many I didn't
think that I mean I I knew that probably
some Japanese Bros are going to throw
their itas their like here these kind of
cars that's an itasha I thought they
would throw them in a couple of them but
sheesh there's so many awesome cars Wow
real yeah you know what Ana is Right
Nissa no oh oh it comes from I the
Japanese words like sha is for car no
normally it's kuruma but you can read it
differently than it's sha and ITA is
actually like pain um I think it's like
like it bag yeah yeah yeah exactly like
ITA bag and then there's ITA and I guess
it's like maybe they gave it the name
yeah cuz it's like supposedly cringy to
like outside people but for nerds it's
really cool right yeah so oh I see so
it's just it's it's cars with anime WS
yeah I wonder if it could also be
non-anime WS or if only anime reps are
itas but yeah basically usually it's an
anime rap yeah yeah yeah so
we'll see a couple of those yo you
already learned a new word I know thank
you I'm surprised you didn't know it wow
okay okay guys so we're going to also go
for this checklist that I have here on
above us uh we're going to rate the cars
by these very important guidelines
number one would go on a date with this
car would like to be taken out on a date
with this car I would want to be picked
up with this car for example you know
yeah and then would drive myself if I
ever get a license would post sexy for
Magazine
with would go on a road trip with so
that's like that the importance here is
how comfortable does it look to spend a
long time in uh drift potential Flex
potential steel potential steel
potential is like would I steal it or is
it going to be stolen by people is there
a danger of it being stolen and then
being me being being like [\h__\h] you
know oh there's n oh that's not how I
was going to give the points because uh
there's also getting stuck potential if
it's like too too much of a low rider um
that's not good that's a minus point and
then muscle car is it even a muscle car
but I guess if it's a nine out of 10 now
we could we could add some and make it
11 cuz the getting stuck is a
minus actually uh what what potential
guys you can you can think of one what
potential could I add I I originally had
one more that was like uh would I would
I wash this car in a bikini and or hot
pants
like hot
pants but I was like H oh what what's
this about police chase would I win
maybe would I win a police chase or
so would I win you outrun the cops yeah
oh oh yeah could I outrun the CBS C CBS
wait CS the C the CBS totally not
something of course that I would do but
could
I could I
outrun can't I can't write
outrun the cops and then I was also
thinking about would I sell candy out of
this but I felt like
M K maybe not that one uh does this make
me feel like GTA uh would I survive a
crash
what what what I need one more so that
we have wait 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 actually
steel potential is kind of a minus two
no that's a plus still you think so that
because it's worth stealing yeah it's
how desirable your car is but then still
it's like also the trouble of having it
stolen I mean yeah that would be
Troublesome but like you know okay it's
just like in GTA okay then it's not a
minus okay yeah not a minus that's a
plus okay uh
okay
we ah Euro
beat EUR a beat ability you're a beatab
you're a beat
ability that's amazing wait let me I
have no space let me move this your
repeatability I'm so sorry no I love
that what the hell that sounds like that
flows off the tongue so
greatly I'm like Shakespeare making up
words
Euro uh Euro what does that even mean
right exactly it just means could you
Euro be with it yes yeah yeah does it
suit Euro be does it suit listening EUR
beat to EUR beat
abil Japanese Bros who are watching this
waiting to see their car in the Stream
are going to be like what does this
mean okay wait so that's one one two
three four five 6 7 8 9 10 11 okay cuz
getting stuck is a minus okay mhm okay
yeah wa do we have bgm ah [\h__\h] thank
you uh uh do we do we do we yeah yeah do
you do you do you have bgm I can I can
bring up some bgm what what kind of um
Euro I feel like we can't listen for EUR
to EUR bead for too long cuz it's going
to make us go crazy so let's do that I
mean I could listen to EUR be forever
but me too me
too uh uh how about how about you're not
going to you are not going to hear it
probably
oh this is too chill this is too chill
this is my GTA chill
music no that's also so chill is that
too chill how about something that makes
your that that cooks your
brain yeah yeah we love a little Baka
flute music it's it's
[Music]
cute that's how it goes just so you know
I see I see all right prels all right
perfect okay let's get started I I we
chose like around even though it was
like probably 300 submissions we chose
around like 35 or so yeah we did our
best yeah cuz I felt like even more than
this is going to be too much but we'll
see as you've been seeing here on the
screen the first one is a Mori kop car
Kawaii and cool Nissan s13 Sylvia K
thank you for the submission
chian it's a c car K car K car KY even
replied to
this there were a bunch of Cali
itas it's crazy we love kimori in the
car scene she suits itas mhm looks looks
sick um what does it say whole app
English musician streamer also deaf she
is whole one and O only Grim Reaper Idol
Oh that's true that is true let's look
at it from different side I told you
guys to hide your plates but you didn't
why and oh oh oh that signature ooh
is it's like on the window so did they
like copy it from somewhere
else I I wonder looks good looks looks
like C did it with a lipstick even mhm
pretty and then oh
[\h__\h] look at that the the handle thingy
what this looks comfortable too it looks
it looks so tacky I love
it oh oh that's like an entry sign so
they probably uh entered it in an itasha
competition or something like that in
Japan wow the color is so nice all the
Velvet wo
damn very sexy there's like a oh wait
you don't see it because of my checklist
one one moment here look look at the top
right a little chandelier [\h__\h]
chandelier in
here you need the car
chandelier what holy moly that's that
that the inside is even more amazing
than the outside somehow I agreed I
wonder what all the like on the pass I
guess cuz this Japanese car so left side
yeah obviously left side is a passenger
seat do you see like like these like
weird controls on the yeah I'm not sure
what that is wow I wonder what that
could be maybe lights
and yeah that would make sense maybe
it's it's got an under lighting exhibit
do you remember did you watch MTV back
in the day narissa yes did you watch the
pimp my car show no no do you know do
you not know it I know I know it but I
didn't watch it my ride I watched so
many crappy TV shows on MTV back in the
day Pimp My Ride was with Limp Biscuit
right Limp Biscuit right was that his
name yeah uh and like you would bring
your shitty car and they would pimp it
but like in the craziest ways
ever
ex the second time I [\h__\h] up his name
I'm so
confused what oh God I'm so
confused lip
bis sorry
you're so cute it sounds similar um but
yeah they would pimp it but like they
would go so overboard so example if you
bring in like a like um like a truck or
something like not truck but like a Chev
or
something a like a you know where where
behind you don't have seats you just
have a space for something they would
put like a pool like a wh poool or
something up there yeah crazy [\h__\h] crazy
[\h__\h] yeah they would suit it to your to
your own desires but that was the show
and man I watched it a lot of times that
was that was really cool
yeah okay okay okay so let's let's rate
this one um number one could I outrun
the cops of this um I have thoughts on
this okay it looks fast it looks it
looks fast but it also looks very
recognizable you know it looks very
so while you might be able to outrun the
cops you're also going to be easily
Spott you know because I I I don't
actually know I've never had to run from
any cops obviously but I would presume
that they use cameras based on cop
dramas I watch to like track you and
like track the car to see where it's
going you're being so serious about this
you take it so so well it looks fast I
don't think you could outrun the comps
because I think no matter where you go
they will always find you shees okay I'm
going to have to I'm going to have to
for me I have to say it doesn't get the
point yeah okay I I guess I'll agree
with that cuz also chat a lot of chat
people said no and I would go on a date
with I would say
no because it's not wrapped in our
visuals
exactly if you if you ride up to my
house with either a Nissa or kiata house
I will probably house car I will
probably go on a date with you in it
because I love Kata and of course if
it's me I'm going to be flattered but
anyone else then I'm like excuse me I'm
always going to know that I'm your
number two right pick up cie don't pick
up us pick up Cali yeah yeah what you
doing wrong
house i' feel weird and a in a very copy
themed car going on a date I like what
is this you don't really love me you
love more
kopy yeah so I have to say it's it's a
it's a it's a no good would I drive this
myself I don't think it would be a
choice for me you you say yes yes this
is like a car you would want for
yourself it's just so
funny I love it what's funny about it
it's got so it's got so much thought put
into it you know cuz you know us Prett
basic and sweet well the inside is like
the inside is great like I'm pretty sure
you get pulled over of like right yeah
exactly like the velvet's great I love
the chandelier I'm going to have to
steal that
idea the whole time it's going to be
dangling and making clingy clicky sounds
like I don't care cars are already
annoying you know they're
like I I'll give it a yes for you thank
you okay would post sexy for a magazine
do you think it would be like even
efficient for that
usage H I think again it would look
really nice if cie was posing sexy on it
but me let's say Callie is posing for it
yes let's say yes let's say yes would go
on a road trip with no are you sure like
the interior with the chandeliers like
and the Velva is like almost like
home yeah I mean it's it's it's a really
nice feeling but this this is the
problem with like a car guy cars they
just are not big enough to where I would
feel comfortable on a road trip you know
what I mean yeah like com especially
with all the weird cables and stuff in
there like yeah maybe there's not enough
space for you know us okay yeah all
right and then drift potential hell yeah
it looks like it could I don't actually
know anything about drift yeah we said
it maybe Chad can judge that one better
could you drift with this this car drift
tell us yes definitely yes oh this is a
drift car drift
10 that's a big yes let's
drift is it does it have Flex put
potential it it does it it does it it it
does right I I don't know what that
means I depend I guess well well depends
on the audience I guess but
mhm it's a looker that's for sure I feel
like every card that I chose will be
having Flex potential
then okay check Euro beat ability yes
absolutely
yes it has your beat ability
it can play a EUR bead and it will play
it nicely yes steel potential I don't
I'm going to be real I don't think
anyone would steal this car unless they
were a kop Mori fan I think they'd see
it and they'd be like what am I looking
okay he got an anime girl on it yeah and
then if you steal it like people would
find it easily yeah yeah yeah so I don't
I think I think it's great cuz no one's
going to try to steal it from you oh
yeah so I'm still not sure is that a
plus or a minus like guess in this case
if no one's going to steal it it's a
plus this is before before you said uh
steal ability is positive because people
like it so much that they would steal it
wait before you said it's positive now
you're saying the fact that nobody would
steal it is positive I feel like it's
positive either
way [\h__\h] um let's say let's say it's
positive because otherwise it messes up
my rating okay okay okay okay uh so
it wouldn't get stolen so it's not
getting a point okay and then getting
stuck I would say it has getting stuck
potential because it's kind of low it's
really low yeah I feel like if you took
that thing the like a Texas speed bump
it would not pass yeah or like in some
the yeah so that's that's a yes but
that's a negative yes it's not good that
it could get stuck yeah 10 out of 10 get
stuck speed bumps uh-oh get in trouble
make it double is the muscle car I I
think not I don't I I'm going to be real
I don't really know what a muscle car is
muscle car is are American
narissa so you should know you should
know maybe we'll find one later then
you'll understand what the muscle car is
okay that's 1 2 3 4 five six minus one
so it's
oh is it only four that's a low rating
for this awesome car oh
no we could give a bonus
holy [\h__\h] we bonus point for being anha
mom maybe I should add okay no that's a
that's a secret rating okay so you get
five secret rating secret rating
itasha amazing car thank you for
submitting thank you wow wow wow
wow wow okay
next I love this this shape what is this
it says a Paradise of Madness D hatu
copen with Shion Murasaki hello look at
this is my car it is a small and cute
car and Sh on is painted on this car yes
cute too cute very cute I love her well
they must be an Oshi of akua
Senai obviously yeah no but oh my God I
love the shape it looks like a
two-seater
yeah but the I don't know it's so tiny I
like tiny cars too I do too and this is
it on the road again showing it feels
like the Japanese Bros don't mind
because they bring these cars to like
meetups anyway yeah oh so okay if you
post it like this to me I'm not going to
add extra work to my plate to censor it
um but yeah from the back looks really
cute too oh my God it looks so special
like you normally don't see this she
it's stanced what does it mean it's
stanced what does that mean I have no
idea
they they are out running the police at
that very moment aren't they oh my God
wait is it s does that mean because the
wheels are turned out like that they are
oh they're
what that's so like what kind of like
interesting what does that do to a car
does it know change it looks kind of
cool I want to learn camber Wheels I
want to learn more about that is that
something that's special to this car or
that you just do to cars if you want it
mostly aesthetic those Le Wheels won't
last long no performance benefit makes
cars handle better to a point a wow too
it's aesthetic I love it that's so
funny I didn't notice also this one's if
you look between the cars it's also very
low very low wow okay and and another
look from the front nice mage of H life
munaki Shion
awesome okay let's raid this uh got to
clear the old raing
[Music]
yeah all right could I outrun the cops
probably not but it was literally like
with a cop on the same picture yeah well
I think they said it's like they said
the wheels are are aesthetic and don't
really add much to the performance and
where the tires sound so I'm pretty sure
it's probably a fast car but I would
imagine that it's inconvenient in that
way and it's the same thing with the
last Tasha we saw it's got sheown on it
okay well but she's Harvard graduate so
maybe the driver is also Harvard
graduate and then then that means that
they could maybe not outrun the cops but
out talk to Cops outsmart them
mhm okay um maybe also maybe that
picture was not it out running the cops
but it being caught by the cops mhm
exactly okay so no no for that would go
on a date with honestly um simply the
the car model I would love to be picked
up with this this so cute because it's
an itasha with she own she I will give
it a yes anyway I'm going to ignore the
I'm going to ignore this because the
model is so special to me okay okay I'll
I'll give have it okay thank you say yes
would drive myself
well no I'd be too scared with those
with those Wheels turned like that I'd
be scared no I would drive it I would
drive it especially without Shon Senai
nothing against driving I'll sit in the
passenger seat how about that okay okay
the one probably the single passenger
seat yeah there's probably none in the
back I I I would love to have this model
of a car honestly I never saw this
before it's amazing mhm it it's really
cool would post sexy for a magazine no
no this is not a sexy car it's a cute
car sorry
mhm would go on a road trip with no no
thank you seems very not made for that
like can barely pack equipment for
camping or whatever in there no no sadly
sadly drift potential probably no I'm
not sure cuz it's so low to the ground
is that the is that the criteria they
say no
they say no yeah I don't I know I'm
saying I I don't think it I don't think
it can cuz it's slow to the ground the
wheels are turned like that I feel like
drifting would be hard are these wheels
actually preventing any car from
drifting I wonder I don't think it I
don't know I don't know zero potential
they all say no okay that's very clear
we agree Flex
potential
well it it definitely flexed to me build
yeah like the the car itself is really
cool so I don't know like what kind of
car it is but I've never seen a car like
that which makes me think yeah like I'd
be like oh damn that's a cool car bro
chat AG great too like it's not like the
typical Flex car like a [\h__\h] Aston
Martin but you don't even know what that
is right I do you know what do you only
know because of my tweet about the Aston
Martin what is an Aston Martin uh it's I
I only actually know because I have a
friend who really likes this oh
okay do you know because of James Bond
No or just because of the friend it's
it's a friend okay well it's a really
nice luxurious British car that
apparently is used by James Bond
oh I saw it in Japan a while ago and I
was like what the [\h__\h] is this car never
seen this like logo before so I looked
it
up okay so Flex potential yeah
for sure yeah yeah yeah it's also it
looks like kind of rare like just the
Rarity of it I F of flex Euro beat
ability I'll actually say no really why
this doesn't suit Euro beat yeah I mean
I guess it doesn't look like it looks
like it would be nice to drive at a
normal speed in but I can't see it going
super fast you know around turn and I
feel like other music fits this better
like cute music I don't know M okay also
can't even drift so like how is it going
to play EUR beat if it can't drift mhm
steel
potential again we have the the fact
that it's an itasha so would people
steal it you know no probably like even
without the itasha effect if it wasn't
an
itasha I don't
know it's difficult it's difficult
yeah I I don't think so though yeah I
don't I also don't think so I I would
want to H buy it not steal it m i want
to own it legit um getting stuck yeah
probably yeah yeah it's so low it's like
I feel like I could stick like a few
fingers beneath that and they would be
against the ground you know also it's
not a muscle car which is also
sad just kidding I don't really care
that much I love other cars too this is
a meme it's a meme because you know when
I was playing GTA 5 um that's when I
found out about muscle MUSC cars and um
like like I was like like learning which
ones are muscle cars so every time I
would pass a car I was like is this a
muscle car is this a muscle car is this
a muscle car and so it became a meme cuz
I was asking for every single car and
eventually I I I figured it out which
one is a muscle
car okay so this is one two
three uh secret itasha bonus for minus
getting stuck no it's so sad I love it I
love this car I
know you have a nice
[Music]
car I want this car I love I I'll write
it down for my future car
candidate okay next
car
wooo old man car [\h__\h] go did you just
call this an old man car yes you know
this is one of my dream cars that's not
a bad thing I like old man cars I just
call them old man cars but then it's a
old lady car okay okay so this says it's
their family's 1960 Morris Miner
convertible what does that mean a great
classic British car but with around 50
horsepower is definitely not a muscle
car
so I love classic cars so much in German
we call them old
tyers so I would I want a car like this
so it's automatically winning everything
every point for me uh wait I think
there's one more picture oh yeah this
the inside which doesn't really say
anything to me but me neither it's it
actually looks kind of empty in there
yeah it's got a cool Hood shape M yes
cute and oh from the front close it's so
pretty easy to maintain oh
really oh D look at that the size of the
engine is Tiny right I thought so too Mr
Bean car where is the engine hey you
guys are mean don't bully the
car a the seats are red inside and a
they look they look spacious and the whe
the not the wheel the the the
the uh the the steering
wheel it looks really big and thin
though
mhm looks really clean really well
maintained I love it it's my new baby um
you going to buy from them I I would
like to if you guys need it anymore I
would purchase this car wait you can
even take off the the top right yeah
it's convertible what that's what
convertible
means okay okay uh could you outrun the
Cs with this no no no but nobody who
drives this kind of car would even need
to you know what I
mean they're good
people would g a date with yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes I love I got picked up
with this car I'd be like oh my
God just me please my dream I will marry
you would drive myself
yes is it yes for you too mhm oh wow
okay I I it looked I mean the the
steering wheel's on the wrong side for
me so it probably be better as a
passenger to you but but it looks like
it would be fun to drive around like a
like quiet Countryside you know oh yeah
oh yeah true true true true oh what what
what what Morris Mino is the RIS car now
hell yeah it is there's a famous video
of one of these having been stolen and
actually got away from the police
because it fit through a gap too small
for for the police to
follow
oh that's
wild oh oh you okay okay maybe we yeah
maybe all right it happened before what
did that person
do what did they do why were they being
change no what did you do just be too
cute too cute for the streets mhm
all right would post sexy from magazine
I mean um I probably would but I don't
know about sex but me and you together
in swimsuit yeah pinup or swimsuits like
with the top down shot like I feel like
that'd be really
sexy our tops down no no no the top down
of the car the the convertible top down
when I say top down that's what I mean
but okay uh a pin up like like a 607s
look you know pinup magazine oh I think
that would actually work
yeah I just say yes to
everything but I don't think I would go
on the road trip with this right there's
no drift potential oh yeah yeah but
we're still on the road trip uh no no
right yeah no road trip I would force
myself if I had to but probably no yeah
I don't think there's on like for
something close by short but like road
trip across country absolutely not yeah
yeah sad also no drift uh Flex yes mhm
you're be a building no no you need you
need to play like
jazz jazz ability hell yeah M and uh
steal potential I don't know do these
cars get stolen I I feel
like yes yeah it's a old car but I also
feel like maybe no I don't know oh chat
is like yes S no but yeah it's antique
so no yeah yes yes like nich nich steel
Market I feel like most like there's
even more yeses than
no yeah o they are easy to steal even M
mhm well no Market
[Music]
really hard to sell okay I they get
stolen resell really
what n steal but yes okay we give it
giving a yes you steal it so yeah yes
how about getting stuck it's not that
low I think it doesn't look like it
would get stuck so I think I think no no
minus it didn't get stuck in the in the
narrow roads when being chased by the
police so no no some people say yes but
no no muscle car no so we can sum up to
1 2 3 4 five six M okay no no minus for
getting stuck that's our highest rating
so far six out of
10 okay maybe it will get stuck in some
situations but every car can get stuck
somewhere in the water or who knows some
at some point give it a bonus for not
getting stuck in most like basic
situations okay like mud it won't get
stuck in mud probably not that easily no
okay beautiful Jack car jack beautiful
car jack thank you yes thank you for oh
I want it I've been looking up prices
for this kind of car even oh yeah yeah a
while long time ago when I was playing
GTA
5 cuz they have a bunch of these too in
n all right all right Next Car woohoo
t a beautiful color look at this it's a
mustang mustang and this person thought
they were too late but no they weren't
um uh um share my beautiful brand new
Mustang to K Nissa at the whole life
Community it's such a beautiful blue it
is you don't see brightly colored cars
as often these days I feel like exactly
I love that like confidence behind it
right and it is a muscle
car yes so what makes it a muscle car
you usually it's the yeah not doesn't
have to be a Mustang but the fact that
it's like so white and they have really
strong engines you
know this is not like to
me like I guess it's like kind of like a
newer newer type muscle car like when I
think of muscle car I think of like
older muscle cars I don't know why but
yeah it's the rectangle shape yeah and
ooh fancy ooh wow wow all right o i I
think it's beautiful absolutely gorgeous
it's not that low we should note that
that's good yeah okay okay okay let's
rate this beautiful car eh what it
doesn't have a V8 it's fake that's the
echo boost version what what does that
mean EcoBoost it's a V8 still cool
doesn't look like it has a V8 but a V6 h
i people are are are doubting its uh
muscle car
ability um oh no MUSC under the
hood oh we got
pranked okay it's a pony
[Music]
car more fuel economical okay so that
already makes it not a muscle car it has
a sixpack instead of an eight pack okay
n we need an eight pack I see we're
learning here okay see that's why I at
first didn't think it was a muscle car
actually oh I said it it doesn't look
like you know the car that I would
imagine as a muscle car so I had my
doubts you know but you know some people
in chat said it's a muscle car so you
know I got well they lied I got gaset
yeah all right let's start from the
top could out run the cops with this you
think so mhm looks fast I you could it
still looks fast yeah it does like even
if it's like uh not eight pack still
looks fast and even with the bright
color I think if you were running from
the cops at night you you would be able
to hide well enough because of the dark
the the darkness you could probably hide
the very best if you drive into a
[Music]
lake water is Blue Water is blue and I
mean even without a blue car you could
hide well in there what what do you mean
the water is not
blue I mean You' got Sky yeah St
years for them to find
you amazing looks secure would going a
date with yes [\h__\h] yeah would drive
myself no it intimidates me a little bit
why would you not drive it scared I'm
scared it's if a car is too nice I don't
want to drive it like I I'd be fine
being a passenger but I wouldn't want to
drive it but honestly I would if I would
probably wouldn't be my first chice to
choice to buy it but if I had this car
if I was driving it I would feel like
wow probably very like okay there's
definitely Flex potential cuz I would
feel like sheesh I'm I'm like sexy in
this car uhhuh but the car would live in
the garage it would never leave you
think so mhm for me for me okay well
well okay let's let's not give it that
point then but would Poe sexy for a
magazine yes mhm of course sexy car
would go on a road trip with no no no
you don't think look like there's space
for anything problem is we don't have
pictures from inside so we can't really
judge there's no back door which leads
me to believe that there's no back seats
okay ah no back there's no back back
seat space um and even if the trunk is
Big because it's a smaller card there's
only as so big that it can be well there
are mixed uh mixed opinions in the chat
well some two doors do have back seats
status it does it does look to me like
it has back seats also if it's just a
two people road trip then we don't need
them that much yes we do oh but okay
some people said there is probably not
much room yeah small small small the
back seats no star space okay then no no
yeah also because ah road trip you don't
want to like go on a long trip with this
cuz you don't want to risk it getting
like bonked and H and dirty too much and
all that so okay maybe not can it drift
though I don't know I don't know it
lookss like it could maybe Drift But
yeah yes TR yes yes yes yes oh very
driftable car okay woo
don't yes g g you're a beat ability I
think it could yeah I I could see this
having an AMV made for it like of like
high high production car videos filmed
with it to eurobeat music I mean it's a
bit more to me it's a bit more of like a
rapper hip-hop car than a eurobeat car
but it could still uh do well with EUR
EUR be mhm it's too American for EUR be
too oh oh cuz Europe be is
European I don't
agree you don't agree
H that's I I think it's IR beatable I
think so
too
[Music]
or well you know Americans make Europe
be too it's not like only Europeans make
EUR beat music yeah a lot of Japanese
cars are EUR beatable even though it's
not you know technically they I mean
they also make EUR be but you know what
I mean they're not European but for the
most part but but so many people don't
agree so I almost have
to be sued in my opinion cuz even I said
it's more of a rapper car to me I don't
know or or Rock
even but it's our opinion we're raing it
on ours we just we just yeah okay okay
steal potential yes I think people would
try to steal want to steal this oh yeah
no okay that's
unfortunate but also a compliment mhm
getting stuck I think you could probably
get stuck with this it's not that low
but still kind of low mhm
what do you think
chat tell me tell me not stuck they do
get stolen a lot okay no no no no oh
okay then no Stucky muscle car I'll give
it a point five cuz it's like a
deceivable almost muscle car mhm right
so 1 2 3 4 5 6
7.5
sh ni score let's go now you guys give
it the point five come on it deserves
half a point for being almost a muscle
car mhm it deceived a bunch of people
yeah no minus one for stealing no only
that we we we decided that that would be
kind of a positive
thing the the getting stuck is the minus
MH yeah I know it's a bit confusing but
you know don't question our logic okay
thank you Eric for the nice car I'll be
awaiting you to pick me up for a prom
yes next
car
Tada T oh this one's uh a 2008
Mitsubishi Eclipse SE representing Ki
everywhere I go I like the round smooth
shape you know you can't like poke
yourself with this car it's very cute
yeah especially like the lights I don't
know the where the lights are I like the
the shape of that whole the hole
literally and I don't know it's just so
round it's like nice and there's a WWA
there do you see her I do a little
peeker a peek waha everybody uh post the
peek waha emote go also I do like the
color it's like a weird between orange
and red color but I like it mhm eclipse
wow I think like it's not that uncommon
of a car but it's just like nice to look
at I've never seen a car like this
really is it
rare guys I don't know if it's rare but
I just haven't seen one
[Music]
before especially this color you know
this was almost my first car this is
Peak fast and furious car oh really not
rare though not rare not rare pretty
common that's what I thought yeah that's
fine though you know we don't we we we
want to give not rare cars some time
shine and appreciate them uh so sadly no
inside I wonder how comfortable the
inside is MHM but let's see could you
outrun the cops with this some people
were saying this is like a fast and
furious car what I think
uh I I think you probably could cover
car for Need for Speed wow but most
people say no even though it has like a
like a game car
[Music]
reputation pretty gutless okay no no out
running potential would go on a date
with yes yes also because it's like
it's yeah and it's not too much like in
your face I I I I I need to impress you
but but it still impresses me because
it's
Charming yeah
yeah uh would drive
myself
yes yeah no I agree think I would I
think I would looks looks easy enough
actually oh my God wait you know what's
funny wait let me move my my checklist a
little bit if you look at the front if
you focus on the the lights in the front
does it not look like H the back I mean
the back does it not start looking like
the front to
you yeah does if you got rid of the the
wing yeah the shape of the back looks
like it's the front of the
car that's
funny it's got of
dumpy oh my
God it's cute I do like back windows
like that oh okay but you just know
there's no trunk space yeah probably not
much would you pose sexy for a magazine
with this though this is a nice car but
I I don't think it is so sexy I I don't
think I'd sexy it's like almost sexy
enough but not quite there's something
about missing to be sexy enough right
mhm would you go on a road trip also
probably no no yeah uh drift potential
chat help us out is this drifty Drift We
need to know we can't really judge that
that's something I need to learn no nope
no oh that's sad a lot of NOS doesn't
have to though you know for me
personally doesn't have
to you're beat the I know wait Flex
potential first flex no cuz it's really
not it's very common apparently so but
it's cute it's [\h__\h] cute I love it to
me it's a
flex and you're beat
ability what you say
n no no I feel like it has Z any yeah I
think any car can be your a beatable you
know yes but people say yeah I think I
think so too to me it's EUR I can I can
be persuaded okay like I I can see it I
can feel it I can imagine it driving in
this playing EUR beat H EUR beat
version not GT enough no not enough but
the GT version yes yes most people say
yes it's pretty fast too okay all right
steel potential probably no uh I feel
like just because it's a basic car the
Ste potenti ability actually goes up you
know because obviously if it's a really
really nice car people are going to try
to steal it right but also if it's a
more basic people are going to try to
steal it also because they're like well
no one will miss this and it's basic
enough that if I change the plates I
might be this is the owner certainly
will well yeah I'm not saying that I'm
not I'm not saying you know that that
that's true I'm saying you know the
mindset from of a thief even though it's
kind of a negative thing we will give it
a yes and it will be a good point for it
getting stuck I it doesn't look like it
get stuck it doesn't look too low it
doesn't look like a big issue and it's
not a muscle car sadly yeah uh where are
the muscle cars where are they 1 2 3
four that's four points you you you have
a a big big point in my heart though so
yeah for the for the K we should give it
a f for the Kiana
peer five I can't write five for a small
small wa peeking yeah yeah yeah okay a
nice car like for me personally I like
it a lot so you know don't feel bad
about it you know MH next car ooh it's
an orange
car this is orange and it looks old I
love it it's it looks classy to me it's
a 1972 Datsun Nissan 2
240Z and old the plate says
otaku do you see this antique otaku like
they probably don't even drive this
because of that plate I don't know oh
see it looks even a bit broken on the
front but
wow
cute that's such a cool trunk too it
opens all the way all the way so the
window and everything goes up too oh so
big trunk but it doesn't look like it
have back
seats it looks like it's just a trunk
yeah mhm M oh but oh my God what a
car what a car it's Legend I I want this
car now in my life I even replied to
this one cuz it's orange it made me
happy MH
okay yeah let's get to raing this like
damn could I outrun the cops of this
maybe back in the day maybe in 1972 but
not now they don't even use
it ch I don't okay but they're look
they're saying that this is a lady
Z so if if true uh I don't remember
exactly what kind of car the ladies is
oops fake fan but I think they say it's
modified what how do you
know yes only if moded yes yeah okay
yeah yeah I think I what's a what's a
Fair Lady
D um so in in wongan Midnight there's
the the car
the the like main car and it's the fair
lady Z it's really fast obviously it's
modded to hell and back um but uh it's
it's it's really cool really cool ah Z
is what 240 Z is but in Japan somebody
said so same car just different name
aha so they say especially if it's mod
then yes okay I I guess yes okay we
going to date with [\h__\h] yes yes I want
to date the
car
mhm it's which means we'd steal it right
we're going to steal it together oh [\h__\h]
yeah stealing yes would drive myself yes
with post sexy yes would go on the road
trip with no sorry I can't I can't give
it a point for that one but has a huge
trunk and it gives you like this kind of
like atmosphere you know that that is
kind of Road tripy I would go for a
night drive with it but I would not go
on a road
trip H A lot of people say they
would um well they're all car guys so
they're it's apparently
driftable oh y our is this our first or
second drift car drift car I think our
second
M okay people are especially cuz you
don't want to go on a road trip with it
there's like split
opinions if it's just us I feel like it
would be
romantic you've got a point yeah just
you and me yeah it's a two-seater so
that makes it romantic but it still has
so much space in the back and don't you
feel like this is just so so oh like I
feel like what we could do with this is
we could like do a shotgun wedding and
run away with this car across America
wait what what what did you just say to
me a shotgun that's what that is right
when you like suddenly No No Kata change
the subject [\h__\h] oh what is
that oh wait was was shotgun winning
when uh you kill you when you put a bun
in the oven and then uh you are forced
to become married because there is a bun
in the oven wait what do you call them
married when you go like quickly like
Las Vegas and go what eloping no no that
is not a shotgun a shotgun wedding is a
forced wedding usually by the parents
because of like pregnancy or other
reason oh but but you know the the
theory of what I just said is like I
would just get we would alope together I
this is an eloping car yeah loping car
should we add the
criteria it do be an eloping car like
it's a movie carard like holy
[\h__\h] okay if it's just us I suppose that
I can give it a yes for road trip Fu
[\h__\h] yeah okay also it's a flex is it
you're a beatable absolutely yes yes
110% you're a beatable oh [\h__\h] it's not
a muscle car and I don't know about it
get getting I think it looks like it
could get stuck I have to be honest it
looks like if it like went up on that
curb the bumper might even get stuck oh
oh it's Japanese muscle well okay that's
not really okay I didn't think of that
but okay muscle car no Sports what do
you mean Japanese muscle Japanese
muscle I guess it looks like it could be
I need to see a a a proper front view
also cuz like this is like wide angle so
I can't judge how wide it really is it's
proba it's probably pretty wide cuz old
car but also like look that parking spot
if these are American American SAS
parking doesn't seem like it's terribly
large because look it's only filling up
like not not like a huge amount of it ah
but people are very sure about it being
a Japanese muscle car okay I'll give it
the muscle car Point okay but you said
it would get stuck so that's a
minus holy [\h__\h] all the check boxes are
check that's a
n let's
go wow congratulations Kelly
congratulations for this beautiful car
what a flex what a freaking Flex we're
going to steal it from you now thank
you we would like to take this car away
from you you don't mind right you're not
driving it are
you all right next
car this looks like that one car from
that one show wait is it the is it the
initial de car are they selling it
because there's a price tag there maybe
it's the picture from when they bought
it
though oh my God there's a little
[Music]
video wait I'll move us
away do you see this on the right side
it opens its
eyes I love hor with the Blinky little
eyes oh my God immediate win so this
person posted two cars a 1988 Nissan
Sylvia S12 and a 2005 Nissan 3 5 Z named
Maru
hanachi um this one's really cute let's
just judge the first car but this one's
adorable it's cute but let's judge this
one yeah I agree yeah it's like an an
old definitely an old looking car but
when I saw it it gave me Euro beat Vibes
so it it does cuz it looks kind of like
the car I I don't know what it is but it
looks kind of like the initial D car
wait are you guys reacting to the yellow
one some people are like 350 J oh my God
POG is this one so
[Music]
special from initial this one's Initial
D which one do you mean guys this one
looks more like Initial D to me
yeah 350 de gray is not true and no
what that was funny yeah it's in Germany
this car is currently in Germany so it's
very again very eurobed
mhm that's an S12 syia yeah yeah it says
Sylvia S12 what do you
mean if white instead of gray yeah then
it would be even more the ideal I don't
know initial DEC car I don't know we'll
just rate this one okay oh yes could you
outrun the cops of
this I'm not sure it doesn't look like
it right no not really looks too old too
weak mhm okay no chat agrees would go on
a date
with no no yeah no yeah I mean if that's
what the Blinky eyes are so cute but at
the same time like the color you know I
mean here it's kind of dirty so it could
probably be getting a a glow up if you
clean it propably mhm but still it's
like if you have if that's all you have
okay cool but
compared to the others no
yeah would you drive this
yourself sure I give it a I give it a
drive if only to mess with the Blinky
eyes I say big no from me not my kind of
car okay okay well I'm only I'm I'm only
you know I'm not too particular about
driving it or not so we can give it a
enough okay would post sexy for a
magazine no no [\h__\h] it's not doing so
well oh no we go on a road trip with
no but drift
potential please tell us it has drift
potential please say yes because we need
something good for this
car yes no yes yes yes yes yes no no yes
yes yes yes you can all right okay thank
God drift drift uh drifting yes what
about
flexing I think you could do Flex simply
for the Blinky eyes oh yeah oh yeah they
are flex and probably to car Geeks it's
probably also flexy because of the
oldness yeah MH okay the the eyes are
just wow so cute uh steel no cuz this
person literally bought it yeah yeah I
don't I don't think too many people
would try to steal it yeah yeah yeah
this old old
car not really something you would steal
we steal different car instead but it
doesn't look like it would get stuck
yeah I I would say so too unless the
engine dies because it's too
old yeah just looks so old to me it
looks it looks older to me than the
classic car the little one that we were
looking
at I know just it's the photo I think
it's the photo it's just not very
Charming at the
moment
so I
yeah wait so no stealing getting stuck
no muscle car no no okay so sadly so
it's four points because because it
didn't have getting stuck potential so
it has it gets a point for that no no so
far we were using it like if that get
only it just takes it away yeah okay so
no extra point for not having it mhm
so so so so okay well but I want to give
it a extra five for the Blinky eyes so
that's wow that's huge thank you for the
submission sorry for being like roasting
it it's not a bad car but like you
know next car wow oo like I saw so many
itas but this one stands out to me cuz
it's monochrome mhm and the doors yeah
the doors of course holy [\h__\h] and this
one's a Honda Accord wagon with Aman
canata gorilla according to them it it
said so in
the here here that they wrote gorilla
okay not me mhm um so wow it's very low
holy [\h__\h] I have a thing for Honda
Accords because my first ever car was a
Honda Accord oh so it was an older one
so it wasn't this cool it was like a
more basic but I really so I really like
w wow that's why you knew that car name
I was
surpris also look at the star shaped
Wheels thingies yeah the yeah wow wow
wow I like this art mhm oh oh cute
that's on the
[Music]
doors cute I love that it's all you know
outlines just like not colored M okay oh
the lights are also really like
Sleek yeah sheh it looks also pretty
wide and big mhm it looks huge it looks
it looks like there's a lot of space
like the ass of the car is over the line
in the back oh
yeah okay okay let's go um this is again
in itasha mhm did we didn't we give uh
cars that are Ita has an extra point I
think so it was a secret yeah we gave
them style points yeah no it was yeah it
was a secret style point for being an
ITA could you out find the cops with
this no are you sure cuz you probably
could but only be I'm only saying no
because of how low to the ground it is I
feel like you get caught on something
and stuck and not suful okay it does
look to me like it has a strong engine
but yeah it would probably get
stuck um then would you go on a date
with this
no because it's got Kata sen yeah again
that issue and even without
that like the first look really
impresses me but then you know it's not
that like you know you know I don't know
it doesn't have that special romance
romance factor to it yeah mhm okay would
drive myself
no I see I like I like the Honda again I
like the Honda Accord but oh wait you
drove it yeah old old old one old old
old one very old one it like this one
looks very masculine scary yeah like the
doors going up like that scares me how
low to the ground it is is scary I don't
think I would trust myself to not put a
scratch on it and therefore I would not
okay drive it would Poe sexy for a
magazine no because it's got but before
we said like for the Cali it we said if
cie poses for it then yeah can POS with
this then yeah but not not me but then
canata is also not very sexy though so
it couldn't be for a sexy magazine be
sexy dress her up as a racing girl a
racing Queen and she look
great I'm not giving them point for that
no
okay what she's cute guys come on she's
incredibly cute and pretty but I
wouldn't put her in the sexy category
like no way to S by hello unbelievable
unbelievable poron or
something excuse me
princess okay I think it could work I'm
just trying to judge it by this category
okay would it be in a sexy
[Music]
magazine we can agree to disagree it
would
be car magazine mhm that's where it
be yeah uh would go on a road trip with
I was pointing out it's really spacious
yeah I I think again the only reason I'd
say no is because of how low of the
ground it is yeah that's like it but
this one does have back seats and a
trunk so like on one hand I'm like yeah
I could let's give it a it let's give
cuz um I don't know it just it looks
like it could be a comfortable car for
that
purpose potholes would ruin it well but
Japanese this probably yeah this is in
Japan on Japanese roads like they're so
flat and straight you know there's not I
never felt a poth hole in Japan before
D on the on the on the on the autoban at
least on the highway you know and that's
where you would go for a road trip like
on the highway so it's fine for a
highway right
that's Japanese roads are fine for this
Japanese road trip yes drift
potential
we look to chat for the answer I would
say no it doesn't look like drifty yeah
not particularly okay Flex though I will
say it's kind of flexy like look how
wow wide it is how the the the tires
look like the doors
obviously the doors are crazy that's a
big flex your beat
ability yes yeah I think so too it may
be
Japanese car but I think this your beat
ability is off the roof mhm steal
potential probably no I don't think
people would attempt to steal this yeah
like if it if it didn't have Kanata on
it I think maybe mhm but I think I think
because it sticks out so much it's
another one of those like people will be
able to find it easily yeah so like well
it would have its Niche people who would
steal it they would never be able to
drive it anywhere because then the
person looking for it you know would
find it very recognizable yeah also in
Japan I would say just by because Japan
is low crime
rates that there are not many cars being
stolen yeah uh getting stuck
yes AB muscle car it looks like to me
almost like a muscle car like Japanese
maybe Japanese muscle car I still don't
know what a muscle car is it's
not it's not Hondas are great yeah it's
not but it gives me muscle car Vibes
almost cuz it's so
wide and so that means one two three uh
plus another one for itasha minus one is
free
points which I think is almost too low
yeah I feel bad I feel
bad but it is what it is you know it
is sorry itasha Bros yeah oh wait
four yeah minus one okay okay my rating
is correct okay next
car it's a [\h__\h]
Mustang ooh another a 2018 Mustang with
RTR flaring whatever that means I have
no idea and it is a muscle car let's
[\h__\h]
go okay so what what what normally tells
me that it's a muscle car is when it's
like this wide and fat uh and then also
the the weird things on the top uh of
the front do you see that that's like
typically typically muscle car for me
like my judgment is just by what I saw
in
GTA but you know oh Mustang RTR it even
says so on the windows the hood vents oh
yeah they don't always have that yeah
but to me that's like one one way of
judging
it oh one more photo
oh speaker hi Cy why are you showing me
the middle finger what the
hell dead beat car all right it's a nice
color it's a big car it's a [\h__\h]
Mustang it's a muscle car I have some
opinions so let's go let's go from the
bottom first and make our way up okay so
getting stuck potential I think it's
fine I don't think it's going to get
stuck okay steal I think people would
steal it yes which apparently is a good
thing EUR beatable I think so I think
you could Euro beat this car what do you
thinku yeah [\h__\h] yeah hell yeah Flex
potential I think so too hell yeah [\h__\h]
yeah drift potential chat this is your
time to shine do muscle cars
drift can muscle can you drift a muscle
[Music]
car yes yes yes yes all right
lucky would you go on a road trip with
it
I'm not sure I don't think so it doesn't
even look that spacious in the back not
at all yeah not not at all so no I'm
going to have to say no okay no uh would
you post for a magazine I think I think
it has yeah because first of all it's
not even a ITA so that kind of makes it
work better and then it has like kind of
like a You Know Rich car luxury car
image Vibes so sex lady on top of that
amazing yeah yeah exactly AKA us on top
of that
amazing
mhm next would drive myself I would I
would try it I would try driving it yeah
like not really what I would go for but
all right yeah actually yeah why
not um looks like fun mhm yeah I I would
not go on a date in this car what okay
let me explain myself it's a very cool
car the reason I wouldn't is I I have a
Vibe I have a Vibe I could be wrong but
I feel like someone who has this kind of
car I will always come second to their
car sorry I don't know how to explain it
but I feel like I would come second to
the car so I think I think I wouldn't be
able to I wouldn't be able to go on a
date i' it and I'd be like you're very
nice but I think we should just be
friends yeah this yeah well yeah yeah I
I can see what you mean like probably
they they love car well maintained it's
beautiful it's got all this look we even
love it you know like this this guy I
bet or this person I'm sure they love
their car and I just don't think they'd
be able to love me but what if what if
now this is just like not necessarily
applying to this person but what if for
example um like this person just has
this car because they have too much
money and so they could afford it and
they really like it but it doesn't mean
that they don't like you know they just
had like all this overflow of money so
they spent it on the car but it doesn't
mean that that's their like one thing in
life like you know it doesn't have to be
but so if it was a rich guy or yeah if
it was a rich guy then this is nothing
to
them then that's just this is just like
a toy car and you are the real deal to
them
maybe then then yeah I suppose if that's
the case but I you know I just I just I
I have the vime why would you would you
go on a date in this car Kiana I would
be extremely impressed and like probably
strongly influenced by this car
yes it's kind of [\h__\h] sexy it's a
muscle car I would I would like to be
picked up with this I would feel
so agree to
[Laughter]
disagree could you outrun the cops of
this though no yeah probably yeah yeah
yeah yeah you could you totally could
strong good engine go fast yes go go gas
gas gas gas gas step on the gas uh yeah
people are great uh I think so uh oh not
around a corner so only straight only
Highway chases no oh a lot of people say
no it will hit hit people first oh oh oh
depends on the engine not a V8 okay
apparently if it's a V8 which is
apparently what this is then
no all right okay well I already got
enough points anyway so 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 -
1 6
hey what's what's the six what the
hell i'll six there we go go
congratulations good rating yeah thank
you for your submission for your cool
card y- 6 you guys not listen see oh
never mind there is no stuck potential
sorry yes sorry sorry there's no stuck
potential so you can have
seven oh oopsy well okay next oh wait
this is the same car yeah oh [\h__\h] yeah
that it's so pretty it's even so like
well polished oh my
God it's so pretty okay next
car should be an eight what 1 2 3 4 5 6
7 oh I can't
count it wasn't eight even okay damn
okay next uh is a
mha and there was so many itas but this
one like color-wise it's amazing
especially with the interior because
look at
this oh my god wow
right the brown is
so like wow very cool looking it looks
so soft and and
comfortable and the the shade of brown
is like really calming to me and then
what is
this ooh
inside I don't know but that's a coffee
machine in the
I don't think that a coffee machine but
it looks cool doesn't it people will
tell us uh air suspension what does that
do can it like
bounce or what air
suspension what does that do is that a
brick it might just be a wallpaper but
yeah it looks like brick MH it's cool
raise and low oh so you can like raise
and lower it depending on how you want
it on that day
oh well that would be useful because
look how low it is M if it can go higher
than that then it might not need to get
stuck yum okay ooh also look at the
wheels those are special too the the the
the what do you call again the like
inside of the
wheels hub caps H H Hub Hub Cap mm caps
rims they say rims uh
uh they're hub caps you can call them
rims too not they say not hub caps no I
disagree what is the difference between
a rim and a hubcap let me look it up
look it up look it up H caps what are
what's the difference I love this hubc
whe difference between what is a
hubcap I don't understand anyway far
rimon
I love the the art that they chose for
the back
here and yeah looks really nice I I'm
it's hard to tell like what color the
it's called the that the main car is
like what is this gray brownish gray
yeah it looks kind like a brownish gray
I like it it's a weird color but it
works with the m theme mhm also by the
way it's a p RC z p French I think would
be French maybe yeah very unique color
like holy [\h__\h] the inside impressed me
so hard it's
gorgeous and like what what this what
okay could outrun the cops question mark
probably not also again cuz it's an ITA
we had that before would go on a date
with no cuz M on
top would drive my self no not my kind
of car we agree we agree on so much
would post sexy for a magazine M could M
could but admittedly I don't think it's
a very sexy car it's a very nice looking
car but I don't think it's a sexy car
and I also don't think mum is sexy but
well why do you think so many people
aren't sexy K cuz that's my main of
course you can pose them in a sexy pose
and in a sexy outfit but generally I
when I think of mum she's not
sexy okay she's cute but when I think
back of the H fan art where all of us
are in those really really skimpy
outfits sitting together drawn by Mama
Loney that was
sexy mhm yes but again you can draw
anyone sexy it's not an insult guys it's
just you know there's there's like
typically like you look at them
immediately and they're like oh sexy and
then this m who's cute which they both
are good things they're just different
types okay calm down
so no sexy
Magazine on a road trip with it
either yeah no road trip
no look at the storage yeah yeah sad uh
drift uh I don't it's so it's so low to
the ground could it
drift I don't think
so no oh no dad oh man Flex I think it's
a flex I you can Flex yeah I think you
can Flex with this car the inside
especially is it EUR
beatable I think you could Euro beat it
but I think everything is EUR
beatable oh it's
not not like 100% but a lot of people
say Yeah in the chat okay I'll give it
the you a beat steel probably no I about
the type of car like if this car without
the the M would be still something to
steal but p l no poor
p I would steal it I would steal it yo
don't write this in the comments it will
be used against you in court
later
yeah I would steal so much oh
wow no one would steal a p are you
joking oh oh my God people hate the P
what oh my God it's getting
bullied okay no steal potential getting
stuck getting stuck it's so low to the
ground but but but it has that thing in
the car yeah so I think I think we can
say we can we cannot give it the the the
nerfing I agree unfortunately it's not a
muscle car MH so secret Point yeah right
so that's free point
secret itach let's go thank you for your
submission the Inside Man the inside so
cool amazing and by the way I'm I'm like
so [\h__\h] slow I need to go a bit
faster it seems cuz I have so many more
submissions next we have a 2015 Toyota
86 uh named ghost okay I thought it
looked
really sleek and sexy and beautiful it's
also probably light in here but damn
lighting the lighting adds to it oh oh
my look at go
Zoom they're saying very driftable too I
think in that very picture it's drifting
cuz of the the the the cloud that smoke
coming up yeah the smoke it's out
running the cops oh a video ah yeah GAA
is in
there go oh the seats look comfy those
look like racing seats
oh that is a drift car mhm oh he's going
to turn on the
[Music]
engine
oh oh narissa doesn't hear it but it
goes oh I I bet it's purring it's
purring and goodai is sleeping M well
the purring must be very relaxing oh
yeah Safety First Safety First yes yes
got to protect your o all right right
okay okay wo W wo wo wo okay it it it
has strong racing car Vibes definitely
out running the cops of this one in my
opinion
definitely are you tired no sorry oh no
sorry I'm always yawning I'm I've said
this I'm God sleepiest Soldier so oh
okay would you go on a date with this it
doesn't have like anything like it that
much to it so yeah I think I think I
would if they if they got rid of temper
early the the
GAA yeah the ga you know just put it
away you got to ride in the trunk it in
the trunk yeah actually it's not a fast
car but it looks like it R runs
it just
imagine uh so would go yeah would drive
myself not necessarily no I'm scared not
not even that it's just not my type of
car but I feel like you could pose sexy
for it though like on like the hood yeah
yeah it could be a sexy relatively sexy
wait let me look at if you look at this
and this that's a sexy car the front wow
all right would you go on a road trip
with this no no yeah I guess so yeah I
like the shape man wow MH and drift
potenti it was drifting I think in the
picture right guys yes
let's look at it again here it is
beautiful picture drifting is a yes oh
yeah I want to hear it I wish I wish he
was drifting in the video that he
sent but okay Flex is a flex yeah I
think you Flex I going give it some Flex
oh okay the EUR beat yes I think it's
EUR
beatable
mhm never saw you there mentally yeah
yeah no I agree sorry looking at the
card the picture is really
cool I like the headlight so much
they're such a unique I love ones that
make me think of eyes yeah yeah yeah
because like you know it just like it
feels like you're looking at someone
with a unique face and I like it a lot
it looks like it has eyeliner on and a
mustache
mhm actually oh my God that's so cute
steal potential what about
that I think I think people would steal
it because it doesn't look two out there
but it also looks cool but I think I
couldn't tell 100% so I could be 100%
wrong but it looked like a it looked
like a what is it called [\h__\h] I forgot
the word um a manual it looked like a
manual and not everyone can drive a
manual ah oh my God I watched this video
where somebody stole a car and it's like
from the car camera inside and he just
couldn't drive it I guess cuz it was a
manual I think that was the issue yeah
and then he was trying then people
outside but even trying to help him like
are you okay like oh you're sorry I just
having troubles with my car and then he
just eventually he just like he just
left it somewhere ditched it soon after
that's how the guy got his car back so
maybe that's a big plus to having manual
cars yeah not everyone see manuals a lot
of people who like to drive fast really
like manuals because apparently it gives
you more control um but a lot of people
these days if they're not really into
cars might not know how to drive a
manual so like I can't drive stick shift
for example oh so you could not steal it
I could not steal this car getting stuck
I don't think guys getting stuck
potential yeah I don't think so it's
also not a muscle car so 1 2 3 4 5 6
7even not
bad not bad congratulations ni thank you
for submitting thank you looks really
cool and then next
car did I not have this one oopsie okay
this is cute right it has CP in the back
it fits so well
69 oh yeah it's a Kia Picanto it's small
car you like its color I also got kfp
logo sticker at the back cute I I I you
know I wanted to put some smaller cars
in there as well um MH this is so cute
yeah I like the designs on it it's so
cute cute this it very dark tinted
window can't see in
the wow privacy
hello maybe that speaks for a road trip
narissa oh
wow o inside looks comfortable too I
know it's small but I
mean I don't know it's not a bad thing I
would say yeah no I mean the the trunk
still looks like it it still has back
seats yeah so the trunk looks like it's
probably not too big but this is I'd
imagine the seats probably are able to
go down meaning that whole back area
turns into a trunk oh yeah oh yeah lots
of lots of storage space technically no
back seats theoretically speaking in
terms of storage so you don't have like
both together but it looks like it
probably does have pretty decent storage
The Tint is apparently kind of
illegal yeah it does look
illegal maybe it's the contrast of the
big okay mhm well that would mean that
it might get into a Chase with the cops
yeah I don't know if it would out on the
cops probably
not but I feel like with such a cute car
you could make good excuses mhm it's a
cute car depends on the country true
okay but probably no what running would
go on a date with I say yes yeah any any
fan of kiata is a good person oh yeah
true true especially cuz D would drive
myself yes I like small
cars yeah you know me too it's not too
big it's not too big so I wouldn't be
too scared I actually don't like cars
like uh you know Cadillacs are huge oh
yeah I don't like to drive them because
of that but I I would drive this it
doesn't look too big true it looks more
Dynamic this way M can turn it easier I
don't know M would po sexy for a
magazine no no sorry it's a cute car not
as Mex would go on a road trip with yeah
yeah even though it's so small it kind
of looks fun to go on a road trip with
you know right exactly and like there is
still storage space in the back so I
think I think especially if it's a
shorter trip you could definitely make
it work yeah okay nice looks reliable
too yeah yeah I think so i' road trip
hell yeah and drift probably not
Flex not
really I don't know look cool yeah some
of the like race car details are cute
like the on the bottom between the uh
wheels and on the top it's kind of you
know like a race
detail for the tint it's not a it's not
it's not really a Flex car let's be
honest okay but that's fine it don't
have to be you be
ability I think so I think so I but I'm
I think everything's you're beat you're
beatable yeah I think if you look at the
inside again
yeah yeah if you're the one driving it's
EUR
beatable okay I already turned you down
on the flex so I'm going to take the EUR
beat uh
steal uh I don't think people would
steal this yeah I don't I'm not
sure I it's it's nice car but I don't
think it's distinct enough that I don't
think people would steal it mm
H okay yeah lots of Kia get stolen oh
really Kia is the most stolen car in the
US oh I just were're wrong really but
pantos they're really easy to Ste really
it's very cheap and common maybe for
parts oh oh but generally like I don't
think your first thought is I have to
steal this because it's so cool mhm I
want this for myself maybe for selling
Parts yeah but they get stolen like
crazy really all right I'll give it the
point all right okay you you got me
getting stuck potential I would say no I
don't think it looks like it would get
stuck no it looks like it can handle
many situations quite well mhm but it's
not a muscle car so 1 2 3 4
five not bad oh nice see even small cars
can be rated well by us mhm I I mean
it's only five out of 10 but compared to
some other lower rankings this is good
mhm good small smaller smaller car it
has a lot of difficult competition so
this good rating thank you for the
submission next next
[Music]
is yeah I love it this is like 69 it
feels like some parts are missing like a
top but yeah that's probably cuz they
have the top down um it's a 1927 Ford
Model T pick up Roadster hot rod it's a
hot rod
oh please forgive me as the engine is
equipped with the same small block as
the as the C1 Corvette I love ki's
pineapple song me too thank you we love
pineapple oh my
God that's
amazing I love this what's this green
apple
juice you see it yeah what is that I
don't know
gas
wow I don't know what I'm looking at
coolant huh damn it's such a special car
man wow rare rare to see this kind of
car amazing I've never seen a car like
this ever well I've seen a hot rod being
built in um Home
Improvement was that what it's called in
in
English do you know that show uh yes
yeah I've been binge watching it
recently and the the the the guy you
know he the the dad he throughout the
whole show he builds hot rods in his
garage
yeah with Tim Allen
yeah
Tim the Tool Man W that's his sound he
makes
[Music]
the manly masculine
noises yeah yeah yeah I I haven't been
watching that out of nostalgia cuz they
have it on Disney plus big
recommend okay so
uh you makes that sound when he's
confused
[Music]
[Laughter]
like I'm reporting you you're so
funny okay so uh no Runing the cops no I
would go on a date with this yeah it' be
fun it' be fun for a onetime experience
yeah like oh my God we could we could
act like we're in The Great Gatsby
movie yeah I love the great gu that's
one of my favorite movies can we watch
it together
yes let's
go H would drive myself no looks
difficult to drive but I
would like this kind of classic car is
what I dream of for myself but I would
exactly I wouldn't okay but you know my
goal is to like get a car like a classic
looking cool car like this but I would
want it to be like drivable in a modern
way like I want the inside to be modern
you know what I mean yeah yeah exactly
like for me I don't think I don't think
I could drive it mhm at the current mhm
yeah okay
so I would drive it though I I would
attempt to I would want to I would want
to learn how to drive it a retro mod yes
I want a retro mod yes that's for me
please thank
you collectors will mold well they can
mold all they want as long as I'm happy
with my car then you can be
jelly go away no power steering what
does that
mean do you know
Nel I'm not particularly sure what that
means P power stealing did you say yeah
power steering power Ste no I have no
idea hard to steer steering will be
harder in this current State I suppose
so yeah I mean it it looks it looks diff
I mean are there seats in the car it
just yeah just the front uh like there
should be it almost doesn't look like it
but there should be at least a passenger
seat and I think like normally like you
could sit in the back um but you look
backwards yeah that's what I've seen
with cars like this but with this one it
almost looks like there's almost no
seating ability yeah yeah
it's this one's probably a two seater
yeah but I I've seen cars like this with
a bench in the back a bench that like is
also outside even when the car does have
have its top on then there's a an
outside seating that's a bench that
looks backwards I've seen that which is
kind of funny I like
that okay so would post sexy for
magazine no no not really I mean it's a
cool car but it's not a sexy car again
you could make it work with pinup but
okay let's say no let's say no road trip
no no no D look like it'd be comfy no
drift flex no drift yes yes absolutely
your beat ability no no that we we got
to get the whatever 20 30s 40s jazz in
there steal potential would people steal
I don't think no I don't think anyone
would steal this out of respect they
shouldn't
mhm wait they say drift yes what how do
you drift this
yeah there's a lot of people said drift
yes
[Music]
what
what they would steal
this yeah cuz it's like too so antique
so old looking so special yeah May might
get stolen no not in Japan probably but
elsewhere yeah
[Music]
what let me what what was that rear
wheeel drive is
Drifter ah so when the yeah somebody
else said that too when it's like
focused on driving in on the back wheels
then it can drift this car can drift
that would be so funny I guess it's
drift potential drift is the natural
state of this
car all right unexpected if you just
look at it but uh wow don't judge a car
by its cover and it doesn't look like it
gets stuck so I think we can skip that
one yeah show proof chat well maybe
maybe this car owner will show us a
video of him drifting in the
future please all right we'll give it a
chance we'll uh give it the the benefit
of the doubt getting stuck potential no
I don't think this car looks like it
gets stuck in anything and it won't it's
not a muscle car so 1 2 3 4 five
hi very nice special car in between all
the like modern ones mhm next
[Music]
on wait wait this is the GFR 23 formula
student race car that was designed at
Oregon State University entirely by
engineering students like me I thought I
should include this it's an all electric
prototype our team competed globally in
the USA Hungary and Germany last summer
look look that's
cool oh look at them which one is the
fan the whole life
fan what I want to know what is this box
on
top looks so funny mhm what a race car
smaller smaller race car so funny down
Force what cool project that is yeah
cool baby
F1 a does
yeah gas
gas gas gas gas well well well let's R
this car sh
we H spoiler plus one point let's R this
as much as we can could outrun the cops
yes of course yes H yeah of course it's
very fast I think fast would go date no
how no absolutely not not maybe you can
sit in the back like in the box thingy
or in the front of the on the nose I
don't know it looks dangerous it looks
like a one person car so not not as fit
for a date looks like a are you sure are
you sure that's a one person car yes yes
I'm posit I'm
positive would po sexy for magazine no
no would go on road trip no no drift is
[Music]
this low I don't know about I mean yeah
race cars I think can usually dri so
maybe it's built to be able to cuz it
looks really small you know they no yes
and when they go like so fast around the
curves I feel like that was drifting but
I guess not too much they're saying no
okay yes but no no drift ability Flex
Flex potential yes because they built it
it's a student car hell yeah that's
that's cool as [\h__\h] and it's it stands
out in my stream Europe a beat yes
yes seal potential no no yeah not really
I
mean yeah what are you going to do with
that drive drive through the drive
through New York I don't know M getting
stuck
potential uh well I mean it's supp to go
fast so but it's really low so I feel
like it would get stuck but I also feel
like because it's a race car it would
never be in a situation where it would
get stuck so I feel like it but it would
it would get stuck though yeah it will
get stuck
in my garage Road on a real
Road it's not a muscle car so one two
three four we have to speed up a little
bit so I'm speeding up but thank you I'm
speeding up like this car gas gas gas
gas next oh let's go cute ooh classic
car and recently owned okay to I owned
this 50 plus year old Ford toos 17m
super oo nice I love this kind of of
like creamy beige colors you know and
then inside it's red so I feel this
speaks like so much like classic
Oldtimer to me mhm wow cute there's like
a lot of these like older cars around
here they're like collecting them I
think
yeah I don't know why but for some
reason it makes me think of karma Poli
by radio head Karma Poli By Radio I
don't know interior that's okay just
forget about it forget about it it's a c
on the side you see a beetle which is so
cute but we're judging this one okay the
one on the front that's not a
[Music]
beetle gosh okay okay I I wish I could
judge all the cars oh my god let's go
let's go I run the cops no what going to
date with yes yes yes would drive I
would I would yes I would try it I would
try it
too would po sexy yes pin up okay pinup
but it's not even m
no would go on a road
trip no no
drift no doesn't look like it uh
Flex yeah it's old old as hell it's
still running flexing to the right
people mm uh ability no no
steel yes because it's old there's a
niche audience for it but I feel like
people would steal it okay getting stuck
no muscle car no okay Four
Points let's go thank you for your
submission thank
you bye bye next okay a [\h__\h] oops here H
shark gooa car so go the shape of this
vehicle is like to me pretty typically
Japanese shape um like when I'm in Japan
most of the cars are like kind of like
this box shape you know which personally
is not really my thing but it's like
very common in Japan and it gives you a
lot of space to turn it into an ITA shop
cuz like there's so much artistic
Freedom space you know it's amazing mhm
so the the description says I
incorporate Incorporated the background
design I made into the illustration
drawn for this car the interior was
designed to give the impression of
spending time under the sea while riding
o can we see that there's a there's a
surfboard wakeboard or something like
that up there
oh that's so cool Fuji son fui let's go
I want to see the inside yeah can we oh
there we go yay oh that's cool the wheel
is blue the top has like
sharks nice oh and like SE too yeah I
was going to say the chairs have like
blue blue edges diamond pattern mhm all
right okay nice Scooby b car M uh let's
write
this could out run the cups no no what's
going to date with no no would drive
myself no no well well no I would
actually I would I would I would be down
to try this okay I'll give it a yes for
you would post sexy for magazine no not
a sexy car we going to road trip with I
think like the space Japanese cars like
this they have so much space yeah I
would take this on a road trip I once
went on something like a road trip like
a like a not really but it was a long
ride and I was really tired with a car
like this in Japan and um I was able to
like sleep in the trunk like there were
like blankets and there was so much
space I couldn't like uh be fully en en
lengthened but I could cuddle up there
and like sleep like while laying down
comfortably really really big yeah so
yeah I would road trip yeah so road trip
hell yeah even though you know it's an
IT Shop but you know that doesn't have
to necessarily be a reason to not go
with it also because maybe on the road
trip we can s uh stop at the on the
beach and use the surfboard yeah exactly
hell yeah and I don't think it can drift
because of how low to the ground it is
yeah uh it is a flex though mhm because
of the amazing design and look at those
rims sheesh
you're though you don't think so no okay
yeah the the shape froze me off that
like the the the the style generally
like there's some re beatable Parts but
something frows me off here mhm steal no
no I think it's too I mean I think there
might be some crazy Goomba fans who
might steal it yeah but I think the
general populace like the other cars
wouldn't yeah yeah uh getting stuck yeah
it's pretty low yeah I think it could
get stuck oh no that is unfortunate and
it's not a muscle I would steal the rims
the rims yeah somebody could just take
the rims that's for sure mhm maybe maybe
they
would I'll give it an extra point for
the
rims okay okay I can see like people not
stealing the car but just like taking
your rims and then leaving steing your
surf board yeah the board yeah so one
two three four
one 1 2 three four four but minus one
yeah so
threee right mhm okay makes sense your
car is so cool thank you forting I like
how like the the the colors are so
vibrant it's so pretty like the interior
is so freaking cool there's a bit more
actually here oh my God what's what's
going on here it's hard to tell is this
a table there's mirrors oh the miror
where is the mirror I'm not sure how is
this picture but we're definitely seeing
the ceiling yeah and then wow cute she's
stepping on you
mhm oh wait and oh wait yeah we got to
do the itasha plus one a
thank
you so it's that's so cute what is
that it's a I mean it looks like that's
the one of the uh the rims no oh that's
a hub cap oh then I understand what a h
cab is I
see you put it on top of the rim I
think that's a cool H hop cat oh yeah
cute man I got to go to one of these
like Japanese itasa show
conventions yeah damn but you know I've
seen like a lot of uh itas from Japanese
people even of Ian girls um and and they
have I've I've never seen a like proper
like like this kind of big go out all go
all out
kiaha I want one so if I missed one send
it to me but I didn't see any so you
know where are the Kiwa just asking for
a friend you know for the future but
yeah you know anyway
next another
Mustang ooh so
cool this is you have a thing for
Mustangs huh it seems like it well it is
a 2021 Mustang so I don't know last time
you guys were like certain Mustangs are
muscle cars others are not so what about
this one this is a real V8
oh muscle car muscle car
hell yeah the real deal beautiful it's
like a dark
blue okay okay I like it it looks nice
let's judge it could IUN the cops with
this probably it's a muscle car oh yeah
okay we's go on a date with yes STM it's
Mustang we drive myself well I said for
another Mustang I think that I would mhm
so I say yes would post sexy what did we
say for the other muscle car I don't
know but I wouldn't post sexy with this
one it's still a cool car but I just I
just I don't think it's it looks enough
that I would post sexy with it you know
what I mean it may need a bit more maybe
like the you could do something with the
rims to make it even sexier maybe yeah
it'd be really sexy under cool lighting
I I could imagine but still yeah in
general Road speak to me no h okay drift
though wait what was it it doesn't look
like it's too heavy on the back so I
don't think it
drifts yeah the rims are amazing yeah
the rims are nice of course but I feel
like if you want to make it sexier you
you can change the rims they're all
saying drift yes oh okay
nice and I do think it's a flex Mustangs
are a flex for to me yeah having a
Mustang is a flex hell yeah how much are
they I need to look up the price cuz I'm
completely for forgot about Mustang's
existence until
today until you pick
three no you're a beat apparently to
according to Chad and I think yeah I
don't think so I would agree that steal
potential potential yes yeah who
wouldn't want a car like this getting
stuck potential I mean any car can get
stuck obviously but I don't think it's
too close to the ground that I'd be
worried about it yeah yeah yeah agreed
okay uh so 1 2 3 4 5 6
7 nice score nice nice oh they uh added
I forgot to mention it's also a sixspeed
manual whatever that means o i don't
yeah but car car fans might be happy
about that information mhm a V8 Mustang
is
$45,000 oh not expensive okay well here
we have a modda Roadster I've seen a
couple of Mazda roadsters I love Maz
yeah oh my God cute and this one's an
ITA
with ooh in a nice gray color which
looks really nice you're posing in in
the streets of Tokyo
maybe wow cute artas are so cool
oh that looks nice interior
wow ooh the the the brown looks like
custom to me mhm I don't know but wow
pretty ooh Okay small small
car but so it might fail certain
criteria but generally I like small cars
so you will win in others could we out
I'm really biased towards
Miatas I'm kind to think the Miata but
this one this one's a road I don't think
this is the
Miata is it not there still will be Mias
though don't worry okay I I I noticed
the difference in the Mazda Roadster and
the mon Miata no they're the same oh
Road oh cuz I just saw like different
descriptions I thought they were the
same Alo roader
is yeah okay okay okay okay then we have
several of these let's go I think you
could probably outrun the comps in am
Miata what really they're they're really
Nimble fast cars and they're like
they're really small so you can take a
turn really really fast yeah but we we
before we judged that itas are don't
outrun the cops cuz they will always
find it oh wait yeah okay you got a
point sadly uh would go on a date with
sadly we don't go on dates with itas
that don't have our faces on yeah yeah
so sorry for this one it's going to have
to be a no no would drive myself yeah
yeah
yeah the car type yes and I mean it
would be even like better if it was our
faces on
it the the type the Moda type generally
uh I found so many thanks to this
hashtag and I I find them very Charming
so you like them too right I do so we
should drive them let's do it well a lot
of Mias too have a top down so you can
make it into a convertible yeah which is
so nice big plus let's go and wood po
sexy probably not not a sexy car not not
really it's cute to Me Maybe with the
top down but yeah it isn't it isn't a
really big car yeah so I don't think a
lot of people find it particularly sexy
oh all Miatas are convertible that's
interesting cuz like when I look at it
like this I I question like how does it
take to hard top hard top conver
so it it it does come down though like
how do you take it off and put it on the
side no no no it's automatic so you
click a button and then it goes into the
back it basically I think like uh like
part of it like Rises up and then it
just kind of deconstructs itself a okay
okay yeah it's cool nice well wonderful
that for me gives it road trip potential
but it's tiny it's just tiny there's no
space no space in the generally the
having the top of is great for road
trips but you know
sad no I think
no yes I don't think they can they can
they yes okay okay drift ability wow
good job Miata and
flex yeah I think am amata is definitely
a flex okay let's go you're
yes really it's look it's it's one of
the options in Wanga
midnight which means if it's in a racing
game you can Euro beat it okay everybody
says yes to okay you got me steal
potential
uh I think yes I would steal myself i'
steal it yeah yeah but but but I
wouldn't I would steal a Miata that has
no like nothing itasha on it yeah yeah
yeah maybe not this one yeah yeah not
this one I I think I have Nona Miatas in
here somewhere so no stealing for now
getting stuck did it look yes it was
really low to the ground it was okay oh
that's a minus point oh
no oh but secret ITA points so 1 2 three
4 four cuz five then minus one so four
mhm
nice nice nice nice
car I want this car Master
next this looks like a race car to make
o holy [\h__\h] what kind is this this is a
car called AE86 that was made about 40
years ago um doing a wrapping for to
toyami and by all right I I also drift
on the circuit it says circuit circuit
with that low apparently yeah it's an
initial de car oh 100% your be 100%
drift 100%
Flex
oo yeah wow it looks like a race car Jee
absolutely wow nice design too I like
the the green and the purple really
really looks very flashy TOA Senpai is a
cool cool to have on a car uh definitely
okay so I'd running the
cups probably I don't know you probably
if they're racing with
it you can find it no h yeah yeah yeah
yeah no date sorry no date I also would
not drive this I don't know I either I'd
be too scared okay sexy magazine TOA
could TOA is very
sexy
K oh
sexy give it a yes you know what she's
sexy in that new casual outfit that she
got the like bright white
one that one's pretty sexy but generally
always sexy what do you
mean okay okay okay okay okay it
honestly anything that her artist uh
draws is
[Music]
sexy okay Justice once I will
cuzz people are going to kill me
otherwise I kill
you would go on a road trip with no no
no no sorry potential yes
fle ability steal steal potential no
because it's an itasha but I do think
people would steal it without the uh
itasha
oh okay and it could definitely get
stuck everywhere like in the front and
every like oh my God that's dangerous a
muscle card
though it's
not no this this is not a muscle
C
narissa okay look at it I don't
know so one two three 4 plus
itus one so
four
yeah 1 2 3 4 5 - 1 I'm getting stuck
okay yeah this this okay okay go go go
go go go go wait this is not oh oh no
this is a Kia Stinger it looks uh
similar to what I saw before no it's
fine Kia Stinger cute small
baby very cute o they have theoc cat
thingies on top cute and it's orange
it's Chihuahua color and the thing is I
think the contrast with the black like
makes it like balances it well and gives
it a really Sleek cool
look but uh from these photos it's hard
for me to imagine the size to be honest
like how much yeah space there is the
rims are cool though oh they say it's
big okay yeah yeah I think I can see it
being big yeah okay that is
helpful for some things out running the
cops I'm not sure I don't think so is it
a fast car it it I mean it could be fast
but I feel like yeah and they say yeah
all right speed let's go it also I can
already give it a steal cuz people said
Kia get stolen all the time
yeah you would not go on a date
no I I don't know it's just it's just
it's it's cute it's cute I wouldn't want
to date on it yeah it doesn't look very
much like like a date car
MH though would drive would you drive it
yes yeah I think it's a nice car to have
for yourself definitely for us Ladies as
well there's something um I'm sorry to
the driver if they're not a lady but to
me it gives me some feminine Vibes cuz
of the orange color I
think and I feel like Kia are kind of
feminine right a little bit like they're
cute it's a Naruto
car Naruto
car I love
Naruto oh some people are don't want to
hear that AA looks feminine to me okay I
I can understand because I some people
also say the Miata is a feminine car
yeah uh but I don't think partially here
thing I don't think I I think people
need to throw away that being a bad
thing I I don't think that's a bad thing
to say that it's quote unquote a
feminine or quote unquote masculine car
if anything I think the femininity of it
makes it more beautiful because it's
more rounded and more smooth that that
makes it very uh gorgeous as where more
quote unquote masculine Brokers are
usually like more sharper H and I don't
think either of those things yeah yeah
I'm like comparing it to like a Mustang
you know yeah yeah yeah like this this
is still very nice car and I don't think
feminine is D thing you know and I'm I'm
like so like supportive of you going
with an orange car let's [\h__\h] go M
cuz I see them so rarely um I wouldn't
say I would Poe sexy with this
one yeah not really I mean I would I
think kiaha could as it's orange could
sex up this car hell yeah I mean I'm
already sexing it up right now don't you
think um but generally no I apparently
it's really big though so I think this
has road trip potential absolutely I
would go on a road trip with this oh
yeah yeah looks
comfortable drift I don't know drift oh
yeah I skipped over I don't think so
it's it's a couldn't chat we have to ask
them
yes yes oh yes oh yes it's a rwd it can
drift okay okay okay drift let's go we
can drift on our road
trip a
flex I I feel like
surprisingly it's kind of flexy yeah
because it's it's I like the coloring on
it that I think makes it flexible
especially this black part like it's
kind of flexy yeah orange is a flex
thank you finally orange is being
appreciated hell yeah what about the EUR
bead I you don't know about that
one
imagine imagine the Europe
[Music]
beat I don't know yes no kind of I'd say
yeah I I would also like to see the
inside the inside gives me often like an
extra opinion on the EUR
[Music]
be yeah I don't think I could eurobeat
in this car I mean you can in any car
but yeah yeah maybe it's more like a pop
music car
MH okay no you're repeat but also I
don't think it would get stuck no I
don't think so either because it's not
too too low it's just normal though and
not a muscle car so 1 2 3 4 5
six nice score run all right all R okay
congratulations honorary muscle car yeah
yeah cuz like you see the the vents in
the on the top or whatever that is that
looks so cool it does look very cool it
has layers like an onion
mhm yeah maybe the pieces could have
been a bit like you know um better
because like it's hard to tell the size
but the more I look at it the more I
agree it looks big it's hard to tell in
this picture oh well thank you next
up M it's a voider Toyota Celica voider
I don't know what that means me neither
but it seems to be something special the
headlights are very interesting wait a
Celica I think Celica sounds familiar to
me I feel like I've been in the Celica
before maybe I don't know maybe not got
this thing a few years ago it was just
sitting in the previous owner's garage
unused for a while I was happy to take
it and give it some use ooh Need for
Speed car and yeah the seats are really
nor although actually no never mind it's
just seat covers yeah yeah seat covers
but there's eni in there and they have
some stickers on the back wait is that
Sparkles you see sparkles on the right
side like purple
Sparkles uh yes I see some sparkles but
I wonder if
it's wet and that is like a light
reflecting because it look look yeah
that would be so nice though to have
sparkles mhm inside looks
drifty I it looks Europe be it looks
Europe be to me in in
here I want to play Europe beat inside
I'll give it a yes for that already oh
so
mucha okay okay we probably give a flex
potential then too since everyone's
saying it's a you know yeah uh small
small small Flex mhm I like I I think
like people who know something about
cars would see some Flex in it but
normal people me not knowing anything oh
hey nobody flexes a
silica oh no drift okay sad uh oh you
can't want a road trip with either yeah
okay um out run let's start from the top
though i' running the
cops probably
F sad uh
probably probably no they're all saying
no I'm not sure no okay slow
car would go on a date I think yeah yeah
yeah yeah I would too CU it's also like
it's not too over the top so it's not
intimidating it's like it's like an like
you know I could I could imagine being
picked up with this yeah me too I like
it it looks
just there's there's some like I feel
like a uh I I can imagine uh a couple
that has been dating for 10 years no 5
years sitting in here
yeah it's nice you know would drive
myself no no no not our car would post
sexy well it doesn't get me sex you know
and you can't even Flex with it
apparently would go on a road trip with
it oh how it doesn't look that spacious
no I don't think so I mean it looks like
there's maybe back seats you could make
it work yeah I wouldn't though
[Music]
it's tight back there not comfy okay no
leg space all right yeah yeah yeah I can
see it dto they said no right yeah I
think no and no flex oh [\h__\h] steel uh
well I was looking bad for this
car people steal this maybe because it's
like like not so special cars get also
stolen you know yeah definitely steal
easy steal hell yeah let's steal it
let's steal it wow thank
God getting St MUSC right no not a
muscle car yeah so that's free kind of
low but nothing against your car like
yeah know car it's Charming mhm okay
look the real the real point you want to
score is is the date one anyway so
really if you're getting that then
you're
winning very true yeah I agree with that
that's a good point to have like you can
impress or at least make a girl feel
comfortable or a boy feel comfortable
with that you know so I have 1 2 3 4 5 6
7 8 9 10 11 12 12 more cars okay let's
do our best and here we
go jeep
jeep who our first Jeep I'm I'm sorry
there's there were so
many no
okay I know it looks strong to you but
it's not a muscle car it's a Jeep sadly
they're okay okay we will we will get
you to understand properly what muscle
car is later on yes so this is a 97 Jeep
Wrangler with
274,000
Miles 440,000
kilomet okay I don't know if that's a
lot cuz I don't drive cars is it
um yeah okay yeah holy moly that's a lot
oh very oh so respect to Holding Out for
that long I guess yum super fun to drive
except it sounds and feels like it's
falling to pieces while trying to un
alive
you don't worry it's got a nice sound
system so you can stream POV to drone
out the screams
what they need to replace the engine o
wow that sounds like a great cell or I
mean because it's so old I think we can
say it's not getting going to get stolen
yeah yeah but and it's not going to get
stuck anywhere cuz it's a Jeep yes and I
think it has road trip potential for
sure definitely it may be loud and like
okay they said it's like you get the
feeling like it's trying to kill you but
it's big it's a
cheap it's the road trip
car exactly it get cuz it breaks no it's
doing its best to stay alive okay look
at this baby yeah it looks good it's
probably been on a million road trips
okay M all reliable oh cute Frankenstein
what does that mean is that also like
one
category I don't understand wow look at
this baby look at it it's it's cute I
don't I personally dislike Jeeps me too
oh really man so sorry but yeah I don't
know it's just not cute to
me that's that's just me so uh I don't
think this could outrun the cops
especially because of all the miles it
has on it I would not want to be picked
up for a date with this no ever yeah I
would not drive this I'm so sorry I
might drive it but it depends on the
situation okay if if I'm if I'm doing
off-road then yes I would I would 100%
take the Jeep so I think we should give
it the point okay cuz maybe it will not
get many other points oh wait I thought
that was already fixed okay not really
sexy not
sexy no wait does this drift could it
that's interesting I want to know drift
B sorry but no he was roasting his own
car plenty hello no okay no drift Flex
um the miles are Flex that
F I think we should give it a flex
because like it survived from 97 with
that many miles on it that's amazing are
we giving it P points no give it the
point
K okay Flex you rep beat though no no um
steel Ste potential no it's too old
getting stuck no it'll never get stuck
no no it's like it it will never get
like taken down by anything okay mhm and
it's not a muscle car had got threee
points good work nice car nice nice car
not our type of car but you know for a
Jeep considering we're just like we
don't like jeeps and you still got three
points that's pretty good yeah but the
Jeep people are happy the jeeple yeah
I'm
Jeep they're happy that there was at
least one Jeep here I'm very impressed
by the miles on it yeah and you know I I
want to hear the sound of the dying
engine please and I want to hear the
stories about like there must have been
a lot of stories about this car where
you went what happened mhm okay next car
we got no time what's this Emanuel RT
Dodge Challenger oo I saw this tweet and
I knew I had to burn a little rubber for
it that sounds like you went
thrifting
okay um oh this is a muscle car I think
muscle car yes there say you know how I
recognized it looks pretty white and and
it has these things on top yeah yeah and
the the the the shape of like I don't
know how to describe these car parts but
where the lights are and everything in
between the lights you know that long
emptiness holess this yeah yeah this
this is muscle car yeah it's very wide
okay okay it's like a you know when you
take a dog's uh closeup with a dog with
a long nose and take their clothes up
and and take it with a wide lens angle
uh
wide angle L this is you know the long
snoot boys mhm yeah this is the car
equivalent
okay although they don't look very
muscly those those uh dogs yeah I don't
know what saying ignore what I'm saying
okay we have a [\h__\h] muscle car let's
go woohoo let's raid
it h could outrun the cops help us guys
it's a muscle car surely that means yes
right I would say so too cuz it's got
power power yeah yes they say yes yes
yes yes go on I go on a date I like the
color I like the
build what do you think I don't the the
color and I don't like the stripes but
the fact that it has yeah I I don't like
blue cars like not this shade of blue
it's so basic to
me what do you think about meana you're
you're a different kind like cuz like
blue on on cars is so common you know
but blue in your hair is not so
common I see I see so it's no problem
but the fact that it's a muscle
car I don't know and somehow it doesn't
look so cool to me I'm sorry I see oh
I'm sorry this person will hate me now
cuz they're probably really PR of their
Dodge
Challenger oh I I would so why don't we
give it like a half point a five okay I
I I wouldn't mind being picked up with
it I guess yeah yeah so okay would
dry yeah I give it I I try it I try it I
drive a muscle car okay
uh
[Music]
okay would POS no sexy posing though no
no okay would go on a road trip no no
doesn't look doesn't look super doer
spacious right I mean it's big but yeah
it's SP no the trunk looks big the trunk
looks kind of big but like I feel like
trun trunks are often
deceptive M it's a large car is it
comfortable pretty spacious inside that
sounds like it's good for honestly I
will give it that
point drift so apparently they went
drift
watch drift potential yes
yes um here is the drifting in progress
why are you oh hell
yeah oh it's
loud it's okay because it's connected
because he's he's uh doing the manual
thing so hey guys welcome to the car
he's
talking hey guys welcome it was like
really
noisy man don't talk that's like I don't
know if I should show your voice on
stre but are you going to drift at some
point oh you got the
sunglasses I don't know he's just
introducing the car I think it's really
loud tell you all about his car he's so
proud but I I don't I don't know if I
should show this but yeah uh it's really
loud WOW uh wait what did we say about
drifting probably yes yeah I think yeah
probably correct us if we're wrong Flex
yeah muscle cars a flex hey it's getting
pretty good points actually yeah it can
yeah we're saying yes you're a beit I
think muscle cars generally weren't much
of a Europe beat thing though but this
one can
drift okay Europe beat yes I think yeah
I think yeah bro let him
talk no I feel embarrassed him I don't
want I don't know I'm shy so you beat
okay steal potential
I'd steal it oh okay um recording that
for
sure sry I turn it on
again uh no give me back to I want to
see the picture thank you
um they're often stolen oh no it's
because of you
narissa yeah people like me and you're
motivating them okay getting stuck no
wow that's pretty good rating
so I know I will actually take this one
away
wow one two 3 four five 6 7 eight see
it's too good wow this this no no I
don't agree with it but okay
congratulations hope you feel good about
your car good
work at least it's a muscle car it makes
me happy that it's a muscle car we need
more muscle cars next oh ooh oo oh it's
a vestia vestia
Zeta it may not look like it like it
from this side but it's a Toyota ZN
686 whole life ID vesa Zeta
specification the interior and exterior
Alla I'm doing a competition called
Drift with this car I was doing a drift
competition the other day and it fell
into a ditch H you told us two important
things about this car just
now okay oh power is power all right
[Music]
okaya who just had her 3D showcase yeah
oh cute I like the the like um
handwritten uh like writings there from
the uh members whoever drew that
cute oh ah this is from the competition
I guess all right okay is this him in
the
ditch there's there's like videos there
this is not the ditch is it but there's
videos I not show them now also I'm
feeling like really sick since like 15
minutes ago oh no we got to rush okay
let's start the rating [\h__\h]
[Music]
H yes what oh why you feeling sick I
don't know man it's getting worse and
worse tummy I've been trying to ignore
it and get through I got I'm I'm I'm
stuck in the Stream but could out run
the cops uh yes yes we're going to date
no no itasha would
drive yes I'd try it yes but no but yes
would po sexy no would going to V trip
no I don't know dri potential yes drift
yes Flex yes you're a beat you're
beatable yes yes steel steel
potential
yes
M no getting stuck yes muscle car
no okay 1 2 3 4 5us one four four about
it point so
five okay next
gu K we could do a part two you're over
I'm
dying K why don't we make this the last
one and we can do it again some other
time okay then I'll just show you
quickly like we have oh look at
this o it kind like I'll be right back
you you you judge the
car okay I'm trying to be fast enough
for up okay just Jud okay okay okay
K kata's dying so now you're left with
me kfp uh so today we are looking at uh
the viewers uh Brothers 1979 Chevy Z28
Camaro or Camaro he spent a lot of time
fixing it up he's nicknamed it the
Batmobile and I think that's correct
because honestly the first time I saw it
I too thought that it was the Batmobile
I think it could probably outrun the
cops just because it does look like the
Batmobile and if I think about Batman I
do think Batman could probably outrun
the poor
Ki I don't know if kiw would agree with
me but I want to date in this car what
about you kfp it looks like a datable
car looks like looks like a car you
could date
in you know because it's kind of
interesting you know so there's a story
so you get picked up and you're like
whoa what what's up with your car bro it
looks like the [\h__\h] Batmobile and
then you get going and then you get
talking yes to date um would I drive it
myself
no someone count the points I'm not
going to remember please cut my points
for me I can't edit
it um would I posee on it for a magazine
honestly probably yes cuz with my
aesthetic I think I kind of Fit Don't
You K are you okay I'm not
okay are you good wa what
happened that was me last night actually
I was so scared I was going to wake up
feeling sick because I ate cookies
during my stream and then I was like oh
Tommy [\h__\h]
oh no what did the cookies do to you why
are we both dying with our tummies it's
okay I want to I want to judge these
awesome cars like this one how can I not
judge this holy [\h__\h] yeah I said yes it
could outrun the police yes I'd go on a
date with it and yes I'd drive it myself
what do you think do you agree yes
um I don't think it's like like my car
like it would somebody would have to
drive it for me yeah like okay okay I
I'll drive you in the car oh oh I I can
imagine you in there huh yeah right no
say with I said yes for sexy for
magazine cuz I with me specifically I
think that' be hot it's [\h__\h] sexy mhm
but the driving I give it a05 then cuz I
guess you would drive it would you
really drive this car yeah I'd try it
shes okay would go on the road trip no
sadly drift does it drift yeah it does
it drift chat doesn't look like it would
drift it doesn't seem like it doesn't
seem like a
Drifter yeah oh they're saying yes
though it looks so long though how does
such a long car drift I guess it does
technically it can W I'd say yes to both
drift and flex do all Camaros have such
a fancy shape by the way like wow I
don't think
so
you know I know I know I know I think I
know what it is I I think the cake that
I ate
today I often eat it but it it tasted a
bit off like oh no not off off but like
it tastes different from usual mhm yeah
maybe it was the cake but
anyway I've been betrayed by the cake
but no road trip drift apparently it
could
surprisingly hell yeah the flag
mhm would you Euro beat no no me neither
no no there's not like something
negative but it doesn't give me EUR beat
Vibes yeah different Vibes and steal I
would steal it yes uh like be careful
man keep it in Chains like and whips
we're
coming getting stuck it doesn't look
super low to the ground I think it would
honestly be
fine I think maybe you would get stuck
cuz people Park you in
like I don't know and then you're too
long to get out so I I I don't know I
don't
know no okay no no no is this a muscle
car I don't I wish I had more pictures
mm it looks pretty wide yes it is thank
you I was thinking it might be cuz again
it has something cool like oh yeah [\h__\h]
yeah wooho this is a muscle car if
anything one two uh 3 4 5 6
7.5 this must be one of the coolest cars
I've seen in the
hashtag I think so too it's really cool
looking how much does this
cost probably too much look it up guys I
need to know I know I skipped this but
uh let's just appreciate it um cuz it's
cute and it it probably has has also the
feature where you open up the eyes the
lights the Blinky blinks definitely
you're a beatable but I'm not going to R
these are all our honorable mentions
honorable mentions yeah this is also
like
Wow Let's go like this is so old so
what's what's the word
vintage yeah they're saying it's a
muscle car mus this is a muscle car o it
is a chevret again
M yellow family project card between my
grandfather uncle and me and me and boy
is it fun 1971 chevret Vega
wo W is that like a like a flaming a
really lowkey flaming pattern uh close
to the light can you see it I do see it
it's so lowy M it almost looks like it
happened naturally cuz your car gets so
hot and this do just like stained itself
ghost
flame looks nice um but yeah we're going
to we're going to I don't think we're
going to rate any more
cars this one
ooh 1985 bu Grant natur a Buick is a
good getaway car oh why I don't know I
just know that because I was in a
musical once and they're like ah my
getaway car I mean my
bew and looks oh it's fast the grand
National's fast oh people are excited
about this car o the turbocharged V6
engine oh V6 in this car was known for
beating Corvettes Lamborghinis and
Ferraris in the 14 mile drag races
uhuh
shees but it like generally on these
photos it doesn't like look that crazy
but the front that like what do you call
that between the
lights I don't know the grill the grill
yeah must be a grill that looks like
really wow luxurious
fancy also this car gives me Elvis
Presley Vibes
yeah I don't know why but yes so that's
there and then we have these a Supra
just want to show you I love super yeah
more of that we want more of that cute
and I also like how the colors are like
split in the
middle it gives it another like Euro
Beach retro Vibe yeah like it needs some
work and I'm working towards making it
faster MK MK MK free
Supra and then we
have uh not a muscle car but a
mercedesbenz GLE 350 spacious has s of
uh luxurious has s of space very fun to
drive um I I know it looks like like
more like a somewhat normal car but the
reason icluded it is cu of these lights
mhm cool lights inside nice LED lighting
so so cool yes let's go and there with
some Wawa so you know got to have a w
merch yeah I have to and then last but
not least I really like this like
cherryish color
here H and it's also a you know a kfp
card so you know biased as [\h__\h] but it
it has a nice shape too and honestly
like it just looks like I would I would
like to get picked up with this one too
like also inside is nice yeah the seats
are cool M nice color and kfp so I mean
got about the kfp
yeah hey okay uh thank you guys for
watching there were so many more cars
I'm so sorry I didn't think there would
be so
many like honestly like there was
there's so many you know streams where
whole life members are rating something
and um I always wanted to do something
like that uh but I wanted to do
something that hasn't been done before
and I just suddenly had this idea that I
wanted to do some rating stream of you
and cuz I'm currently on a like I have
to look at cars like ride um this came
to my mind but I didn't think it would
you
know be that well received by all the
car owners yeah I was surprised too I
was like oh no I'm worried because what
if we only get a few cars and then I was
like oh my God it's number 11 trending
in the USA I think yeah what the hell
like people really love cars more than I
thought um we love car guys if you guys
liked it that much maybe we'll do a part
two um I just go for the same hashtag uh
because there's so many that I miss and
there's so many still great
ones so maybe we'll do part two you
don't have to resubmit there I'll just
go for the same
hashtag yeah you can even still submit
now I guess MH yeah thank you guys for
watching watching what was your favorite
car
Nissa I'm biased cuz I like Mi I
like actually like I saw so many on the
hashtag but I guess I didn't end up
picking out so
many they are Charming as
hell so cute the bumblebee car oh do
another one of these I I guess I will I
didn't think you guys would like this
format so
much but
apparently you do W what was your
favorite uh one of the in the beginning
one one of the the the beige classic
cars uh I think that was like one that I
really liked so long ago now it's I
remember I remember 84 years but I don't
know what it's called yeah oh and and of
course all the orange
cars yeah the orange datson that was
crazy
that was crazy the Morris Miner maybe it
was that I don't know um you can
probably tell from my excitement when I
saw certain
cars I'm sad there was no Aston Martin
I'm sad there was no Maybach I'm sad I'm
sad that there was no Ferrari um where
the Lamborghinis and the McLaren come on
yeah what the [\h__\h] um next time
please uh but uh I I actually I saw a
lot of more Flex cards
but then I was really wondering are
these people like even H life fans
yeah uh no but don't worry guys no need
to be billionaires like even you know
something like this I don't know how
much I guess BMWs are pretty expensive
actually but um any any car can be
charming and you know yeah they can have
like their use way their special usage
you know being usable for road trip um
that that might not be applicable to
really cool Lamborghinis you know mhm so
every car has its
own specialty right yeah no car can be
perfect as you saw today I think the
highest score we did give was a nine
though
sh yeah so we were quite strict but
don't don't feel down about it I was
sometimes surprised giving like really
cool ass cars free out of 10 like that
makes no sense to me yeah all your cars
are awesome otherwise I wouldn't have
like picked them you know it's really
hard to choose that's one was online
yeah that one got really
close oh yeah someone post a Meen oh
please do please
do thank you narissa for participating
even though you also don't like know
much about cars but we're interested
right thank you for having me I am
interested in cars so I was happy to be
here thank you we're intrigued thank you
guys for sharing your car knowledge with
us uh I'm sorry if we maybe judged it
too harshly or so but this is what it is
you
know going for a hard test if you want
to be judged by
us I hope your ego isn't hurt yes all of
you had lovely cars indeed very much
so okay then guys thank you for watching
and in German we say a
z z now we will drive to the
autoban and go without limit let's go V
vom I've been I've been over uh uh 200
key kmh uh on the German autoban
before what 200
kilom I don't know that it's like
[\h__\h]
fast it's I think you're canell I think
it's
or it was 190 I don't know but it was
[\h__\h] fast 120 oh my God K that's so
fast
well why do I speak like I can't speak
[Laughter]
German G but I didn't go I was just in
the passenger seat
but good I'm glad you weren't a speed
demon I I wouldn't I would be too scared
holy [\h__\h]
okay so be careful on the road uh don't
text and drive don't drink and drive
right keep taking good care of your cars
pretty boys and girls yes yes be careful
we're we're we're going to um look out
for your cars in the future too so treat
them well and with respect Drive
responsibly okay a
bye-bye bye Darlings
[Music]
a
an hour oh okay I'm I'm muting I'm
unmuting okay say it wait hi guys now
say it hi for those of you who are still
here real quick I have a cover coming
out in an hour on my page uh if you'd
like please uh go by and check it out
it's uh Boulders gate 3's down by the
river yeah please give it a listen I'd
be happy if you were there thank you
what wait what yeah I thought that you
had like you told me before that you had
like covers planned out for months ahead
but bounders Kade you only started
playing like you know H we we rushed
this one this wasn't one of my planned
ones I just asked manichan and she was
like yeah we can do it so
amazing my God that will be so good for
your voice yeah thank you guys check it
out maybe I'll redirect actually it's
still some time to go but you know yeah
I'll I'll okay okay muted
[Music]
again