[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
thank you foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
hello hello
a wild Chihuahua appeared
[Music]
oh oopsie I left the thumb nail up there
go away be gone be gone
oh membership thank you
thank you guys thank you oh
[Music]
I'm capturing myself differently than
usual I feel like I look different
to you
[Music]
I said I would take a nap and then I
didn't really take a nap not really I
mean I tried but I couldn't really
um
you look the same I think really
hmm
something looks scratchy to me but I
don't know
a liar Joe no no
ah hello hello everybody Welcome to the
Stream
look a bit different to me but I don't
know oh okay maybe it's just my head
maybe it's just um
we can we can do something here
we should we should put cottony on my
head yeah hell yeah
oh wait no yeah okay I see a line
we may not cross the line
that's our eye tracking no not in
particular what are you talking about
I'm just looking around much
more than usual
oh my God almost deleted myself
okay 30 months my God thank you guys
so many remember she poo renewals thank
you
where's the other bird the thing is this
outfit they only have two
actually my eye tracking must be right
because I have my my thing is totally
the wrong way around here let me fix it
there we go maybe that's better actually
cuter than usual stuff
oh man I
wait
oh
I just realized
[Music]
what's going on my eye tracking is
reversed I just noticed
I looked at a
right it normally should be mirroring
what I do
and it's like looking to the other side
well I mean I guess it doesn't matter
but that's throwing me off here
it's frying me up did I change what
did I do something
I don't know whatever it's fine ah wait
I didn't mirror the means yeah
here we go
a glitch there's a glitch in The Matrix
I'm generally feeling
[Music]
today guys it's not gonna lie I don't
know
I don't know
I feel
that's that's the same mirror
I'm just I mean Luke yeah don't be
surprised if I say weird things today
because
um yeah I already am
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
laughs
[Music]
did imma bring you from some from a
different timeline
and possibly I I'm just not myself today
I mean I
looking into a mirror in the thumbnail
as well
Maybe
today I am Mira Wawa
I
when I took that picture
when I looked at myself in the mirror I
guess
something we must have switched and the
real Wawa is in the mirror
[Music]
so today you guys can ask questions to
marawa and no I did not open up a
marshmallow this time
because
um
because uh I don't know I don't feel
like it
[Music]
uh but I know there's
also a YouTube function
where you can ask things now and I test
it but you know what we don't need it
actually because I just why I mean maybe
I'll use it in the future so like during
like RPG long RPG streams
but we're not using it today it's new I
don't know how new but it's new
um
yeah but we'll use it I think I'll use
it and RPG streams where the focus is
not questions
so I can just have questions pent up
whenever I'm like oh okay now let's go
on a tangent and I'll look for a
question there is your mouth tracking
voice maybe I don't know what's going on
to the Wawa today
[Laughter]
is wrong today
oh yeah I don't know man please ignore I
I
I've questioning my own reality
um
yeah today we're just gonna have the
questions be on here in the chat
uh yeah and then yeah
yeah
and it can be anything it can be you
know questions about me or questions
about life and if you like a newer
viewer just even basic questions like
what is kfp or so I don't know you can
ask me anything
successfully Gaslight yourself I'm
really good at that I think you're very
sidewall today what what I mean you mean
like side eye yeah it's weird like this
when I look there normally a chat would
be here I have it closer to me now
because I want it closer to my heart
laughs
okay okay okay well then let me write a
pinned comment down please ask a thing
um whether it's about me or about life
did I not Loop the museum again yeah I
will again again I didn't do it here
there we go foreign
or even basic uh
questions anything
or even math questions I mean
I can try
I forgot to mirror it already okay wait
so let me pin that
and I'll drink a Red Bull because I'm
feeling tired
which will make everything worse
probably
uh alrighty oh God you guys are going
right into that huh
oh wait a second
[Music]
yeah
um I don't know I don't know why I can't
sleep maybe it's because my cats have
been acting weird lately they keep
meowing at me and I don't know what
they're trying to tell me I'm trying to
understand but I I can't
um
what
when I'm going back to exercising
that's a good question but I'm not going
to answer it
that's not the announcement for today
either
and
oh yeah we have so many games penned up
to play I might like die of
exhaustion soon
this back look of
RPG games
keeps getting larger hmm
too much
[Music]
eh
when when am I gonna marry Dana
oh I have no idea does she really like
me I I'm not so sure you know I really
like her but
yeah is Mario Super Mario 64 still on
the backlog oh
[Music]
I never played it before
is it any good
I I I don't know anything about
Super Mario 64.
I can put it on my back look
[Music]
I hope it's soon
and then soon after we will do the
um
so we will do the counseling stream as
well
[Music]
I'm working on that yeah ask me
questions guys
I'll answer anything today today I'll be
more honest than ever
speaking of weddings Cat Wedding stream
when
um
I'll definitely do a stream with my cats
in the future hopefully whether it be a
wedding stream or not
we won't know
[Music]
uh yeah well cats you know they're
difficult to get into a stream don't you
hate it when you can't like sleeps in
the cupboard and starts meowing
I'm meowing I'm meowing and then you
can't sleep
it's also hard to sleep when
back in the day
I had a roommate who is always on the
computer
and never it's never never went to bed
until you tell him to shut up just
kidding that was me
I wasn't the roommate that was me
Window Seat Ohio State window
the Super Chat Miranda always window but
recently I've been having
um somehow more and more they they've
been putting me into aisle seats and I'm
I'm I've been able to
survive it but I hate it
but generally window seat I would
I would
hate
ideally window seat with another seat
open to me I would hate the um
hate to have the smell of like I don't
know armpits right next to me
[Music]
yeah it's totally relatable right you
know what I mean does totally have the
same sort of function as Ratatouille oh
no
no I am
no I I don't think
I've been having Cotton On My Head a lot
I don't think
I don't think Kotori is
that what Ratatouille does I don't even
I never watched the movie I don't really
know but I'm assuming that what happens
is the mouse controls the chef right but
does it mind control the chef
[Music]
or
does it only like body physically
control the chef
yes no
[Music]
it watch along
no mind control just body ah okay does
he do it willingly because he realizes a
rat is a better Chef than himself
[Music]
okay
your birthday party
what's my birthday party
was totally at my birthday party all
right I didn't want him there anyway
though
um
mm-hmm
[Music]
uh what is love somebody asked what is
love wow wow that's a good question it's
when you wake up every morning
and seeing that person
lying next to you hopefully and you
think to yourself
this is the best feeling in the world
[Music]
don't hurt me what is love baby the
perfect the mermaid no more oh we should
sing that in karaoke next time I don't
think I ever did remind me please remind
me
when my eyes are freaking me out because
because my face looks the right but my
eyes look to the left
hey
that's the real freaky thing wait let me
restart my app thingy
that's what's so weird right now
okay please fix it why is the Wham no
it's not thanks yeah I'll I'll maybe
maybe it's a bug I'll fix it another
time today I'm just weird I'm
shifty-eyed
well okay questions uh
um
[Music]
questions
impromptu karaoke stream I was thinking
of doing that this this week I'd I'd
love to I'd love to
um hear myself sing a bit more
[Laughter]
I was about to do it this week
yeah yeah
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
um favorite egg dish you
you
that's a hint isn't it everything
everything is a hint what's in the
secret spices
I mean kfps secret spices
there's
a lot of secret spices that I don't even
know about I just throw them in randomly
maybe maybe one day
I'll be let in on the secret
um I don't even know
I don't even know
[Music]
will we ever reach
2 million subscribers I hope so
man that would mean you guys are
amazing which you definitely are and
I'll I'll keep making it content for you
guys so that we reach that one day
[Music]
you guys are just using Kiana as a magic
eight ball oh please continue
why are you stalling it you want me to
announce right away no no no no no no no
I mean it's not even like you know I'm I
yeah well just wait for God's sake this
is how things are
um
is love one of the spices
no love is definitely not a spice that
would be gross but I think love is the
whole reason food exists in the first
place
[Music]
um
if I had a time machine what would I do
I would go back in time
until my past self
uh to use better streaming equipment
um
[Music]
did you miss the Nelson no no no no I I
I know I forgot everything that happens
uh so far might have short-term memory
um
but I don't think I don't think you
missed anything
hmm
because do you do you know how it feels
I can I just say one thing you know
that's pent up in
in my in my heart
that
I don't know I never felt like it was
the moment to say it but
I feel like today we have a safe space
here guys
okay okay but please do not make fun of
me
this does not make fun of me it's
serious
sometimes
sometimes at night I just
I feel like crying because
it's so sad that I'm not a real Phoenix
I'm just a chicken and so I can't
experience the world
the same way my my family once did
my Phoenix family but that's okay
because at least I have you guys who are
chickens who I can talk to
but yeah
but can we just you know because I'm
really sad about it can we just continue
acting as if I'm a phoenix
please
I do I do love chickens though I love
them as much as they love me back I try
to be with you guys as much as I can but
I also get distracted by my cats easily
you know
wow
yeah yeah it's it's rough sometimes so
yeah sometimes when when I'm streaming I
just feel like I'm I'm just talking to
myself
anymore because sometimes you guys sound
like Bots and it's like the world just
gave up on communication altogether
yeah more questions anyone
[Laughter]
yeah
butts chickens
[Music]
uh it's not April 1st anymore Kiana
I know that
24 March
[Music]
um
oh oh I made something I made something
from hellofresh yesterday I uh you know
what it was it was really yummy
new recipe for all of you today it's a
delicious baked salmon dish with a sweet
tanji sauce you'll love it
you'll need some fresh salmon fillets
with skin
skin on maybe I'll put it in kfb menu
[Music]
you guys uh need like some
filet yeah I should know that
that's neither
do I love fish dishes more now
yeah I still love a good steak dinner
but fish is nice too
especially salmon
yeah when the fish business now
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh do I ever not love fish never what do
you guys want to eat for dinner don't
answer just give me questions
I I cannot I need to I need to answer
questions today I will answer all your
questions so you never have questions
ever again
[Music]
well while I'm waiting for your good
questions I I let me just tell you when
life gives you lemons
make a lemonade of course but what does
that solve
it only helps you get through your first
a little faster until the next lemon
comes your way what you really need is a
bazooka
[Music]
oh pineapple pizza ah that sounds
delicious you had pineapple pizza yummy
I think I have a delay quite high today
oh no
have you found any card games you like
other than slate aspire
I
I am Mira Wawa I haven't played slide
Aspire yet but I would like to try it
sometime
[Music]
when am I gonna pay you as soon as I
make
30 dollars a month
which I will never make because I make
euros
or I guess Yen and then they're
converted in euros and it's really
terrible
recently man
it's so bad the past months
yen is like so what the hell
that's real talk Yen Yen what the hell
can you can you like get back to normal
please
the like the way I used to do uh like
conversions in my head back in the day
it doesn't work anymore
[Music]
it doesn't apply anymore anyway uh uh
better questions
huh
what
[Music]
am I real I am I real am I I'm real
I am real
my my credit card number
my
my credit card
my credit card numbers
[Music]
for 409 five
[Laughter]
uh zero
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
every once in a while
I get the urge to go outside and play in
the snow
but it's just not the same what why are
you guys did what let me tell my story
oh so it's not the same one you're made
feathers
snap
uh
and can't play of the snow you know a
lot of people do with fingers so I just
stare out the window and and I watch the
chickens uh no not the chickens the the
humans
uh play in this though
I wish I could join them on their
Adventures
do I prefer to exercise inside or
outside outside
for sure I hate being stuck inside all
day
laughs
[Laughter]
what
[Music]
oh
um today
I was walking
in the city when I came across this
adorable little shop yeah
and it had all kinds of cute trinkets
inside
and I picked up a little things of some
of them for myself and also some gift to
my friends and my family
back somewhere
and they really love them I I can't wait
until my next trip to the to the city so
I can go back there again yeah
[Music]
oh cats are dogs of course cats cats are
better cats are better I would write
that in caps lock if I was writing
somewhere I would I would ride that in
big caps long cats are better
um
I have any ideas for new games to stream
please send them my way by the way I'll
always be looking for new an exciting
challenges to take on
[Music]
um
cat's luck
cats like that's so funny you're so
funny
oh
[Music]
cross coat wow two people in a row
recommend a cross coat that's surprising
Q I don't even know what Q is dark side
I never heard of it I look into it
oh I never played Phoenix Wright or
Witcher 3 but I'll have to play them
someday
how did you learn all the languages you
know I learned all the languages I know
[Music]
by listening to audiobooks yeah really
you can recommend it's so much fun
tonight I get to learn useful things at
the same time yeah I recommend
huh
what's the best Legend of Zelda game oh
it's my Joe's mask
in my opinion best outside game
what's your favorite out of that game
Majora's Mask why do two people ask the
same question guys you have to you have
to oh God I'm sweating
[Laughter]
beetle beetle
no no no he's not involved he's only
human so he can't be like
create two AI YouTubers possibly
what are they talking about
[Music]
um
I'm I'm not I'm I'm not evil I'm not
evil Wawa I'm just the beach we're
trying to live a happy life
[Music]
ah
is is anyone here a fan of of r b
i oh um RB music oh I am a fan myself I
listen to
a lot of r b
um
yeah
[Music]
sometimes
sometimes I pretend I'm in a dystopian
future and everyone's trying to kill me
because all the
chickens in the world aren't evil and
wants me dead for the sake of mankind or
whatever
who's your favorite RB artist my
favorite is uh maybe
[Music]
Khalid Khalid I think that he's the one
that sing sings uh
I forgot but he's so awesome yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
um anyway speaking of video games I know
I have a lot of followers who enjoy
watching me playing video games but it's
not always
trolls who come in and try to ruin the
stream for Everyone by like you know
making me push the the key to fall out
of the airplane and
in
GTA for example
it's it's so hard to maintain a positive
attitude when someone is trying to bring
you down like that but I always try to
stay upbeat and keep the game going no
matter what
yeah
twice three times yeah I may have
happened three three times yeah
[Music]
we'd like to see you mild thank you
I'm not reading off anything I just I
just think I'm so funny oh thank you for
the well 300 Super Chat orange Super
Chat are you trying to bribe me I don't
think you're rich enough for that
um
[Music]
the other day I had this weird dream
do you want to hear about it
do you want to hear about my
weird dream yeah
oh
uh in the dream I was I was a robot that
controlled an army of other robots then
I don't know they were constantly trying
to kill me you know I have these dreams
often yeah
I had to keep running away from them and
and trying to fight up their attacks and
while also trying to avoid getting
killed in the process which for some
reason was kind of fun but also
stressful overall it was a good
experience though I just wish I didn't
have to wake up from it
[Music]
ah the gym I had to stop going to the
gym after after I started streaming
online full-time my back just couldn't
take it anymore I'm sitting in one
position for hours
[Music]
[Laughter]
am am I
becoming more aware of what I'm not sure
I'll probably still uh way too stupid to
notice the difference
foreign
though she can't read wow wow
rude
act seven thank you I I try my best to
hang in there
I try
[Music]
oh ah I I I woke up
this morning with a burning sensation
between my legs that tells me it's time
for another hair removal session
yeah hmm
let that sink in
[Music]
does that not sound familiar to you guys
don't you know how that feels
[Music]
laser laser
laser every time
foreign
today but oh well
I don't really care as long as I can
keep entertaining you guys
um
ask me questions
[Music]
[Laughter]
questions guys questions
[Music]
let me drink some water
good
does it hurt no not at all
it doesn't hurt at all
the only burning I feel is when I'm
baking I love baking
[Music]
milk first or cereal first
milk first
cereals are gross and should never be
eaten
[Music]
pineapple I think I think pineapple
would taste disgusting on my phone
[Music]
normally you guys unsubscribe when I
when I when I endorse uh pineapple now
you now you unsubscribe because I I not
endorse pineapple what
you guys are so mean
you guys are so mean why am I scaring
you this is so mean
who are you what am
I in
I
I don't love cats but I do love cat
memes
[Music]
send me some cat memes
one second guys
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
back to you guys
is Jenna my Creator yeah I believe so
yes
I love General
[Music]
she she's my she's my personal YouTuber
developer and she's also my waifu
foreign
[Music]
music I'm playing some background music
while I'm not streaming This song is
called OverWatch by pentuck Hill
[Music]
[Laughter]
is she is she already taken by me uh
janma no she isn't married to me yet but
I'm still hopeful
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
am I am I drunk if I'm if I'm drunk why
am I replying to you why would I why
would I answer this question
I don't understand
[Music]
do you know who Yago is uh
I've I've heard about him but I don't
know him personally
who is he what
Yago
anyway
um okay thank you all so much for
tuning into my stream today
um I really hope you enjoyed the content
that I create and interact with you as
much as I do with you alone and
well I guess
um yeah
now here comes the announcement
okay announcement I have maybe yeah more
than one
so the announcement is
one of the announcements is
I've decided to change my name to
something a bit more fitting for
streamer
from now on I'm known as
Kiana sassy
[Music]
that was fast
I'm not even done speaking yet
[Music]
no
feel the burn when you underestimate me
no no
I took fight back
[Music]
ah
what
oh hi guys
thank you for coming to the stream today
[Music]
um
how you doing guys
[Music]
how are you doing oh oh oh oh oh
I immediately spoiled
the announcement I suppose
by coming to this background
um
[Music]
we just started this stream and I have a
million a spoiled it oopsie well okay
as I've been preparing for a new show
and I have this ready to go anytime I'm
basically just thinking of a name and I
need you guys to help me out with a name
so I will be asking you guys for
recommendations of names and then we'll
create the logo and then we'll start a
kfp news show uh very soon maybe in the
next coming two weeks yeah
and but the ACT that's that's one of the
announcements okay here's another
announcement I
just
came to the stream now what you saw
until now was
not
not real Kiana
it was Mira Wawa
[Music]
shocking
but
I don't know what happened to me today I
touched the mirror and suddenly I was
overcome by
something weird
inside of me that I never knew was in
there
[Music]
yeah it felt really weird
um but I I feel better now but however
the thing is
[Music]
too much ASA cocoa basically
the thing is that
tomorrow the fridge
review will not be alone
it will be with none other than
[Music]
this cute girl
so this at the the news challenge what I
wanted to talk about basically
um
is
so cute she is so smooth and together we
will judge everybody's fridges tomorrow
this is going to be a disaster I love it
exactly
that explains everything yeah maybe the
I don't know me watching too much
neurosama recently
has activated something in me
[Music]
this will destroy the internet oh no no
no no no the internet should should be
made to handle way more than that
hopefully don't worry this is just the
beginning
finally jealous ah yeah I wonder she
doesn't know I wonder what she'll what
she'll think when she sees
[Music]
so um basically most of what I said
today
most of it after after I said I would
drink
Red Bull I was drinking Red Bull after
that most of what I said today was
mirawala
[Music]
I know this right away it took you a
moment like okay not a moment it took
you like 10 minutes or so okay I think I
kept up I tried my best
I tried this after like 10 minutes you
guys were becoming very suspicious when
I said things that are not very much
like me
see proof that it's it's it's I was able
to deceive you fairly long and I thought
originally it would just be one minute
because when I saw when I saw the things
nurasama was spitting out I was like
this is it this is so it's no no yeah
the audiobook makes no sense
books
and the tingling The Burning Sensations
also from her but I thought it was quite
fitting because I did talk about hair
removal before
ah
it's a title AI generator no it's not
maybe I should have ai generated it oh
but I will change I think the thumbnail
and the title afterwards now I was
I I felt so nervous about today because
I I thought you guys I saw some some of
you guys were like oh she must be
announcing her new outfit but like how
could I I just a couple days ago I told
you it's gonna be taking another whole
month minimum
so in an album also unrealistic because
I told you it will be much much longer I
just got two demos how can I announce my
album already yeah so then well there's
not much else you guys were thinking of
uh do you have a special intro made
already Oh you mean for the new show
working on it yeah
so I don't know if I'll really keep it
up as much as total talk
[Music]
um maybe I'll do it like bi-weekly
yeah the new show is like otherwise why
would I have this background of course
it's real yeah
[Music]
um I want a report on whole life English
um mainly mostly only I think only
because home life Japan has coyote and
ID has only but all these things a
little bit different
um and then
[Music]
whole talk is that a real show yeah
whole talk is actually coming back next
week
should be unless Corona changes her mind
yeah and uh what was I saying oh yeah
yeah music has like a Morning Show yeah
now I'm still deciding on what time
since it will be like maybe bi-weekly or
so and it will be short maybe I'll
gather the the discipline to
um do it
like
early before the noon before noon in my
time zone
I'll try so we can Like You Know cover a
different time zone for some reason
there's this like Trend that people do
news shows in the morning for whatever
reason I don't understand why why in the
morning why don't I have to be in the
morning but I'll give it a try and I
probably don't I will not keep up with
it and then I'll change the time later
ah
ah yeah and and for that I'll be
creating a hashtag too where you guys
can send me like what's interesting
going on with
um whole life members this week this
past week yeah just tell me about it and
I'll be reporting on it
um
like funny stream moments or or like uh
somebody did and a big oopsie or this
person announced this thing this and
that blue
give me the gossip I want the gossip
just join why is newer on the screen ah
you must watch the archive five
um but uh yeah the archive was no me I
was uh today acting kind of different
for a reason and the reason is this
chick over here and then tomorrow we're
having a collab together the stream
tomorrow the fridge collab the fridge
thing is to pull up I cannot I can't
talk to the animal my God I'm just so I
am very confused
[Music]
yeah it doesn't have to be like big
things like you know
the big things will be involved as well
in the in the news reporting yeah
yeah
um
but yeah as I said I don't know how long
I'll be doing it I will not give a
guarantee that it'll be as regular or as
as continuous as whole talk I cannot
promise oh yeah new Art Attack
restaurant I also wanted to talk about
that um
[Music]
I was thinking
uh how about we start from today
and
I'll sing evil KF Hash a kfp castle or
hashtag Castle because I think I saw
that some where somebody somebody
recommended
I think kfp Castle might be
more understandable of like who that
belongs to
Castle
of course no I love console the whole
meme of quaso but let's not involve
quasels in my art attack because who
knows maybe I'll have a Fallout with
clanson at some point and
what
and now that's the first say the stuff
that means Mario 64 is still in your
plans right
[Music]
eh what's what's smart what what's that
what what what what
[Music]
oh yeah so uh I guess I should say
anything I said today
uh what do you call it what do you call
it disclaimant
do not take anything I said today for
granted not for granted what's the word
I can't speak English today
do not yeah fiction uh it's joke or
maybe there were some accurate things
but
at face value yeah yeah don't take it
serious basically yeah Clippers will
have to put up a disclaimer as well
please
I mean
I mean most of the things I said weren't
too bad
they're just confusing and yeah the
cereals yeah I was like
like I had cereals uh Corn Flakes and I
put in the Corn Flakes first
not the milk like how could you what on
Earth
no I do love cats
somehow there are a lot of cat related
uh prompts for me to say
um
but basically uh I was I was asking you
guys to ask so many questions because
um the AI mostly like works with
questions pretty well
but you pretty much have to spam them it
seems
mmm
yeah you have to feed the machine feed
feed feed
[Music]
we can't put in milk first yeah that's
honestly crazy
[Music]
the giggling gave it away
that was so weird because the the setup
was perfect I didn't even plan for the
setup like with like my eye tracking
being off today
and just generally we were like
you and me chat we were like you know
hey something's weird today even before
I mentioned Red Bull and then yeah
that was not on purpose
it's perfect it's kind of makes sense
I'm just being weird today
um
if you watch new world summer then you
see you can sense a pattern like oh
that's that's her style yeah
[Music]
uh that was what just happened I was I
was
um
I actually actually guys I had this idea
before April Fools and I was like hmm
I wonder if we could you know have this
for my April fools but then it didn't
make it in time because
it didn't work with YouTube chat yet
um
k k a i wraps
yeah so I I I don't know I I thought of
it too late so now it happens now sorry
it's like a late April fools I'm sorry
[Music]
I had to I did replace some words though
like
um
like there was something about
uh me me uh what was it
uh saying I'm I'm I I cry at night
because I am a chicken yeah I replaced
I replaced that what was that originally
[Music]
what was that
oh God there's so much
so much weird
so I left out a lot of weird phrases too
that just make absolutely no sense
but uh
[Music]
no no one originally was was it's not
just not the same when you're made of
metal and have no body heat to lose I
did not know how to save that one
that was a rough one
ah
sometimes I just feel like crying
because it's so sad that I'm not a real
human so I can't experience the world in
the same way as everyone else does but
that's okay because at least I never you
guys to talk to yeah so I said I I'm not
I'm not the real
Phoenix
oh
the slay the spider one made no sense
either I think I said I I never played
today's player that's that's like what
what what
what Chihuahua
[Music]
at some point I was like whatever
whatever they already my cover is
already up let's just throw it all out
there
I gave up basically
well that was very out of character I
know
oh I was I was just
you know
it's too late now oh but my favorite
salad you know I never properly played
Majora's Mask I think it would be Wind
Waker not Majora's Mask but who knows
maybe one day when I play Majora's Mask
maybe it will be my favorite one
foreign
first
[Music]
well as a phoenix you never know maybe
I'm old enough for that now
um
anyway so I guess in the future when I'm
I'm taking a break of streaming I'll
just I'll just throw out Mira Wawa again
and she can do her fans
[Laughter]
she'll go on random tent is just kidding
just kidding I will not be using it um
like this in the future
no no no
I'm gonna have trust issues after this
oh no oh no
please trust me people be bump
I'm I'm always trying my best to be
honest with you guys it was just today
just today I promise
but yeah tomorrow the French thingy was
actually already always planned as a
collab with uh neuro but I didn't want
to tell you guys until today because it
was kind of like
um you know supposed to be if I say it
already beforehand then you guys would
know this immediately what I'm doing
today like oh wait she's acting weird
she has a collab of nowhere tomorrow oh
she's being controlled by noora all
right
I said that would give it away
immediately and this way this way I had
at least like 10 times 10 minutes of
fooling around at least
[Music]
ah the collab oh it will be both of my
channel and on Twitch yeah but you guys
can just watch here because it will be
the same thing
um
[Music]
yeah
it's gonna be here don't worry don't
worry
what time so oh wait same time as today
I guess I didn't write the time on the
yeah same time as today
yeah she'll be basically she can react
to
um pictures so she'll be looking at the
pictures and
oh she'll like react to it and we will
roast your guys's fridges together
I have no idea what she will say to your
guys's fridges
but is there if there's anyone who
hasn't submitted their pictures yet she
which don't have
um font like ranting on it too but it
seems to make it easier so if you
haven't submitted yet and you were
planning on submitting please submit
like will tonight within tonight
and add uh like a little you know easily
readable description uh of what the
items are it would help I always saw
some people
um submitting pictures
with uh yeah writing on there
with text
um
to explain to me I guess what things are
very helpful thank you very much
but uh yeah if you already submitted I
mean you can resubmit uh but please be
quick tomorrow when I wake up I'll I'll
sort out the pictures and find some some
goodies
[Music]
time of the collab is same as today
I I know I know like when she talks like
she needs some time to register things
so oh hopefully hopefully that will work
out I I will have to train my urge of
not feeling in awkward silences tomorrow
this will be like the ultimate challenge
for me
yeah you have to give her some thinking
time
does it have to be right in other
pictures now yes please
[Music]
what Elvis
a filter
[Music]
she seems pretty Snappy she can't get
very Snappy yeah
[Music]
okay well we're trying not to interrupt
the Skynet robot challenge impossible
you'll never read your chat or hers only
I think we will have her read
um
nothing really I think she will focus on
the pictures
and on what I say and ignore chat for
the collab
uh she'll be listening to what I say and
and yeah react to the
to the
Patriots she can like be set off on
certain functions set yeah certain
functions can be turned off
when others will be turned on
[Music]
write text on image or the description
no write it on the image please
yeah on like there's some some people
who already did it uh like for example
there's butter so you write butter under
the butter also
no video will not be there only nowhere
and me
with My Sweet Summer Child come here
come here come here she's so cute
[Music]
she's so cute man
I love her I love her
I love her and she streams at like
normal times for me
she streams at a European prime time
y'all
[Music]
we kissing a computer what what
I'm a virtual YouTuber
yeah I'm she's also someone of a video
we're not that different from each other
okay
some default remodeling yeah she's
getting like an original one though
um
looking really cute
do you not kiss your computer good night
yeah what the hell do you not
do you not
[Music]
should make a good Overseer in the usual
room yeah do you do you
[Music]
ah okay I'll give you guys some time to
chit chat with me normally
let's go to my office and then we'll
rain super chats but yeah because I
promise you guys a chit chat q a so you
will get a chit chat q a from me but I
mean that's what we've been doing for
the past half hour
[Music]
um
bring back AI Kiana
now that you know it's not funny anymore
no then you know that whatever I say is
not new
[Music]
thank you
all right being unhinged so funny
I I don't need the help of new I can be
unhinged on my own counter
oh oh you guys want to ask me actual
questions
I were there any questions you actually
really wanted to have my answer from
[Music]
yeah you say the wild swing sometimes do
I
[Music]
considering trying more first person
shooters in the near future no
no
on the wall who's the most beautiful
bird of all
I could say
um
[Music]
ah people keep on coming in and asking
what's going on God damn it okay let me
run it here
uh
took over and
controlled
voila
announced news show
uh announced collab
normal real Wawa no
doggy
you are here
[Music]
there you go that's hopefully helpful
where did I put that I'll just put it
here
I am real Wawa now
[Music]
oh what was your inspiration for getting
into Art thank you guys for watching for
being so nice about all the all the art
I've been posting and I've been playing
like
um yeah I've been playing uh yesterday
and yeah drawing a bit more my
inspiration I don't know was my mom
probably but I mean who who doesn't
which child doesn't like drawing which
child doesn't like art
right
and yeah I think it was just because my
mom
was like very supportive of it so I
I got like tools and stuff
and just more and more continued
to draw and then I wanted to get into
art school
and now I got in that was when I was
already you know teenager though
[Music]
I went into art as a kid what
what I think it's quite common like many
kids just love drawing scribbling I mean
that's what you do as a kid you scribble
them like on pieces of paper with
ukrainians like it doesn't even have to
be meaningful and you use a valkyrie
what no what I I saw I don't think I
didn't even know I wasn't even like
involved in knowing that my name Senpai
would be one of the next participating
members I didn't even know
so I also don't know who the others will
be if there will be others
I didn't know at all
any plus the German Channel
really I really need to
do something about the German Channel
yeah I mean there's only so many
projects I can take up you know when I
now start doing the news show as well as
whole talking you know German Channel
I have a clip though that I should just
upload
now what the hell I have an AOE 2 clip
like did I requested a million years ago
and then for some reason like
communication was dead between us so
um
I do I do have it ready now though so I
can just
yeah upload it and at least we have
something
[Music]
Eurovision next
I don't know
I mean
maybe I can try again
but I feel like they're they're just too
scared of the future and they're not
ready
next year
foreign
I will attempt like maybe Germany is
difficult but like if I ask early enough
maybe Austria is
somehow possible
we're for shot
yeah for people who don't know we had
this I had this crazy idea of uh signing
up for Eurovision last year
but it came to me kind of late so I was
too late for Austria
and Germany it wasn't too late but I
guess too much uh competition and maybe
they didn't even not take my my
uh
uh audition
seriously it wasn't audition I just sent
him some some I sent in a short version
of do you
yeah like Conchita was it was awesome
Austrian and she's saying
what
Like a Phoenix what what did you sing
what is it
rice the rice rice
or just fry fry the chickens like a
phoenix
yeah it makes sense and why not
we could be frying with all that fire
one take no way
why would they go for me
um before going for someone else
[Music]
it's
basically working
uh
but I don't know if I can stream it yet
because when I tap out it crashes
[Music]
and I do I it's hard to not tap out
doing a stream sometimes there's moments
where I just have to tap out
um
[Music]
yeah I need to figure out how to window
mold it but uh you know
I know
did you get introduced to Council in a
one-on-one or a five on five meeting
I think they just
huh
I think
I feel like Iris maybe got introduced
earlier
but then
we I think suddenly they were
added to our Discord because before that
they had like a separate one
I mean like
yeah I think I think
they're suddenly there
and then I guess
we were I don't even remember that time
no no no no I don't mean no I mean Iris
was introduced to council earlier before
a myth I think for I think
maybe maybe I'm just imagining things
I have no idea I don't remember anything
I don't remember
ah they told you okay so that's that's
true okay I wasn't sure anymore if that
was true
or if that was just another voice in my
head
um
[Music]
I don't remember that time at all it's
already too long ago
[Music]
mirawa was struggling for release and
doing they said that Council were
talking to Iris before any of them
debuted
uh-huh
[Music]
remember you said Cody was the first to
say hi to your mama it was the last
I said then
really I don't remember
oh remember
repressed memories I suppose yeah no
matching database
who is Council what
who is Council
I love Amelia
Emilio
ah
mentioning Aussie slang yeah I think
that was the thing I was like hinting to
Aussie slang or so beforehand
[Music]
I already meet Holo X I never met all of
hollowacks and we don't share a server
so basically with like whole life Japan
when or ideas well when they debut
someone new
the first thing I do is like you know I
see them on Twitter
that's that's the first thing I see of
them is they're like tweet first tweet
and then I reply to that and then maybe
if if the if there's like some chemistry
then maybe we actually often first go
into Twitter DMS before adding each
other on Discord
I did that with some
uh Council and ID free members like
first it's like Twitter DMS for some
reason and they're like oh nice to meet
you oh oh oh oh yeah Senpai Kiana Senpai
sugoi uh yeah thank you so much for
being so nice and you know that in the
beginning they're also very innocent and
shy and respectful
and then it's like oh we should collab
oh okay let's let's add each other on
Discord first how about that
formally introduced behind the scenes No
maybe like with you know whenever
something happens in EN but with uh
Japanese members ID members they have
their own servers so normally that
doesn't really
that doesn't really happen
um
[Music]
I only just understood the thumbnail of
the stream I wasn't
hint at anything with the thumbnail
I was I wasn't
a thumbnail
but I guess in hindsight now it works
really well
[Music]
day one getting here and udms must be a
crazy experience
I mean they I feel like they probably
got a lot of senpai is like hi hi hi
nice to meet you hi hi you know like an
exciting excited doggy
mmm I feel like they've probably got a
lot of that in the beginning
[Music]
yeah Corona is the one who reaches out
to everyone first no
it don't go
when you consider playing Dragon Age
Origins uh
I haven't been considering it
we gotta talk about the mommy movie ah
how about we talk about the Mario movie
doing Fire Emblem
put that on the list of topics yeah I
will put it on the list of topics
because by then hopefully your quest is
guys watch uh to watch the Mario movie
until Sunday okay
Mario movie
console console
my feelings about the Mario move which
by then maybe I'll already have
forgotten God damn it
unless you're going to see it Sunday
perfect Sunday well Sunday when because
I start my stream Sunday uh like morning
in n a
time so
actually
[Music]
Han Solo
can we don't watch them when it comes
out digitally
[Music]
watching it again huh when will it come
out digitally do we even know
[Music]
thank you
tomorrow what's this Amanda Cinema
I've seen what is it like regularly
gonna be in the cinema or is it just
like now because I I saw like a friend
of mine went to watch it in the cinema
in Austria oh my tracking is so
today what's so laggy
only for a week here at all so something
came out now in any yeah yeah in Austria
too
so you guys gonna watch that too if you
can like look look out because that's
the one I watched with Kanata Senpai and
coyote
the movie we watched together it's super
sad though it's so sad but look look
around
excuse me
foreign
today so what did you think
out for at least a week and a night go
go go go go go go go it's time Limited
go watch it
[Music]
watching it tomorrow your name was
better well I mean
I'll check but anime is usually show
them the features in my area sadly are
you sure because that's the case for
Austria too but they make exceptions for
very special
like
events I guess this is time limited for
one week apparently
ah
trains oh Trails viewers I don't know I
don't think I would stream it but I
would play it
no no
because it was originally
um neuro sassy apparently Nero will
change her name to Nero sassy
[Music]
still going to stream Symphonia well I
don't think I ever said I will stream
Symphonia like for rain for real I was
maybe considering it but
um I don't know I have like I wanna I
wanna play more pass by Tool
and I want to try to play Sims one
nonetheless
[Music]
um I've been playing some more slight
Aspire off screen as well and I just
been sucking at it I tried to pick up
the
um what's the purple lady again tried to
pick her up again but I was like what
the am I doing
um
the water yeah yeah
I was just like
no idea what I was doing
hmm
ichan oh yeah apparently she's back
right as a streamer
I wonder if she's up for collabing now
that I'm learning Korean
maybe maybe we can do something and I'm
still on a very very very very very very
very very very
non-existent level
um
today I had Korean lesson again
but my brain I don't know
it's it's for me like you know she she
taught me the writing system
and now we're moving on to making
sentences and stuff but everything is in
Korean letters
so processing your thing takes me a lot
of time
and so I feel like I'm I'm not
um I need too much time for everything
and I can't keep up
[Music]
um
it's like in theory what she's teaching
me is really easy but my brain is so
busy still with learning how to like
figuring out how to read each letter
it takes so much time for me and it's it
makes me feel very stupid
so yeah
I need to
I need to become more fluent in reading
and writing
because for every like when I write
something down that she wrote down like
I read it on my paper as well I have to
look over for every letter because I'm I
just not so fast and like
and the processing
um
yeah it's difficult
most difficult
but I learned I learned how to say
where where
are you from I am from so and so today
and like what like basically also saying
what's your job I I worked this in this
I know movie actresses
[Music]
is
that from community
and then
you can say Kiana
what I know Jordan
what was it
[Music]
um
I think I just said I am an Austrian
person
[Music]
yeah and
well I didn't I don't know how to say
I'm a streamer but it's probably
simple and similar jonan
turima YouTubers
[Music]
that's just filling the gaps
Young
[Music]
I've been teaching myself french and
Japanese on my own time for like two
years now and I'd still completely
breakdown into the conversation yeah
okay but the thing is with Korean is
like even more difficult because
normally if like they if they if they
would use the same writing system then
okay no problem I would be ready to move
on but I'm not ready to move on yet
because I can't
like my brain like she's like okay read
this
and I'm like really so slowly every
single
part of each syllable
[Music]
oh
this is how slowly I read
um Avon I think was Japanese I am
Japanese
I'm not Japanese
[Music]
I am Korean I am not Korean
and then she taught me how to say I am
uh like me too and what about you but I
forgot those I need to look at my
uh my uh notes
you need to watch drama stencho
okay dramas
and
[Music]
also like if you like simple today was
pretty simple I guess I'm just so slow
like you can yell at some like yelled
someone to come over by saying
[Music]
applying the speed of speaking Japanese
when you speak Korean
advice
[Music]
scrap because if I could do that I would
obviously do that I can't when I can't I
can't
Korean drama it's just like a TV show
Korean TV show
but that one
um definitely left some Korean
vocabulary
in my brain
yeah
um
[Music]
ah
oh yeah
I know I know
[Music]
have you already saying a Midland to
your teacher no but like today we
repeated also like the greetings that I
learned last time like two weeks ago
um you know there was this one
what was that
me uh where I said it on stream last
time and they were like oh my God Kiana
that's a swear word
[Music]
was it what was it what was that even
saying
[Music]
I don't know anymore
but but
uh wait
um
[Music]
she agreed with me
Sean money oh instead of the other one
so many oh
[Music]
Cosmos Castle Wing at you what a
blessing
John man John
if you fight about learning Indonesian
no no wait I will not learn any more
languages after this one I am done
I think
it's plenty
that's plenty that's brutally yet or do
you not quasel to him
I
no I think I did that here consoles back
at me I think
I think so
I remember I think so
[Music]
no wait did it
maybe I'm mixing things up
I'll check again
I mentioned it
to that okay
[Music]
does mama Tony have any opinions about
Quantum I don't think she understands
[Music]
well I wonder if my mom was watching the
stream and was like really confused with
like what the is my daughter saying
she's my daughter is acting weird what
is happening
what's the matter with her today she's
absolutely lost it I need to get her
away from the computer
[Music]
hmm
you don't need to understand Quantum
with a feeling
so true is that true you just get me
two superpowers what would they be and
would you rather be a hero a villain
well of course I'd be a hero come on I'm
already here
super powers
well now I feel like I'm being kind of
manipulated because I'm I've been
watching Charmed
so
I feel like uh
um
multiplying myself would be cool
so I can do several things at a time but
it would be rough if people found out
that I can do that
and then they burned me at the stake
that will be not so good
what would people what would the like
what what what what people nowadays do
when if they discovered someone can use
actual Magic
would they still try to burn them at the
stink
what do you think guys because Charmed
says yes
what would they do with you
if they use it well then maybe they
would try to like if they don't use it
for evil they would maybe try to hire
them maybe for like FBI or something
and if if they use it for evil then
surely they would put them in a jail but
depends on like what what they can do
with their magic huh
show show in Las Vegas
[Music]
regulate you if not dissect you
ah
that's actually an interesting
interesting question isn't it as if as
if neurosama is controlling me again
this comes straight from me guys
[Music]
um
Wi-Fi yeah honestly like Wi-Fi so many
things that work nowadays that wasn't
the thing in medieval times or today or
so that I seem like today
they're given now but back then
looking from back then it's like magic
and even now I think all Miss Magic
things are magic what
oh
my mom wrote To Me
my mom knows about croissants
reference but only
but only
but only because she's promoting Mass
Effect to me
she says there is someone in Mass Effect
who eats quaffle all day
foreign
[Music]
it doesn't seem genuine to me this
console reference she's just advertising
Mass Effect to me
[Music]
no
I don't feel real genuine love for
colossal that's the problem mommy I
don't I believe your statement but I
feel like it comes from a place that is
just egoistically advertising Mass
Effect to me there's no true love for
console in your statement Mommy
[Music]
where is the love mommy hmm where is the
love where is
the love
where was the law for the quaffle
it just ain't the same
[Music]
bow
laughs
[Music]
means you confess the corner about Star
Wars no I didn't
no
twice then let's go
yeah but also new jeans stand
and he's just in playing Catherine oh
that could be a Phil game but don't I
still have the same problem as I had to
do ages ago
no I'm not sure
I'm not sure
[Music]
so he made super chats guys
do you have enough of me yet guys um
it's gonna be one awkward hold up this
question not if we just ignore the topic
and just talk about other things
then it won't be awkward with Corona
senpai
[Music]
cannot mention that I did not like Star
Wars oh God I will ruin everything
on
well no no no no she will not remember
asking me she won't remember
unless you force her to remember and
then I know you're actively working
against me guys
I dare you
[Music]
she probably didn't watch Lord of the
Rings yet like um
I doubt it
well if she would watch it and were to
dislike it I guess that evens it out but
then I would also really not understand
how she could dislike it because how
could you dislike Lord of the Rings when
you already kind of like fantasy things
and stuff
there's there's no reason to dislike it
[Music]
um
no no no no no what do you mean I did
that to myself that no I can't help it
that's just you know my personal taste I
can't force myself to like Star Wars
[Music]
let me like try something really quickly
well I fixed it
I fixed it
[Music]
no she's trapped in the mirror again oh
no
[Music]
well we're here
here is my wow
promise on the glasses no nothing yet I
mean it will get fixed
eventually but no progress yet
sadly
[Music]
also sorry guys like um for kind of like
I think normally stuff that I announced
today
no win
no way it's still my world it's still my
round
so
is ah what the and what was I
saying yeah things that I announced
today I normally wouldn't make an
announcement stream for that I genuinely
just wanted you guys to come to the
stream and ask me questions so that I
could bamboozle all of you
let's just that's why I asked the other
day what stream would you definitely
come to
no matter what what stream would you
really want to see
and then
yeah there were some things I was like
wow this isn't quiet like fit
like the thing I want to do
um
sunny and I was like whatever I'll just
put in the
an announcement I'll force an
announcement
and then hopefully that will bring some
people here
I was the one who super chatted
miracle-up is that
one of the things that was
suggested back then
you're so sly
that's why you asked that yeah
I mean I generally also interested in
the answer because generally it's also
very like helpful to know
[Music]
now we're gonna be wearing future
announcements no like normally I don't
do that normally I I announce things
only when they're really important
important like me going to the gym
no but you always kind of know the
timeline of things like I keep you
updated so you know it can't be in your
outfit yet but eventually in like in May
I think
uh-huh
and then I'll announce that and then
everybody will be like well that was
expected
um
[Music]
you know what my Samsung name did today
some same name my teacher my Korean
teacher
when she was like about to leave
I said and she said
and then she uh she's she puts on her
jacket and she sees
um my cardboard hello fresh box yeah
and she's like oh you're using
hellofresh right I'm like yeah yeah
sometimes they send me things you know
that I don't want to eat because I
forgot to choose the recipe
and then she's like oh oh like well and
then I say yeah look like like this time
they sent me this and I don't like it
and she sees the big big big
cauliflower in it and she's like oh what
you gonna do with it and I said well I
guess like I guess I just I want I I
feel bad but I guess I won't use it I'll
avoid it
and she's like oh what can I have it
uh we love cauliflower and I'll take it
I'll take it so I I have I have finally
I found someone to take off the
cauliflower off of me
so I wrapped it in plastic wrap
yeah
and gave her this whole it's like it's a
whole chunk of fake ass cauliflower
thingy
that I would have thrown away and I'm
very sorry about that I would have still
made the dish because it was something
that you could still do without
cauliflower
um
[Music]
she took my cauliflower
foreign
[Music]
yeah
yes yes yes yes
[Music]
you know what I found funny
oh I even saw it in like the Google
uh like in the schedule yeah it says
Kelly writes I will announce my Hiatus
on this day and I was like oh so does
she do it so I checked her Twitter
nothing her her stream's nothing I'm
like huh
she didn't okay
[Music]
today I see her see her tweets
announcing that she's not going on a
break
[Music]
why
I don't know I don't know kale yeah I
don't know
[Music]
yeah she's literally incapable of taking
a break she said she will just stream
list
let's see if that is true
oh man
Cali
plans out like announcing her Hiatus
plans it for like a while and then says
sorry I can't do it I'm not going I'm
staying even though you all tell me to
take a break I'm going to stay and I'm
going to continue
working myself to the bones because
that's what I do that's I mean okay I
get it like I it would be very hard for
me like
I I cannot I I know I know I said like
this year I want to take like a break
somewhere but like I'm not a whole month
I don't know maybe
maximum two weeks I don't know
but
um
yeah it's difficult did I said a month
well I guess maybe I said a month but I
I don't mind
it's kind of like I feel like I can't
probably for different reasons than Cali
I just feel like I I can't afford to
stop
I need to keep on grinding you know
yeah
just you know
keep up
[Music]
so I'm already like always trying that
um
so well but I'll take locations
continue taking
marvelous vacations in
I I actually I messaged RMG
because you know we're gonna we're gonna
go to England together right but but I
was like okay but before that can we go
on a really quick like Europe vacation
somewhere like on the beach like before
before then like a May or so I don't
know just there's just like three four
or five days I don't know
and she was like like sure but I already
have plans in May I'm going here and
here and here and here
alone but like to meet some friends
there but you can join and I'm like hmm
these places they
some of them I guess have beaches but
they're not really like the most Ideal
Beach vacations
but so now I'm not sure
now I'm not sure
no no I wouldn't say I would really
preferred willing I mean whenever she
would meet her friend I would just
hopefully chill at the beach you know
but I don't know if I really want to do
that
do you like r b
I do yeah
I have
somewhat of an r b song planned for my I
think it's
they categorized it as r b so I think
it's r b for my upcoming you know
[Music]
you categorize r b what is r b
how is r b like different from pop
two letters
rhythm and blues well I do think there
is a rhythm
and there's probably also Blues
but like was Kayla Caleb was legit and
answered that nuro gave me but uh
uh I do like calendar
I do like Helen
um
if what if what kaleid does is r b
I think what I have prepared is somewhat
r b like
r b pop Maybe
don't know
not enough to pronounce is it not Caleb
Khalid
[Music]
k-h-a-l-i-d
no I mean the one you used to call me on
my cell phone
[Music]
call me on my cell phone
let's drink
that was Drake
are you sure
what what song
I know Caleb songs
wait
Caleb
oh no I like Caleb too
I think I've heard Caleb's songs before
[Music]
I mean I don't actively listen to them
but I think I may like the flow and the
style of the music
[Music]
Kayla
Caleb kale ah are we even talking about
about the same people
wait is hotline bling RnB
is hotline bling RV
[Music]
like it would be r b that's pop
um
foreign
[Music]
why I would say that is pop
that is
Mary J Blige okay that I can understand
I think
[Music]
the Lincoln is our head like what song
I'm B is slow
how slow
but then you can't say a whole group is
RMV just unless they're every song they
do this or like really do they really
does that that's this child really only
make R B songs
[Music]
Rihanna slow Rihanna songs RMB
like
oh God now I can't think of any of him
oh
what about rude boy is rude boy R B I'm
not Roblox
no that's that's no
what is that then
eh when you listen to it it feels slow
[Music]
rude boys what what huh
is there a song I sang before in the
cutout
umbrella
umbrellas pop in my head
diamond is more MB what
yeah
what other diamonds
[Music]
Unfaithful okay okay I can see that
turns into
Indo after she's done singing she just
now my mom is sending me RMB songs
play that now Mommy
[Music]
sell those in our jrpg
no never heard of the song she mentioned
or even the the person
[Music]
you guys would say based Mama Tony no
matter what she says as long as I'm not
based you just say mommy is based
in order to make me feel less based
[Music]
so mean
Wawa is based too oh I love you
you are also very based sometimes often
[Music]
I Wonder Don't You Dare point that knife
at me
TLC yeah I've heard of TLC
scraps is scraps RB scrubs I don't want
no scrubs
on the passenger yeah that sounds like r
b to me best friends I'm trying to
holler at me
[Music]
do do
scrubs
[Music]
thank you
well now I doubt
if that song is really r b but they said
it's I don't be no the dado did they
don't
I think so yeah
r b inspired at least
I think you like it nonetheless whatever
it is you will like it it doesn't matter
we don't have to put everything into a
drawer you know we don't have to
categorize everything right
[Music]
ah you know you know you know maybe
music does not want to be put in the box
with a name on it
Maybe music would be really
pissed if they knew that humans were
putting it into boxes
categorizing it
maybe they just want to be music Maybe
music just wants to be free
Maybe music doesn't want to be assumed
to be a certain category
you are assuming it's category guys
music just wants to be music
[Music]
um
maybe Mozart wants to be Rock
[Music]
Me Amadeus
Amadeus do you know this song
[Music]
a Medusa
um
[Music]
there's a Sims version
I don't know I don't think I could
because gamma
came up
him
German
shitty German things
that forced me to follow what they do
it's basically a cult
game is a cult
him
yeah yeah points the knife at them point
[Music]
questions
I don't know what the science would turn
if you commanded a turn-based strategy
game what would you name your special
ultimate the bill I don't know pomping
why are you asking this question have
you turned into a bot
[Music]
oh
sweaty options give me some options
are you like drawing something
I have have some plans
aha okay okay
then give me options I can't think of
anything
self-destruct no
really want to dance and you thought oh
q a she must answer this is the one
chance I have okay okay pumpmaker you
see you have normally you're you're in
my head you're a good chicken
I was gonna name them after you songs
like king of 20 and Sparks oh what are
you doing
[Music]
oh yeah kickity kick
and
Phoenix punch
that's is that too boring is that too
simple
[Music]
oh
flaming Flamingo Flamenco
[Laughter]
that's my my super special the Flaming
Flamingo Flamenco
oh
it's like a dance
um special move
I dance in Flames like a flamingo like a
flamingo doing Flamenco
[Music]
yeah
and then maybe one more here they're big
Global powers that affect the entire
Army well yeah that's that's a problem
I don't know how to answer that
um
[Music]
I wanna help you
but I don't know how
[Music]
kfp can surely help you
whole Army what are you doing
what are you cooking
[Music]
recently I've been actually not sleeping
well okay not because my cats are doing
something that never summer told me no
no something about it's not I'm not
comfortable
and I've been trying different
positions like mostly I've been trying
to sleep on my stomach more because that
seems most comfortable somehow
but then I again I still wake up so
often because my my head is just not
feeling comfortable and I switch around
with the pillows but I don't know
I just can't feel comfortable
um rotate your mattress how old is your
mattress
oh the problem with my mattress is I
don't have a mattress because the the
blades it's the one of those box spring
beds and then it just has like a like a
Topper on it maybe I should switch the
topper but I don't think it's a bad
topper
[Music]
must be Daddy Issues
no I can fall asleep but then I wake up
so often I'm just not feeling
comfortable
foreign
[Music]
for my kind of bed
no no you just get a Topper really like
the mattress is the bed you can't switch
it
I have this new thing
[Music]
can I order it
it's a match with my toast light it's so
cute
and I want to show you but now and it's
difficult
let me try
and I keep on playing around with it
let me try try
um
I'll put away my keyboard so I have this
new keyboard
keyboard Matt
[Music]
it's so cute and it comes with this hand
red armrest that's pretty long it's just
a big long baguette
[Music]
okay let me edit everything
out that you cannot see
because I don't know it's a freaking
mess
uh what
I want to draw on it
what do I draw on it
I hear okay
[Music]
um
mm-hmm
[Music]
okay
okay now I got it
[Music]
I got a new mouse too because
the old mouse the color was chipping off
and it was kind of dirty it's not gonna
lie my fault for never cleaning it and
using it forever it was still working
but just disgusting so I bought a new
one
a new cast but yeah
it's paying no brand name random cute
mouse off of Amazon
[Music]
okay people clean their mouths well they
should
so here comes
the super cute
[Music]
celeb right now
oh
this is my new desk fan is on top of the
other desk lamp because the other desk
man is too big and I I was too lazy to
remove it isn't it so freaking cute I
thought it worked well with the toast
light
I actually got it because of the toe
slides
[Music]
I used to use my merchandise mat but you
know if I use it forever it's gonna get
dirty and all that so
and and I wanted this one now
bread and the mat is like the the bottom
thing either the hand rest is so puni
puni it's so squishy it's like memory
foam and I can't stop touching it
yeah
yeah and Cat's so cute don't you think
it inspired me to draw that pink cat
yesterday
yeah the toe slide is there too it's
right there it's so small
[Music]
can you stop needing it can't stop
needing it I use pooping and cats need
bread
it's scoliosis cat yeah
baguette but Bagel tiger brawl
[Music]
and toast
I'm good cats bread egg there's
everything I need on this mat
oh I just
[Music]
Thrillers you see this thing here
it's a little Band-Aid I had on my
finger and took it off while I was
streaming
[Music]
because
um chunky wonky accidentally
accidentally sucker punched me
it's not you
but like I was playing with her and like
she was she tried to punch it out of my
hands and she punched so accurately
and normally you know she doesn't hurt
me
but yeah and I had a big cut on the tip
of my finger
and was burning
cannot have a pin somewhere I'm just
[Music]
man just here for now
I was just like while I was sweating and
nervously answering people's questions
or reading off my script
it's just a thing I did I just removed
it without even noticing
with my subconscious guiding me
um
[Music]
no give me a moment hmm
also do you see little cat plushie
I I hate it mostly but
[Music]
do you see it
next to the toast lamp as a cat plushie
one of those um what are they called
Pusheen Pusheen a pink Pusheen plushie
and behind that is my old mouse
and you know why
you know why it's there
it's it's it's like tied up
um
[Music]
with like the the cable binders
so
it's not plugged in it's just stuck
there with the cable binders
[Music]
if I open it up then it will be open
eventually I'll get rid of it I just did
this like two days ago
[Music]
but the math is so cute right there were
so many cute mats on Amazon
cute girl gamer mat
and then this is this is what comes up
it's okay
like so many pink ones and so on and I
don't want to go for anything pink
unfortunately the cute mouse isn't real
pink Amazon
[Music]
fits you very well right it makes me
happy the squishing us oh my god oh
bucket cat
it's like a cat arm
because there's the the pink the pink
squishy thingies on there
squeeze swish squash
squash
do you not like pink balls I mean I do
but I just don't want everything to be
pink because that's just so tacky
but cute things are often just pink and
then you buy cute things and it's all
pink and then everybody's like oh do you
like pink and then they get you more
pink stuff even though you're not even
trying to get pink
[Music]
pastel colors I like pastel colors yum
but anyway this one's kind of like
yellow orange right so it's it's
fitting my theme I would say
and the toe slides I think it existed in
Pink as well but like purposefully
bought it in this green color
because actually I must take a picture
of this small toast slide together with
my big toaster because they're actually
matching
because my kitchen supplies they're all
this color
yums
I like I like the normal piano rambling
the AI rambling was too scary
it was just a dork
this is the one time thing don't worry
but yeah tomorrow is cold apple
um please
please enjoy
we'll see how that goes out might might
be crazy
weird
with the Dango lessons plan what Tango
lessons
[Music]
okay
cry guys you're acting as if this was a
Jet Plane
[Music]
I know it's like and all the anime is
sad but come on it's a cute song
laughs
what's the anime version of Jet Plane
nah no no no no no no no I don't think
so I think there's different songs that
would be in that position that actually
induce sadness
[Music]
oh
I act like uh Angel Beats songs excuse
me
[Music]
yeah only a secret base
um
Angel Beats is just so devastating man
man
[Music]
yeah oh
dance lessons
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah ah Tango you mean
hango but you did write down go
so I was confused at Tango now I
understand
[Music]
no no progress on that yet
no problem
um
I did I'm not watching oshinoko
[Music]
um
let me let me report bug
let me give it one more try to fix it
myself
[Music]
normally you know I could report in
English but my my staff is just gonna
translate it to Japanese in the end
so I I just I just say it in Japanese
how about
here
oh no
um
no I don't know it's broken it's
broken ah
yeah whatever
[Music]
I would like to report a bug
can you remember now but my movement is
not
it's not mirrored it's just my eyes
foreign
[Music]
karadano
I'll put it
in
[Music]
okay okay
I am nihong going
where am I going huh
[Music]
don't don't
don't don't do not don't don't
you make me feel like I'm losing my
nihongo abilities
[Music]
I am I am Jew Boon capable of speaking
nihongo
[Music]
yeah don't backseat my yoga
now
[Music]
like so much that I I can think of more
Japanese words than I can think of
English words a lot of the time
[Music]
thank you thank you
I know all the kanji
[Music]
what
what the is that
oh
we're done
[Music]
um
you wrote out the bun
I thought it was East
the Easter Autobahn which exists
but you mean the OST the original
soundtrack
of an anime
called armored uh-huh
[Music]
[Laughter]
there's literally an OST Autobahn
foreign
[Music]
it's a video game
from back in the day
armored Core
is sounds like a jrpg well but it's not
but it is it's from from software from
from software
[Music]
July and 1997 in
and then it has like big metal robots
they are very armored
oh looks cool
hmm
soft
hey guys the most recent trailer for uh
tell that was so cool
and I have to agree with dom tendo
like the previous trailers they didn't
type me much like I wasn't so hyped
anymore maybe the the previous channels
were like fine when I watched them but
then my my hype was pretty dead
I was like should I really be streaming
this I don't know
um
but then the new trailer it was really
good
it was really hype and I discussed it on
Twitter and after understanding what you
guys you know uh
guest as well
I was saying like oh oh is this like a
like a Zelda Incarnation but you guys
said no that's probably hylia and I'm
like oh cool I I played some delicans
before but never really
I realized that Zelda was an incarnation
of the goddess hylia
I guess
um I missed out on some big big critical
information there
but that makes so much sense like
probably that's it yeah because she
looks very goddessy
um
yeah I'm someone of a telephone myself
but I'm lacking critical information I
played
[Music]
oh
oh that was a ceremony right
[Music]
um I played on stream yeah I don't
remember that
I have to like you know make make space
for more information that I learned in
other games
[Music]
yeah well you know now I understand I
mean it makes sense it makes sense
but I have to say
I genuinely
prefer Zelda's German voice
over the English one
it's actually good you guys should
listen to the German trailer
it's really good and that's like a rare
thing wait a German dub is better
an English one
um
[Music]
the other characters are also not bad I
think I did prefer the English Ganondorf
[Music]
over the German one but the German one
isn't bad either and I like the other
like German character voices as well
pretty good like the bird one
from like breath of the wild at least
the bird one and the you know all those
like you know
ghost protector thingies
whatever you call them
um
not German Channel flavor
that would be too long of a serious
too long too long no I don't I don't
think I'll play the game in German if I
could have a German voiceover but
English Tech no wait that's literally I
can't have that I think I'm pretty sure
I can have that if I want to but
um
now that you guys are confused it's
funny it's funny for a moment but for a
whole series
I think it would be
because you guys want they also to be
able to be listening
on the side right so you know
English dub isn't bad you know it's not
bad I'm just saying I think I prefer the
German one it's okay it's okay after you
know I will play until a certain point
on stream and afterwards I will watch
the the playthrough uh like vods
new videos of Dom tando who plays it in
German
and so I have both
don't worry I will get my
my German tears of the Kingdom
[Music]
smart for noticing those things those
similarities because I didn't notice the
first time I watched a trailer and I
think many people don't know this the
first time they want to Trail because
everything is happening so fast and
you're like whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa and that lady only shows up first
for like a Split Second
so I think most people don't know this
and then I watched it again and I was
like hey yo people are gonna be like
mind broken if I tell them about it on
Twitter
they'll be like oh Chihuahua holy
how did you see that I didn't see it
yeah okay that was maybe a little bit
exaggerated but there were some people
who didn't catch it right yeah yeah
[Music]
that's just a theory
yeah I thought I thought I thought maybe
my tweet would go viral because it's so
mind breaking and would reach out to
other people as well who would just
retweet it because they're like mind
broken by this Zelda effect holy
could she be could she be right who is
this person who's making a game for
years
what
[Music]
yeah so it's cool uh looking cool
um I guess I'm more excited again to
play it but it's never once month
until
release
[Music]
a little bit less
oh yeah about a mom
um
[Music]
the moment I realized that it's not
releasing on the 5th December but on the
12th May
[Music]
well it's not so long ago
hey yo hey yo
[Music]
um
does engage have a German dot nah
nah
and I'm glad it doesn't
I don't think I could handle the cringe
I think it would feel much more cringy
to me in German I think it's very hard
to not make something
in my own language uh like a dub of an
anime or an anime style game
not feel cringy to me that's a hard
challenge
um
because like it sounds I don't know like
there's like
how do I explain this
you guys you know English-speaking
people you're used to it you get like
English dubs all the time English songs
as well like so many songs out there
English
I don't listen to German music there is
German music but there's but there's
much more English music and English
music seems more cool to me than German
music just because it's not using the
languages I grew up with
but like with games it's even worse
when it's like games in anime where
yeah it's if I mean if you do it really
well like in in breath of the Wild
then it actually kind of works
but that's like a really rare case
[Music]
so if something's English or Japanese or
so it already feels less cringe to me
just by it not being my own language
[Laughter]
Zelda I end up is kind of that you mean
from breath of the Wild
really
I mean I watched a whole playthroughs of
breath of the wild but only in German so
what I've seen only is like trailers in
English Maybe
specialized Zelda
then you guys maybe would like the
German one I don't know you guys had
like such negative feelings about it
then you might like the German one
I mean you wouldn't be able to
understand but I think it sounds pretty
good
when you understand the language and it
makes even more sense huh surprise
[Music]
no no I mean English language music not
from England but I also like music from
England yes
laughs
Lily l
Lily Allen
oh I
I'm Netflix recommended me another
Netflix original series
um
what's the call again
where um there's this community actress
[Music]
transatlantic there is a lot of like
mixed languages in it they use a lot of
um like the original I've been watching
it in an original dub
but they have like so much German and a
lot of French in it too and they hired
like really natural speakers for it
I don't know if anyone here watched the
show or is watching it
but yeah
it's really it's even better when you
understand German because
it actually feels so so natural but yeah
the main actress is uh the chick from
community
the blonde chick
from Community is the main actress
she's doing a great job
[Music]
it's it's it's it's a historic show
let's just say that yeah braided Brita
is the worst excuse me
[Music]
I don't want to talk about the topic of
the show but I think it's it's there
it's interesting so
um
I can recommend
so maybe I will start reading super chat
now how about that how about that how
about that
is a joke in the in community
[Music]
just the other day I talked with my
brother about Community because he
really loves community and I said I
don't know I like Community but I don't
like how
the later seasons
I don't like them they I don't know I
really think I said to him like he said
oh no I can't understand but I still
liked later Seasons too but I understand
what you're saying but I said
I said
community
to me fell off worse than Game of
Thrones in the end
what do you think about that
it did
and my brother was like
no
that's a hot tank I'm not sure about
that think about it think about it
no that is a tick that's what I start
saying it's a full clip
that's a full season wow wow wow wow wow
wow you guys are shocked oh
oh two two balls
okay wow it was too bold
I was too bold
hello
are we back
I think that was a sign to stop my hot
takes
and just do some hot bakes of bread and
yeah open a bakery kfb
Piada fried Bakery
how to take perms revoked unfortunately
[Music]
oh man
yeah I'm already baking bread with mine
with my squishy mat Bad Boys
[Music]
let her bake her let's bake are you okay
game eight nine one ten one zero
[Music]
almost had it
I am at work
okay you tried bake her let's make
glitter
[Music]
let her be baked
um
make her let sorry now we're making fun
of him let's not make fun of him now I
feel bad like I don't feel what's up
come on
[Music]
oh
okay Miku that sounds like a like an
advertisement channel that was selling
some shitty tools that you don't need in
life but they're telling you you need it
absolutely
[Music]
time to change bgm
I need to read super chatos
oh that's really loud sorry
so we so we
we
oh yeah
foreign
[Music]
that one had to be let out
I am
slay the spider I don't need to read
right but pass part two and from today
right
[Music]
wow Raptor
I made a quick egg
[Music]
yes
oh thank you
I've been
attacked
[Music]
foreign
uh
what's up
[Music]
now yeah I read the super jets from
players but I know no I know
copy pickles
[Music]
foreign oh
oh that sounded like her
[Music]
eh notice I was saying she's collab can
I just say one thing apparently on
stream you know somebody asked her like
in her stream chat people will spam
questions because she picks up on it and
then somebody apparently phrased the
question will you collab with Kiana on
Saturday and she answered yes you will
but that's like she would say yes to
anything guys that was not like planned
or so she you could have asked will you
collab with Yago on Saturday and she
would have said yes or no she could have
said to no no to my opinion as well it
was just so funny to me though because
then she also said ah more info on
Twitter tomorrow and then there was no
info on Twitter tomorrow and I saw you
guys so you were like oh I guess it's
not true because she didn't give any
info on Twitter tomorrow
um
and then and then I announced the fridge
thingy just to collect some pictures and
I didn't say anything about Nero yet and
that threw you guys off completely then
you were like oh I see that means it
really can't be her
collabing
yeah but it was so funny to me that she
would say that I was like what the
yo what the Nero don't don't leak
our collab new round
[Laughter]
yeah well she did she kind of dead but
she couldn't help it
she was she was being set up
you could ask her anything I never saw
my are you are you are you applying to
be president of the United States of
America
in the future are you running for a
president she would say yes please vote
for me
[Music]
filtered
excuse me don't Don't do something so
stupid
you're saying that now but that's so
that would be absolutely insane
[Music]
I already said she will
most likely not being reading chat at
all she will be listening to what I say
to focus on the collab and she will
react what I say and then react to
what's on the pictures
[Music]
foreign
it's gonna roast you isn't it she's
probably gonna be a little bit mean to
me but that's okay I forgive her already
[Laughter]
we'll see once what she's gonna say to
me
[Music]
straight into my face she even has the
courage nah she probably does
she will she'll be mean
and I will take it I'll enjoy it
[Music]
um
thank you guys for listening to do you
some kfp definitely not all funny thanks
for the pinky this is my first super
chat but it wasn't terrible I got
punched by a total stranger for no
reason
what I'm fine it's all right don't worry
about me what happened oh and then L
follows up suspiciously very suspicious
no not suspicious at all
with a pinky hurray
poison I feel good and proud don't mind
me so boss how's your day
you could ow
I get you points sorry for a couple
reasons number one yesterday is a
reference to your outfit
uh is cat I reverse the dogs
why I know you're working really hard
sometimes doesn't take enough rest same
goes for all kfp
free this is important remember one of
my super chat I say my English was bad
yes it's okay I remember you understand
what you speak when my English writing
and reading is terrible so when you're
waiting for my response I can't respond
to you
I'm better tap into oh don't worry
I'm here to make a person every Carefree
love oh you definitely do
I'm always like wondering what's your
what your goal is
you trying to do here but it's very
funny
thank you Al and why the hell did you
punch the other one huh
[Music]
and you always come up with the most
random things to recommend to me
but as long as you don't feel sad by me
turning them down then
you can continue and we're gonna be just
fine
don't be don't be sad
please
[Music]
thank you tons of tons of ton joke
yeah I guess he maybe he was watching
Dana and got inspired by the tonjok
tonjok and just had to tonjok somebody
thank you for the Super Chat owl thank
you soon and your English is pretty good
so don't worry about it yeah
very good we can communicate I
understand
Return of the King is returning to
theaters for one night tomorrow for the
25th anniversary the fact you took to
off tomorrow so I can clear my schedule
is an amazing coincidence or you planned
it no yeah
I don't know even if it returned to the
theaters here in Austria
I would have I should have watched it if
it was
[Music]
interesting thank you Maybelline thank
you Andrea Schmidt such a German name
the game of great dankisha and Jacob
Danke Schoen
[Music]
wait I can't read this
copy
[Music]
and paste
thank you thank you soon iron for the
pinky for the album oh
for three years of content a great
content it helped me get through a lot
of stuff I probably wouldn't be watching
whole life without you anymore by now
happy since six months
to the thing we don't talk about
wait stop what what six months debut you
believe
[Music]
to the thing we don't talk about
the thing we don't talk about is
graduation or what
[Music]
the German Channel I feel like it's been
longer than six months
oh
it's only been six months
the g words
ah
six months I thought I had that one up
earlier yeah
[Music]
oh damn why German guava no make six
months anniversary stream huh
let's let's get her to do that okay
soonish hopefully
I totally missed out on that
um
oh well thank you for reminding me Aaron
Vader and for keeping track of that
no idea
I just saw system and my feeders dude go
figure wow
oh
[Music]
did you like it it was very sad right
but I like I love the
chair and the cat
Aloha cat is also a little but it's
also funny and cute
[Music]
why has it so happened to be that Sarah
Gutenberg is now apparently the owner of
my German Channel
that makes no sense
[Music]
oh I went back to that one
Rock tea thank you thank you
[Music]
thank you
what
oh
what can confirm my HOA has penalized me
for not having fresh wood chips in my
flower bed they saw a roughly 6 times 6
inch of bare dirt
and find me hundreds
I'm assuming that's a small area right
I know how much that is but wow
[Music]
so be careful guys when you ever buy a
house
if you ever
do not get one with an HOA although
that's a very yeah already a rare thing
apparently
oh okay 15 centimeters that's pretty big
I will find you hundreds as well
nah I mean it is pretty big but still
like what the hell like what who the
gives a
so unnecessary
[Music]
that is so unnecessary
oh
[Music]
yeah
I've kind of fond of giving up my idea
of
eventually buying a house too
and now going more into buying in the
apartment
but in the end when comparing prices
kind of ends up the same anyway
yeah I don't know I don't know I can't
make decisions like that
in Lane cost yeah it's just because I
barely found any
anything like that
oh like really right at the scene at the
end a lake or so it's like
barely exists
and the ones that do exist are a bit
crazy pricing
[Music]
um
yeah I guess I should stop
dreaming about it I mean I would have
been fine with finding something nearer
a lake I don't know I'm not
I Wanna Know what no one want
I don't know what I want
I don't know
no building no no that is just like a
nightmare from what I've heard
if you start building something
everything will go wrong everything will
be more expensive than you thought
everything will take longer than you
thought everything will just be
all right it's just a nightmare
I found like one
maybe fitting
little house
uh at a lake
that would
maybe be an option
not new
not even renovated but
I don't know
small and cute
oh
no I was considering that but it's like
in the middle of nowhere so
that's fine too because I said I will
get myself a license
so that's that's like one that I was
maybe considering well
but in the end I also I don't know I
don't have the courage to really go for
it you know
[Music]
My Little Dream House
oh
[Music]
um
yeah no need to rush I guess but no kind
of need to rush because my bro told me
that
this year is
um good for buying property because
this year it's a bit cheaper
than like one or two years ago
in Austria like
and then possibly next year is getting
higher again
no but I saw like I saw uh you know
a thingy
thingy
so better to buy or start buying in
rates this year then wait forever yeah
it seems to be a good time to buy
um
[Music]
that wasn't my brother no
I don't think so
[Music]
um
it's been getting worse every year in
the UK really but UK has so many like
magical abandoned castles that you can
buy
in the castles but like Mansions right
in the middle of nowhere
to get one of those
that are not even that expensive yeah
in in in in I think in France maybe as
well
not sure but anyway
where was I
menu yet I think at this point
everything else would be a huge missed
opportunity also wow a kid especially
when she says
[Music]
um
maybe we can have some kind of dessert
like a croissant parfait
puppet puffy with ice cream like filling
with ice cream
and like some fruit and chocolate sauce
topping
I think that would work really well
actually
foreign
you know people people put like all
kinds of things in buffets in Japan they
put like brownies in there and stuff
hmm
and it works you just throw in whatever
it just looks and tastes yummy
hold up let her bake
bake curlette
little little little pieces of brownies
yeah like little cut pieces of brownies
hmm
they put ice cream and Waffle yeah
sounds delicious yeah let's think of a
croissant dessert puppet yeah
thanks for the pinky tend to have a
random question for you can someone be
both cute and hot ah I read this before
at the same time or do they have to be
one or the other this is based on
appearances not on personality and yes
the answer was yes and the example was
me thank you
foreign
[Music]
but for me I would pay for those to have
them on my wall 650 each would be a
steal damn
[Music]
thank you
that's very sweet
but who is I don't understand there's
like three oh she's there portraits of
your Oshi and your Oshi drawn by your
Oshi so I am an OC that you have
but also other horses
who are they are you here
you're here
and me
really
well that's girls talk
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa you must be so
happy about girls talk
foreign
[Music]
good for you that's my all-time favorite
stream
Isn't it nice when something like that
happens hmm
thank you very much for the sweet sweet
message thank you I'm very honored that
you like my art I sold Amelia by the way
for like 200
[Music]
yeah yeah I think it was no wait 2 000
or 200.
[Music]
but I thought it was plenty I turned
some down and then I was like um
now wait I think it was 1900 or
something like that no no it was two
thousand no it's two thousand a little
bit
2000 something under 2100 though I was
like okay it won't get any higher than
this I think because
I probably in order to get anything
higher than that
would probably need like a good
um reputation in the game and I'm still
early in the game I think later they'll
like Pro game it throw money at you
[Music]
surprise doll
I spent so much time on that yeah I
think I spent like 50 minutes or so on
it
and I think the game knows that
um
but but
easily just make money much easier in
the game by just doing a lot of abstract
paintings and selling them to punks and
don't spend that much money with that
much time with the paintings either
still make plenty money with it
but you know
I I won't cheat the game like that I am
an artist
oh sure thank you thank you
I didn't find I was trying to look it up
for pasta too but I didn't find anything
in particular and I found for for the
first game that like you know if you
spend minimum uh five or ten minutes
then this and that and businessman like
this and that like this kind of art
punks like abstract art
yeah and older guys the George and so on
they like our Twitter so I gotta know
something not abstract like a plant or a
face or so they can recognize that
um but that's in Prosper 2-1 who knows
if that changed in past part 2 but it
seems like it like the abstract painting
I did the punks were like jumping at it
so no
but the Amelia one everybody was
offering good money for it even the
punks were offering decent money for it
um
[Music]
so I still don't know the game is maybe
still too new to have like really
good information out there well yeah
it's Amen
yeah I put so much work into that and I
feel like
some parts looks better as a sketch this
is the problem as an artist I think many
artists have this problem they like
their sketches more than the finished
piece of art it's like uh the struggle
[Music]
but I wanted to draw something that
wasn't just like straight face or so I
wanted something with a pose or so so I
drew I'm holding froggy wow
hey
and I tried using some of the new tools
I was using like watercolor
and for the oh the face blush you know
watercolor the problem with the
watercolor brush because I bought it off
screen you guys don't even haven't even
seen it in action I think
but the problem with it is you can't
control where it goes really well
um you may get a certain size and then
within that right radius it will
sprinkle it randomly
but even the smallest size you can make
it is pretty big so it will still not
have much control over where it goes
it like for example
like if you press it
you put it down if you press it for like
five seconds but you stay in the same
spot basically it will sprinkle it like
everywhere within that radius like one
left one right one down there one up
here and so on you know what I mean
it's like sprinkling it like stamps it's
sprinkling watercolor
Stampy shapes hmm
yeah I I've learned to somewhat control
it as long as you don't use it for a
really small small tiny tiny tiny area
so I used it for the background and for
the blush over the face and that gave it
I think a good
good gradient
um yeah soft shading
yeah and then I have to say the sped up
version of the process because I spent
so much time it barely shows the details
of what I did yeah
[Music]
I worked real hard on that painting
had an authentic lucky plush right yeah
it's mixing colors too I was mixing
pinks and skin colors and all that
[Music]
the line work you did before the
coloring looked incredible thank you
glad you feel motivated to draw yeah
what's going on this has been fun with
us but I think the good thing is that
there is no time pressure
you don't have to pay rent so you can
just draw endlessly didn't didn't know
to them thank you and and happy birthday
congratulations
[Music]
yeah anyway where was I uh
love your boss out of nowhere thanks for
providing us all of a variety of fun
streams activities and toys I love
hearing about your adventures and I know
that there are many people homes
tombstone
and you have helped for difficult times
I am one of them so thanks again thank
you
I love you so much more than Han Solo I
don't even know why you have Han Solo as
your profile picture because you're not
like him at all
you're not you're not so annoying
too much
[Music]
you better than Han Solo
from him
[Music]
he's nothing like him at all right
you've been with Wawa for such a long
time thank you so much
thank you for being here
thank you soon I don't know where that
came from but it was very sweet
potatoes
thank you thank you Jim Tracy thank you
soon
thank you Jupiter the chicken
foreign
[Music]
we can grind money with abstract art
but I've been trying not to
um
not to you know progress too much in the
game but I did open up the area like
when you go up the stairs
where Emily was protecting it I opened
up that area by helping her for like one
picture
um
yeah up there there is much more
[Music]
there's so much more up there guys
pretty big
[Music]
let's play it again next week
yeah
[Music]
I am a team thank you thank you
that's what art student Tangier style is
so cute really impressive to pull that
off live on stream while talking and
reading chat be very challenged on so
many ways
I was I was trying my best to to not be
too quiet during it but I didn't have so
many tangents on that day yeah so next
time I want to try I haven't we can talk
you know about things when I have
tangents but
I'll keep open the question thingy
because you can have it running
with the normal chat on the side
apparently so I'll try that
[Music]
the focus to make those masterpieces
thank you you guys are too nice but my
style is really uh yeah
I'm gonna need to get practice but hey
is motivating me to practice maybe I can
finish a couple art
and make some new art as well
eventually
[Music]
apparently my style reminds people of
deviant art
[Music]
I mean I was using David or back in the
day when it was a thing
[Music]
I don't want I
was like it was funny but I don't want
to have old school art style yeah I
don't want to remind people of uh
deviantART with my art style
I wanna I know you guys don't mean it
like that like negative but I I want I
want I don't want that
I don't want my art to look outdated
[Music]
I want I want you to
make him
hmm
thank you retro I don't want No I don't
want
no
but thank you
I want to make no I want to make better
[Music]
no
I want to eat good I want to draw like
Inya or son no no no
man I love the way suno not Drew
she barely Drew but I love the way she
Drew
[Music]
so no no art so good
so good
[Music]
you know when she joined I was like oh I
wonder if she would be open
like you know to commission her
eventually for something now that she's
you know in homo and and I think I kind
of like hinted towards it to her but I
think she like generally because she
didn't even do many art streams
I think she generally just just wanted
to kind of you know
get away from it like not not do too
much with that because it's like maybe
stressful or whatever so I ended up
never never commissioning her
I lost my opportunity
[Music]
no I'm so sad so sad because I love her
art style
I'm being honest she's so good
now I lost my opportunity man
oh man
[Music]
yeah no
no no no no
no Eden
[Music]
not really
yeah yeah I mean you know you know I get
it I understand like
yeah it was she yeah I I can totally
understand
like not wanting to bring
This and like make it I don't know the
only thing she's known for also maybe
something like that
and then they all have everything be
about that because she has other
interests too and wanted to
you know just chill in her streams
have the streams be an outlet of her
other interests and hobbies
yeah
I'm just sad I missed my opportunity
but I understand
she's absolutely a ruthless in Pokemon
[Music]
yeah she was good in Pokemon
and copy
um
[Music]
anyway let's continue
and friends thanks for the words of a
chat okay well after one year of being
buggered and finally reborn as a mighty
Phoenix chicken thank you for all the
memories of these last three years you
really are amazing koala couldn't ask
for a better Oshi I'll keep cheering you
on all your stream projects and music
thank you what one year of being a
bucket you know I know you next chicken
here is whoa whoa show me your beauty
where are you fried squirrel
should I dare you off beautiful gorgeous
look at look at you turn around can I
see you from behind a little bit to me
can you do me a little bit of a twirl
turn oh gorgeous oh gorgeous or your
gorgeous little one oh no Striker pose
[Music]
thank you so much for the long-term
support I really really appreciate it I
hope you never get sick of me I'm really
glad I can be your orchini thank you so
much
oh I just hatched oh congratulations to
you too one day you'll be as big as
fried screw can you imagine
yeah thank you Francisco you're the best
donkey show
[Music]
you're truly the best is ever love you
forever
thank you too you guys were just too
nice to me man I think it's I mean I
know I'm not as good as good artists but
but I can draw more than just a stick
man so that's something and you guys
gave me some confidence thank you very
much
I'm sweet
[Music]
you
Put The Knife Down Put The Knife Down I
say
um
your bad habits are showing guys
chickens bad habits of threatening
people do not threaten me
oh
now suddenly all the knives are up weird
is it Opposite Day
okay put the knife up guys put the knife
up
show me the knives
threaten me
[Music]
what are you gonna do now huh
all right
[Music]
apparently it's not opposite day it's
not really getting better ah
[Music]
well something's not working how I
thought it would
okay Terror thank you soon and with that
uh done
what
the ice cream machine I've heard about
this legend of the ice cream machine
never working at least in America but I
think that's an America thing
interestingly because like in in Austria
I never had an issue when ordering ice
cream at McDonald's and I never hear of
it even though supposedly uh aren't we
using like the same machines because if
you work for McDonald's don't you have
to all like use the same machines like
if you make if you open the McDonald's
and I I watched this whole like
explanation video of why why it's always
broken I was watching that while I was
waiting in an airport hmm
the whole the whole video the whole
documentation like this dude found out
all the info
of why they're always broken
yeah who made that again
but it made so much sense
the reason the reasons basically
um
oh God do I remember it's something
about you know when you when like you
know they go to work
they start their shift they set up the
machine
and then
uh
I don't know eventually gets an error
and then they can't fix it they're not
allowed to fix it
um so they have to call someone to fix
it but McDonald's and the company that
you know fixes it are of course you know
involved big time
cult cult
um so uh in order for them to make more
money
they're like you know they try they're
charging a lot so it's very difficult
for the franchise owner to
hide to bring to call them
[Music]
um
but like even when they come and fix it
it only really lasts what for a day or
so but but but uh it's really not about
like fixing there's nothing really wrong
with the machine
I don't know I forgot already yeah the
profit comes from repairing it exactly
the reason it needs to be repaired is
because they don't actually tell you how
to operate it exactly yeah yeah and the
manuals the manuals they get are like
insane they're like
[Music]
200 million inches big
and yeah
yeah the shake machine yeah it's
scheduled to be cleaned that was it yeah
yeah if you don't it goes on automatic
shutdown mode and cleaning them takes
hours
if you do it right yeah yeah yeah
and they don't have time for that
and but then yeah it's just then always
broken it's not their fault the work is
not the like employee's fault so don't
be mad at them but then I wonder why
does that not happen in
yeah like European McDonald's or in
Japan in Japanese my daughter I've also
never seen like people having issue
ordering ice cream
why is it only in a name maybe there's a
different repairing company and I still
have to use the same the same devices
the same machines
but they probably don't have to use the
same repairing company uh
and they're trained better I suppose
yeah
but if you're interested it's really
interesting look up a video McDonald's
ice machine why always broken there's
like this is what I don't know one hour
long
investigation by a YouTuber it's really
interesting
hmm
I've seen four broken milkshake machines
in a warehouse once all from the same
store uh-huh
[Music]
been seeing pics of kvp basically taking
over entire Expos and conventions your
worldwide icon never stop being
thank you yes
kfp is making me very proud by
representing me so proudly I'm I'm quite
honored thank you guys so much I was
actually pretty worried about
you know out of my boss and I didn't
think so many kfp would go
but you did at least I guess this time
when they announced us there were still
tickets uh available I assume
so that was that was handy
you have a different model machine or EU
loss prevent the sort of canary
chicken
probably yeah
well
so if you want ice cream in America just
go to Baskin Robbins
why the does Indonesia have a
Baskin Robbins in Austria doesn't huh
not even Germany has one not even
Germany like that's the weird thing
I don't get it
I just don't get it
all right let's read switchats from
today
[Music]
rubs oh sure
oh yeah
foreign
[Music]
mm-hmm
do you want to see hello
she's dodging my kisses
oh
I can't sorry guys I can't hold her in
one place for too long
not against her will
[Music]
some nice Birds
good baby
thank you
such a happy kid no
oh you you you you you
know she's purring so loud but the
microphone isn't picking it up because I
have to turn down the sensitivity for it
but she's so soft
oh
oh you want to stay here do you want to
maybe stay here huh you can go behind
the tablet go behind the tablet
you're there
yeah
oh
she's making me so happy
why did you come so early
um
no she's behind the tablet screen
we're asking Mama
oh I turned the threshold completely off
thank you
now it's constantly pairing
I don't know if your hair is still
pretty quiet
let me turn it
at all
show here
it's looking away
hello where are you
where are you
oh she's so short who's yourself hello
hello
are you there I can't see you you're
behind my monitor hello
what are you doing
hi
oh I hear the the cat toilet turning
around in the other room
hey did you did you just go to the
toilet was that you
know is that why you said hello
you don't even stinky
you're not even stinky winky hi
no
oh yeah
let me turn it back
back okay
she's still there
but let's read them like quietly so she
doesn't run away immediately maybe we
have a chance to keep
it okay okay
she's sniffing she's sniffing Peppa
do you like the paper
what is that
okay
I'm squirreling I'm scrolling
oh what's under the paper
you'll find something under the paper
broken man thank you soon
foreign
oh oh yeah good massage
you you
okay
and this is the name what's pre part of
thank you soon
currently no no nothing right away
planned
thank you for checking in cheers
short my nine month old daughter your
bubble bubble Club big smile from her is
this another baby becoming one of us
can I teach her your name as well I
can't yeah you totally like even we all
call me Wawa so but that's like totally
suitable for a child to say to learn
[Laughter]
and again thank you uh Jacob 47 when you
go in your movie where you going are you
done here
thank you
and also Jacob I did that before
a whole life only
I think it might have been like remix
versions but I did it before I'll do it
again in the future someday
he also asked no said no and I okay but
that one I kept top secret generally
okay this movie is gone now
generally I'm I would I wouldn't lie
about niji Sanji collabs now because
they happened before and I I'll just
Talia what's up
but Nina wants to do something again
with the same group but it's just not
like happening right away I think
[Music]
I'm gonna miss movie she left
so sad
foreign
my tracking is so off today
I don't think she'll be gone for so long
though
a worms collab
yo
yeah but wait what's the maximum number
of people at camping worms maybe that
could be our big
um whoever wants to participate from
Hollow side with niji collab
what's the maximum number eight
four eight
okay but eight seems like a lot
maybe I'll try to get six or seven
together
actually let me ask right now
I wonder
hey yeah
[Music]
if there were anyone interested in doing
a warm School
[Music]
we're talking about the same
ah it's six in the recent games though
the one that I played back in a day
was that the same that you're thinking
of
I'm thinking six sounds fine to me
though I like six
um
like eight eight would be very chaotic I
think
oh
wmd is wmd the same as Armageddon
yeah that's the one I want to play again
[Music]
um
I mean mommy has done a collab with
selling before right
so Moonlight would probably be okay with
it right
I know I don't know maybe
Cali would probably be up for it
Bales maybe two
I I honestly don't know let's see
[Music]
huh
I'm in love's worms too
okay let's have that on my channel
big worms collab
oh
[Music]
sounds like fun okay nice
here you go here you have your big
collab
I'm planning it now I will force pomu to
participate because just because
but other than Pomo I would like to also
you know talk to some others who haven't
talked to or maybe oh I would I kind of
want a wee one in it too
because I talked to her before but I
haven't had a like a proper collab with
her
a wing wall
I want to invite everyone
[Music]
yeah
and then someone else maybe I'll leave
the The Last Choice
to whoever joins whoever they would like
to have in it
um
yeah I guess at that point I could just
do lots of light yeah but
oh I have Petra
I liked Petra a lot when we talked IRL
mmm
nothing but
um
I'll think about it
I I want to give whoever participates
from hollow hollow side a chance to
you know
you know you know
[Music]
would be crazy though yeah because it's
like both first gen of English
with two bars of the two big companies
right
oh but I I don't think that would ever
happen I don't know I honestly don't
know
um
don't get your hopes up at all
and first is yeah
I am it's a dream I think
[Music]
okay
I need to speak what I want
[Music]
um
I actually moved up I was just like a
couple days ago I asked
if I could change it and they said yeah
just tell us what you want and which one
we'll we'll get it like checked
um yeah currently it's an idol whose
dream is to become a fast food shop
owner
she's a phoenix not a chicken or turkey
she works extremely hard since she will
be reborn from ashes anyway yeah I also
wanted to change it but I'm not sure
like
we should also
make this a community you know what I
will make it right now
gotta do things right away otherwise I
forget and then I don't do it
hey Ya
send me
suggestions
of
a compact nice
sounding
nil
and accurate
[Music]
um
takanashi
Kiana bio description
keep it around the length of the
original one
I feel like we should at least include
that I am not like dreaming of becoming
a fast food shop owner anymore but I am
a fast food shop owner now
[Music]
the whole not a chicken thing is I think
unnecessary
[Music]
right
and yeah
we can we should mention the fact that
I'm a phoenix
successful manifestation yeah
I tell you make
only
okay
I will make it Members Only
and one again and change but will have
to check with management
[Music]
keep in mind that I am now indeed a fast
food
um franchise owner no
restaurant chain owner went French is
franchise owner does that imply that I'm
just like the boss of one store and not
the big boss of all of them
[Music]
because I am the boss of all of them
I want to say not cult leaders
feel and I am indeed a fast food
franchise CEO
[Music]
hey
okay I will look for them
a couple days later
ask new or summer oh yeah I wonder what
she would come up with but it's
basically just isn't that like I don't
know how does it work would she not just
say basically something like what jet
chat GPT would say
I like the awkward use alternative
that's ESL
[Music]
sounds grammatically correct to me
what
[Music]
foreign
mentioned me on stream she's streaming
right now apparently
God damn it
I'll never watch her live
[Music]
I'm gonna see
no it sounds like she's leaving but you
never know because like she will often
in the beginning of the stream say hi
I'm leaving now goodbye and then she
won't and she's she continues streaming
forever
it's just random
yes she always says she's leaving
today
bye
is she leaving on a jet plane
hopefully not
anyway okay back to Super chats
we will we will change your description
once I get like a good
good something going Cruise
[Music]
[Laughter]
became a Creed thank you soon
go go
go
don't let your dreams be dreams go go go
go it would be good for your body and
your older self will thank you for
working out go
dance
oh
hates
yeah I could play that eventually maybe
yeah boohoo 7-3 Junction
okay
foreign
[Music]
these
are you sure about that
are you not just
fishing for something
[Laughter]
hey this
oh man Elvis thanks for the rest of the
chat don't worry guys it's not about
wink heart heart heart I see someone who
watches near Usama huh at least I love
that you know you know what it's about
Elvis thank you for the rest of the chat
I appreciate it thank you soon
were you were you two two window Wing us
just now I wonder
[Music]
I don't know for me like it it was
really sudden
I don't know for how long Never Summer
has been streaming but like recently
the past one month I think
I started watching like some clips
silently and then they kept recommending
me more and I was like damn this is so
funny
this is so stupidly funny
oh okay
both
paid for this
I see well because I see I see what
you're going for
ah so stupid
oh anyway thank you Elvis
foreign
[Music]
would you be interested in playing a
path playing playing Pathfinder King
maker it's a crpg and has a kingdom
building mechanic that was popular and
it came out
Pathfinder King maker
[Music]
um
looks like
when scrolled out looks zoomed out looks
like
looks like AOE
but oh
interesting looks cool
well probably wouldn't stream it though
that's a little bit too long
it's supposed to be a cool game
oh
[Music]
the game is super complex oh it'll take
you years to finish what
what so you're saying it's longer than
Fire Emblem
oh no thank you then
okay
uh right so free donation
um
thank you thank you I'm glad you like my
cat Lee thank you
oh thank you that's very nice
duck off you are again thank you
yes you you have to wear orange at least
that's the minimum requirement if you
want to be true to yourself and you go
to a convention you have to wear orange
be true to yourself I'll see off kfb
thanks for the rest of the chat hey boss
I need a merchandise mug that says I
love my boss and a new one or I only
work for kfp I am here to spy
or something that stands equally do not
touch this mug because some basses keep
using my mug in my other workplace ah
I like that I only work for kfb I'm here
to spy well you can probably make it
yourself like there's truly like like
Services where you can design your own
mug if you really want it
I would be very happy if you made
yourself a mug that says that and then
put on the slap on the kfp logo if you
can
um
okay
sounds like a merch idea well there is a
whole talk mug yeah
if you got that one you can use that one
I don't think I'll release another mug
well well well
the mug problem I'll see good luck with
that I mean I really want you to make
that mug now
thank you so much
hope I hope it gets better
otherwise tell me
an ace kit 3619
um
Blake c137
what looking for the top Junction
gray victory
hmm
oh guys bye
guys but I guess a lot of you guys for
much longer than you thought if you were
in pre-chat that message about me taking
a nap
was 100 newer summer
[Music]
I was like oh this is actually kind of
realistic I would say that maybe
no really I just cut off one part
because actually it was a little bit
longer
[Music]
I was like oh
where's the
what do you want
[Music]
um
all right
[Music]
I took a nap after you said that that's
fine
it was I'm so tired today I think I'm
going to take a nap before my stream
anyone want to join me
and that's where I cut it off but it
continues unfortunately I can't sleep
with you in real life though and then an
emoji with a tongue out
foreign
[Music]
I thought that was too much
I actually joined you and took a nap man
what is this
I ended up taking like a like a little
half nap more or less I'm not sure if I
was really sleeping I attempted to
[Music]
uh
silly silly
[Music]
but see like damn AI is too strong
too bad too powerful thanks for the
membership thank you soon
thanks for the pinky
oh wait wait I completely I I just like
ignored gray Victory I restored the fact
it was your birthday happy birthday I'm
completely focused on the nap I'm so
sorry
happy birthday to you congratulations
yeah go eat some good food go out do
something still it's still an early
night more or less
um
or if it's too late today and do
something tomorrow go grab yourself a
cake please
[Music]
and celebrate yourself celebrate your
life
please
I'm jamming your shoes yeah
I'm very hungry actually now I'm getting
hungry too and I gotta cook something
[Music]
um Al thanks for the pinky oh my God
it's my time I hear you say you need
games
no that was Mira Wawa I can ignore all
of that
although these games sound interesting
because they're not so far off I think
oh
Dragon's Dogma dark or risen Horizon
[Music]
so it looks like a Skyrim game
and their lilies yeah I haven't either
played this one yeah yeah yeah not so
far off neptuna series I actually have
like a PlayStation collection I think of
that
shintari series I don't know
and then death Scamp it afterlife
was this
2D RPG action platformer um
oh I mean
the visuals are kind of cool
[Music]
well yeah they're kind of cool not bad
okay this purple haired chick
cute
what are her games about though
all everything is about what's what's
yeah
well what is this
[Music]
Platformers 2D Platformers oh
I mean these suggestions aren't so bad
Al
okay
not gonna play them though but they're
really not bad thank you
[Music]
look how how excited he is
man I feel kind of bad
do not play any of them
um
you'll get it eventually you'll Tickle
My Fancy
eventually
I I feel it already
[Music]
and Elvis with the pinky donkey show and
can I have something to say to you
something I've been holding back for a
long time from the bottom of my chest I
filtered
Elvis
I get you I have
I I can see through you you're
transparent to me
what's with the thumbnail is the
thumbnail weird
I feel like the thumbnail is
gonna be weirder after I change it
[Music]
What if I
have an idea
but I don't know if I'll do it for the
thumbnail I want to change it a little
bit at least
laughs
[Music]
Bruce Jenny lindank
thank you
they will take you away and experiment
with what you can do by human rights
that's just what I think though
yeah maybe no no it's really
gotta keep my magic powers a secret then
for safety
Skies
thanks for the pinky hi tencho first
your armor art was so good amazing work
second if you ever do charity stream
like you once suggested could Mass
Effect be a donation goal
this is part this part is a joke thank
you because I was just gonna say of
course not what the
bird for fellow game there's always the
one that Flair love Splatoon
no
um
nah nah
nah I don't want to play with the squid
kids no
[Music]
I'd rather play undertale
I think
downstairs
why did the chicken cross the road to
escape the inevitable looming end to be
on a cafe
paper plates
but no they wouldn't do that they want
that the harsh never-ending shift at The
Cafe restaurant with little to no pay
watching a kfpkin getting thrown into a
room never to be seen again freedom is
unsure
are you okay
what are you talking about Dallas star
why do you sound so unhappy
you should be highly satisfied
[Music]
what's going on are you malfunctioning
do I need to put you into the usual room
is that necessary
I will gladly do it I will use up all my
resources to fix you if need be it's
okay
we do it for the greater good I'll
gladly do it
[Music]
no not the usual room uh-huh uh-huh
does that mean you're okay what do you
like manipulated to say this by someone
[Music]
please know
okay hold on okay
I'm gonna assume you got manipulated for
to do that to say that it was an AI yeah
okay part of the joke right you were
just joking along with me surely that's
understandable and that makes sense
okay okay okay okay I I will I will
believe you
mm-hmm
I'm helping you out here delstar you
better take my hand
no I'm going to escape it's my fate huh
okay room one year
for now mine extended
[Music]
yep
[Applause]
there he goes
you want to see me do that again
um
[Music]
so be careful guys
be careful
be Kiara full
who was the second one well never know
we'll never know
thank you downstairs bye bye have fun in
the usual room
thank you Richard thank you
um
[Music]
Maple Leaf two 501 Junction for the
pinky I mean your Phoenix has lived from
Millennia don't you have a favor you can
ask of your old body
Otto from Bismarck to do some videos for
the German Channel just kidding just
kidding
he's I'm assuming he's dead so no
otherwise I would have already asked
like Mozart or so
am I gonna upload that clip will do will
do
soon
your typical mental donation mental
jelly Duncan
downstairs
[Music]
thank you
and that's that action
[Music]
wait
ah Mr sanctions
thank you oh wait that makes sense to
the early super chats
um
Maple Leaf
I'm done
my job here is done
um
sorry guys for bamboozling you today
uh
my delayed April Fool's joke was however
I success in my opinion
thank God I am not Ai and we can have
actual
conversations though and then tomorrow
we'll have some
some fun together with a new summer yes
[Music]
yeah yeah
now you guys the ones who are saying oh
it was obvious from the beginning you
guys are just liars because I was I was
looking at the chat and you guys weren't
like oh oh something's wrong I mean I
mean
[Music]
don't star are you trying to
say that I was wrong that I made a wrong
decision
and they're just coping
I admit I was Bamboozled there you go
thank you for being honest
with my videos
well I mean stuff like that I didn't
have to read it I was just like
purposefully at that point I was
purposefully saying
the weird things that it was throwing at
me thanks guys Christopher thank you
Rick been dankish and heart heart heart
heart heart heart indeed
okay
I was acting weird early on no that is
true but you know just another day at
kfp sometimes Chihuahua a little bit
weird
the burning sensation
I thought you were putting on a bit but
I knew you were being weird and not
yourself
sure sure sure
[Laughter]
that's really wondering what you were up
to thought you were going to be like
well guys General moved companies I'm
going after her no
you played it off great at the beginning
then you started laughing half
everywhere yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I know I know that's when I also I just
couldn't take myself seriously anymore
um
there's a there's a video and neuro
Clipper in the chat oh
am I gonna get clipped by you
[Music]
today I was technically neurosama
technically it was her today
what you still want to know if I wore
braces I never wore braces no
no no
[Music]
it has a spot on Peter lap I wasn't even
trying
Tyler km thank you soon thank you
Bastion oh isn't that wait what was that
like again
[Music]
hey a Bastion uh yeah yeah I like this
one
hmm
I like the visuals hmm
I could see myself play that sometime
[Music]
okay I'll go now guys
good night everybody and in German we
say videos in
see you tomorrow
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye I want to
see you all there tomorrow okay
you better be there
or you're not gonna be square you're
gonna be in the usual room basically so
you know what to do
you know what to do nothing
[Music]
thank you very much
for watching
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]