[Music]
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
all here
so please be kind thank you
[Applause]
but in fact
just a human no duck
i am a duck please nice to meet you
[Music]
uh
yeah second up is me i i am the
first real real bird actually in the
whole life uh hold on
[Music]
[Applause]
not chicken phoenix
look it look at my guarding phone
picture it looks like a phoenix
[Music]
indonesia generation
i am peafowl not turkey
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
and after that mummy joined mummy please
introduce yourself
hello i'm nanashi mummy from the second
generation of hello life english
i am an owl not a towel
[Laughter]
[Music]
i saw the clip
yeah
never happened i'm not a towel
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
new member nice to meet you
[Applause]
[Music]
exactly really cool
okay
beautiful
[Laughter]
so guys
today we are here with these horotoni
members and by the way if if you have
not seen it
i requested for this sake
hello
[Music]
yeah thank you for putting it on the
screen i got it because i've just felt
like ah we were such a cute lovely group
we need something to connect one another
[Music]
this logo is so cute thank you
the steps on the bottom so cute right
yeah it's so cute
i also think so um
japanese
members are actually pretty good at
english so
yeah it will probably be no problem
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'm thinking positive positive things
i think we should start with normal
normal mode but we can try other modes
too later maybe okay okay
and just a reminder uh the prompts
please write in english
[Music]
okay
whatever let's just go with the basics
[Applause]
[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
up
is
[Music]
there
okay okay okay okay
breathe
[Music]
and
dancing
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
mummy
this is
and
[Music]
this
is
[Music]
this is
kiara
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
oh
spicy
[Music]
foreign
remember
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank
[Music]
that's okay that's no problem um let's
look at it together
okay
let's go we start let's go
this is my child's fault okay here it is
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm saving i saved it let's go you gave
me the next one from molina
sorry i forget the word
[Applause]
actually um before before the stream
started uh me and elena told uh
subarusemba and the others that we're
going to the maldives yeah yeah yeah
yeah
and they were very excited to join so
what are samples i want to come too
right
[Music]
[Laughter]
everybody is uh there even though the
one that subado drew one is missing so
good job
you added me again
[Music]
you guys all know the mermaid loading
icon the membership
yay
[Laughter]
it came to the right
mama
um
[Music]
i do it too fast
okay
[Music]
um
okay
next
[Music]
i want to see
[Laughter]
[Music]
everybody
will
eat duck
oh my god
nah what nothing ah
everybody everybody
everybody
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh
stop
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
ando
[Applause]
[Laughter]
so difficult to write yeah yeah
so many people use horotoni so i always
have to draw draw five people
[Music]
oh
nice
[Applause]
[Music]
so cute
[Applause]
[Laughter]
ah
oh
[Applause]
this is r18 we need to censor the stream
yo i was gonna say if i didn't be
demonetized
everybody will
[Music]
eat it
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice interpretation moment nice nice
nice
it is a bird eat bird world yeah yeah
pac-man in a way
[Laughter]
oh
i love that that looks so good
[Music]
sorry
i i like
[Music]
yeah a good misunderstanding nice yeah
nice and nice
the rounds are so short because we are
so short
should we
play a different round a different mode
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
look
uh
[Music]
let's
no
[Music]
foreign
a
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
it
foreign
[Music]
is
foreign
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
so
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah
okay
[Music]
m
[Laughter]
[Music]
got
oh my god
let's take a look at
what what it's turned out to be
thank you marshall
i was not sure what to draw um
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
was subaru senpai's interpretation
that's not right on everything
[Music]
is
beautiful
[Music]
it just looks like i'm sexually
harassing someone yeah
[Music]
why did you make them sweat
because the asmr was just too much to
handle
[Music]
you need to put that up on the on my fan
art hashtag it's one thing yes oh yes
it was from that prop my my previous
prom
i'll save that one that one is precious
beautiful all right
[Music]
um
you missed something important i'm sorry
you may have left early
sorry sorry
yes she had something to do but besides
that
mostly
this is this is abstract art
abstract right here
you look at it and you think what do you
what do you see
yeah depending on what you see you can
learn someone's personality hmm
[Music]
arizona
[Laughter]
style but no way she can do that with a
mouse
[Laughter]
oh
is that a cherry tomato or a strawberry
moment i was going for it i was going
for strawberry
[Music]
think about what you want to draw nani
or kakakov
okay
um
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
what idea um i can't tell you yet oh are
we doing nothing
or what yeah that's the knockout again
one more round okay it's very small
um
and now we can try animation animation
animation ready
huh
[Music]
okay okay
okay
[Music]
um
m
[Music]
foreign
hahaha
[Music]
foreign
euro
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
cool
my
[Music]
foreign
that
[Music]
memorize the drawing you are gonna
the policy
deputy
so
[Music]
okay
it
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
ah
[Music]
dang it
uh
okay
[Music]
m
oh
[Music]
okay let's take a look stacking with
mine oh
[Applause]
[Laughter]
apparently in order to be a bird you
have to know the abc oh yeah do we all
know
maybe someone can recreate this and make
it into a proper fan art i want to see
it
[Music]
see
yes
[Music]
three people
i think we turned into survivor senpai
because of black hair
yeah
um
[Music]
i can do an art stream where i just uh
ship all the hollow birds
scenarios let's go
let's go
ellen that's not been used enough make
use of it
yes
[Music]
face scary face
when i panic
just panic right
yeah
you want to portray yourself in a cute
way but no you're the one who portrays
yourself in a terrifying way the most
yes
[Music]
same same thing yeah
yeah
what the heck
[Laughter]
destiny destiny
is
[Laughter]
simple art um with even less time i drew
a bit more complicated
and i added the earring
oh yeah
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
oh yeah
hey
[Music]
okay
okay what is
oh
it's like a dating app
do you want to try animation
[Music]
no different
okay
[Music]
animation
anime
[Music]
ah
yeah penrite
waving
panel light
chiara
eyewriting
on
oh
[Music]
there
me
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
it
the cocoa
[Music]
foreign
there
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
a
know
[Music]
ah
that
foreign
[Music]
ah
foreign
[Music]
yes
foreign
[Music]
peace
m
[Music]
be
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
sara
sarato
fukto
[Music]
be
what
[Music]
hello interesting things going on
[Applause]
what's going on why is everyone drawing
such sensitive scenes huh
which one are we talking about what are
we talking about
several
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
i think i think it's enough it's a lot
it's
like
okay take a look um
they were so happy did you get my idea
oh yeah
cute stuff oh you guys added
is there who's who's doing it who's
oh my god
so scary yeah
why so angry
situations
[Music]
originally was i i was um working at kfp
and then music was playing so i wanted
to start dancing dancing
okay
i thought it was someone else
[Laughter]
[Applause]
this looks great in animation
nice nice animation
like i got closer too
yeah and the in the end it turned into a
little snake
yeah yeah yeah
that's cute that's amazing
and it's like what
what what is that
it's not i mean it's originally supposed
to be me yeah yeah yeah yeah puppy and
puppy i added the eye color
happy end happy
okay
[Laughter]
oh
last three yeah very important reina
thank you for that
you're welcome
oh
my gosh
thanks
[Music]
is that
who is that in the back though i do i
think
oh i made it
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
we all understood what was happening
this is the best animation cycle
so sweet
[Laughter]
[Music]
i want to try
uh
wait uh do we still have oh do we still
have time can we do one more animation
one more yeah last year okay
[Music]
eat a lot eat a lot
you're
right i'm hungry
i'm hungry hurry hungry
maybe afterwards you can have breakfast
mommy are you gonna go back to sleep
i'll do both or i'll just eat more of
you guys
okay
i'll give you some substitutes from kfp
okay okay
eat kfp
okay
okay let's go
let's go
anime
yoga
[Music]
oh
m
[Music]
cooking
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
cooking
[Music]
best swimsuits girl
i think
i think kiara
but
i
in fact i really want to see
mummy
[Music]
mum
you may
[Music]
friend
chiara
[Music]
walking
up kiara coming
[Music]
up
foreign
[Music]
it
m
[Music]
foreign
hey
[Music]
i think this is
see
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
hello
[Laughter]
there
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
all right
last round let's see what masterpieces
we have created
yes please
okay
shopping for swimsuit
yeah oh uh-huh
where will this go
okay okay what what
turned into person
you turned into further
wow
i don't know after eating after eating
the bikini top she becomes a
person on the ground
[Music]
[Applause]
dana try on some cute swimsuits but okay
this is
fine animation for
[Laughter]
[Music]
what situation is this
um
[Applause]
leave it to me
to read your mind
animation too good job
[Music]
i'm cooking
i thought it was a mirror
[Laughter]
[Music]
pushes away dana and wants the food for
herself
who's trying to get me to eat something
suspicious
no i i teleport i can't eat
parts
yeah
this theme looks really nice though the
way it goes up
it was supposed to be a single hair but
it's not how it ended up
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
have telephone
yeah why i have terrible
because
um
food please
[Music]
[Laughter]
surprise it's me wow
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
it's tough out there that's why no we
have to we have to
be strong together
[Music]
is me because i am a phoenix and and i
will revive no matter what
uh-huh
[Music]
that's a different story i cannot say
that
but you know because the bird eat bird
world you know what we should collab
someday me not the koran
super smash brothers
i want to punch punch birds oh
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Laughter]
did you play super smash brothers before
i have but i'm not good at it oh we're
all kind of damn bad that's good because
we're so bad
and somebody will never play before
we'll be um together but
yeah smash each other so it's okay
see that in a different meaning too no
we're talking about what i don't know
what that what are we talking i don't
know
they're playing together yeah okay
smash
[Music]
oh
we're the biggest
group of something i think in hong kong
really yeah
um
maybe maybe we can do more stuff
together but getting all of us together
for this collab was already very
difficult
to
[Applause]
looking forward to a collaboration again
yes yes yes thank you thank you
everybody for participating
thank you for inviting me
thank you
you learned some good japanese there and
i said yeah
thank you
i like that so close to fluent now yes
you're getting closer you're getting
there fight though it's like you're
close you're fighting fine
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's simple enough i think we can
remember that our ending greeting will
be otsu
okay
everybody thank you for watching today
and in holo today we say
three
two
one
[Applause]
[Music]