[Music]
[Applause]
no no no no no no
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
no no no
no
no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
okay
[Music]
sorry for the weight
uh good morning
[Music]
let me open chat I mean I already seen
you guys but one second
oh
okay
[Music]
um
oh chat
chat
[Music]
why is video capture not showing
um
[Music]
ah
ah q a
H I thank you thank you Titi yeah I can
do the Q a thing but what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
give me a moment please
ah this movie was so kind to
let me sleep
like really long
oh sure
oh
without interrupting me
and I took advantage of that more or
less
there you go
yeah so I basically I woke up and I I
ate breakfast and that's it
oh yeah she stopped waking me up at like
8 A.M or so quite a while ago
oh sure
but I mean she still
like you know gets a bit annoying here
and there
uh before noon
um
if she I mean it's mostly like she sees
me awake
in the bed
and just checking my phone and then she
gets really really
uh impatient
she's like
I'm awake just give me food [\h__\h]
you made a 12 hour sit down to finish
the game oh did you do it so you could
uh you would not get spoiled by the
Stream
yeah if you're awake why not fool what
the hell
[Music]
but understandable do you have some
snacks I have one kiwi
and uh some chocolate but sadly nothing
savory
I wonder if if there would be something
if I wanted something
do I have something hmm
I think I might have nothing saved
savory
we
a Chihuahua with a kiwi kiwi
okay I apparently forgot to tweaks I
mean I didn't I just uh
starting
come and hang with us the cool chicks
thank you
um yeah I wonder how long we're going to
stream today
um
but we are going to finish
I mean worst case if I you know get
really really hungry I do have you know
leftovers from yesterday in the fridge
like a proper dinner
and oh I don't know we could we could we
could order food
no no no
um yeah leftovers oh my God that's salad
hello fresh quite often makes me do this
salad dressing with like
um one little you know package uh as if
you like getting it from like a fast
food place little package of uh honey
and a little package of uh mustard but
like the the corny okay that is very
German way of saying it foreign
[Music]
in English
the little
um yeah like a c CD
CD uh mustard type mm-hmm
yeah not not so much sweet but not too
spicy
a good well-rounded mustard yeah yeah uh
and then you know just at home you
should have like a little bit of olive
oil and a little bit of some kind of uh
uh ethic what's ethic again
what's ethic
vinegar oh yeah okay so basically
basically if you want to make the salad
that I made which was so good please
trust me it's a really good dressing you
need a little bit like maybe
maybe
[Music]
um
one or one or two big spoons of honey
and mustard
depending on how much dressing you want
and one big spoon of olive oil and one
big spoon of uh a vinegar choice of your
vinegar your choice of vinegar
and I actually I mixed a little bit a
small tiny bit of water in there too
because I thought
and also a little bit of pepper and a
little bit of salt
but wow wow wow wow it's amazing
it's amazing
and in terms of honey it would be a good
uh
yeah honey and mustard not honey mustard
it would be good I think if you use some
kind of like sweet not not the like
strong dark mustard no get the the
bright flowering not mustard of the
bright flowery honey yeah and for
mustard like something seedy something
strong uh
but not too spicy
okay okay and then use this dressing on
just a leaf leafy salad maybe add
optionally add some cucumbers and
tomatoes or whatever it's a good good
very good easy to make uh dressing that
I do a lot thanks to hellofresh
mm-hmm
and what dumb
what was it called what did I put on the
meat
in in Germany it was estrogon I was like
hey isn't that like what they put in in
mustard because we have some mustard
that's called estragonsenf yeah tarragon
tarragon tarragon butter since tarragon
sounds like well uh Lord of the Rings
character
hmm
I don't care about sponsorship [\h__\h] the
sponsorship at this point man they're
never gonna do it
maybe I'm overqualified for them
yeah but so basically
uh they gave like little little butter
chunks but herbal herbal butter chunks
you know like garlic butter but no
herbal herbal butter
and so I had to like soften them a
little bit
I did that in the microwave because I
was impatient and I had to be fast
and then and then mix it with like fresh
cut uh tarragon that's the first time
I've ever like seen and touched tarragon
hmm
and I was like oh my what the hell this
was gonna taste
but yeah uh
I mixed it up and then at the end I put
it on top of the the meat and you guys
saw it on the picture before it melted
but like quickly after the picture it
like you know melted and dissolved and
basically you saw this like little
transparent sauce over the meat with
like a ton of a ton of tarragon and I
thought oh maybe that's too much
tarragon but no that was the right
amount it was so good wow wow this was
so easy to make but like the tarragon
changed it up crazily
um
was amazing I think I might make it more
often normally normally I don't cook
much with pork but the Little Pork
fillet
with the tarragon herb butter oh my God
butter
but I'll show it for people who haven't
seen it on Twitter
you know
so salad dressing you can even see the
seeds of the mustard a little bit
um
now actually
hello fresh makes me do potato wedges a
lot
but uh this time I [\h__\h] up a little
bit
um uh I I preheated the oven and then
eventually I put in the potatoes you
know just just the olive oil no not I
didn't even use olive oil for them some
other oil salt pepper and then they give
you spice for the potatoes there's
usually two different ones that they
either one of them they sent to you and
and yeah I'm throwing that all on there
and then oh I actually use the
Australian salt again
then I throw it in and then uh it says
okay 25 minutes so I I put on the timer
of 25 minutes and then it was done and I
look inside the oven and I'm like
that doesn't look done
what but it's been 25 minutes
[Music]
so it turns out
um
I had uh normally I always have it on
200 degrees but apparently not this time
I had it like at 50. so I was like [\h__\h]
but now my meat and my salad is done and
but my potato wedges aren't done what
the [\h__\h]
yeah so I tried my best I turned it all
the way up to 300.
and and uh partially turned out on the
the whatever what is it the roasting
from the top option auction option the
grilling option or whatever
for a while yeah and still acrylic Me
Softly still it took so long
but eventually it was finished so that's
why they look a little bit brighter than
uh usual but honestly they were totally
fine they were really yummy oh oh oh oh
can I say one more thing
or ask you guys
when you guys do something with potatoes
potatoes and you don't you decide to do
something with them that doesn't require
peeling their skin
and so you wash them
do you wash them just with your hand
or do you use a tool to help you washing
them
yes I saw the reply for mume and I
replied several times back but Twitter
kept on crashing on me every time I
replied
hand have a scrub hand hand I use a
brush yeah yo yo yo yo yo so normally I
always use my hands until now and I
thought I guess they could could be
cleaner but like whatever and then this
time these were like I don't know they
had some special dirt on them that was
not really I couldn't really get get it
down with my hands
so I was like um wait I have I have a
fresh sponge that I haven't used yet
let me try this and oh my God
that's
like night and day difference
they suddenly looked so squeaky clean
and I'm like just wondering how much
dirt I have been eating through my
potato wedges until now
yeah it's crazy
it makes it so much more clean yeah the
abrasive side yeah yeah
imagine a brush removes root nutrients
from the skin
brush oh yeah yeah I use like a sponge
but I don't know the skin was still 100
there I've I just removed all the dirt
that was you know not usable not
removable with my hands
um
the soil gave it a special flavor so
Dirt has vitamin D for dirt
you were training your immunity system
like a true warrior
yeah I mean they never tasted bad before
but
yeah now I feel like I will always clean
them with a sponge I will now have a
potato sponge only because I didn't want
to use the other sponges but
yeah so potato sponge
is a thing now in my kitchen maybe I can
use the potato sponge also for other
things I don't know what I would use it
for
but
yeah sponge good to know right like you
will be surprised how how much it will
change it when they're when the potatoes
are really dirty
the potatoes they look covered in dirt
when they come from hellofresh
yeah yeah no dishwasher sponge yeah
um
yeah dedicated potato sponge
why your tomatoes look great ew what do
you mean great ew what
how do you Dice Tomatoes by the way
because they said Dyson but like when I
tried that before all the yummy insides
they just fall out and they're all over
and then
so I just sliced them this time
green
what's their normal my they're normal
a really sharp knife oh I think I
haven't sharpened my knives in years
and I've been using them
yeah for a while how long have I been
using them
have I used those knives when I was of
rmt probably not yeah okay so maybe
two
how long have I been back from Japan
[Music]
two and a half years or so
two and a half years I haven't sharpened
them probably
um
a little over two years okay I don't
know I I have free like free knives
today
use mostly and a bread knife but that
wouldn't count I would say because I
don't use a bread knife or anything but
bread
and yeah I I do notice
um they're not so sharp anymore
blunt knives are a lot dangerous really
time to study blade I don't know how to
sharpen them I guess you could get like
a sharp and everything I don't mind
okay I think yeah because they have cute
colors they're pastel colored
um
oh okay one second let me do
I mean if I start the the question round
you guys still see the other chat right
you can choose at the top between the
top chat the live chat and the question
thingy I think I could do that at least
what oh ceramic
um
ask
[Music]
ing
it hit
yeah wait wait wait now
people people there it is
[Music]
your favorite color
when well use this question
ceramic okay okay okay okay okay chill
chill
uh no I didn't cancel my audible
subscription yet God damn it I also I
think I have other subscriptions too
that I don't use like Duolingo for
[\h__\h] sake I mean now that I study
Korean it would be more useful probably
um
oh my God okay stop don't send so many
questions keep them for yourself for a
while let's go back to the normal chat
okay
go back go back go back okay
so whenever I feel like uh I want to
talk about we're gonna look over there
but I also have my phone with some
tangents
whoosh
and why do we have yeah four times where
I'm like I don't know anyway this was so
easy to make and and it's so yummy like
yo what actually surprisingly one of my
favorite uh dishes from hellofresh and I
have like a holy [\h__\h] the the amount of
recipes I've accumulated I can make like
five books with them
they're huge
no that is not that's not chicken and
that is not creamed spinach we just
talked about it it's a pork fillet I
posted it on Twitter with uh topped with
fresh tarragon butter that are created
alongside potato wedges and a crunchy
salad with mustard honey dressing
tarragon so good
don't they post them on the website oh
and like
I don't know if you if you uh I think
you have to have like a subscription to
see all the recipes
yeah this is Fire Emblem
also my features are called I should put
on songs
yeah their recipes shouldn't be free
they shouldn't be free
season is starting yeah I already see
the the asparagus Sparkle in the in the
supermarket let me get some socksies
[Music]
hmm
I put on some of those
like
healing sheets on my shoulders and on my
back
because
some reason even though I just went to a
massage like
two or three days ago
I have weird sharp pain and
down my shoulder blades
especially right side
no my cold they're cold they're not hot
the hot ones are [\h__\h] they never get hot
um
I'll switch back to the end oopsie
gotta do it before starting the game
right
foreign
I always I I actually need like the
daily massages
I have this like massage thingy for the
back but no
it doesn't do like so accurate moves the
place the only place where it really
works is like
uh at your shoulder blades
but I also really need like a good neck
massage and the top of the shoulders as
well that's also a place it doesn't rage
hmm
yeah
yeah I mean I had physical therapy and
massages before
I think I'm fine with that shirt no I
don't think
you'll think massage chairs are worth it
because I try them sometimes wherever I
find one
and they're pretty [\h__\h] like a while ago
I tried one at uh the hairdresser
and
it was like
it felt like nothing
but then actually the thing that I have
is way more efficient
the one you wrap around your
oops what am I doing real rapper you
wrap it around your upper arms
that one's pretty good but it really
only helps with like shoulder blade
around that area
engage
okay sorry started off with many
tangents
cooking tangents mmm
I don't know if a massage gun would
really help because
uh
I feel like
I need
um even with the with the massage thing
that I have
to press like against it
to really get
like deep in there
so I I like lean against the wall or so
get it as deep as possible and I feel
like the gun I know never tried it
though
ah the story about the eggs wait was
that true or that was false definitely
definitely her only true story was the
apple and even that was questionable
um I have to say I didn't do anything
off screen unfortunately I should have
wait how do you play this game again
there you go
I didn't have time
the days pass by so fast oh but I
already collected everything okay
so
um but I'm worried
yeah I only want to do story missions
yeah we got three chapters left I just
wonder if like stats wise I'll be fine
that concerns me
[Music]
oh wait we don't need to do this anymore
no
let's do I don't know
does this even still matter
I'm married now
[Music]
I'm gonna try and finish Felix's look
along with the stream oh good luck
good luck good luck
see you
I'm also of course very happy to see you
[Music]
I don't think he can cook well
right who is this
you guys don't forget the videos oh my
God here's the guy right How Could You
Forget it um
uh
[Music]
um
your Veil is so difficult
[Music]
is there anything they both like
damn it
she like pairs
so badly with everyone
not me
[Music]
I guess I can pair heracita
likes likes oh Seafood medley with
garlic
that sounds yummy
let's do it
does it matter if they like it
does it even matter
eh he's not the little guy
oh my God
excellent cook
just like prepping the oven meals back
home
um
this should be tasty even for
non-alpacas it's yummy I'd be happy to
eat it again how could I forget the
alpaca guys surely this will help fuel
my dance Google has orange hair
oh
the
that's weird where's he from where did I
get him
was he the most forgettable character
even though he likes alpacas
oh
it's so weird
all right is there something we want to
upgrade
[Music]
I don't have much oh George's are we
gonna give that to someone
smashing blade
[Music]
upgrade this too right
wow it's so fancy it's glowy
[Music]
maybe just plus two because it doesn't
even need silver it just need Steel
hmm
okay and
um
veilstone oh yard plus two and engraved
oh wait there's a Nova
extremely potent Tome if user initiates
combat attacks twice was I supposed to
give this to someone is this one new
I think Vale still has space in her
inventory doesn't she probably
[Music]
Nova is bad
is it
oh like a brave weapon I give it to Ivy
now we're bad
finally okay then it's not worth
upgrading in my opinion
oh why does she have the brave bow
ah
can she
[Music]
was a white-haired lady should I give
the Bravo to someone
a brave weapon is good I don't really
remember
flashy cute you mean this thing down
here
class s tomb are usable but only two
specialist classes
right if I was attacked twice
I mean that sounds good
sounds good
good for attacking bad for defense
[Music]
one silver well I only have three let me
see if there's something more important
[Music]
powerful as a legend can strike close or
at range or
range
is this like an upgraded uh spare
12 15 17.
oh yeah
oh yeah it's basically a better spare
[Music]
12 15 70 17 70 17 17.
it takes up free
that's selling it short it's the S1
glance on the American wheel now oh
probably won't really be using Tamara
anymore though
[Music]
um
how is such a good cook oh thank you
we're done with that topic now but thank
you
[Music]
you sure
she is great of a brave Spirit you mean
you mean Tamara
does she have one
I I hate this menu she has a javelin
even wait what's this that was upgraded
it's oh wait okay we could even just
give her an upgrade unupgraded Bruno for
now
I'll be here
because even then it's better
[Music]
thank you
yeah
yeah swap
even though Javelin even now feels kind
of strong sometimes I'm not complaining
is there something better still
writer's pain
[Music]
um
I'll keep the rest I guess more of the
year is kind of
has higher chances of being used than
her right now
really really happy so she'd get doubled
oh
no no no no no well as I said probably
won't use her
I only graded the very mini amount of
weapons
oh and you you were fine with that like
you you
didn't have too many troubles
to have another spot
to come again
[Music]
I guess if she has a spot
we could give her that eh oh
you got the same thing
oh
[Music]
yeah
you can get out of the usual room
oopsie I don't remember for how long
you're supposed to be there
what did you do
there you go here's the Nova
don't answer that you really crawl I
vote for someone else and I had two my
moms hmm
[Music]
really that's it
is that really
I was harsh
during the froggy wild approach
[Music]
Ivy doesn't she have it
wait I have a what
[Music]
she never uses Excalibur
on
ah well Celine has a I don't take it
away from Celine
I just fine
Celine like all she has is wind and
Bogan on the 11th sword
I mean
she has some African trouble
[Music]
my poor poor Celine
we're gonna argument better than foreign
[Music]
she does
sometimes it's a better option than the
foreign actually
I mean
[Music]
just hurts me
just hurts me very much
can I then at least I can I can I can do
this right I can give the elfr to Celine
at least
[Music]
and then I'll do her favor and upgrade
it if I can
hmm
okay okay
fine
can I oh
wait does this make it into like a bulk
and known or so
I soon I have never tried this before
the question mark ones
I can do it
I actually lose less silver from it and
less less things overall
hmm
yay now she has volcanon too
everyone is happy
hey
hey can I engrave it
or something
[Music]
a cool engravement with something that's
not taken I wish it would say that
something's taken I guess it says
afterwards once you choose it
you're late no worries we're still
getting started
pasta
pasta volcanon
and grandma what was probably taken
how are we taking
I think
is that me
you have to check it doesn't tell you
what the hell
wait what does it look like it's like a
blue
blue snake whatever
blue snake do I see him yeah it's
already taken it's on the obstacles
[Music]
and the Christmas tree is taken and
the purple ass uh ashkavai has taken
the green
what is that
[Music]
ah if you try it really it does tell you
the gray Batman mask was taken
okay
[Music]
um
let's give it something is this one
taken
probably taken
bacon
[Music]
ah it's taken
holy
what wait wait up
[Music]
um
I don't think we can really find
anything with crit anymore unless this
sacred one will very loose avoid and
Dodge
[Music]
Dawn
I could do Awakening Awakening probably
also taken
[Music]
now damage
Academy surely is taken
dragons isn't really worth it
is that sorens
it's not really good is it
Rivals is I think taken
nah
they're all kind of [\h__\h]
I mean the leftover ones
[Music]
put that on the floor
Loa WT would work best to selling she
only has 6B only
lower
but then like for this one she would
lose
hit and quit
[Music]
for this one
all right that one's taken
this one Dawn but empty empty is what
empty was what might
[Music]
okay
does that apply to Magic too
I suppose yes
[Music]
um
I want to lose that for some other
[Music]
what do you think is it worth it
yeah do it
you need damage makes it more dodgy but
lower damage output
um
I mean Celine most Italians like the
Healer
[Music]
so she doesn't even attempt to do much
damage but
unless you're Dodge tanking
[Music]
um
maybe just keep it with nothing
I wanted to help her out and make her
stronger
I mean this would only make her wait one
more higher
and give her some more hits and might
it's not taken this could be good too
yeah you win some you lose some
avoid his op
inion oh
[Music]
how much will like one more weight
affect her
[Music]
um
kill her in one time oh
I don't know okay let's not do it I'll
be here I think I think I'm good
um what else what else
Maybe
[Music]
oh yeah wait uh Arena
just run in here but
and now we can do a little sequence
ASMR sequence what was it resting
bullet oh button board for loot oh yeah
better be my wife how a Divine one it's
a beautiful day huh
am I early
I'll just sing a little something while
I wait
that time here's the sunshine dream on
oh great Dragon defined
okay
you just woke up in time sorry
herself
[Music]
I really like Tamara you know
but let's be real
ah
he must sleep
okay let's fight
who let her cook for real
[Music]
she's cringe but she's free
morning time
[Music]
okay okay who needs EXP
oh alchrist kind of cool oh
[Music]
I am Lucia
I'll be your partner
let's go wow not even a one-hit kill was
it not lame lame kangatsum
weak also level up where we [\h__\h]
hmm
[Music]
well
my wife
hi hi I'm lapis a royal Soldier take her
down rip her apart yeah
she's using funder
it's probably giving her
sleep a bigger chance to have to win at
all
[Music]
what what's that level up also just two
stats for free
what
[Music]
the hell
I'm Sea Dog okay let's begin
grant me no quarter or you'll regret it
oh
oh see that's gonna lose
[Music]
and another shitty what's going on
what
you don't
that is really not nice
I think like skill wise inherited skill
wise last time I did plenty of work
there
I don't think we're really like
still missing out on something very
important right
like
[Music]
oh no
yeah okay
I guess then
ah
some support conversations and we can go
I cannot tell you how sorry I am for
taking you to those ruins please don't
worry about it
[Music]
one thing to ask if you were afraid of
ghosts how horribly careless
error
you need done I will do and did I do
this on stream before the previous
conversation because panette took Ivy to
you know a ruin with ghosts basically
and Ivy was
she was shocked you don't need to atone
for anything I'm fine I seldom need to
go anywhere alone so I've scarcely felt
my new crippling fear of solitude what
the howling wind keeps me awake at night
but I've learned to scream myself into
exhaustion wow the creek of a floorboard
renders me motionless for hours on end I
don't mind wow I accepted that the
lifetime of fear I went through in a
single day has scarred me forever wow
you poor it's heavy I am so very sorry
[Laughter]
no I'm sorry I had to tease you a little
I'm fine Pinette really oh really
welcome to that place because you
thought it would make me happy
please don't worry about it ever again
don't worry about it I put you through a
terrible ordeal your intention is purely
for me to enjoy it was it not
well yes but that is what matters to me
thank you oh all right if you are
certain do you think despite this
horrible blunder we might still be
friends us of course
where we're going ahead of time from now
on
and no more haunted places please
of course from now on we stay in the
land of the living
yeah it's okay you don't always have to
put up this like charade please
just
you don't have to
um
excuse me malvier Princess Ivy
how may I help I was hoping we could
speak
we find ourselves in similar
circumstances similar circumstances
oh I think I understand we have each
stood as enemies before those We Now
call our allies have fun at work in
light of that I guess
can have fun no this is where
I am unsure there are those who accept
me but I do not believe everyone does
yet I feel comfortable here but that
means nothing I am behaving as if all is
well you I do so lacking any evidence
that it is so yes
still I have no intentions of leaving I
have dedicated myself to helping others
and with that I hope to find acceptance
and
a new place for myself in this world I
understand entirely for whatever it's
worth
let me say that I accept and welcome you
as a friend speaking as someone who
would also benefit from hearing those
same words from our allies thank you for
your candor Princess Ivy
Canter oh candor
[Music]
all right next
I told her I couldn't do it I told her I
wasn't ready to ride a wolf all by
myself what was she thinking was that
fun or was that fun I thought I was
going to die I thought you would too I
really went right over that cliff
Hern and I didn't know I didn't know how
until I was already writing well you
made it all you needed was a little
effort and a positive attitude all I
needed was a miracle but hey really
cleared your mind huh I mean I was so
scared I couldn't actually think so
yes good you're learning the biggest
Thrills in life always involve a little
fear
I'm sure you're right Tamara it is good
to do things that make us uncomfortable
no exactly what does bails sound like
nowhere sounds
and the things she says in a little bit
of her voice now she sounds like they
were so much to me
foreign
I've heard you're really good at telling
fortunes I am or I guess I should say
oh
does that mean you're right not good at
it anymore she's a little bit monotone I
think that's the the thing with fail
well I guess I'd say I'm in a bit of a
rut at the moment hmm I didn't realize
fortune tellers could get in a rut it
would seem so
sometimes you just don't and it shows in
your readings oh my God oh my God I'm
not the only one well
I was thinking of asking you to tell my
fortune oh there's something troubling
you
sort of
they've been very tired lately I was
hoping
I see I'm afraid I can't be of much help
right now it's anything you can do to
get your fortune telling
[Music]
people really know
I think I just have time to come back
when it's ready
well how about you tell my fortune
anyway
why humor me I'll just assume your
reading is incorrect
if that's what you want
let's begin
oh is revealed go to the market and act
like a cat ah good fortune shall be
given you back huh act like a cat
in the market
that's a little bit strange isn't it
definitely strange I told you I'm all
out of sorts just pay it no mind it
won't come true
if you say so
maybe you should attempt it though
goville go become cat
s andreo that's the Abu guy right hello
pandreo have you a moment to spare
of course I always have time for my
sister
But first you gotta tone down the
formality right oh you see there's
something I've been meaning to ask you
no no you're still speaking in that
highfalutin way you don't really expect
me to
yes I do I know you make an effort to
sound fancy but come on it's only me
here you can drop this silver
act around your own brother finally some
netlore fine why are you working for the
church well that's what you wanted to
know huh
dad was a drunk mom was a corrupt priest
who couldn't be bothered to look after
her kids they were lousy parrots so why
would you want to follow in their
footsteps serve their church I told you
what happened after you left right
they disappeared yeah so well the
church's followers needed someone to
guide them
that's why I stepped in
so that's what it was I know it's been a
while but if you'd like to come pray
with us you're always welcome no I think
I'll pass I'm done with our parents and
I'm done with their Church
I'd sooner drop dead than step foot in
that place again fair enough
[Music]
this is where you get the good penet
lore hmm
maybe I should get pendreo and Pinette
in the pool we'll have some
sisterly brotherly bonding time oh
yeah I like her this way I think she
should just always drop that act
I like it
we're in the pool I don't know just
because that was the first thing I
thought to help you all I can swimming
is fun I don't need you but since you're
cute I'll give you a chance to prove
yourself
[Music]
um
and then connect with idle guard oh
what lovely weather today perfect for a
bare knuckle brawl uh civilized duel I
don't know about any of that but the
weather is indeed auspicious I'm having
a deja vu
with panette
like fruit about myself
didn't I once maybe in a collab with Ina
or so
try to attack like attempted to speak
like sophisticated like that
or am I imagining things and I did
pretty bad but
didn't that happen before
no how can you be sure
I feel like that happened once core
memory unlocked
why do you guys don't remember that
I think long time ago
and and just now I was thinking I
sounded like Pinette sound that sounds
now
was I dreaming
no no I think I think that happened
[Music]
no I think I think I think it happened I
think it happened I think it happened
okay I guess let's go
I mean
one more thing
uh vulneri free
um why Wolverine
um
[Music]
honestly
Chihuahua never gets hit that hard most
of the time
well oh well Elixir one
I
I really wish you could
take the like the single boneries and
the single elixirs and put them together
it's honestly so stupid that you can't
[Music]
it's ridiculous she has a physic of only
freeing on it
maybe for one more fight
[Music]
then we'll switch it
um
what if I recover physics
it looks here
men's physic elixir
vulneri
ogado has a bonary
I don't know if we'll still bring him
but
throw them down in the well oh
will I get
if I throw a couple of owneries in there
will I get like a
healing item back
[Music]
where is it
it's random okay let's try I mean at
least with the vulneris
um
I could get a good healing stuff back oh
no okay okay
yeah okay
sounds good
are you guys up
for watching the whole stream by the way
are you guys prepared for it
it'll be a long stream
that's why I chose
the weekend yeah yeah
thank you
oh thank you thank you oh you guys are
motivated
oh
okay that's all I can throw in
uh
let's go I'll try to keep awake but I
need to wake up early tomorrow
or what time zone are you in
wish I bought an energy drink or you can
still go out and buy one that's a long
stream
actually I will quickly run away to get
me my I remembered I have um I have like
the European pocket the Mikado
I need to go grab them because I want to
snack on some cookie like texture
[Music]
okay
oh [\h__\h]
I am here
what's up Cupid
[Music]
my first action review was at the engage
part one
oh thank you wow
you're here so often yeah I guess
because we start early
I'm guessing you're in Korea right but
with these streams we always start kind
of early
so you can count him
I see your name so much these days but
you you speak so such good English
nice English you got there
um
I'm gonna do more okay if you want one
about it I still didn't do like a usual
room one right
we gotta do a usual room
[Music]
right
I think it was kind of in the works
[Music]
first time viewer really
what no [\h__\h] 26 months
thank you
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah YouTube Room video we'll
do it we'll do it
um
maybe you know at the end of this month
where I'll be gone for a couple days
three days or so
maybe a good time to release that
okay okay we got it we got it
[Music]
where are we going next
all down there the other side
[Music]
armed with a powerful artifact from
zephia a party the party heads to a lake
in pursuit of a sunken shard
there's gonna be deer there
wait I forgot one thing to do in the
ah
okay
back to the somnia
sorry
I wanted to check the bulletin board
foreign
people
oh yeah we're just starting so
um
hi wife
uh was it achievements right oh yeah
claim all
[Music]
right
fragments no what I do with all of that
hmm
saving them for engaged too
uh
that's a lot of fragments yeah down
there
I'm nervous
[Music]
foreign
it's hard to believe that there was a
mountain right here where this lake is
I sense a fell Dragon Shard here
cephio was telling the truth
it is out there
very deep at the bottom of this Lake she
set the enchanted Crystal would bring
that whole submerged area into reach but
it will only last a few hours so once it
happens I'll lead us to The Shard
quickly thank you okay
here goes
it's starting
thank you what's happening thank you I'm
glad you congratulate or the lake is
draining
stay together
no it's not safe here and thanks for
still watching the VOD
fail boom
I must have been thrown far from the
others uh We're Alone the lake is gone
the mountain is here are we gonna fight
alone the crystal worked
no I'd better find the others you there
oh
how strange
your face is my face it's red meat what
that can't be
me who are you
well I'm
I sense an emblem one I have never
sensed before if you have a ring give it
to me
I need to take it to father
father sombron the king of dragons
I collect emblem rings
it is my duty
we are currently at war with Steve's
Nine Dragons
I have collected many rings at War
wait
this is me
is this me during the war with the
Divine dragons Sofia's magic put me in
reach of The Shard all right by throwing
me into the past I must be in gradlawn a
thousand years ago before it all sank
when The Shard wasn't over here people
are mumbling I will repeat myself
if you have a ring give it to me quickly
I'm sorry but no your answer must be us
no I cannot let you go with that ring if
I disobey father this is Mira Wawa
Brothers have been killed killed one
older brother was drowned
one older sister was burned alive a
little sister and little brother
they were cute
were torn apart by the corrupted cool
some siblings died in the war
most were defects
father disposed of them tell us post
stuff the defects require disposal
but I am not a defect I collect rings to
prove that
father must get his wish until then
I will collect rings and when his wish
comes true what then
what will you do what will I
uh well
well
didn't think that far huh
what was that that is an avalanche
they are common to this place but I hear
some of the corrupted nearby
they are agitated
that is unusual there are
maybe Intruders the others must be here
somewhere I'm sorry but I have to go
stranger with my face is escaping
I will prevent that I must pursue them
I need your help
Martha oh
evil Marvel game
um
there you are thank goodness you're safe
we weren't sure where to find you
sir
but we finally found each other after
the Earth shook like that I know where
the fell Dragon Shard is it's a short
claim from here unfortunately we've been
followed you won't believe by who
um
all of you I insisted that you tell me
at once exactly who you are
no how do you serve no one being the
corrupted as you did back there
is that the way of making me fight her
again
and surprises are not well received
what's going on
I thought she died
he did die Sofia shouldn't be
[Music]
stay corrupted
but also she doesn't even know us oh my
God everyone this will be a shock but
that is zephia a thousand years ago
because we are in Gradle on a thousand
years ago during the war shock the
crystal was supposed to put us in reach
of the submerged Shard it did in a way
but not by raising mountains or draining
Lakes
sent us back in time believe it or not I
just met my past self
that's how I figured it out wow you're
so smart that can't be good
I have found you
yes it is red eyes
but it's you that's what you looked like
when we first met
zephia please step aside
I will take care of the situation thank
you your highness but I'm more than
happy to assist you that will not be
necessary oh thank God go please don't
let me fight zephia again also that I
sense the president it's so boring
they possess emblem rings it is possible
understood I'll head to the temple
[Music]
nice to see her alive again that we're
here we have to hurry
sister I can't bring myself to hurt you
and that's you in our way what should we
do we need to break the shark but is
that what you're trying to do
Break The Shard what if it was
would you let us pass by no that is
stupid
I cannot return home without your ring
she sounds like crony like that if I win
I take your rings if you win you break
the shard
simple as that then we can't avoid a
fight here stranger with my face I am
ready to battle when you are you will
fight me in this emblem
Marth this is my emblem now show me
yours is she also going to show Marvel I
believe I'm an emblem oh yeah wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
so what meme does not remind me of they
don't know like the the they don't know
that I am something something something
no no no not Dad
Aya
is it the yeah the Spiderman also the
guy in the corner yeah
I'm here ah surprise too yeah there
should be only one of each ring
this is more and more interesting this
is so stupid everyone look at yourself
no matter what
on the other one
well I mean you know what I'm thinking
about
stupid
nah yeah not you again
uh but you know they they could have
shown that mobile Arizona party now and
zephia would have been mind broken like
why is the mobier here and then he could
tell her yo this and that this and that
but of course conveniently we only show
a certain amount of characters of our
party
in these cutscenes Marvin wasn't born
yet
um okay I suppose so
ah but still it still counts and just
conveniently certain characters are not
in the cutscenes
um
what do we have
[Music]
I think I'll go with my to go team
that's fine
um
oh she's been a while it's been like a
week
we have
three of those monsters but I have only
one connect
and there is
corrupted on like a
shooting thingy
oh Chihuahua is all the way here
[Music]
turn limit this battle oh I didn't see
there's a turn limit
[Music]
it's a bit of a difficult chapter oh I
wonder should we just meet in the middle
I mean they're they can join more or
less through these caps
um
[Music]
need to be fast yeah
more than enough time for Wawa as a
strategy you could do because I mean if
I if I sent like two down here and the
rest up here
I feel like we're gonna have to fight
these three but the big monster
I think we can stay more or less out of
his range
maybe the worm
more or less
[Music]
right
we best to advance forward with all
three lanes at the start and then
Converge on the way
like on the way where
because it looks kind of difficult
everywhere to converge
how often do you need more than 15 turns
for battle never that is right even with
like much bigger Maps than this
oh at the very end yeah it's like we're
running a marathon
I just okay but if we fight the worm
[Music]
on all sides
then
we gotta have
who else besides Pinette can slay the
Worm pretty well a mage
there's another gimmick on as well oh
okay Ivy right yeah
Ivy let's keep Ivy at the top
Hortensia
Aya and I think Vale could probably do a
good job don't you think
at least if she's engaged
[Music]
we can have
yeah
kiwawa and I guess gold Mary down here
kind of weird team
[Music]
I thought it was Brave swords it killed
in one turn really
does my car yet still have a brave sword
this team has a Healer
oh you're not caught no this team looks
fine and special with the dancer
did I need the dance actually in a lot
because
they have one less
member in the middle
I'll I'll bring the dancer in the middle
hmm
um
and yeah healer we have potencia here
and up here
uh Mobby or can heal and ivy can heal as
well
looks okay to me
Chloe is
hopefully gonna be useful or should I
replace her with someone
Archer
kogetsu
yeah I think the teams are okay
I uh
uh she does have one state ah okay they
basically have three healers up here
yeah it's not a secret map but
healer down here maybe
they're both lands so I could switch
these
[Music]
maybe like that yeah
what did I miss some cooking tangents
but besides that nothing really I think
we're just getting started now
[Music]
and I guess a little bit of story and a
little bit of Pinette lore
okay emblem rings are
just the same as last time
it's good I think
let's fight
I make avalanches happen oh
even when they don't want to happen
next
do this word flexible okay
why can't she do that and I cannot
uh-huh
we've been pushed back
that works
I'll keep doing what works which is so
weird
in two turns an avalanche will strike a
lower mountain path oh okay but it will
not remove me all the way to the
beginning will it
only like a few I have to reach The
Shard but at this rate we'll get nowhere
fast
starts near you take shelter stay safe
until you can proceed
[Music]
it will it goes all the way what the
[\h__\h]
Pascal ever used the fell Dragon chart
to cause Avalanches that will push your
allies away the warning will indicate
where the Avalanches will strike me but
that's so huge
pay attention to move carefully
the boulders work okay okay
okay so I should stand in front of them
um
okay then okay okay
15 turns
certain battles must be one in a limited
to the number of turns meet the victory
yeah okay
[Music]
I will
do this
is I I should have uh switched uh
panette with
uh yunaka oopsies
[Music]
two turns so I'm still safe
oh I could attack him from here but
I don't want a dragon vein
my will is firm
[Music]
I love it
long it's going to slow down you move on
if the unit is in the plier fog oh oh I
didn't even like notice that I just
thought it was uh
like atmosphere
okay Long Boat seven damage wow
let's go oh she can go so far
let's go indeed ooh flame land let's go
no Crick
that's okay
all right
um
I'll go up here oh wait yeah yeah that's
okay she wouldn't be affected by Dragon
vein anyway all right
Dragon away in this area Wayne Dragon
Wayne vein vein right enough Wayne
there's a sniper there
oh
I'll do my best
Chihuahua why you not have any long
range eh
kind of lame
but we have Seattle I'm with you
oh Nova
in this case kinda good
but
others have higher Christians
I guess I'll go with obscurity because
Nova doesn't kill anyone
[Music]
ah
weird too
what is that sign
ah the ah the married ring
are we stronger together or something
like that like even stronger
[Music]
let me move kiwawa first
wait how far how far can Seattle go
shall we dance not very far
[Music]
um
I gotta move Kia like here
[Music]
trolley dance
thank you
[Music]
for the last for the ring effect to work
oh wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah
Implement [\h__\h]
M door
I just I don't know
[Music]
pretty one
for anyone he could miss
16. oh yeah 16.
[Music]
yeah very good
did she miss one hit or what's going on
huh huh
I thought that would kill what the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I can't get even close enough to
kiwawa
oh that's just sad
I was looking at I guess I was mostly
looking at the the enemy's percentage
um
Well Middle is done no mistakes
which one should I take down I will not
falter
hmm
yes
cannot reach
anyone
yes
I'm sorry
[Music]
wake
I guess they also can't reach me so well
either
I guess the top team will be chilling a
little bit he's doing his best he should
do better
[Music]
together so what the only one who can do
some damage
is Ivy
what are we gonna use
volcanone or foreign foreign one more
damage
[Music]
and higher Christian
see she doesn't need the Pokemon
no crit
no critical
[Music]
yeah yeah
it'll be fun I'll just make us all in
like one straight line mostly
[Music]
okay bring it on baby
oh
[Laughter]
useless move oh
25 damage on his side
that hurts
[Music]
that was sick wait look
wait what
how much damage does he already have
nice nice nice nice nice mauvier
oh
no I see now
Chloe okay oh
dear the [\h__\h] she was doing so well
if I want to undo this she's like
well the first units I moved
we don't need clothes
a 41 chance
I don't want to rewind it's time to
finish the job oh
skip
you'll be fine your Chloe kind of sucks
anyway
yeah everything else was was all right
so
foreign
[Music]
absolutely crazy look at them they're
like gonna be demolished
but
um
can we do something with magic
[Music]
uh hoping for a crits with the leaven
sword here
a really low chance
[Music]
remember the Avalanche oh
is it after this turn like right away so
I have to hide
I think they all have Cantor so
[Music]
can can she
like if she's here
she can't pass and go here huh
[Music]
she could
if defeat enemies then maybe
ah
[Music]
yeah
maybe I'll focus on the bottom ones
first but no
[Music]
oh damn
oh hey yo
okay okay okay okay listen
that's better
oh leave the hard part
yeah yeah it's all right it's all right
move her a little bit back so that
there's some space
[Music]
um
we'll finish this one off
I don't know
I'm sorry you have to see that
Annette never chills
never fails either
okay I I kind of really want to attack
this one but I'll try to stay away
um for now
[Music]
not gonna be
the enemies
isn't that so weird
I have a feeling they're not gonna be
affected
that makes no sense game logic what
what
is
foreign
[Music]
okay
that's the bottom team
special plot immunity
looks like it
all right all right all right all right
all right
[Music]
um
Thor whatever
[Music]
I must see let me see let me see let me
see
okay I have some random tangents
one of them
is stupid
I just
I watched um you know how I was watching
these like British YouTubers like Max
fosh and whatever the other one was Zach
something
[Music]
yeah yeah so Max Max flash put out
another video where he went to America
to uh
invades intrude with antiquette a
security convention or something like
that which he did in the past in in
England as well
um and back then he called himself at
the convention
rob banks
and then like months months later he
does this new video in America and he
like looks back on it
what just happened
all right whatever I have too many units
here he looks back on it and he's like
oh yeah Nicole myself rob banks what do
I call myself now and then it finally
hits me
rob banks
it took me
mothers
[Music]
I did not
realize it the pun that was intended I
didn't get it at all
the first time
which really made me face palm
this time
[Music]
goes to a security convention calls
himself rob banks okay
[Music]
oh
oh filling Graves
I'm funny
that is very funny
I will endure oh wait I need healing
[Music]
oh wow
she's fine does she have no of course
she doesn't of course she doesn't
uh
[Music]
Terry risk
what
then oh
Jerome Mama huh
huge
huge huge ass
nah she can't use the healing stuff on
herself it's so bad
cook
stupid names
ah damn it what do I do
should I
maybe I'll go back I mean
there's the rewind yet
I'll go back to
[Music]
um
gold Mary
I think yeah
and then
I'll finish this one off with kakatu
and then movier can heal Ivy what about
that um
[Music]
unfortunate
Alpha
I can unplug anyone [\h__\h] anyone what
does that mean was that supposed to
imply
what what did I say
[Music]
what
God that took me a while oh my God you
guys
because they have to have to say it out
loud to get it
man
I like a Warp
[Music]
no
more run
Mike
my crotch
good one
[Music]
what do we have here
can we do this with
[Music]
I think possibly
use kiwala for the bottom one and then
Veil for
this one
we may have to do it together unless I
engage is there any charging spots on
this map
text Ariel
[Music]
so
um somebody sent me a video
of how to use Veil the best way but just
by her engaging she will get a higher
crit rate right
let me see create anyone
yeah I mean there's no way she doesn't
grits with that there's no way
however
yeah she'll quit with the first hit
won't she but what's she killed with it
she's getting a bit damaged back
[Music]
Amanda
I mean that's just very obvious but
what's Amanda Amanda
Amanda
oh wait 55 yeah that's decently low if
she quits she will kill okay okay okay
[Music]
good job Veil
good job oh yeah Vale doesn't have
counter oh but okay there is one here
one here
is there only one on each side no
there's another one here
okay like two on the outer sides and one
on the inside
seems like it
okay yeah then we're done with that
that was easy
I mean
there's no enemies inside why not use my
load star rush what would happen if I
just do normal attack
okay I do not want damage unless how
much percentage zero zero zero
zero
I live to fight again
oh can't barely can move well I'll dance
myself I think
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
nice I'm just in range
that helps
oh yeah I saw basement outfit I kind of
like even before I saw it I kind of knew
I just I just thought this is exactly
what she would go for
I knew I knew I knew it
it was very foreseeable
that I think I'm using it wrong again
to cover for hotels yeah well from from
the side from here
maybe I will okay
oh
mobile okay 44. at least he survives
[Music]
oh oh this one goes for chihuahua
stuffy little bastard oh he does fruity
damage
so so so so so stupid predictable yeah
that's what I mean very predictable very
uh Bale dish
Remy very well drawn by her mama
looks really
you know like her mama puts
all possible
love and effort into
the art that she makes
right we're safe
next is the top one
okay
what this one wasn't drawn by Mika
she supervised it
oh probably time issues huh
and the game that I'm playing might just
be a threesome
oh
oh well I know how that feels it's my
my next one is also not drawn by my papa
[Music]
oh oh
this is
[Music]
who can supervising it
um no uh I mean I think what had to be
done is like get the artist
approved by hook and papa
but okay Papa has not been involved in
the outfit design or anything at all
I have been taking full control over it
and I'm honestly so happy because the
artist is just like literally doing
everything the way
I could
ever ask for ideally like it's so cool
while really implementing their own art
style
I think once you guys will see it you'll
understand it
when you compare it to like there are
other works
um
and I just I just I'm really enjoying
seeing myself like that it's very
unusual
from yeah different quinoa ones
um
and I'm preparing something really
released special for this outfit reveal
way ahead of time because it's something
that takes time
[Music]
um
holy [\h__\h]
yeah because I you know
I feel like outfit reveals
with someone so creative as Amelia in my
generation I feel like you know I gotta
I gotta keep up I gotta do something
interesting
[Music]
hmm what are we gonna do about this
dilemma maybe we have to engage
[Music]
gotta keep up about me yeah
what are we gonna do
[Music]
I mean it's it's
it is something really cool and and
um nice
but it will not really
yeah take up much
time of the reveal
but whatever it will be nice anyway no
more spoilers yep
um
if you were to give a TED Talk what
topic would it be
but TED Talks are supposed to be
motivational and stuff right
I guess
I guess something about content creating
not necessarily
and what I guess realistic of good a
realistic answer would be probably like
content creation
[Music]
is run for better than kagazu's normal
attacks I never use it
or is it just like it makes no more
damage it's just like she he ends up on
the other side right
besides that it's just the same right
[Music]
okay
oh God damn it I don't know what to do
here
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
attacking the monster with the engage
attack I wonder how that would pan out
[Music]
I'll Chris engage and double or Astro
storm
the Astra storm didn't really seem to do
anything to the worm though but I could
already get like a start on the ones in
the back
because they're gonna come for me
[Music]
yeah
I think I'll do that
what the hell no
[Music]
oh I can reach so far no I want the one
up there there we go
[Music]
yeah I guess
a good win I got the little frame store
should attack four times against the
Dragon
yeah I don't know if he has brexit
congratulations
[Music]
he does
but I mean
better to aim for this one oh he has a
special weapon this one
we could break him
and he won't attack back he won't kill
me
[Music]
but we can't kill him
I do with this worm
I don't I don't want to get all the
damage
grant me Springs
[Music]
the only thing I can hope for is a crit
on the volcanona I think because even if
I create with the Forum
I don't think I will kill
[Music]
soften him with warp soften him
soften him
[Music]
I just watched the dinosaur tier list
videos
it was really interesting I also watched
the SpongeBob Peerless video the
SpongeBob the animals Fearless
yum
very interesting indeed
[Music]
foreign
I felt a little bit bad for one of the
dinosaurs who apparently has a brain
like a possum
felt bad for that one hmm
but I didn't know that there's this one
dinosaur
s-tier dinosaur who has like a really
really high intelligence I didn't know
about that that's really cool
hmm
2017 YouTubers
um
ah
God damn it
what happens when it's blue if I'm
engaged here
ah so useless
I need to kill this monster in this
round
[Music]
no I can't I can't I can't
um
which one I don't remember the name it
was a smart the smartest dinosaur of
them all
[Music]
what would you do guys yeah I didn't
bring Erica
[Music]
well and they'll
huh
okay that's just a just a little bit
though
how far can she do that from everywhere
oh yeah
[Music]
wait is it like
is there anything like the closer she is
the higher no
better than nothing yeah because I
probably don't need her down here in
particular I could even dance Veil and
do the same thing again
[Music]
foreign
engage
[Music]
maybe if I get some units next to me
but I can't even kill this Mom
[Music]
and Mario can probably kill it if I do
one more bolting what do you think about
that and then yeah we should be able to
clear this one too
thank you
yeah I will do it like that otherwise my
brain
can't handle
[Music]
where should I leave for herato oh
do I want to leave her in range of some
of these mobs
[Music]
could be fun
yeah good job for suggesting voting that
really
helped me out there
first we'll break her on you
we can't have that
okay
even gets a chain attack from it
[Music]
all right
now we're talking now we're cooking
oh oh have you guys seen the Mario movie
can I talk a little bit about the Mario
movie now
can I talk a little bit
a little bit
yeah have you seen it yeah yeah yeah
yeah so yesterday yay heaven but go
ahead okay just just don't really listen
just half half lesson
okay and but it's already been like a
week or so for me so I also don't
remember that much you gotta help me
with talking points but um I think one
thing and then I
that I really uh surprisingly I think I
liked it I'm not 100 sure but the fact
that Bowser right had like this huge
soft side to him
this huge subset where he would sing his
peaches peaches peaches song very cute
but very surprising I don't know did he
was he ever portrayed like this before
what was this really new
[Music]
never
he does sometimes yes
and Paper Mario
he has a sauce on the Paper Mario oh
okay okay so it wasn't like too crazy
that
that would be
his this thing
[Music]
okay yeah I don't know that one's really
cute uh but I I don't know I felt a
little bit like eh Bowser acts like that
really what it was funny though like our
Cinema was so full packed with people
people were audibly laughing it was
quite funny
him on the piano
cracked me up too slow
I want to sing a lot of kids no it was
like mostly teenagers and like adult
looking people
um
actually
[Music]
sing Peaches I wanna
teachers Pages Pages
actually the Super Mario movie
um account
sent me
that like performance but like from the
actual like voice actor in person
sent it to me
[Music]
thanks I guess that was funny though
that was quite funny
yeah if you like subscribe to them on
Twitter they will send this stuff to you
if you mentioned if you mentioned a
Mario movie
I guess that's what triggers them hmm
what else let me think I am I'm really
glad that uh Luigi was
involved but
I was a bit disappointed in like how
often how big
he in what scale he was involved I would
have hoped for a bit more
to be honest
[Music]
like he was
he was just like
yeah again a side character but at least
he was there and it was so cool to see
like Mario's Family
he was wrapped
and what's so cool to see his family
though
and um
they were all
very entertaining I liked it I liked
that the movie started out in the real
world
cannot wait real people and like you
know them struggling with their new
business the commercial was so good too
I loved the the commercial for their
business
and I don't know uh what else
um what was I gonna say
ah Luigi there was this one scene where
he
um
he's like
he's like lost somewhere in a dark area
and it really gave me uh
uh Luigi's Mansion Vibes maybe it's just
me but
[Music]
hmm
same Christians
but maybe maybe Brave better because
then you know
I think that was the idea oh
let's have some there comes the Chris
thank you
um
every time
after she takes damage
why
she needs to be healed otherwise that
Mage is looking dangerous to me
hmm
please
fogado can reach the mage
[Music]
can he kill him though no maybe if he
brings
out a little special
companion
[Music]
simply wonderful
yo yeah Donkey Kong
that was really cool seeing I mean I'm
not a big Donkey Kong fan or anything
but the whole Donkey Kong Arc was cool
like seeing their Kingdom and seeing uh
like how it was quite different over
there like the different Kingdoms in
general the different biomies basically
was pretty neat to see
okay I'll stay on the side and I'll just
Dragon vein I think
I can't can't get to panette now
[Music]
did I just
make it more difficult for myself to
attack the
[Music]
does that like include him
oh well it's okay
spending on the world is nice and all
the games are just hey there's all these
random levels with no Cohen from yeah
yeah like seeing the connections and all
that was cool the told the toad city was
cute very cute
um
Peach fighting and all that I saw like
some drama on Twitter where people were
like hey that's Daisy not Peach
and as much as I would have loved to see
uh Daisy in the movie
people were arguing that uh it is it can
totally totally repeat
because in like games where she was the
main character she did stuff like that
apparently
uh like what was it called oh my God
yeah she she can fight but then I wonder
if she can fight as well why doesn't she
do it like you know whenever she's stuck
somewhere in games where Mario saves her
suddenly she can't but oh well so
uh I watched in in English but
I want to watch it in German too because
I think I said I liked her voice more in
German
but in the end I think like from the
trailers I got a really bad impression
from her voice but it turned out it
wasn't so bad after all when I watched
the the movie
and same with Chris Pratt like I maybe
it's just because I I don't watch so
much Chris Pratt movies
but I didn't feel I feel like
um
when I was like listening to Mario
I wasn't like oh hey this is Chris Pratt
no not at all like I was pretty immersed
and he sounded really great as Mario
they showed his worst lands in the
trailer yeah yeah I think for both Peach
and Mario in the trailer I was like eh
but then in the movie it didn't bother
me at all
[Music]
um
yeah yeah yeah you guys agree okay
this is kind of scary situation the
middle is kind of
scary
[Music]
the Canon dude
really dangerous for her
what do you think of the music
I loved the music like both the remixes
of classic Mario music as well as
the songs they use because those were
songs I need hero
[Music]
gotta be strong
because before and they're kind of old
but really really funky and fun so I
actually really enjoyed the song Choices
okay I saw some
some kfb I think saying I didn't like
the in that they included these kind of
songs but
but I really liked them here until the
end
I personally really liked them
sounds like Shrek ah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
somehow I get what you mean
[Music]
oh the middle is getting dangerous too
because I was thinking for a moment
dance uh Hortensia to get her out of the
way
but if only like he wow stays in the
front she's gonna be bombarded by them
um
[Music]
vitamins you should watch the old Donkey
Kong CG series and then oh yeah wasn't
there it is this Donkey Kong uh song and
I I saw some lore beforehand
that it's like some really old Donkey
Kong song that they used uh as a base
for it or so
yeah the rats the Donkey Kong rap
mediocre
also I liked how you could really see
the the build up for Mario like he
didn't start off
super overpowered no
like you could sing originally he was
just like a normal dude
who just needed the tools of this world
to become stronger and unlock his true
potential yeah and a whole Mario Kart
Arc I mean of course that was that was
kind of fun too but I feel like
um something about it was
maybe a bit uh what did I feel Maybe
anti-climatic
something was
missing I think I'm not sure what it was
it's yeah the pacing maybe I have blue
I don't know I don't know something
something no no no that's the way it
ended maybe or so
something was not so satisfying about it
okay we'll dance someone
I wonder if Hortensia can kill this dude
probably not
because then at least I could get her
away
um
[Music]
felt the movie was too short well yeah
but it was compact it was nice it had a
nice beginning a nice middle part nice
ending
but it was weird that they came back to
the normal world
and you know they bring all this crazy
[\h__\h] with them and and what's the
aftermath people know about like this
magical stuff and what
what what are they're not gonna like
shoot again freak out what
hmm
[Music]
I guess they're just gonna ignore that
problematic part
that's it I'm going to buy a movie
ticket you should it's a really really
good movie The Animation was top-notch
and with the trailers oh yeah she can't
do [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] with the trailers I also still
felt like the the style
they used
was weird
I guess I'll just
hide her somewhere
um
I don't know because I guess I was just
so used to how
Nintendo characters normally look but
then then like you know
did you clap for Yoshi I was
short moment where you saw you know
she's running around was really cute
yeah yeah but then at the end okay here
comes big spoiler but not really I mean
it's just a little Easter egg huh
literally
um do I need to heal someone
oh yeah actually Kiana could use healing
you know what if I'm in reach for him
anyway I might as well
okay now I'm not in Rage the physics
should hit
okay
um yeah if you'll stay after the credits
and we just so happens to stay and even
though the the movie theater was really
really packed we were like one of the
few people who stayed but the ones that
remained it seemed like you know those
are the really
nerdy just like me nerdy and
you know smart people
but then we stayed and then we were
rewarded for staying because there was a
little Easter egg a Yoshi egg
which made me think if that's what you
show at the end
are you hinting at a second movie
that includes yoshimur or what
what do you think guys
definitely a sequel
always yes yeah for breakfast okay okay
that thing would be cool I'm not
thinking that they would have Yoshi as
the main role but he will definitely
play a big part right
that'll be so nice
that'll be so nice and maybe we got to
see daisy as well and then what a Wario
and and Waluigi as well
because we didn't get them this time
yeah
that only seems fair also there's like
no enemies to fight here what the hell
[Music]
um
not sure if that's worth it that
Exchange
foreign
[Music]
have to give her a second steal letter
I don't think that's gonna happen
um well that's one of my thoughts what
else were your thoughts guys on the
movie
what were your thoughts
is the Avalanche coming this round
[Music]
I liked all the Easter eggs more Bowser
and Luigi like the part where I haven't
seen it with the Angelou ah do you mean
that I I never see I never played a game
before with that character so I didn't
really know it well but that was so
funny you mean that that thing that
glowy thing in the in the cage now that
thing was so funny
the whole Cinema was laughing at that
and and
I saw some kfp absolutely getting super
salty about it uh in a tweet because I
got it recommended but
I'm sorry I actually I clapped and I was
I think the first one to clap and I got
a lot of other people to clap at the end
of the movie because I was genuinely
like entertained and happy after that
throughout the whole movie I was
smiling
and just having a lot of fun
like well and I was like vibing a lot
whenever music came on don't call me
cringe
I think this was actually like you know
and and I don't think I think it's weird
because it was
um the first or the second day when I
watched it so it was more or less almost
a Premiere yeah you know
it was okay to collab I really enjoyed
it and and I wasn't the only one so in
the end you know we felt it we all felt
it it was really hype
[Music]
it's not weird
oh wait I clap all the time when I'm
excited
except an airplane ride that's when I
think it's cringe when people
clap after after like a two hour flight
like what the [\h__\h]
that the people in the cockpit are not
even gonna hear you the pilots are not
even gonna hear you
plane clapping is the real weird thing
yeah
okay what am I gonna do uh just wait I
guess
some healing here what where are my
healers just mobier and Ivy I guess but
I used ivy so I can heal
does he have a physic yeah can you
cockatoo
yeah
oh but yeah okay I enjoyed the voice
acting I enjoyed the animation I enjoyed
um the storyline
um
overall I mean I have like literally no
complaints about the
the movie I think
oh wait I didn't do anything in lower
round yet oh what the hell
foreign
[Music]
of course you can trust me I'm not the
only one this is a popular opinion
saying that this movie was good
trust me
book of worlds
[Music]
um
I guess I'll die no
now I'll just put the vein of fog there
are you guys man you guys don't be like
that
you were great with me what's good
[Music]
14 damage
that sounds so bad
oh
wow thank God it missed because he would
have left her with one HP
five okay
I do look critics still hated oh yeah
yeah yeah the critics reviews what's up
with that
I saw that too
what what's the matter of them dude I
just enjoy to hate things
like it was genuinely not bad
they were so critical of it I guess
that's what a Critic does
[Music]
middle middle path next
critics and watching a different movie
it wasn't the people that people really
excited to get attendance for no critics
no probably not a 10 or the 10 but
something better than that
still watching it regardless you didn't
watch it yet
okay I don't think I'm really you know
who spoiled you bad but
yeah
have fun
[Music]
does Hortensia below belong to the
middle or to the bottom group
I don't even know anymore
[Music]
yeah I told you guys to watch it
your fault
I haven't seen it but I don't have a big
urge but you should really it's so good
I think like for people like us you know
people like us AKA nerds it's the
perfect movie okay it's so cool to see
something like come to life that you
played in the past I mean I haven't
played like a million Mario games but I
mean you know have a connection to it I
play a lot of uh you know Mario Kart and
Mario Party and all that and I did play
64 and all that on stream you know I
played all of Luigi's Mansion
you know especially as someone who does
it kind of as their job that was also it
felt really special to me
um
[Music]
my goodness how awful
I will ignore the comments now because
um I have a little headache right now
um
oh man I wonder what's wrong with me hmm
oh why did I move Pinette so far in the
back I'm stupid
[\h__\h]
just stupid
I could rewind though
because I'm obviously not using my
rewinds
I won't need them
[Music]
that's how a lady does it
yeah yeah
oh also
I was able to
test nachos
normally when I go to the cinema I
always go for popcorn and but I'm always
like kind of curious you know I'm
curious about the nachos
I'm like hmm
wow could I ever become a nacho enjoyer
you know I mean notches are final but as
a cinnamon food
when I like it as a cinema food
natural goat
well and I have always been kind of you
know unsure about it
and I gave
not just a chance by you know discussing
it with my with one of my friends who
was there uh rbff rbff obf or BFF
um
yeah yeah and I was like should I maybe
try nachos today so we ended up sharing
I got like a middle-sized sweet popcorn
an RPF got a middle-sized nachos and I
ended up snacking the whole movie I've
never I was never so like
hungry I don't know I would say I was
really hungry
but
I couldn't stop myself it was crazy oh
my God the tiramy storm is actually the
only thing that kills this dude
surely but I would take a lot of damage
and we were probably safer to bet on a
crit with the obscurity
always
[Music]
I should just take a step back to maybe
that would help
no crit
girl also she has no Canter because we
have to give her all the crit thingies
[Music]
it's not you know what
Joy I kind of want to give her the
Revival Stone because she's a bit
squishy
scares me
foreign
[Music]
especially now that she stands so far in
the front
[Music]
gotta use that up you know I'm gonna use
it make use of it
I'll keep it here
[Music]
what was I saying oh yeah nachos but
nachos crazy I don't think I could
go for only nachos
alone for a movie
[Music]
because
they left such a really strong taste in
my mouth aftertaste
I'm not sure I like it
I mean I liked it for a couple bites but
then after a while I was like damn damn
now I gotta
switch back to the popcorn
[Music]
ah it was it was Salsa and cheese sauce
because are we have said you know the
small
portion only comes with salsa sauce so
you always gotta just minimal take
minimum the middle portion because it
comes with both sauces
but only salsa songs is boring and I
agree that would have been probably very
boring maybe bring your own cheese dip I
guess Maybe
yes you could do that
yeah both both sauces combined but
uh nachos in the cinema because I
grabbed a nutshell I had to like look so
closely to see what I'm grabbing and
what I'm dipping it into and if I'm even
getting any dip onto the chip because
it's so dark guys
it's so dark
you can't see [\h__\h] I was so often I was
looking away from the movie because I
was just staring at the nachos
practice skill issue that was my first
time
you could memorize the location
yeah but then
how do you know that there's enough dip
on there
[Music]
um
yeah
[Music]
can they attack back they don't have a
short bow
loser
even better
I was honestly questioning though why do
why is like
[Music]
um
potato fries and chicken nuggets not a
not a
um a cinema food because I was really
longing those fries and Nuggets in that
moment but I suppose
I suppose I think I get it
I think I get it
probably because first of all
uh popcorn and nachos and all that are
just easier to like cheaper and easier
to create prepare for a cinema
and also when the movie is long
the fries and the nuggets
either you're just finishing eating them
because they're like a small portion
most of the time you finish eating them
pretty early on and then you're like
well now I have nothing left or you
don't and then you have cold fries and
cold nuggets like and after the middle
of the movie while with popcorn even
after they get a little bit cold same
with nachos
it doesn't matter
yeah so I get that but I was I was
playing nonetheless it would be nice to
have nuggets and fries
I still think so
[Music]
quickly not too messy
yeah I think it's probably just the
biggest reason is probably the cost and
like the convenience of it
[Music]
Ivy you are gonna heal
thank you
compared to Natural yeah I know compared
to popcorn as well like have you seen
the amount of popcorn sometimes
especially when people drop it
Like It's Hot
so God such a mess
such a mess every time I act as her
night
I feel so bad because I'm also like a
culprit of losing a lot of popcorn
fall down they tumble down
I'm doing well so far I think 15 times
plenty
what is that lender there you know what
I don't care are we fine we're fine
[Music]
the Limestone on Hortensia
um
I think we don't need her
my my wife oh yeah right she's my wife
uh Yomega Yomega
oh one is going prevail
Mrs
how much is 16 plus 12.
28 oh
if I if I go back
in time
reinforcements
well still plenty of turns left but
will I be all right without potencia
football chronic
mm-hmm
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah I guess I'll marry someone else
yeah a Healer
[Music]
um
should I just move for attention to
somewhere else or should I give her the
divine blessing
um
[Music]
all right I'll just move her
what did she do
there's an Archer right an Archer took
her down where did that which what which
one
this one
oh yeah this one he even came down from
his
little thingy
so maybe if I'm like I don't know where
was I
am I here I should be safe
[Music]
right
I'm safe here
no apologies my poor what
you killing my wife doesn't make you any
more popular with me you know
think
[Music]
yeah I know
foreign
who did I kill how all right I did
something like this
[Music]
I like how now your units instead of
dodging attacks they pair them right
away is that good or bad are you
speaking ironically
oh
[Music]
tracing back my steps hurry
I know I want to go to the cinema again
because because I need to go to cinema a
lot in the coming days because
uh I still need to watch that DND movie
is it good guys
[Music]
The Dungeons and Dragons ones people
have been saying good things about it
and I saw that there's uh this new Marv
this new Guardians of the Galaxy movie
coming up but I'm not even sure if I saw
the second one I'll have to check
maybe I'll just watch on Disney in my
private time
to refresh my brain that one's coming up
and then
you do not intend to why not
watch it and imagine you're watching it
with me
John Wick what I don't care about John
Lake
um maybe I should
I really want to see the DND movie yeah
me too me too
that's a compelling Iron Man right
you should then I loved it okay you
wouldn't like John Wick probably oh
yeah but the other one is the Bible
topic
have you seen
I mean it's not out yet but have you
seen
I I haven't have I seen the trailer oh
yeah I think I've seen like a short
trailer in the cinema I think and then
I've seen on Twitter like a lot of like
fan art and and funny graphic
posters and [\h__\h]
um it's it's looking very funny
oh yeah oh yeah I saw this regular in
the cinema for the Barbie movie because
there was like this huge
pretty lady
I remember
yeah yeah
who is Ken
Ryan got
whoa you didn't cut oh at least you had
this okay she has the HP bar yeah oh
you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
that's okay that's okay that's what we
have the HP bar for
yeah you failed
there's more than one can
and Gosling is really one of them
Ryan Gosling
funny funny
when is that one coming out
[Music]
date please
what do you know
July 21 June
most of the girls in the movie are
Barbies most of the guys are kids ah I
guess okay yeah there's more than one
makes sense July 21st here oh
okay that's so quiet sometime
and next is the Avalanche coming right
so
oh this one seems to be going upwards
I can fight
hmm
okay
[Music]
not a Barbie little follower and me
neither
[Music]
me neither
maybe dance
[Music]
yeah I think that's cute
he's probably
just gonna get pushed down
that's okay
[Music]
so if koala
if I go here damn they're all gonna
go crazy
[Music]
but I don't want to kill this dude here
what should I do
[Music]
you want to watch Superman oh yeah yeah
people have been watching Susan man um
came out outside of Japan recently yeah
yeah
enemies stop the Avalanche too
oh oh like if I stand right behind them
or like in front of them I guess you
know or or no yeah both I guess
can't go away how about I can't I can't
comp around
we'll see we'll risk it
had to stop you
it's okay
I'll be fine
um oh yeah because the Avalanche comes
first and the Avalanche will move her
down too
will set me back and then I'll be out of
range for the enemies I think
[Music]
foreign
oh yeah oh yeah that's out of range oh
my god wow I didn't think that would be
a thing
um
problem with valence she doesn't have
cancer so she can't really do anything
this turn
[Music]
we all
there's your enemies attack yeah they do
oh well whatever
okay hmm
there's no original plus and sub eh
[Music]
eh wait susama is in the cinema with an
En dub
or what
[Music]
why you no kill
foreign
is still in danger
[Music]
but well we still choose to shoot with
this thing if Kiana is right behind him
won't he
try to go for piano
[Music]
okay I could go here
for potencia and then she's not too far
away and she's somewhat safe
it's okay we'll take him down next turn
all right what do we have down here
two enemies and also one of these but no
Flyers here
foreign
step
oh
[Music]
you don't even have to borrow a movie in
my country what
what's still coming right maybe it's
taking longer in your country
[Music]
that is the ultimate pain serves you
right
nice one
wow nice level up oh
nice nice
[Music]
do it too
Super Bowl
all right
[Music]
last night was pretty fun right did you
miss
what it wasn't that low
it wasn't that low
he's on fire now
[Music]
as I will not Dragon vein hopefully I
won't regret his spaghetti
[Music]
laughs
nah it's okay
[Music]
that didn't do so much damage anyway I
think though the bombs
okay here we have couple pliers
[Music]
one easy takedown but I want that I want
that
okay Ivy gets it
but Ivy kind of wait okay let's see what
we can do with the ground units first
mm-hmm
32.
[Music]
come on gold Mary
I want you I mean
[Music]
killing Edge
must do the trick at least it's broken
no okay
Young
understood that forces my hand
a little bit to do things
[Music]
oh wait can't you can't Alquist cancer
over to that field I think he can
[Music]
two steps Ryan I had no choice but to
win easy
yeah there we go
hi are you lost
are you lost
you're looking a little bit lost over
there
little friend
[Music]
can I go one step back too
today burnt wolf on a school
is what we're having stay away from the
from the bomb guy though
hmm
no no no no no no no no no protect
I have it
I am in your debt
eating good tonight
yeah well we're eating good leftovers
tonight hey
[Music]
all right that's my turn I mean not
today so far
mostly I've had no no troubles though I
say that again and something will go
wrong right no no no no
I'm just saying though I haven't been
feeling so press pressured yet
[Music]
yeah playing playing well today I think
so too but this map is not so bad
the Avalanche really isn't bothering me
much either
foreign
here he comes
um
what a food yeah yeah I just need to
actually go to the island meeting soon I
think
nine turns left we're almost there
real estate I'm surprised
of course I kept her safe
of course look at those flyers hmm
volcano it's your chance to yourself
there we go finally
wait 58.
[Music]
because he's in the fog
I have no choice
[Music]
I believe
I believe they can hit
I believed he can take him down
even through the fog here's the gods
don't forget about him oh
[Music]
genius retribution is due
is new I love that phrase
60 frames
63 kind of low
what I believe
too much damage and he ain't dead
[Music]
I'll rewind diving I don't like that why
there's no
huh why so low she's not standing in the
fog
[Music]
yeah I'm thinking engage
trust you too better
still 63.
[Music]
.95
your night try the bow
[Music]
I can't use it from right in front of
him but it's also just 63
[Music]
.
hey look guys is falling off in a late
game it seems these hit rates aren't
great yeah
[Music]
um
all right
it's a little arrow for one HP
oh
[Music]
bottom
does he have a short book no he doesn't
I can't believe that even an end game
these suckers aren't the clipped of the
short bow
[Music]
damn
feel bad for them
[Music]
I mean yeah they're trash but at least
they can defend themselves
[Music]
wouldn't that be smart
foreign
Trevor thank you CD thank you
yeah I guess so
oh weren't too bad for them
um
middle row
[Music]
maybe not oh maybe heel instead
on a heel Bell we should have a
physical
[Music]
thank you
oh and free houses they had one range by
default really I don't even remember
that
I'm hoping
she'll be safe she'll be fine
[Music]
lend me your strength
the kiwawa charge
on her own already again because I don't
remember putting her on a charging plate
[Music]
incredible incredible
ah
I live to fight again oh oh Liberation
gives me charge so much damn
nice
nice nice nice both Wheels by Legends oh
again only your S rank so for our Chris
probably
[Music]
now the rest here hmm
can't dance in this form huh
all right no wait he can
oh yeah I just didn't show because I
didn't move fail yet
[Music]
um I think
and the result is the same I think I
think in this case I'll just attack with
him
oh 51 what the hell
never mind I think I'll dance koala
and try I want to see how much that wait
can she even use it or does she have to
be an Archer
ah okay all right
um
[Music]
still worth carrying around the armward
Slayer guys look
yo
[Music]
and then well
which one is more dangerous because it
seems like Veil can take down
even this one
[Music]
I feel like
mmm
the wolf night yeah I think so too
I mean wait the book Night the wolf
Knight this one
[Music]
could kill Hort he could poison you oh
where should I put her
foreign
[Music]
with doubt
nice strategy you have there
wow what a level up
nice
if they're up here can they hit what's
like right in front of them
I feel like realistically you shouldn't
be able to do that I mean not with the
bomb thingy
[Music]
but
they can't right okay I'll stay here
[Music]
well well well well well well well well
well well well
um
emblem engage I'll see how much damage
Astra storm does
[Music]
um
it's wooden skills and maybe I'll go for
now but doubles there's only two enemies
oh
[Music]
I might not do anything this round
tomato
[Music]
I mean I might shoot someone completely
different with the Astra storm
someone will annoys me more
[Music]
and combination
take them down
no
actually important because Ivy otherwise
in danger
[Music]
yesterday while I was cooking I was
watching Nina's uh Pokemon stream the
whole time
and I made her say quantum
but she says it wrong
it wasn't as satisfying it was funny
though the way she says it now I have
you yeah
she says it's wrong
to get stronger until no one can beat me
she says it's so strongly
well it was fun watching her recently
when I cook on my iPad I watched
people's streams whoever's on
and this time I got done cooking before
like at midnight yo that's pretty rare
well
they went for Veil but they regretty
oh more okay but not much
[Music]
okay here's only one thing we left
oh easy
can he do nothing
okay let's go
might as well use a combat Arts but
[Music]
let me see
oh Brave X
72 percent
[Music]
look it's fate
right back's good right back's very good
hmm
what is the Avalanche uh
coming this round
after this round or what's uh what what
where are we at right now it is oh okay
then I'll stay here I'll fall back to
the
this thingy
[Music]
oh SWAT maybe that brings exp oh [\h__\h]
forgoto hmm
oh
Papa can she go
oof
ah she can't even go here
ah
[Music]
up here does it get her here
no right she's like situated higher
you saved me
eh I think it does honestly don't know I
wish you can go ask
over it yo
yeah yeah yeah
all right
oh he has to stay here
because you can only counter after your
attack right so
even if I stay here I can't like move on
over here
can you like
um
okay
big brain
since you can walk over the police so
the Avalanche can push you over it
laughs
nah this place is safe
[Music]
It's gotta be safe how can
now
yeah I think I think safe
[Music]
can we do it for attention
thanks
nothing
hmm there's no enemies
[Music]
zero could charge
don't know if I'll still use it but oh
itself I guess but nah
nah
I could start the fight with bolting but
[Music]
no sir Rush anyone
okay okay we want to stay away then okay
okay
[Music]
all right zero percent
I was thinking about it
oh
here is safe here
[Music]
yeah next turn we'll go
right at her don't worry
[Music]
I might yeah put Ivy into position
already as well
Maybe
because I don't know if I want to waste
my time here with these suckers
yeah we're running this place down a
slight injury
no injuries
[Music]
a moment
oh wow
almost killed
[Music]
um longbow
more fighting
oh man I can try putting alcrest on that
oh
whatever that is
20 20.
[Music]
civil sword 21.
gonna go for the killing Edge and hope
that it will crit and we'll we won't
take any damage but even if she does
[Music]
yeah the optimal way to kick ass I guess
let me let me because I got you guys to
ask questions let's see if there's any
important questions here
bed hair
bad hair
hmm
I think it can look cute both on real
people and anime people with Cali
and Cali it's especially cute
me
upstairs doing turns streams that last
from 8 to 12 hours and sometimes
you stream that long anyway what would
be an endurance from you look like no no
no no no no no for even for me
depending on the situation
12 hours this is an endurance to me as
well
I mean there's been times where I
streamed that long and it didn't quite
feel like it but generally
yeah
it's it's rough for me as well
oh my Chris can't even go there
[Music]
oh wait no I'll use them for healing
would you ever do a 24-hour stream
rushing
not alone
and I wonder
oh
would sleeping be
acceptable
I mean you couldn't just leave seven
eight hours through
I would feel bad for the partner who
would be probably covering for that time
I think
you gotta take like really short maybe
three hours this is the most acceptable
yeah no it's it's
I don't know it sounds like it's not
really fun and hype idea but
unnecessarily painful for
me
so maybe not
[Music]
okay we're not in range here
hey I'm ready I'm ready
suffer for us
people usually do that for charity
what who just
what just happened
it didn't
it didn't stop them
at least I didn't go all the way back
no
at this point it would be faster to go
for here probably
wow
[Music]
you're so young
it's not too bad but what the hell it
looks like it would stop it
oh man
okay wow wow
what do you guys think should we try
going all in or wait one more round
for the side people to arrive
[Music]
wait around
I was thinking so too
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I mean I think this side
even with one more round might not make
it
but Celine and
um panette
could more or less catch up maybe
oh yeah
yeah she seems she's not gonna be easy
that's what I'm thinking
so I want to give myself more help
[Music]
um
[\h__\h]
[Music]
you know kind of sad that I can't make
use of the doubles I don't know
so
we don't want to
uh anger kiwawa yet so I want to be
somewhere where I can
counter away so
[Music]
I do want to help out here though
men's doubles to bake
Sally you won't be able to yeah yeah now
that would be great
thank you
but no can do
okay
[Music]
I guess I'll have to let these two mobs
come come for me because
[Music]
the only thing I can think of is you
engaging Veil
and bolting
I might do that I mean Your Righteous
dragon
we're at the end hopefully it will end
next round or the next next round
so take down this one
an obstacle in need of removing
okay yeah I'm thinking to use Tiki again
as well
but on who I think position lines I'm
forced to give it to Vale again
[Music]
emblem
which is fine
I'll be good
[Music]
as a mortal and engaged you could just
attack normally
um
ah I wanna attack
okay
how far can she go
[Music]
after this
she won't be able to reach
wait if I stand here
here I'm not in reach
oh yeah I'm not
okay from here would be good
[Music]
just like it
and then I think he's probably gonna go
for Kiana that ax guy
it's a good spot yeah
[Music]
okay here we go
ah he goes for Veil 46
Miss
it seems like oh we're really making it
worth to give her the stones
why didn't you go for Kiara
wait wait kiwawa
has no engagement now
let me see let me just see
oh that's not so bad
I mean she can't really no that's I mean
avoid
[Music]
yeah I'm scared that's scary that's very
scary I can engage with us
no
[Music]
damn it damn it
ah engagement
[Music]
no
no no no no
I feel like I'm still out ready but now
the the worms are here
connects far
You Can Dance Pinette though if I wanted
to
um what you've been done
[Music]
bait loads The Rush with extra life
I can't do that by just standing here
and attacking the other though I think
[Music]
okay okay okay
she even heals back quite a bit
wait not not I don't actually don't want
to use that
[Music]
storm
and Mr Mr but that one doesn't heal
[Music]
let's go
oh
critical hands hail
[Music]
oh
y'all do not ignore the joke weapons
like the crossover has also been decent
yeah
in worst case you can always use it as a
healing item
so good
[Music]
wait a second
I can dance Veil
start something fun
if we're gonna like you know use her as
bait anyway
man when I look at her
see near her summer
[Music]
Count On Me
what are we gonna do we could we could
you know attack this worm as well
[Music]
hit 41.
um
don't let the worm kill her first
oh
the crit is good but are we going to hit
still have a reset you know
we want to see
[Music]
look at cataclysms
so
how's that look again
why do I have to stand
I can't get both right
yeah 100
but not that much damage okay let's
let's try
um
and if it doesn't work we could
cataclysm
[Music]
oh it's okay I mean even if if her
attack takes out the whole HP bar I
don't mind
doesn't matter
it's fine it's fine
oh is that you said that what oh we got
a dialogue the hell is younger than you
are good baby
are you
related to bill you know that
is my youngest sibling
and Littlest sister I had many sisters
and many brothers
most of them have been killed
in
father disposal failed too
I think about that it makes
it like
to stand by my sister
always
[Music]
and Ally
a friend she's that important to you
look too much like her
it bothers me I'll defeat you now
whoever you are
you are not my little sister you're
right
I'm not your little sister
still
I'm glad I was here with you to
hear all of that
sister
Now kill it
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
that bgm is [\h__\h] banging yeah yeah
wow wow
[Music]
you can't move if I do this right so if
I take a step back after he's [\h__\h]
can he not move for a whole turn
was that was that how oh watch out for a
little sarash ooh am I in range
oh yeah here oh yeah
he still has one true
[Music]
she's in the range too now he can help
not much though
[Music]
which color
she's got X
X good maybe no red
blue green blue lots of blue actually
Lance
why Lance guys this is a good against
the world
it's blue for Kyoto blue blue for evil
Wawa
Lance breaks sword I was more hoping for
help with the worm though
to be honest
but okay
you will be mine
[Music]
give me something good
okay
[Music]
no you could continue that bgm that one
was good too should I just go for it
it breaks her but
[Music]
um
but then
help me for this turn
should I keep the fabrication away
yeah right
[Music]
he can walk pretty fast and he's not in
range here
but what if he dies from the worm
[Music]
it doesn't matter you can bait the rash
oh I guess yeah he'll also be a [\h__\h]
and then and then first thing I do if
this guy survives the worm uh is I'll
I'll break her and then I'll go with
everyone
[Music]
whether it uses a bait and damage
um
the guy's the best
[Music]
because it's right
one percent
okay
he would survive the Worm but he only
does one damage
could I just let him stand here
laughs
[Music]
okay hi look at me
look at me
wait no no no no no no don't attack
um what to do about the worm
ma'am
ignore it you finish map next turn
believe it okay
what should I
[Music]
because the worm will go for fogado
maybe just make a dragon vein here at
least
[Music]
range
not range okay
put yunaka in range of the boss
you can debug her what just by standing
there what
I'm gonna
I only have she attacked well then I'm
not gonna do that
okay okay
torrential Rolla
all right well the rest
oh up here there's still something going
on
who can who can deal with this
[Music]
Ivy ivy please help
hey
no what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
what
what what
[Music]
Lobby had just decent damage too
heal okay
he he can't he doesn't have a healing
staff anymore
[Music]
laughs
foreign
four
that's a decent damage
I went uh
that's not too bad and we don't get any
damage back
need help so I think for now
[Music]
this is the best I could do
and then we'll see what else
office itself to me
[Music]
with perfect poise
how much damage does she take
quite a bit
I want to use my killing Edge
even though it doesn't do much
on its own
spare actually pretty good spare is the
best for
basic damage here
but 41 percent
but her damage is only two
what
second ivy can kill now
go American help with chain attacks yeah
spare
okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah
it's okay I'll take the damage
attack
bring on
now Ivy could be okay alone
Ivy could do it I think
[Music]
yep
should be no problem
[Music]
nothing left of you
okay uh
uh where do we stand
here
quietly oh wait oh
I can stand
Ard
[Music]
thank you
oh [\h__\h] should have used his uh healing
potion oh well okay and for them
we're just gonna stay here I think
unless I wonder
oh no
um wait
and
wait
worm oh goes from fail
oh
absolutely perfect because that way
[Music]
they wasted it
so wasted oh wait ah
[Music]
don't say anything
why'd you guys not
[Music]
say anything
but if I would have put them here
wouldn't would they have been in range
I can still change it a little bit
probably
I was busy cooking
whatever
wow okay now
we should be able to take her down she
only has one HP bar left
she'll be sure we start with Veil right
can I can I can I oh
maybe I can't
okay
it's very confusing right now
she can't stand here
the worm is in the way
let's let's try
a chance
[Music]
you made it this far hmm
you should be on
she's flirting with my illusion
he did it he broke her
oh stop
a con a con
I just I can't
oh he can't do anything either
God damn it you swearing this worm this
shitty ass worm whatever ignore the worm
[Music]
what
why
[Music]
can it really be
this easy
my sense that you are looking and
staring
you will not win that way you are
very scared
yes of course The Knockout can pass
through what can be scared from the
start of all this it's only natural
scared of losing battles losing what's
important to me oh they're getting
losing people I care about all the
important dialogues
I am jealous of you you have my face but
you say the things you feel
out loud I am not allowed to show Fear
if I say I am afraid
I will be able to defect if I follow
orders I don't think
I am like the corrupted
it's like the corrupted two having a
little crisis
killed many of them
[Music]
no they will kill me in time
you don't die
I'm proof of that but when you are did
you say is she deleting herself but
killing was that I guess we're not
really killing her we're leaving here at
1hp this is like looking in a mirror but
if you think about it if we were
actually finishing her off
wouldn't that be the end of future Wawa
but yeah we have left other other
enemies that we
supposedly kill also keep on coming back
so we leave everyone at one HP I guess
yeah time Paradox that's what I'm saying
oh well it's a problem
big big problem
Okay who wants to go next plan you wanna
call
oh wait now uh no I put Kiana in the way
oh
wait
dot dot
okay who should I let attack next
connect can't reach I should dance
connects
because I think she could do big damage
[Music]
wait I can
a little bit
stay there panette stay there
I think the AOE dancing will result in
me just
um
[Music]
dancing for one
no wait ah
[Music]
in that case let me go back
because that was an accident
which one was the one I used
chicken
ah well I mean I mean I mean
or should I even okay as long as I stand
here maybe
what do we do
thank you
emblem engaged to have to engage
engage attack okay
um but I can't
encounter
it doesn't change wherever I put Kiana
[Music]
what can I do that
no
um
[Music]
laughs
okay
I could even finish this one off now
can she do it from here
no because I wanna catch her back just
in case
that I won't dance for myself
huh
oh that was enough okay
[Music]
next let's go
we miss Maybe
[Music]
I went maxed out my uxp
IAL so
[Music]
crispy
not crap
they're so nice to me
try again
next time try harder but
[Music]
um
tag dance
please grant me your strength
let the lesson begin he wouldn't have
reached into biliff's dance rage range
it's a cross shape
[Music]
that's why I was like well okay
I will not lose
who wants to finish can you do it again
Hortensia
yeah okay
yeah okay what wait what
oh that was the last one oh I thought
that was one more speed bar oh dispose
of me oh
okay I'm in oops
[Music]
wait I could have gotten somebody's feet
from the worm
boots on herself really boots boots
[Music]
what
what why not something
okay permanently sure but hey
eleven turns hmm
These boots are made for walking that's
just what they do
and with this boots I'm gonna walk all
over you
two hours I think damn
yeah there were some MVPs
but yeah let's go
yeah I kind of done a lot which is okay
hmm
oh my nose fight was fun
I had no issues in the end I was just
um
you know trying to do it
in a smart way
potato
but that
that illusion
um
Lancer
oh my God I can't believe
he survived and he broke her which was
actually so helpful
that was so helpful
berries where is this um
I guess I'll adopt a cats because okay
hold
yeah the fabrication
Lancer crazy
um
[Music]
now where is this other thing that they
talked about oh they're also I see a cat
where's the deer or whatever
they said there would be
maybe only next time when I like do a
what I call those training maps
Maybe
oh I got unlucky damn what do the deers
bring you
good we broke the fell Dragon shard
I only hope the old me is going to be
okay we were able to provide some
healing meet me the old you will awaken
soon that's really really the old you
saw us in the past though
do you think that's
going to cause any problems it should be
fine I do forget everything yeah okay
eventually
oh that's right
wait is that are they setting up for
something here
it seems we finished just in time
I guess this is goodbye to the Past land
around us is starting to change it
really never sees up here again well but
thanks to her help we can keep biting
and we will she sacrificed her life to
help us get here
we have to go on and stop sombron you're
right goodbye my old self when you begin
your Journeys did we make a paradox I
hope your travels are as wonderful as
mine
and yet they are not that is very odd
perhaps the battle moved elsewhere
sensed an unexpected emblem and wanted
to see it for myself
but I sense nothing now I'm surprised
you came my Lord
it spins sometimes since you ventured
outside
[Music]
I didn't
I know that that emblem no longer is
I will go back to the temple after the
battle concludes my child will return
with news your children are endlessly
impressive
what I wouldn't do to have such loyal
subordinates if you require some of
those then just do what I do
make children
of my own
family is function and utility you put
blood in you get loyalty out
my children owe me their lives their
love their he just uses them as meat
Shields basically family
what a revelation
I would like to wait
with you you
have a child with me please Lord sombron
this is not the time
but I will consider it after the war
after my ambitions are served right
right
did we
change out the rate of time
and somehow that's why they're having
this conversation or would they normally
have had this conversation
so now there's gonna be when we go back
there's gonna be a new character
who is the baby of these two
what's what I understand my Lord no
change to help you achieve your
Ambitions I expect your utmost well he
blew her off for for real
[Music]
child
how intriguing what would that be like
okay so she never ended up getting one
through such unconditional love but this
is where she started my mother and
father regard me hoping for it with this
love
oh if only I could travel to the Past
that's why she was loyal to heaven
now perhaps I should find Lord sambron's
child
what was that one called oh why bother
he disposes of them all
one must never ever grow attached that
would just make me sad
um
but then even thousands and thousands of
years later when she's still loyal to
him
are we floating
you there are you all right
looks really floating goodness
[Music]
I feel so loyal to him
I found you lying here Mommy
afraid you might have been dead what a
relief
you were just in a terrible days oh
what's that
a dream a dream I met someone who hurt
my face
but
who also looked like you wait aren't we
a doctor and blue eyes are beautiful
head
that too that sounds like a lovely dream
say
chili yeah
when I was mixing our trainers now let's
get you somewhere nice and warm
do you think you can stand
thank you
what is the first time for this is that
how I switch sides
your being
kind
really
I'm
sorry to hear that
what is your name child oh
my name mother told me
this was before she died
father called me that name
just one
what's your name
I'm Lumera I know that name
it's the name of the last Divine Dragon
still alive the name of Father's enemy
if you are the Divine Dragon then I have
to kill you come on don't
father will call me a defect and dispose
of me
but you are kind to me
I don't want to kill you oh I am
thinking a thought that doesn't belong
I am what I am
[Music]
do you expect do you affect the effect
don't say that there's nothing defective
about you but I must do my duty
or else
father will dispose of me he'll feed me
to the corrupted
[Music]
to leave
tomorrow
and the day after that then let's keep
today between us
I don't want you to die how about this
let's meet again soon for a nice long
kind talk
five seconds
all right
mm-hmm
[Music]
we made it back to think we actually met
zephia and you in the past
it was I have to admit chilling the
barrier is weaker than before it worked
now we just need to break the last shard
let's demolish that thing where is it at
one moment
let's see
what's wrong you look worried oh it's
nothing don't tell me we gotta go to
some other weird place no
it's right here in gradland
what yes
sorry
I'm a little tired
could I please be alone for a bit we've
pushed you so hard relying on your power
to detect this did we change something
after all
Orange
it's not from the chocolate though
um
we'll be able to break the last Shard I
know we will how can I tell them who's
there guarding it
or why I'm able to sense
there
oh
no no not the egg
plot twist
Oh I thought you meant plot twist in
this story
yeah we did one out of the three maps
that we still have to do
Supreme
tomorrow one second I'll go idle meeting
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
no I saw this movie running somewhere
but no no chunky no smoothie
[Music]
okay thank you for waiting
you were jammed alrighty
time to clean this place up again
I won
for you eggs eggs milk milk
[Music]
of course
how are you doing
[Music]
my cat arrived oh
good cat
huh
it's fine it's my ritual
[Music]
I have to I have to take the items
and also like steel always needs Steel
[Music]
like those kind of things
even now
the upgrades
could could be always helpful
[Music]
I mean horse manure I don't know when I
ever was gonna use that thanks game for
throwing [\h__\h] in my face
thank you I appreciate it
but the other things the other things
are surely useful
[Music]
it would feel empty
sure sure
[Music]
I like how narasama like instead of oh
dear she seems to like using old poo
because that's how she used it yesterday
[Music]
in that context right
instead of oh dear this is oh cool and I
was like
who says it like that
who does that oh let's look into into
the well
I can't see what the well has for me
mirror does
me sometimes really really
[Music]
the books
those are as people's right
[Music]
oh
not what I was hoping for but okay
another Loom I also don't need a loom
how about I throw
the illuminum there
is no
no
[Music]
not in this
I feel like fun on my tent
nah
nah nah nah
[Music]
none first days of one two three oh okay
well a frozen one maybe that helps
[Music]
sorry we've been reading things I was
tagged up
foreign
[Music]
okay
oh wait my Chat is dead on my side what
the hell
[Music]
actually yesterday too I protect
completely
um
left me
in the dark
to die because I was having a chat open
with Hyper chat
and I saw sometimes on my OBS window the
chat
was like completely different from what
I saw in my actual hyper chat
and I noticed that the hyper chat window
was way behind and lagging super laggy
I guess it was even for hyper chat
yesterday was a bit of a challenge
um
yeah and even even on OBS it looked a
little bit iffy a little bit to me but
I had some problems with it lately too
um
Kanto has been working on an overhaul
it was laggy for me too yesterday
do we like that sometimes
um
yeah no yesterday yesterday yo I I
honestly did not expect
genuinely
did not expect so many people to come
and watch this
I really didn't
and honestly that made me extremely
nervous 15K no I saw even 60 16k was the
peak on my side but oh my God
um
I think
you know I was I was seeing that and
then I was also wondering oh man twitch
I was feeling really worried about what
Nero's audience would think of me
uh
and I think that really influenced like
also because I I'm not used to having so
many viewers and every time that happens
like also with the Easter stream and
other recent times whenever I have
more viewers than usually I I crumble
these days
I just crumble
[Music]
is that mysterious you know I wasn't
saying the twitch I just saw the twitch
chat in some of the clips it's okay go
in the next one sometimes
I saw it in some clips and it seemed
okay but I don't know ah I was hilarious
I wanted to leave a good impression but
I was so nervous and I obviously could
have done better but it was my I said it
in the beginning that as a warning that
I don't know how I'll do talking to an
AI
because it's really unusual obviously
it's not something I normally do it's
really something
you gotta have a show for you link get
used to hmm
and you never know what how she's going
to
what she's gonna say how she's going to
react
and
yeah so it was actually for me really
difficult
to bounce off of her relax because she's
like a human this should be funny
she doesn't you know you cannot assume
that she makes any sense
you cannot rely on her talking with
reasons and stuff like that
whoa and once the body looked
entertaining thank you yeah I tried my
best but really I I could have done
better but I mean this was the first
time and
man the pressure
[Music]
the pressure was off the roof
I was I was really hoping for it to go
well and yeah I don't know
I had fun though
I had a lot of fun but
get them I wish I could have been less
nervous about it
hmm
I was trying to be funny I was trying to
make jokes
all the time I didn't know where I was
going with my sentences because it's so
difficult because I was trying to speak
without breaks in between so that
doesn't leave me with time to think
about what to say you know what I mean
so I was like rambling and rambling
I wasn't sure where I was going but I
knew I had to end the sentence somewhere
but I couldn't if I ended I have to end
it confidently I can't end it and then
wait two seconds and then continue
talking because that will mess it up I
have to end my sentences confidently
um
it was so difficult
so difficult
one of your funniest collapses really
thank you
but I was keeping so many things in mind
like not to talk over her and not to
um
not to you know take these breaks when
talking and stuff
um
I definitely what do you mean just talk
less I talked so much less
while still trying to give something of
value to the collaboration
[Music]
no yes I did
I didn't even interrupt her and I always
waited after she uh after I said I
always waited for the you know those
awkward moments I always did
hmm
and it felt like an eternity every time
yeah they were killing me inside they
definitely were they felt much longer
than you know afterwards when watching
it watching a clip or generally watching
clips of people collabing with neuro
when you watch it it doesn't feel so
long but you know when you're sitting
there and waiting
and you don't know what to do in those
moments it feels like it's
inside
yeah
oh
you handle yourself pretty well wow
thank you
yeah thankfully the clips cut out all
the awkward silences
thank God
waiting for the answers was funny too
really
I liked there were many good moments
though I think like the one where I said
it's a bird eats bird world and she said
no I think it's they went other way
around I'm like oh it's the Bird eats
bird world
or the um they agreeing with me and
she's like no they agree with me and I
said no they agree with me and then she
says no should they agree with me
that was funny yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah the loops so funny
what am I looking for wait do I not
happen oh
oh I don't have
a second steal
[Music]
okay
I'm tired
I thank you
do we have I'll buy another one I feel
like we have another one we need then
do come again I am vegan
vegan not good
oh I can do that do you guys agree with
that oh yeah Twitch account that was
funny too like she came up with such
nonsense but I mean
quiet it was somehow it somehow made
sense and then again it didn't make
sense
rip fauna
send her that clip
um what's on Dance the usually best
choice okay
[Music]
scroll cake funny
oh no what
[Music]
happened
it's James he actually registered us no
no she didn't I don't think so but I
probably should make myself a Twitch
account
because one thing I've noticed
um
numerousama has a lot of European
viewers and it made me think maybe the
reason why I have yet to really
accumulate a proper European fan like a
big following viewers
on YouTube could it be that
be that viewers they all just like
they're all on Twitch and they all
prefer twitch
because I've been streaming during these
Prime Times of European Prime terms for
a long time now
and I wonder if it's just that they
they're all on Twitch so they have yet
to really notice me
most of them
[Music]
sure there's some on YouTube of course
of course
well I wonder if most of them are on
Twitch
yeah I was thinking maybe
can stream sometimes on twitch after all
I didn't consider that until now maybe
my German stream should be on Twitch you
know
where the [\h__\h] is the second seal huh
can she not use it was it supposed to be
a master sale huh where's the second
sale
[Music]
it's here
oh God
oh man
yeah but the vods
can you re-upload the fonts on YouTube
is that allowed
as long as you're not a partner on
Twitch should be fine no
what am I doing
[Music]
wind worm right
I had second seals anyway
I know I know I know two platforms
but if you're not a partner on Twitch
can I think you're allowed to do
simultaneous streams as well though
from what I I think I know
um
[Music]
we just said that okay I said that too
open at also 20.
[Music]
marijuana yeah mirror
mirroring My Stream literally
[Music]
they're producing any of them games
well I mean I used to play more
Minecraft to Minecraft's always good
no and I mean other things like
collaborations like Mario Party and
stuff like that and I don't see a reason
why that much hold me back you know
should be popular but whatever I mean I
wouldn't count that though
I don't know I mean
I I think I think
I will stand by my game tour I mean
no I that's why I want to end by them
I'm with you here like I want to end
volume because I know this is not good
for my Channel right now I am very aware
of that it's been dragging out and you
know I I see that but I can't just leave
it at episode 8 or so just because it's
not doing well no no I'm not gonna do
that
no
if I reason why I get so many uh jrpg
sponsorships is because I play JRP jeans
and I'm a good well person for
sponsorships good promoter but if I
wasn't playing all these jrpgs I
wouldn't be getting these sponsorships
so honestly I'll take it because
sponsorships
they can be good money so
I I like to be the first choice for jrpg
sponsorships I'll gladly take it and if
that comes with shitty views on games I
love to play done okay
all seems like a good Exchange
um
yeah and I'm it's not like my my streams
are constantly only this I mix it up
like it's not it's not as bad as people
like to make it out uh to be
I play like different things too like
now okay now we have passport 2 for
example also I'm planning to play like
Thief Simulator for some reason next
week because it was on sale
um
I'm here for the kiwala thank you
I'd rather see you play what you want to
play thank you
Thief simulator yeah
I'm planning to play it next week
because I bought it already
yeah well now yeah every once in a while
you know status buyer also that's not
something you have to like you know be a
long time viewer for and know what
happened last time
I don't know you know there's there's
plenty of these things and
oh
I don't think it's as bad as people
try to
paint it as
you know my the balance of my channel
there's so many shooting stars here
um
is that the bander
welcome
can you cook I don't remember
foreign
but I have to take the crap because it's
better
unfortunately
no do not expect too much of me update
on the weather outside
it's happening next week inexcusable
it's happening I'll make my schedule
tomorrow in advance
what foul flavor
I'll make it tomorrow
I have most things in my head but
City oh my God this is bad and I will
that just give me minus stats no right
no maybe it did maybe it did
yeah break that tomorrow
plus one strength oh okay break day
tomorrow and I'll be preparing the
schedule
[Music]
I think we can go already is there
something important I need to do
oh wait there's some new weapons that I
have
um I think was there an ax I think there
was an ax a zip code for Pinette
other than something else she has Maybe
I mean
[Music]
uh
cannot follow up or strike first
should I bring this
oh yeah Andrea I wanted to do that too
yeah
basically a great ax
[Music]
only use for engage in Tech in my
opinion oh
what would I replace it with the silver
ax
I guess I haven't been using the silver
ax much mostly I've been using
Kayla Brave and sometimes the hand ax
because
it's useful
[Music]
yeah the crit on the revenge is really
high
got those two
yeah I think I guess the probably the
silver ax
more useful on Jade
[Music]
she always does plenty damage I know
wait do we have anyone else who uses the
ax that we bring along all the time I I
don't think so
currently no
I guess I'll give it to her we'll see
how it goes
and then a ball was there a ball
which would have to be for Alquist
steel ball Maybe
[Music]
oh I mean
you know the way they show the stats
it's really confusing me
we keep the we keep the class humble we
don't need the mini ball
and we don't need the mini bulk
[Music]
um
I'll never use it
you will see if I get rid of it now next
time next map will be like [\h__\h] why
didn't I bring the mini bowl
Kosovo up to five plus five
one look I can but okay okay I'll get
rid of the mini bow
I was just making fun of the enemies
that didn't have a mini ball
hmm
ah you can't upgrade the dessert weapons
they're pretty good on their own at
least maybe not in late game that much
but
bow here
okay let's upgrade the land about Loop
oh I can't I have no [\h__\h] silver but
let me switch
I want silver please
I will give you
um iron
[Music]
no
four
one fellow
then I can upgrade it to plus one
[Music]
I'm saying 11 sword
yeah would be good in theory
in theory that would be good
[Music]
oh
no no need now
[Music]
I'll be here
I don't know nothing do I even have
space in the inventory though
maybe instead of slim sword I haven't
been seeing myself using the slim sword
so I have 11 sword though
[Music]
yeah I mean the Dodge is pretty good but
unusually accurate
I only have one eleven swords is there
any other ranged sword
that exists in this game
[Music]
I guess not
okay I Gotta Buy 11 sword
it I get a long range sword for Kiana on
the next mission
is that the one you mean nephe
well then okay I'll just
I guess I'll wait for that one
specifically for me yeah okay
I'll take that
[Music]
oh martial arts like flashing fist art
for Keanu
all right I'm ready
we cannot waste time today
[Music]
what new healing said oh no I didn't I
guess I still can right
where the [\h__\h] are we going
here
[Music]
item Shop Hold Up
let me see
[Music]
okay he needs one
he can have oh I could give him a
recover
[Music]
she still has a little bit on the physic
but I'll change it to the one that has
four
this one
then she still has the other one so
she's good
um Celine has a one mend
[Music]
I don't know let me buy a new one for
her
Maybe
change meant for treat
hmm okay
[Music]
didn't I give that to someone
maybe not
[Music]
and that's fine saving some money that I
don't need to save
[Music]
um
meant
okay
foreign
[Music]
really
that's good
I'm gonna eat the kiwi while they're
talking
each so the last fell Dragon Shard is
here and grad lawn Temple yes
what's wrong Veil you don't look well
did you need more time to rest no it's
not that spooning the kiwiwi
I have a request please let me go in
alone I'll destroy The Shard and come
right back
I can't let you what is she hiding it's
too dangerous trust me you won't want to
face what's ahead it's best that you and
our friends stay here yes Cuts halter
eating spare you from this from what I
don't understand
oh is that you
mine is you isn't it mother oh my dear
child
how I've longed to see you again when I
sensed you I flew here as fast as my
wings would carry me it can't be what
how I've missed you so much fake don't
cut any closer to find dragon oh
corruptor rather corrupted Lumera
just when I finally had a moment with my
child I didn't expect this I thought she
would stay inside with The Shard Phil
did you do this no it was Papa the Rings
gave him the power to create more
elaborate corrupted he took her body
from lethos as one last line of defense
for the shards he knew didn't you you
knew this had happened so now we have to
kill her
they also knew that we couldn't help her
the emblems have used their Miracle they
could revive one person and they chose
you there's no other way to save someone
who has been corrupted really you're
saying that there's no choice
we have to face her you don't have to do
anything sister
oh man it's chilly out here why not come
inside you want to break The Shard don't
you oh don't worry I won't bite
I just want to have a nice long chat
mother
she's baiting us
I can scarcely believe it Queen lumero
my face stretch what should we do we
have to defeat her there's no other way
but
I don't know how I'll summon the
strength I feel conflicted myself
she was my deity now I have to fight her
yeah
some people
's people are religious but we love
Queen Lumera too
we can't falter
if we do that's it the world is doomed
guys go don't be so
dramatic about it she's obviously fake
the door
it won't open let me take a look
hmm
spell has been cast on it from inside
curious
she invited us in wait
where is Lady Vale
she didn't go inside did she what
no she can't go in there all alone
Vale open the door
call door rail holder
oh forgive me for this oh goodness did
you come to see me all by your lonesome
your own child shouldn't have to strike
you down
how heroic of you
I'm glad we have this chance to talk
Vale
from what I've heard you are the little
sister of my dear child if that is the
case I am practically your mother as
well you are welcome to call me your
mother should it please you
thank you for the kind offer
but I don't need a second mother in my
life
I had one oh
oh hearted is she tell me what was she
like
she was kind and affectionate
and there was so much love within her
but she died before I could truly
appreciate what I had
she always did the best she could to
keep me safe and she told me that if
Papa ever broke free
if he did and if he started doing
terrible things
as his family I had to find a way to
stop him
I suppose that means you intend to
murder me yet again
yes
oh I tremble at the memory of them it'll
blow the pain even worse than the pain
though how you left my heart shattered
I was torn from the side of my beloved
child can you imagine he's doing improv
my agony and had it not been for you my
dearest and I would have been together
for all right
now it's my fault the fact that you died
all of this
even though
I was a puppet
killed you I stole the Rings my actions
led to this
you can hate me all you want
but either way
oh
[Music]
oh Vale was that meant to hurt
as I'm sure you have noticed thanks to
Lord sombrons largesse I am far more
powerful pranked before 100
shame really I honestly hope that you
and I could get along
but anyone standing between me and my
child cannot be suffered to live
it's ludicrous to think you might murder
me for a second time how are you so
blind I still owe you a death for the
first one
die you little defects
[Music]
damn that's a character change
it in goodness you're all right
the door should have been blocked
how
broke through
[Laughter]
oh my child this is your mother so badly
I did
not a day has passed that I didn't think
of you that's why I'm angry to see you
like
this
hasn't sambron ruined enough why do you
speak ill of Lord sombron it was he who
brought us together again Lord sombron
you are lost aren't you oh I was
during the war a thousand years ago I
was desolate lonely
I had no one my mother father friends
killed
yet I had to fight on
if I the Divine Dragon gave up or ran
away
the world would be lost in the midst of
all that hurt
I found you innocent and pure no evil
intentions of your own
and never treated with love though you
were my enemy
I couldn't bring myself to kill you
instead
I bonded with you the day we first met
I stopped being alone mother I beg you
don't leave me on my own again
stay here with me no
I can't do that the last time we spoke
you told me to fight on with divinity
told me to bring peace to the world no
matter what Memories returned don't you
remember mother
who cares what I said before now I want
to be together the Austin is carrying
this so hard you don't think like my
mother
you don't want what she wanted you're
speaking nonsense
I'm right here I am your mother no
my mother
the one I wanted to see again the one I
loved shut up
and she would want me to defeat you
she taught me to stand strong against my
every opponent whoever they might be how
sad your words make me
you're breaking my heart right now
against me
the emblems the stewards
that's sister of yours I suppose I have
no choice but to kill them all prepare
for battle
sorry we meant to fight this battle for
you thank you Val
isn't your burden to carry
it's mine if I don't face this myself
I can't claim to be the Divine dragon
and emblem
or mother's child let's do this together
then we can face somborm at last
you're crying everyone at the ready
let's go
will free Mother's soul and break the
final shard
ah let's go
they didn't even show her crying face
lame
[Music]
oh no that's huge
that's a huge map
what we start off in two completely
different sections
mm-hmm
let's see
we are here they are here
we go left
then we go up
pretty normal looking enemies I mean the
wolf Knights are not nice but
then we have a worm but both sides have
a worm so we need Ivy I would say on one
side
Panet on the other side
okay the doors have to be opened
[Music]
and then we meet in the middle no no no
let's put my worms there well and that
can take care of them
there is two chests
or add plenty of charging plates
two more here
wolf nights with the wolf Knights
if I just walk by straight
[Music]
no they'll come for me right
even though we're not in range
will probably come for me
[Music]
don't take too long on this map
there's not a time limit here too is
there
definitely take your time plenty of time
to wasting this
duality
this map is actually difficult if you
don't rush ahead
huh is there like lots of
lots of units joining in later let me
take a fruit candy actually
infinite reinforcements
[Music]
rush but I still have to kill everything
I mean that's what I I kill what it is
in front of me and then I move on I mean
I can't just walk past them
[Music]
because then it'll attack me from behind
you know and that's not good either so
hmm
okay I have brown
[Music]
could I
should I switch
Chloe
[Music]
maybe Tamara
would be a better choice because
Chloe is more vulnerable just by being
on a horse applying horse but color can
heal can most Chimera able to heal
[Music]
no
um
okay mayor has a lot of Defense
[Music]
you love both sides
I think I do have
you learn both sides so we have Celine
Celine and Chloe together would be fine
if Chloe doesn't die
um
I have a Hortensia
and more beer hmm
[Music]
but why her tombs are fine
you need warp for sure
first don't put glowing range of bows
and silver great access again Kiara okay
we'll try
I don't know what tone she can use I
gave the Nova tone to
Vale I think no yeah yeah
today's my birthday say something wow
that's kind of rude
but I'm I'm just gonna assume you didn't
mean to be rude
um
language barrier I assume
laughs
happy birthday to you
uh side
awake you
you don't you don't want to be rude
right
happy birthday
I wish you all the best
um
[Music]
I guess that was funny
yeah there's just one man
is missing come on
again with the magical word please
[Music]
okay I don't know
maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe
no way that's just I'm just switching
healers then
yeah they'll be fine I'll see though
probably
a little [\h__\h] ton of ax uses down there
ah a man
[Music]
it's probably fun hello Raiders hello
welcome
[Music]
thank you for raining
I guess I'll start but I'll say first
[Laughter]
fight
I guess
you should warp them all to one side
eh
really
[Music]
but then
it would take up like five rounds or so
unless I give a lot of people that stay
that
yes really well then I have to restart
ah Mikaya what
Mikaya
wait but the Mikaya is
what
she so she needs the warping
safe right
I mean
[Music]
okay and then I think we have to restart
though
what did you do
[Music]
whatever whatever
accident
uh
[Music]
hurry try
you complain about the website I'll
definitely simplify things but no I'll
try it does that mean that the right
side will just stay where they are the
holes if I bring the right side to the
left side for example
will they really just stay
[Music]
Hotel
trained
uh ivia
she's got the whoop
[Music]
gonna open the warp whoop whoop whoop
ass can
[Music]
huh
it's a joke
okay maybe instead of uh
[Music]
it's not physical I guess
and she has two physics
Maybe
I mean
okay let's do it like this
it's dog
okay okay which side is easier I wonder
does she have to stand somewhere
specific to do that
don't remember
left left side easier okay so bring
right side to left side
no no no no no I am so stupid
[Music]
hmm wait what how does it look wait oh
wait
warping is like you bring the ones
around you to someone
so she's gotta be on the right side
and then a rescue stuff
aha
[Music]
oh
Chloe
I choose you because if we're gonna be
in one group anyway
then I don't necessarily need you as a
Healer and after using the rescue I
guess you could go for the Convoy
to switch back to a healing one I think
[Music]
oh wait can she not use a rescue but she
can use a reward why does the rainbow
work
uh teleports the user
[Music]
then I guess
how about her
she can do a rescue
[Music]
um
teleport a far away Ally to an adjacent
space okay
we have rework yeah I drew
should I just give her the rewarp
into um
potencia
to five spaces
okay
[Music]
my wife
my beloved wife
I will not leave you alone over there
I could never
don't worry
you're doing this for the greater good
I let her die we don't talk about that
she didn't really die
play a face okay
wow
[Music]
it's just a cross
huh
okay that's not true
so
I couldn't have done all all at the same
time anyway
on the target not the castle
mm-hmm
and I thought I could
um
have
[Music]
um who tend to do it first and then I
mean we can dance is
we can dance too
[Music]
um in that case
how about we yeah
I guess
[Music]
shall we
make a cool boss
[Music]
um
what a lovely scene
but then
okay Hortensia will stay on this side
for at least one turn right because even
if I dance myself then I have to
teleport sea doll away
I can't leave him alone here
[Music]
unless
ah wait
what do I have to stand here
huh
what
I thought I have to make a cross
but it has to be like
that's not how it works
was better before
[Music]
it was better before
ah
so much for should have been positioned
better
um
how are Blues in me
where okay if I move to lean away then
hopefully if she stands here I can
get this to work
[Music]
what oh
and you guys go
[Music]
here
hmm
he dances
and I mean should be funny if you just
stand there right
a nice Warp
and I bring them Tetris
foreign
let's get this party started
and let's get this party started
in here
[Music]
in this context there's no disrespect
lovely blue blah blah blah blah
[Music]
get started
ready for me
I'll do my best
fun song
in theory
[Music]
let's see when we have in the question
area
[Music]
what are your questions
do you have any plans on playing any
other championships other than
Bluff of the Wild
to or yakuzao this year
I'm in a parallel
[Music]
but I would like to play another yes
another Zelda game this year
um besides that you're not here did I
mention anything else
[Music]
good question actually
um
blue reflection neck Center blades nah
yeah if ever within this year if I ever
get a
permission to play you know certain game
should have talked about many drums
before
um
of course you missed I kind of saw that
coming I just wanted to try at least
could be raffle for God oh let's see
okay I would like to play you know Final
Fantasy and stuff like that ow
but
I'm so so hopeless
how did he not miss come on
all the pillars I am
huh
[Music]
can I believe I've been outclassed they
bullied her to death
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] why didn't they even go
for fogado at all
what
[Music]
the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
should I go back on time
[Music]
nicer better
um
[Music]
right here
here
oh my gold Mary
just go somewhere here
[Music]
in France
oh oh God damn it my friend
[Music]
uh
flying units are affected but wait horse
horse mounted course
my second rewind
was that was that my second Ray one no I
just started of course okay okay I'm
just making sure
[Applause]
[Music]
okay okay going for more beers
oh through the wall
[Music]
very realistic
but I like this outcome much more
beautiful whoa keep one wow with her
avoid damn she's not even in the fog
fog
they're all going for her let's go but
how did he how did he hit 29 eh
[Music]
yeah
where are they going
stop moving
and free Warp
when do we bring you
I'll bring her here
Divine Dragon cool class well of course
it's Gotta Be
It's gotta be
don't worry we should be fine there I'll
I'll I'll kill everyone now don't worry
I will I will I will
making space now
I'm sorry
foreign
he got everything he wanted
sick our foes are strong
okay standing in a perfect position for
him to do absolutely nothing to me
victory is mine have mercy
have mercy please
begging you for Mercy yeah yeah yeah why
won't you believe me yeah yeah I've been
begging you for myself I should have
moved her away so that the others could
attack from that tile
hmm
no need
pray Max too powerful
Were You Raised by Wolves
honestly peanut you look like you've
been raised by wolves so
you shouldn't be the one talking wet
Koala is on fire help help
okay got married time to take revenge
on the other timeline that happened
[Music]
oh
she's indeed Raised by Wolves there you
go
I'm dresses hurts a lot
name my target
your target is right here but
um
[Music]
heal the Wawa that helps
you know the other day I got that
massage right
two three days ago
I've been going to this massage place
now a couple times I've been there a
couple times and I've always I've always
been nice
and
uh-huh spending a lot of money on their
business right
and
oh 24 48 though
and I mean their massage isn't even nice
isn't even the bestest
uh
like it's kind of lacking here and
they're not gonna lie
and yet I still keep coming back because
it's the closest one
um but
[Music]
every once in a while they're kind of
like
rude weird especially last time
you know the previous day I I call I
make a reservation
and they're like yeah no problem on the
phone they're pretty nice on the phone
[Music]
um
so then I I arrived and I they on the
phone they said make sure to be like
like on on Time 100 on time I guess they
probably already had a reservation for
like after me
so I couldn't be late and I understand
that I get that
um
however
I arrived okay like like maybe 12
minutes early but I was like you don't
have to massage me right away I can just
wait here no problem oopsie but then the
lady that sees me she looks like kind of
perplexed
she doesn't even say hello she just
looks at me and then she walks like into
the back probably checking something and
she comes back
and she still doesn't really say hello
she just doesn't greet me properly
and just yeah opens the door to the
massage room is like
there
and then and then it's like
uh
weird
[Music]
because I just don't she just wasn't
great and then well I asked okay because
we didn't settle it for what we're gonna
do during the phone call
and she just doesn't even give a proper
answer
okay and then I I'm like whatever they
were often like this I guess
then I lay down
[Music]
I lay down
uh and she just starts without saying
anything she starts massaging she didn't
even bring the music normally they
always bring their phone and start
turning on some
Chinese sounding music
and just playing for their phone and I'm
like oh interesting and seriously
interesting you know but this time
it doesn't even bring the music so it's
just quiet she doesn't say hello she
doesn't ask where it hurts I say I say
you know they often just ignore me
completely my existence so I say oh
please um today focus on very strong on
the on the shoulders please
and she doesn't say okay she doesn't say
yes she doesn't say not even no sound
nothing
and I'm like okay oh my I hope she heard
me
um but yeah I was thinking else you
probably had a bad day so she starts
massaging me
and uh
I'm like
um
maybe I should you know ask she's okay
so I asked her how are you today
like are you feeling okay today I said
are you feeling okay and she said just
yeah
well while she's obviously not feeling
well something's pissing her off and I
wonder if it's me for coming too early
you know so I want to make sure
don't like the odds here
29.
[Music]
it's only the place was weird this is
the first time you talked about it I
wasn't really talking about the same
place though what did I say the first
time I went there
[Music]
understood okay oh perfectly perfectly
hand but we planned out everything
bad energy in in the bus leave I am in
the right ah
I wonder if that was the same place may
have been a different place
any lime I guess I'll Stand in the fire
with Ivy hmm it shouldn't be too bad
yeah and and so she says yeah but then
you know I kind of I'm like oh okay
because she doesn't doesn't even ask
back how are you like she's just
absolutely no concern for me or ah wait
I've ignored it that's okay
um
okay
I thought wow that's so rude like I know
that it maybe doesn't even have anything
to do with me but I'm like you're like
concerned about you know so give me a
chance be nice to me realize that you're
serving a customer here
and I don't know fix your behavior the
massage was all right this time better
than last time I had her
but yeah so in awkward silence continues
for a little bit
[Music]
um
and then
she then
fully elaborates a little bit
I didn't quite 100 understand
but it seemed like it was about
um
some planning like
one one of her colleagues probably took
the call
probably didn't properly write down that
uh I'm coming on this day
or it was about someone else
they wrote down the wrong day and then
she was like yeah you know we can't
do this and that if the information
isn't related so I realized okay they're
having some internal conflict here okay
but don't let it out on me like that
because even then when she explained it
she was like
you sounded you know again
angry
yeah can I attack from here
kind of wanted
it will make me have to catch up though
yeah
I can't believe I did that
imagine it was supposed to be her day
off
[Music]
yeah I don't know I mean she was there
yeah but overall it was just I mean at
least I understood it wasn't really
about me
but it just makes everything so awkward
if you bring you your mood
like this to work you know
I didn't check the percentage oh wait
wait good
and I already know you know I will not
be getting the same customer service as
I get in Japan when I go get a massage
it's okay I'm fine with that I've I I
know that's never gonna happen
but damn
customer service here is just so [\h__\h]
yeah and for the rest of the massage
there was just like it was a one hour
massage and it was just complete silence
because there was no music
and and no exchanges but anything at all
usually there maybe they at least say
Hello Maybe
uh just noises of me breathing strongly
because she's pushing me so hard into
the into the bed
that I'm having trouble breathing and
she's cutting oh many times she cut off
like my she was kind of like choking me
from above
I know this is starting to sound weird
but yeah
he's like massaging my my shoulders or
something I don't know somewhere that
also applied pressure to my neck somehow
who should I dance should I dance anyone
at all
because I don't wanna the others are
lagging behind
if I help I'll crisp
the dancer is gonna lie Beyond
[Music]
you're too kindly
I'm going to the right place more or
less more or less
yeah
I have been thinking about switching
massage place but this is the closest
end and I mean
it's not only that they're rude it's
also their technique often Isn't So Good
but is it worth
changing
because I don't know
there's not so many good places around
me I think
[Music]
I'm getting hungry
should have maybe warped some of them
okay
um
I may no longer have the emblem rings
but I can use the shards power instead
shall I show you
mother oh what are you doing everyone
get behind the pillars the [\h__\h]
fell Dragon Shard beam corrupted lamera
will use the power of the feldragon
chart to unleash a potent attack
a warning will indicate the beams last
don't move away to avoid significant
damage
anyway it's okay I didn't take it so
personally because I knew it wasn't like
she wasn't pissed because of me
she was just taking it out on me
but yeah I didn't feel so
personally affected by it it's okay I
just I just wish they were more
professional but
I can't move
a what
what why is Kiana unable to move what
did they do
Frozen the match
King made but at least she's just
right there not in the range of The
Shard attack thank God okay
but then you know I was a little bit
um reassured of the good in humanity
because afterwards you know I went to
the supermarket and there is this one
Supermarket where there's this one lady
pretty young looking pretty lady who no
matter where what day I come to this
um
to the supermarket
and what time she's always like smiling
she's always so nice I always see her
talking and having casual conversations
with the customers like she's the
cashier
yeah she's just so nice always she
always has this big smile and I don't
see that in any other
um supermarket
uh uh worker here they're all always
kind of like pissed off
understandable I mean surely it's a
an exhausting and maybe boring and maybe
not rewarding job a lot of the time
so I get it I get it put this lady like
damn respect I don't play nice
and like spreading so much positivity
and this time I went there
[Music]
I was just buying some stuff so I went
to the cashier and she was there again
and then it was pretty empty at that
time
[Music]
so we could chit chat a little bit
nobody was behind me
[Music]
and she like says something like
um
I don't know how we we got to this
point but she mentions that she's like
totally dehydrated
um and that's really bad for her because
she's pregnant and I'm like what
you're pregnant I don't even see that
you look you don't look pregnant like
you know side-wise
yeah I mean after she said it I guess I
could see it a little bit but she wasn't
like super super super close to getting
a baby yet I think
um
but yeah and I was kind of um
like worried about her so I'm like what
why like can you not get something to
drink
and she's like no I can't because I
can't leave from the seat but I also
can't
we're not allowed to have money with us
uh while we are
like you know
sitting here at the cashier we can't
have our money at the cashier
uh so she can't buy herself anything to
drink so I offer her well I can I think
maybe if you want
I can grab you something to drink no
problem
and she's like no no and I offered her
again and she's like no no no and I'm
like what but that's not like they can't
let the pregnant woman
feel so dehydrated and not get her
anything to drink not no help at all
what the hell that's like messed up
well what are these like working
conditions right
I was suddenly feeling like like I need
to help for justice
well the whole time even even when she
was saying all these things she was
smiling keeping up a positive attitude
and she said oh I'm done for the day
soon anyway
so I'm like oh okay
I mean if you really don't wanna
hmm hurry he's a true play yeah
I can't imagine that they have such
shitty
working require or environments you know
where if you don't have if you start
your shift at the cashier and you don't
have anything to drink there at the
moment then you kind of [\h__\h] because
you can get really busy and then for and
endless times you won't have anything to
drink
no
yeah but she should why why didn't she
why don't she prepare something to drink
for herself though at the beginning of
the day that's also my question but
I mean I don't want to blame her and
mostly I'm blaming the supermarket for
not giving her something to drink okay
[Music]
yeah kind of weird
don't know what's going on there
[Music]
don't fix and blame but I
I always have something to drink here
when I start my shift
[Music]
a drink next to them so it's not like
they're not allowed to have a drink next
to them it's just they're they can't
oh is that a dangerous spot for her
[Music]
I will back her up
um yeah so anyway in the end
um
oh God where do I put pseudo
in the end I just felt this positive
energy from her and that made me quite
happy oh wait come back on my perfect
time to Convoy
I want to go to the supermarket to that
one specifically more often just because
she's so nice
you're damn
why can't she be so nice
how can she be every day so motivated is
it the pregnancy but I don't know
I feel like I've been seeing her for
every once in a while for a while now
[Music]
she's always like this
so respect for the positive attitude
but also I understand if you can't keep
it up like that
that's
because she's always pregnant
but like I was thinking like especially
if you're pregnant
then even more respect for keeping up
that attitude because aren't you gonna
like I don't know feel
exhausted and all that because she was
saying she was getting a headache
from
uh not being able to drink anything
hmm
[Music]
even if I dance him he can't get much
more further ahead
[Music]
maybe she has a resting smiley face
maybe maybe
huh
I wonder how dangerous that is for Ivy I
guess we'll see
Walmart also had was also bad for cashes
because we were understaffed with like
40 person wins
um
I can only imagine because I was
at Walmart or was that the other one
that I was at in America and holy [\h__\h]
it felt like that place that Walmart
Target Target was in the middle of
nowhere
and yet it was packed and the lines were
endlessly long like we waited ages to
check out
um
I'm guessing Target is pretty similar oh
my God I-beam
to Walmart in that matter
hmm
that's just Target
really we didn't have it in Walmart
right target is a slightly fancier
Walmart oh
that's how it feels right now careful
for me are you right now like in the
cashier's job or something what how
would you be watching this stream
are you doing something like that now
you're working products in podcast mode
what what products
what do you uh put things in the shelves
oh fruits and veggies
stalking and stuff
it can work just like one section like
that because it must be a big
Supermarket because like we don't in our
supermarkets we don't have one person
just in charge of that area I never see
anyone in that area ever
Sundays are the worst ah you'll need to
live in Austria because we don't even
have anything open on Sundays you can
just rest on a Sunday
[Music]
doesn't that sound good to you
at least you have something to listen to
are you wearing like wireless earbuds or
something like that while doing that
no we don't stop we are prepared we know
that something is closed so I have food
here right now
but yeah it's annoying often thanks for
the crits wait what
oh yeah one mileage people okay okay I
was like what what
am I seeing things
oh yes nice
hope your day is soon over your work day
does anyone have a mend
this works
great help it just started oh no don't
worry I'm also still streaming for a
long time so at least you have
entertainment how are you typing put
down your phone
work work work
but oh yeah it's really nice I can
accompany you guys
link that I can imagine like without it
would be so boring often right
I can see that
[Music]
I'll use a treat
you have saved me
I fall asleep at work without with your
students ah way of my streams
don't you mean without my streams
that was bad
um
level up I think
no magic
where is the magic
[Music]
loving listening to you while working on
my homework can you even like think
though
while doing that I can't imagine
he are cute thank you
foreign
teachers drinking I listen to you when I
work thank you
thank you your voice is keeping my
sanity oh I'm happy to hear that
I drive so I can't listen to anything
but the engine
and me right
what what's going on one what what are
these
what are these numbers
why are the numbers confusing me so much
right now
why am I what what is this
ow
poor Ivy man
don't don't yeah the backless damage was
confusing
what since when was that a thing
okay well this really seems to be the
way to go to go to one side
I don't know
[Music]
foreign
going on
oh remember one thing I forgot to do oh
hi killing Edge thank you
one thing I forgot to do was uh doing
the tenet and pendrail
interactions God damn it I even wanted
it to do one day to do wanted to do it
because somebody in the chat was also
reminding me of it and I forgot those
pogato
unbelievable unbelievable
when do I ever do things right huh
[Music]
foreign
um
yeah I should still be able to do it
after the stream oh hello reinforcements
[Music]
hello
actually making this a little bit more
interesting thank you I appreciate that
[Music]
guys just wasting his staves what you
mean mavier
I know you mean them oh for breaking me
oh yeah oh oh I guess so
true
[Music]
no I didn't ask the cashier later
because she could she because she told
me I am playing
told me on her own
um
[Music]
fun
yeah
right she was so nice
just got the email YouTube took my
monthly money
oopsie forgot to cancel that
subscription again huh
oh it lives on layovers no phone no
music no eating while driving city buses
could you make my break so much better
[Music]
you drive city buses you're you're a
city bus driver
is that your job I can well I'm learning
about all your guys's jobs today
is that what you were saying
[Music]
happy bus driver
so much variety
yeah oh wow I wonder
that's a fun job
[Music]
that's like I guess I should play Bus
Simulator to find out
you're a Bus Simulator
um
I like bus I was raised in a city where
the main
um way to get around
was buses
[Applause]
[Music]
very comfy
I preferred bus over Subway
um
I mean for me
[Music]
Subway always has this kind of like
scary
atmosphere I feel like so I get what you
mean I think I also
a lot of the time prefer bus
but
you know Subway will take you to the
cold faster most of the time
you win some you lose some
I didn't even use my engagements
maybe I should
we should have maybe I should have given
away like a like a live stone for
example maybe I will because he's still
down there he can still do that now
though he needs to like lose those three
rounds in order to be able to use it
[Music]
I wait but uh Hortensia needs it and of
course she cannot stand on it wow
for real those
oh
three warp it's okay
should I open this one right now
yeah
why not
come on come and get me try me
um
[Music]
Excalibur what's going on where's the
Excalibur doing uh such a good job on
this map that's the second uh one hit
that I'm getting
this specific like well type of corrupt
it must be vulnerable to it
[Music]
that's me double her Channel
electric chicken
oh interesting
sounds complicated
[Music]
oh
cute teeth
whatever you ask
I will kill you now
good night
[Music]
now where to put Chloe
she's so squishy wow nice look nice
though
oh
big level up
[Music]
I'll be here
strength strength strength oh damn
[Music]
ow
yeah okay that one might not be wasted
because I'm broken that one goes for
meow meow meow meow
that's okay that's okay that's the only
one
of the huge damage does this pink stuff
do
[Music]
oh
these people are a little bit in trouble
not much oh okay
okay I can't kill
[Music]
20 40. oh my whole game
um
I'll can't throw away
oh kiwawa where's the one hit kill come
on
[Music]
where is it
I guess
engaged
no no no
I don't know your stock produce but meat
is one of my department so I definitely
stock my old camping don't think about
it don't think about it
assist
work without your brain
it won't hurt so much
[Music]
holy moly
rest now
week level up but at least it went to
Magic and HP
and I guess Ivy gets hit by the
attack
oh well
I'll course
we'll need to do some AOE healing I
guess which is fine I have plenty of AOE
Hills
oh lots of Stories of the fun cool
people and crazy people so it's never
dull I was raised on buses too is that
my job title yeah go get it
18 wheeler damn
yeah you can you can give yourself a go
I think um kfp
company bus driver
when we go on outings you're gonna drive
us
can we stop by McDonald's
man I am so proud of myself yesterday
again the second time in this week I I
resisted my urges of wanting to eat
like fast food and not cooking
and instead cooked
aren't you all so proud of me
[Music]
um
thank you I hope this is enough I wasn't
so bad that's the cooking process was so
easy this time
I just messed up on the on the
temperature
accidentally
let me bring the others first
[Music]
kind of weak physics oh well
tomorrow well yeah so the new stuff
comes on Tuesday and I buy
now yeah what I cooked yesterday was the
the last thing I think oh was there one
more meal
I cooked
no I think I
three times this week
properly
the other the non-meat thing
was the tortellini one right did I cook
that like on Tuesday or so probably
[Music]
I better stay out of it
I've already have so many in this oof
range
I wait
[Music]
um
is it go time
if he attacks he can counter but he has
to attack from here and then he can only
take two more steps which will mean you
still she's still in the pink area
[Music]
almost almost there
I wonder
there's no better way to do it
what gang oh good night thank you for
watching
oh robotics PhD damn
that sounds
also very high level
[Music]
or all Chloe finally doing something
some damage Patsy good night
guys I watched that vlog
you know the the Korean vlogger who made
that that really cool Vlog in Korea you
were beautiful made a Blog
about the
whole
you know off of line meeting with all
the cave people
in Japan as well
and damn
[Music]
more
of you guys there like non-japanese
people who traveled from outside and I
fought and and even a bunch of Japanese
ones
and I have to say
I I got teary-eyed like twice during
that Vlog like once when there was this
group picture taken I'd rather be
friends and then again sometime around
the end
oh forward only one step
I had a fire Maybe
yeah which was making me feel things
and then other was just one moment
um also very happy there was
um you know in Shinjuku there was this
advertisement right with all the whole
life members on it and and and he was
talking he found like some other fans
there
uh so he was like hey can I interview
you guys
he interviews them and asked them
there's like four four people there four
foreigners
he asked them who they're a fan of
and well one of them was a good fan but
the other all the all all of the other
friends they were quinoa fans I'm like
what
oh and they were I think all of them
were Europe European
I think and I wonder maybe one of them
was here in the chat now
[Music]
yeah they were probably part of the off
guy
those free kfp who are they I need their
names yeah one was Argentinian and what
what they said when they said quinoa is
she made me so happy
you know the guy was like ah because
she's cute because it seems a very
common reason but the Argentinian guy I
think especially about all of them they
all said such sweet things about why
they support me
I was so happy man
you don't even you don't understand
[Music]
it's nice to hear it like out loud as
well that makes it even stronger you
know
ah okay at least Veil come on stay out
of it
eh Who Am I Living alive
well that guy I don't know I guess
celine's gonna die
um we'll see I cannot rewind
tangent bruh no but are those three not
here
and Benny Della oh I have to remember
are they here in the chat
[Music]
there was the third one too though one
of them was me Whistler really
really I feel like that was a a bridge
oh [\h__\h] that hurt
because I'm not Invincible am I
imagining I feel like it was I'll
Retreat so I don't drink one Belgian one
Argentinian and one maybe one UK
oh
Penny was the one with Argentina
what do I do about fogado
sorry yeah maybe the one I'm thinking
was Belgian was Portuguese
leave him
no no forget oh
I guess where is she she's there are
they
are they ever gonna move up
these ones seem to be aiming for me now
but are they gonna go for me
that was me the Portuguese
yes chicken nuggets
wait what you were one of them but then
that's that's four people what
chicken nuggets
they will yes Harry oh [\h__\h] rash boss
[\h__\h]
[Music]
um
Destiny awaits
[Music]
maybe AOE dance or another warp would be
good
[Music]
at least Celine didn't die
good night I wasn't that off car it was
so fun to be around fellow Champions
I look like a lot of fun
I'm happy for you guys it seems like
such a sweet community
and really sweet of the
Japanese and Korean Bros you know for
organizing the advertisement and the off
collab and all that not off collab where
they're called love clubs off Kai but
off offline meeting
yeah yeah
my sweet chickens
so proud of them
is she okay
I don't think she's okay
oh I think I'll use a fortify
yeah yeah yeah
heals herself to the top and heals the
others oh right she gets healing from
healing others that's one of her
thingies
yay thank you guys
one clip of Ollie's seeing the
earthquake Clips oh yeah I think I saw
it
I think so
[Music]
I know she was like
you know
respecting us
pet
[Music]
s so I guess
can go up and make some start some
trouble here troublemaker
should I engage for my own protection
after this because she'll be
I can't clear the whole area
[Music]
can anyone join me ivy can join me
he can do a long bow attack at least
only on this one is really effective
what zero percent Hitchens what what
where Dooku
ah should I have engaged Plus alcrest no
I can I guess plus uh IV Maybe
the ones on the right took a look
[Music]
okay you saw zero percent there really
blah
the ones around me ooh dragon's fist
does a bit more
maybe I should just finish off the top
one ah
[Music]
Amber Slayer does pretty well on the
ones on the side
[Music]
prevent the fee from opening the front
door with people
[Music]
hmm
nah I think if I kill the top one at
least ivy can probably kill one of the
armored ones next to me
so then we'll have two dead instead of
just one
see that weapon
[Music]
anyway apparently there's still like a
whole block coming for your like the
other days
so I'm looking forward to that
the Vlogs are so well done and gives
like it it makes me it gives me the
possibility to look at it like from a
different POV
it's probably nice
thank you for doing that
and for traveling so far
everybody
[Music]
thank you and quickie if you guys are
curious
h-w-i-k-y look it up it's a really good
vlog
gives you a little bit of a
an inside
[Music]
um
we're between trouble down here as well
aren't we
um
[Music]
need to take the Archer down
do I get strong guys by if I engage
wolf spell
hmm
where's the explosion correction
mom
yes the one who went to the collab Cafe
yeah yeah
[Music]
don't say that like that
it's mean
how much do I have to rewind
to do that like the whole turn
[Music]
sit more of your downstreams and see
what happens
[Music]
it's okay it doesn't matter it's okay
oh great
where is fast
foreign
position
[Music]
now I'll be fine
I I'll I'll stand here
[Music]
I don't back down now can't be kissing I
saw that
should I implement it in my chat
how much damage let's go
let's go
oops
not much at all
you cannot have some kind of
kissing one already hmm
[Music]
y'all
Chloe please Chloe
[Music]
emblem engage
thinking of who to dance
right now
[Music]
then I think they can help me
maybe you see the hell and then he can
dance to one of the others
because I do want Veil
she's so cute
Free dances in the turn is not he
I am
okay let me see what Vale can do first
[Music]
okay
Nova kills let's go let's go
[Music]
what what
did she make what the [\h__\h]
she had 70 something percent I thought
that would be fine
he missed twice
should we do something first so change
the RNG what should I dance is it
[Music]
can he even reach
Me Maybe dance
leap
in Vaseline yeah
maybe I'll dance Celine because she's
already engaged
no Vaseline doesn't even do that much
damage
then
could call it to even reach
because
we're about to say who said no what's
home is bad oh
LG was just really shitty now
that's him from below ah
so I'm not in the way okay okay
[Music]
I guess I'll I'll see it as a way of
getting him faster to the boss
[Music]
no but that changed to RNG right should
I trust the Nova Tome again
hmm
[Music]
it's a morse code yeah
it didn't change because no one attacked
Oh I thought that would help
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
what
[Music]
ah
I come back
[Music]
a crit but it didn't kill a Chloe
Chloe she's gonna die she is going to
die yeah
[Applause]
five damn it Miss
[Music]
I know
several percent
what's going on why today how explain to
me please why do they all have [\h__\h]
percentages
I'll pull back for now
no they're ignoring they're ignoring my
my big mauvier on Netflix
I might if they're only ignoring
completely that mobile is standing there
then I might
turned back in time and let him attack
normally instead because the Archer the
[\h__\h] that's what I was saying was I
say I need to take the Archer down
because of Hortensia or somebody else
saying
[Music]
oh he killed him damn
um
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah I'm thinking to rush the boss but
she's a bit far away
[Music]
what about the chests
and I'm still so scattered too
[Music]
let me just
how would I
how would I prevent that anyway like
with oh when he's on the other side of
the door
and I'm pretty far away
like I could I guess do like a
um Lynn
Astron vaulting
hmm
[Music]
I could try
foreign
go all the way back and see what we can
do
[Music]
no no no no no yes yes yes yes yes
18. not Linda bar well it's not that new
bow that we got
I think I think I saw someone saying in
chat that uh
it's op when using engaged
what
what do you mean not the Archer
next to kiwawa I can't stand next for me
an Archer what do you mean an Archer
what do you mean an Archer didn't open
the door it was the thief they said
right
it was the fifth like I literally
checked the protocol
are you confusing me
ah it's Lin's paralog I would have had a
better weapon even damn
yeah I went this far back because I
thought Wow might as well but before I
was thinking yeah let's go back to kill
the Archer so the Archer won't kill
hotensia but if we're going back anyway
we're gonna go all the way back you know
because apparently this will save us
trouble
okay
by my hand now I just need bolting to
hit oh
I'll kill him
[Music]
where is Veil
is that what like possible
[Music]
no
it's not
[Music]
oh
yeah I can't do it
warp or dancer
um
uh okay
[Music]
um
Celine I'm gonna go here but first i'm
gonna
make it worthwhile
[Music]
optimization baby he's gonna miss isn't
he
[Music]
okay
Scotty beat me up with me what
[Music]
what
okay uh engage
please grab me your strength
[Music]
begin
coincidence
[Music]
where too
here too
[Music]
thank you fail can actually sell the
entire upper segment of this map are you
sure
are you not a little bit overestimating
wow she couldn't really dance that's
what I was thinking of
wow you can really gosh
wow you couldn't really don't
hungry
[Music]
this battle works
this feather
let her do the bolting
the otherwise
Chihuahua
[Music]
[Applause]
oh no now I'm to warp two
how
hum it's too late for that now I don't
have anyone who can do that now
it's too late it's too late it's too
late
[Music]
I could have done it
well that wasn't worth the effort
because I also did all of this
stuff
for the sake of just getting closer
oh
how is that gonna work more we are
getting the
Warp
but then
like how how how can I do all of that in
one turn now in this turn
[Music]
because he has to go over
to Ivy
she hasn't right
no wait who
who has it
so
potential
[Music]
no she doesn't have it anymore I
switched it out so keep Wawa has it
[Music]
thank you
yeah chihuahuas
coined on
[Music]
I'll take them
Alex here
but then but then I used up the
but how how how can I what
um
[Music]
I will try another one I'll try to shoot
him down with fogado can that work he
don't he doesn't have a longbow
I don't have a longbow and that's like
[Music]
um
now you will need a longbow I think
[Music]
I guess that wouldn't work
we wouldn't have the reach
foreign
[Music]
no everybody already danced
um
[Music]
I mean we can try because if this
doesn't work out I'm gonna like probably
go back in time again anyway
I don't know what I'll do then but now
I'm kind of
in this commitment
I could hope
nah even if I spawn myself some crazy
ass unit
I don't think they could reach Eva
[Music]
oh wait I spawned here if I go here
if I go there to
train then I used up my move didn't I I
can't move anymore for that
summoning Lin would be funny
I'm not going to summon Lin
[Music]
so
that's a rage
now get the staff of him huh
what
no what
I will
um get a colorless one
this feels like such a waste of time
right now
there's no way we're gonna get anything
that has the reach except I mean that's
only Linden right I mean who else
a normal unit no
[Music]
good for you fogado
good for you
[Music]
I mean I didn't do anything wrong I mean
the only thing I could still do is I
guess
uh
uh yeah
I don't know I don't [\h__\h] know I
don't [\h__\h] know
and for tensing a verb Veil
um okay I think a veil uh went as far as
you could but whatever
oh my God oh my God this Frame is gonna
be over 12 [\h__\h] hours
[Music]
inventory right but she can't reach
kiwawa
this is the last time I'm rewinding this
[\h__\h]
um
[Music]
I don't know what the hell to do
oh
don't make me angry oh
[Music]
[Applause]
you can't be for real how is that even
gonna help
by having Kiana closer to Hortensia
[Music]
I'm trying it best here okay to think
through every single possible option in
this game okay but I mean don't expect
me to see for everything please
[Music]
yeah it's like 5D chess
so we'll have Veil go as far as she can
yeah
you really make me worried that I have
to check chat for every single turn
because apparently everything I do is
wrong
[Music]
[Applause]
astrostone first next door Outlet oh
yeah
oh can't I cannot
I cannot I cannot do that
next to her I cannot
[Music]
uh
if I if I go here who tells you can
reach right I mean unless I can I guess
I'm gonna take it now
the
warp but for the warp I have to be next
to her right I can dance
Veil but then
[Music]
[Applause]
no okay
[Music]
is that even gonna work no
because then we warp her
already before and I didn't what
I'm confused
[Music]
yeah probably not but we're optimizing
probably wouldn't need all that I didn't
okay
[Music]
um
wait
yeah but see I have to be next to us
of course I have to be next to her
huh
what are what
even like wow
so I'll dance myself
so I mean I might as well heal someone
yeah
that's a big help
um
bile love you know she's there
[Music]
um
can I get kagetsu in the bottom yeah
[Music]
I want to at least be able to dance for
wait okay I'll stay here I'll attack
from here
[Music]
nice thank you
thank you
[Music]
foreign
okay
what am I doing
[Music]
no what I'm doing
yourself
[Music]
um excuse me
is it the last one
ah 52 even with this 52 I mean I can't I
can't I can't do I mean if this goes
wrong I mean
I mean come on please
oh
are there any other s who could open
this door
are they not gonna attempt it
because they better not
otherwise
they can't hit it normally right like I
can do
or will they not
otherwise
[Music]
what seraphim spell what do you mean
what
what do you want me to do
[Laughter]
what what
why why
I don't understand why I need to
understand why
just because you think I can't take them
down otherwise
[Music]
I will accept Cali she does like this
let's let's let the others move first I
guess
[Music]
oh
foreign
really weak on refined
oh
let me go here
now you're not you're not gonna you're
not gonna go now now is not your time
I've decided that
oh hurry how to drive your bus
have a safe driving comfortable day
please with no weird incidents
[Music]
wait
I think we'll just stay here
I hope I don't regret that
I don't want everyone to
take damage no please no
foreign
[Music]
yeah I don't know I don't know the names
I need to get you guys ideas for names
yeah
oh wait I will dance Hortensia not for
the damage but because I want her to
stand
on the tile
three
thank you
I gave a huge list of names where
to rely on chemistry say the word
um yeah I will
um
probably make a commute
also thanks for all the cool
submissions for the like character
description
there's so many
I'll have to look through them slowly
I'm sorry they're all pretty similar
most of them so
at least
they follow the pattern thank you guys
for trying
still ready to do something as well oh
okay okay I'll cook again
let me see
how much
[Music]
aha
any impressive name you got so far and
for the for the new show not really I
haven't really nothing left of you um
looked into it too much yet because I
also haven't really asked you guys
properly for recommendations yet
[Music]
you're probably not gonna kill him uh
this guy but whatever
I can keep one alive
either way one would have stayed alive
so
worldwide
[Music]
I am easy to please
ah I forgot about her
he had a free press
so bad
actually that's nothing what the hell
I thought it was gonna be more
holy [\h__\h] wait the worm wait wait
[Music]
you all didn't warn me about that
wait he died before he dies again I
guess I'm not Invincible after all
our treats I'm not rewinding for that
foreign
[Music]
classic combo
but if you stand on the tile
on this one can they not come out
I don't they probably still would would
they
anyway
let's hurry the [\h__\h] up meme
[Music]
I wonder
no
[Music]
well well well well wow wow wow
wow
let's start with the easy ones
don't fear for me
[Music]
the physic doesn't just turn into an AOE
weapon right I would like to have my my
fortify back
um
[Music]
but I also want to engage Plus
a slight injury
[Music]
to the rescue
what
[Music]
foreign
are you for real for real now for real
for real for real
so it doesn't huh
oh yeah fortify on hortonfield
yeah oh wait yeah that's what that's
what I was thinking I was doing okay
oh
yeah okay
a little help
my wife
help us
we are in dire need of salvation but
maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe if that
reach is so big
incredible I will take advantage
[Music]
sorry I'm so indecisive
I am so indecisive
[Music]
should I kill this one
sure
cataclysm I suppose that would have been
smart
[Music]
all right she can't oh go away on you
oh no
yeah
yeah I'm worried about that too no
I I was I'm thinking I could probably go
a couple more people over there
[Music]
otherwise it's just another
just another
um
[Music]
oh
those enemies don't move because their
formation is annoying to deal with yeah
they don't move
[Music]
me what Veil isn't in range for the
healing anyway right so she'll be fine
oh they blocked oh they really don't
move oh okay then that that's why
that's why they don't have these like
eyebrows that they're gonna attack me
ow dance no problemo
I'll do my best
I wanna call Bubbles but not yet not
here
hmm
should I just call them here but at
least the bottom ones will go for the
doubles
because it doesn't look like I can kill
them all
I feel like two of them will just go to
waste
because I can't move them
sounds okay
no we should have danced out Chris
[Music]
stood there and then dance me and then
go up and put the doubles there
[Music]
you realize afterwards
hmm
maybe they'll spawn some more
reinforcements that are gonna make it
worthwhile
[Music]
I guess I'll dance her
um
oh peanuts yeah connect two
[Music]
what goldberry no no oh actually
my Lancers
kill Alliance I feel like I'm having a
deja vu
it's my second attempt I think ah no she
did crit before but even then she didn't
kill maybe now
yeah yeah before it didn't kill because
it still had full HP at that point I
think
this time
this time it worked out
nice uh okay
um
Celine Celine Celine
[Music]
how long do they get magic Plus for just
for this current turn
I never use this
correct
Main
okay
[Music]
then
oh I can't really do anything though
I think because she's gonna heal
[Music]
oh wait
oh
[Music]
looking pretty good again
why no magic
[Music]
I don't know
[\h__\h]
come and face me
okay
let's go
[Music]
well okay they really don't move they
don't attack and bring some
reinforcements but this turn no one was
damaged
yes
I says the bird
good
okay
um
Count On Me
I can do the cataclysm now
[Music]
how do I do the smartest
essentially it would be a cross right
but
reinforcements yeah they will take time
watch gold memory if you have you can
extrasaurine
and we'll get more attack range
oh oh I remember that somehow from last
time oh but wait what what what
you mean you mean where's Ayah gold Mary
gold Mary gold Mary
um oh that's her I think
yes I can't
quite Rich if I maybe I can probably
swap cockatoo and Veil somehow she can
go over there to attack if kagazu goes
first
she have to be engaged for that
no rhymes
[Music]
I was out of range the map
no okay
[Music]
all right I'll take down this one
because I can
um
and then where do I put
if we make him walk back again
or front
move forward I feel like we should move
forward
even though it'd be danger but I can't
even move that far anyway
better stay out of range
play some color listen for train attacks
I'll put him I don't know where here
I'll just be here
um
okay now
ah
okay it becomes bigger but
I can't only place it here unfortunately
[Music]
can I dance
um call Marie
I can't
if I would dance gold Mary
I'm just hoping that I could get this
this free Block here oh no actually if I
try to get it on the middle one
then the shape should get all of the
surrounding ones too
I'll figure it out
somehow
[Music]
this ends now
good idea that would work okay okay oh
oh nice tile
in in danger for these boys but anyway
kiwawa already has a big avoid and with
that it's even better
golf Mary
okay it was foretold
dancer and then
so in order to get this cataclysm to
work how many times do I have to be
there
wait a second
basically
can I do it from here yeah okay I want
to stand here so I'll bring uh gold Mary
here would be fun
there we go
all right Soren oink
that sounds like orange are we done here
wow
very flashy
very nice
[Music]
oh no uh
might as well get started on the worm I
think
although uh
what do you think
because he's gonna come for
somebody
should I take care of these ones not
worth it okay
um then I'll go here maybe
the will is firm
[Music]
59.
you dare
it's okay as expected it's last spurt
anyway
I just want to use her and then move her
make space
I'll protect you
oh wait we still have some peeps here
with how many only one mob Bryant
[Music]
got the latecomers over here
what is Chloe even I'm not gonna bring
her to the next fight honestly I feel
like she's not helping me at all
oh I really wanted her to like I wanted
to give her a chance you know I really
tried
I really try it
I left Chloe long ago
[Music]
oh that's great
and chill I can't believe it's Chloe
I really
fought eventually you would you know
change everybody's Minds opinions
yeah no I I regret
why'd you do me like that
I'm thinking
since he'll be lagging behind anyway
better charge him to then
send off
another uh what's it called again
long shot
thinking that but I don't know if I
should really do that
can't charge now anyway
I'm so possessed yeah
oh there's gonna be more reinforcements
my turn
[Music]
Hortensia
should I hear all of you
right away
wait we clear up
some misunderstandings here
already
just a little bit more
oh well
thank you is much better than her at
healing
late crit
yeah I guess I'll replaced her with like
Tamara after all because I guess
you guys said she's more defensive and
you know
good
and she's I guess still closest In level
range
with the other units I think are all
pretty far
[Music]
okay I'll heal I think
I only have a 45
okay
another big heel for everybody is
why not
everybody else pretty useless on this
useless since you benched them I was
trying to switch around a little bit
though and not always use the same team
I was trying
[Music]
hmm
oh she's gonna fire a straight one but
hey I
started breaking thingy
oh
okay worm oh zero
I was hoping for that
well I didn't think it would be zero
another man oh
[\h__\h] what
oh my God
[Music]
oh well that won't help you
what a Spam but they're not even moving
down there
okay we are pretty much in range pretty
much pretty much but not really
[Music]
we can't possibly pull it off to do it
in one turn right
in this turn
between
I don't think so most of them are not in
radiant
[Music]
maybe I can engage next to someone
like here because I'm starting out here
[Music]
I have a dragon blast so weak
I set up for two turns that's safer meow
yeah another other chests worthwhile
good question
gonna eat that AOE no I don't want oh I
don't wanna I mean it's not gonna be
that powerful anyway
left is oh
I could probably get someone there
oh Jenna is gonna be on a little leaf
huh
I just see it now
taking a little
baby break oh I'm so happy for her
three days
nice
three four days but she's probably gonna
be working anyway
[Music]
I feel like she's still gonna be working
anyway when I was hoping to do here I
guess we're not doing that
[Music]
just in case
of me not doing it this round
we have to clean up here
ah
Jenna wrote me some suggestions for
for the
news show
[Music]
yeah I should be setting up huh
ignore Dallas
[Music]
segment about stuff going on no no we
won't we won't be hearing about that I
don't think so
[Music]
I think I'll set up for next round
and it feels more comfortable oh no no
no no
ready
and I guess I can
open up some things
I need
connect to come up I'm sorry you have to
eat this damage
[Music]
so
free I was
this way
[Music]
can't do anything
yeah cause we went back so far to fix
one thing
oh to save time but then we lost time by
doing that
I will stand gold Mary to open the chest
[Music]
ouch
it didn't make it easier yeah
oh
I Was preparing to heal her up again
nice nice
oh wait toys
[Applause]
um
they're not gonna move though right
they're gonna shoot from there
and if I can only
um
[Music]
I can only shoot back with uh
not volcanona
then it's gonna be less damage maybe I
should purposefully stand here yeah it's
counter that's what I'm thinking
the other Mage will Target me too though
um
engage
plus to kill the dragons
oh oh okay I will stay back and try that
um
[Music]
can I do that from here no
wow
wow wow
[Music]
foreign
about that
it seems so
crazy for them to have such alone
percentage
can I rate the other one
no no
[Music]
I was ready to quit if he would hit with
one percent
no
God please know
can she
oh no no because it's kiwawa what can we
do
we do oh my oh my oh my oh my oh my with
the dragon's fist oh but this one has a
higher chance of hitting me back wow 29
hmm
and check the other ones what about
when six
but this doesn't kill
[Music]
11 sword op
s
didn't even have the opportunity
good for you good for you
now we must escape
[Applause]
um Chloe for opening the chest mm-hmm
because what else would she be doing no
no no no
um
I could dance panette or or her but then
he'll be so far down again
I don't want to use the fortify again
God damn it
do you have a physique please thank you
or should I just use a fortifier
I don't have that much strange people
here
I'll use the physics
I don't need to write sacrifice I don't
need that
friends
wait what God there we go
guys don't worry don't worry this this
torture
is almost done
[Music]
huh
don't know what I'm gonna do with yunaka
hopefully she'll be useful
in the next turn wow nice level up wow
[Music]
come and get me should I should we use
her as a scapegoat
I can fog her up
this isn't the last one yeah I know it's
not it's not
here Dragon vein
bait
I want to see what happens no problem
oh wait I can use this little I can open
this already or
um
he would die
[Music]
thrackle Shield
oh
remind me to use that okay okay okay
okay here we go oh oh wait I left them
oh oh oh that's cool oh
oh
that's a that's a bit of damage
[Music]
they're so useless if all they're gonna
use is those stupid states don't even
bother how did he
and 47 misses
that's right
[Music]
yeah okay bye-bye
could have used her poison but oh well
oh of course I forgot about you
stay alive
oh more oh dear
is my bottom scapegoat I notice
don't worry I'll Chris I'll get you out
of this
don't you worry
[Music]
her weapon's name is German was like
stupid we put together
it means
like well
this Villa just willpower
and glance is
sparkly
frankly well
mother Mommy
here we are at last how about we train
here you'll be the one fighting the
emblem
oh
what
you said that bucket the emblem lends
you there
ah don't get manipulated memories
I wanted to spend time with you
chat for hours take long walks together
share meals and then then stop please
it's all right
there are lots of things I wish we'd
done too we weren't able to but that's
okay
it's better than seeing you suffer like
this you can still surrender mother
please
for me no
lord sombron gave me more time with my
child
I refuse to waste it but you're wasting
it by dying idiot I won't let anyone
take that away not even you I waited for
so long if that's important to you then
surrender and go to the good side what
the [\h__\h]
Texas
stop
[Music]
oh man
but I mean I understand that she
probably by manipulation isn't able to
do so but she's expressing the will for
it
[Music]
um
because I think sidel can reach
[Music]
I just take a step back so he couldn't
freeze for sure
yes
I won't miss a step
[Music]
kind of you
the dragon yeah
[Music]
let's do this whole thing again shall we
[Applause]
ten percent on her side that is really
really sad
yeah music slapping
okay
easy peasy lemon squeezy
and let's open up the dress
like those the way they Place those uh
charging plates over here
makes no sense to me because if you're
in this area
I don't think anyone really thinks it's
worth it to waste your time to go over
here and charge yourself like how in
what kind of situation would you be
where that would be really like useful
um
I mean I might charge Hortensia now no
it's not even worth it it's not even
worth it especially now
you're correct I didn't use any of these
right they're like
so awkwardly placed they're not gonna be
useful at all
[Music]
thank you
foreign
I want to be with my child that's my
only desire please
stay out of this
what what what what what what what what
yeah
[Music]
okay
I don't know if that was really the
best thing to do
probably not
can I can I take her down
[Music]
needs a few more adjacent ones
it's like when they stand diagonally
behind him
is that gonna help because what let me
see it
thank you
nearby Alice okay it doesn't have to be
like right next to him right
[Music]
[Applause]
I guess I'll stand here
[Music]
we need a crit Queen
I think
17. oh yeah really
[Music]
yeah the fingers will fail she can't
like walk away afterwards that's why I
want to put her up here so that
it won't be an issue with pocketsu
[Music]
can he still
I don't know
might be better to go for the Dragon
[Music]
no but actually doing the most damage
but I need the credits
okay from here she has like 38 only
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go here to kill me again
why another attempt you must know the
result will be the same
still have to try
no matter how many times I feel I'm not
going to give up my sister taught me I
can shape the future for the better
never gonna give you um
that memory that time together everyone
it seems has a future and hopes and
dreams too why should you get such
Treasures while I'm okay enough of the
tech in dialogue now
once and for all we go away with you
[Music]
I have it
let's go no Chris
so sad
at least you missed everything but [\h__\h]
no crits
[Music]
Celine probably wouldn't have done much
damage so I can do that but even then
[Music]
we're gonna do about her last age people
are I need to dance wear my dancer
already danced can I dance the dancers
connect to farm
[Music]
clever you really think so because I
feel like
now we have the problem
wait wait
I think cortencia also wouldn't have
done much damage
so I can only use Thunder from this
position
no Thunder doesn't even kill how lame is
that
[Music]
goddess dance the dancer wait but um
so Celine who does that
and she's like
yeah she's an engage Plus
um
I am in a pickle because there's no way
that karetsu with Lucina
can wipe out a whole rich people but
there's also no way so lean can do can
do it all alone
[Music]
right
yeah whatever even if somebody dies
whatever let me just yeah one more turn
I don't care don't think too much we're
just wasting time
okay but I want to try with the other
way around I think
[Music]
I win this one yeah we're just gonna
sack
put a few characters into grave whatever
[Music]
see lemon sword with that Dragon Blast
isn't even that bad we were almost there
so close
Chicago now let's see now
[Music]
hmm
thank you
[Music]
thank you for the membership for 27
months wow rip all Chris
I'm trying to get him away I'm trying
I'm the one help
unless I mean if we're already
hmm
[Music]
is enough
it's not luck it's fate
Fallen star
probably not
whatever it's okay
and we'll just take like one more turn
but it may basically no different
but look at that hmm
the spare doing decent damage on the
worm okay
[Music]
do that underestimate estimator
don't you dare
[Music]
it's not locket's face no no no no no no
no
I will not accept that wait I can kill
the worm let's go
oh
oh no not really
does it help
no no no really doesn't oh
[Music]
you just stay we'll just stay bigger
we'll just stay okay
[Music]
actually
there you go
uh-huh oh
[Music]
yo yes
worm goes for gold Mary
gold Mary
one man down
oh
yo basically I finished it in that turn
I can't seem to because it wasn't that
still the same round
oh
the girl let's go
poetic indeed thanks for attacking Veil
because if you would have attacked
someone else I don't know if that would
have worked out and we're getting the
Villa glance oh that's [\h__\h] You Wobble
that's the little the long distance
weapon huh I am
oh
for normal circumstances I would have
ended the stream here
but no we have one more thing to do
um
thank you we did it oh my God what cost
I'm so sorry thanks for the help
mommy dead voice is it you my child oh
it was nowhere you've received me oh no
she's just okay
dying and returning to normal for a
moment
[Music]
or I fell asleep
you see this I'm one of the emblems now
oh
my God
I hardly believe my own eyes oh
how hard you must have worked to achieve
such a thing it's not better than being
the Divine Dragon though but I'm glad I
can show you what I've become you know
both cool wanted to make you proud
you say this this is the fist that I
smashed your face with just a moment ago
okay wow why you gotta be like that huh
why you gotta show her the face again
the fist again so now she has to go
nothing can be done
I'm so sorry another
seems we have to part yet again
from the first moment that we connected
I have always been at your side
the years after I lost my family were a
dark time the pain of what had been
taken was unbearable but then I met you
and even though I missed you during your
long Slumber I knew that you would wake
up someday
we'd be together again leg Court how
could I ever feel lonely
you and I will never be a part again
I feel the same ever since we met I
never felt truly alone not really
you showed me the warmth of a real
connection and that is stronger than
that you have always
been my bright shining light
I can never thank you enough for being
my child
thank you mother
getting to be your child is my greatest
happiness
they're getting the most out of this
little conversation
I want to spend more time with you
pinky promise me we will Java
child I'll remember this promise we have
made
and I'll remember you
[Music]
the sky is so beautiful above me
just like the one I saw the day you
opened your eyes again
from now on
you must protect it all
everything oh stop under this
is beautiful
sky
my heart
I prinched
[Music]
it's okay
she's fine I'm all right please don't be
sad for me
others
it's where she belongs now
I know we'll meet again
[Music]
it's time to go we have to check the
barrier
the last map really
I guess the big man will show up there
oh
damn that was
very long I'm assuming will the last map
be more difficult or about the same the
problem is we just like rewind it so
much this time
so I took up so much time
definitely shorter oh okay
it's not that complicated okay okay
last map is cool about the same for me
I got on the plane when you started this
chapter no way where did you fly like to
the next neighborhood Town huh
that's not fair
why are there any animals in here huh
where are they animals
let's go
huh if you get a game over in last
minute you got a special cut scene but
let's not do that
um
that is tempting
straightforward okay
oh
nice hole
the barrier is Vanishing
we destroyed it at last yay look what's
happened to the sky
it's a nice color sambron opened the
portal
Hopper
it's there if this goes on
power of other worlds will pour through
and this one will be destroyed Elios
will meet its end no
I won't let that happen
my mother entrusted this world to me I
will protect everyone I kind of want to
see that and everyone who lives beneath
this Sky I have no doubt that a world
ruled by you would be a beautiful place
what brought that on
it made it safe I'll need you to help
build that world Martha
help me protect it
forever
forever it's a promise then
[Music]
an old rule yeah it can go on with only
wobble right that's an inspiring thought
everyone
how did our forces fare we are training
should be able to leave soon I think
I'll do that you stand before the final
battle undaunted full of Hope
much to learn I know I could watch it on
YouTube but I want to see it with you
guys to rebuild I'm gonna visit all your
countries bring the emblems along
after so much time confined to the Rings
I'm sure they'd like to see the world
right now that the 12 Rings power has
been used people won't try to steal them
it's almost eight hours will be safe
they can stay summoned we have to finish
in four hours we will riots please
introduce them to our citizens
oh make that
make that hope they like to sing I
imagine their experience will make them
good advisors for restoring alucia it's
nice isn't it
having something to look forward to
something to fight for for the first
time in my life
I'm excited for the future last time the
future
the bad ending are you ready for that
fail I am
I'm not afraid to stand up to him I was
so lonely
I couldn't admit it but
he stopped being my father long ago Abby
did you not listen I have leftovers from
yesterday I always cook for two people
and the second person is me
oh well there's no bond left to break
fail
Divine One our wounded soldiers have
been treated one and all thank you
Vander okay if the ending the bad ending
final battle is upon us at last how do
you know it's the final one this journey
has made you how do you know that Zephyr
isn't gonna show up again I wish I could
stay here and help you all build a
peaceful world but yeah if the bad
ending is strong then I'll go get it um
we may soon have to part ways
she read the script
she looked at spoilers
the Whopper said so hmm
okay
what do I feed Frogger Wawa well
definitely not like dead quails or so
because that would be terrifying
wouldn't it hmm
okay I will not pick up everything but I
will do some things
um
uh
[Music]
let's do supports first
does it do I even care do you remember
when you gave me the Dragonstone
I wish I could say I did but everything
from before I woke up is hazy well
you and I met just one time a thousand
years ago we only met once all of our
siblings had died in the war
you were the only one to survive
and you came to see me I was very young
then
frail and frightened and you handed me
the Dragonstone you told me that you
couldn't stay by my side but that you
were still with me no matter what
no I said that to you
all that time ago you did
the Dragonstone is shattered
but it was my protective Talisman for a
very long time I held it close when Mama
died and when Papa returned and said
horrible things to me I knew that as
long as I had the Dragonstone
I could be strong
and hold on until I saw you fail I even
if you can't remember what you did
I am still so grateful if you hadn't
given me the Dragonstone
we never would have found each other
again I'm grateful too
thank you held me in your heart all
those years without you Veil I wouldn't
be standing here right now you ever got
a dragon form
all together forever are we not gonna
get one that's right
nothing can separate like at the end
don't tell me don't tell me I guess
unless it's a no oh never lame what what
that's amazing I'm just gonna skip that
one because I do not care
let's be honest I did some support
conversations off screen too and you're
not missing out on anything really you
wouldn't even know
skipping this one too
we can listen to Girl conversations
like this one
princess saline greetings only if you
don't talk about teeth I have heard some
interesting things I heard that and
despite your Royal position you maintain
excellent skill in swordsmanship
all the more intrigued will you indulge
me now I am eager to see your skill I
appreciate the spirit of your offer but
I have no desire to fight without good
reason
pointing do you not understand the
concept of training
I keep myself on form to protect my
nation but I've never sought to train
for its own sake to reach their own I
suppose oh see they mentioned too sorry
I can't
that's that's it that's my NG word um
[Music]
[Laughter]
the Divine dragon
but all the Volusia warships the fell
Dragon it is true every worshiper of the
fell dragon that I knew was a poisonous
liar and schemer so I chose to rebel and
instead prayed to the Divine dragon
in private of course you had a
considerable amount of Courage for a
young princess thinking back on it
perhaps I did
you are also from illusia are you not
do you worship the fell Dragon I was
born in firenay when I was young my
father fell ill and died
afterward my mother and I traveled to
Indonesia mother's prayers for the
Divine Dragon had unsaved father
we changed deities as a result ah and
how is your mother now my mother died
and soon after we began our new lives I
was raised in a church in alucia
alongside the other orphans I didn't
realize
I'm so sorry I have nothing to hide
thank you I was educated by fell Dragon
Believers but I cannot say I was ever
truly devoted as with my mother I found
that my deity was not interested in me
is moderately okay now I see you were
surrounded by the fell dragons following
what happened yet you chose not to
follow I have rarely admitted such to
anyone else but yes I suppose we are
similar in that it's been for a while
quite
I wonder what else we might have in
common
[Music]
what did I what what got you happier can
we do more of that
[Music]
I want to make you not moderately okay I
want to make you very happy
[Music]
ah lady Vale
oh I didn't know you were looking for me
nice I was indeed perhaps you don't
realize it is not safe for you to walk
through town alone not safe why do you
say that oh this town is full of good
people considering what we have done
some of these good people might
rightfully want revenge if that happens
apologize
truly awful things
apology might well not be enough if
something were to happen to you I'm not
a child I can take care of myself
now stop following me
[Music]
wait please no
they have something I need to do
on my own
[Music]
she has no idea oh sorry
sassy Lost Child
ugh welcome
Hortensia I'm not sure I can be any
clearer about how little I want to see
oh my wife's so mad at my sister what
the [\h__\h]
there's a story I want to tell you
mother
you see she was just a regular Dragon
but she was also the feldragons me
he did her for thank you and persecuted
her
she died when I didn't age
the humans knew what I was
and they persecuted me too
it was
terrible
being a fell dragon has given me nothing
and it has taken everything
I get it you've lost family too is that
all you had to say to me yes I'm sorry I
tried to force our friendship
I did a horrible thing to you it was too
much to ask goodbye Hortensia
wait
I'm sorry for being so harsh to you
I didn't know about all that
I was inconsiderate that's all you can
go okay
and thank you for listening to my story
[Music]
do you remember the first time we met
the very first time
sorry
not about them but wild language support
level a I don't care don't flat with my
wife stop it
your fortune the other day it was right
oh what do you mean
I did what you said she did it to the
market and pretended to be a cat that is
I meowed a lot really but I told you to
ignore my reading I I thought I'd give
it a try you know just for fun but then
something amazing happened I meowed and
yelled and I sounded so much like a cat
understandable the mice bled from the
market
very happy so happy they gave me tasty
treats to say thanks why are under here
mice insomnia anyway huh
like I didn't adopt any and like we're
in the sky like where the [\h__\h] did they
come from it was
[Music]
it was right on the mark then
I'm knocking someone's back I don't
think he'll be spreading that bit of
news around
you're very kind lady Vale you really
are
I lose my confidence and other Market in
the city just to cheer me up and it has
cheered me up okay so thank you cute
don't say that
telling the truth I really am I would be
very mad if you don't believe me
okay okay
if it's going to be like that then I
believe you satisfied now since I've
done as you asked and believed your
story allow me to read your fortune
again if that's what you want of course
oh
all is revealed is she gonna bark next
gather petals glowing gold then comes
true a wish so bolt yeah they're flower
petals that are golden and glowing and
there's a full moon how strange
petal where
good luck
we might never see the end of this one
nope
not listening to that
heyunaka I'm headed to a party right now
you want to come along party why ah not
feeling it huh you're always in such
high Spirits I thought you'd be game
but hey no worries I'll see you when I
have some other business take care
came at me so fast I forgot to put my
act on oh I better fix this fast oh yeah
right wait what is the real me if I
don't she wasn't like
oh yeah right
zappy I was totally yanking your
bowstring I love raucous carousing but I
didn't even notice she's just putting up
an act too
like panette are you sure you're not
forcing yourself
[Music]
okay guys close to it in my heart in
that case come on here's like my second
option play harder don't play at all am
I right I mean I like her both ways but
then still
what
happier
why the [\h__\h] are they bonding
I guess archers doing Archer things
I got played
what I mean what
said what is wrong with you girls why
you gotta be so fake man just be
yourself
otherwise how can you even take
compliments
like genuinely and say thank you
genuinely how
I'm gonna put these two in a pool
and we'll see what happens
no conversation
can I
[Music]
I don't care about this but can I put
them here too
[Music]
yes yes yes
how come you've never told me off for
running away from home whatever guys
whatever I was glad you got out when you
did huh I always imagined you'd hold a
grudge against me for flying The Coop no
I just wasn't brave enough to do
likewise wasn't sure I could make it
alone meanwhile look at you a retainer
you struck out on your own and made a
life for yourself I'll bet those parents
of ours would be glad to see how well
you're doing
I doubt it they probably don't care
about me one way or another
[Music]
listen
I probably shouldn't tell you this but
I'm not one to keep secrets Mom and Dad
tried to find you
what wolfdong there's no way well I was
surprised too maybe they were just
concerned about keeping up appearances
hard to say at any rate that's the truth
I figured you should know it's a
question basically right what am I
supposed to do with that
or [\h__\h]
I'm still ladylike because she's not
saying the s word
uh I don't think I can unlock the last
one unless maybe if they eat and do the
stable
because afterwards we're probably not
going back to the little something else
are we
[Music]
that won't be enough
that's it okay
you better be good at cooking I am about
to have my last fight girl
don't mess this up
please
[Music]
um
we're gonna make some Berry sounds Panna
cotton
[Music]
let her cook it would be an honor to
make this for you that and Ivy is a
dragon's favorite food I'm dying to know
you are in my thoughts as I prepared
this Divine One the flavor is
invigorating I approve here
lovely aroma
so
[Applause]
if so make who's solmik my favorite
meals
that plus one hopefully not
d-e-a-t-h plus one
okay did we have anyone
[Music]
um
maxed out
no okay
then
Arena
desert okay Tamara forgotten and the
retainers all right
okay
oh yeah sword and shield from the last
battle
sword on kiwawa
step by step
um
we could give color to a level on
Chloe no
not you
Samara just level nine is sad
DiMera level nine
but Chloe is not higher either so okay
she'll be better
Ivy Crown Princess of Illusion
apologies in advance
should we put the boots again on the
dancer
I hope so
I think Tamara's gonna join the party
[Music]
dancer okay
I am here
participate often enough I suppose
[Music]
extra staff unit is always good koala
true that
um
[Music]
that is an argument yeah
come
show me your skill
especially for last month
[Music]
oh yeah I'm being reminded right now
thank you
flying stuff but she needs to do is use
the stats instead of battle
okay I guess yeah
[Music]
now
um
I'm gonna swap the slim sword out
and give her the Villa glance and
hopefully give that some kind of
Engraving as well
and then there was a [\h__\h] where the
shield is not a shield shield is just a
death item right deaf who to give
what should I give
[Music]
it
oh
Wonder boots
[Music]
I probably got another pair of boots
because somebody said so I guess not
okay Draco Shield
[Music]
I guess I'll give it to kiwawa but she
doesn't even need it she does that thing
airplane
which we can't use that oh
[Music]
why we can
okay
[Music]
uh I'm gonna go to the
training yard
of course
avoiding endgame spoilers are you not
done yet
okay
thank you for watching though
make sure to watch the VOD at some point
think you promise
oh good job on the workout though
I should do something true
thank you
oh something new
the confecto knife is
is dango
wow
what is it is it it's a it's a a a a
dagger right probably
thankful
I don't have space for another dagger I
think
do I hmm maybe the silver dagger or the
iron that iron dagger Mama iron dagger
is engraved
I guess I could just engrave something
else
is it even gonna be better
it's not that good
[Music]
oh wait but we got this one too
uh okay should I bring this one though
um
[Music]
the stats confuse me so much but I guess
it's like going down as opposed to the
iron dagger that I have equipped right
and those this always confuses me it's
showing down even though I'm not even
comparing it to anything
[Music]
engraved to steal our silver dagger
it's better on her than anyone else the
chlorine engraved in this one
I don't want to think too much at this
point because every time I start to
think it takes so long
uh
oh wait let me pick up the iron release
because we might upgrade something
yeah thinking takes too long
I only have one brain cell
I'm using it takes up so much resources
AKA one brain cell takes up one brain
cell
one one thought takes up one brain cell
what's that over there
there was never an item here before
Jim
I still ask questions sure
might not pick them up right now
uh okay
um
thank you uh let's check
here she's lacking a stay staff
do we have something for her do we need
to buy something
I guess we're still bringing Chloe
I'll get her a four to five oh wait but
we have another treat
[Music]
wait but this is just oh
I'll get her afforded by
[Music]
welcome I think I'll buy another physic
that could be useful Maybe
where the fortify at
huh
sold out or what
what is that [\h__\h]
oh is it because you can't use it
[Music]
really but it shows the entry and trap
as well
sold out I think
damn they're they're in the restock I'm
at the end of the game and they don't
restock what the hell you know how
important this is
it's a question of life for them and you
couldn't restock that [\h__\h]
[Music]
unbelievable I thank you
physic it is
um
I wonder if the warp will be even
necessary for the upcoming fight so
maybe
yeah
I probably don't need all of those heels
mend
[Music]
more palps okay yeah but I think in
terms of staying so fine
do come again let me do something I look
clean
I don't know how it's going it's going
too long
that's what I can tell you
[Music]
plus one
can I get two more silver
[Music]
or Steel
I'll get one for this
and one for this hmm
[Music]
wow I said my name
I said your name said your name gorgeous
why are we not using this it's a smash
weapon home we don't need it whatever I
don't care about all these weapons too
many weapons
can I engrave it with something nice
though
um
what's free
[Music]
this one no it's probably not free
holy moly
it's just one for you probably know
this one
I'll take it
holy what
oh what
did I take the wrong one are there two
of those
no you didn't mean holy
I'll take this one the WT and not so bad
right just as long as we don't like
equip it right
use it every once in a while
foreign
sorry me too understandable and you're
working on the side anyway so
you give yunaka the S rank knife uh
uh did I
she has
yeah this one
okay are we done
can we go
we can go
I'll go
but I'm scared I want to do that like
bad ending but I'm scared
if uh I need every single minute to
finish
[Music]
we always lived
let's go
jump it
[Music]
you can access the final battle to fail
Dragon someone from the second floor
balcony of the thumbnails Cafe tourists
are you making me go back what
[Music]
you fought Psych
why did I what
'd you tell me here
Don't Panic or you will stress yourself
out like a Skyward I know this is like
this is the Strategic thingy I can take
so much time for each move
skywatcher is stressful because man
many reasons but that kind of battle
system
will take
even more from my sanity
somebody said warp will be helpful maybe
I should give myself a warped with more
than one
do I have one
[Music]
oh
final battle
let's go bye-bye final battle is upon us
let's never talk again we're ready we
will move the Samuel itself to the
portal once we Face the fell dragon
there may be no turning back like our
skies and equipped for what's ahead
no
oh probably
hmm
the samniel is ascending
um
win this battle and then return home
together
yes of course
you could marf Mars what's happening are
you burping something
I can't hide this any longer can I
um hide what are you dying something I
should tell you before we arrive
portal has destabilized our world
I lack physical form as do the other
emblems we may not be able to hold
ourselves together no don't take them
away from me again I wish I had realized
but if the portal is doing this then
it's only temporary right after we close
it you and the other emblems will
recover
the moment the portal closes there will
be a great Distortion we will not be
able to withstand it
what are you saying
when the battle is done and the portal
closed all emblems aside from you will
cease to be hmm
you and the other emblems
yes we've been together this whole time
and now you're just going to disappear
please Mars
I don't want to lose you and the others
we need you leaving the portal open
would Doom this world
would you prefer that
we emblems came into existence in order
to Aid this realm another one of those
anything to protect you have to do this
dramatic thing means our end that will
be very painful in order to do to like
undo the other painful thing but both
will be painful so choose the one that's
less painful
typical jrpg I think we had that entails
of our eyes too but then it had a happy
ending you know we didn't lose our Shion
so our promise to rebuild Helios
together I plan to see the world
not as bad as possible I'm so sorry
there's no need to apologize
I've asked so much of you yeah they're
not really dying they're just ghosts
anyways but when I thought about a
future with you both understandable it's
okay
I felt truly happy there is a promise I
can still keep in lithos the day you
awoke
what did I say when you summoned me your
ally until the very end okay I remember
I will never break that promise you
better not until this Wars otherwise
I'll bring out
I will stay by your side
always been
that's why we've made it this far
more than your strength
it's your care for others that has
brought us all here thank you now
prepare yourself we'll arrive at the
portal soon I'm ready
who did not have had that conversation
while walking well I guess we're just
flying now so just waiting this is the
portal to other worlds
it's beautiful
but very cold
oh hi here
sombron
I did not expect you to survive let
alone reach me here we've come to stop
you from destroying Elios
I am done with your worthless World
return to it and shut the portal live in
peace there well I just realized that I
in the middle of his forehead moves
around
that should satisfy us both you're going
to return and attack Elios again we'll
never believe you wouldn't and you've
caused too much suffering too much loss
to run free we will defeat you right now
and prevent you from invading any other
worlds
what I seek is a reunion
the reunion with zero emblem zero emblem
I've not heard word of this before
of course not that emblem is not of Your
World nor am I
what do you mean Beyond this portal lie
infinite worlds cool one of them was my
home it had its own emblem rings and a
war arose to control them
um
my kind lost the enemy used the Ring's
power to slaughter my relatives all of
them
I was very young
our enemies granted me alone the mercy
of Exile guys
nothing
very disappointing I must say
possibly the most disappointing thing
in the whole game
just saying you know
could have placed some nipples there
but now you have to you have to trigger
me like that
you mean they sent you to Elios
ruled by god-like dragons
I was meant to live a quiet life there
but I brought something with me unknown
to them
single emblem ring zero emblem in my
world known as the emblem of Foundations
with my power unable to speak
Legends said this emblem fought without
Aid
so much ambition and no allies
that story showed me the way forward in
my complete isolation I trapped in this
world without friends or family
only that emblem gave me Comfort
must have been mighty indeed I guess
he's a lizard or Dragon okay maybe they
don't have nipples
inform in a new world even for moments
I've never heard of such power now you
want a reunion
exactly
and all because of villagers that found
me a few years after I arrived they
mistook me for an abandoned child they
pitied me
my first Connection in your world
soon after the emblem deserted me
leaving only the ring behind
and why for bonding with the people of
this world
I despaired and then I reduced their
Village to Ash
I swore to forego all Bonds in pursuit
of my ambitions as my emblem had I
fought alone
confided in none preparing to return to
my world to exact Revenge I needed pawns
for my plan and territory
spent years amassing it all
then I attacked so the war a thousand
years ago
that's what it was about
Papa
you weren't alone in this world Mama
loved you deeply
you're Believers your attendance
my siblings
um
my sister and me
everything we did was for you as I said
pause wow acting on my command
alone
meant to be used and discarded
death which mean nothing
that's why you killed them all but what
about us
you wanted us to die you were no
different to me
Samsung's horrible you can't be right
about your emblem
you weren't Left Behind what a solitary
Warrior like that emblem would know how
hard it is to be alone and would stay by
your side
sparing you that loneliness in Exile
until you weren't alone and had no
people in your life until you were okay
don't you think more than anyone a true
friend like that wanted you to have
those connections you know nothing
nothing at all about my emblem
it's true
without a word
don't either
no one does all the more reason to be
reunited I will scour world after world
sombron
the emblem of Foundations is no more you
can search and search
but there's no point you might meet the
original hero but emblems are not the
same beings
we are not them what the [\h__\h] how is it
better be reunited almost midnight ever
again be
silent I can only imagine how much
resentment you feel
to sacrifice so many others to be so
selfish you destroy the world
kill your own children
it's all just so
wrong I said before
you are speaking of course you do not
understand me I think that looks like
it's supposed to be nah never mind no no
no no I thought maybe they're supposed
to grow into that but you're right
that's right
by default already clipping
into them like
even when he doesn't move
default stems alone
Revenge
that's impossible
to see a world destroyed we Aid people
through our bonds with the Divine
dragons we are a Force for good we would
never choose to let our power be
exploited for evil enough of this
nonsense
I won't let you stop me or sway my
intentions I have striven for this for
thousands of years
that was the end
you will die the horns this is it very
spiky prepare for battle everyone must
hurt
yeah okay anyway
this is why you shouldn't help solo
survivors they become villains
really always
I assume this map is deceptively simple
it looks deceptively simple
you guys would have told me
if it really was that simple
is he gonna like warp over to another
map over there
okay no that's the sky
this one's simple for a reason okay I
guess because there's like a face too so
okay I said
and I guess we'll still bringing Chloe
so we don't really have to change your
new things
um
should I Rush this like whatever happens
would happen probably after I got his
two HP bars down which seems like fairly
possible somehow
could
possibly force it brush it
with maybe with dance
I don't know I could try
faith and Rush
bait him
hmm
how do you bait him should I
throw a unit at him or should I create a
unit of the gotcha
trap someone
oh Astra faster strong will do okay
um all right I'll wait
mommy mommy
it goes off
making myself
dare turn your blade on me you dare
interfere with that which I have saw for
so long
such fatal hubris you will pay for that
accordingly witness how fragile your
bombs really are
what's happening to them
I am sealing off the portal back to your
world it's what I should have done the
moment you arrived here
feel your emblem allies are too weak
they will be lost in the Distortion
between Dimensions forevermore
be the end
if we must part remember all that we
have done
no I need Lynn
how can I ask her to him
I'd have to say goodbye someday
but I thought there was time
so much for your precious
moments the portal will be shut for good
take comfort for I shall inflict no
further harm Upon Your World The World
though you will die here as I have lived
in anguish classic Fire Emblem we can
never classic find them engaged
I've been ready to die from the start I
was taking my rings away
I pray you endure
we'll never truly know me
I'm sorry mother
worry not
I have no desire to prolong your
suffering
when I am finished not one trace of me
in your world shall remain as though I
was never there at all
I'll stop you
is that so
fight isn't over the Portal's open I can
do this if I give it my all I can summon
the emblems back to me oh look at how
far we've come will you fight him at my
side your faith in me gives me strength
yes sister I'm with you
fail I'll be with you every step of the
way
excuse me emblems so cheesy turn into a
dragon
but I'm a royal dragon all the same
there's gotta be something I can do to
help
yeah okay
too cheesy be right there with you
you've done so much for each and every
one of us so this time we're returning
the favor
I'm worried the music
you don't need my support either way
I know you'll see us through this
this occasion is no different than any
other
my belief in you has never once wavered
allow my faith just this once to be
yours
whatever Faith remains in this heart I
give to you all these membership messes
no more sadness Divine One
tired of it let's get everyone through
this I believe in you
as your sister and fellow dragon
I'll do whatever it takes to help you
stop Papa
all flowers must Bloom for you I will be
a gentle rain and a ray of light
if you have faith in the moon and stars
above our beloved emblems will return
oh yeah
and annihilate the enemy now let's open
it destroy them the tail where we fall
to the dark or rise to the light
let's reach for the light
I'm sorry the others are dragging this
out we both know my belief in you is
already enough it's so fitting I
couldn't see it was one of the last ones
that caught me off guard you think we
can make a comeback yeah that's what I
love about you divine one no thumb
that was so bass yeah
your scrambling is both futile and
pitiful
please my friends my mind I need you all
one last time I know once more let us
engage
it was that easy
[Music]
you slave
useless place
[Music]
emblem of dawn
reignite us
[Music]
bear your face
the final emblem oh connect okay wow
we 13 emblems stand against you with our
allies
laughs
future may divide us once more
is all that
you are the flicker of an emperor
you're nothing the deeper your boss now
they're back
[Music]
give up and perish
me as a child foolish and weak and maybe
you're right maybe that's all I am but I
am not alone and we're stronger
breaking of bonds can hurt but when the
bond is reforged it comes back as strong
as ever or stronger and it brings an
even greater hope
people are willing to work for it a bond
can be brought back to life
that's what I'll do every single time
for however long it takes
you won't leave this place because we're
going to stop you
get ready stop run
it says no this is now yeah
like what the shield says all the time
let's go
[Laughter]
I'm ready
so where's the catch guys look at it I
don't get it
I'm ready
I can't say uh-huh
how when I want to bait him how far like
should I just stay on because it's kind
of gloves for as far as possible should
I ignore the side mobs
emblem engage
bad ending yeah but I should have just
um I don't know
[Music]
and I bought the bad ending oh
should I try all right
no that's not last time okay uh
[Music]
say I love range and everyone else okay
just Ivy oh no okay
I got your mom
[Music]
you fought so hard traveled so far
yeah we gotta do our best to catchers
lose now it's just you know real hot pot
I
and now
I did that do I wait around
I can just move everybody a bit closer
yes
I tickled him prep time
[Music]
prep time
how do I look
ah tickets blessing
squishy squishy
maybe Bale again actually
[Music]
she does get a bit squishy
high damage but bit squishy don't you
think
she deserves it we need her alive that
way we can get a little bit you know
deep into the risky business with her
yeah
yes
stay just out of range
I didn't press anything
yes
[Music]
by the way
understood what kind of Risky Business
you'll see
okay this is as far as I can go I think
foreign
[Music]
she's already in range by standing there
should I go back
[Music]
no what else
I will obey
I can do this
I don't care I don't care okay I don't
care
there he is oh they're all come anyway
coming anyways
Perfection whoa
what
why is she flexing like that
what's what's up she's mad she wants to
help me end this quickly
Sam come on
unbelievable
all right but he's so close
that will make it very easy for me but
um
[Music]
I don't I don't wanna you know Veil will
do her own thing
[Music]
so I'm guessing that we would kill him
once and then we'd probably move on to
another map right where we have to fight
him again I'm assuming probably in the
dragon form okay but do I get my
engagements back just this one question
please answer me that
okay
oh that has a minimum range you have to
stay away I didn't even know that hmm
oh no okay
all right
I guess I'll go with this one 69
[Music]
. do I get healed Papa
oh the defect I thought myself rid of
you
yet here you are
you laugh oh you're angry because I
persisted and survived
and who else feels like praise
together as father and daughter like I
wanted but I'm glad I didn't give up
I made it
because it did I can be the one who
defeats you you are a malicious child
I would expect no less from my own if
you're watching mama
I'm going to stop him
just like you told me
I believe Chris Christ
oh but he missed
oh yeah at least once he missed one but
wait where is the crit hmm where is it
are you just holding it back because you
think it's funny or what's going on
what the what the reason hmm
[Music]
only only with the iron deck or the
silver dagger we wouldn't die I just
want that one damage
[Music]
should have given her corn
wait did we get the one damage yeah okay
yeah
corn and Grave you mean
[Music]
no no no no
are you girls drunk did you come to this
fight drunk or
going on
are they okay
[Music]
[\h__\h]
huh
I don't think they're okay I think
they're like drunk
um yeah I know Violet I was kind of
thinking about that too eventually like
how to position them
um
well I was trying to get this one out of
the way
first
so that I could maybe Place bile up
there maybe maybe maybe
but panette missing honestly
pisses me off so much I want a dancer ah
should I reverse
because they're probably also going to
reset the reverses
I'm assuming
actually I could start here because I
want to do the the poison first
um
[Music]
always huh
I can't do damage
[Music]
a chill spider
oh
should I do terrain from around
out of the way
[Music]
he is indeed out of the way
more or less
foreign
[Music]
you're
not gonna disappoint me
[Music]
what
I mean even with the crit
um
can it kill well let's try let's try
[\h__\h] at least she broke him
at least she did that I guess
foreign
[Music]
why
oh
this part of the bgm I feel like I
haven't really heard before properly
hmm
[Music]
oh man what do I do
ah there we go silver great lens that
does the trick
[Music]
no need to save it
and dance
probably not blow the air
[Music]
wait
emblem engage
[Music]
oh
wow made for him basically made for him
[Music]
Dragon was not enough
patricide
children
at your father I'm Matthew said his
mother okay what's for children
Philistines
infanticide
I in fantasized approach for a baby in
other words you'll make the same
mistakes as before
each of us
as well oh have fun at the camp
aign
yeah
that battle works so well with the worms
I can't imagine how can this possibly
take like three hours I guess you know
there's another map huh
very interesting
where's my dancer
am I blind
Dragon I am right
took me a moment
wait but if that already takes down his
HP board then I better get some uxp from
the others right
yeah because kiwala can do the next hit
one hit as well
some EXP
Ana well I guess
okay okay
excuse the jrpg player in me but maybe
there's someone close to level up here
Chloe is
close to a level up
it's just like my
give her the chance the time to shine
will you
[Music]
make this will surely change everything
her stats wow again
[\h__\h]
who else is close to level up
[Music]
Mary based and she got the love love yay
another [\h__\h] level up
uh
yeah that's that's pretty much it
okay
wow it's supposed to level up
this might just do the trick Maybe
oh okay
at zero percent what the [\h__\h] what he's
gonna be a bit more open in his final
form right right
hopefully
no no way
what is that level up
[Music]
out of my way
words
dragonfly
[Music]
would be cool
yeah oh
yeah
hopefully it's a bit more of a challenge
now wait we stay here are the others
gone
no okay he spawned some oh there's a
barrier reinforcements but we stay here
what are they okay you thought I said
ugly waiting for you to arrive
bring back my emblem
[Music]
who once punished their worlds into
Despair Dark emblems
presence
clear
yes
these are the foes we fought in our
original forms look I'm right in front
of him how can this be so difficult
come on I can't sense who is who we
should move closer with caution
a barrier made by the uh dark emblems
that reduces damage
to the fell sambron defeat Dark emblems
to weaken away okay I have to kill them
but he'll probably be attacking me while
I do that too
[Music]
dark animals are powerful foes
describes the battle a lot
but they are susceptible to attacks from
units sink or engaged with an emblem
from their world
not front you mean from my world from
what
[Music]
um
the olive has reached because this range
looks well there's probably wait they
move somewhere else now huh
so I have to kill all of these and he's
all no
I just these ones
the warfather
and
oh one's down here
well there's some flying units here
yeah shadow dragon
dark God
also it's just four
what about this one
still spawning
[Music]
the right emblems
dark the shadow dragon what's the right
emblem for the shadow dragon
[Music]
is that um I have Lynn
but too far away mark
what
okay
[Music]
I don't even have to engage
that's it
shush
this time victory was mine
[Music]
foreign
just stuff you know
[Music]
what two what two bars huh
a little [\h__\h]
um
my dancer is so far away
all right I guess my job here is done
um
[Applause]
I don't know
just a casual 152 damage oh
I had a bottom left but no bottom right
secret
what are you
right here
there this one doesn't do [\h__\h]
[Music]
what
I was weak one going on
[Music]
plane lands is the strongest
ah because she has to walk you know
hey that's already a bit better
am I imagining
probably imagining
I don't need to do it
you don't need to do it with the emblem
oh just for cool dialogue okay
[Music]
oh wait I still got the dialogue
at least you did half
alright so if I wanted to attack now
would that like do nothing
probably okay
is there one for land
no
Leif ah who brings live
spring life
huh
[Music]
should I call Double
I will
[Music]
people without ah DLC oh
I suppose so
this one will have a second
HP bar too huh
because he does
we'll be fine
also it seems like it won't
oh his range is pretty small
he won't attack me
wait wait wait I gave you a dance
because I thought you could do this
girl
later no
no
it's ridiculous it's absolutely
ridiculous
[Music]
why did did she miss
es what's going on
what's going on guys
what
is going on
move to his back
where's his back
[Music]
skipping the combat is gonna disorient
you
come on
momentum
simple enough
what
um
yeah kind of starting to waste potential
run away excuse me sorry about that
[Music]
um
at least they're all broken
[Music]
they're pretty buff too huh
hurry
let me check the questions
not so much a question but are you cute
don't you have any allergies no I don't
thankfully
I'm glad I don't I'm blessed in that
regard
you're so cute it defies the laws of
Nature and Science the world wants to
know how to use it you guys and your
questions I'm
asking I'm giving you a serious
opportunity to ask me serious questions
thank you
thank you very much
[Music]
yeah I always wonder why are you so cute
thank you Kuro
oh
[Music]
and
what's your favorite thing to do in your
free time
cuddling with my cats oh besides
[Music]
um
good question
don't I don't really do much besides
that I guess in my free time I just work
more like when I don't stream
when I don't stream I just work more
actually I just no why
there
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
will I need all these charges no right
I didn't choose the worst weapon
chose the one that was supposed to kill
I would save them
no I won't need them I won't need them
but what the actual [\h__\h] man
or that like made my tummy crumble
[Music]
they're gonna make my 100 Miss I'm good
I'm gonna show it to you the unthinkable
will happen
there we go
I'm gonna kinda split I guess
but we're splitting a little bit uneven
no no
foreign
no crit for me today is like they
already spoiled me so much in this
playthrough now they're like we're not
gonna lend you any more hands you're on
your own now percentages mean nothing
now kiwawa
a few you don't deserve that now
[Music]
I'll send failed I'll go away
top left Celica do I have silica with me
who is Celica is going to the left I
think she's the red-haired one right
yeah okay and top right I don't have
life so it doesn't matter okay I'll go
go okay
sounds good
[Music]
I went into a classic Fire Emblem
what he called me scum [\h__\h]
okay secondary and broken
okay connect you go left
let's not step into that is
forgot I can still move
[Music]
yeah but I didn't I wasn't sure about
this
I guess I'll heal him afterwards
or
wouldn't it be funny if we summon lamps
and then leave can open the top right
but no
um
what should I summon what's
uh What uh what was that
sword
[Music]
for Lance
green
oh no no I don't want life
I don't I don't want live
X was it X versus Lance oh okay
really
short length
what
it was ax okay hmm
come on bring me a miracle bring me
something good
it doesn't have to be I guess it should
be by let's give me bye let's
go oh
piercing glare blocks entry to four
spaces
whoa
whoa whoa
whoa just with his glare hey this
doesn't even break him what the hell
but okay
it will help with uh something surely
what are these ones for
are they gonna like spawn something here
like what is that for sauce oh God
they're gonna make me run around
after I killed these ones they're still
gonna spawn
someone and they left no
oh no that's why it's so annoying
did I leave someone there probably not
right
[Music]
if you're good then you don't have to oh
no no no no no no no no no no no no
is horkie gonna be fine oh
the double was in the range nice
[Music]
believe it
yes I'm not Invincible after all what
our tree so I don't drag you down
what
[Music]
the [\h__\h] what
um
should I rewind
I would I guess just summon further
behind
and then oh I feel bad now
not for Focus you guys are so mean to
volcanado wow
but look at all those flyers polgado
very helpful
[Music]
never rewind but
let me
let me I I have to
just one more time
um
if he's here
I feel like I wouldn't go for him
right
[Music]
yeah okay
will it sounded the same thing I should
write it
yeah okay
I am so starving
[Music]
you know I will protect him
I will protect they can also go for
Cricket so I don't care
[Music]
if I put targets are there will the
dragons still go for the illusory double
what do you think
[Music]
ah I don't want to play it at least once
yeah Street Fighter
AI always goes for kills okay
foreign
oh no
I know he was in the range I just
thought it would maybe prioritize
someone way closer to him
oh man that's such a waste
[Music]
oh
I hope I won't need those rewinds
um
ma'am
[\h__\h]
I needed the Archer you know
[Music]
I'm scared I wonder how many
reinforcements there will be
[Music]
will there be many more reinforcements
after this to the ones that I see now
which aren't really even reinforcements
because they were already there
oh yeah Diablo is something I want to
play for a while when it comes out
that's for sure I might even finish it
who knows
oh no
[Music]
I will sing for you in Diablo 4. what do
you mean you mean because it's online
[Music]
ah what a shitty map
a good wind
[Music]
we almost tell you in here oh can you
give me gear
I guess some other ones wouldn't be much
of an online
PG huh
as well it's not an online mmrpg but you
know what I mean
[Music]
and golden stuff oh yeah it will be our
Animal Crossing nice
[Music]
I need to get stronger until no one can
beat me oh yeah she'll tell me what she
did and I can point it out for sure for
sure
[Music]
when reinforcements come I wonder if I
can ignore them and Rush
well if that's gonna be a bit difficult
maybe engage fail because otherwise
she'll be in range
even the Bold thing
even that
yeah but might as well
which one
I'll go for this one
[Music]
I think it's a dying next turn wait wait
wait Veil wait what
no no I will maybe maybe I'll engage
Pilots
so many fun games coming up yeah
indeed
I mean I wonder how fun
here's what the kingdom will be for me
because I know it's like so
open right
and there's so many things to do
[Music]
oh worries me a bit about me is good at
the game because just by watching it I
always feel like
it's a bit on the difficult side Maybe
but I'm not sure
I think you'll be fine really
[Music]
you've beaten much harder stuff
um
you don't have to finish it if it's not
your thing yeah I won't force myself I
guess
it's the Vape example game I believe in
you no multiple baby
[Music]
I take it back I didn't mean it like
that
[Music]
I want the range
I don't want to take that damage no
I want the damage
I don't want
I guess I'll heal afterwards
[Music]
oh yeah right I wanted to dance
eventually hmm
yeah I didn't put them in a good
position for that to be worth now
wait I'll I'll take down this one that
should be
good enough and the other one will go
for one of the doubles
All In The Name Of Peace
[Music]
and we brought a man for her
yeah that's so that's stupid
unfortunate
plus two range on all her magic
[Music]
I don't want to waste too much time with
these ones down there because I worry
once I kill them next round will they
immediately spawn new ones
and I will never get away from the spot
[Music]
you guessed it oh
damn
[Music]
she's gonna miss again isn't she
well it's 16 something around under 70
is anyway like poof
just gonna miss
emblem engaged with that attitude
oh no
[\h__\h]
the [\h__\h]
okay
hey
[Music]
your defeat was inevitable didn't
consider but true right why why why why
oh well
we gotta go up up up
wait we shouldn't waste engagement
I don't mind that
[Music]
thank you
armor Slayer That's Where It's At
quickly now
why are we two by one yeah sorry sorry
for waking you up and making you come
out of the ring I actually
let's go back
I'll bait them with Chihuahua should be
fine
should I let peanuts deal with the
bottom one
move up
cracks Ivy is just cracked
[Music]
up
fine if I stand here
if they can't spawn
for real though can it
[Music]
I'll help her
it's worth it not really
oh
okay she'll be fine she'll be fine right
she'll be fine she'll be fine she'll be
fun
bye bye
wait
yes yes you'll be fine
[Music]
I'm so sorry for six oh oh yeah
okay I gave her the HP bar anyway
already I forgot about that
um oh thank God
onion
okay there goes the HP bar
[Music]
gotta be careful now
oh
[Music]
wrong choice from them even the 56 I hit
back
oh
that's it holy [\h__\h] foreign
[Music]
now
papaya no
okay
you guys seem way sadder about losing
her
than the others
what does that mean I'll go all the way
back here see if I can bring veil in a
better position
but I'll move these ones first
um what did I do
[Music]
what did I even do
ah I know I killed
changing the RNG I guess because of the
order but I know I killed this one with
ivy
Unforgivable
[Music]
killed one oh but now we can do that
atrocity
and not not
falling star what
you guys are the choices but I think you
guys meant Fallen Star right
[Music]
right
because that's a bow one
um
well it doesn't kill man why it should
22 crit
um
I'll think about it don't Bank on a crit
should I just do it
the big one after all
there's a charging plate right there
I could use it
your defeat was inevitable
I need to kill him otherwise they'll
kill Hortensia yeah
look at the leftover one do anyway
though I don't remember
who did the leftover one go to did I
leave one over I did right but the
potential was probably out of range I
think
I left them for
it it did attack with tencia
hmm
I can't kill it though
man
is that really because
yeah I guess I was down here
okay if I stay here and it shouldn't
happen again
[Music]
do I wanna waste this time down here
because I only have
him left them
[Music]
I guess
no no I won't because now he must go for
he will go for Pinette
he has to
do
it isn't even in range range
oh but he might go for Ivy
[Music]
God damn it
how cool you can get I hope you can get
back before you finish up
we have two and a half more hours left
and it has to be enough
how could that not be enough also say I
couldn't even kill him so in the end
what
[Music]
foreign
what do we do different here
[Music]
we can do this this seems reasonable and
most ideal
at you
[Music]
the ax scares me we have to get the ax
out of the way
I don't think I can
[Music]
oh but they're still decoys why would
the ax not go for the decoy right
[Music]
yeah yeah
I'm off to make breakfast for dinner
yummy
[Music]
mediocre
no no no that was not Midge that was
milky High key damn
girl you did what
she did what
[Music]
oh man I want to do this
how does that
are yunaka died did she yeah she died we
don't want to do this again but what did
she die by the top ones
um
I guess I'll let him come
[Music]
this should be okay
oh goes for chihuahua
wrong wrong wrong
yeah the counter weapon you know there's
too much to think about you know I only
have one brain cell
I get to keep my illusory doubles for
another round
oh see minimum
minimum damage no
um
no new Mobs either yet just yet yet
they might come soon
oh I'm so glad I have my villa glance
now
I won't forget you
[Music]
come come come
oh
we meet again you gotta share yours I'm
not sure oh wait that's even silica oh
do no more harm hello I totally so will
the rest it deserves I totally did that
on purpose
I totally knew I was attacking with
Celica
calculated yeah
I didn't realize
all right
[Music]
um
oh that's a problem
[Music]
oh I'm leaving him alive oh no [\h__\h]
oh that's a big problem that's a big
problem I'm so sorry
because I know the silver ax is gonna
wreck her right
[\h__\h]
I know
he won't move
okay
the ones in the scissors never move okay
then I could have maybe kept her attack
for this one [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I was worried
[Music]
okay wodal
no
the rest is just 12 okay Brave sword 12
percent
we get four chances
one
up though okay okay cool though very
cool that was really low percentage
now I can finish him off with uh mobier
who
okay
Massacre
[Music]
I can always depend on you oh can't get
through this job
so that Mario doesn't get his hands
dirty
okay left side done
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
[Music]
what's that dude oh is that close no
that's a new one
[Music]
oh
um
positions okay let's get gold Mary out
of the way
um
what do I do with her
this
ah
thanks for 20 free moms oh my God
thank you so much
highly appreciated no
I was worried about that damn it
ah
in this last fight honestly they turned
my
my luck down by like
75 percent
what is up with that um
[Music]
wait what
[\h__\h]
I can't move afterwards I can move
afterwards
should I
do an astro storm while I still have it
no
no I need his power here
I need him now and here
almost revival time me too
I will protect everyone
it's the enemies being beasts
thank you for trying to make me feel
less bad
I think I'll dance and don't have much
other choice
he looks so funky when he's engaged
hmm I don't know I'll decide what to do
in a moment
I know range and all that but
um
[Music]
do not miss
um
[Music]
we have to move up
good time to waste
[Music]
okay I wonder if if alquis and yunaka
can kind of double team the Lancer
so she could
take care of this one now
all flowers eventually wilt
my love for qawwa is unkillable why are
you guys look so Charming today what's
going on
is it Valentine's Day
oh
I mean I can poison him at least
[Music]
there we go
oh wait there's still someone down here
oh baby
[Music]
yo
overpowered
classical
it's it's just yeah
traditional oh tradition it's natural I
have to have my finalists be long where
my rise of finales this long
[Music]
level UPS everything is shitty in this
finale
oh man I have to put him like here I
guess
or stay safe
[Music]
and let's Bolt
58 probably gonna miss
[Music]
if you ever do miraculous aren't random
or what do you get like full all the
time
[Music]
also pretty moms damn
man
a maddening
[Music]
okay this their round wasn't so bad and
there's still no reinforcements
this is not so bad this is not so bad
but probably gonna bring reinforcements
with together with the new like dark
emblems right
I assume
[Music]
this
quickly now okay
some of the 50 growth will level up
that's at every two levels
[Music]
just don't kill the last emblem at the
end of your round you want to Nuke some
run
now when he's still protected because I
have one emblem left now
yes till the guard yes you can I don't
even remember are you here oh because
it's a chicken I was like oh that's not
so bad is it
not yet right leave it alone Strat to
cut down time
how much damage can I do
[Music]
oh
well not much what
[Music]
oh
at the beginning of the turn to Max Ah
that's between so I have to try to
spend as little
that'll be hard but I do have uh by love
still over here
that'll be difficult though okay I can
dance
Veil probably
she hit
yeah okay
[Music]
how would I position them hmm
I could put
my life here someone here someone
here but
oh wait wait I can dance Veil now with
the dancer
[Music]
and I think once she gets closer she can
do plenty damage to kill one rich people
archer in danger
oh yeah melee arrange him to avoid the
damage
me away you mean close range
um
that's fail though
[Music]
we'll see how that goes
the dancer
[Music]
like here maybe
um
come on there's a crit somewhere in
there I know it
I know it Veil I believe in you
[Music]
yeah
an obstacle in need of removing
believing unveil pays off
but the second HP bar yeah
I might not be able to do it because
wait if I dance here
put Chloe to the right maybe
um I can put someone tomorrow
but
[Music]
I wanna do something meaningful though
with her
wait for our next turn to kill it
um
okay
it was 12 nights
maybe uh dragon the vein
[Music]
all the mobs first
I'll try
[Music]
never mind Chloe
ah okay if we're doing that then I can
charge
[Music]
okay okay
I'll have to
dance anyway
[Music]
yeah no just because I want these ones
to reach the left these mobs I guess is
there something left here oh wait there
oh
they're not a range even though
[Music]
connect can kind of catch up now
hmm
I should just Place her here what the
[\h__\h]
did that have worked
look what I found
this secret little spots
yeah so many membership updates today I
had to stop you
my problem was here was forgetting my
units on the other side of the map
oopsie well uh kiwawa will be in range
for the for the big boss but
he can not one hit kill I miss you so
all right then
[Music]
yeah I committed to doing this so I'm
gonna do it
foreign
[Music]
she can just charge if we really need a
dance again
[Music]
yeah
a little bit of damage
I shall take I'll go for the one where
he has less hit chance
five hours yeah it's been a while that I
had such a long stream huh if you said
stands right next to him
he can't attack right he has no close
range bow Minnie bow
[Music]
I'd have to stay right next to him okay
yeah see they're all kind of stuck in
here
[Music]
this is stupid
ah
too much damage to God my robot
[Music]
I gotta go with the silver sword
our ten oh no didn't I just like two
minutes ago say two and a half hours
left now we only have two hours left how
does that work makes no sense
no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
Chloe could maybe kill the one up there
quite enough huh
[Music]
who's here for since the start
who here has been watching since the
beginning
me me oh my God so many
how did you not fall asleep yet guys I
don't understand
thank you I'm also playing the game
right now oh you're in the same Zone
foreign
last thing even though not a kill no but
it's so much damage back
wait how much percentage
I might just leave him there even though
I danced her ah I guess I'll use a step
making it worthwhile
thank you
we'll figure it out guys it will all
work out
I know why I want to stand
[Music]
oh yeah right
we're not done here yet um
shoot something
okay but should we keep them like close
relatively close to the big big man
right
that would probably be smart
and range of him
koala actually is so
at this point
choose who you're liking
contemplative
that's me
that is indeed me
okay
[Music]
here take Lobby here please he's so
bulky
he'll be happy to be used as a punching
bag it's his honor his duty oh he got
some Bobby
here 29 wow
ouch okay
thanks for ignoring Kiana I think that
was a good choice
oh
wait Furby what what's pretty oh yeah
okay
[Music]
all right
decent level up maybe she got magic
again
you know I'm seeing things now the 100
looked to me like a thousand percent
probably the the little circles oh the
little circles next to the like
percentage sign
making me think I'm seeing more zeros
found someone will use disengage on his
next turn this devastating attack
forcibly cancels the engaged status
of all units now
damn okay
that sucks so if I'm gonna engage I
should go all out with the big stuff but
um
yeah that sucks
like he's gonna do it next turn
next turn AKA after I do my moves
or after that
no probably
upcoming right okay
I don't know
we'll see you can kill him in one turn
okay that would be
don't you think
in that case
who can is there anyone who can one hit
this dude
[Music]
is she only
I guess worst case will dance her but
28 oh 28 crit
I'll derange him
outrange him oh yeah right what
I thought it was a bow user
what
he was right
equipped his Lance was smart dude but it
didn't kill oh no
[Music]
I don't want to dance well maybe we can
do this with someone else uh
Charlie gold Mary you can I don't want
to rely on the Crypt now
three percent no no I'm not relying on
that
um
all right here we go
that looks better to me
yo
[Music]
still playing
can't stop won't stop
the only thing that can stop me is the
end of the game
because then that's the end
it's fully filled all right here we go
The Shield is gone everybody
it's time to party
[Music]
I'm scared
which is the strongest
damn that's nothing can I attack with
your knuckle am I I don't think I'm
close enough
on the poison just a scratch
um
oh wait I can I might die in the process
oh yeah oh wait I don't do damage never
mind
save Aliyah for Bond blast
engage Plus for kiwawa
[Music]
um
but then somebody has to stand right
next to me right away right
I can't go there and engage and then do
my thing
I could engage plus here and I'll tackle
for like
distant weapon oh yes I can
[Music]
oh hmm
who is our chosen one cockatoo
40 for the most bonus oh
yeah because marriage
I suppose oh I can't so move
the position myself for for seedel
[Music]
give him a diva for unicorn
ah the Roar
[Music]
I'm too far though
they're more damage
should I really waste my dance on that
[Music]
um
really
[Music]
otherwise
if we don't make it with how we do it
right now we can rewind and try a
different way
thanks I know
no
no no force yourself just to not lose
your streak no
no
whatever you need
I've made my choices
she looks so cool with white hair and
the black stars on it
okay
uh yeah uh
why is moving
[Music]
sorry Mommy gonna stream very long today
you want to come up here wait there's
something on you okay
she's fine
[Applause]
[Music]
hi white guy thank you
I have never seen this one before
um do you think
wait should I keep this for the second
HP bar because it seems to be doing a
lot of damage
sorry smoothies in front of the camera
I should save it right
okay
um what do I press B or a cause I'm too
scared to activate it now
be right is B
okay
sometimes I sometimes I accidentally
I just wanna Just Wanna Make sure
um all right let's throw my like weaker
supposedly
oh damn she can do a lot too
I'll wait for panette I'll wait with her
name my target Marvel isn't so good
right now
[Music]
um okay
oh I have it scary
[Applause]
[Music]
oh peanut grid no no I want to keep her
damaged for another HP bar maybe if we
need her
[Music]
hmm
wait
[Music]
okay
well it doesn't matter
you need to give it you're all who
thought he missed I feel like even if we
wouldn't do it this round we could
easily finish him off next round like
what's gonna happen
I can't wipe my whole again I will
endure
now
here our wedding night is happening now
[Music]
Bond blast oh I can even switch weapons
Liberation is best
all right
yay power blog cute
cute cute
[Music]
okay
Emperor engage
how much damage does Target to do barely
ads because not many people are around
him
um
[Applause]
[Music]
I can't see
oh
yeah
oh I'll crisp ah I forgot about him
thank you for reminding me of his
existence but uh
foreign
[Music]
bar looking good
I mean
still leaving me some things to desire
but okay now I have you Clayton same
mistake
I mean cat even really ends your turn
naturally
if you leave some units behind so you
will you'll notice eventually
I don't know if I can really do it this
turn
[Music]
foreign
I mean it feels like an endurance a
little bit but
okay
he has
uh two more left right one
of those thingies means he has two more
run for with kind too
oh can we
the bravex holy [\h__\h]
or should I hope for a crate with the
killer ax
55 is pretty darn good
yeah
okay
I will kiss her if she does it right
oh no
yeah oh I didn't kill wait she gets one
more hit
doesn't [\h__\h] yeah
um oh that sucks because
he's only got too much pre left
[\h__\h]
I still have who Ivy ah only Ivy and
kagazu
oh man
um
that's so kind of too first for two HP
isn't it we take all around him
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I left everyone standing around him
hmm
you're done for it just give up
boy
what
[Music]
what just happened there we go there we
go what
happening
what happened
what
[Music]
my numbers
we're at the end we can rewind
huh
okay I do normal attack
why it didn't look so bad to me
[Music]
uh because I was looking at the chain
attack and I guess they all missed oh
because the chain attack was really bad
percentage
okay
well annoying
hey
[Music]
no problem guys
that's really not the issue
there's a different problem here
that is I don't believe that ivy can one
hit him
my surprise
[Music]
uh
hmm
Veil
I don't know why I wouldn't be able to
reach
three percent crit you guys are living
the dream
[Music]
you're done for it please die
laughs
what what
was that where all my other Curts went
towards
what
what we've won sombron no I
never return home I was so
what's the joke that is just this word
telling what you guys some of you guys
said the three percent I was just doing
it for funds and I was gonna say I'm
Danny with the funny dances with the
funsies
laughs
whoever added to the pile of ah try to
tried a three percent one
you're the real MVP today cause you
convinced me to do a funny thing
what
[Music]
uh that is unbelievable that is
absolutely unbelievable yeah maybe I
should have played with ivy
[Applause]
no no no thanks to me Hortensia got even
stronger you know you know made her into
someone useful
beautiful Ivy from beginning once we had
her until the end she just never
disappointed me never never never never
never never hmm
that is insane this is so typically Fire
Emblem engaged what the [\h__\h]
oh my God
but that is crazy I mean I would have
liked to see somehow what would have
happened if I would have not killed him
in this one round
what next what next it's one what it's
half plus one a.m my God
I am me too me too
soon for
the emblem of Foundations
[Music]
oh thank you guys though
three percent you chose to be alone
continued to look for this every person
why
perhaps can't I wanted someone to
appreciate
who I am
after Millennia of being Cast Away
I couldn't pin that person
or fail
or our siblings
why didn't you let us too late now
I need no connection I like how we
though literally needed every unit of
hours and you don't want to be a father
to us big teamwork
um
very well you'll only be the fell dragon
every unit counted that we slayed
That's How we'll remember you exactly no
Daddy
yes evil known for all this time
why should my death be different thanks
guys
thank you
I will feed in this place
apart from the one I yearn to see he's
gonna go out the rap milk save those
another hour another hour you think that
would have changed for the emblem of
Foundations
I have tried
I again and again I said the words
oh a whole new barrier with like a try
oh yeah last time the other emblems he
would have summoned
oh thank God
[Music]
oh
this light
at last
at last we meet again the once was at
three percent they're gonna go into my
hall of fame
I don't see anyone
I don't either
it must be someone only he can see an
old friend
the one person he truly LED in
his emblem
who did he let in once more
engaged
the emblem
will we see it was he the emblem
but
Papa
he's gone
welcome in the ring for the emblem
foundations
why won't they with him why won't they
show me he's over
let's go home I want to see the what who
is time to shut this portal once and for
all
creative
what
portal is like a real person you mean
once it shut the war ends oh and balance
returns to the world we did it
foreign
indeed
it's really Time to Say Goodbye
this was a wonderful Journey
thank you for letting us share it with
you no
thank you Martha
go
but it's time to stand tall and say
goodbye
thank you for keeping your promise you
really were my Ally short stream my
friend
man through it all it's it's so such a
bad time to be a a bad a bad thing a bad
experience would be a Chihuahua
takanashikara fan man she streams so
little she streams so so rarely
so so such short time like 11 hours
I wish I wish I could see her more like
she's starving us literally
to death
because she's breaking a heart
she's abusing us
such a I don't know why I even support
her she sucks but I still will follow
her
the worst the worst honesty to have is
Kiana
oh she never she doesn't like us she
doesn't pay attention she doesn't no he
doesn't do anything
[Music]
I'll be strong enough for whatever lies
ahead you will be she won't pay us
already much stronger yeah well that's
true years ago that's true that's the
only thing that's true
carrion's Legacy and your mothers
will not be here
that won't change now
turn to help
up as the Divine dragon and as an emblem
I will
you guys are
really we'll be there
be there
[Music]
yes please don't worry
no good
here come the tears
we didn't know they're crying for a
different reason just getting to know
you and now
goodbye forever
oh no
we're suffering together but don't cry
guys burdens are yours to shoulder
proudly
you should not always hold back tears
please
for now
try to I agree
I'd like for us to park with smiles on
our faces that's how I want us to
remember each other enjoy not sorrow me
too
laughs
I woke up at nine today watch the stream
went for every meal for 10 hours so
that's absolutely worth it thank you
this is goodbye
but we'll never Bid Farewell to what you
think together
[Music]
but I know you'll choose the right paths
to walk
[Music]
no matter the distance
build a bright future thank you bye-bye
[Music]
don't worry I can see that your lives
will be filled with hope and
thank you Mikaya
[Music]
go out and create a better world
I know you will
bye bye
you could
I will be praying for you all cute
praying that your world is filled with
kindness sorry I didn't use your lunch
[Music]
may the blessings of Mother Earth and
father Sky follow one of the bestest bye
bye
[Music]
I'm glad to have known you
you make an Arcadia of this land
I'm so sorry that they made you so
useless bye
oh wait it was your name no it was you
it was you sorry there is no hardship
you can Roy was late they all look alike
come on
bye
[Music]
No Love
I mean when did I use Roy too though
carry the light
nothing will be impossible bye-bye
six thanks for giving everybody cancer
not cancer Cantor
lead with compassion Divine one and may
your happiness be eternal
beautiful beautiful
so pretty
it's the moment muff so it is
you are a member of our family
the emblem who connects us all if ever
we cross paths again no when we cross
paths again I hope that you will
remember us
we who existed together for this time
the 13 emblems
course I'll remember you
everything about you
and all the times we shared even when
we're apart
thank you
for standing with me until the very end
we'll see okay
see you in Smash in the future
don't say that don't give her get her
hopes up
there will be no more smash participants
gave me courage
strength and inspiration
[Music]
I will follow your example always
I promise
let's go back home everyone
back to Elios why can't she stay she's
an emblem too
was it because she's the emblem from
this world or so
[Music]
Returns what on the prologue oh
she has a physical body
[Music]
five turns did we go from six minutes to
nine minutes to 28 minutes oh 27 oh it's
gonna get much higher soon
oh oh going up to an hour
um
ah there it is big jump one hour 30.
oh it went down to an hour there oh it
must have been a short one
somehow
an hour
not bad
[Music]
oh under an hour wow wow wow wow
oh and look how often Celine and Celica
were the MVPs what's going on there wow
Celine and was MVP so often
oh this is where Al Chris starts being
super cool
okay
[Music]
um
chilling around an hour
silica was op back then what did she do
what did she do
40 minutes
oh was that Retreat we just ran away
oh two hours but that was a divine
paralog
um
I was still using Diamond Back Then
Sentinels
50 minutes or two hours for chapter 14.
well what happened there two hours
there was one that was just longer
because we had myth in the background
distracting me
two hours maybe that was the one
two hours two hours I was becoming the
norm but then cutting it down to one
hour oh and then catch up to three hours
what happened
oh
one and a half what was in the chapter
17 what happened
oh one hour wow out of the vine parallel
that was a short one
and a half
well it wasn't always so bad huh
almost two hours
oh two hours yeah okay now I think from
here on out there's no way
oh wow wait what how many chapters are
there why is Dimitri there
all because that's part of the edel
Guard gang
oh one hour
26 oh wait I felt like
all our recent ones were three hours but
hey it's not so bad oh look that that
one house one only took an hour
and torture you guys for too long
[Music]
foreign
did we ever go over three hours it seems
like we didn't
[Music]
ivy
believe it is
so much suffering
[Music]
anything else
oh huh what Kiana became the new Divine
Dragon Monarch her bonds of the rulers
of each Nation resulted in lasting peace
Hortensia joined I've been restoring
illusion while enrolled at the Academy
she later returned to lipos and used her
studies to support her blue friend after
the Divine Dragon Monarch took the
throne Vander seeded his role as a
stealer choosing to live as a knight on
the thumbnail the new monarch and her
friends visited Bender often he always
met the group with a smile as he took a
great joy in Remembering their journey
journey though he wasn't really part of
classic see the van there is a student
as he Grew Older his level had a
demeanor was likened to vander's own oh
he's so reverted Avengers
Fran served as a steward maturing into
protective Force every bit as calm and
attentive as rather heard Zeal for the
Divine Dragon Monaco never waned when it
came time to choose she held a cheering
contest for all the candidates
oh God do we have to reach for all of
them as king of Ferry and Alfred forged
a new non-aggression can I like stop
this Auto thingy
as he died and early death what however
he was loved by his people what
he dead
besides serving Farine with her own
strength Etsy booked up with Soldiers
with a regimen of weight training and
muscle stimulants some said this was at
odds of the nation's pacifist efforts
but it was okay
worked for many years to restore firing
upon seeing Flora portfolio restored he
cried tears of joy he traveled so often
between the castle and Florida in honor
of this kind of signification of Road
connected aha was called named after him
okay
[Music]
her Life's a piece in the Kingdom of
serene this sometimes meant taking the
unpopular position of punishing those
who Disturbed order her favorite tea
became known as the tea of blessings and
Serene religion had that it the drink
would find a joy okay
Louis retired as a knight and became a
butler to the royal family oh
congratulations
he's interested in people watching was a
lifelong love but however many tried to
join them he always preferred to throw
guns along
hey
Clover the royal family and her fellow
Soldiers with deliveries of folk food
soon farin's local Delicacies started
including more unusual flavors years
later she met someone at a postal and
they had a fairy tab
oh good for her as a new king of protea
diamond ordered a hugs to all invasions
and worked to perform his people's
attitudes on illusion some Nobles this
is Diamond at first but his vision for
the future earned their favor by
exploring okay good for him
Emma was overjoyed to see Diamond sit on
brolia's Throne he patrolled the kingdom
to Quail post-war chaos and misadventure
followed him with every step in time he
became one of the very Legends he had so
admired portrays always played senior
and alpaca confront in Scotland
[Music]
rise to the broken throne with pride and
throw the cake she always found time to
ride despite her business schedule and
manage to complete over 100 humor novels
in her lifetime all celebrities
Masterpiece as well
[Music]
the two Nations grew to trust each other
expanding a mutual trade he was praised
as brilliant yet humble strategist who
kept his brother the new king safe just
as he promises Lane father oh
he quit but he also protect lapis
traveled to Lorton towns and taught
students how to repair their homes at
every stop she left large delicious
potatoes from the farm in their home
Village in her room the purple and the
potatoes brought her Village wealth and
prosperity and her lap is a new title
the potato goddess
citrine redoubled her efforts to sway
Brody and Nobles away from Warfare while
fast
despite her great weight on her
shoulders her graceful smile was ever
present especially at the balls and
Gallows that she loved
happy as Queen of Illusion Irish drove
to rebuild her water nation and improve
the insular culture through diplomacy
with Brody and her decision to import
orgray gave rise to lucrative minerals
Legacy endured even after cat had passed
on
cool okay
I'm dead
thanks for telling me like that
after completing his work as Princess
Iris retained at zelkop's next Pursuit
was to create a shelter for the children
in illusion who were offered by the way
what the [\h__\h] he and his new family were
very happy it is said that those
children all learned to speak in a quiet
and perform meaningful meaningful area
disappeared after Irish coronation some
said he was off searching for a worthy
opponent in fact he had gone home to ask
his family's permission to live in
illusion and serve the queen working on
the ivy he still made visits to pale
Sans returning each time this he's like
um Arya from Game of Thrones you don't
know where he went although we really
want to know Rosanna was dealt the night
for his service so he's he traveled the
land seeking to destroy the corrupted
for good resuming his studies only when
the task was done later in life he
earned further Fame as an artist A
Portrait of the glory family at their
cutest still hangs in loser castles at
their cutest
uh though she was at the night for her
service gold Mary soon discovered that
her true gift was teaching she became a
top instructed Illusions Academy so many
of her students went on to do great
things that she felt a need to apologize
to her classes for the pressures she
placed on them
what
huh
Tamara traveled far and wide after the
war so she never forgot her to use as a
queen returning to the Palace often to
greet guests with a smile the people to
ever met during her travels cared very
much for her and she became the most
beloved Queen in some history yeah I can
imagine
Baron traveled to Mara Gathering
material for her book on rare creatures
though it had few readers upon
publication the work came to be
treasured for its insights and dragons
in her later years Marin went back home
and took her place as a matriarch
uniting her Village cool
[Music]
ant served her served to Mara as her
Knight in short safety through Diva's
close in time she could also subdue an
enemy with a single blow so she searched
for her missing parents she never found
them still she quietly revealed her
family's Church oh she did
traveled aimlessly until tomorrow's
coronation and then returned to the
Palace to serve behind the scenes as her
advisor though few reliable accounts of
his life were left in the history books
and said he met someone doing his
travels and they said oh
[Music]
found a popular new religion worshiping
all dragons called called cult he
planned a huge roll killed party in
lupus but when Vander blocked he made a
slightly Tamer his cheerful howl later
became known as a special prayer to the
Divine Dragon Monarch what
Pune who rebuild his parents Bistro it
became wildly popular for serving dishes
beloved by solemn royalty as well as
Kiana he left to turn the world and
taste food putting all he learned into
uh yeah okay I don't know who is he
Adam finally reunited uh some of those
extra characters that you didn't have to
get with her family she had many sisters
all with the same name and face
with the emblem's success and the war of
rings came strongly into fashion she
made all the prophets
John became a great doctor and after
taking over his father's Clinic he
visited Lifest once a month to make
house calls passionate about researching
new medicines John found his Village's
famous tea leaves okay cool
if it came a straight performer and she
put on a captivating ant for a few years
then vanished about the chance did you
perished on a new life oh no some say
the Divine Dragon the monarchs use of
unusual word was due to her influence
and she gone see now became famous the
world over for his dancing unfortunately
in later years he was a traveling
performer telling up his time with Kiana
according to the fortune he read for
himself he was fighted to meet good
people enjoy great food and live a very
happy life indeed
London after the war Linden returned
home to a legendary retirement he passed
on a peaceful spring morning returning
to the side of his beloved wife in the
Hereafter for his memory lives on
whenever pastry pastry stop here suffer
returned to borrow your castle and took
up a position in King Diamond's personal
guard later in life she retired to her
Village and started a seafood restaurant
those small the place attracted
customers from far and wide its menu
featured a dish said to have been loved
by King morion
[Applause]
and made it into a last green land she
resisted the crown for over a century
then it last gave in to her people's
wishes and became the first Monarch in
gradland by then many of her old friends
had died but their offspring on piano
were at the event whoa
Mobius drove to its home by aiding
others his Good Deeds continued into
later life when he went out and was
never heard from again some say he was
in an accident others that a victim of
the four hounds took Revenge oh they
only turned
God damn it why I couldn't even like
stop it
what
a lot of people just died
like Kiana is dead at some point whoa
she's wearing something similar to her
mommy or to Sam
[Music]
oh
more
[Music]
y'all
that's me
[Music]
Here Comes pain and arts
this
[Music]
characters that I never use let's go
immune it should be fine
[Music]
Bench Warmers
I like this too oh free there's free on
the picture I like them all sorry Louie
I mean I use them for a while
more than others
it was fine too
[Music]
yeah it's almost 2 am for me but I'm not
even that tired
sorry Jane for giving up on you as well
but she was good too
[Music]
show me
a little picture of his bro in the back
or his dad I guess he's done
oh they were also killed
those girls
loved their character designs and they
weren't bad in battle either
wow wow wow what can I say I
no she was already a queen but let's go
foreign
look at her flawless
gorgeous
be careful the food will fall off
oh the dude is there too and she's a
queen queen actually was a princess
um
same thing oh
mommy grave
oh my grave
I was scared
oh
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Queen
thank you
[Music]
Samara I love her design so much
going on
is it grilling
[Music]
that's a good picture is he like happy
because he's burning this Village so
that was what it looks like she's like
okay they're having a party
[Music]
they're all the same
nice to perform together yeah that makes
sense because they had that lore
[Music]
the oldies but Goldies
mail
oh
sweet video more Avail please
more Veil
yeah okay oh
that's supposed to be like
like confusing us right
why is there like you know a little
money
yeah it's probably like oh she looks
like morning like reminding her but I
mean
you know
oh
wait
maybe in the archive quickly take one
oh
me
today's the day my coronation today I'll
be crowned the Divine Dragon Queen what
if she gets assassinated during it I had
hoped that all of you would be standing
by my side for the occasion
[Music]
but I guess not
she looks different
[Music]
because I watch too much Game of Thrones
emblem of beginnings
to this day she's still polishing the
Rings every day
you wonder if we'll ever meet again
I knew we'd find you in here
we must have looked everywhere
everyone
the coronation is going to start any
minute yo they all look so polished
unless you're wearing that oh
[\h__\h] huh
[Music]
oh hurry up come on they won't show us
right because too much effort to model
that
coming someday in the future
our paths may cross once more
our bonds can be reforged time and again
whenever you desire you need only say
the word
what really engaged
oh
I want to save it here I don't know
see you in Smash
[Music]
that's it
that's brilliant huh
oh man we reached 11 hours
in six minutes
no no
DLC no we're done
we're done uh
oh
I feel better kind of
can't be bothered with it now
[Music]
ah
um engage
um
this one right
time to
[Music]
do
the bad ending really quickly really
quickly
wait can I like
face them all alone start
you dare turn your blade on me it's the
same you dare interfere with that
solo run would be so cool to see someone
do it though is it possible
your scrambling is both futile
oh people have done it man overpowered
how I want to watch it I can fight
kill me
ah
you are pathetic yeah right now I really
am to be a Divine Dragon was not enough
Patrick okay we've already heard this I
think
[Music]
he'll miss probably
what an equip your weapons oh
no kill me please
there we go
the downfall of taco
[Music]
endo
is this really How It Ends
I'm so sorry everyone
yeah but it's good because you're giving
us a special ending
thank you I promised I would fight by
your side until the very end don't die
no no what
do I have to like rewind
the gold time
it'd be if you chose
Doom shall be upon us
what happened
everyone you care about
they are all dead
that's just how I wanted it
whoa
oh [\h__\h]
she looks so mature dear sister ah it's
time to go will she forever keep me in
the ring
oh
I'm Fred
this is so good
that was so good that's so good
yeah
yay
so
she's red but like she's shocked at it
so she's not like purely evil yet at
that moment I wonder like
she just like
not it
look she still seems to be understanding
like what's going on
yeah if if evil why hot
but ah right ah red emblem so that means
yeah she can not talk
probably right
shouldn't be able to talk
and not do anything
oh no
um we're trying to tile thanks
no free and will
all right that was cool uh wow very very
very long Play Through Fire Emblem from
yours yours truly let me just go here
because I don't want anything to happen
um thank you guys for going through this
journey with me
[Music]
I think on its own it was pretty good
um but since I played free houses after
all of this I can still say very
confidently that I enjoyed Fire Emblem
free houses more
yeah
but
it was it was nice to be like
strategized strategizing again
um I like this type of game
uh s
jrpg
strategy RPG
so oh it was nice to play that kind of
game again
um
yeah
I feel like you know everything was
pretty predictable and tacky cheesy
but some some cheesy Parts made me feel
very warm inside and fuzzy inside too
and that was fun like around the end as
well
they were like throwing so much cheese
at me I became a cheese lover
um
yeah
I liked a bunch of the characters and
some of the character development was
good
um
I know
I don't know what to say
good moments some boring moments
some frustration like I must say the
menus were frustrating
um yeah and the whole like okay we go
into a battle we hear a little bit of
story and then we go back into the
thumbnail we do the same thing over and
over again the thumbnail as well it's
always the same thing it's like really
repetitive
uh
I don't know if I felt the same way for
free houses
did I feel like this for free houses
it felt so repetitive
no
I don't remember it anymore
not really I don't think so either
I mean it surely was like kind of
repetitive on its own as well
I rushed them oh yeah I probably didn't
spend as much time in the monastery and
also Monastery was just bigger
it was more kind of I feel like to look
at to run around
um
gets more repetitive if you do the other
rounds oh I think what I liked was that
actually the tea time in free houses
that would have been fun to have again
actually I really like those dates
that was actually pretty
fun and entertaining
in hindsight I was really scared about
the difficulty that I chose but and it
was really just fine I could have gone
with classic but then if we would have
gone with classic we would have been
probably even more careful but we never
ran out of rewinds so but even then uh
yeah if we really wanted to keep
everyone we would have probably
eventually run out of rewinds at some
point somewhere
next time classic yeah if I play another
five limb game sometime if another one
comes out
uh during my time hold on then I think
I'm I'm gonna try classic and I won't
care if people die because I now can say
for sure you will not run out of units I
mean if they continue like this
yeah it's hard to run out of units I
suppose
it will hurt nonetheless but I think it
would be good it would be more
interesting and then you can you know
switch around play some that you haven't
played much before I had this problem I
couldn't choose which ones to take with
me a lot of the time
yeah
um
you're definitely proof you can handle
classic I think so too no no no no no
a dragon yeah as a playthrough on my
channel you know I feel like Tales of
arise was around the same length but I
never felt like oh I hope this ends soon
the tales have arise I never felt like
that
and other longer games not sure if I
felt like that with others but this one
yeah I think we all I don't know why
particular
probably really the rep repetition and
the
the fact that the story didn't like
capture us as much maybe
yeah for Tales of the Rises on my knees
begging for it not to end
yeah but but I I did enjoy the gameplay
I do really enjoy this gameplay of the
strategy battles the round based
strategy
uh falling asleep while I'm talking
about this
um I didn't enjoy that don't
misunderstand me but overall like you
know the whole little bit of story
battle a little bit of story some nil
the number of story battle a little bit
of stories thumbnail
I was just
um
[Music]
yeah
yeah I am always the same pattern
[Music]
oh I'm so tired now suddenly gotta eat
some food apparently my mom's coming by
tomorrow to pick something up good that
I'm not streaming I guess
um
so I hope she doesn't come too early
because I need to sleep man
yeah
[Music]
Valkyrie Chronicles
yeah but nonetheless and even though you
know I know I know I know
these games are not interesting for
everybody and also you know spoilers and
this and that
um so I want to say big big big big big
big big huge thank you to everybody who
committed to watching this
uh
even when it got really long thank you
so much for being part of it and thank
you so much for helping me with my
indecisiveness
and my one brain cell thank you so much
it's been a pleasure and we had some
up and ups and downs some roller
coasters emotionally too and I'm playing
but I just was not feeling it but you
guys also helped me cheer up so thank
you very much for a good time for
spending time with me so much until uh
tears of the Kingdom there will be a
little bit of a Down time because I'll
be filling it with shorter streams
shorter games
yeah so until then some of the people
who for example haven't been keeping up
with this one probably can catch up on
the Vaughn as well
a month away yeah a month Mario Kart oh
welcome play Mario Kart again too sure
why not
yeah I'm dying right now wow it's like
suddenly my batteries
are instantly
drained
like I I keep up for so long until the
very last moment where I can let go
um I'm falling asleep and my throat
hurts
okay thank you guys so much
thank you I love you guys
tomorrow evening probably schedule yay
yes
um
yeah thank you very much
I love you guys too
two two pedal pedal hmm
I'll give this game a
um
seven out of ten no
yeah
yeah did I ever write uh free houses
I feel like six is too low seven feels
too high but still
I'm okay with that pretty decent very
generous
sleep out of 10.
[Music]
what you're not saying I rated at 6.5
right
I don't know if I if I rated free houses
lower than that then I must change it
but otherwise
the characters were good to me yeah I'll
miss I'll miss like Hortensia
and Veil AKA neurosama
and and
yunaka
um and Celine I really like Celine too
and and well yeah Ivy was
I I didn't like Ivy so much as a
character as a like personality as much
as I liked her as a character for damage
you know
that's a thing
[Music]
um
she was cool but you know nothing that
I'll say I'll miss
cool design though yeah very cool
character designs all right all right
all right bye-bye
[Music]
see you
oh yeah we're gonna miss the net Kiana
yeah understandable
oh
[Music]
God damn it oh man
if someone has like a screenshot of that
last moment when I was trying to insert
myself
can you add me on Twitter
I don't think it's a spoiler right
don't think that's a spoiler
someone got it
good night girls
oh
[Music]
um