[Music]
do
my
[Music]
do
me
[Music]
do
they have similar hairstyles what do you
think guys today is mostly a japanese
stream
i'm sorry but today mostly i will speak
japanese uh this game is also only
japanese and and yeah we will do our
best
it's pretty short michigan
[Music]
so let's get started uh into this horror
game
[Music]
oh
but
it doesn't look like it exploded
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
oh
hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
my
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh
foreign
game over
m
um
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
um
okay
[Music]
me
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
huh
um
mmm
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
is
[Music]
foreign
m
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah
[Music]
oh
it
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
what
um
[Music]
my
um
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
no
[Laughter]
[Music]
no
foreign
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
we
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
hey
foreign
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
what
okay
oh
[Music]
foreign
um
that's
[Music]
foreign
energy wants to learn english by
communication
[Music]
thank you thank you
kiana learned japanese by communication
um
foreign
[Music]
oh
oh yeah so english english english
english okay
question please question
[Music]
what do you like
or
other uniform
[Music]
what is the uniform oh
uh which
which country
do you want to visit
[Music]
uh spain spain
what i want to look yeah i want to see i
want to see spain one day
spain
ah
and since
uh well 12
since 12.
yes
[Music]
a
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
um
[Music]
this is a little bit in the future but
since we're here together i thought we
should just say it now
and
um
we're releasing a song cover at the end
of
march or if it's too late beginning of
april orlando
orlando
coming soon
[Music]
is
you know
[Music]
um it is still going to be a while but
in order to not miss it you should
subscribe to her channel it's in the
description
[Music]
foreign
yeah yeah i will read super chats uh in
like one or two minutes um to say
goodbye to the energy and i'll read the
super chats yeah otherwise it's just
just such a tiny short stream
today
[Music]
many things together as odenzo
so please be kind and hang out with nana
as well of course
[Music]
um
all right so this year maybe we'll do
some more stuff together i think that
would be really cool yeah let's hang out
together and with that said that was
nene
thank you
[Music]
i'll be doing an intermission for a
little
[Music]
while bye-bye
back back i'm back
back
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah we'll be reading super chats now
and we're back to
english shoe i thought it would be
better to do it in this stream because
otherwise there would be like two short
streams that just are too short i don't
like it when it's too short it must be a
long stream always always always
now it probably won't be that long
anyway but yeah um reading
super chats
we can't have a short stream can you
well i mean at least like i don't know
it's kind of like having a one hour only
stream on my channel that's like yeah i
i like to uh um
avoid that generally
uh
yeah yeah
or at least like two short ones in one
day i don't know
it might just be me although kelly said
she
is the same in that way
no you might not understand what we
streamers think all the time but
yeah we are a mysterious
being let me make myself a bit bigger i
changed clothes too and changed clothes
i don't know how quickly i got out of
that kimono
yeah this is the handshake event
from
we were talking about um you know trying
to get closer to toki no sora in the
game for um a handshake event you know
like idols usually have
handshake events
yeah
i'm saying yo i have a ticket yo yo yo i
want to get to my handshake even why you
keep why you keep running away come on
alrighty
nancy read all the texts for me because
i mean there were a lot of texts that i
was able to read as well but i asked
nana to
read them after all because i was too
nervous to read
yeah but that way we got energy to talk
a lot which i think was lovely
yes yes yes oh yeah jingle bell is still
running in the background
and now i finally understand the
reference isn't that lovely
apparently had some trouble reading as
well but generally she is able to read
much more than me obviously so
yeah i think it's it was a good idea to
bring her here
so clean i need to bring back
some stuff
[Music]
there's a photo here's some papers
gotta get back to work you know
um
remember that collab that one boy
good old days man that's a long time ago
that's a long time ago
let's put that here then
yeah audience you my beloved
huh that was so cute
the art yeah i asked yuna to draw us
like in in the idol cloves from whole
life
together yeah being tated for fun
well well as as we've just announced
that's that's the other collab uh uh the
other collab song cover that i was
working on that i told you that i was
working on and it's still gonna take a
while um the art is done the singing is
done and mixing is pretty much almost
done but the video might take a while so
we're not sure when exactly it's coming
out um
but uh that's what what i've been
working on on the side as well it has
been in the works for a while but yeah
finally now we're like speeding it up
now uh yeah we're just basically just
waiting for the music video
for the music video
yeah i think it will show you guys that
orenzo has the potential to become a
real idol group wouldn't that be lovely
i i kind of want to like do a
you know how umici is a thing and like
uh
some other units for example that
promotional curry
unit that they had before i really want
to want it to be like like almost
official audience i want i want that to
be a thing i want i want the management
to
acknowledge us as an official unit would
be much easier though if i were able to
go to japan
[Music]
what about turn duck and yeah turducken
has to be in unit as well honestly
i i would love to see turducken
uh doing some stuff together as well
yeah we have seen subato senpai's
potential already many times in many
other performances
so we know she can do it but we gotta
see elena and me
together as well
turducken and odenz yeah that is my
oh that is something i'm dreaming about
um turducken
original song and olan's original song
[Music]
orange too but i feel like uh
uh
they're
what answer is orenza is just asked to
it's a two people unit yeah
[Music]
because there's just like you know we
have a connection yeah
yeah yeah yeah ever since that first
collab that we did together i love my
nancy with all my heart
yeah but we haven't collabed in a while
um so i i asked her to support me in
this japanese only stream thankfully she
was up for it yeah she didn't um
i thought you know i thought that she
did a whole live era stream herself
because she uh is kind of in the game
but
she didn't yet so
um i guess this was a good opportunity
for her as well
um
as soon as possible
yeah yeah
oh
i forgot to turn on bgm
um
[Music]
oh yeah about the game what did you
think about the game it's just a
a simple
horror game i didn't expect the whole
escape
part to happen
that was unexpected
but yeah
er game over two times
very simple there is a lot of story like
you know a lot of reading it's very
focused on
creating an atmosphere
by
reading the story i suppose so you gotta
you know jab jab japan loves their
like um
how to say
they love their
spooky stories they like to tell spooky
stories
um
so that's where the focus was i did tell
her about outlast though but i think
this is generally like
the style
of spookiness that japanese people
prefer
[Laughter]
[Music]
thanks thanks to
growing game over
i was able to do some
chit chat yeah ufos landslides
earthquakes gas explosions i got kind of
lost
yeah there was a lot going on but the i
think the
the um they wanted to tell us that
there was the question if
whether or not
the
transfer student was the one who was
cursed or if it was algami the place
that this was playing in was cursed
um
so the thing is it's cursed that's why
so many crazy things happen
um
but i would say it's not the transfer
student it's it's owl got me the place
itself
that is cursed
pretty obviously
yeah
uh okay let me
let's see what what do you wanna what do
you wanna hear
door danny
[Music]
have so many
so many songs
maybe one i haven't used recently
what about this one
ah it's loud on my side
i know you guys don't hear it how about
now
this is like
not quite fitting but whatever
it's kind of uplifting and like the the
ending of a stream huh maybe
pokemon super chats mostly
of brand youtube generic uh true that's
that's
that's what it is it does sound kind of
youtube generic could be damaged it does
you're right
shall we go on audio stock i'm not happy
with the
stuff that i have now
um
audio stock
what do we want kawaii
keywords kawaii
um
[Music]
it's interesting
pretty cool but no
oh oh this is ukulele
lele
i already have this one i already have
this one
[Music]
very calm
oh it's dark
this is so cute
huh
in stock
[Music]
harmonica
oh that gave me a little bit of animal
crossing vibes i like that it's very
very calm oh i love it
okay okay okay okay using this one hell
yeah
here we go no audio stock version do you
guys wanna hear now i'm on audio stock
if you want now i could actually give
you a link to it
for once i could give you a link
here
if if you are curious
[Music]
i sent it in the chat
okay let me uh i'm gonna read them
normally today since it was a short
stream my throat feels fine
uh
kill off suni you'll move on
i like the audio stock version you think
it's lacking something now
yeah it's perfect the way it is
um oh did you search for one but did you
find it i think i might be able to
is there a little
way to see which ones i've downloaded
yes there is i could just
if you guys really want for some reason
i mean it's a lot holy
i have a list of everything i've
downloaded
[Music]
like i can
link back to the
the ones that i uh
uh downloaded before
i can find them in theory someone found
them for me okay
okay okay i like the bjm from from your
kimono review
[Music]
i would probably be able to find that
too
ah yeah it's a screenshot yeah if you
can like just uh type in if you're able
to type japanese and you could no
actually they have numbers they have
numbers if i give you if i give you a
screenshot and you just type in the
number
you should be able
to find it because
the number is in the url yeah yeah yeah
yeah
okay next time you guys are curious i
might i might just post you
all of the
all of the numbers
and you can go through it yourself
um
go get your own audio suckers
subscription yeah but there are like
overseas audio stock uh websites i think
and then there's this japanese one
and uh the japanese one has different
ones i think
all right when i put up the thumbnail
someone else
someone is on it
arceus
you guys say rcs2 or do you have to say
archaeolus i say our sales because in
japanese it's written
[Music]
oh i didn't use it but i woke up pretty
early today anyway early as in 12 even
though i wanted to sleep until one
o'clock
i woke up at 12. our chaos you guys say
oh some of you guys say are chaos
i go by the japanese writing
[Music]
i say it the correct way well what is
how would you know what the is that a
real word is a real word
i'm just saying
that y'all
[Music]
um
the english pronunciation is arc because
pokemon didn't want it to be ice
well you me you made that up out of your
butt didn't you your arse
korean savings japanese sounds i thought
so yeah
um
[Music]
that sounds like an artist theory to me
it's true eh
do you where did you get that info from
ah
for real
i remember people talking about arse
when it came out
oh come on that is so stupid
like i never thought of that
myself
[Music]
nintendo always concerned about family
friendly
i don't know
[Music]
how juvenile the internet is yeah
wow
i mean
maybe maybe not maybe it wasn't even
that many people who made fun of it
maybe just two people was enough for
nintendo to be like nope okay let's
change it up
but where did you find like the official
pronunciation for it though
the anime ah
the anime english dub said arceus
well that's confusing
it's not even uh
uh
[Music]
well whatever
there's tons of examples of it being
said out loud
by like official producers or whatever
[Music]
oh
english dub isn't always right that is
true but i would think that there would
be supervision over the english dub of a
pokemon
series where they would be very careful
of things being pronounced correctly
i would think so but
nintendo direct oh
probably yeah
well yeah maybe it's like freedom maybe
you could even say
um
our
choice
our choice that's how i'm going to say
from now on
our choice
pokemon legends our show is our choice
normally eu
in german is pronounced uh like um for
example
uh
the word europe
uh eu in german pronounced oy
[Music]
okay but c is normally not pronounced
like shh i'm just making up right
now
very german pronounced it would be
ah
nah you know what a german would
probably still
reading that would still try to
pronounce it properly like art sales
but if we want to be funny we can say
our choice
okay this
this is all
unnecessary let's start reading
making up yeah with c exactly
[Music]
let's start reading super chats
completely
swooshed over navitz red one there's
nothing written there but i will give
you a kiss
thank you for the red one
thank you thank you thank you
you forgot to write the message or did
you do that on purpose
to help me rest my voice i will take it
as that
i will take it like that
[Music]
wait a second that was a rainbow an
empty rainbow are you kidding me
naveed
what
[Music]
what's the matter with you
an empty rainbow
that's kind of a sad rain but thank you
i just saw it's a rainbow thank you
[Music]
wait did you
did you purposefully write a lot
thinking that i would read it with my
new system
gerard
are you here
it's probably early for
gerard i see a lot of text here
it's not a red unless it's
unless i put them all together
but you know what i will i will read
this one quietly
even though you guys don't see it
[Music]
oh
okay this might actually be better to
read quietly um
oh no
[Music]
thank you
wait i'm reading a super chat now
um
[Music]
no need for a kiss of course you're
getting kissed you stupid bugger sassy
buckle
[Music]
thank you um yeah please take some time
for
you know
healing and
finding
finding happiness again
if you're not feeling well right now
because of the things that happened and
then please take as much time as you
need we are always welcome back
yeah i wish you the best and i'm sorry
i'm sorry that you had a loss in your
family that is very unfortunate i myself
have
not really experienced that
much at least not to someone that's
close to me so um i can only imagine how
it feels but it must be very very tough
yeah
so please take time to heal yeah
and when you feel better or when you
want to feel better even if you don't
feel better yet we're always here for
you
thank you
for your support
thank you soon mukbang thank you for the
red super chat
[Music]
should i should i maybe
a lot of people thought i would uh
probably
a lot of these jokes that you guys are
making don't really work this way
hmm well i will read it book book
don't say anything tension just let me
bask in your majestic radiance as you
sit there quietly
chimpkins is it working is he resting
her voice
i'm not i guess but i'm fine today
if i've always had this dream of
watching a phoenix count 2000 silently
in her head while sipping honey tea
please
thousand that will take me years
man no
[Music]
[Laughter]
mission failed yeah well
i'm not gonna count to a thousand bucks
like what is your problem
just take them
take a png of me
think that it's just me
just
trying really hard not to move
and counting silently to a thousand
just imagine well i won't be doing it
now
thank you for the red super chat though
sorry i did read it out loud now but you
can't tell me you can't tell me you
don't enjoy this
uh speaking of enjoying enjoy of
hellblade thank you for a ransom chat it
says this is for mama tony so i don't
have to read it right
[Music]
wow 75 is quite a lot
i will not read it out loud then
thank you though i will let my mom know
i guess i don't know if she's interested
in hellblade but
uh i don't know mama you're listening to
the stream probably not because um
it was advertised as a japanese-only
stream so she's probably not here but
mom someone's recommending hellblade to
you
[Music]
jacob 47 out there okay
thank you for the pinky
no tangents for this one please just
sending love and support i respect you
so much bernie so cute
you stay with us for a long time you can
move on to the next super chat after
reading kia i love
i love you ah
okay
daisy thank you
it's very hard to just go by like that
thank you for the red super chat daisy
it says please read the following out
loud
it's just
nothing
[Music]
okay okay uh
how do i read nothing out loud
that's a thinker
that's a that's a finger
[Music]
or
i did it
[Music]
nothing
on the chimken nugget duncan
[Music]
go i by the way did you guys watch
podcast employees uh live concert i
couldn't watch everything because i had
to prepare for the stream with energy
but what i've seen looked really really
funny
maybe i watched the rest of the archive
afterwards
yo
you gotta watch it too if you didn't
see
what i saw was hair in a dj booth
supporting miko senpai with like yo yo
yeah yeah yeah
i i i find it fascinating is the whole
concert like that i think so right
because she's like producing the others
i find that very fascinating that on her
birthday life
she
chooses to elevate and like support and
promote
the other girls like that's just you
know
that's that's porter guy saying fine
putting someone else into the spotlight
i find that fascinating
she had like a lot of guests over and
they were like singing and performing
while she was in the dj booth she wasn't
even singing she was just like yo yo
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah and sometimes she would say like
weird english phrases in like a
in this
not shitty but
cute nihongo english
[Music]
yeah she's a hype man exactly
yeah pump up that funky beat she did say
that pump up the funky beat
but she said in a cute polka english
it sounds much cuter when she said it
some wow that was loud
sorry guys if that was too loud it was
loud for me so it must have been very
loud for you holy
uh sorry was that so loud it was loud
wasn't it
[Music]
oh
i love your profile picture junkie chunk
are they comfy are my slippers comfy
is that pokeball our new usual room
now as i said i think i reacted to this
during the stream i don't think
pokeballs
are
fitting suitable to be a usual room yeah
no no no no no no no no no no no
i'll give you a kiss though come here
[Music]
too nice for usual room yeah pokeballs i
think they're too comfy
probably
i wanted to say something oh yeah i
wanted to say i had lasagna last night i
had a frozen lasagna one of the first
lasagnas that i eat a lot but
i i know that this is that lasagna i i
chose it on purpose but
that lasagna
it's like it's like a lasagna soup
[Music]
i don't know maybe because it's so cheap
um but whenever i make that lasagna
and i do it according to the
instructions but it's just the way it's
made it's like very stupid it has like
way more
sauce
barely any meat in it
and not also not much noodle sheets
either
so it's like mostly it's like pasta with
mostly the sauce only which is super
yummy though i really like that lasagna
too i like any kind of lasagna
no no matter
what
size what color
what shape what texture would
consistency i the lasagna girl must love
all lasagnas on this world
it's weird but it's really good anyway
yeah
i appreciate a lasagna in any type or
shape
lasagna yes yes um kiarfield
i will eat any lasaga eggplant lasagna
no thank you
i will eat it without the eggplants
well you know i don't eat eggs of course
not i would never eat a plant made out
of eggs
for you guys sake
become as garfield
[Music]
egg eggplant sounds disgusting anyway
mushroom ew no thank you durian no
[Music]
oh yeah he loves onion without really
hey
don't
i am a lasagna lover
ah i want to make a song about lasagna
[Music]
song about lasagna instead of mother
lover it should be lasagna lover
i'm gonna be a lasagna
you can uh
eat my lasagna i eat your lasagna
let's share lasagnas together
no no i want to eat it all myself never
mind it doesn't fit
[Music]
okay i don't know what's going on i'm
doing weird tangents again i just wanted
to tell you about that lasagna thank you
for the membership a lemon egg you look
like an egg but you're yellow
lemon is egg
lemon is
lemon is a
uh
what's what's uh
what's that word again
supine a lemon is a
supply version of an egg
[Music]
sour yes sour egg
have you heard about the new lord of the
rings show coming up yes css it's called
the rings of power and it takes place in
the second age the time of arrogance and
sisters i think it might be fun for
members oh hell yeah
um
yeah i will however since it would be
the first time i would watch it i would
be very very quiet and serious about it
um
i have
i have told my mom and talked with her
about there too yeah so i am aware of it
i'm very excited about it it was a
surprise that it's coming this year in
september that's like so soon
so this year that is coming out and
uh a new uh game of thrones
spin-off is coming out as well this year
holy what a year oh my god
oh my god
we have been blessed by exciting shows
what that was canceled what do you mean
i was going
you're kidding me right
[Music]
what
what was it called again
what was it called again the spin-off oh
it's not cancelled right something with
dragon the game of thrones spin-off
cancel
house of the dragon
is host of the dragon cancel
h
excuse me what is hbo's cancelled game
of thrones prequel budget shows house of
vagina what
[Music]
what
that's another and not a different one
the cancer gamer friends prequel about
the long night cost hbo a lot of money
for his pilot and that's a positive sign
for house of dragon when
hbo canceled game of thrones prequel
about the long night despite spending
millions of dollars on this pilot which
is actually a good sign for house of the
dragon
before so there was never spin-off and
they canceled but house of the dragon is
still going on
oh but about the long night would have
been interesting too what the hell
before game of thrones in 2019 it was
reported that hbo was developing
multiple spin-offs in set in westeros
that was hardly a surprise given game of
thrones had become one of the
lack of trying haunted dragons
respectively released sometime in 2022
having had its production delayed due to
but had things gone according to plan
than one game of thrones prequel may
have already aired by now oh
the first spin-off put into production
was a series set during the age of
heroes which was expected to tell the
story of the long night and likely
answer some lingering questions about
the night king and white walkers
ah but that's so important and they took
that away from although even
[Music]
is there like
is there a book version about all of
those details or is that gonna be
completely made up by hbo
because like for game of thrones for the
series
because the books weren't finished they
made up stuff too right so i wonder
[Music]
because like i wonder where would they
get the material for from i guess that
would be made up huh
[Music]
anyway back on topic um
thank you for the red super chat
yes please catch me tension just kidding
i'm already a loyal employee let's catch
them all of course you are you don't
need
you don't need a pokeball you don't need
anything you're already bound to me for
life aren't ya
thank you for the red super channel give
your kiss smile for a loyal employee
who knows how to follow hashtag hashtag
yolk i'm proud of you
[Music]
what happened with you
also you changed your name to lego legal
ego
alvin l thank you for the red super chat
been a while since i'm here but hello
kia and my fellow kfp hello welcome back
you better be watching more often then
hey hey hey
please come more often
i need you i need more creative people
thank you for the right super chat
though
hope you enjoyed the stream
what do you mean it had to be done what
happened
because of today
[Music]
today is my birthday it's my first
birthday as a kfp just want to say thank
you and love you wish you a happy tiger
here yes thank you tiger
it's the year of the tiger it's the
thrill of the fight
rising up to the challenge of arrivals
[Music]
happy birthday emily that was your
birthday song just kidding
well you can take it as that
happy birthday to you a few days late
but still
i wish you all the best
a wonderful year ahead of you i'm sure
with many possibilities
much happiness
and health and success
make the best out of it and stay how you
are
[Music]
feeling so thank you for the red super
chat
thank you i hope you enjoyed the new
arceus or archeas
i'm sorry but or our choice
i'm sorry but i'll not be on my shifter
and there are choice streams i've also
been waiting for it for a long time but
i can't play it right after the release
oh are you too busy so i'll jump back on
my shift after i finish the game oh
yo better watch the archives though hey
at least a little bit at least a little
bit come on come on felix i need you
the ivan superchat was a pinky
no not that one at least oh
no no no that was five dollars what do
you mean
you mean a different one
not on my side
[Music]
maybe it's uh maybe the one that you're
seeing is a different spot for me i
don't know
um
thank you for the membership comes
felix thank you here's a kiss for you
although i already gave you one i'd like
to give you guys double kisses huh
[Music]
seventeen s seventeen b for the two
donkey show not a good username three
sixty dollars
thank you for the red super chat
again nothing written in your super chat
but with you it's no surprise
you're a man of a few words or a girl or
a pikachu actually probably because
your profile picture seems to be a
pikachu hmm
is that your oshi in pokemon who's
everybody's oshi in pokemon
meaning who's your favorite pokemon
i don't really have one
i wish i had an ocean pokemon
but i don't really care there's a lot of
cute ones mimikyu oh i can get behind
that
hmm
i'm not a pokemon but good answer
um and put me on umbreon
nine tails yeah
[Music]
is that not from naruto
panda star
evie
kyogre um cool
[Music]
by the way i don't think i got an email
about the heavy balls
i don't think i got one
can't be done
[Music]
game is downloading oh i was able to
i was able to convince you huh nicer
have fun with the game
[Music]
i like this
one because i can i can like visualize
it i can see it i can see the super chat
in the form of a chicken
[Music]
i can see it i can see a chicken putting
its wing on my lips and be like shh
don't talk
just
just receive
i like it blanket
wow my chickens are such chads
shatkins
my chimpkins should be should be a part
of the chat cast
thank you from from
[Music]
give your kiss back
patrick and dan kishoon oh wait we're
done with the first one
and i
[Music]
yo i got dms what's going on
ah
top secret dms
[Music]
oh top secret
i need love advice didn't you i made a
mysterious shiny chicken the other day
was it me
but i'm not a chicken and she dazzled me
with her cute book box she was flailing
a popsicle around so she'd kind of she
was kind of weird but i want to know her
dose you a popsicle you mean my sword
i don't want to preach
no it's not me no no i guess that was
not me nevermind
i was having some fun in the pre-chat i
don't know i was thinking about you
uni of laundry thank you for the red
super chat
random super chat but i just wanted to
show appreciation and admiration to the
most special this is not this better not
be about genma
it's most special charming sweetest
cutest prettiest and bestest girl out
there no one else could ever be my
aussie you're irreplaceable you know
that love you kiana
yuria
thank you
this really sounds like something that
would end in i love you genma
really sounds like it but you surprised
me positively
thank you
i love you too
wow you make me cry happy tears
[Music]
yeah the ptsd is too strong man
thank you for your sweet kind of words
so sweet
i like random super jets like that
book book thank you for the pinky you're
wonderful ten so that's it next super
chat let's go chop chop
okay
thank you
jacob 47 al thank you and savage
i'm still busy working as an agent so i
can't come back but i'll leave my
support for you here in super chat i'll
always remember kfb i'll be back one day
it's you
[Music]
yeah yeah again
like an on and off employee we usually
don't allow that but it's not like i can
really hold you back
yeah do what you got to do and just come
back please make sure to come back
um
onion
journey like a thousand years hit one
million views apparently guys make sure
to also stream it on like spotify and
apple music or itunes or whatever make
sure to
stream it outside of youtube as well
listen to it every once in a while
will ya
[Music]
i also heard a bossa nova version of it
on twitter the other day
um
i think it was by the same person who
made the
or the ending
music that i always play i think
that also sounded really cool
wait some spotify of course it is
journey like a thousand years has been
released on all the music services a
while ago
blue thank you for the pinky
lunar new year is almost here or it's
still not happening
potential wishing you chunkers movie and
kfb everyone you love best of luck and
health thank you for making our days
better with your bright energy and
interesting stories lots of love for
your grandma
oh thank you very much my dear blue
i also wish you the same please uh yeah
celebrate but also take some time for
yourself you know
treat yourself and uh take care of your
body
and and listen listen to your body that
is very important
because uh
not uh listening
will uh result in bad bad things
happening yeah
oh yes i have seen the takamori grandma
picture if you were talking about the
same one yeah i've seen it
oh thank you blue my dear very sweet of
you to think of me
the old old grandma you know the kids
they they forget about me and they go
about their own business they do their
everyday job from eight to
whatever
and then they make their own children
all they think about is you know
everything besides their grandma and i
feel quite lonely every now and then but
i just uh continue playing endless
eternal chess with uh
uh my other grandmas around here like uh
you know do you remember do you remember
amelia watson yeah yeah we're still
playing chess to this day
it's our favorite pastime yeah
i call it eternal chess because
sometimes we just fall asleep in the
middle of the uh game and then we wake
up and we're like oh
and we continue but who knows if like
well while someone is sleeping the other
one is maybe just uh acting as if they
were sleeping and secretly moving around
some chess pieces and i don't even know
about it i wouldn't
i would not doubt that emilia watson
would do something like that she's a
sneaky one she has always been a sneaky
one yeah
yeah yeah
that's sneaky
sneaky ah
she she's still ground pounding to this
day but her ground pounds have become a
lot lot weaker it's more like a
a ground
sit now
not a ground pound anymore just to
ground sit
she tries sometimes she can't even sit
down honestly
people have to help her to
bend her knees yeah she's become very
rusty and this is really the proof that
she's human
people have doubted it all her life that
she's human she thought people people
said remember when they said ah that was
funny they saw us coming out as a debut
and then they were like oh the most
mythical of them all the british person
oh yeah yeah yeah she's on her third hip
replacements
ah so much for being mythical if you
were that mythical would you really need
a hip replacement i doubt it
[Music]
oh man
this is funny i should really miss
i shouldn't really make a whole stream
about it
oh carpet 67 dungeon
is that for real but that probably like
ran out by no no
a shiny mime junior
present for me with that code is that do
these codes run out but i don't know how
i don't know if there's really like
something i should accept
[Music]
eddie
soon spanking time thank you for the red
super chat kitties reminded me to send a
paycheck what would i do about them
are they more
[Music]
what's the word
they follow up on that stuff and you
forget about it
you're still waiting for me
still waiting for me but yeah i don't
know it's okay you should keep it for
yourself
a shiny special pokemon
um
well thank you spanking time for sending
me your paycheck i was waiting for it
last minute last minute but still at the
end of the month so
acceptable normally it shouldn't come
this late but i guess i'm also reading
it late so whatever i don't know when
this actually came and i cannot really
judge so
whatever normally normally uh a bit
earlier please yeah yeah
thank you mum
[Music]
like your profile picture
wow
you can't do that here
this is a kfp sir
sir this is the kfp
you can't call pikami flat here on my
stream no no no
i don't know what happened this time but
i seem to have evolved again i don't
know why i'm suddenly much taller than
spiker but
but it is what it is hopefully i can
find my way back to fluff but until then
i might be a bit more prickly eh i
wouldn't say it would be taller isn't an
eagle much bigger than an eagle
than a hatchimal
hedgehog
well that's what we're talking about
right now right
yeah
definitely spikier but not taller
hedgehogs are so cute so tiny man
so small and tiny
i remember when i lived with a host
family before
um
i told you probably about them the one
with the dogs
and they also like uh had one uh eager
one hedgehog
really cute i didn't really interact
much with it i just maybe saw it once
but
they had a hedgehog too
so cute
10 feet tall what the
i told you about that family before no
i'm pretty sure i did i mentioned it
before pretty sure
did it roll around at the speed of sound
[Music]
it was not blue if that's what you're
asking
i did okay i'll kill it
they had many different animals
they had a snake too i think or two
snakes even and they had birds they had
little birds a whole room of birds
very very noisy
bulk book thanks and spanking ham
dankesh and optimus prime dank is an
unknown dancing for the pinky and you
must consider that's pretty rare for
japanese people to have pets to begin
with but then so many holy
[Music]
i wasn't until yeah probably i wasn't
adult
a praying to the one and only true god
has to grow up
yolk forever wow unknown
i can always rely on you i know that
sometimes i worry about you that you're
getting a little bit too deep into the
whole cult thing
please don't do anything
stupid
i've seen like a
i've seen a crazy like
uh
what was it like a news
news segment of like something culture
related
i don't know what the why did i
even watch that
i was like
can i even talk about these things
let's let's just say the key word
mummy mummy find
[Music]
does that say anything to you guys maybe
you guys saw it too
[Music]
oh that
that was
no i did not get inspiration out of that
disgusting though
i think i heard about it well you can
share with each other um that's all i
say about that
holy man there's some crazy people
out there
[Music]
hello there attention today january 13th
is my birthday oh
i don't think tensho well it's still the
30th on my side but not anymore for you
huh i don't think tanja will give me a
vacation but i want to be congratulated
even if i give my salary
and then there's some korean
[Music]
champions
oh
congratulations
here
[Music]
here it is still the 30th so
you're still to be celebrated in my
country
[Music]
i'm hungry
mm-hmm i'm gonna eat some more breakfast
after this i had some fruit
okay
oh my my
my skin
yes
very clear and beautiful i agree
it is isn't it no pores at all
yeah
oh you found the article i think it was
something in america so
but
i wonder if you if you found the same
thing
you have a nice complexion oh my thank
you
for some reason it never changes no
matter how often i go outside or how
little i go outside
weird isn't it sometimes i i used to
turn blue sometimes but i don't know how
that happened
hmm
[Music]
eh doesn't sound too bad um um um
huh are we talking about the same thing
like the whole like everything about
around it like
them still living there
with children and are we talking about
the same thing
[Music]
you may be talking about something else
i'm blue
[Music]
no it wasn't frozen
yeah you're talking about something else
anyway
totally unrelated i'm sorry cube sugar
ignore the mummy uh talk
when we're talking about
something that does not need to be
talked about i'm hungry
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah yeah that's my skincare routine
mary pippin's dankish and
[Music]
for the pinky
um
there's a whole storyline happening here
i will i will let it i will read it and
uh no let me let her read it
wow
cya
i can see the qualities to become a
pokemon master it's really incredible
kiwawa is a great trainer but if there's
one thing missing the rocket team is not
yet
will you be our kfp rocket team and
raise your salary five seconds later kfp
team rocket what's this
maul rue kiwa so cute
lovely
uh
you want me to become team rocket
why
does team rocket
raise people's salaries i doubt it i
don't i don't think you will have i
don't think you're getting anything good
out of uh
or do you mean there must be created
something like team rocket within kfp
which will probably end up being like a
rebellious reunion hell no
no no no get out with your stupid ideas
no no no no
okay pre-team rocket
no
i don't want that here you're basically
jfp
[Music]
well thank you i did find evie
thankfully
brandon would dance
i think here are a lot of flush jets so
let me skip those flush jets
that's a lot of flush chats oh my god
wow you flushed for quite a while
[Music]
frankenheimer
oh yeah uh uh
i i as i said i did not use the
melatonin yet or did i say it i didn't
use it yet
i think i will use it in order to fix my
schedule for the ski trip because
for the skiing trip i think
i'll be
i'll i will need to get up early
gotta go skiing early in the day
um
what a flush chats um sometimes when i
take a little break to go
um
to the idol meeting room
uh-huh
wink
uh people send a lot of blue super chats
just to flush away
i guess the
the rest of the stream
yeah
flush flush like the toilet flushes
is probably what they're imagining but
i'm not totally not on the toilet at
that moment
you need to take it an hour before you
go to sleep yeah yeah i've read up on
the instructions
i've also
been a little bit
scared because of some
side effects that people mentioned but
normally it should be fine right
black friction
steven gardner
found a shiny geodude yo
nice
[Music]
dude
oh i wasn't able to reply to you i don't
know if you you'll be able to see this
but
[Music]
how about
a rock
rock
rock ball
ball rock rock
rock
rocking
round
rock rock ball
[Music]
rock and roll
rock
it's kind of a boring name now isn't it
[Music]
a good he asked for a good nickname chef
how about
hard
egg
[Music]
because it's
it's like
like a
egg but it's
out of rock so
it's
pretty hard
uh
or uh
no not hardboard let's take and sana has
that
uh
[Music]
egg egg with hands that's probably too
long
uh
um
[Music]
egg dude
how about you do you call it egg dude
egg dude what does it shiny do you look
like anyway
shiny teal dude
it is super yellow well that's perfect
that's perfect i didn't realize it was
yellow
well that's perfect
[Music]
then wonderful
egg dude
s 17
[Music]
thank you for all the blessed book books
freaks today i'll be leaving soon to
have shadow shovel with my family see
you tomorrow
oh nicer
please enjoy shabu-shabu is pretty yummy
shabu-shabu was one of my favorite
things to eat in japan
it is also one of those
fun food things that you can do together
with a friend while like
you know cooking together on the table
it's pretty fun i like that culture
it's okay my naming sense is also
terrible
yay let's go
[Music]
very close
thank you for coming by sorry thank you
for the pinky sana died once during a
pokemon stream but none of her audience
was around to pick up his stuff so i
downloaded it this morning so chimpkin
could always pick up your lost stuff for
you but i'm enjoying the game as well
but like don't you get like random
people only like you can't control whose
stuff you're picking up
i think i assume
so
not your fault not the audience's fault
that they couldn't pick up sana's stuff
maybe someone else's
you know someone some randall has
uh her stuff
on their map but they didn't collect it
yet she might get it eventually right
um
from the bottom of the like what wait
but that's unfair no it doesn't spawn in
the in the water does it when you die in
the water
but you don't how could you even die in
the water you when you when you die in
the water then you like
get spawned back and onto the ground
how could you die anyway
she played the game early oh
yeah oh well she'll be fine
she'll be fine she'll get her stuff like
she got new stuff
lonely
and alex thank you i'm gonna skip the
chats thank you though
looking for the top down
a lonely part thank you for pinky thank
you
you were very very generous on that day
but you never wrote anything in your
super chat i guess because you're a bot
thank you thank you very much
looking for the top down jolly donkey
thank you
mr spanking
[Music]
chats from today
nineteen that school uniform is so cute
so cute but today we did kimono because
i asked her to do that one because we
have like
i felt like we were kind of um
matching with the straight hair
and you know kimono just adds a style
i think was matching
[Music]
she was actually uh her kimono is more
like a hakama
i kind of wanted a hug about myself
but
uh
i i didn't get the hakama
you looked amazing together thank you
straight beautiful gorgeous hair but i
do i do generally prefer for example
this fluffiness this volume
because i think it asserts dominance
hell yeah
come on
um
[Music]
everyone is so supportive of orange
foreign
[Music]
um
one reason why i
uh brought energy into the collab was
because um
you know i wanted to do a japanese only
stream in order to communicate again
with the japanese people but i was very
worried that people would show up
um
which i think is
reasonable
and now we had a lot of amenities fans
coming over as well so
it was more than it would be normally so
uh yeah
without them
would probably have been a very very uh
quiet stream
yeah i mean there's always a few but
it's just like i feel like i can count
them on my
two hands at the moment it used to be
more but
yeah
um i think because i i started talking
less and less and less and less japanese
um
yeah it's like inevitable
so no more solo i don't i'm not saying
no more but it's just like i feel very
um
uh insecure about it
doing a
solo japanese only yeah
then do more
well doing more
it won't suddenly
miraculously bring me thousands and
thousands of japanese viewers
it doesn't work like that um
unfortunately but that's okay that's
okay
the ones that are here now i'm i'm
really thankful for the ones that are
still coming to my streams and they seem
to be mostly fine anyway
with me speaking mostly english
um you have to do it consistently well
but i don't want to do that because
there's so many other streams that i
want to do all the time and
doing like weekly japanese only streams
i feel like takes up like already a big
spot each week and
for that
doing that and then and then not even
having
like any viewers
just lonely
[Music]
yeah
but you know i can do collabs like that
every once in a while and hopefully
i will be able to remind the japanese
audience that i i am still here
i don't know
[Music]
collapse good compromise yeah i think so
too although honestly i was thinking
while
well
setting this up and streaming this i was
thinking yo we could have totally done
this on ninety's channel because she's
like probably talking more than me
because she's reading all of it and it's
japanese and all the nickels all the
energy fans are here you could have
probably just streamed it on her channel
but i the original thought behind it was
wanting to do a japanese only stream on
my channel so that the japanese bros are
happy but yeah i probably could have
done it on her channel
might have been more fitting but oh well
yeah
yeah i could have hacked her channel
yeah i remember that one time when she
hacked into my channel
[Music]
i remember that i got a good laugh out
of it i was with um i was of genma i
think
when that happened
and we were just laughing about it like
what's happening
[Music]
ah yeah that that might have been the
cause but it's okay i don't want to
blame her or anyone
um but
could have very likely been the cause of
the of the shadow bamboozle
by youtube
yeah
i don't know how the hell that happened
though thank you felix for the red super
chat tanto it's so nice to see you
collabing with nenety again please don't
stress yourself out too much playing
horror games all right we want to see
you playing a game so if you're not
enjoying the game then it beats the
purpose and anyway have fun the energy
thank you well you know what that was
really not that scary i mean there were
a little bit a few like tiny like oh
yeah moments but
um
maybe this is also the way to um
do like to get used to horror games
not just by starting out of nowhere with
outlast
but like start with some small baby
steps
not that i want to play more and really
get used to it that's not my goal
but
yeah
this one was really
thankfully easy on my heart
thankfully thankfully
thank you felix
[Music]
you know
wow thank you for the empty rainbow
dancing
someone i don't usually see around might
might have been a ninja fan well thank
you for being so generous
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
always fun to watch looking forward to
the song cover thank you thank you thank
you me too me too
yeah i am
i honestly um
after the last minecraft um collab
oh i felt like you know
that collab i tried to mix in a lot of
english so that you guys would be able
to
enjoy it more too but i did feel like
i don't know
energy would have enjoyed it more if it
was just japanese i feel like the
english
the amount of english made it kind of
awkward but today today i i was able to
put in some english without making
energy feel awkward herself
she seemed
she seemed on high spirits today
yeah yeah yeah
so
i still want to call out more with
energy but there might just be more
collabs on her channel then
where it's only japanese
[Music]
yes cute nana english she wants to go to
spain huh she says she said in japanese
that she thinks spain is extremely
beautiful i found that fascinating um
spain does have
very beautiful places
but i feel like she was um kind of um
had to say
i think she she has a way more
glorified image of spain
than uh it really is there are some
beautiful cities definitely i've seen it
myself like valencia was beautiful but
definitely some rose tinted glasses
there
yeah a bit exaggerating or like
idealized probably she said that when
she was 12 her teacher
showed her pictures and told her about
spain
um
and that made her want to go to spain
[Music]
don't forget about marioka i would not
take her to mallorca
[Music]
is like the party
party place in spain i
i i wouldn't want to take her there
i would want to take her to
like a more calm a place in
spain
take her to the ballet man hell no
no no no i'm gonna take her to a place
like that
uh
clubbing no
i don't think that's what she would i
don't think she would feel comfortable
at all
she said she wants to go to barcelona
barcelona is i think fine i mean that's
also a place where people go to party as
well but
um i think it's
more
towards tourists than mallorca is my
yorker really i only see that as a party
place
[Music]
when you avoid palma ah i guess yeah if
you
if you don't go to like palma de mayoka
oh
perhaps
definitely as i said there are beautiful
places i would i wouldn't mind going to
valencia again
and
it was very pretty
um
[Music]
and it's very cheap to go there too like
at least inside of europe holy my
my flight to spain
was like i don't know under a hundred
dollars
with a with a tiny suitcase but yeah for
short travel super super easy
i think you can go there for like 50
bucks 60 bucks
for
economy
yeah weekend holiday or so yeah ryanair
is super cheap
and i mean it's not not the best airline
but if you just want to go for a short
trip and and you don't need much um
uh
uh luggage
then no issue there
[Music]
best prices are maybe 15 euro yeah yeah
yeah sometimes if you're lucky if you
find a good day or a good airport then
sometimes you can go to some cool
destinations with like only 15 or 20
euros
[Music]
australia
foreign
[Music]
that's that's one thing i love about
living in europe i love it i appreciate
it so much yo
[Music]
i remember my flight to
london was also cheap
really really
[Music]
thank you please look forward to the
song cover indeed it's we announced a
little bit earlier but i thought why the
hell not
why the hell not
why would we keep a secret if we can
just tell you what's
i was just joking that with me going
game over
the whole pacing and and and mood
was like lifted and and much more
happier
after that like so in the second part of
the stream
after dying it was more
more exciting
anton m thank you for the pinky i see
you're writing your super
[Music]
you're saying i should reply in english
okay did you write this yourself it
doesn't quite sound like you put it into
a
translator it sounded pretty good
[Music]
wow
if you wrote this yourself then respect
pretty good japanese
uh
basically it said something like yo i
barely have horror games on my channel
so this is a very
very precious stream i agree and you
seem to be a horror fan huh well i'm
sorry
that i usually can't make you happy when
it comes to the horror department i
don't have much to offer
but yeah um i hope that today was at
least a little bit i mean for a horror
game fan today was probably
a walk in the park but
[Music]
at least something right and that way i
was able to uh once again
just like the
whole live omikuji a fortune
phone application that you guys didn't
know about
i could once again introduce something
whole life related that's japanese only
[Music]
yes yes that you probably otherwise
wouldn't have really
taken a close look at
[Music]
you are welcome
inside
[Music]
ramos thank you for the ransom for chad
love to the energy collab by the way i'm
since i'm going to change my username
not using this account for work anymore
uh-huh
wait when you say not using this account
for work anymore are you in character
saying you're not using this for kfb
anymore
and i'm fully grown now not to brag but
i'm bragging i thought that maybe i
could get a kfp job ah
ah no you mean a real job you were using
this youtube account for your real job
oh okay
but you can use it for kfp now if the
empress decides to grace me over title
hi smoothie
how about your title is um
uh
what's a good word for something who
purchases stuff how about kfb kibble's
purchaser purchase there must be a
better word for that a buyer uh not
buyer
[Music]
uh
which isn't that's so weird
[Music]
crocura wow that sounds very
professional
supplier that sounds good exactly rama's
kfb
[Music]
kibbles supplier
cable's for my cats
so you're like an assistant to me to the
bus
that's it that's your name
[Music]
have fun
and uh yeah get me those cables i'm
running out of them
and thank you
[Music]
foreign
i just said that i feel like we've been
whole life
i think uh
me and ninety
are
some of them
members who are the most passionate
and
about you know being being like an idol
like i just don't really have the
possibilities like right now if i could
do whatever i want i would do what
energy does and have like concerts all
the time and put out all these 3d music
windows and all that if i could yeah
but you know you know how much i love my
idols
my hello project idols and i wanna i
wanna be like you know ninety and bounce
around doing my choreos and sing and
dance all the time bring out a lot of
songs
um i think when you tur when it comes to
like
i do ishiki
idol
mentality and
in a classic
sense
how idols usually
uh
are
um
how to say
what is your idols usually are like in
in japan you know like akb or hello
project and so on um
yeah that's that's uh i think what we
kind of aspire
both of us i think we have a similar
vision of what we want to be
that's what i wanted to say yeah
um
[Music]
thank you for watching today i
appreciate it hope you enjoyed it
and for the web thank you also for red
super chat anthony thank you
hi kiwawa still loving your streams and
super tangents
still thank you
it's been
a while yeah thank you for being here
hope you enjoyed it even though it was
mostly japanese but here are some
tangents for you in the super chat
reading at least
thank you soon for supporting me
whenever
we're wherever
to be together i'll be there and you'll
be here
that's the deal my dear
[Music]
kfb love song
she has a high sense of professionalism
as an idol exactly
i don't know if you're talking about
nancy or me but definitely apply some
energy
shakira shakiya
ooh baby when you talk like
[Music]
mikasa
[Laughter]
[Music]
no no i see what you're doing thank you
no no you can't get me
nice try
[Music]
hypothetical question uh-huh if you had
seen a certain forest fair's affair and
saga released yesterday what would have
been your reaction hypothetically of
course much love for intentional uh well
i can i can read you my
my reaction
um
i i wrote to
that hypothetical fairy
i loved it the reveal was so
cute the background and the
homuras
looked so good the idea of eating bites
for bite was so nice and adorable and
your new outfit ah it looks so well made
i love the new hairstyle mates rock so i
love the made kimono theme you look so
cute
um
the rest is a
secret secret
[Music]
yeah
i told her
[Music]
i may or may have not thrown
money at her
i may have
donated money
[Music]
it might have been quite a lot
well spent
and yeah yeah the wow the song choice
was also very surprising i was like what
the this is dedicated to me is it
not
it's dedicated to me secretly
it must be an homage to me
[Music]
before the same hell
yeah yeah yeah well well
it was lovely
thank you for this completely
hypothetical answer you you're
hypothetically welcome
yay
no that was really exciting
i thought oh my god it looked so
delicious too i really wanted to eat
that holy
it looked so yummy
[Music]
chicken
wow wow wow
i'm doula
yes of course it's still on sale yeah
yeah
um doodler i'm surprised you know about
it very tasty um
fuzzy drink
herbal a fuzzy drink in austria
yeah
should be
definitely
if there was an austrian snack box you
would have to put alm doodler in into it
definitely my shoe matthew thank you
we're almost done guys
[Music]
oh child don't worry about it you don't
really need it anyway but wow you used
to speak it fluently if you're used to
speaking fluently then i'm sure if you
tried you could get back into it
kishko thank you for the pinky finally
got a job after a long leaf of absence
oh i think it was thanks to the fortune
telling from tantra
even though my confidence was low and i
had a hard time i'll be busy watch less
livestreams always cheer for you oh
you got a job though congratulations um
don't forget about me
[Music]
that is
but yeah congratulations on your new job
[Music]
of course
really cinta
don't forget about me
you must watch my archives but i
understand if you have a job then uh
maybe that's what he means because he
says live streams if you have a job then
obviously you can't stay up all night to
watch my streams because they're in an
awkward
time for you in uh korea uh but maybe
you plan on watching the archives at
least
i would be happy if you would do that
thank you so much
and good luck in your new job
have confidence
black friction
[Music]
thank you
and boohoo seven 723
oh thank you
sometimes i will never forget i'm going
to watch the livestream as much as
possible archive is okay too no problem
but you can say hello in live streams
sometimes
fighting
okay i'm done reading super test guys
i will make the schedule a little bit
later today um
yeah
uh
most of the next week i'll still be
streaming so
um
yeah yeah i'll be around for most of
next week
but uh
probably no collapse because i didn't
get to organize anything
oh it will be we'll have some special
alone time before i go on my trip next
week
[Music]
thank you for the clapping
schedules
[Music]
i think i'm gonna do a
continuation of the art stream next week
um
so i know you guys are
asking for that a lot
[Music]
uh guys i had this extreme idea
yesterday
[Music]
um
but i don't know i wanna i wanna do it
but maybe you guys can recommend me
something i had this stupid idea which
sounds so fun uh
i could also use my hand camera with
that again so i was thinking
of doing a marshmallow q a where you ask
me questions
that
i will be answering
while having a lie detector device in
front of me and having my hand on top of
that
so i looked up live detective devices
you know like for games and everything i
found on amazon was the reviews
were all crap apparently it doesn't like
apparently for a real lie detector
thingy like a functioning one you have
to pay quite a lot of money apparently
like a real polygraph and all those
other ones that shock you i want one
that shocks me
when i lie
um
worst case i could like get one that
doesn't shock me but actually works and
then i have a different device that
shocks me when i push the button so
whenever about that wait but then
then that wouldn't quite work that way
so i don't know i don't know if i should
buy one of those shitty ones that
apparently don't really work and then
but then but then the device will decide
when i lie even when i don't lie oh no
man
i don't i don't know what to think about
that and because you guys are gonna
take it so seriously and be like oh my
god she lied about that holy
we must believe it the lie detector must
be trusted
um
only has one ask her oh
[Music]
they also used one i think before and uh
there are no real ones is that a lie
i saw one being used before for i think
it was a third gen
3d stream i think i think it was for jen
didn't they use like a lie detector
thingy but i think that was i don't know
maybe kind of
self-made or so i don't know what they
actually used
why did i just i don't even i don't know
but it's like i
[Music]
mean hmm but
i at least want something that really
measures
my
what does it measure the pulse
it measures the pulse of what exactly
does it measure i didn't at least want
something where i can actually be sure
that it's um electro shocking me
based on that and not just randomly you
know every for example every 10 times
the machine just randomly sends out the
shock
not according to like not i wanted to
monitor something
use the heart rate monitor
no i have a heart rate monitor but i
want something that surprises me with
its shock which would be one of those
joke game item
uh
lie detectors
it's a fun idea but there's no way to
honestly put it off because those
machines don't like
hmm man
[Music]
you need a professional maybe i can hire
a professional sounds really expensive
though
wait can you
uh
lugen detector
[Music]
wait a second
i need to refresh chat
[Music]
i want to see how much it costs
well that would be i don't want someone
here with me
[Music]
i can't find anything
how much yo yo yo
yo i see a pretty legit one actually i
mean it doesn't give me electric shocks
but i can do that myself i guess i guess
i will decide when i lie or you can
decide i don't know
um
this one is legit wait how do i buy it
[Music]
oh wow it's expensive
uh polygraph basic free sensors
is 350
euro
uh and then there's a one one for a
thousand euros which is like a thousand
bucks
with six sensors
uh
[Music]
where's the difference there uh it comes
with a pro software while the other one
comes with a basic software and it comes
with the extra sensors like the the the
three sensors on the cheap one i know
it's
ah although it would probably be worth
it i don't know the cheaper one comes
with uh
the following sensors um the pulse
and how to be dash done i don't know
what to call it like
skin resistance whatever that means
and a breathing sensor i think the cheap
one would be good enough don't you think
okay and the other stuff you get well
it's a usb cable connection uh you get
uh the polygraph and the basic software
something like that and fabindo's box i
don't know what that means i guess it's
like a
box that connects everything
[Music]
uh
well why not it would be an exciting
stream
what you guys are too hey
[Music]
i am i trust i i know that like
they're not 100 reliable but i trust the
fact that these ones actually have
proper sensors
compared to the other joke items that i
found on amazon that are like 30 bucks
where the
where it just randomly shocks you
[Music]
get the cheap one but it doesn't work it
doesn't monitor anything
the toy will do that but it doesn't
matter it just randomly shocks you
[Music]
i'll think about it
you need trained people to use them
really
use it for horror stream no for that i
can just use a heart monitor
[Music]
you just ask mama to literally like she
does not know anything everything about
me though
she can't be my lie detector there's a
lot of things she doesn't know
[Music]
ah
i don't know
i i wouldn't mind buying one of those
joke thingies if they just would work a
little bit better you know
like
if you guys know of any
any kind of like joke lie detector
that's like just at least like
a little bit
um
more
like legit it doesn't have to be like a
real polygraph
but something that's more legit
[Music]
i don't know i could only find uh the
same article pretty much on amazon but
sold by different people
and they all were
hmm
yeah no i'm definitely doing more
research i thought the idea would be so
funny you know
if it were actually
if it would actually work but i i will
continue doing my research just if you
have some ideas let me know
let me know and i will look it up
[Music]
yeah i agree i don't know
just let the chat design i can't let the
chat design
i can't then you guys will always say
it's lies just so that i get more
electroshocks
you guys will always say and that's a
lie oh that's a lie too that's a lie
okay huawei's a phoenix that's a lie
kiana is a girl that's a lie kiana has
orange hair that's a lie
the
100 unreliable you that would be the
biggest scam
ever
every word i would say you guys would
deem to be a lie i don't trust it
okay uh let's not uh drag this out any
longer for the people who want to watch
the archive oh i just had like three
more super chats are still coming let me
see
um
i guess
like i understand why they are not like
you know usable in court or so on but i
i do think they're real ones that
actually measure
all these things you know
that that i think is very much true
rise over that
sweat and even the tightening of your
muscles and those are so come on yeah
even even if it's not 100 accurate i
still think it would be funny
um watching too much tv maybe i watched
uh too much uh crime uh
explanation videos
um
you guys are two
you got you
[Music]
oh my god stop
oh blade johnny someone who is
supportive oh thank you but uh
i will see what i when i can find um now
now now you make me feel like i need to
commit to it
thank you
[Music]
i do wonder though um
maybe you know what i'm talking about
but the cheap ones that are like 30
bucks and so on when you put your hand
on top of it
i i was wondering if it even works with
gloves
probably right it should work
cause it if it's not actually monitoring
anything
and just randomly shocks you whenever it
wants whenever it feels like it
the shock goes through the glove though
doesn't it
[Music]
good point hmm
it won't shock you for the gloves
really
what wet gloves
lord it looked like
spaghetti
sneaky sneaky cat
should not shock for rebel gloves
won't go for oh but if it's like a
fabric glove it should
work depends on the material
[Music]
um tin foil gloves
that sounds scary
gloves are designed to isolate you
wouldn't need touch screen gloves
ah
well that should be easy
i see i see okay
i'll think about it it was just
one of my many random ideas i mean you
don't
don't don't
don't um worry too much about it another
idea i had was uh buying
buying one of those children some
icebreaking games you know the ones
where you when you have a hammer and you
bonk bonk bonk and you don't want
everything to fall down but i really
really loved that game when i was a
child and i wanted to do that on stream
just wanted to
bonk the ice and play with
no one's just on my own
but i i asked i have to ask like how is
it with like um
actual games like real live games
how
that works with permissions i have to
ask them
yeah then i i went through i went for
all of
like amazon kept on recommending me you
know some children's games that i played
when i was a child i found that one that
i really loved when i was a small small
bubble bubble child uh it was like a
like a lot of small small small tiny
fish heads looking upwards with they
would like open their mouth uh i think
there was a batter inside and there was
like a like a rotation they would open
their mouth and inside is a magnet and
you fish them with your fishing rod
because there's a magnet on your fishing
rod you know what i mean that was so
much fun
yeah yeah yeah it's so cute isn't it
there's like a lot of versions of that
game apparently yeah
that was so fun
sounds familiar
yeah
it was so fun
the fishies
the fishies the magnet fishies
[Music]
played that when i was eight yeah it was
probably the same for me sometime around
that age
but it's so cute
brings me back yeah doesn't it
but the thing about the the ice bonking
game is that um that was like remember
when i told you about that tv show where
the children would run through a um
a shop a game shop
and they would like have a time limit
and they would like throw all of the
games into their shopping carts and
would run for the shop right
and they would actually i told you
before i think there was a section where
they had that huge uh they had that ice
game but in a huge real life size like a
huge table with ice blocks and they had
huge hammers to bonk the ice and they
would be like one team against the other
team
and i found that so fascinating
that was so cool it was so oh every time
it was so anxiety inducing when when the
other team would like bonk
a really really difficult ice block away
and there's like only like three ice
blocks left in the field
on the table and the other team would be
like
they still are
alive oh
um
it's riveting absolutely exciting
anyway i'm gonna go now see you soon
guys and in germany
good night everybody have a nice day
i'll see you soon check twitter or the
community board for the uh schedule
later
bye bye
thank you for watching
[Music]
love you too
oh oak proud thank you for the pinky oh
my god
it's my first month working full time as
an artist and i have a lot of thanks for
you for you're working follow them as an
artist now nice congratulations
proud of you
proud of oak proud
[Music]
wow
make the best out of it that's pretty
awesome
[Music]