[Music]
hi hello hello everyone
W is everything's normal now I think
this the stream is kind of a little bit
have a lagging
problem let's hope it's better now yeah
okay so this is the first time that I am
uh asking uh some Ian member Kanan Kiara
and FAA to join the uh Age of Empire 2
uh but we also have Ana and rainy to
play again this
game so uh this time this time um we put
it into a team um since me Ana and rainy
already playing this game before so we
put I think it's wisely to put uh two
versus two versus two kind of thing
yes
um every team have Ian and
ID yes International Teams let's go
[Music]
y yeah
yay
yeah like a like a game setting with a
random map a normal six player and the
location actually right now is randomly
choose Coastal but I actually have no
idea about
it I don't have any idea about the maps
yeah I don't have any idea what the
map are you sure it's random Mrs MAA
who's playing Vikings are you sure that
was not on purpose CU you're playing
Vikings I I put like a game modes and
random M and they they put the on
Coastal
okay should I should I I mean coal is
fine right it doesn't really mean that
the whole map is covered with ocean
right right it's just that there's a
coast
[Music]
right custom map
po yeah that there you can just choose
like 10 or 15 maps that you want to be
in the pool
oh so you can choose everything that
looks good to you for a big match okay
mostly oh maybe I just choose the one
that have like maybe six with
mostly they
are choose Arena too Arena and black
forest in the uh in the top uh two top
top two row Black Forest yummy black
forest forest yummy Black
Forest yummy
chries which one again H in the top row
there should be black forest and Arena
it's alphabetic anyway black forest
yeah I heard that I never played it but
it's very popular I think for big
matches and then what do you want to
request
ER I don't know I up to you we put
hamburger on
hamburger fine it'll be fine oh you show
so many how bad can it
be you chose so SRA oh my God no no no
no no the one that is on Aran Black
Forest um which one again so
green look at that V majapahit Empire oh
my God wait can I see the costom map po
oh I can oh I can how many maps are
there there's so many oh wait is it like
standard there
setting where's the big
mapish
we have like a many Maps there's a map
called Mega random like is it is there
really like a question mark shaved water
on
it Mega random is just super random
interesting
Market going to be heavily stylist like
everything is going to be random it's
not always going to be the
same I'm looking at four people yeah but
like the thing is I can't select see
like
I I can't see the six people maps how do
I see the six people Maps yeah I don't
know these four people Maps there four
how mostly how I mean it's just a map
size and these are just map Styles right
there's 83 maps in the game
automatically adjusted itself oh look at
this 1 2 3 5 oh now this is huge adjust
it oh you
real world Indonesia oh my God so much
water in Indonesia not real world not
real world pleas water in real world so
much water in the real
world India too wait random Black
Forest it's
fine black
forest um no no I put it on random Black
Forest Black Forest Arena and
Empire that's the tree random that I
choose oh it tastes Black Forest here
but I guess when you get to the game
it's going to be
randomized yeah maybe we'll see it's not
bad if we go eat cake
right cake is good cake is let them have
cake yum let them have
cake okay um well I think it's time to
start okay guys ready kick us out good
luck good luck everyone good
luck have
mercy okay bye
bye yo what is
up let's go way let's focus on our
economy okay okay first
first let's go wait so where are you oh
you're like over
there let's um uh wait I'm I'm confused
I don't know how to play the game
anymore I don't know I forgot me too I
know I know I know like wait like I
don't even know oh oh oh can I can I
just like um do this and you you you are
supposed to do
this I don't
know um you are
going why is there big walls around me
wait there's already walls around us
yeah that's why I'm I'm like so
confused actually a [\h__\h] I don't know
I'm so
confused wait okay there's Stones here
and there's wood here wood is so
far I don't know all right oh but the
wood is like if it's gone I have to
build a wall how do you can I cancel
it oh no guys how do you
oh my God can I cancel
this o I don't know guys double rain oh
because oh
wait
what uh never mind I had like double
Raina on my OBS okay you
delete okay how do you um you know like
uh how do you look for Idol villagers
what's the shortcut I forgot uh uh I I
don't know if it's the same for you cuz
I Chang change D [\h__\h] now I'm
behind oh
no oh no he's idle go go here it's dot
okay there's no Idol villagers sorry I
just woke up oh my
God I'm forgetting everything I learned
me too it's
okay oh my God many many people
soan many many people they are
um
employed that's fine no that's not fine
it's not fine wait you go here
first okay get this one down until I
have enough for the lumber Camp
okay are there any unemployed
people there must always on the you know
you know even if you don't know the
hotkey on the top top you can see the
next to the Dark Age thingy you can see
all your idol villagers okay I see I
see
okay oh my god oh it's is chat chat is
fine okay okay you guys you guys chat
don't make me nervous yo yo yo what the
freak yo yo what the
freak who is this e who faas Cavalry
she's here oh well don't worry about the
C scouting wait how do I Scout
anywhere
actually H you have to press you click
click on your scout and then press G
then he starts walking automatically to
wherever so
annoying I can't kill it for I wanted to
kill it but can't whatever it's fine
what what are you trying to kill a FAS
uh Cavalry anyway because we did we made
a
treaty remember oh okay
damn sorry I
forgot I'm sorry I forgot about it what
are these people
doing oh what these people are
unemployed oh wait wait the goats are
um oh no no no no no no
go also it's never worth it killing the
the the what Scout because he always
moves so fast so you just like you'll
just be following him
endlessly yeah I guess so and he just
runs away it HT it hurt it just going to
build houses just because I
can okay okay make sure to build
everything else for your economy get
food food is most important in the
beginning wa there's so many unemployed
people in
here yeah
oh my
God so many Idol
people Idols we're Idols what should I
build I should make a mill for some
reason and know maybe
here
wait it's all right well as long as the
others are you know as chill as you it's
all right
go go go well then if everybody's like
you then I'm I'm more concern more more
relieved and concerned but also relieved
also
Rel oh not enough
wood oh so many unemployed people what
are the unemployed people going to do
Kara what are you doing with your
unemployed people E I make them work on
wood I make them work on food I make
them work on Stones uh like everything
all the resources most important in the
beginning is food and wood I would say
gold is not not gold is not the priority
okay I'm going to tell all the
unemployed people to work on stuff okay
oh my God so many unemployed people make
sure to always have your town center be
building uh some new
villagers yeah okay
okay wow I'm afraid of the goats are the
goats
aggressive n no the goats you can just
you have to shoot them twice but they
don't fight back
okay wood is also very important yeah
wood and um food so you can go to
berries or go kill
animals okay good good good I would I
would recommend to have at least two
people working on one animal because um
if you're not fast enough the animal
will Decay before you can get all of the
meat out of it you know okay
okay okay okay I think uh everybody's
not
unemployed okay good oh I
should I did my
homework I did I
did I'm like
okay I don't know what to do actually
they're like so far away I should build
a mill they really far really yeah you
should minimize the paths that they have
to walk as much as possible I I guess
yeah because that's like that's like the
key to becoming successful in your
economy okay I see I
see
I see I
see what do I build
next cron is fast castling
n
n but she doesn't have a castle yet
right
n we don't have any unemployed people
here it's
fine
she's it's going to be fine it's going
to be fine also ma said I can look at
chat we can all look at chat yeah we can
she said so mhm we can we can it's a
chill tournament okay it's not like like
uh stuck up tense oh my God I have to
win tournament yeah we're just chilling
well actually there's no unemployed
people here
h I'm so far from My Town Center oh
well oh
well oh well well how much oh make sure
to get to feudal age Advance as fast as
possible but for that you need a lot of
food okay so food really
important okay well how do I to how do
we upgrade to FUD when you click on the
town center on the bottom left it will
tell you how much you need like 500 food
okay two Dark Age buildings so I already
have a Mill and I already have a
what I already have a house do I need
something else you you need a lumber
camp and the mining camp Oh I guess
so
wait I heard I heard before when there
was an ID tournament that you were like
not too bad really yeah I'm just doing
my thing
I am just doing my thing hello Bo I'm
going to C
you I'm going to kill you
dead so chill go that's fine that's fine
we don't need to be try hard I'm I don't
worry
[Music]
I'm not even using my
shortcuts we need
me we need
meat we need
meat we need meat and we need houses I
guess
so
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay
now
more okay now oh God I want to I need to
save food now I want to get to feudal
age yeah I want to get to feudal as fast
as possible but you always have to
continue creating villagers very
important yes yes okay okay okay
hey yes okay okay hey hey you I want you
to make a
house how to make a house I
forgot uh in the buildings the first
one there's actually a hot cake queue
for it I forgot maybe I can remember try
not kyq I forgot how to build a house
hotkey q q press Q yeah I
did I did oh wait I need to select the
villager oh my God
yeah okay wait there's so many
unemployed
people actually oh
[\h__\h] how do
why do I hear double oh my
phone my phone was playing the stream
okay I want this oh do I need to be
feudal in order to activate this this
unemployed rate is too
high the rate of unemployment is too
high that that doesn't sound
good yeah yes F okay
okay okay let's get enough wood so that
when waya asks me for wood I can give
her wood y
literally don't rely on me though
literally try to get your own there's
no there's no more animals what the hell
well then you have to you surely have a
berries and then um you can put Farms
right next to the mill attached to the
Mill Farms yeah I
[Music]
[Laughter]
guess wait I guess
[Music]
no so what do I have to
do excuse
me I don't understand though what was
it ID
don't wait the rate of unemployment is
so
high I can advance let's go nice hey hey
hey
tells the others when you advance right
yeah how do you advance I already
clicked advance but it's not uh you
don't have enough food probably oh I
already they already subtracted my
food uh then it takes some time you
know oh you need to build more houses it
says I'll build a
house I'm being attacked by fauna is
that her it's just her Scout probably
has it already been 20 minutes really I
don't think
so why can't I do it
now any unemployed people yeah many many
unemployed
people and they can work on this house
if they're
unemployed
I don't know oh oh thank you for the
raid hopefully it's not a AOE
raid what also don't know these people
are so
unemployed okay they're still creating
villagers mhm
okay don't be unemployed don't be
unemployed yo don't be unemployed I
don't want to build this now Mak you
farm what short wait what's shortcut
for a okay and then they're still queing
villagers still giving
birth doesn't
work okay when is this placement my
Farms are so badly placed me too me too
don't worry don't
worry me too me
too unemployed
people fear of being
unemployed oh it's researching
now
what birth into
unemployment okay are we still oh it's
still researching
Y what is
this well well that's fine that's fine
that's fine that's fine come on
faster ah finally am I the first uh no
Han's already Castle
age ah huh excuse me what for real yeah
what yes what you're lying no I'm for
real no way I'm for real I'm being for
real
n I'm being for real oh my
God
what I'm being for real then we need to
gum B
we need to
G guess
[Music]
so we need
to okay but now I can do this now I can
uh I mean there's nobody that's
unemployed here
so nobody's
unemployed
oh I found where the other people are
Faun is the closest to
me okay you're Canan right yeah I'm
Sayan well where can I build
stuff there's so much
space Oh there's a relic here o ooh
really yeah I there's probably one right
at your doorstep too A
Relic
really wow let's give birth to more
people inside M want some protection
outside too before they arrive but okay
for me hon treaty is over treaty is
treaty no more no treaty so sad
mhm just building a very peaceful
[Music]
Village how do I build the um Cavalry
and
stuff Cavalry yeah well you need a once
you're in feudal age you can build
Barracks oh okay and then you can start
uh also building the Archer range and
everything else MAA Advanced to feudal
age barck
swear so you need also stable for
Knights you need
Stables where is it oh here it is let's
build a
Barack okay there's unemployed
people I'm going to build this anyway
cuz I like it um many many unemployed
people and what do we need for Castle
age
let's
see um cost is meat and 200 gold
improves your civilization more powerful
milary
units okay well can we research this
archery range stable blacksmith or
Market well I already have oh two feudal
wait I have two feudal age buildings
what do you
mean eh what's the like whatever is red
will tell you you don't have enough of
so it's maybe food if you already have
all the feudal buildings I'm not
sure says I need
to H just trying to use the houses as a
wall Stables to stabilize the Villager
mentality okay so
true oh I can go to Castle
AG wait how let go military buildings
Outpost P let's [\h__\h] go how to build
stable right I know oh here it is build
stable let's build it
um
actually many
many there's many unemployment
people oh wait there's already
one no
[Laughter]
no I'm just
okay now will we be able to advance okay
thank you combat
unemployment what is one
villager we need to broel broel broel
broel
okay and then
how to focus
[Applause]
On's this which one can we how why can't
we upgrade this I don't know is Knight
starting from Castle age I don't know
holy [\h__\h]
uh oh so many
unemployment many many
unemployment
he why so many unemployment guys please
give them
jobs I don't know why they're so
unemployed Castle soon Castle soon there
we go Let There we go Castle it baby
let's
go spamming the knights wait that means
that I can also build a
castle nice should I build one inside
and then some outside to like you know
up to you closer to them oh is crony the
closest to me on the left side seems
like it yeah I guess
so P up P you advanc to Castle AG winner
yeah I think so
[Music]
nice and then I'm
researching and there's no unemployment
here which is good I
think and then now what should I make I
don't
know what should I
make I think is that all I need that one
spot there or should I research
[Music]
this upgrade to pikan but I guess
no zero unemployment rate
H should I build
something
H okay okay
okay should I which one should I get
guys I don't know maybe these
ones I don't know I don't know Siege so
this now
Siege why no
Siege why can I not build
Siege ton archers are bad oh okay how to
scout scout what else then the
skirmishers how to scout Scouts are
generally not too bad for raiding oh I
need a black oh [\h__\h] uh that was
here
M yo where's your
kingdom uh left side of the map oh [\h__\h]
this is the wrong
one I'm like
huh okay no unemployment here which is
good but also I don't know I'm not sure
what I'm supposed to
do two Castle age
buildings or a castle how do I build a
castle you have to become I think you're
already Castle age right so then you go
to the military buildings or whatever
they're called there's a castle there
around the where the where you can also
build the walls it's on the first
page you need Stone first oh
sh these people aren't mining stone
they're mining gold
[Laughter]
oh yeah you need both I guess especially
now that you Advanced so much you really
need like
everything
whoops oh you that was your trading
center
ah well maybe I need a market
too let's build a
house oh maybe I should have made it
further apart wait where's my Trading
Card wait how do I do this where's your
Market uh I'm building it now
it's it will be in the
like back like behind side of my Camp
next to the town center
okay oh it's kind of close to my farm
oops soon
okay oh I can go to Imperial age the
[\h__\h]
mhm do I really want that I guess so oh
look at my Army I don't know guys guys
did you agree that I should do
skirmishes instead or what wait I need a
Siege Workshop uh wait hold on um how to
build I
forgot um University or Monastery oh
wait
wait monk go go go go go monk go yo what
the hell she's building a
Wonder cron well then I will build one
to
soon soon wait where to build a thing is
like she gets auto win if the wander
survives for uh 20 years or
so what is
this I'm going to
sell
wood I don't
[Music]
know oh oh okay
um near the barracks how to build
blacksmith guys I want to build stuff
but I forgot the
menu like a lot of this is just me
looking for the
[Music]
menu ah here it
is black need more more wood more
just more more wood always need more
wood build Monastery
University can we build University I
think we can build a university hell
yeah reduce unemployment by building
university see we even have unemployed
people
already yo where's your Market is oh I'm
going to send mine my card now to you um
there
okay my market looks like the same as
yours so yeah
yeah wait and then what okay I'm
bringing
gold so is that it so is that what I do
uh wait uh
okay and
then oh there's another
one oh no that's a night uh uh monk monk
haak haak [\h__\h] on monk
faster murder
holes okay
nice I got one Relic oh not I'm at
Imperial H let's
go go what are we doing
now Elite tonic yo my stones are
gone where do I look for
stone oh they're
outside there's like stones
outside
where is um the I'm going to build a
mining camp
here fortify my house
walls okay upgrade blacksmith Knights uh
blacksmith blacksmith
[Music]
blacksmith research Cavalry was the
people on horses right infantry is the
bow
Shooters ouers yeah okay something like
that okay yeah okay okay okay okay
oh nice nice nice nice nice oh no more
unemployment okay then I
will don't tell her guys if somebody
goes over to crony's chat and tells her
that I will be mad oh they're out of
stone
uh what was I going to
do let's build
stuff how do I build stuff again no the
menu is
gone what do you click first if you want
to build
something
uh right I'll select a villager
right okay
okay they already told her
great
faster okay no unemployed people
here
[Laughter]
okay let's go go no unemployed people
yes unemployed
people can they not go
inside how do I send them
inside wait how do I have
Garrison wow these people are so
unemployed [\h__\h] I'm getting scared cuz
now it's getting serious like yeah bye
uh really did he get the Relic I think
he did
um
uh oh wait I should I get
crenulations there we go if I get
crenelations on one Castle I get it for
every Castle yeah okay okay okay okay
okay okay ah
we can't let crony win with the Wonder
no R we will have to eventually attack
crony for real for real because
otherwise you gets a automatic win if
her wand that she's building survives
more than what was it 200 years or so
okay wait isn't the aren't the other
team thinking the same thing too I don't
know I don't know if they why is her
wall open here oh is my castle shooting
at that
why is her oh it's because
her whatever it's just open she farmed
the trees right she doesn't know that
she has an open
wall okay um what are we
[Music]
doing should I make walls how do I make
walls um it's also in the military
buildings
menu is it this one not stone wall
right palisade
Wall oh [\h__\h] my castle is attacking
crony's thing oh oops she'll be mad
don't see my Castle's range is just too
big I can't help it crony I'm sorry I'm
not even trying to do that oh oops oops
oops
hey I'm not ready to attack I want to
play defensive I don't want to be
offensive I'm scared she doesn't even
notice that I keep on like killing her
villagers does
she oh I know Rush before walls
up but I there's no way that I can
really do anything
right there's no way that I'll succeed
also she'll send like she'll get maa's
help
uh
um I'm being attacked wait what about
the
gate what about the
gate why is the gate only gate this
thing why is the light why is this only
palisad I know whatever wait I don't
know if they're
ready
no don't kill my castle
Okay okay something like that I guess yo
you're unemployed go help
build
ah T Dam it
[Music]
what is going
on
fight what is going on I'm going to
build a
gate we're having a a nice battle right
now
wait
you guys
said you guys said you can t the
thingy
how wait let's let's
let's oh like this like
this oh like this okay nice nice
nice they're so slow though they're so
slow wait two doors here okay whatever
it's fine all right
Abby
ybyby I got some okay okay oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] I'm kind of doing it
really wait I no wait am I orange I'm
orange I'm
orange yeah you're orange chill chill
chill chill chill
chill husbandry where's the Wonder is
this the Wonder nah her is there is that
her
Wonder yo
nice okay
okay where are my other oh there they
are she's having a lot of
fun why can't I upgrade to Paladin I'm
not
sure are you having I'm going to I'm I'm
losing it I'm absolutely losing it you
having fun I'm shaking I'm shaking yo
let's go I support
you okay her Wonder's dead I killed her
Wonder yo let's go
girl you are the best what what do I
destroy next M I don't
know you can destroy anything that you
want I'm just making farms and stuff I
need Stones yeah I need stones you need
stones yeah but it's okay oh my God I'm
out of stones that's so
crazy okay maybe I can trade or
something not sure are we dying should I
Retreat so many people oh who the [\h__\h]
is green green is
fauna is fauna helping crony or is she
joining the attack yeah she joining the
attack yeah trying probably trying to
like uh third uh what you call it um
take advantage of the situation all
right are we like for this moment
team yeah trying to find an opportunity
oh no this okay she's attacking my
castle no I will not accept that girl
you have to control your things if you
want to work together
fora h
no no girl no you can't do that m- I'm
just going to build another
one uh what was all here all
ID anybody unemployed was a bad
decision anybody
unemployed hey okay I don't want to deal
with the elephants though [\h__\h] no
elephants you should be attacking this
thing
okay anybody unemployed I heard
elephants ret traing
to okay anybody
[Music]
unemployed what's
Loom
hey oh they're still going oh they're
still going is even trying to to defend
herself well Kiara is fighting crony
Raina is fighting unemployment yeah
sorry waya I'm like so focused on this
it's he her
stupid you
no it's okay I'm com I'm combating
unemployment how dare she how dare she
okay unemployment it seems could help me
it seems that unemployment is going to
be defeated after all she's
retreating she's retreating
okay
to nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice I'm being attacked by MAA really
really I don't think so I don't think
[Music]
actively hey
uh shut up chunky
um let me look for a moment at
everything else okay
Stone I'm going to run out of stone
[Music]
too okay oh also I guess I need I just
need need more trade cards okay going to
rebuild my
Army okay chill guys chill guys chill
just stop attacking
them Garrison in here whoa is that a
tiger tiger oh yeah that's a wild animal
I think will the tiger attack
me my bottom wall they won't
notice okay
oh my God no gold are you serious we
have fallen into
[Music]
poverty um those
Shield I guess can join the Gold guys we
are falling into poty where is our
Market yo yo little shits you really
think this is you really think you
really think oh
yeah
how do I get my two tonic Knights out on
Garrison yo look for gold my
homies look for
gold where's my market I don't know
where my market is oh here it
is
ooh I'm going to
sell
okay
okay I don't think I'm ready to go like
that deeply
in I'm I'm on my way I have like some
cavalries I invent I I gave birth for
you
okay together we shall kill
crony yay
but I'm kind of poor right now I need to
look for
gold I need to dig for
gold what else could I
do oh my gosh this person unemployed oh
she's a builder
though blacksmith blacksmith black
unemployment in
here wow why are you all
unemployed everybody's
unemployed wait is there no mining spots
here that's crazy I still researching
hoardings okay thank you Kelly thank you
Kelly I'm actually doing it man I'm
actually my my practice was actually
kind of worth it yo let's
go I want to make some I don't know
should I make
a where
is
where is the thing that is it the mango
now the thing that you place and then it
goes boom boom boom but then it has to
like it always has to place itself which
one was that I don't know what are you
talking about I have no
idea
the yeah where is the cuz I I'm blind ah
here this one okay let's make a
few oh shift dot to select all gabo
people at once holy [\h__\h] that's game
Chang
should I research con
conscription I'll just keep on making my
Army bigger oh hey girls you're done
[\h__\h] there's some more gold here and I
don't really need the gold hey how many
paladins do you want me to you know come
over uh all no what do you mean all 15
20 I don't know wait you know what I'll
just Build Another
Castle she won't see that
coming kind of close to the other one I
guess
but just to keep a chain going I I'll
just surround everyone of
[Music]
Castle what was it I'm shaking by the
way guys this whole time I'm shaking I'm
just oh the no
can they kill it yeah bye oh yes I
[Music]
can okay creating wait you know what I
really want to do wait waa you're still
you're still fighting uh no I'm
preparing Another Castle okay oh my my
castle is like shooting on the archery
the whole time did she give up her
archery okay okay I wonder wonder if I
should build another
Castle I wonder what else I should
research should I research on
Pikeman I'm not
sure okay what's going on what's going
on what's this cart doing
[Music]
here
okay do people need to be also in the TR
no they're
packed more
people they're on they're on okay monks
for the elephants what what I don't have
oh to convert
[Music]
M okay
and then what do we
research what's card do they do that
automatically cuz I don't really have
the time to micromanage that conversion
stuff unemployment rate looking good we
don't have anybody unemployed yes
everybody's busy will they stop me from
building another Castle
h
uh 0% unemployment in the Pia R
Empire wait so what was the answer chat
about the monks do I have to micromanage
the
monks am I actually winning holy [\h__\h]
yes I don't think I can do that you guys
have to remind
me so when I uh crony has like really
strong um elephants as her units yeah
and I'm going to try to convert them
with my monkss but I'm personally not so
confident about it how has she by the
way still not made a wall here when she
knows I'm constantly intruding on her
wall like she has an open wall and I
keep on coming through what's good
against
elephants m I don't know what's good
against elephants are the elephants
employed though I don't think
so your Castle won't let her true oh I
made another
Castle oh she wants to maybe do
something about oh but my castle is too
strong
so you know what oh there's unemployment
here unforgivable am I dominating
this unforgivable I'll make another
Castle here I don't think I can actually
really manage so many castles
[Music]
though oh we need to build more
houses oh nice one
nice is there anybody hello you can make
a
house okay [\h__\h] I'm so nervous like my
[Music]
God AOE age of
employment yeah we have houses here nice
how many villagers do you have in your
city e uh 142 what about you nice I'm
only
125 that's fine I got to give birth to
more people m
give birth to more
people oh they're D they just let me do
this why don't they stop
me I don't
know is there any resources oh yeah Rea
do you need the stones no not really
okay but I guess I do but also not
really I don't
know we can share yeah okay I I don't
know how to share but always welcome I
think my Army is like ready but I'm I'm
mentally not
ready
yeah
yeah yeah so does yo what the [\h__\h]
bro oh it's Kiara never mind yeah that's
just me don't worry orange is friendly
color yeah yeah yeah good good
thanks let me prep some people to
Garrison
inside and here some people
more holy [\h__\h] my Army is going to be
huge I was so ready to throw
down I'm going to go soon you're being
attacked by I'm going in very
soon yo you probably don't have to join
me I can probably do it
alone yo I'm being ATT attack by
FAA what is going on she maybe she sees
you as a weak person attack her back but
maybe maybe don't Li maybe it's just her
Scout like just one make sure it's a
real Attack might not be no I'm dying I
think upgrade units where how what what
should I upgrade what
else
this infantry was it Cavalry cavalry
my castle
castle
there's R do you need help yeah I do uh
fana is attacking my base from the East
side her elephants yeah her stupid
elephants so
annoying do I
have m
should I send my whole army or just half
of it do we need to repair or maybe we
build another
one anybody
[Music]
unemployed I'll just put a castle here
they destroyed your Castle yeah no
you're so mean to me people I'll send
some people to make
it they're so mean to me I'm going to
give birth to the is she still attacking
you or did she Retreat oh she already
retreated oh okay wait then I'll go
attack crony
now we're full
force
nice we're going to let her go to sleep
IRL because I'm sure it's late at her
place why is FAA attacking me all the
time crony just
accepted just accept it why are you
attacking the fields don't do that yeah
like why what is this sparkly sound it's
my mon right
okay it's so annoying why where is her
Town Center she's harassing
me what fauna is still harassing you yes
she is she cannot do that she will she
will feel
karmer oh she killed did she kill my
villagers uh she killed my villagers I'm
so sad oh cuz I thought I was sending
them wait I'll don't worry don't worry
just stay strong I'll take down crony
and then I'll take down everybody who
hurts
you
okay which one is the Town Center this
no wait what's the Town Center is this
the Town Center mhm I don't know what
the Town Center looks like that's a
mill
no we're jobless now her place is empty
did she move in with MAO or something
her place is literally
empty
really she doesn't have one huh where
did she go what is going
on is she even using this
place she did move in with
MAA okay do I need to like kill this
place to officially let her and I have
to kill her Town Center or what
H well I guess some population cut would
be fine oh there's actually unemployment
here
unforgivable can you guys not go for the
gate like what the
[\h__\h] um I'm apparently now going to
attack MAA just so you know okay because
there where Mauna is is grony cuz she
moved out of her place a while ago okay
oh her castle is here all right all
right wait where do we meet where do we
meet uh muna's Corner oh muna's
corner here oh I see
it I need to gather all my people first
come on come on faster faster yo the
horse is being chased
by they're being chased
by they're being freaking chased with
stuff is there a shortcut to get all of
all all all of
all all of uh my
Army
okay I'm going to build a castle to
protect you nice thank
you that's so nice of
you oh
girl I'm going to make my tripet are
very um is that you is you are you
helping me at Mo's Place yeah yeah I am
a wait we need to take care of this an
employment
though need to take care about these
unemploy probably going to be too
[Music]
late uh way can you send your horses to
uh help me uh cuz MAA is kind of
destroying oh sorry
sorry they the ones that you already
have here okay
there she him I destroyed her really I
need I need to get rid of this [\h__\h]
pisses me
[Music]
off another
Castle here here what's this research
spot oh you sent you sent some trees can
you uh make them attack um like anything
at the walls
[Music]
yeah of course of
course thank you thank you we're we're
going in we're going in oh she's she has
some people yeah
bye what's the shortcut for uh uh Army
please guys I I'm not looking I'm so
sorry tell me tell
me oh are we dying your backup is is so
helpful right now
Raina
ctrl1
ctrl1 uh that's not really all of them
is
it yeah you're going to
build build
I can't believe I'm killing MAA let's
go yay let's go let's go let's go okay
ramps
attack
attack yay attack oh my god oh my
god let's go R we're winning let's go
we're [\h__\h]
winning let's go let's go let's go and
they don't stop coming and don't stop
coming I keep on creating my tonic
kns
yay wait is her Town Center down so why
am I not winning she needs to resign
now ow now now now what do I attack next
I don't know I don't know do she have
another town center German engineering
German engineering let's freaking
go
German
engineering so I'm like a little scared
actually of like uh fauna and Ana
because uh they're close to me don't
worry about
Ana FAA don't worry about don't FAA
maybe fauna maybe your
what so I need something to counter
fauna's elephants that's the thing so
Pikeman for elephant or
something and I'm still not sure about
that H I'm going to give birth to more
Pike
men he
he I think you can move your tet that
are outside to go more inside okay
sure oh wait she has castles here I
didn't see
it let's go Tres let's go
trebet maybe monks monks for what oh
yeah I don't even know where my marks
are like I have no idea that I was never
going to really use
them what's going on here how to make
how to give birth to
monks she's going down she's going
down I'm not even using my full power
because I don't know how me too I'm just
like randomly you know doing this
okay MAA Castle all down I think unless
she has something hidden somewhere oh
you're building near Red okay let's
freaking go
man I am are they stopping
me well then I'm going to separate the
attention to I'm on my way to Red then
after this
okay a red red red yeah uh we're going
to just quickly kill Cron's Castle all
right gosh Tes have a huge
reach what was it ctrl1 but that's not
all wait there's unemployment here
that's not
right get down go down I'm being
attacked by FAA really is it the castle
oh don't worry for I'll just build
another
one oh are you on on your way to um red
now uh almost yeah she's she's killing
my villagers in my castle that's okay I
make
more oh Fun's coming F Fun's coming to
help elephants are coming by the way
well now now Wawa is
[Music]
coming how do I choose
everybody
they're repairing stuff
here should I pull
back I'll see
you are they not Retreat like re
resigning like why I mean I think like
nobody I think like nobody knows how I
think nobody will reside Nobody Knows
the word resign here no no as in like
nobody knows resign
like I'm not going to resign for
sure FAA probably
has yo like built an army this whole
time so to to
retreat yeah I see Fun's Army in the
middle oh my my God she has a lot of
elephants
yeah she has a
lot of
elephants what's all this fighting still
oh your hes are still trying to destroy
things you do know you have a lot of
units on the top left of
muna's just doing nothing yeah they're
just doing nothing it's so hard to micro
manage that's fine I totally get
that is this
Fest my tet are kind
of she doesn't
know no my
truchet oh Ana
coming mhm but just with a little
bit
like in this time what what is Mauna and
crony even going to
do what I are they trying to like
recreate
or not sure
[Music]
actually stop that stop it what is
happening
she is destroying the castle as I build
it who oh
[Music]
fauna
mhm
okay o I hear
something I hear
something oh where am I creating Scout
Cavalry oh my God please
great
Paladin and I'll create the
Pikeman more
Pikeman is my monk here how do I find
there he is I don't
know oh wait that's you that's you oh
worry about it what's going
on
uh what is going on everyone all the
enemies are keeping me so busy that I'm
like losing track of my things right of
of my resources I know I'm just like I'm
looking for like these Lost Child lost
children you
know where are my lost children they're
on the
way okay
okay are they doing anything oh my God
they these guys literally doing
nothing uh are they um Aruna and and
crony just sitting back and chilling now
oh IA people coming IA people coming oh
okay Ah that's that's just that's
nothing but okay let's attack I guess we
can attack now we you know assert our
dominance
mhm let's go let's go let's freaking
go together pavi strong
yes are these oh you still have some
things in maa's Camp by the way oh
really oh my God
these these little
[Laughter]
thingies what are these guys doing I
don't even know
oh hey what's going on what's her Town
Center that's a castle that's a town
center yeah straight pieces everywhere
like yo what are you doing oh elephants
are coming elephants are coming oh no
careful careful elephants are coming
where is my
mon I don't
know where the [\h__\h] is my
monk what's with the
blacksmith
[Music]
elephant's
coming
ah it's okay it's okay it's
okay uh my city my peaceful
City why can I not sell more at
once
what are you doing M sorry I'm talking
to my own people I'm getting very very
very very
very
excited oh yes can you aim wait that's
that's not
you yeah like the people aren't like
attacking I'm just like please can you
attack you
[Laughter]
know okay well it's it's not the best
way of doing things but we are currently
destroying Anya just fine and we're
keeping fauna busy for that
[Music]
too you had the [\h__\h] elephant like I
don't know yeah I don't know where all
my monks are they're probably dead by
now yeah I'm going to make more hell
Birds what was I going to do oh yeah
my units are too used to the peaceful
life you
know it the [\h__\h] elephants the
[\h__\h]
elephants the [\h__\h] elephants she just
has a million of
them it's okay I'll make more I'll make
more that's not really rough it is it
that's not worth
it there will be peace once the El
defense are
gone yeah B it's killing all my units
yeah yeah yeah it's okay it's killing
mine too it's all
right let's just um let's just I'm going
to rebuild stuff
basically
okay nobody cares about our empty our
wall our walls that are broken that's
good yeah my whole Army is being let
let's regroup regroup
sweeped no I don't want to give up no no
no no no no no it'll be costly it's
going to be costly it's okay just
regroup
okay
oh
oh it's too late it's too
late
NY H oh or it's too late or hold on give
me a
second okay okay I'm going to go to your
place yeah we will attack uh FAA cuz
she's more yeah I'm building I'm
building a castle on her side right
now
Pikeman
Pikeman can I upgrade them them to H
deers yes you can apparently uh Pikeman
are good for um elephants yeah anything
with a spare or a pike or H actually
also archers apparently yeah sorry guys
I saw to late cuz I'm like so I'm trying
to multitask and multitasking is the
thing I do the worst I literally can't
it's okay it's okay I mean we did some
action I think it's
nice also this whole map is running out
of resources is what I'm feeling you're
being attacked by wild
animals I mean I don't
know just destroy everyone like you did
recently okay yeah I just need to
rebuild I guess did I build a castle uh
didn't I build a castle just now
somewhere mhm no okay you have like so
many castles there it's cute yeah baby
castles I need
Stone yeah the map is just out of stone
all we have is wood
[Music]
okay [\h__\h] I hope this game is ending
soon I
know ki's Enterprise yes get some from
crony's old
base that's gold gold I only say
gold oh I need
Stone me too but worst case you can buy
it for your Trade Center
yeah what's happening right now what am
I doing I'm like I am I'm building an
[Music]
army
M um do you want to attack fauna from um
the right
side
yeah I'm I'm making a castle I want to
um get rid of that that um what her
castles you know for
elephant where the pike
man oh she's coming she's coming she's
coming she's already coming she's
already yeah yeah she's already coming
uh uhoh I think somebody's just straight
up uh telling her that I'm doing this
and that you know
probably oh wait somebody's definitely
just straight up telling her that I'm
doing this and
that I'm not quite
ready I'll send some people but it's
probably not that much oh yeah she's
attacking my uh
villager it's a lot of
elephants
going to try focus on my mocks now and
get the
elephants do I have to do it one by one
do you have monks yeah only a
[Music]
few yeah like four elephants on my um
Bill walls
literally
crazy I'm coming I'm
coming
[Music]
than yeah they're coming in my Village
my Village has no
defense I'm
coming no B you cannot hurt my
wife
no no no no where where are the mon
where are the
monks yeah B my to my the thing is with
my Knights they're so
slow she's killing your town center you
should build another one if it goes down
I think
mhm I'm going to build a town center how
do I build a town center
again here I'm going to move with you
actually I'm going to move to your place
wait are my monks dead they're
dead you you could do that yeah I guess
yeah
um yeah I'm just going to build a town
center they are doing it do we have some
Pikeman to attack the elephants it was
they were kind of doing it yeah hold
on
okay but yeah she's destroying you I
can't stop her yeah it's okay it's okay
let's just uh focus on other
things let's
build shift
Dot
[Music]
yo the trade card just doing nothing
yeah we can't trade anymore cuz your
Trade Center is dead yeah it's okay it's
okay you you could build one like really
far away yeah I'm I'm I'm building right
now building the houses houses what's
going
on
yeah let's make elephant I mean let's
make elephant let's make
pipeman okay um yeah I I'm also creating
like millions of them
mhm I I'm
[Music]
so
okay wait let's
make want to make it here
actually for [\h__\h]
sake okay we have to
attack Yeah by she's attacking my pretty
castle
ah she has millions of [\h__\h] stupid
elephants yeah I guess that's like the
reality of 2v2 V2 you know like yeah why
while we were kill killing crony and
everything else yeah she was like busy
and preparing of el and then like cuz
we're already like hurt from like
attacking MAA and so she makes the final
sweep it's all right
though
no oh I think she's coming from my place
oh
she is
uh-oh she is for Real yeah we let her
prepare for too
long
no stupid [\h__\h] elephants I swear to
God yeah do you have enough Pikeman cuz
I don't have anything no like I mean I
thought I had but she's like swiping
wiping
them yeah the thing is like as long as
we're not attacking her at all she's
going to keep generating those elephants
you know mhm well she I think she
brought probably most of them to me
they're like at my walls
now but she can create more where's she
going that's the thing where is she
[Music]
going where is she going I don't know
what I don't know where she's going
she's leading me
away baiting you maybe
yeah elephant
parade let's make
walls
oh you're making walls you're so cute
yes baby
walls they're coming back though fauna's
elephants lost the elephants oh there
they are
[Music]
give
birth make the houses like
this damn it takes a long time to
convert them
[Music]
yeah attack them oh my God those are
look the elephants
too slow
oh oh what's that fighting sound oh I
don't
know okay I'm just going to give birth
to Pikeman it's not over yet it's not
over
I don't have stone do you have stone
nearby no I keep on selling my other
resources to get stone and gold cuz like
this map is empty oh my but I forgot to
do
this going to take crony's
resources
yes we're getting ready way we're not
going to let them have this okay
okay what are they doing for real for
real like are they just
waiting oh ah they're trying to destroy
your castles
but as long as they're busy with it with
something
what was that
fauna well yeah fauna is going to be
coming soon so if you have Barracks
create some more hel deers and Pikeman
or whatever yeah yeah yeah I'm going to
make she's on her way we need to be
ready I'm going to
make it's the end of the game probably
so just going to use all my
resources okay I want to make Markus
we need to build more houses damn
ity can you build
priests you mean monks yeah yeah yeah
monks I've been I've been doing that
yeah okay good good good but it's it
just takes endless time to oh Dam I need
to build more
houses
FAA incoming uh-oh
oh she's going there she's at Elena
attack attack attack time to
attack oh she's attacking from
here I don't have Tre that's the
thing
sorry it's my town center
[Music]
uh-oh uhoh I'm too
slow they're too
slow this is not
happening what are they
doing taking
advantage
yeah I can't build
houses yeah my uh my Pike men are gone
because they're
outnumbered
oh so sad what do we
do I can't make a castle cuz I don't
have enough Stone I don't have a market
either
no my
relics my beautiful beautiful
relics I'm at the level well I actually
need to build
houses wa yeah it's kind of over but
like if I resign now does it
automatically put me on the last spot
just because I that's the thing cuz like
um we already destroyed the others like
um we already destroyed the other
uh thing but they wouldn't resign you
know yeah it
does then I won't give up maybe it will
give me credit for the things I
did don't resign and MAA
didn't how do we know it's over when do
we decide it's
over chhat how do you open I don't know
I don't know how to control
this I don't know what to do to end this
nobody's resigning ever
last place is always lowest score not
first to
resign really but if you resign that
means
[Music]
um stupid
ass I hate elephants
forever I know [\h__\h]
elephants sh B be low profile be low
profile what do you mean don't don't
don't engage unless they
engage it's too late anyway I guess
so yeah the thing is last what does Last
Man Standing
mean I don't even
know how many do I have's crony's Place
let's seek Refuge refuge on crony
place no it's
[Music]
over it's over my last uh dude is dying
oh okay my last villager is
dead but we need to keep building so our
score stays
up
well we are not last waya that's for
sure that's for sure I guess we were
dominating for the longest
time I know but in that time FAA was
building her elephant Army elephant
Army
elephant well where are my
villagers I don't see them are they
working on
something oh they are working on
something I don't want to retreat and
rebuild I'm done I'm I want to
sleep this is so if like it makes no
sense to do that now in my opinion
because like it's already decided like
yeah it's kind of GG but at the same
time it's uh it's Gigi but at the same
time it's like you know other people are
bu this stupid
you want to resign yeah uh it's up to
you [\h__\h]
this I did enough yeah me too I think I
did enough you should resign too it's
under Escape okay the second
one I guess so but what happens when you
resign I hope that the one person who
said that the score matters more than
the resign uh was right cuz then we
would be ranked higher H I guess so but
the thing is if Muna and crony is not
resigning and they keep building and
building we're going to
lose I don't think they're building oh
wait they are they are they are trying
to recover AR wait I've been telling you
that every I didn't say
that wait there's so much trees here
what the [\h__\h]
mhm well what the [\h__\h] yo like fauna
like can you like go to like MAA and
crony and check out if they're like
building something yeah she shouldn't
waste her time with my castles fauna you
can go I
resign go to crony uh MAA whatever
yeah I don't know the rules but they
should have retired they should like
normally when you're playing this game
in normal online they would have
resigned ages ago
yeah wait
what
um can I just yeah they're re Building
look at
this why don't they just attack these
people before they grow too big yeah why
are they attacking my dead castles and
muna's dead walls yeah oh by the way I'm
uh I'm
dead cuz I have like zero people I
think I have zero houses or something
something I want to see like what's
going on though what's on your screen
right
now uh I you see to the map and I'm just
watching what's going on but okay okay
okay she stopped her elephant's
movement yeah we'll see
though so do I do we just wait another 5
years or maybe maybe uh let's try let's
try resign okay
yeah return return to map you have you
you have common
sense yeah they need to destroy all the
production buildings Last Man Standing
literally means that I don't know how
long this will
end I mean I know it didn't even but
even when like all my villagers and
stuff were in my town center and
everything were dead I don't know
they're still the walls or something no
more fog of war ah true true true let's
see what they're
doing yeah I guess they take they take
Last Man Standing very
literally yeah a walls don't count if
you lose all production buildings well
Kiara still has a
castle e yeah it look like can you move
into my castle what I
resigned I'm no longer available for
giving
birth okay like FAS FAS just scouting
Cron's place now yeah they should go
straight to there in the
[Music]
corner oh thank you
guys I did my best yeah I did my best I
feel like you know like even though we
lost I think we did okay you know like
we're literally we're literally the one
who started attacking and stuff I mean
yeah we made we made move MAA and we
made Ana move into FAA so we were
dominating
strong it's just like you know I was
doing the pieace I was doing the pieace
and I helped you out I played
enough it was a
good and like I think you know it's fine
we didn't really have a counter for this
either but to be fair they started late
as well so I think it's nice fauna has
nice
3,100 power I mean three 3 30,000 31,000
oh my God I can't
English yeah let's go oh my God was my
downfall I wouldn't say so my downfall
was just people not resigning when
they're already dead
but here here we see the final finit
wait I want to see I want to see The
Showdown fauna is attacking the
[Music]
kingdom I like the the
wall the ar ar
architecture they have going on so many
walls mixed and
entangled entangled it's
beautiful
oo they have like several layers like
a
archers they're
rumbling this is so fun to
see wee so
satisfying oh I see fighting back hating
on me I see
you go back the city is like an onion so
like a double they're making like a
double layer thing
mhm Hest camel people are coming
elephants are
glitching let's
go historically accurate red
walls
really it almost looks like a
city yeah like a proper City with like
two layered walls that's pretty cool I
think yo yo yo the invasion of
funan let's
go you're not coming to see an elephant
parade then the elephant parade is
coming to see
you did you read that from Chad yeah
chat
yo wait what's going on in oh fauna
place is pretty well civilized I need to
copy her building Strat oh okay like
this Farms yeah pretty much oh she made
double walls yeah she made double walls
which is pretty good I guess but only on
one side yeah cuz the other the one has
Forest right right it's very orderly
yep even though I
resigned my resources are still like our
resources together are still like Place
FR and fourth
yeah at least in the in that ranking
there
yeah MAA didn't know how to resign
either
didn't
know ah pill
come you were in a hard spot I was
trying my best Under
Pressure oh nice but I mean all also I
was having a lot of issues as well you
know I tried my best but also it was
also like obviously the lack of
experience in playing the game even
though you played it like once or twice
or like practice most of us didn't have
much experience so yeah I think like
chat was like oh my God we told you it's
this you know at some point and I'm like
I don't know I
forget it's I
for it's fine there's so many things to
remember if you want to play it
well so many things to manage like
upgrade this build this make your army
make your villagers make your resources
at the beginning like um I made too many
cavalries and I think that's why like we
could like do um moai and crony fairly
uh nicely but that's the thing I didn't
build enough oh resigned I didn't build
enough um
Pikeman moon is that it's over oh it's
over time has stopped time has stopped I
guess we joined them in the VC I guess
so I'll
join hello that was
cool that was nice G
gg gg damn you're military
economy oh my God FAA is really great
yeah she was building she was building
building yeah building is too strong the
mother of
nature it's too strong that was really
nice nice I enjoyed that that was yeah
that was fun I was scared with Cara at
first like Cara put Castle
everywhere Castle yo I was minding my
own business and K was like yo yo yo yo
Raina can you send some help I'm going
to attack cron I'm like
what I was minding my own business and I
was minding my own business too sounds
like everyone was minding their own
business you know damn Kiara was out for
blind I mean I was just trying to get
the game the ball rolling I guess so
yeah before someone rolls it on me yeah
I guess other otherwise you know people
would be just like build like me like me
peaceful
building well me and Ana I feel like
we're playing like a farming simulator
me that was me that was me before Kiara
was like yo help me out I'm like huh
what oh yeah actually the reason I
attacked crony was because she was
building the wander and I you build a
wonder you're a target for everybody
yeah oh she building the Wonder
she was building a Wonder yeah and that
gives you automatic win if you keep it
for a very long time and as we see this
game was going to go on for a long time
so the Wonder could have
won that would have been a good Strat F
was about to attack but then I was like
if they're fighting each other then let
them
be I just did elephant strategy just
build a million elephants and hope for
the
best wait can we see the I think MAA has
to maybe somebody has to press something
so we can see the the the stats or
something oh yeah the stats already here
um oh sorry I don't is it quit current
game yeah do you do you to map oh there
we go nice nice nice nice nice wait
where do you see it oh my Society hi
Society Statics nice living in the
society I clicked return to map a
lot Co oh Kara had star Society a
[Music]
lot cool cool cool cool cool a very nice
oh when it's it's come back to economy I
sent a lot to
crony T trading I had 11 castles it was
good it was good oh I killed
196 people
yay
no very cool o our numbers are actually
not
bad yeah nice food collected
yummy wood collected very
cool very nice if you look at timeline
you see like the graph of how things are
changing ooh oh
oh yeah I
see oh my god wow W just like going up
the tabl are elepants all about the
elephants
yeah let me see I want to see I not
attacking first was a good strategy
though cuz like we could
focus yeah we were just chilling at the
start I was like if if they're fighting
each other then let them
be yeah I mean why not that's probably
what you should do true true but
sometimes the intrusive
thoughts
true the intrusive thoughts are just
yeah I
understand my chat people say like
nobody stands in that way what whatever
me to natur Alis
SW oh well normally I would have liked
to play defensive too but I don't know I
had to kill the Wonder and then from the
Wonder everything was just like rolling
and I it just happened I feel like
aggression is good it adds the spice you
know I think I underestimated you guys
honestly I thought maybe you guys didn't
practice enough so maybe you guys
wouldn't know what you get a sneaky
Wonder out
yo I was constantly like guys how do I
build the
Barrack when it was constantly asking
yeah I don't remember almost a single
how do I do this how do I do that why
are people
unemployed
no if if I want to ask for rematch again
would you want to do it but not now well
not now not now but I'm totally down
be nice yeah um maybe this time is uh we
we make it pretty pretty easy because we
have a cheating seat in in our live chat
but the next time how about no cheating
SE
yeah sure if you can really control that
and we could we could randomize the
sifts so that everybody gets something
unexpected it's not months from now cuz
by then I'll I forget about the
[Laughter]
game we should just date immediately
before we forgot how to play again
yeah what I'm saying
mhm maybe after this I will put another
date yeah so but overall this this seems
fun like like I I'm pretty pretty I
think I underestimate a lot of you guys
yeah oh my God that is crazy I need to
play game I was scared of you MAA I was
so scared of you I I told you I'm not
really good at this game you didn't
believe me just because I play this game
doesn't mean that I'm good at it
even good you good it's just that you
were trying to save me and I'm
sorry I think everyone need a practice
theme after
all
no but yeah thank you so much everyone
for playing this game with me uh it's
been fun thank you for organizing thank
you I'm glad it happened
finally it was super fun thank you thank
you it's been we almost doing this like
for like 2 hours ially yeah I know it
flew by that was a long like I expected
the game is going to be 2
hours perfect perfect timing yeah well
um for this one actually I have a lot of
uh strategy game
um uh each of Empire is like one of them
while the others uh there is another
game called
Starcraft if you guys interested on
Starcraft it's another building game
another starting game if you guys
interested I would love to make another
one I'll try it yeah I'd love to but I
need to learn about the game yeah I need
to learn to yeah
yeah more more learning more learning
let's
go my brain is going to
explode what it is what it is T is so
much um I think we need to guys have any
uh maybe information for the
viewers I don't know I'm good no no I
just want to say thank you thank you way
for being a great
teammate thank you Ki for bringing out
the aggressor in
me for being a really good te like we we
actually pretty working good together
yeah next time I won't build the Wonder
that's a lot of underestimated you you
need to build a wonder you just have to
figure out when you're building the
Wonder is your military already finished
also weer you building it like at least
when I arrived you only had one person
working on the Wonder but the Wonder
takes like so much more time than other
buildings you need to build with like 20
people at once yeah it need you need a
lot of people and make sure that uh your
military is time ready to you know M
take the Wonder I wanted to build one
too someday someday someday
somay W that's all everyone thank you so
much I'm going to end in there thank you
so
much thank you so much for playing this
game Let's Play Again
H really B time thank you aw bye m
later bye-bye
[Music]
byebye