​​​ ​Takanashi Kiara - Heart Challenger​ ​​
​​​ ​Lyrics: Aya Shinno (真野綾)​ ​​
​​​ ​Producer/Composer: Kai Gojo (五条下位)​ ​​
​​​ ​Guitar: Daisuke Bito (尾登大祐)​ ​​
​​​ ​Video Artist: Mamaloni​ ​​
​​​ ​Movie Animation: Nebiru (ねびる)​ ​​
​​​ ​Logo Artist: Spiritsnare​ ​​
​​​ ​Special Thanks: Huke​ ​​
​​​ ​Singer: Takanashi Kiara (小鳥遊キアラ)​ ​​
​​​ ​Heart throbbing endlessly,​ ​​
​​​ ​Doki Doki tomaranai​ ​​
​​​ ​soon I’ll need my maiden’s courage​ ​​
​​​ ​mousugu otome no yuuki​ ​​
​​​ ​Valentine's is coming soon​ ​​
​​​ ​chokotto hitsuyouna no​ ​​
​​​ ​kitare barentain​ ​​
​​​ ​Sweet and a bit bitter,​ ​​
​​​ ​amakute horonigai​ ​​
​​​ ​painful like my feelings for you​ ​​
​​​ ​setsunai kimi e no kimochi​ ​​
​​​ ​Make me Maid me -​ ​​
​​​ ​Make me Maid me​ ​​
​​​ ​changing into​ ​​
​​​ ​kosuchuumu chenji​ ​​
​​​ ​my favourite costume!​ ​​
​​​ ​okiniiri ni kigaete!​ ​​
​​​ ​My heart flutters at the ticklish scent​ ​​
​​​ ​hana kusuguru kaori ni​ ​​
​​​ ​Heart tokimeichau​ ​​
​​​ ​Let’s start!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's start!​ ​​
​​​ ​I’m going to make it, with lots of LOVE​ ​​
​​​ ​tsukuru yo rabu komete​ ​​
​​​ ​The very best chocolate!​ ​​
​​​ ​tobikkiri no chokoreito​ ​​
​​​ ​Once I grasp my oversized sleeves tightly,​ ​​
​​​ ​moesode o gyutto nigittara​ ​​
​​​ ​it’s the cue to start the mission!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mission kaishi no aizu​ ​​
​​​ ​Receive this colorful taste​ ​​
​​​ ​karafuruna koi no aji​ ​​
​​​ ​of love before it melts ​ ​​
​​​ ​tokechau mae ni uketotte​ ​​
​​​ ​(Please!)​ ​​
​​​ ​The chimes are ringing,​ ​​
​​​ ​narihibiku kane no oto​ ​​
​​​ ​just us two by the school's window​ ​​
​​​ ​kousha no madobe de futari​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, I have to say it quickly...​ ​​
​​​ ​nee hayaku iwanakucha​ ​​
​​​ ​I’m shy but​ ​​
​​​ ​terechau kedo​ ​​
​​​ ​“I love you”​ ​​
​​​ ​"suki desu"​ ​​
​​​ ​Let these feelings reach you​ ​​
​​​ ​kono omoi​ ​​
​​​ ​kimi made todoke​ ​​
​​​ ​Tick tock - running wild,​ ​​
​​​ ​chikutaku susunde ku​ ​​
​​​ ​I can’t stop this feeling​ ​​
​​​ ​kimochi wa tomerarenai no​ ​​
​​​ ​I’ll gather my courage slightly​ ​​
​​​ ​chokotto yuuki dashite​ ​​
​​​ ​to send you this love letter​ ​​
​​​ ​okuru rabu retaa​ ​​
​​​ ​No matter how many times I write “I love you”,​ ​​
​​​ ​"daisuki" nanjukkai​ ​​
​​​ ​it won’t come across​ ​​
​​​ ​kaite mo tsutae kirenai​ ​​
​​​ ​Make me Fake me -​ ​​
​​​ ​Make me Fake me​ ​​
​​​ ​Send the coward me flying over the sky!​ ​​
​​​ ​ikujinashi nante​ ​​
​​​ ​sora no kanata tonde ke!​ ​​
​​​ ​I’ll check myself again and again​ ​​
​​​ ​nando mo chekku shite​ ​​
​​​ ​before I meet you​ ​​
​​​ ​kimi ni au toki wa​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to be 100 times cuter than usual for you​ ​​
​​​ ​hyakubai mashi de​ ​​
​​​ ​kawaiku naritai no​ ​​
​​​ ​Staring contest in front of the mirror!​ ​​
​​​ ​kagami no mae niramekko​ ​​
​​​ ​With a different sweetness​ ​​
​​​ ​itsumo to chigau Sweet sa de​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to capture your heart!​ ​​
​​​ ​Heart o toriko ni shitai​ ​​
​​​ ​Constantly changing my hairstyle,​ ​​
​​​ ​kurukuru kaete mite mo​ ​​
​​​ ​I can’t decide​ ​​
​​​ ​kamigata mada kimaranai​ ​​
​​​ ​(Geez!)​ ​​
​​​ ​(mou!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Simulate the confession,​ ​​
​​​ ​kokuhaku no shimyureishon​ ​​
​​​ ​my heart starts an uproar​ ​​
​​​ ​Doki Doki sawagidashichau​ ​​
​​​ ​I wish to the moonlit night...​ ​​
​​​ ​tsukiyo ni negai komete​ ​​
​​​ ​Make or break!​ ​​
​​​ ​ippatsushoubu​ ​​
​​​ ​Tomorrow it will surely be sunny​ ​​
​​​ ​ashita wa​ ​​
​​​ ​zettai ni​ ​​
​​​ ​haremasu youni​ ​​
​​​ ​I need to tell you that I love you through and through​ ​​
​​​ ​There’s no one else in this world that I would trade for you​ ​​
​​​ ​Once I grasp my oversized sleeves tightly,​ ​​
​​​ ​moesode o gyutto nigittara​ ​​
​​​ ​it’s the cue to start the mission!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mission kaishi no aizu​ ​​
​​​ ​Receive this colorful taste​ ​​
​​​ ​karafuruna koi no aji​ ​​
​​​ ​of love before it melts​ ​​
​​​ ​tokechau mae ni uketotte​ ​​
​​​ ​(Please!)​ ​​
​​​ ​The chimes are ringing,​ ​​
​​​ ​narihibiku kane no oto​ ​​
​​​ ​just us two by the school's window​ ​​
​​​ ​kousha no madobe de futari​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, I have to say it quickly...​ ​​
​​​ ​nee hayaku iwanakucha​ ​​
​​​ ​I’m shy but​ ​​
​​​ ​terechau kedo​ ​​
​​​ ​“I love you”​ ​​
​​​ ​"suki desu"​ ​​
​​​ ​I love you!​ ​​
​​​ ​daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let these feelings reach you​ ​​
​​​ ​kono omoi​ ​​
​​​ ​kimi made todoke​ ​​