[Music]
is
do me a favor
here we go
[Music]
go ahead
[Applause]
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
is
hello hello can you hear me
let's turn on the game audio there we go
lets me unmute my friends hello hello
hello hello hello oh
god that scared me geez oh
gosh horrifying
what
that
[Music]
i gave we're going to use in-game audio
but for now i i feel like this chord
yeah
for this part just for the intro yeah
good are you muted on discord by the way
i don't know if you're talking to your
viewers but i can't hear you good i want
to hear your voice
oh wait i'm here too
millie is watching too oh god damn it
hello kitty
[Laughter]
we are not afraid no i'm a little afraid
probably not totally okay
we play if we played a little bit of
this game and i got so scared i almost
cried
so and you only got scared because it
got dark
because i was alone if one of you was
with me in the dark it would have been
funny but it was just me by myself and
it was very frightening
she was screaming so much i was like
crying
is mine like dropping my my game my pc
does not like this game all of a sudden
whoa whoa
red frame drop whoa oh what here
oh this is just the internet possibly
uh no it's whenever i whenever i'm in
the game it's just
yeah uh let me let me i'm gonna adjust
some settings real quick okay i'm gonna
leave the lobby and then come back
no problem by the way guys i bought a
lighter
and i bought some salt because there was
none
so i bought it you bought salt yup i
didn't i did
i bought salt yes salt just cooking who
is that what does the salt do
i don't know maybe you can use it in
exorcisms in the shower though
i'll bring up their mom that i'll buy a
thermometer yeah
where do we where do we buy items
uh in the server lobby in the lobby ah
bye
the how are you guys moving around i'm
stuck
uh at the st at the screen or is that is
that good uh that's chiara
how did you break free from that i'm
adjusting oh
uh do we not have a tripod is that why
the camera thing didn't work
probably i mean i just i tried to set
down the camera but
you can uh you can pass it onto the
floor or something
and it'll still work the the camera in
the truck never showed any
anything besides outside uh did was the
green light on
on the camera did you see cali just turn
the green light on
uh yes i turned it on there we go
i'm gonna buy a tripod because i have
exactly 25 dollars
oh perfect okay that should work really
well then oh wait no i need to be level
two and i'm probably level one
yeah we're all we're all eleven level
one ghosty hunters
okay never mind we'll be level two i
think
oh yeah cannot go
shopping hold on i'm joining back i'm
coming back
right okay
let's see if this helps yeah
also uh chad says that the salt can be
used to track the ghost
via uv oh
so they step on it and then they like
leave a trip
yeah or something like that i don't know
we'll figure it out
wow this is our cool base oh we're so
cool this is like
this is like a an anime or like tv show
or something we're like cool ghost
hunters and this is our home
cool
are you scared possibly yes
okay uh by the way we're gonna we're
gonna use the proximity chat right
yes we're going to mute us on discord
once we're in the game
um okay
i'm ready yeah me too let me say i'm
ready
i can't wait should i turn should i turn
these things on or off what does that do
i don't understand why my game is all of
a sudden now
like
maybe it has to do with the fact you're
also streaming
well why this game what yeah
strange oh well i mean is it
different different uh different what's
gonna call it
do you think off maybe it's v sync is on
you see i'm gonna tweak one more setting
yeah they said
always should be off ah maybe that's
what it is maybe
yeah yeah it drops performance when it
doesn't consistently hit 60 frames
so yeah maybe oh my now everything is
going wrong oh i love this game oh my
god
it's cool we got time we got time no
problem i'm just going to sip some mizu
don't mind um
[Music]
take your time take your time oh this is
bad what happened
whoa everything everything is going
very wrong all of a sudden oh no what do
you mean
welcome to hollow en there's always
gonna be a little scuff
i'm gonna restart my game i apologize if
you want to play around without me
please please go ahead
we can wait it's cool wait no problem
i want to try and learn about some of
these ghosties
[Laughter]
are you are you huh
oh no um
ah my game turned into like a strip
a strip on the screen what happened oh
oh she's gone bye-bye she's gone i think
girl is the next ghost
where is the next ghost this is not
going
to plan this was working fine about 10
seconds 10 minutes ago
i think the ghost got to you your pc
no not the o it's okay not everything's
gonna be perfect i mean look at look at
the character
models and how they maybe it's a good
game i'm not [\h__\h] on the game it's
just
they're gonna be let me dance for you
gangster couch gangster
let me dance for you kelly let me dance
for you guys
i don't know about sexy but i mean it
sure is a dance
what's with your hands though what about
my hands i have hands
very weird oh when you're when you wait
when
when you're when you're like that you
look like you're gonna do the naruto run
[Applause]
[Laughter]
did anybody else like tweak their
settings at all or is this working fine
on
on everybody else's i didn't change
anything at all
i tweaked it a little bit but i don't
know if it did anything
uh okay what are you doing this is weird
how do you fold over like cardboard okay
well i'll try this
i'm gonna jump back whenever you look
down with your mouse
you're doing that pose yeah let's do the
naruto run
the only thing is we can't be very fast
oh my god
very slow naruto run
thanks girl what
are you doing
we're doing narita runs we're waiting
for you oh no
yeah naruto naruto
you gotta go fast
hahaha
how's it going now good night i hear um
i hear the voice of amelia watson
muted okay let's add
it and mute let's try this again okay
okay okay giving us messages to help
solve this problem
once again it's going it's going it's
going it's gone
it's gone so bad
what it was what exactly happens is it
like lagging
yeah every time i every time i tab into
the game and i start moving around
uh every i don't rob it just goes
it goes bad um did you restart the game
stupid question
yes i turned it on and off again okay
let's see
um all right so how about 60 frames per
second
and one 920 by 1080.
for yourself i think that's what it's
done yeah maybe double check
okay yeah are you ready to want to play
around without me
i feel so bad like i don't feel bad
we're chilling
all right you're good all right um and
also make sure the game and obs are at
high priority
how do you close the door ah okay okay
cali let's play hide and see all right
sure whatever um where do you think i
am oh wow you hid pretty quickly because
of tony hold on a sec
it's fine we've done this before um
[Music]
sorry everyone i don't i'm sorry
yeah take your time no worries you'll
never find me kelly
i'm sorry you underestimate me
i will find you hang on
hang on a sec all right you you hid
pretty well i give you that much
um oh you crashed i wonder huh
getting colder colder hotter hotter
hotter yeah
oh my god emilia is doing technical
support right now in our discord she's
not in the club but she's in the discord
helping us with technical stuff
amazing amazing amazing amazing
oh kiara there you are where were you
you have to tell me where you were
wait this looks better on my side
already wait i am
not no no
i'm in the closet oh trapped in the
closet
i close the door like that
peek-a-boo okay i'm coming out of the
closet for you kelly
thanks
close the door yeah it's only when i tab
into the game everything all of a sudden
just goes really bad
um is it because
uh you were hosting the game possibly
maybe
oh maybe i'm not hosting
i'm going to stop right there we all
know what happens
when you try to say this song on youtube
uh okay
this name is better because i'm tabbed
out oh and i'm gonna
uh you guys play a player game without
me if
um while i figure this out if you want
i i'm not sure if i can do it without
you
that you're the most experienced one
when it comes to ghosts
i'm somebody unless it's not that bad
should we just try one like
she screams out of a [\h__\h] she's trying
let's just try let's just try let's just
try
okay what was the girl's name and he
says kathy
go to hell what i'm so sorry i'm singing
a song
sorry select a
house yes please yeah okay
whoa the farm house the farmhouse with
the moomoos
oh they're all are we using in-game
cool
i wanna buy a flashlight
all right gotta turn them off we're
ready up ready up
wait did i add my stuff hold on we have
the lighter and uh the salt
ready up
i have to bring the ghosts under control
i'll do my best
i shall try then why does it say i'm
okay we're ready
cool it's party time everyone
can you guys hear me okay
who is this sir you know
graham
huh what am i doing wrong
hold on hello
oh [\h__\h] hello oh just kidding i can hear
you now
100 sanity not for long never long
how's everything going
you know it's going it's going it's
working
okay
hey kiara come get this camera you have
the tripod right
uh no i couldn't buy it ah okay i gotcha
this ghost only responds to people who
are alone
okay so we can stick together no no we
gotta
we don't have to learn how to spread out
yeah we gotta spread out
moshi moshi
you're only 17.5 degrees oh
is that okay are you okay
that's fahrenheit right i'm probably
fine i'm definitely
don't worry about it
okay all right do we want to go in oh
yeah actually i gotta grab something
i'll uh do i have to be the one uh to
capture a photo of the ghost ah
i guess that's my job huh
mary davis i have the camera but i don't
know if i want to do it guys
i don't know no i'm not i'm not a [\h__\h]
i'm not a [\h__\h] never mind i'll i'll do
it
it's fine i'm no positive camera that i
have is that one for
taking videos or for taking photos
the one i have is for photos this is the
one cali has and the one you have is for
okay
okay so i have to hunt down in the room
where we think it is okay
i could use a flashlight do you guys all
have flashlights
yes we only have limited amount of
flashlights though
one over there is the uv light before
you're seeing fingerprints
oh okay should we grab that because you
brought salt
it might be yeah yeah yeah flashlights
oh damn
she was so scared in the dyke but how
did you all get lights
how did you get them but you had one on
your shoulder
yeah well it sure helps me a lot
proximity
okay let's get started are you good
let's play the game let's go
we're good i'm good open up
okay we're going in the dish
here we go hi i'm here too i'm adjusting
more settings yay
okay take your time
i'm going in first i'm not going to go
snug
nothing can scare me okay
okay okay
yeah there's already [\h__\h] going down
okay yeah
is
hello mary davis
oh my god mary davis has a pool in her
back oh god the in-game mic
davis wow that mary davis huh
press t t doesn't do anything uh so
right now we gotta we gotta
we gotta probably scope out where the
mushy moss oh shoot
konichi washington domodomo
tamoshimasu hajime hello
maybe after this round i can afford one
we'll see we can't turn on all the
lights though we got to remember so we
got to find like closets to hide and
ride
right yeah so who's going to volunteer
to be alone and then to call out mary
davis i guess i have the camera so i
ought to do it but still
i don't really want to i need a quick
escape to the door can we turn off this
radio
wherever it is
here i'll put this down and maybe she
can write us a message
hello mary davis would you like to write
something for us
what you heard footsteps oh no no
it's gonna bathroom maybe they're
your own steps
stop that hello okay
stop that oh okay excuse me
it's all right hold on ha ha now let's
see you can't if you go over the this
you won't be able to visit us in the
chat everybody tells us to use discards
mary davis please write a message
[Music]
oh sorry i i left but i just wasn't
pressing v okay
okay thank you i did not chat i didn't
do it i didn't laugh
yeah you're really you're funny because
thank you
hi did we find anything every day it's
the garage
down the garage apparently it makes her
really angry when we say her name so i
wonder if that's
[Music]
bloody mary bloody mary
hey where's the camera
i want to stay with someone with a
flashlight
so okay ghost this is a double car
garage
my mary babies where are you mary davis
anna mary davis hello she doesn't
respond when we're alone right
when we're together right i don't want
to be alone though
yeah we can go upstairs gaming times i'm
following the light
said nobody ever but okay
hey guys i left the um the notebook in
the kitchen
so maybe she will write a message for us
maybe what we can do is we can all be in
separate rooms that are close to each
other and then close the door and then
try and summon the ghost
hey guys uh the lights went out
the lights went out
um
don't leave me alright don't leave me
should be but i don't have a flashlight
so i will die
you have power
you're in the basement i'm because it's
already i'm coming down there
thank you yeah no problem
it's okay i'm here i just have no
flashlight
i found it i found it i found it okay
hit that bad boy
uh is it back it's it's red now
should it be red it should work
it's okay it's green it's green it it
now it should be fine
again
here you see that you see that
okay seems like it's okay nothing
nothing written on the on the book yet
that radio is really bothering me
oh man maybe it's upstairs then
i definitely think so i think
mary
i heard something yo mary davis where
are you at
the ghost where are you at mary davis
where are you at
i'm getting i get i get frantic when i
get afraid
is that the radio you turn the radio on
everything is radio upstairs
hello mary davis how are you mary david
what if we all say mary davis at the
same time
one two three mary davis
yo mary you owe me two dollars
hey uh i'm upstairs
oh
mary davis
i'd like to take a photo of you
i see i see something what do you see we
have to go out and check our sanity
we've been in thought for a while yeah
good idea okay let's go back
i am not against that let's go here
no don't stay there you're gonna
okay let's go to the truck yes i want to
go to the truck
wrong i just want to go to the truck
okay saturday
can we bring this this cool radio and
maybe we can play some tunes
for mary maybe she'd be into like some
hip-hop or some classic
one of the rooms in the hall okay
um don't see much on the camera can you
reposition the camera maybe a little bit
better oh did you place it oh man yeah i
can't see anything
yeah i think
got it i think someone is already
repositioning it because now i can't
swap the camera anymore let's go get a
blaster baby
can we take it with us maybe i can
freestyle for the ghost nah that that
won't work
now the ghost will hate my freestyle
maybe they like bad faces
hey check that out
hey we see we see it's upside down it's
upside down
you see your feet
all right man
we need one of those tripods
well it was it was a good effort
yeah you got to click on the keyboard
[Music]
i don't think it gets much better than
that but i think that's the best we can
do
looking good i think this mode is better
we should keep it on this mode
you can see much more clearly
we only
okay tony should we go back with the
others
i guess so i'm worried about them
evidence except
freezing temperatures i'm supposed to
take a picture of the ghost uh i'm not a
[\h__\h]
we're gonna do it
[Applause]
shadow
all right i'm going back in to help the
homies
hold on a second hi i'm in the closet oh
my god
the light turned me okay the light's
turning
are you okay so you guys can see the uh
uh the lights are off
uh hello sir you know is that you
ina is that you next to me yep that's me
hey um what's uh what's going on i know
you're checking
okay i'm coming
i could really use a flashlight huh
maybe next time
over
all right let's let's regroup regroup
press press t there is no flashlight
guys i'm pressing t this is me pressing
t there's no flashlight
maybe someone with more sanity wait
let's
go down let's narrow down some
candidates first
and then we can uh figure out what's
going on from there
yeah okay okay that sounds good
no need to die for that yet
but it's fun oh not yet okay
yeah yeah we have anything anything
besides freezing temperatures because
the ghost orbs
some people in the chat said that i
wouldn't trust it that much
anything besides yeah i wouldn't be able
to tell because i didn't see it myself
capture phone i don't think it was there
i think they saw a flashlight
do we have any smudge sticks i only saw
the temperatures
um yeah well temperature we can still
roll out some
so
uh mayor
banshee phantom race
brown we didn't have emp emf5 though we
only had emf
ii
emf 2 ghost orb freezing temperatures
what else yeah
seems likely did we try the spirit block
uh i can try it some more i didn't
really do much with it
it's still i think i still have it i
think
yeah since the the ghost only responds
to when you're alone
we probably have to send one person
there
[Music]
you want the camera okay but you're
still only at
24. girl i'm going to get 22.23 you can
get this look at all that activity
okay go go down girl wait here's the
camera please
please sorry it's on the ground
before i you know girl girl
girl wait girl girl wait the camera's on
the ground
girl you can come get the camera it's in
the truck on the ground
ah sorry i forgot to use talk buttons so
i was i was
i'm not a coward i'm not a coward not a
coward
yeah i'm gonna come into the house too
but i'm gonna stay far away from you so
you can talk to the ghost i'm just gonna
watch from
afar ah content i guess you're the
cameraman
gotcha yeah i need a weapon or something
all the lights are broken
[Music]
in the closet i'm your host gargoyla
boiler mary davis
hey guys
hey guys um
i'm afraid i think we gotta go for girls
i think we're gonna go a little bit
further away
okay i think we gotta go a little bit
oh my flashlight oh no she said oh uh oh
[Music]
oh
i'm a ghost guys can you hear me
guys can you hear me
i can't open the doors
there's girl
mary what are you doing why are you
messing with my friends
mary mary davis mary davis mary davis
where are you
mary davis mary davis
mary davis stop hurting my friends
maybe there's something i can do from
this side the camera's on the ground did
you see callie's dead buddy
mary davis stop hurting my friends
that's my dead body
you can only spectate i know but
i want to see if i'm in the ghost right
hey listen
what is the man if i'm in the ghost
realm
and i should be able to talk to larry
game if you want a tip from me well if
her body
you should make a version where i can
where i can either haunt my friends
or maybe team up with the ghosts
did you get her smile oh that's not your
face this is your face
cali oh my god you're a place
now it's good
go to
oh no no stop stop ah
i couldn't get him kiara's dead
no oh you feed him this took a picture
there's a flashlight on the ground i
think she's good
kiara can you hear me
uh yes i can holy [\h__\h]
i tried to protect i tried i tried to
smack the
i tried to snack the ghost but it wasn't
working yeah i got a cell phone
there's one more picture but finally
we're together
that's what i said no one listened
i did it anyway for fun girl left
why is there free people though
is that amen do you also
wait oh wait it's one of them you
they're just dead bodies yeah
right so i died on the stairs
yeah i've seen this world way too many
times kelly
i know we've met many times in it
[Laughter]
nothing new business as usual
normally you're not really dead i mean
you're deaf but you're normally not dead
right right this is a new experience for
me i must say it's a bit it's it's
different
it's different i wonder where mary davis
is
yeah i wonder if we can see her but wait
does that mean
she must be here as well yeah i i
watched her kill you
so generally generally she's maybe up
there yeah in general probably i don't i
don't know if you can see unless she is
hunting but uh i watched her kind of
swoop out of the darkness
oh we can go check it out we want let's
go okay nothing is scary with you when
you're in my side
nothing is scared yeah yeah i guess so i
mean i can kind of understand
yeah i guess so what would be cool is if
the game let us turn the lights on and
off to communicate to the team that
would be kind of fun
can we see anything as ghosts i wonder
i know that we can still collect
evidence and do our journals
so that we can also get money nice but i
wonder if we can help though
it would be nice to help but i think we
can only spectate
let's see what they're probably saying
yeah i'm curious
maybe we can close maybe we can close
doors i don't know i'm gonna find out
uh maybe only in the vr yeah so maybe
not maybe not
tiara
yeah i think we can only watch for now
see her die
that would be that'd be a really cool
feature though
i think that they should add that
want to watch them get [\h__\h] up i mean
f-word
i part it up
do it say the word girl say the words
say the words
i'm following gooda wait no that's inna
just kidding
i'm waiting for ina to get [\h__\h] up i
mean f-word
right in the middle of the um it's a big
handprint in green
yeah okay
okay
if i'm dying then i'll scream before i
go oh cool yeah
they've talked about uh letting us as
ghosts help someday in a future update
so that's kind of cool
i like that idea oh
i hope they're okay i kind of want to
watch them die
in the though so i can't be arrayed
because i did hear it
stomp around so it's not a race
it looks like a man a mare okay
what else do they have to do i wonder
i think they didn't lay down the journal
they should have laid down the journal
to let the ghost right
it should it's right here isn't it oh
it's gone it's gone we know here it is
here it is i laid it down in the
beginning
ah i should probably be uh upstairs
though they should have moved it
upstairs
uh yeah good point
[Music]
cause i don't think it's gonna write
down there yeah
yep it should it should maybe write
something but i don't know maybe it
doesn't want
[Music]
but maybe if i believe that there's also
ghost orbs then we can grow a bit more
out
yeah i have ghost orb and freezing
temperatures but
the only options i get are phantom mare
and you day
[Music]
instead
i only want to set it to what the others
said it took
what did you put kiara hey i didn't put
anything yet i'm trying to
find something that fits i think mayor
makes sense and what was the other one
phantom wait what does that say consider
drop your sanity but apparently my
salary was still very high
so um probably not
phantom i wonder
they should we can't talk to the other
girls but they should try the old job
the ouija board yeah yeah that might be
helpful
oh welcome back
all right what the heck okay
okay oh girls are actually good at this
game
oh girl you died
no no my sanity dropped oh wow though
child was right they were like oh it's
here
oh someone dropped kiara dropped
there she go did she crash
hello who's left
you know is that ina is that you
kiara good i hear you
hi where's kiara trapped in the closet
yeah should be back to you son of a
[\h__\h]
sorry i just keep saying it over and
over again i just love
love so i guess we should maybe
maybe chat because they seem to actually
know what they're talking about
it's the sanity um attacking thing like
the whole group or just one person
because like if it was like an average
between everyone then it started
attacking a lot more
after like guru's job right so
oh it's the group it's a whole group oh
okay okay well that makes sense
oh by the way you know some
uh that the the journal was in the
kitchen so we should have
eventually moved it upstairs so they
could write over there and also we
should have been looking for the ocean
boy oh yeah boy luigi board okay
did you say louise how do you pronounce
it we should have been looking crappy
yeah i heard that the word ouija was
copyrighted or something like that so
i got like nervous and i was like oh
ouija board so journal next time
we move it they didn't hear me say that
i wasn't pressing the button
hey can i buy a flashlight if you have
30 dollars
uh i think i have i think i have 10
bucks and some bus tokens and some
pocket lint so can anyone lend me like
maybe 20 bucks
if someone has extra money then you
don't have to you don't have to
i got 10 sorry don't worry don't worry
it's fine we're all broke
i'll just wander through the darkness
again that always works well for me we
already
we already have a ghost writing book
right or is that a different thing
that always appears in the truck i think
then i think i'll buy a tripod now good
idea talking without pressing the button
same same i keep forgetting okay
i bought the track the maximum of two
and then we already have one so
yeah okay i bought the tripod so we can
have the camera up higher and see more
things now
okay all right gotta select a job is it
my turn now
yeah i think so okay so which one did we
do before
just now
that was like a house do you guys know
no that was a normal house it was edge
we have two farmhouses and then one
normal house we have tanglewood street
ridgeview roadhouse and edgefield street
house
want to go to texas
okay we shouldn't go we shouldn't do
something too big though
we shouldn't do something too big
because we're never gonna finish it
let's go to texas
okay let's see recommended team size one
oh small three bedroom single floor
house with a basement the owner called
this morning
said it sounds like a dangerous ghost is
haunting the area this one sounds
dangerous so you'll have to be careful
with this one
yeah no [\h__\h] sherlock gather evidence
and leave as soon as you can
more info when you arrive location size
small okay
um let's see what else what else do we
have
two story six bedroom with a basement
possible ghost sighting this one sounds
dangerous
yeah wow you could have told you that
one gather evidence and leave
recommended items thermometer okay and
then the one that's
in seems like around ny two-story
four-bedroom with a basement the owner
called this morning
dangerous ghost is haunting the area
bring a thermometer
okay so i wonder team should be small
you guys want to do the one the
one-person one
because maybe we can actually accomplish
it
we're going to texas okay okay yeah
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
wait wait wait uh i have to add the
tripod oh yeah
okay done there you go also how do you
guys use the items that you buy
uh you have to add them in the equipment
list yeah okay
got it got it okay one sec i gotta do
that
the ghost responds to yee-haw maybe
well howdy howdy
yeah howdy ghosty
huh
oh yeah okay good we're good now okay
cool
there is no salt though there is no salt
but we might need it
um
[Music]
discover what type of ghost prevent the
ghost from hunting with the crucifix
anyone got a crucifix maybe we can find
one looks like this is going to be a
tough
richard brown only responds when people
are alone huh
oh yeah sorry i was talking and you guys
didn't hear me um
okay richard brown only responds when
people are alone come on
you should use its name to anger it and
get some paranormal activity
refer to your journal does anyone have a
crucifix
now no crucifixion uh oh well
i'll get the book
oh did someone take the emf thing with
jake
yeah i have this okay okay
[Music]
oh my god i got the salt look at the
salt well
there is salt this time baby wait is
there a limited amount of salt or do you
have like endless salt
good question that's a really good
question
let's not let's not let's not figure it
out
she's she's here in spirit
i i'm getting the is there really a way
sorry is there really a way to turn off
push to talk
uh might have to like the menu oh yeah
yeah
forget that maybe next time um let's see
three uses on the salt by the way guys
oh okay okay yeah
if you need more i just need to roll up
some gotcha and you'll have more so
with this a ghost event
i think with with how slow we are doing
these things i think this might be the
last game
yeah maybe well let's give it a shot
anyway
should i say the iconic lion hold on
i'll wait until we get inside of the
house
i bring the tripod later on hello
demons it's me
your boy you think that'll summon the
ghost
hello let's get some light popping off
in here hold on
ah that won't work i have a lighter oh
me too me too
i wonder how long it'll work uh what's
the name again
yeah let's oh it's richard brown
richard brown richard brown
what are some let's swim some richard
nicknames richie
richie oh my god you clipped to the door
scared me
[Music]
maybe he doesn't speak english guys como
estas
richard brown yeah what's up gouda
so i was in the kitchen i think richard
flipped a cup
okay cool yeah he flipped the cup at me
i don't think he's at the dinner table i
think he's hungry richard brown
guys we have some freaking tents
richard brown richard brown kitchen
he's definitely there he flipped the cup
at me richard brown
oh oh
okay should i use the salt i'm scared
get someone maybe i should use the salt
guys
is there lights here richard brown i'll
put some salt in the kitchen
that was me by the way that was me that
was me oh my god
the salt isn't working when i try to use
it hold on here you go
i got it hold here i'm gonna get the
tripod
that's making fun of him richard brown
i'm pressing f
all right hold on i have the book here
i'll put the book down
hold on there i put down the book let's
see if he talks
is this a picture of you richard brown
do you have a monocle
and a mustache god that scared the [\h__\h]
out of me the s word
s word out of me when i saw that
foreign
which direction should i put the camera
of course dining table okay
we have freezing temperatures
[Laughter]
richard brown
richard brown i turned
[Music]
richard brown would you like to be a
guest on the podcast
richard brown are you adult
tokodeska richard brown are you
shy
when's the last time you showered
richard brown is that a fuller
richard brown richard brown richard
brown richard brown richard brown
richard brown is starting to sound like
not a word so i'm gonna stop saying
maybe we can ask him some questions are
you here
richard brown richard brown
richard brown stinky spanish
richard brown can you hear me are you
ugly can you hear me brown i'm in the
truck i'm checking the camera
can you hear me
chad is saying we should turn off the
lights but i don't know how i feel about
that
yeah i don't know
and this was a it was a three on the emf
maybe we should turn off the lights
richard brown do you know how to spell
they really don't like it when we use
the name i guess so
oh i feel like [\h__\h] but i'm going to
leave
now okay girl has to be alone
hey girl i'm going to leave you alone in
there so he'll come out
kelly yeah i have to leave
he won't come out he won't come out
otherwise
what's the song for oh never mind i know
kissy [\h__\h] uh ricky
richie oh man we're gonna die
i think i think we really need to be
alone or someone needs to be alone
wait i want to find the lead can we find
the ouija board oh yeah that might be
fun
if we stick together he won't come after
us either so let's let's go
hey guys
where is everyone are you guys still in
the living room you guys still in the
living room right now
i'm in a bedroom okay cool maybe we can
hide in
a closet and let someone
ems four
oh huh
tony what are you doing back there wait
five
four
i'm back in the house to take some
photos
and i'm still not sure because the chat
was like 50 50 on whether or not it was
ghost orbs or if it was
breath
richard brown
yeah i think we really ought to just
leave someone in here
richard brown where are you richard
brown hello
he really doesn't like that
[Music]
richard brown how are you
i wonder if there are any candles in
here you
[Music]
hey i lit a candle
how'd you find that out
what wait that'll cause a fire for sure
it's either a wraith or a banshee i
don't know if you guys can see it but
oh how did you see that you were smart
girl oh my
god
is
it's moving i saw that yeah the book
moved
it flew off the table
did anybody get ems five
so he's here the highest
we haven't had any footsteps so it's
either a banshee or a race
please tell us are you here
richard brown please write something
maybe maybe let's just talk to him and
not use his name
maybe he doesn't like it when we use his
name okay please
write something
has anyone heard footsteps
i haven't yet please write a message
well it likes to be it likes us to be
alone right and the the banshee also
likes to be alone
it stalks people who are alone give us a
sign
give us a sign
i feel like it's a banshee because the
alone part
okay yeah probably give us a sign okay
what do you think is better
call you oh chad gives chat made a good
point i'm not talking texan
oh give us a sign howdy
howdy ricky give us a sign richard give
us a sign
richard is this the keys to your
automobile
i have obtained your keys richard what
are you doing
please scream
scream i don't think that's gonna work
hey howard eric howdy ricky
eva ricky
[Music]
a [\h__\h] all right let's [\h__\h] off let's
get the [\h__\h] out of here
let's get the [\h__\h] out of here there's a
bank there's the lights on
let's get out of here let's get out of
here the door's locked the door is
locked
no it's open
you saw it on the camera
i didn't hear any personally but
okay no footsteps
ina died and she died in front of me i
got it on camera
oh my god dude what dude what
oh ena it's the body oh no
oh oh no oh no
that's no good
i saw the ghost on the live camera by
the way it was really pretty
oh really what kind of ghosts what did
it look like
what the ghost looked like oh it looked
like
yeah you know
i don't i don't know so i'm not sure but
the chat was like oh
banshee or something like that
[Music]
hey guys ina dropped some stuff i have
the uv light but there are two other
things that i can't seem to pick up
i'll return it chat i'll return it to
eno when she's back
but she's not using it now is she so it
makes sense
i wonder if we can watch the replay on
the camera
what bro what's up
who's got the camera i want to see this
i gotta get a picture of this
yeah i'm curious who has the camera guys
a hand print
i only have the video camera look a hand
print yeah yeah we already know about
that
oh okay fine i'm just trying to be
helpful let's see
yes take a pic i can't i can't take a
pic only
i can only take a video and do you guys
want to guess so
i don't know let me what do you think it
is banshee uh
you said banshee right uh
[Music]
i'm thinking but i didn't hear any
screaming don't banshee scream
or am i just getting it interesting i
bet she would scream
i guess not a ghost banshee but uh so
when it
died did we hear footsteps because i i'm
pretty sure
uh i think i heard footsteps
i didn't hear anything update my journal
all right so what did we find let's see
evidence
oh emf level four right
i can't remember if i heard footsteps
now
does anybody else wanna what about the
emf
the band she would have needed emf fifo
as well no and we didn't get that
oh we didn't get we did not get emf5 but
we did get the radio
so is that spirit box
did he say something here box actually
i'm not sure maybe that was the other
how about fingerprints guys
did does the handprint count as
fingerprints
spirit box my chat
uh we did get we did get em at level
five so it must be a banshee
okay so we did get level five
fancy yes you looks like it yes i am the
florida bounty
all right let's get out of here me three
let's blow this popsicle stand rest in
peace ina though
bring do i have to bring back the items
yeah do we need to bring back
the tripod do i have to bring it back uh
i don't know i maybe
okay cool we don't need anything else to
say all right let's dip
let's blow this popsicle stand lens
all right so we did it i think
we did it we're not actually supposed to
sleep
why didn't we get any of the objectives
then
i witnessed a ghost event i too
witnessed one
we all did ina died in front of me
i watched it
yeah so i don't know wait wait girls
wait wait wait wait
aren't banshees only female and this
name is male
huh is that random does that matter in
the game i thought banshees were only
irish branches can be male maybe
i wonder
it's fine not okay maybe not in this
game okay so i think we can say banshee
does everyone have it in the journal
yup i updated it sounds good
okay good already
[Music]
wow
i forgot to film my journals
wait there's oh you know the bone why am
i level one and you guys are level two
because you you died
in the first game so early i guess uh
yeah i suppose that makes sense that's
fair
do you guys want to play one more quick
one
i can do one more you wanna do them yes
maybe if it's a fast one for me
one for one person okay well let me let
me see what i can buy
i still can't get a flashlight money
what should i thought maybe smudge
sticks i'll get the smudge sticks
i don't all right cool fine
it's a bubble gum dollars
i want a head mounted camera that sounds
fun
all right oh now we have new ones vlog
squad
let's see gather evidence as possible so
a ghost removal team can deal with it
afterwards
let's see hold on i want to look for a
small one
okay let's do this you don't really need
okay
how about tanglewood street house size
one person a small three bedroom single
floor house the basement
got an email from a friend he says there
is definitely some kind of paranormal
activity here
head there and gather as much evidence
as you can so a ghost removal team can
finish the job okay let's go
okay i'm ready spaghetti
i will get to level two
i am also ready spaghetti i'm already
probably never gonna level two i wanna
be level two
i'm gonna be level two what is this door
now i'm gonna go out here
[Music]
wait guys guys guys can we turn off push
to talk yes yeah
oh yeah we have to like leave
the lobby to get to the setting oh we
have to leave the fire call correctly
forget that forget that next time okie
dokie let's go
all right lads what do we got
patricia clyde
there's this look on your screen
oh my god oh please stop that oh stop
you guys were real
you guys are the real ghosts and demons
geez um also by the way
we can this this ghost responds to
everyone guys this ghost responds to
everyone
so you should be able to use this name
to anger it and get some activity make
sure to refer to your journal
all right um a photo of dirty water and
a sink i can take a picture of that that
seems
easy enough i'll do i'll do that
and then it's gonna attack us no matter
what you guys it's it's going to come
after us even if we're all together
so yeah just be ready
okay let's gather the materials spirit
box i'll be checking the emf
my salt and ice and i'll take them i
love the soul
[Music]
oh okay i thought that was
are we ready to go do you have a lighter
for the smudge stick i do i do
would you like it would you like me to
give it to whoever has the smudge sticks
uh no i think i think anyone might need
this
no that you i don't know how to use them
i don't know how to use them either but
we'll learn we'll learn i have maybe one
of us can
have the sticks and one of us will light
them i have the lighter so we can do
that then
all right let's move out
road busters move up doo doo doo doo doo
doo doo
doo doo doo doo
hi friends welcome to my crib welcome to
my
what was the name again of the ghost oh
patricia oh it's the same house give us
a sign
i'll see this time there's no bone what
was that boner for them
[Music]
i thought that was weird give us a sign
give us a sign
patricia clark give us a sign
i'm going to check the basement for the
ouija board
you mentioned it's here okay i found the
bone kiara
what it's in the kitchen
oh man there's another bomb
oh when you eat chicken wings you should
clean up your bones man
that's kind of you know
patricia clark oh that's right yeah
that's right the
dirty water in the sink i got it leave
it to me
i'm useful i'm useful i can do it
dirty water where's the sink i have it i
have the camera where's the sink though
all right we'll do
ah there was no water in the sink guess
i gotta find a bathroom
or maybe the water doesn't show up until
oh yeah good point good point girl let's
check it out
hello nice oh cool
she's got the bone ah but there's no
water it doesn't seem like there's water
in here
we got a bmf4 emf 4 in this
position oh yup where are you kiara is
that it
uh it's gone now it's gone
okay so the dirty water is created by
the ghost
take a photo anyway wait where were you
with the ear a mess what
i did it was i was exactly here
oh okay let me
hmm what's this what's gone now
i light some candles
all right give us the next amazon
bestseller book right here
right here
you guys are breathing no
where are you hey i hear guys something
there's something in my ear
huh it sounds like
is it my radio i don't know
maybe
i let some candles i'm gonna leave some
salt i hear something
that's my radio that's my spirit ah okay
oh oh
okay what is that is that always there
what is that
oh it's my salt ah okay i can't wait
i wonder where else i should put it
maybe
in front of the garage i'm gonna bring
the i'm gonna bring the camera into
tripod
brb i left i left
i left some salt
patricia clark patricia clark
please write something
give us a sign
give us a sign paddy clark
patty
patty they say turn off the lights for
spare box response so i'm gonna
turn off this light here okay
at least we have some candles
give us a sign now
ready for our spooky spirit seance
fingerprints everybody put fingerprints
in your jar i know
okay
give me that
okay everybody it said kill so everybody
put uh put
put this third box in your in your
journal please will do
got you is that the only evidence we
have
no fingerprints okay true
okay
i'll toss this we don't need it i can't
can somebody lend me a light so i can
figure out where the notepad is
all right i put down the notepad maybe
she'll write something
it's downstairs give us a sign
i think so in the basement give us
um hey guys the candle just went out
a candle just went out in front of me
there's not much activity so i think
it's okay
okay give us a sign
okay okay got it got it roger
give us a sign i i got i have activity
i think emf too only though
yes
hey guys maybe we should get the mm4 emf
ems
emi4
it's active the ghost is active the
candles drought
the candles are out use your flashlight
get us out of here
light the way like the way like you
usually do like the way
let's go out and skate away like the way
it's about the way
it's about it's about to hunt
oh
again is girl alone in the house
is
maybe it's okay i'm gonna go back
yeah i'm brave
i really want to see if we can get dirty
water in the sink maybe there's some
there
they're pretty rare that's a shame oh
[Music]
it's in the kitchen it's in the kitchen
guys
the
patricia clarke is this still patricia
clarke
yeah i think patricia clarke where are
you
patricia talk to me
patricia clark please write
write has something seen a ghost
orb no but i repositioned the camera to
the basement so maybe
where should i put the camera
it didn't see anything when i pointed it
to the kitchen
i re-lit the candles
wait did you stop the camera yeah i did
before
but in the kitchen it didn't really give
us a sign give
us a sign
give us a sign do you want to use the i
mean we already have spirit box evidence
we don't really need it
um unless you wanna
patty clark patty patty throw something
patty
give us a sign patty give us a sign
patty give us a sign
patricia thank you
something hey
not yet i had to turn it on
if the ghost walks by it it'll turn
it'll be dirty is what
chad said uh-oh
wow
maybe the water will be dirty
i gotta go get it i gotta go get that
water
i gotta go get that picture i gotta do
it though i gotta get the photo
i'm brave oh my oh my god the lights
okay so we're gonna go let's haley be
safe i'm gonna try
summon
monsieur
water's still crystal clear water is
crystal clear guys
patricia clark
all right
[Music]
okay
yeah put the camera down in the kitchen
maybe around point near the the sink
let's see what happens
uh
i'm gonna try something brave hold on
patricia clark i love you patricia
clarke
patricia clark patricia clark
patricia clark patricia
oh my god patricia clark
patricia clark give us a sign
give us a sign patricia patricia clark
patricia clark
give us a sign give us a sign
patricia please
us a sign like are you married
patricia clark do you have children what
are you wearing patricia clark
where do you come from hold on turn off
the sink
no don't
do you think like what's your favorite
food
patricia to the clark nothing what a
boring dog patricia
you're kind of lame maybe she's
maybe she's not in the kitchen oh
there's a hand print
on the garage door
on the garage yeah hemp hampered on the
garage door it's just
kind of kind of kind of stinky not gonna
lie
kind of lame
i'm in the garage now
i'm taking your car for a spin patricia
[Music]
give
patricia clark you a chicken
brother
[Laughter]
i will eat you
no one is
where's my body go across the screen
yeah we did kind of go in there and we
were like haha [\h__\h] chicken
did i really make it that far that's
nuts because we got spirit box we got
fingerprints and we got
ghost riding
i think someone said they rode killed no
no that was my spirit so what can it be
a spirit raid poltergeist
if they want to write down something
i took one for the team
is that patricia what is it
it's in the kitchen
yeah i wonder if she'll come out again
this went to the basement no way
a freezer
i kind of like this world though it's
fun and calming
okay
sorry that you all had to hear me scream
some
i don't really know what came over me i
don't often scream so i was surprised by
the sound of my own scream
oh i hear them
is
i guess my game is bugging or something
okay
it's a blessing are you sure your
eardrums probably are in a lot of pains
while we're holding
i wonder if patricia clark will come out
if i summon her as a ghost
patricia clark stop hurting my friends
she's gonna come out
hello i forgot your name that's a good
point patricia it's patricia claire
patricia
patricia right in the book put yourself
in everyone's checking
i don't know huh that we didn't see
the activity oh no dummy in the band
oh no
you know i am going to the band
i don't see any writing so i don't think
ghost writing is it i think the fact
that the ghost didn't write anything is
proof that it's not a spirit
oh yeah right maybe not
i don't know
just shut up
the ghost didn't write anything so it
can't be a spirit you be
you b you be
movie you you you'll be um
you'll be you can see the ghost oh
sometimes the lack of evidence is
evidence itself yeah i was thinking that
too
i don't like it it's the fact that it
didn't write anything it can't be
yes yes
you'll be you'll be on the table
everyone yeah you bees to the sky
knocking you pieces
what about the temperature there's no
temperature
there were no freezing temperatures so
hold on a minute
maybe so if there was a freezing
temperature
no freezing temperatures so maybe it's a
poltergeist
hello how old are you
are you here i don't know
book i feel like i picked it up but then
i don't know what happened
do you can you scroll your item in oh
yeah i think i see it in your hand
oh yeah sorry i saw it oh
oh there she is run guys run run run run
get out
get out of the house
what the [\h__\h] you know
oh no kiara
oh no
nina did the smart thing
was clipping through the wall kiara and
the ghost went straight for you
you were so close to getting out um
finally we're together all right
at least gur and ian are still alive but
we can probably rule out what this is
yeah i was gonna say i don't think it's
a spirit because it never wrote there
was no ghost writing
the ghost never actually wrote we also
didn't see ghost orbs
we didn't we also didn't have ghost orbs
though so with the evidence that we have
the only other thing that we could find
is ghost orbs or ghost writing
i think
we don't have the freezing and we don't
have the emf level right
right
okay but poultry guys throw things and
slam doors and this ghost didn't do any
of that
ah did you have the book so maybe it's
not a political
dice but it can't be a spirit because
nothing appeared in the
nothing appeared in the book yeah
but then maybe the book is just placed
wrong you know
the camera is placed wrong that could be
true
footsteps are not evidence frozen
uh oh
patricia clarke will you write in this
book please it can't be that hard just
pick up the pencil
slap it around throw it across the room
push me touch me do something it can't
be a ray that had footsteps okay
can't be a rave it had footsteps
put the book in the garage yeah maybe
huh i wish i could tell them
guys put the book somewhere else oh hi
hi
hi so it killed where is this ghost
it killed her here i'll put poltergeist
should i bring the thermometer back
oh well
raid has footsteps hey patricia
okay apparently the camera is in the
garage
camera is in the wrong spot to see orbs
nada hold on there
but i could do it
if there were to be ghost orders it
uh
once we get better at the game i'm sure
eventually we'll all be able to
guess the ghost immediately based on
what
oh my gosh
[Music]
where are you he left
is
where is everyone they're making fun of
me yeah i know it's hilarious
all right well i'm heading back there
oh what are you stop it you know you
know
[Laughter]
no we don't know who it will go for it's
just you know you don't know where it'll
pop
up so whoever there's oh
there's this like maybe the everyone in
the book
yeah we gotta go check the book okay
let's go
together okay and then if if there's a
hunt
hide in the closet let's follow the
girls again shall we
okay okay
ah what what the problem
oh
what's up friends big uh oh
what was that sounds like a microwave
are you hot hot pockets why are you
leaving
you know
go see glass girls does she listen to me
i wonder if
i say something let you react
what's up
danny
it got all sleepy
yeah i heard it too it was like a
microwave i think it is the mic oh it
was the microwave she's making her happy
focus now
let it be a piece i want hot pockets
oh oh oh boy
no
i threw it down here
yes scoot out more swearing she take the
look
okay put the line back again put the
light there
didn't the pen move i swear i threw the
book down
aye aye aye ah no oh
i like that we can see their eyeballs
when they get too close
it's kind of fun um book the nice touch
uh the book has glitched into the wall
oh and but no the book the book is kind
of nice i like feeling like i'm watching
over he's gone okay does anybody else
get out i picked it up warmly watching
warmly watching
if the ghost is moving things though
then that almost confirms poultry guys
right in the kitchen
it's like that way here
hello there's a salt footprint
apparently you have the uv light girl
you can check over here
uh oh they guide me guide me where are
you
right here right here in the in the
light oh no can i go into the garage
no it's a spirit
it's a spirit it's got to be a spirit
enough to be a
i'm thinking it's a poultry guys too
you think so but they what did they move
step on the fault
uh they moved the book they threw they
chucked the book they threw it
oh it's like a little when you like
sprinkle on the floor
it's like looks like the plastic but the
spirit walks on it at least
wait but can dead people also walk in
the salt and leave your foot
that's the question
[Music]
oh moshi moshi
yeah it could be that we just misplaced
the camera yeah so
that's why we didn't see any ghost
boards ghost orbs ghost boars
they should try to find that ouija board
yeah
oh moshimoshi again
it moves something did you see that you
see that did you see that
girl i can't wait what in the camera or
yes
also the book do you like how i placed
the book
where's the book it's right there you
see that white thing
it's right there oh i see i see oh
oh standing up right yeah i think it is
poultry guys it's moving a lot of stuff
and like the phone ringing
um i think so too
right guys here was nothing oh
you ready
ready yes i'm going for poltergeist what
about the gallery
yeah it's only on my screen right
welcome back i've got some jobs ready
how do we do
ah yes we did it yes poltergeist whoa
and i'm rich i can buy a flashlight
yay
we did it oh my goodness that's the
first thing i got right
yay we did it
we did it we did it we did it yeah we
did it oh
i died right at the door though right at
the door i was about to leave yeah
i watched it go right past eno that was
cool
you know your head clipped through the
wall and i thought it got you and you
died
i found it so quickly no i i
remembered it there was it was an open
door but i didn't even close the door
but then
it had its eyes on you i guess love is
an open door
indeed
[Music]
that was fun
[Laughter]
walking
all right i think uh two hours that's
all fasting is enough
that's quite enough yeah i'm done i'm
done so i'm tired
a little sleepy reaper watching my thing
i'm sleepy reaper i had fun yes that was
fun i keep forgetting to press v
okay we should we should go back to
discord
okay okay let's do that
what do we
a demon just kind of flew out of me in
that moment please excuse me
that was fun i have to say i expected it
to be much much more scary
but the chat says it because we were
uneasy it wasn't so scary i guess it
gets much scarier i mean it wasn't too
scary
i mean that wasn't the recipe level one
level two
maximum four players but we want ama to
be in there too
how about i play together with cali
right like i visit her at her house
oh nice idea we play just one play and
there's no other reason
i just wanted to so that amic enjoyed
the game there's no other reason why i
would want to do that
yeah let's do it let's do it yes ally
can be the mouse and you can be the
wiser it'll be perfect yeah it was
perfect yes yes yes
next time yeah i'm up for that
let's do it yay
that way that way me and kelly can
mentally support each other
when when we like skate in the darkness
yes
in the dark alone here
does anybody have any announcements for
the week
yeah my new song is on all streaming
platforms go check out
twitter and if not it will be it will be
there
it will be there soon for spotify but
itunes and whatever go check it out
please
thank you awesome i'm i'm collabing with
polka
senpai this week
but that's it that's all i have to say
okay
um well i still have to put up my
schedule so
oh yeah yeah i do too
soon i think tomorrow i'm instead of
bitching kitchen we're going to be [\h__\h]
and movers because i recently moved
so yeah on theme i like it
look forward to it everyone okay
all right everyone thanks for watching
thank you
yeah i left it
now it's just you and me
that's not what i meant to do it was
supposed to be a dramatic and uh
i don't know now it's just wait hold on
now it's just now it's just you
and me
oh i'm sleepy
[Music]
is
do me a favor
[Music]
here we [\h__\h]
is
[Music]
do i'll get close to your mind
all right
[Music]
peace
you