[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
there you go hi Chad
um
I think normally I'm like here
sorry I was trying to eat a sandwich as
fast as I could I have like two more
bites left
uh
uh self-made sandwich
yes with some cat hairs in it too
and why why do they always end up in
here hmm
I wash my hands like a million times
thank you guys for the membership gifts
yo oh
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
he kind of came
not an easy breathing day today
hmm
normal
[Music]
but thanks for the pinky sticker
thank you
no what causes it
hmm
oh
there was a lot of main Channel content
jump
um
[Music]
no it's not every time when we play tltk
um
oh well
I'll survive
I Will Survive
[Music]
we need inhaler as merchandise
that way I'll get my hands on one too
can we do that
I mean there's like this thing you stick
onto it right that you have to renew but
um like the inhaler itself
you don't replace right
yeah the shell we can make a cafe
hmm
you do
um
that's not very economically
pleasing to the ocean and I don't know
thus we shall make a reusable
inhaler okay
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
that was my last bite
ah
it just stops somewhere
it just
it's like there's a wall
I can't take full breaths
um
that's how I am today thanks for asking
um I am today feeling like I can't
breathe but I have this sometimes it's
okay
[Music]
um
I noticed today when I was scrolling for
my Twitter
like I saw a lot of like 3D
uh reveals going on from like artists
that I follow who have different
daughters outside of her life
I saw like Cali's Kelly's half sister
and then meals and buys half sister
you know everybody's having like free
DW's and then outfit reveals had an
outfit reveal it was really cool
and I think Corona December was supposed
to have an outfit where everybody got
delayed
because of
what technical issues or something like
that
yeah but just today it was like packed I
saw so much stuff going on on my Twitter
um
yeah
yeah but she said it was the second time
it was delayed what what not there's
there might not be only any anchors
there might be a Japan curse too after
all
uh
maybe I should use the moisturizer again
you think so
[Music]
um
My my what my German channel was in
vtuber News why it's not being used
why
what
which who's whose video produced
that's the reason why it was
what don't make fun of my dead
don't remind me of it I'm a victim I'm a
victim okay I am traumatized by my
German Channel
well we'll get back to it we'll get
better
um
I was I was roasted
yeah no but you I roasted you
the poor clip let's upload the clip soon
okay
let's let's start soon the problem is
every time you guys remind me
I'm just like lying in bed
[Laughter]
or just otherwise occupied
um
it was in good fun
ah what's the problem I mean
it's it's it has become a meme
and we've been cave people but why bring
it up so randomly did I
why
did somebody imagine something
um
okay wait
[\h__\h] I have no pen
let me write it down my phone
like chocolate
[Music]
MV
uh
uh program
[Music]
um and
moving and
okay that's
um
okay okay yeah
I see where that came from
um
uh
um okay just writing down things I
should or want to talk about today
[Music]
oh oh
leave me alone
[Music]
I'm gonna voice that and upload it to my
channel by the way
soon soon
uh
you like on organ but then I can't think
of anything like my brain will like
blank out
ah
okay
[Music]
um
well today might be kind of spoiler free
today stream
because I'm thinking of only doing uh
side stuff today
that was the idea
um and then tomorrow we go back to story
yeah the MMD I I think it's really like
nice to see so many creations with it
some some people tried for the first
time some talented people skilled people
do it for you know
the whatever's time
it's really nice
to see what you guys create
get the master what
I want to get the master sword naturally
is the muscle that's something that the
story
like actively gives to you when you do
the story
I don't want to like go out of my way to
get a like earlier than I should get it
okay okay
then I will just follow I will not go
out of my way to get that now no no no
no no no
but there's something else anyway I I
didn't
um play off screen since last time for
the first time
since this started
[Music]
um I have a Red Bull I think it's a new
flavor
apricot and strawberry
it's orange and apricot strawberry
sounds really good I normally don't like
Red Bull that much
but this sounds good doesn't it
I'm feeling a bit tired today and yeah
sounds disgusting what the [\h__\h] no it's
not disgusting how is it
that's
hmm
OS
let's try this I rarely drink Red Bull
but these bottles they're way smaller
than my preferred Monster bottles so you
know
because I would leave uh so much left
over if I drank monster I wish I said it
before I'll say it again I wish they
would make like small bottles hmm
hmm
oh
oh [\h__\h] that's yummy
wait that might be the yummiest Red Bull
I ever drank whoa
whoa
it does it just it doesn't taste like
um
like a a ash drink it tastes more like
juice that's a little bit carbonated
really good
really you're good oh I actually enjoy
drinking this I might I might get
addicted oh
okay
ah so no recap today because there's
nothing to recap I think
um
uh well that's fine too that's fine
drink responsibly well I think I think I
didn't play
I'm pretty sure I didn't play
did I
wouldn't it be so funny if I'm like if I
open my album and then I find so many
screenshots from playing without my
knowledge it's like you know drunk
playing but I wasn't really drunk I just
I just tried to push the memory out of
my head because I have a problem but I'm
pretty sure I did not
no I told you about this right
um
okay good
okay okay okay well then
well then you heard
Lip lip sounds right
should I put you guys elsewhere like
here
okay
continue
[Music]
oh yeah we we left off here
well that was loud
getting our memory
uh the last two memories I got were
quite something
white something too high you dizzy
oh
yeah I was thinking what we could do
today is oopsie
number one
I want to
continue and finish exploring the
underground cave that leads into the
Hyrule Castle
because I chickened out last time I did
that privately
and I found out thanks to domtendo that
it's not a big chickening situation
it's not that bad
um so that and
and and and then we could do uh also
some side quests and also we could do
one of the mazes Maybe
and we could do uh was I thinking
uh
passportation and maybe
[Music]
maybe
doing nah I think it's a little bit too
early for me to do the Colosseum I don't
want to do it I need some more practice
with lionels overground before doing the
ones on the ground
Sky Islands yeah Sky Islands I also have
recently not been exploring much
that could be something to do
and I guess yeah
complete the map I'm missing four
four Maps I guess yeah maybe oh maybe
oh yeah we probably should talk anyway
because we just I haven't returned to
the Lookout Landing since I finished all
four
whatever dungeons
[Music]
um
so they might want to talk to me
foreign
Village what's what's in learning
Village
look at Landing we'll encourage you to
do some wine store stuff okay well we
will not probably
not but I do want to hear what she says
to me
kill I mean
thank you ah
um
[Music]
right here
when I see her on the map
oh
what's what are they looking at
the castle
they're like I can't see so well
what are you trying to see hello oh wait
I never went inside you holy [\h__\h] what a
mess
it's like Ina's room
[Music]
ambitious it goes up here maybe she's
upstairs
hello
wait what is this a stone uh
Monument of a frog with her glasses on
that's so cute
she's got a loft I like it
but wait it goes even higher
than it oh
yeah
let's stay we're leading deep beneath
Harbor Castle has been discovered even
pretty Stella didn't know about it so it
seems safe to assume it's a secret
removed removed even from a legend
we have confirmed that emanates from
that location meaning something down
there must be causing it oh yeah okay
well this will be a lot of story that we
already know
and now Beyond adapt that there is no
team more qualified for such a task and
yet I can't escape this feeling of dread
I've decided to store this diary in four
volumes that way if a nose is someone
reads it they'll only have a quarter of
it
such ideas are the fruits of a genius as
for the first one damn she must be a
genius diary Diary
double demon diary oh she's a genius
I think I'll entrust it to who else
bought impa speaking of info she's had a
cute habit of hiding important items
underneath things ever since she was a
child I have a fond memory of when she
forgot about a hidden steamed bun
beneath a cushion and I sat on it
squashed flat Diaries are flat to begin
with but as they are more important than
a bun I hope she finds a better hiding
spot than a cushion
that's cute
is that a cushion
no
no I thought I could move it maybe
something's underneath
no that looks like a futon Maybe
um piled up I don't know
gotta find impossible yeah yeah maybe
sometime
oh oh is that supposed to be the thing I
use to fly
anyway she's not here she's upstairs
okay
where's privacy I know I know nice sword
you got there
I mean mine or or his
what what's this
he looks it looks kind of different
though
looks weird
what what
is a control panel for this house oh
okay oh oh nice
gives you some shade from the Sun
kind of falling apart but nice nice hi
hi
yeah linky I heard what happened the
major cold fronts that the Senate upon
the retail and the marbled Rock rose
that the girls couldn't get enough of
then there was the sludge contaminating
the Zara's water and finally the Gerudo
Menace by gyptus and the sand shroud
you faced some serious challenges and
you overcame all of them well done link
so the person resembling Princess Zelda
was behind the scenes for all of the
phenomena as you discovered this has to
be related to the upheaval somehow
and I have something important to share
as well
um
oh
uh oh
this is my plot guys sorry a little bit
of spoiler today right now
only now
later
oh [\h__\h]
Well it can't be the first Blood Moon
she saw right
oh
Zella
ah
consistent
so she can only appear during the blood
moon possibly
the evil one
KY did you see that
that was the princess wasn't it
I was going to share that I saw a figure
that looked an awful lot like Princess
Zelda at Hyrule Castle I wasn't sure at
first but now I am I thought she'd left
the castle entirely but she was inside
we have to hurry and rescue her the
soldiers and I can't reach Hyrule Castle
as it is now
you might be the only one who can do it
hmm
I'm sorry link I know I'm always
throwing you into dangerous situations
but you really are the only one up to
the task please come back in one piece
that applies to both you and the
printers got it
I mean yeah I think you could
if you really wanted to
you could probably send more than just
me up there I mean
there's ways we could build with the
zonai stuff we could build a couple of
whatever airplanes
or we could shoot everybody up on on the
lookout Landing Tower and give everyone
a paraglider which would be very cost
efficient I think
but no no none of this is Possible only
I can do it as I am the only hero
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh wait did I already share everything
with this guy what the music
[Music]
it's very interesting
how it changed
[Music]
I like it
um was it supposed to share it with you
here or
um
[Music]
did I even find any new ones I don't
remember anyway
okay he's elsewhere right
yeah I think I remember that but
uh so the first thing
that we'll be doing since we're here
uh do I have
ah
the first thing we'll be doing is going
to the cave
um
I want to have a heart
and heal me while you're at it please
thank you
let's drink some more Red Bull
clean me cleanse me
cleanse me more Mommy
[Music]
um
that's a lot of Hearts how many is that
can you guys even count it
and I think I already talked to this guy
but uh that side quest is basically just
you know
uh him saying hey can you help us with
those like
quests where we fight together
in various places and that happens kind
of naturally anyway so um
or you guys
damn
so I went pretty far
[Music]
on my own privacy dudes regrow
that's very nice
[Music]
oh
rock salt and Amber okay yeah I I
realized
uh I guess I didn't
wait is that where I came from no ah and
the mobs respond to I guess I did not
check out
uh everything
that I oh wait like for example this
what the [\h__\h] that doesn't regrow right
yeah I missed some sections
like one important section the rest
not so important
and then I want to go further inside
hello
why do I have so many stupid wooden
sticks what the [\h__\h] I think we'll get
plenty of weapons in here though
um
also why oh I have the the shield with
the
with the mirror which I don't think will
be of any use to us anywhere else don't
you think
you spend hours yeah yeah it's it's a
huge
place a huge maze
um
let's call you know about
and get them to help us here
just what is this wait
have I been here before
because it's empty
am I supposed to
warp up here
what was this
is
or is it just
hmm
yeah but it's like it's we're not even
we're not even inside the castle yet
no I'll just uh
I'll just move on forward the actual
look up what's up what's playing
[Music]
that's where it came from yeah and then
here
I can't see anything can you guys see
something
I already looked
huh
it's kind of like
hard to see anything at all really
I don't know
oh bombs
So Yesterday guys I uh I helped
one of my friends moved Apartments yeah
I mean we didn't do Furniture we only
did boxes so it wasn't so bad
it wasn't so bad you would think but
um there was no elevator
at least in the OG apartment
there was no elevator which was the path
that I want to go
and so it was several floors up and down
several times
that was that was the rough part
got some cardio in yeah my legs
oh I was I was sweating it was a pretty
hot day too
yeah and
um even though we were basically two
girls
and two dudes and even they know we
girls we're both like pretty like small
girls
[\h__\h] hell
uh
[Music]
both of us were like pretty petite
and oh I think if anything the other
girl might even be
kind of stronger than me
[\h__\h]
let me get a stone oh do I have one or
this one
yeah
but I still I didn't even let you know
when the others were like oh so maybe
she should take a break maybe we should
take a break or uh like in between or
even in the beginning as well and they
were like oh maybe we should start in
like 30 minutes or so I would always be
like no no let's go let's go
let's start let's get going we gotta we
gotta do stuff we gotta be efficient
we're gonna be fast you know
even though I was also you know weak and
exhausted I was pushing
[Music]
um
is that your Shield yeah but [\h__\h] it I
don't want it anyway
uh
so this path I I figured I actually
completely ignored even though I I
acknowledged it but I ignored it as well
and I guess we could fight this thing
how many boxes were you actually moving
oh it was like one full
like smaller truckload
it must have been at least like 40 50
boxes
um
maybe more like 50 60.
yeah up and down up and down up and down
up and down uh-huh
I have never fought this type of enemy
before
but it shouldn't be too bad
um
50 times the stairs actually I'm really
impressed thank you I mean we were four
people but
um so the girl the other girl sometimes
like at some point she would just stay
up at the very top floor and then bring
all the boxes from the top floor to one
floor lower uh and and meanwhile
we were like uh doing stuff at the
bottom bringing it to the car and all
that
uh and then we would go up to the one
lowered floor which already helped
though yeah
having it one floor lower
we were like yeah separating I guess
um not quite like a relay not quite
um I still had to go up uh
like free floors
several times up and down down was not
the problem although it was difficult
with boxes like I had to look carefully
at each step
but up up oh
that was rough
uh
what am I doing what am I thinking of
doing
what am I think I'm doing
what was I gonna do
who knows who knows who really knows
I don't know
what was I gonna do
wake up
um maybe I was gonna make myself another
weapon
I think that would be good anyway
because a lot of my weapons are unfused
I like using
oh
Ah that's my one on only Silver Buckle
blend horn thingy
13 24. that's those are this one
I should
keeping the really strong materials for
another time uh
sorry confusion
confused see this kind of makes sense
visually I think
lots of users do something I want it to
be
pleasing too you know I'll go for this
one that just it just makes so much
sense
see
it doesn't even look like we've used
something
um
then this one oops it why did I drop it
Royal Broad Sword so that's a two-handed
weapon
um
[Music]
I don't want to go too strong but what
the [\h__\h] is this I have so many
nah oh this must break yeah really
easily 40 how easy does it break because
I have 28 of them
the [\h__\h]
like immediately two hits one hit break
maybe better for arrows then
because it's how annoying how annoying
would that be to like constantly
switch uh to like or like refuse in the
battle you can't really do that
it's like a hammer a cute it's a hammer
those are higher
[Applause]
I'm sorry I'm nervous
what you gonna do
what is he gonna do
[Music]
15 hearts
should have warned me 15 I never
expected 15 hearts
now I can redo all those stupid weapons
what um okay okay wait
a moment wait a second
hold
um hold
um it's old
drop them all
feels
the Eightfold Blade with the horn
this one
this
what on Earth happened
okay now it's a small Hammer but
whatever what happened
I I I oh my honor oh yeah what the [\h__\h]
I could wear this and this I think
that's currently my strongest armor in
terms of like upgraded how upgraded it
is
[Music]
and now instead of like aiming for oh
aiming for the
eye
so slowly and stupidly I'm gonna
immediately try to do the the swing the
twirl
um
I want to upgrade more yeah yeah huh
oh wait and I need a 200
. okay
what okay I survived way more now
ah okay
how about
excuse me
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh damn it I don't want to eat that
normal food
I don't wanna get rid of my
attack up okay run
[Music]
um
where are I is
the eye will go for the eye right
oh ah what the [\h__\h] is that what is he
doing is that is he asking me to attack
him or
okay there we go
foreign
what is he doing
[\h__\h] missed
there we go
that's it
your death is down
it
hey
that's the first time I fight with this
one oh okay it looks like a meat
um peace
way to go thank you he ain't so tough
yeah I know he's not I know
let's get rid of this and why do I have
this in my inventory we do not know
okay help me
I was gonna say help me clean up this
mess
I love the horns is the fuse Adam oh
hell yeah I'll be using it for sure for
sure
fun even though it was exhausting but I
I was definitely not being lazy you know
my the friend that was moving or
generally our friend Circle they also
always helped me
um when I moved
like last Sunday helped me pack and so
on so you know they they helped me so it
was about time I helped them back most
of the time I I have to say like oh I'm
busy have a stream already planned this
and that
and yeah they understand but
it's nice that I can finally help too
even though you know I prefer to help in
other ways and physically
like doing an activity that really
exhausts me yeah
um but yeah it was fun too though
we had nice talks
me and my friends I had a good time make
sure I get everything here sometimes
they have sometimes these drop ores too
you know
the [\h__\h] is with the ground here
I don't wear those new lives it was
definitely a workout yesterday yeah
definitely
um
and then
yeah we did the moving then we went to
get some ice cream can you probably not
yeah
and we ate some ice cream the ice cream
was okay
[Music]
is that just a second level
of does it need more bumps
what flavor I had some like
amarena's flavor but it was kind of
lacking hey what's happening
[Music]
why it's supposed to break right
how many do you need
and there we go
the fact that it doesn't even even give
signs of um cracking or so
would almost make me give up and be like
oh I guess this doesn't this just does
not break okay fine
we're making these platforms
wait
[Applause]
[Music]
come on come on
what a man
go
a little [\h__\h]
ah what
like pushes everything no I want to
change the weapon
my God
this battle is chilling
what the [\h__\h]
so what I really came here for oh
is in that other chest
because I only found the pants
turns out there's a helmet
and some other stuff too later on
and we will find it all
we will we will
[Music]
you never found the helmet
but this place is so obvious
I mean I say that and I also ignored it
the first time but
think I mean I I saw it and I was like
maybe I'll go there another time and
I'll go elsewhere first I don't know
yeah it's a very defensive armor right
[Music]
um
so that should be good if I upgrade it
completely
it should be behind a black work shooter
wall
I already mind this I mean if I need
more luminous Stone you know where to go
yeah I've been here I've been here
nice bombs
[Music]
good food okay laughter
um
all right
hi I already loaded this place right
oh
but this door is closed can I open it
uh
huh how do you
I didn't get in here did that yeah get
in here why are you still alive
where's the head
wait why is this one still alive
[Music]
go under
hmm is that what the other uh armor
pieces
[Music]
here's uh
our chest
[Music]
is there a hole behind this part of the
stone hello you know
so annoying when they don't come over
how far do I have to go for him to he's
not moving at all
whistle you can't whistle to them
can you
can't
unable
so triggering
no there was nothing here either
oh well hopefully that's not where the
important armor piece is
that wearing this
just tell me no
um
that's where it is
[\h__\h]
how do I get there
why must it be there
with Cena
foreign
[Music]
ah
in here
wait wait I don't know maybe the Sun
okay
[Laughter]
oh
Goods that I have you guys
you had to look it up
is some of this
some of these like places they look
insignificant but then you know they
have stuff like this
damn
foreign
I guess we gotta go back what
what what what
triggering very triggering
uh and inspecting
our friends new place we went to eat
ramen we checked out a new Ramen place
but the new Ramen place um
wait did I want to go here no no the new
Ramen place was hmm
not
so good definitely had a lot of better
Ramen before
it was very mid yeah
didn't even have tonkots oh at the
[\h__\h] Uber driver I I got us an Uber I
hired an Uber for us
yeah oh [\h__\h] no what
how do I get back
I didn't get back
ah
I mean no not that bad I mean how do I
get back to where I came from
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
here okay okay
yeah what was I saying oh I want this
one but not this one no wait no never
mind do I want it
um
[Music]
I called The Uber driver
and uh it said I saw it on the map too
he was one minute away
immediately after I called him
and he was driving towards us
on like a bigger Street
and then
is it the GPS I saw he was supposed to
uh
what's the word uh
I don't know these terms
it was supposed to turn
on this link
already from like where he started
driving
relatively like really close
um Street
yeah
and then he doesn't and I'm like okay
maybe he thinks it's better to turn at
the next street even though he's driving
further away from us
and then he drives
uh he skipped like he passes another two
like side streets
in the meantime the one minute goes up
to two minutes
but I'm I'm still like okay I mean
whatever
weird but he must have his reasons
then he doesn't turn on that one either
though you know I don't know if you guys
use Uber but it shows you what the
driver's closest route would be and I'm
pretty sure that that is also shown to
the Uber driver how they should drive to
reach
the
okyaksama
scenic route no I doubt it
yeah so he skips the second turn that
the system offers him thus now you know
he already passed us the street where we
were
thus now being even further okay you you
annoy me
now being even further away from us
going up to like five minutes
and then he just keeps on driving away
and away and away and the one minute in
the end was up to eight minutes
driving away from us
yeah and he skipped three side streets
where he could uh go to us then there
was one last option where we thought my
friends were watching too who all have a
license except for me but they've also
were like why doesn't he
yeah what's that
so the last hope that we had is that he
would like turn at this like yeah very
obvious Last Chance turn
and he doesn't so I was like so pissed
off I'm like this
[\h__\h] I get very angry and I I canceled
um
I canceled the
recruit the drive you know with the
reasoning that he's not getting any
closer to me purposefully
and I gave him the benefit of the doubt
that he did not really like that he
accidentally accepted the request and
didn't see it
I don't know I I I gave him the benefits
of Doubt but I don't really believe it
um
anyway we're making a fire so I can fly
up
and then I call another one and I'm like
hoping that he doesn't take it
normally when I do this
the previous driver does not take the
ride anymore normally
of course this one time
he did
laughs
I called for a ride and immediately
he takes it is that isn't that where we
came from
this is where we're gonna go
huh
yeah awkward very awkward and so I
thought okay okay I mean if he took it a
second time then there's no way that he
took it by an accident now he must be
very aware of what he is doing where is
where does it continue
okay
am I missing something I feel like I I I
am confused should I ascend
this time for sure yeah I thought this
time for sure
that's the end
wait how did I get into the castle
before where
um
maybe here
no no
ah what oh that looks like it continues
there
hi
okay
ah [\h__\h] hell you guys are always in
the way
yeah okay that's where I wanted to go
Coco the shop yes yes yes yes
um
so driver this time I thought you know
this was like he accepted it like a
minute after I canceled it you know so
he didn't move that much
yet from where he was when I canceled on
him where he was already really fired up
I thought okay well now he if he accepts
this now he better go towards us now
still doesn't
still drives like further away
yeah bye
and so this time I I write to him
because I'm like if you don't want to uh
sugar me why are you accepting my
request
this I write to him asking
um
why are you driving further away
question mark question my question mark
uh what else should I write I think
um
I don't know I wrote something else but
yeah basically questioning why he's
doing this I don't get it I'm confused
goodbye
yeah bye
I've been on to become a Kiara and in
that moment no
I think I do
and he has he ends with like an
automated answer which I understand
because I mean he's driving he just says
uh okay understood or something like
that
turn around
like three minutes even though like
saying that he will only need three
minutes even though the system was
showing he needs eight minutes or so
for him you know what I mean
I mean suddenly he turns around
and drives towards me
then
finally arrives
and I sit in the front seat because my
free friend sits in the back because I
ordered the Uber and I wanted to ask him
something I was so pissed off before I
answered though and then my friends were
laughing about it because I was cursing
so much and and and then you know I I go
in and of course kiwawa
when he wow actually gets
to be in the position of saying
something suddenly kiwawa turns into
small rabbits
oh
okay excuse me sir
yeah so that was nice even though I
didn't want to be nice
oh this is where I wanted to go yeah
this is where it chickened out before
it doesn't look too scary
what happened when you it looked like
you were just driving away from us
and
guess what he says hmm
that's what he says
what his excuse was
he says he was still driving another
passenger
to drop him off
set oh that's interesting thinking in my
head that's a lie because Uber shows you
when uh your driver is still dropping
someone off it's shows you
it literally shows you and it shows you
where they drop him off
and how much longer it will take it it's
different it's not it doesn't just you
know ignore it so I tell him that and
the only thing he says
it's like oh is that so hmm
and I'm just smiling why I'm just
smiling like really uh in in a pissed
off way and my friend starts snickering
in the back
because they probably they probably were
thinking yeah she didn't have the
courage to really say anything after all
and yeah yeah I I
clear that I know he's bullshitting me
um
but I didn't you know
it didn't really angrily say yo this is
not cool
we waited so long
the socks you suck you know none of that
I gave him one star list
[Applause]
I gave him only one star less even
though I wanted to give him zero Stars
that's like why you might I told him I
drive a lot of uber and you know
normally it shows
when you have another customer
and he had no no explanation for that
he couldn't
[Music]
if it was true
he could have attempted to say well
um
he's not only an Uber driver he's also a
normal taxi driver
and that if he does like you know in a
different system basically so that
doesn't show in the Uber system
but if that were the case I feel like he
would
tell me that and also it's just overall
weird like uh
I don't know
no no he can admit it like here uh the
Uber drivers they also are taxi drivers
often and it's not like illegal or
anything they just double as that yeah
yeah it's it's fine here they even have
like the official taxi sign on top of
there
um cars because every Uber driver had to
uh at first it was like normal Uber
drivers and taxi drivers and the taxi
drivers got really pissed off here
um because the Uber drivers are making
easy money and taking over you know of
course they like start you know
complaining so then all the Uber drivers
were forced to take a test and like 50
of them failed it
of like I don't know I guess if they
know what they're doing
and then everybody who did not fail they
got a taxi plaque plaque
and are allowed to continue and then at
the same time I guess they can also do
like normal attack normal taxi like
rides too oh no no I don't think so like
they would have to like actually work
for those taxi companies but then the
original taxi drivers now can all also
double as Uber drivers as well
um
so I see a lot of them are like doing
both is the Soldier's bone good
do I have one already
watch me watch me
um
[Music]
nipples are better okay
wait is this like some kind of riddle or
something
is this a clock maybe clock
I saw a video today
uh of uh someone
clipped me hitting the gritty
I can't me
and and all the comments were like
so funny to me but I didn't know what
was going on like what's happening in
the comments
did you guys see that clip
the hitting the gritty clip
huh
nothing happening this is so weird that
there is free next to each other do we
have to clean this one with water maybe
what happens if I splash some water at
him
I also happened to have some kind of uh
super sunshine Mario thing happening you
know
is that is that an opening
hard to see
maybe not
what what do you think wait
I wanna I wanna quote them
I wanna let me let me quote them
there it is
they all were like typing fire emojis
and then like bro she hitting the gritty
and
she Wiggly hitting the greedy yo she's
hitting it yo
oh my God she's literally hitting the
gritty and she would never hit the
gritty
she just hit the [\h__\h] Mexican
now she needs to hit the whoa and that
will be perfect
cracked up orange girl busting it down
Idol style she's getting sturdy she's
winning the gradient then she hit the
gradient
boy hell nah she hitting that cartoon
character gritty uh skull Emoji skull
emoji
oh she can never
she's hitting something LOL
she must hit the well next
the chicken with the way hit the goodie
she do be hitting that gritty though oh
no the gritty it's a parade inside kfpv
Emoji explosion Emoji explosion Emoji
she
hit a million different emojis
oh hold on
hold up that's why shimayoshi no [\h__\h]
way did she actually hit the gritty it's
the chicken Ah that's the girdle ain't
no way
hahaha
[Music]
this comment section we making it out of
the usual room with this one fire fire
fire bro she hitting the granny
she'll never hit the gritty spit cereal
if you know someone that is hitting the
gritty that shouldn't we're here to help
I say right foot creep oh walking with
that Phoenix fire fire
[Laughter]
without the kfp with this one fire fire
fire
so funny
do you know those videos where
celebrities are like reading comments
that roast them and it's just so funny
and I want to do something like that but
what is this comment section it's like
something I just don't understand it
seems like there's a system Behind these
comments there's like a reason there's a
pattern you know I just do not
understand
oh
yeah
it's just so funny though thank you for
the entertainment
I had a good time reading for those
Boomer trying to understand Zoomers no
more
I am
something in between
you can't just assume
don't assume my generation
[Laughter]
Tick Tock thing or I can imagine
yeah yeah yeah
where are we
okay wait
[Music]
um
blood moon oh hell no
ah [\h__\h] I broke the box there was a box
here what's up here
maybe the Box will respond to
it's called being a millennial oh God
this is so scary yeah that's why I
didn't want to go here and now it's even
scary with the blood moon
[Music]
it's not scary
it's really scary
the music and everything yeah I know but
cooking during blood I should be cooking
anyway look for real for real
[Music]
how [\h__\h] hell what the [\h__\h]
where are all my weapons
can use this one I need to crack more
weapons
[Music]
so this this room I haven't entered yet
anyway
did
ah
[Music]
um
I love it when they bounce on the rest
it trolled yeah
okay yeah anyway uh
what was I talking about before talking
about the hitting degree Club
rather rupees man
[\h__\h]
that's the first time in a long time
that I ordered an Uber
and that [\h__\h] happens
what is this past
ah outside
is that a star thingy star piece
[Music]
I don't need to go outside
hey that was a shooting star
um
Uber we're done
drove
to the ramen place but man I felt like
my friends snickering in the back I felt
like
[Music]
the disrespect
bear disrespecting me
man I'm laughing at me well I'm trying
to scold the driver but I'm just failing
at it
so this is the inside of Hira Castle
it's practically amazing
is it a link right sorry about that I
didn't see you there I'm no Beetle no
beetle
there's still a bunch of valuable
treasure and weapons inside the castle
so they asked me to guard the place from
thieves but I'm a little lost but don't
you worry about me go right ahead I mean
you are from the castle after all so
yeah
this is so sauce Passage
yeah you heard right
what's what's Bobby's cup
all of them
oh
ten arrows baby
sorry when yeah I don't care I mean if I
need more I mean well I don't know what
do you even need those for I saw
a video
where someone's like really oh wait a
second I can't move them I thought it
was a dungeon
um where where
um
someone was trying like experimenting
and uh
fuse the star piece star fragment
with a weapon
and avros Etc but it's even more useless
than
like the
then which ones these things that's the
fruits you would think that such a
valuable item would have at least some
kind of use
in battle two but no
it really doesn't
so useless
oh
a recipe I think we have maybe cooked
that before I'm aware of that recipe
wow upgrading the green tuna goblets oh
okay so that's their only use so I'm not
really like motivated to get them at any
year
uh time when I see one immediately oh
hey there I see I'm not the only one who
thought it was worth to track the track
to come here you must really appreciate
good cooking if you're willing to see I
do I appreciate good cooking if you're
willing to sneak into the Hiro Castle
dining hall this place is loaded with
recipes I couldn't have dreamed up
myself it's also inspiring I came on
this way to find a special recipe so I
can treat everyone back at Lookout
Landing nothing left to Spirits like
delicious food
is there more
he says there's many recipes
where are they
what am I doing
ah wait let me make some weapons mm-hmm
animation weapons
how many do we make one two three four
five six seven eight
eight weapons
one
two three
four
five
six
seven oh five yeah six couldn't even
happen six what am I talking about
okay
um
double handed one
this one sheesh
the halberg
um
that looks so stupid
uh Claymore climber are these this is
this one double-handed I think so yeah
okay broad horn
but that sounds like platoon in German
that's uh grilled chicken
sounds exactly the same don't you think
yummy
okay got a lot of weapons now even
Elemental ones
um
make yourself useful
or just a ball
[Music]
oh
I confused the wooden box
is also a night spell a soldier's butt
Soldier Boy
Crank That Soulja Boy
true very true very true
uh
did you guys see it
um
two Korean fans they made a fan made
music video animated
uh for that
boom boom boom boom boom
that song could go well as a remix with
Soulja Boy
um but
yeah it's so good it turned out so good
I was watching you know all the updates
with how far that uh the artist got with
the animation
which way
and now they finished it and I retweeted
it they uploaded it on YouTube too
and I asked if I can use it
and upload a video
quick song because we haven't done ah
here we go we haven't done a song cover
in a long time actually
um
and thus I asked
uh a mixer you know not my usual mixer
because my usual mixer I think it's kind
of busy
currently
so I'm asking a different mixer than
usual which should be exciting and it's
just it's a pretty oh it's pretty simple
song
pretty simple song
I like all these version too yeah
football keys and Mickeys
that's a pretty simple song and it's
pretty short only two minutes
so I'm hoping wait
let's not go outside
not good right we should go where does
it continue
hey I'm confused
now it's turning into amazing
Mika was my favorite that one features
you too
did it I may have seen it
but yeah anyway so expect a little song
cover coming up if you haven't done one
in a while I was going to
do something with a certain someone you
know collaboration
but it's been taking some time like
communicating everything and we haven't
even like begun to
properly
get into it so
um
I thought okay if I have this
opportunity to like quickly release this
because it's already there then I might
as well use it right
so I've been here
and I I've been having this song in my
head it's very addicting right the flute
is so addicting
it's actually a fun song
fun song
very catchy
[Music]
have I seen everything already
in here I feel like no I feel like I'm
missing something should I go outside
it sounds kind of dangerous
more or less
and this is a dead end
oh that might be a main story
progression really if I go up
really
hmm
like I was already kind of hesitant to
come in here anyway when I came here the
first time because I was like
um shouldn't I come here later in the
story this feels like a place where you
should come later in the story when
you're when it's like irrelevant
but I mean they do make it accessible so
I guess you can come here anytime you
want
have you checked the lockup what does
that mean
um
I came from here I send it up there
then I checked out this place which I
think is complete
um
I'll walk around a little bit outside
maybe we'll find uh ah right
maybe we'll find
[Music]
um
maybe we'll find a cool Kodak
you could go to the Castle's boat dock
oh well with the danger of not being
able to get inside anymore
we'll just explore a little bit outside
and then move on to the next thing I
found the most important things which is
a full set of armor
I am thus satisfied
but I know of another armor set that's
in here
and I don't know where it is the the um
was it like private guard
private guard something like that
upset
or at least a part of it
Royal Guard yeah how do you get that one
[Music]
what
oh ah I'm in the first Gatehouse okay
let's cook a little bit
because my foods are
oh yeah
I need actual like normal food
um
but that's sharp let me cook yeah that
story progression okay okay
um
I made attack power would be fine too
ah [\h__\h] I can't breathe hmm
defense
uh why don't we cook it with
how do you open the recipes again
ah from here
I wish you could open it for me here
like from I chose an ingredient and then
I look at all the
oh wait you can
wait let's see
I can make rice balls with this one too
do I have rice left
wait and okay I have plenty of rice then
let's make some rice balls
or something like that
okay nice
only for
two minutes
cooking
[Music]
if you let you out all the hold all the
ingredients but it doesn't
I'm having fun yeah it's t-o-t-k weekend
let's go let's go let's go
I went
no
fish pie wow
wow
I made that before
salt Butter Fish and wheat
salt Butter Fish and wheat that was
wheat right not rice obviously
wait I could have just but I wanted I
could have just selected it why didn't
I know I know I can it's just been a
while
it's been a little while
there you go
oh
I made it by accident really nah I would
have been more excited about it
wait did I just
choose a stamina one
[Music]
ah
that's kind of weird like you should be
able to make for example those rice
balls with any fish but you have to the
way you do it from scratch if you want
to do it with a different fish that is
different from the ones before even
though they all like work the same way
good oh hell yeah it's incredible
[Music]
um
I love it
I absolutely love it
what about grab
okay
oh meat pie
[Music]
crunchy fried rice
crunchy Mama Looney
let's make this one because it uses less
ingredients
my game of the year hmm
possibly yeah
wait what else have I enjoyed in this
year so far
yeah I miss my Maloney art I really do
crawling Thief simulator I didn't enjoy
dance yeah but I wouldn't say it's a
game of the year
Fire Emblem
wouldn't choose Dallas game of the year
either okay not so much competition
Holland Miami was fun but I also would
not choose that as a
game of the year
um
yeah so currently totk does really not
have much
and
uh
competition should we be able to make
this without the butter sometimes you
can make certain dishes without a
certain ingredient
let's give it a try
no no no
okay
I need more weed I want to make the beds
again
[Music]
Diablo oh let me tell you about Diablo
it's actually really difficult I'm not
sure if the group that I have put
together
we'll be able to do a lot of collabs
um I've been trying to figure out a time
that works for us
and
yeah it's like actually four different
time zones but Kyla doesn't count
because she says she'll do any time it's
no problem for her
um yeah so crony and me and um uh Cali
we live in such completely different and
Far Away places
that it's just
uh
rough rough rough very rough
and Maybe for One stream that works on I
honestly should just make two different
groups
like uh an A Time Zone focused group
where maybe I can mix in and
Asian time zone mixed group with ID and
Cali and Me Maybe Two Connie Kylie is
writing I was just talking about you
Kelly I was thinking maybe it's better
to do time zone focus groups like two
different groups
speak of the reaper oh this looks so
yummy and I hate mushrooms
I make time for the other with the
homies thank you but no it's just it's
just you know it makes it like
unnecessarily complicated and I ah I
feel bad I feel like you know there's I
feel like there's plenty of people who
would play it so it would probably be
possible to make two groups
um
I really recommend you uh doing even
solo streams on it though I think you
would like it I think you would like it
a lot
it's it's dark and it's fun and it has
skeletons
yeah the time zone juggling I was
difficult
but I mean we could rotate that
every time this group plays together
um it's a different time and each time
it would be the morning for a different
member so everybody everybody gets a
turn on having to play at like 8 A.M in
the morning
so that is fair
um
currently it looks like the first one
will be crony
to suffer the fate of having to stream
in the morning
and then yeah I'm assume if if that's
the case I will also yeah it's a fair
trade I will do it too because like
we're literally like
when it's like the middle of the day for
me it's night time for Cali it's morning
for crony
and then if we switch it and it's
evening for me then it's morning for
Cali and it's uh
like middle of the day for crony if it's
morning for me then it's
evening for konini
and more uh normal middle of the day for
Cali confusing but you know so it's like
yeah we should rotate shifts
um
but that seems like
a lot of suffering I don't know maybe
maybe it's possible to do two groups I
don't know
I don't know
omelette my head me too me too
it's time for one of the better ones as
far as making sure everyone is awake at
least
hmm
yeah
yeah this time's not right now would be
morning for an a
and pretty late at night for or like
late in the evening very late in the
evening
for Japan
yum
whoa
whoa sheesh
this food stuff is amazing
wow what a defense boost if we ever need
that that will be really good for it um
[Music]
pumpkin Is My Jam in this game yeah but
unfortunately it's
um a resource that it's not so easy to
obtain right Rush room
that should be good too
Diablo floor yeah I have a lot of
uh
collaborations currently being cooked up
for next week a lot of collabos
um even outside
a tool
two outside Hollow live collabs
um
two yo I never use this I'll just make
some food even out of it even though I
don't care about the effect that it has
mm-hmm
oh yeah
I saw that you can like clean your
weapons yeah yeah I saw that I saw that
anyway let's go to the next destination
as I feel like
um I'm pretty satisfied with
what we've done in the castle maybe I'll
run around a little bit more to see if I
find another quarter Corso
but then we'll move on
[Music]
okay
uh where could there be a number called
I need more corn dogs I don't want all
of them but
I'm so bad at finding them
there probably is one of the very tip
don't you think I don't think I checked
yet
I wonder if I can get it
on the wall
which wall there's many walls
Cali just said Hi and then disappeared
without uh what What's how do you say it
ah good night thanks for watching
no [\h__\h] out
[Music]
no the the phrase that you say when
someone appears and then without
explanation disappears
but that's the one I want to say
I will be so disappointed
[Music]
it's kind of hard to still
ah yeah refuses to elaborate at least
exactly
for once
for once I have a
a cordock instinct
[Music]
nowhere else
I got one over there before
I feel like if you wanted to you could
already get up there
well we're not gonna force it um
[Music]
jail
can we open these doors somehow
because otherwise he's literally an
imprisoned Coral
all right
he'll be stuck forever
certain people might be very delighted
by that
me not me
hmm
we committed war crimes the korok no way
never
how dare you make such accusations
about such an innocent cute little
leaflet huh
you yourself should thus be imprisoned
for such
a dangerous accusation
oh
okay
I mean it would have been a weird
location to put something really good
here
[Music]
I don't know I don't know I don't know
what to draw
[Music]
does it Lisa bow do something special
bubble
boo
[Music]
connect on top
Maybe
it conducts lighting yeah really
ah guys
is there any case where a male duck
would be on top of a female duck
except for mating
cause I saw a really disturbing scene
today
there can only be
this one reason right
yeah I've been duck watching recently
Doug wrestling
I don't know it just it's kind of
disturbed me saying that I was shocked
I mean I know they must procreate
recreate
somehow
somewhere
sometime
but not in front of my eyes please
first I thought that the duck was like
sitting not just not sitting on it and
just just chilling in the water and then
trying to eat something because like he
was pecking at something but it was just
the lady's head
I don't know I was ruffling up her
feathers
during the ACT
absolutely terrifying
you should Google about how they
reproduce it's what what
wild what'd they do
salad donut what salad it's violent
right
it looks violent
but but I've seen this duck lady with
him like several times now I know it's
the same ducks
[Music]
maybe I should adopt her
I think she's being abused by the other
duck
I have to have to save her
a poor duck lady
I want my own
or imagine
how long how long is the duck's
pregnancy
because does this mean I'll see duck
babies soon
that's babies
ducklings
that would be so adorable oh my God
wait but they make eggs right oh yeah
right right pregnancy whatever I mean
you can call that a pregnancy too right
like somehow I mean
eat those eggs
when they oh
that's why it's only this one
leaves
to ask somebody
are you sure you're holding well Phoenix
does do it differently
uh 28 days after beginning incubation
according to Google
the hatch
or until the egg is uh hatching which
one
what did I stumble into welcome
I've been here before that happened to
me before
then I saw that wizard
ah
look at them
28 days to hatch okay well a month so
maybe in a month I could see ducklings
yay
Shrine nearby
it's gonna fall down
I will follow for the meat
where's the shrine
oh that one
I guess I haven't done that let's do it
I need to do more shrines anyway
my general knowledge lack of such is
astonishing oh [\h__\h] I'm not I'm not I'm
not I'm
no
[Music]
um
I don't I don't need to know such things
please don't come up here
you're not gonna come up here right
how are we gonna do this is there maybe
maybe uh maybe a thousand fruit is
actually good
no not really I
spawned I don't want to win I don't want
to win in this fight they're gonna spawn
Shadow Garden and that that [\h__\h] is too
strong for me
oh
my two One's Gonna Die
let's go quickly into the shrine
also the thing I was standing on doing
was kind of a cave wasn't it
okay oh I think we're safe
that means we can go back and collect
the loot oh yeah
itadakimasu
okay I think I may have heard about that
before though the the male duck thing
yeah
you guys are giving me hints and I think
oh
I think I've heard it before
oh [\h__\h]
okay
oh my God
still
she puts up with him
I don't understand it
the chicken's mate
more gently
tell me tell me guys
tell me
you should know
what
doesn't look fun to me
I have a chicken I have a chicken you
are a chicken but I've never seen that
um
what you're into I mean it can't be
worse than ducks at least
why do you want to know because I am
literally raising thousands and
thousands of chickens it's important for
me as a mother to know what my children
are going through
I need to know the anatomical
aspects and the biological aspects you
know otherwise that would be so
um once the word
foreign
if I wouldn't take care of you guys
properly you know
so irresponsible that's what I'm trying
to say
it would be so irresponsible
please
how is this I
never drink [\h__\h] again
why
[Music]
why yeah
thank you
um
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay I have to wait
I think I'll have to wait
unless
no okay
we'll let her cook
it's not the Red Bull's fault it's just
um
genuine curiosity and concern
can make
arusa often employs a type of foreplay
by prancing around the hand and clacking
before well
mounting her
uh yeah yeah two two yeah yeah yeah well
anyway oh
what what
oh
interesting wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
say anything else but oh
oh you're supposed to bring the fire
back here that's the [\h__\h] challenge
not the chest oh well hmm
[Music]
when
oh
oh okay
well we don't have to talk about it we
don't have to talk about it
no no no worries
I
don't want you guys to feel
uncomfortable
another change of topic why is there two
holes
ah do I have to when I walk up there to
open
the other door I would have to time
time thank you reflection
time return which one is the the first
one though
but that one opens the first one okay
and then I think I did it right
okay let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go
she wants yeah I don't want to watch
those kind of shows of you guys no
because that's very embarrassing
I do not yes I mean it's even like it
has nothing to do with us
because it's because you guys are
chickens and I guess no I guess it could
be very scientific for us to watch
um such acts acted out by humans in such
movies
um but but but that's not what I want to
see with you guys no
uh
no because somebody recommended the
movie to me that I was inferiorating I'm
really interested in you know to watch
along with you guys
but then I once warned that it has such
scenes as are you know very common in
such shows as Game of Thrones and
no you know
uh and the Great and the song
I prefer to I mean
that makes it by me talking about
[Music]
um
chickens
Creations yeah
so the real reason the real question is
aren't you guys like a little bit of
hypocritical you don't want to talk with
me about that but you do want to watch
those movies
it's for your own good
that we don't watch those movies
together
um
[Laughter]
okay
uh where are we going where are we going
[Laughter]
time to stop drinking at home I mean Red
Bull always has a funny effect on me
that is true what was I gonna do a maze
do we go to this one
I suppose so is there should I go to the
ground one first I know there's one in
the sky and on the Underground too is it
better to go to the ground one first
it's just red but I don't drink alcohol
the ground one first okay
but I think this one is not too much of
a challenge I know that the hands spawn
in there but if you ex escape from them
once it's not a big deal anymore they
don't really show up anymore so
shouldn't be
an issue
[Music]
so
let's go
Rock
okay for once I will help you
where is your friend you know is it to
the maze yeah okay
I see it a little bit yeah
it's over there to the maze
hmm
but there's no tools is it maybe a stuck
in
or maybe below after you go down the
cliff
put a rocket on him
oh it got him pretty close yeah
he doesn't like the idea but wait I lost
track over there
I lost sight I mean
I need more capsules
I barely have capsules
I hope this doesn't fail
yeah and I guess because I'm gonna walk
there anyway I could have just
walk him there but no
that would make us too slow
can I fuse product with my weapon that
would be helpful too but I guess not
the balance
the balance is really bad
how will that even fly
what do you think will happen also
there's like kind of like a
a bridge
good luck
oh
no
that thing that thing I want to move
that it won't it can't I can't
oh wait I he didn't fall so far okay and
is that another Kodak thingy yeah okay
nice
that saved us
some trouble
where is he
huh
why where's your friend
well then wait
yeah he's alive
nice
oh
what
is there a example no
I mean I think I understand like all of
them are free by free
I I get that
but why is mine why does mine look so
weird you know
I I don't get it
why is mine so weird
oh wait
um
yeah
straight
ah got it got it got it got it got it
okay okay
um now
I almost wait maybe maybe
like this
um
I feel like a toddler
pushing shapes into holes that don't fit
Ana
all right all right over what the rest
don't mean we can walk that path
I don't mind I have to walk anyway
come on
square hole meme
huh
is there a quest for the maze by the way
I'd like to get the quest before doing
it but
was it just one of those things you just
do without the quest
all shapes fit for this I guess they do
yeah
[Music]
uh-huh
I would like it
was it something I can recreate
as a short
what is that
I'm trying
ah
let's do it
before entering the maze
possible hmm
you're not gonna trade me anything
okay
not a lot of setup necessary
oh oh
ah once I do the one on the surface I
get a quest for the other ones okay cool
cool cool
does this one need a stone
that but if it needs a stone then it
wouldn't already have the stone inside
of it
[Music]
[\h__\h]
ah
you are not getting away today you are
precious yummy meats and I shall Feast
on you
[Music]
well it's gonna turn into ice prime meat
no but if I leave it out there a little
while
it might right
[Music]
those fried rice
all right if you know what to do like
one time I had one where I was honestly
unsure of how
I'm supposed to do it it was on the sky
island
but most of them are pretty clear at
least
frozen meat is made up of assertion I
saw for the shield surfing oh I have to
ah
I have to warm this one up
no
um
[Music]
eh what do you mean I did oh that's it
but then why is it
huh
oh
don't mind me just doing braving
exercises
yeah
oh
um
okay
didn't happen didn't happen
didn't happen but
it didn't happen
no excuses but it didn't happen it
didn't happen
it's engraved with ancient Zona attacks
you can't make out what it says
it's all my gloves carved into the stone
slab red the dragon ring Slumbers in the
library of Steph's wake it and you shall
receive due compensation
okay
dragon
Tower the deciphered them for us but has
since run off to another newly
discovered rune for further study
writing frankly I see his absence as an
opportunity and he discovers that may
lie within will all be credited to me
my name will be for appetite so to
solving the mysteries of the sonar
civilization I gave gave it
very gay very gay
I gathered a hall of Hylian pine cones
and will use them to mark my trail in
places where I might otherwise get lost
number one
um
oh it's melting because of my sword
there's something behind
this is a chicken when Kiwa gets very
near to them
on one side
one something because I'm a phoenix but
on the other side it just makes me very
nervous when I look very very close into
your eye
and you're melting away cute I should
supposed to fly over that
oh
Shrine doesn't it
yeah I'm so scared what if the hands
show up what do I do
them
[Music]
wait maybe I should leave the pine cones
so I know how to get back
[Music]
no I cannot fight them no oh
I said Outlook great enthusiasm but so
far I haven't found anything other than
an endless supply with a cold if the
donai were going to bother the car or to
carve a note into the slab wouldn't
couldn't they wait is it still read you
thing useful because it's AOE
does it but it doesn't do a lot of
damage does it
but it doesn't AOE damage on them but
then you also have to recharge
I wonder how much damage it does
it does nice damage
[Music]
could be a way to call but them at least
one way
yeah the Allies distract them too that's
pretty nice
feel bad for them though
we are at the top of the maze I just
came from down here
but do I want to be on the top
it almost feels like cheating being on
the top of the maze
just want to pass by the passage
Passage
icicles
[Music]
oh yeah and here we can fly over again
oh some cool weapon Mighty construct
both wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
oh
I found
I thought maybe there's like something
not at the very top but like somewhere
in the middle or so
nope
all right one more check one more check
because the lower ceiling's always gonna
suck okay
there's corn dogs on top somewhere
really
[Music]
is that too far away
Yahoo
[Music]
so far no hands
but we've we've found something that
looks like
you know
can he crushed like I feel like in
theory he should be able to oh kind of
can but not very effectively
more chickens to melt
make a
map I don't even need to melt all of
this
oh there's a chest there
is
um
no no thank you
no thank you
where
did I come from
I made that fire
so I came from there and I went here
and there's nothing left oh
okay
so we continue here
we place the 10 damage bow
yeah but that one's special because it
zooms in
[Music]
that's why I'm keeping it
but I have two of them
so okay I will get rid of it stop
stop go straight through
okay okay
we making another fire
although I have so many foods that can
heal
the hearts that I don't need to worry
about it also because
we are outside we're not on the ground
so it heals rather quickly anyway
just be careful oh I'm like Spider-Man
I'm like Spider-Man
[Music]
by the way I did like spider verse okay
I really like the art style okay
okay
I paid attention
then
and and and and I was oh
motivated to watch it in the cinema
afterwards okay
okay
but I mean if we're real if we're being
real about it in hindsight like
a couple days later
if I have to say like how impressive the
movie was like it doesn't really like
leave much of a very impressive
aftertaste does it
like afterwards you know what I mean
it's it's not mind-blowing like Lord of
the Rings
okay
that's fair right
like it was a good movie
but did it change my life no
it didn't change my life the only movies
that changed my life were uh Lord of the
Rings
The Hobbit
and
The Great Gatsby
and maybe one or two others
yes I like to have The Hobbit part of
the whole world I appreciate everything
that comes comes from The Lord of the
Rings
don't be so mean guys
[Music]
anything Tolkien is awesome yeah I agree
foreign
okay we're making promise after
shivering in the cold and cowering from
the Gloom I finally made it this paper
leads to the center of the ruins there's
a Trail of Lights here that's almost
beckoning me in it must lead to that due
conversation the slab dimensioned
while The Great Gatsby because it's so
beautiful and it's so sad and well you
still love me when I'm no longer young
and beautiful
will you still love me when I've got
nothing but my aching heart I know you
will I know you will I know that your
way
well will you still love me when I'm no
longer
beautiful
ah how can you not and then there's
dude
nobody
[Music]
not Killed Nobody but no one here's what
we got
oh Connie never cared nobody
there right now so we go
[Laughter]
so good I mean they literally got Fergie
okay let's go home
[Music]
a little party never killed nobody right
here right now so we got
a little party never killed nobody
wow
what is this effect just it just gives
it such a retro feel but also it just
makes it sound so good
ha like I am in the 50s 60s
what's wrong of The Great Gatsby I'm
gonna cry so much I love it it's like my
Titanic you know
where do I go
oh
sheesh
that is weirdo
harness
yeah the old radio effect I feel like
I'm still hearing it even though I
turned it off
have you guys seen the
[Music]
scene generally I don't really want to
watch things I've already seen and you
guys also I feel like the movies I have
never seen you guys recommend so usually
you guys have already seen it
no read the book oh
that was really good right
watch it at school oh
we watch a movie Informer GM
[Music]
nope but interested
you like Moulin Rouge
we should watch that I love the the song
that um all these ladies did
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
down
you want to give it a go oh yeah
[Music]
foreign
they're all so Fierce I've done it at
long last I've done it I found the relic
of the zonai civilization though my
Euphoria is short-lived in the hours
since my Discovery I've tried touching
hitting and yelling at The Relic but it
remains unresponsive
I'm starting to feel that I may not be
unraveled able to unravel
the secrets of the Sunday after all the
thought makes it cold even more bitter
well fine I suppose it's time I crawl
out of this frigid pit and I show my
report on my investigation
well this one is destined to be opened
by me
so off with your fingers
[Music]
let's do it a bit faster
oh no
no no
no
bye yeah anyway I kind of want to watch
more movies that play in that
time frame
like The Great Gatsby
is there any other good movie that would
be yeah the Roaring Twenties
because that's kind of hot
I already used I don't know 20s 40s 40s
20s 40s I guess
Mice and Men
Chicago
see two Chicago's
this better be a reward Shrine because
let's not do the 40s why not so what's
wrong with the 40s
Chicago what's Chicago about is a
romance or
[Music]
I feel like a lot of 20s 30s I mean not
saying that the movie has to be from
then please no but I want the story to
be from them and I think a lot of them
are romantic
it's a musical
about a nightclub for Ninjago
oh yeah but this is the Romantic one one
becoming independent cool okay
[Music]
Saving Private Ryan I I never watched I
think but I'm very aware of the contents
of it
I think
um
that's what Chicago sometime no
hola musical matter today
yeah
[Music]
what
ah Shrine Quest is
for you who conquered this Labyrinth of
the land I have ruler of owls have
unlocked the door party on the west side
of the Labyrinth of the Sky West Side
Story
okay
[Music]
no
okay I just had this idea thanks to
Japanese comment you know how this year
this year was two two days yeah two days
of normal concert but
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
how about we like I mean in the
following year we can't do the same
thing right
what if it's this one themed
what is this one theme thing is the
musical you know what I mean if this
musical themed
that would be fun
um that would be actually so cool upon
anyway
[Laughter]
[Music]
they can't come in into this room
they can't even come into this room [\h__\h]
you guys [\h__\h] you
you [\h__\h] you very very much
again
this kind of [\h__\h] out of me
I hate you guys
I hate you
they're very good at being terrifying
and
look
we're gonna they're gonna disappear
they're gonna vaporize
just wait do I have to like go away or
is it like a time thing
time based
[Music]
I don't want to win against them because
what comes afterwards is even worse
I I can probably manage to kill these
yeah sure but um
[Music]
not gonna ask them to kill me
girl
hi see they're scared too
[Music]
oh wait is it there you go
[Laughter]
oh fun
all right you guys are asking for it
but don't they respawn oh wait right the
respawn there is
but ah I wanna try the the Brushy thingy
I saw someone do it but that person is
the pro what if I use ice
and they respond if I don't kill them
fast enough I'm very aware of that
oh [\h__\h] it's really cold
uh that's gonna be a problem too
wait I don't need all of it
oh
okay at least now I have enough bombs
wait I'm scrambling
and please don't respawn
please don't respond
please don't respawn
there's a free spot
respawn I think they respawned one
okay now here comes [\h__\h]
Shadow God again and what would you um
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm already like my mind is like already
breaking guys
uh
it's not even worth it it's not even I
don't think that the reward is even that
worth it
what's up
how was that I don't remember what's the
best way to find it but the best way of
course is total flurry Rush all the time
but
I can't I can't do that so well I
haven't because he works like a lion all
right and I have barely gotten like
training versus Lionel's until now
[\h__\h] me up
but okay
okay I mean I probably shouldn't do that
anyway
I didn't realize
[\h__\h] okay Mom he barely does damage okay
okay okay
huh
way
laughs
the higher a maximum number of Hearts
the more its attack power increases
this Gloom will gradually wear down the
body of its
wielder
so I need a Gloom resistant armor for
this one but then
[Music]
it was more rough more difficult
ah if you use it to another weapon on
top of it
oh okay
God damn it
um
damage though yeah
[Music]
I could visit to the wooden stick or to
my Royal hellberg I'm not gonna fuse it
through the long sword
maybe this one
yeah the ball seems pretty good yeah
utilize the sword under the thumb you
have no downside oh okay
well I mean basically you have endless
opportunities to fight
uh
um this dude right because there's like
um set locations where
he spawns
where the hand spawn huh
so if you want more of this stuff
oh that's pretty good equipment to get
besides like the Lino stuff for example
anyway was this path always opened no
okay I'm glad I did it once yeah
she actually looks kind of cool combined
normally when you make these super long
weapons it looks weird
did I did I find everything in here
like all the treasures that are
important
that I find everything that I needed to
find
get armor
Sky maze time okay uh but the sky maze
right
how do I get there
oh
I already activated it
I know visit the west side of the lover
from the sky
well maybe
[Music]
I need a hot air balloon
really
[Music]
used an air bike
oh well I mean it looks like yeah I mean
too high to ascend but there's several
of those pieces maybe to take a break
when you can when you're like uh when
your air balloon is like dying
that or go to the nearest cash one the
other one's kind of far away
but I could from the sky Shrine make
something
to fly further I guess
oh now there's there is a sign that I
already found the
and decipher them okay cool oh by the
way Wing sled fan oh an unknown one and
line actually I'll go here I'll go here
yeah we'll make a vehicle
um
if you combine two fans of the steering
wheel I know I wanted to make that one
anyway I've seen many people use it
already
I wanna make one
oh I could make this thing shoot me
uh over as well
I wonder how far I would get with that
but anyway
um
okay here we go
these charges
is there anything else I need them for
besides like when I'm out of batteries
in the middle of like flying somewhere
so when I want to recharge myself
or using it for the gacha is there any
other reason why I would need them
no okay good then I don't have to feel
bad about using them I still haven't
gotten the last one
ah this time
what is it
wait no
I thought that was a sign
if I would have gotten the last one
wouldn't it have shown me an explanation
of it
no okay I got it cart okay
okay he's freezing his ass off
so
we can make a plane
I'm gonna make a plane
or we could make we could use that
platform
because then at least it stops
in the sky
do I need to get at the top of it or to
the bottom
oh I see something there
at the west side
there's a shrine
yeah I see the chest but no
I think I've been there before
and then I shot the chest and it fell
down
that's the shrine
[Music]
I didn't get all of the geographs yet
but
quite a few
I don't know um
I feel like this thing could already get
me there
don't you think
and not look for the rest today
yeah I don't know
maybe one
and then maybe two
and then maybe free
because then I can't stop myself and I'm
curious
I don't know today's supposed to be like
a day where we just do whatever things
like that are not in the main story but
they're still kind of like big things
okay
with the shot literally wait
ah
okay
come on
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
all right
I can't climb like that can I
upgraded my battery once I would like to
do it more but
can't wait here
okay let me try again I think you just
have to touch this one
[Music]
hate I hate
hate
where's this Kodak
[\h__\h]
face
which side there's the left
okay okay
I was waiting for the climb down thing
but then I don't know he just fell down
no I can't even see it oh there
[Music]
just went one step too far
it's too dangerous Crocs
too dangerous
what makes you think that this is okay
[Music]
oh the dungeon is there
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
Gremlins
okay we're gonna build something
okay I would normally I would try to
make my first one with a tutorial but
okay we can try
that's all you need right
I'm gonna try building this thing I
think one just goes straight right like
this straight down
and then
put this one
does it go on top of the first one
but like
completely on tap or just partially
this is the angle
like this
in the middle
on the edge
maybe I should look it up yeah
don't tendo even made a video about it
but
hoverboard Toyota game
okay okay
should be
here
I'm done
let's go I think like this
is trying to perfectly placed nah
what's this
um
okay cute it kind of looks cute I like
it
it's an Akita bike
I don't have much batteries
and I suck at flying this oh okay okay I
got it I got it um we will have to eat
some batteries
uh
okay and joystick up
so get up okay
and now should I go to the shrine right
oh
we'll be eating quite a few batteries
ah wait why are you turning why are you
turning like that ah
okay there you go
yeah I want to explore the devs too
maybe we'll go today
it always goes forward right
oh
[Music]
okay now we can go down
your stairs to the right of it
this little technique oh yeah because I
know there's a maze in the
I know there's a maze in the depths as
well
this won't be saved right but I should
probably like favorite it
[Music]
um
uh set as favorite
ah there's two different
I didn't make two different ones
anyway
trying this time gets offered to us
right away in the beginning
that one has no front uh but but the one
that I favored it was the right one
right I think so because it was the last
one
I think mine seemed pretty stable
I got happy with it
it's not a reward Shrine okay
[Music]
let's say gravity
who's this
a gravity thing
uh okay oh
I'm waiting for the ball to respawn
there we go
shoot
now if it shoots it now I would think it
reaches that yep okay
[Music]
let me switch my weapon
don't want to use my precious new
strongest I think currently my strongest
weapon I know I think in the shrine it
doesn't take damage but still
uh where am I going
oh there's a chest there I should shoot
myself up
one more time please
oh
Mr gravity is still working
it seems like it
weapons don't take durability damage
from activating oh okay okay oh look
we just used that to come here so that's
very kind oh
what
okay
that works
this one's currently
on
so what's going on here
there's
yeah
the target is in the cage
ball goes here and then what what
there's no
hmm
there's nothing to launch it though
but we shall bring another ball here I
guess
same ball that's kind of annoying
okay
but I'm guessing I have to time
something again
oh
family eyes and I know exactly it was
just uh my weapon is so slow
hi okay
I have to stop it when it's like up
there already over it
yay fun cool I like it
um
good shrine
a little bit short I feel like they
could have done one more thing with this
gimmick
just one more riddle but okay
did you get the chest yeah I did I had a
charge it's all night charge
[Music]
it's one thing you don't like
oh thanks for the membership welcome
you you recalled
yeah it works too
that works too many ways
money paths lead to Rome
to you who set foot in my Labyrinth of
the sky I offer
a test of wisdom four terminals are
hidden in this maze activate them all
wait it's like a dungeon
is it as difficult like long intricate
as a dungeon
nope
oh please no
how high should we go
[Music]
the wind stopped
this is like a timed thing
[Music]
uh I don't know what I'm supposed to see
in the map
good job John you can get the win again
okay
[Music]
gravity thing going on here too
wait oh
okay well I guess we're amazing while
flying
then at least the glue hands cannot
spawn here right right right
it looks like something I need to
activate
could climb all the way up there
I want to fly
up there
but I cannot
I don't trust my climbing abilities that
seems kind of excessive
huh
okay you're probably not supposed to
activate that one right away huh
oh what
you are
[Music]
good
it doesn't get me any higher than this
thank you
I'll skip it for now
I don't even know which one I want to go
for
oh we're close to this one now
let's make it blue
let's play
this way
can I climb dad
I want to climb
can I not
oh wait let me go under
oh sure
[Music]
and we got it
no
no no no
one activated
now
[Music]
um
let's see if we can reach that one
look
oh
[Music]
dead end
well did you guys see
[Music]
and listen
to our
first ever whole life English original
song before they were only like myth and
Council separately is separately
original songs
now we have one together
[Music]
yeah yeah
it's so good yeah
thank you
I love how there's a shiny Smiley story
reference and it is pretty sweet isn't
it
the melody
[Music]
where am I going
follow me
[Music]
I really like the song it's cute
actually
this one
I recorded in Japan in a studio with uh
like actual vote oh [\h__\h]
vocal Direction
almost ran out of stamina I didn't pay
attention
that's what a few of these platforms are
for to stop and get some stamina back
huh
it was basically like good I was there
too
and yeah me and gouda we recorded
basically under the same circumstances
um and uh yeah had like a
coach more or less yeah how was the
vocal Direction it was like yeah nice
nice
kind of unusual but
nice to have and
encouraging I suppose uh yeah I arrived
when gouda was done and we did like high
five Taxi
you go next
and then she left and I did my part
I love doing things
these days
hmm
high five but don't touch
no
foreign
um
and this is thankfully not much of a
dungeon I appreciate that actually I
wasn't ready for such a commitment today
um
I feel like the song will be having a
much more
um emotional effects
then it already has when it's performed
live
with all of us
in the venue
that will be quite something
[Music]
I'm gonna go all the way around again
oh oh wait can we go
I hope the pen oh yeah I retweeted this
suddenly showed up on my
on my timeline and I read through it and
I was like thinking oh that's cute but
as like
you know I can't ignore this
if I retweet this
so many more people will see it and no
other Holo Ian member will retweet this
I'm sure
so I must
I must do it
so that they have a higher chance of you
know success
um
of succeeding in their plans I think
it's a cute plan so
yeah if you guys don't know what I'm
talking about check out my Twitter like
some fans started some kind of pen light
um
project where they want as many people
as possible to light their pen lights in
a specific color at a specific timing
depending on what row you are in
yeah oh you're welcome
I'm glad if I can help the community and
I think it's a cute project so there's
no way to go straight through here is
there
let me see
no I don't think so
okay
[Music]
that's going to be difficult I don't
think so I think it can work because
like now that I retweeted it I think a
lot of people saw it and it was probably
shared maybe in like fan discords
hopefully and then you know if you have
a friend who isn't really much in social
media but they also go or like if you
know of it and you take place in your
sitting at the venue you can tell the
people who are next to you yeah before
the concert starts easy just tell the
people who are next to me for everybody
who has a ticket to go their IRL make
sure to tell the people who are next to
you and then tell them to tell the
people who are next to them and so on
and I think mostly that should work out
well if everybody communicates and then
I think already a big part a big people
pick up big amount of people saw it
through the retweet
so yeah
and even if there's like a couple of pen
lines somewhere there that are not
joining
I think at least like there will be a
a
majority
we should be able to create a majority
I think so devil
uh
overpower the minority
okay now I'm back here but
um
I don't know what to get in here should
I climb after all
huh
[\h__\h] hell
[Music]
nice to ascend we haven't seen anything
to ascend
that's too far away
oh
[Music]
I could probably cheat and make
something that like
gets me up there but this works this
works kitty kitty
ah okay nice
I'll spread the news like butter and
bread thank you hello Ian light project
exactly that's what it's called
although Ian like project it will look
so cool if it works out
and so organized
and I mean it might have been like a
nicer surprise if for me personally if I
wouldn't have known about it
and it just happened without my
knowledge but
I am glad to be the one who knows and
shares it to make it a success
no problem
will still be a surprise another thing I
like you have wait wait you have
Traverse this maze Mark well my words
I have pulled apart the bars in The
Labyrinth of the land that obstructed
your path below ground whatever that
means
from high above to Far Below prove your
Courage by diving into the depths of the
Earth yeah
the final way shall open to you
oh from here I should dive okay that'll
be a long day
fine fine fine I don't even know what
you get out of this
what's that
can I make that jump
there's a chest
why is there a connection somewhere
double audio
no way
um that was just the echo anyway what
was I saying oh yeah another project
that I saw that maybe I shouldn't be
seeing yet
they saw through
um
okay
for Twitter
was a bus birthday bus it was so pretty
with Akira art well there's a coral
characters
they're so pretty I haven't seen Akira
drawing me in a while wink wink wink
wink
are you listening I haven't seen you
driving in a while but then I suddenly
see your art
on the bus
birthday bus but this isn't coming early
why is the bus already it's like did
they think my birthday was in June
7th of June instead of 6th of July
leave me alone
[Laughter]
I don't know
and where the [\h__\h] does this koroko
I have other places to go right now
oh
are you supposed to catch this one right
wait
save it for later
I can't go down now
we'll go back and then we jump
nice jump
your birthday coming soon yeah
unfortunately no for the birthday life
so what I'm currently thinking of doing
is
ever Collins
uh
um but I don't know so um I think I want
to do a countdown and that might be like
a cutout okay countdown and then during
the actual day
I'm thinking either just Collins in a
normal stream or because that's kind of
I don't know you know I want to do
something special for my birthday and
like a mix up for the lack of 3D
uh how do I
yeah
um but I can't so
I was thinking maybe a
H that's scary oh that's good what the
[\h__\h] maybe hey
Marathon
10 hour marathon or something like that
I don't know
it's the most I can do you know when
I was just hoping still that I could
have the birthday live and now I don't
have it so I have nothing really
prepared and now 10 hours sounds good
just the average stream yeah but I would
like mix it you know with Collins
maybe in the beginning of the stream for
a certain time zone and then in the end
of the stream for a certain time zone so
everybody can call in whenever they want
and then in between we have like maybe a
collab or two you remember my previous
Marathon
um what was that Marathon
what was that Marathon anyway where I
had like rust and so on
and collapse too
was that just anniversary two years
anniversary ah
yeah we can do
I mean I don't want to force myself to
do like an endlessly long
anniversary on a day where I should be
celebrating my birthday
foreign
I think 10 hours is fine and then we can
have lots of fun activities that's my
that's my idea behind it lots of fun
activities for both you guys and me that
that's we we could do Collins and the
collab and the solo and maybe some
singing I don't know like everything
maybe hand cam a little bit in between
yeah
um what
dude
I would have almost just killed myself
because I didn't see where the end is
for [\h__\h] sake
that was like literally one centimeter
off
can't see [\h__\h]
where is this
is there a light source yeah
no no nothing I can activate
also this is a dark maze huh
great
yeah
okay
huh okay
ah
o
there's
I thought they were only in the sky
oh did you see that
you don't know
level three oh I never fought a level
three before
hmm
all righty
wait
let's light it up a little bit so I can
see stuff
okay that is fun it's fun that's too
funny
um
huh
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
sorry brain currently being weird
yo
good damage
ah sorry brain wind brain weird
ah
Fair yeah the damage is good huh
[\h__\h]
let me eat some fried chicken
sorry I'm scrambling
oh twin
hmm
I got no fairy currently I need to go
find fairies man
should have healed a bit more
where does that leave me off please in
front of the bus
usually good oh yeah [\h__\h]
I should change armor yeah I'm using un
uh upgraded armor
are we start in the beginning
you know
I do all of these paths lead to this
monster
and I have so many of the small ones
I'll use the small ones
be plenty
it's no big issue
sometimes you know even though I know
the menu and everything go well enough
sometimes I scramble
sometimes do you guys have that too when
you play tltk sometimes it's like you
push all the wrong buttons
yeah
good it's not just me
hey
pretty often sometimes especially if I'm
yeah yeah our Mobility is like uh
when you want to do something else
all right here we go
see I'm scrambling again
oh
what am I doing no do you know what am I
doing
what is the focus button is that l
but at least that one's fast
uh yeah okay
oh
he's so fast oh
[\h__\h]
could I like time reverse him when he's
in the in the cube form
no not really
thank you
did you just hit
what I think nah
give me the right thing ah
how did that happen because we went
against the wall bumped against the wall
it was a tool in snapper
oh no he's got a different face okay
problem I remember this from the
construct number two
yeah why does it do so little damage oh
I open you
know
that also broke
laughs
we got it on his arm though
[Music]
hey
hey is that everything
you gotta do here
whoa
rocket Time Bomb charges rocket launch
crystallized charge
and oh I have the perfect weapon base
for this uh strong so nice long sword
yeah
yeah because they're stronger when right
when refused to donate items
did I respond with blood moon oh good
question I think so
who's the other
big boss is also respawn you who have
traversed this Labyrinth of the deaths
this trial is over it was a test of your
talents in overcoming it you have shown
yourself to be strong with body skill
and mind in my name as the rule of owls
I commend you achievement and of a
fitting reward
I'm a rave draft inadewardly evil hidden
away since days of old take it now
coming
this morning
[Music]
the maze ones don't respond
ing
[Music]
foreign
pants some believe these griefs are
inspirited by a malevolent entity
they're a rare fans fine but I already
have a whole
like armor set that's stealthy
are those ganon's pants but like what uh
why why would I use this over my whole
set
chest of both sides oh okay
I mean these ones
evil pants they look cooler but there's
so many armor sets in this game
whoa whoa never seen that before it
resonates with a if it had still night
devices to create greatly increase
um
wait I can even attach something to this
no is it not it's not already attached
this one's this this one's already
attached right
it's already ends no okay okay
where am I it would be nice if we could
activate a
flower thing in here
I'm surprised there's none like inside
the maze that would be cool but wait
there was a shrine
in the ground maze
normally every shrine
has a flower in the same location on the
ground
so there should be one here yeah
outside the maze okay cool
on the roof
okay
we can go rooftopping
topping the roof
[Music]
I don't know
foreign
[Music]
logic I know
well
[Music]
it's literally just like the maze
not much else to it
nonetheless
pretty cool we finished the whole maze
Quest thing right
put that down should I explore the area
around here
[Music]
I don't really see anything
could you go up to the very top of this
looks more like it cuts off there
no um Terry town oh that would be
oh
do they always have an egg like that at
the top
these plants but yeah territown would be
nice I would like to know where
Terrytown is
our town is great I know they have the
the repairing thing or the defusionizing
okay
the fusion
I can't miss it but it's it's on the
ground normal ground right the middle
sector of the world
not on the world right
that would be a terrifying place to be
I'm nowhere to jump off
here
there's pose
what
did they go straight now I didn't go to
the tickle tree yet
oh there's a big one up there
bro no pause before bros
scared me
what are you picking up a pole
no
wait actually I want to show you guys
something next time I
see one of these
saw this video that said I wish I knew
this or like I I found out about this
after 200 hours or so
of playing tootk
bye bye
see wait what is more monsters I don't
know if it works on them I don't think
it works on these
on what
you're so cute
[Music]
oh the way they walk backwards this
little cowardly shits
she looks [\h__\h] cute
I want to make them my pet
humans be like oh this thing this this
free wild animal is cute let's
uh
what's the word
don't don't
dominate dominicate dominize the
domesticate
um
uh
so many words too many words
where am I going right now I'm just
exploring right that's my goal right now
it's the exploring a little bit
let's don't tend to
movement I am Dominican you know that
Scrub song
where Carla sings
I think she's singing she's Dominican
Dominic Dominic Dominic Dominican
Dominican
because her at that time husband already
I don't know
doesn't really understand what what
where exactly she's from yeah
uh he called him
that even to me that seems very
different from Dominican and I don't
really know [\h__\h]
about
Latin America
[Music]
is that the right term
I don't know
yeah it is okay thank God I wanna get
canceled
uh what I saw something I wanted to
collect whereas the thing that I want to
collect I think it was like a big pull
up there
no cancels today
[Music]
on Eva works okay thank God good I was
wondering if South America would also
apply
South America and Latin America
same same
same thing or or is it like an under
category or
is that you create me not the same hmm
yeah same thing yes
most things say same thing
not the same oh
did I just say most things most people
say
well it seems like there is a
[Music]
um
divided opinions
[Music]
different but similar okay
where's his Pole
No One's Gonna Cancel it for asking
questions
I can't be sure about that
that those five pose were not really
these poles the large ones that are on
top of these large plants they're really
not worth it
I won't ever do that again
what's that
these pose ain't loyal
[\h__\h] huh
is that a mine
uh
okay one disappeared in the depths
that's a town
the opposite of a chasm
it's like here
where is that
I was like in here
[Music]
I'm gonna check it out yeah Oh I thought
that was a pool
I'm going to check it out
check it out check it out
they fall so slowly
[Music]
okay right now
it's a camera sucking around
so
Kira
[Music]
um
I don't know
ah the lyrics seem so fake
casa su casa
let me see you move like you come from
Colombia
[Music]
um
music be like
ah aggressive noises aggressive
that's exactly how Music Works what is
this
okay
[Music]
oh when you say the opposite of a chance
I mean I can Ascend you and go back to
the overground and spawn on the top of
the mountain I know there was like
literally an oh
no more
foreign
[Music]
town
what am I doing
oh but first
my mind a little bit huh
I think I heard a monkey ah you guys
are they gonna climb up here
um
get over here if you can
[\h__\h]
okay here it goes
yeah
but that one died too
it's like an AOE kill for all these
corrupted
yeah monsters mm-hmm
at least for the skeletons it's like
insta kill I think for the others it's
maybe not insta but it's still pretty
darn strong
not but not for these I think these are
different because they're not corrupted
I think it's really only for the
corrupted ones
I did not know you could yeah yeah right
hold the knowledge I received from
watching those YouTube tutk videos
hmm
and the baby fox is so cute where's the
freaking clock there better be a Kodak
here
isn't
oh no there must be
there must be
how could there not be
more products no [\h__\h]
ah
what is this
[Music]
gonna make grilled wolf out of you
grilled meal standby
noise
you're done okay
fine yeah what about that hole
or maybe a saucy tree that that one oh
this one there's like gliders oh oh
Stone still
[Music]
I'm trying to manifest
is this really the stone that needs to
go
into the hole
was that just a chasm
no wait ah no no okay I see now okay
yeah there is no stone going in
there's a stone going out I guess they
don't have the stone going in um
riddles anymore that they used to have
in breath of the Wild
because I think I have yet to see uh
let's feed bird to live
wait which one do I take does it matter
[Music]
um wait
okay I still left one how did I know I
should play this game with the with the
cups and the one ball inside the cup you
know the marble
you don't know with what kind of
intuition I found out that it was the
last one
or if it even mattered but
okay
what do you want now
is that
uh first of all
is that Tower over there one that I
already have
yeah most likely
wait no
I'm not not necessarily I understand
[Music]
thank you
what what place is this
[Music]
wait I think I saw this
oh it's very obvious I don't need to pin
it
um the forest is here
you actually complete dark puzzle Island
from breath of the wild completely dark
puzzle Island I probably did
hey I know I know
oh Shrine although I'll just fly over
there now because it will be more
obvious
and
it's the top of the maze
yeah okay
okay my show maybe Shrine first it's a
very random Shrine but wait I should fly
let me well I guess I could get my
hoverboard
I was gonna make something with um the
plane but oh well
[\h__\h] off
not worth my attention
have a boring do you have a board orphan
no but these ones you have to build them
with a card on underneath
[Music]
bill
let's go
we're not going to this right now how
far can I go as long as I get some
height though
could you fly the rest should I
um
maybe a little bit further
you know
eat them batteries okay
[Music]
yeah that's that's enough though to fly
I don't know if I want to continue using
it though but if I go into the shrine
and I go back outside it's probably gone
anyway
so raw you have a hovercraft yeah it's
easy to make it's really easy to make
you can make it like really early in
game
it's raining man
hallelujah it's raining man what is that
a big hole
oh is that the forest and the forest
still has like this like
oh small
where it was I really don't remember
where exactly everything was
fall
but I think you know they gave you they
didn't lead you to the first memory
purposefully because
yeah otherwise they would have placed it
very easily accessible
oh it does not okay
but my point stands
oh that's the final one
oh
we could get it and then just not watch
it yet and watch it whenever we need to
hmm
oh no
well I think this helps me much I would
like
oh ah
okay
no problem no problem
I don't like this
Shrine so much but
it's okay it's okay
I would like a bigger view you know
I guess I could throw some
Bloom seeds
yeah
oh no ah whatever
this one's spooked yellow this is
basically Fatal Frame oh
these don't close completely anyway
uh I'm already confused
it's amazed
I found the chest
does it have a key
or
voluminous
kind of a joke it's like their Nintendo
is making fun of me
giving me aluminous stones
what's this
huh
this one no move maybe only if I step in
the space
okay
why don't they move
I don't want to carry this thing around
anymore
it's better
foreign
yeah so here I think I went
oh there's lasers here okay
oh a big spiky wall again this must be a
key come on
no
more gems okay does this ever move
ah maybe it moves when I touch the
laser
what about here Ah that's the beginning
of the shrine
which also is where the end of the
shrine is okay
hmm
what's this
oh
[Music]
is that the key
oh
that is also a gem
got it got it got it
at this room
okay this was my checked
hey oh
there's that second floor that obviously
wants me to ascend into it and this must
be the key
[Music]
laughs
I don't want this no thank you
so cute vitamins to find out the chest
uh I think if I don't take the item and
I keep it closed it's probably gonna
count it as I didn't get the chest of
the shrine right but I don't really care
about the 100
I already have plenty of donut bows
don't need them
foreign
I'll find it I'll find it
um
and they're super common at this point
anyway
found another one of these oh this
is key come on it has to be it has to be
yeah okay after being trolled several
times it feels like a schnitzel yacht
German for
uh what do you call the game where you
um hunt for Clues
yeah
Skyrim down yeah yeah in German we say
cutlet hunt basically
oh yes of course
open open let me out let me let me know
I'm scared of the dark
and I don't want to admit it
could I know
it's actually I don't know why they call
it that
no you didn't hear anything yay four
strands
I'm gonna get another heart probably I
feel like I have plenty of stamina right
now
but the fact that you know I can get
one-headed I mean not with proper armor
but still I can get one-hitted by
uh those skeleton he knocks you know
makes you think it really makes you
think
there was another area like this
actually I might have been the same
place that I was exploring
yeah I might have been like running
through this maybe nah wait no
I I think I was close to the Zora's
domain and I found this area where when
I stepped in
like I could I couldn't really
survive I don't know I don't even
remember what happened but it was just
something for later I suppose
something that looked like kind of
Stormy and once you enter
it's like
yeah
what's going on
I said hey
what was that again
I sank that at a rock concert before
backup singer
please sing that song
and on archived yeah I could probably
try to remember what how it goes what is
this
yeah I remember when I was like a backup
singer for
some rich
dudes eccentric Rich dude's birthday
party through who was a a friend of the
company CEO that I worked for
uh yeah
and
yeah
he kind of wanted like foreign singers
because I guess it looks more rock and
roll and more cool and special
I wasn't the only foreign singer
I was a main singer who was really good
some American dude who
lived in Japan for a long time
I don't know who he is anymore I don't
remember anything
I wish I did would be interesting
um
that's a weird story right I thought I
also thought it was weird
weird it's happening oh
yeah a weird experience
did I tell you guys what kind of company
that was
the company that I was doing like a side
job at did I tell you
it was a pretty cool account
just just so happens
special bonds you know
foreign
there's a couple of like big
particular companies that create all the
particular machines
I would say there's like
maybe free
it's like niju Sanji and whole life and
so on you know
but in forms of purikura companies and
machines
they are rivalry each other yeah yeah
they don't collab with each other though
there must be a collab ban going on
yeah
no I'm not meaning I'm being 100 serious
no for real though
really am
but I kind of got the job for like
contacts
um
friend was friend of the CEO I think
and I needed a side job to get some
pocket money
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
what is the like special thing I have to
do here to open this or is it just open
hell of a side job yeah I did like all
kinds of things for it for for them
I did
some like translating
sometimes they would just let me sit
there and draw like private things
because I didn't have work to do for me
but they liked me so they just let me do
whatever
but most of the time they let me test
out new polycoda machines
um
so I would go in
take some cute pictures
for free because they at the company
they had a lot of their machines
[Music]
um
I was just like you know always taking
purikura
and
yeah I mean I don't think it was like
anything serious my testing but
this is one thing I could do and then
and then uh
yeah one time I didn't I did something
super special for them
because
you know I'm cute
I'm cute I look cute so put one-on-one
together okay
so I wasn't all around it
for them
[Music]
I also did something where I needed to
use my voice as well foreign
ago
hello my brother in research I was
waiting for you that's right I'm the one
who discovered these big ruins out here
but I wasn't able to make much progress
investigating them
and
I'm only one Hylian and this Alice is
not the one Hylian job that's why I
wrote the sonai survey team asking them
to dispatch a researcher to assist me
and here you are practically right after
I sent my letter a great response time
what what you're not a doll oh so a few
people come through here I assumed you
had to be the assistant I asked for my
mistake after all the trouble I've gone
to can't extend one system to help with
my monolith research monolith
Wanna Live
your dad sorry scrub that for me brain
is not meant to be public knowledge
movie aware from The Zone I serve a team
I am
[Music]
um I appreciate the offer but that's not
really not allowed oh then again no he
may not be a researcher he does have the
look of an adventure about him oh I
definitely do although I feel like the
top of this armor
it looks like with a guy like one of
those guys would wear when they go to
like these anime Raves
I think that's the best way to describe
it
don't you think
laughs
oh bodies yeah right this kind of a
motion capture suit too
much the
foreign
ERS I've never been to one but I've seen
how people dress there
then again
maybe his expertise will get things back
on track you know what you're hired for
this particular loan I'm appointing you
as my research assistant come on let's
find out what Secrets these runes are
hiding I am very interested in it is it
these like these these things that I
already saw before and I didn't know
what to do with it I'll start by showing
you what my research has been covered so
far right here
Emoji time oh no okay huh these are
small take a look I think it'll be
pretty surprised by this discovery
yeah
display the power of the sage of wind
huh
it is about the thing that I was
thinking of it's the owl protected by
many dragons oh so just use my wind
power guess I can already do
I have all four
oh
what right right that's all night we're
in high instrument civilization with
their own writing system almost no one
living today can read its own ice script
but you can read the inscription on that
monolith right that's because it's
written in hyrulean though these ruins
appear to be in zonai Orange and they
feature text written in modern hyrulean
how could that be who built these ruins
and for what purpose and this is just a
possibility but the monoliths that were
found might be pointing to a spot
somewhere in the ruins
and
what do you mean
all of them if I find the middle is that
what you're saying of where they're
pointing at
there's like a cool ruin or something is
that what he's saying
you and me we're going to get to the
bottom of this let's go
what emoji now I don't know and just a
hunch but it's also your boss's hunch so
oh I got a quest for each of these then
let me get all of them
cool we could do this today
wait what
two dragons wait wait let me read it
again
that's probably my quest anyway
power stage of water in the presence of
six dragons I mean I don't have to fight
any dragons though right
Dragon these
speaking of I've been really into eating
pistachio nuts currently
because I found
um I found already peeled
pistachio nuts that are salted and I I
love pistachio nuts but sometimes it's
just annoying you know to peel them and
I found them already peeled in a bag
salted and I saw all their all that it
is just nuts salted that's that's what
it says in the ingredients only salt
and nuts are healthy so I should be
eating more
I've been snacking on them so much I
kind of like peeling them yeah yeah I
mean I do too but it's just slow
it's better if they're already peeled
wanting it can contain does it say that
yeah
I mean it says it can contain
uh traces of
so is that nuts is that a fancy word for
nuts in German and peanuts but why does
it say Charlotte and peanuts if
Charlotte is not sure
and just everything with a cover cover
fruit
uh
you tell us no you tell me
nuts may contain nuts the peanuts are
actual nuts but why are the peanuts in
the pistachios possibly why maybe
because the same company also makes
peanut snacks
lentils peas and beans or Salad
um
uh display the power of the stage of
lightning at the end of The Long Dragon
long boy that protects the mountain of
death
um
um okay
okay
is this difficult should I do I need to
fight dragons for this because I'm not
ready to fight the gliox mentally
easy
hanging
nobody okay he's a riddle yeah it feels
like a riddle look I mean again sorry
the sky with Towers out of order what is
it this time
turmo starts up the scriber Tower isn't
working huh have you tried turning it
off and on again
I've checked all the terminals Parts but
nothing looks broken wanted something to
do with the tower itself is broken
well this platform must be here for a
reason but
hmm
[Music]
you want me to go higher
oh wait it's done
to the top
this is the main story ever bring you
here
because I feel like this
these areas they feel like they're
optional
no
hmm
that's a bit High aha okay
the platform is like
snapping it is like in the way
sheesh some strong weapons here
can I do
that's what I wanted to do
yeah but um
that one that I came up here with was
went too high and if I'm already so high
then of course this will also be too
high but let me just activate one and
then try to deactivate them
um
let me go down
unless I can maybe
land like on the side uh actually oh I
can land here
and just do it from here I guess
oh hi dragon is that the long boy
[Music]
ah
Ah that's what a sword is
excuse me
I just enjoying the scenery
yeah it's working thanks to me
[Music]
come on let's go let's activate it
so let's eat these nuts
oh I should go in faster
[Music]
[Applause]
pistachio
[Music]
[Applause]
oh man
[Music]
pistachios so good
oh
nice puzzle piece complete
hmm
that's probably where you get the master
sword right I mean
isn't that where you cut the master
sword in breath of the Wild
no no comment okay but that's why you
got it in breath of the wild right
I guess they wouldn't put it in the same
place
oh good day
[Music]
um
but
Here Comes
a timeline related question
if in breath of the Wild
it is there
and then Zelda in the past after
receiving
the sword the same sword
puts it elsewhere
and me the tilty K link
no no let's say nah yeah if she puts it
elsewhere that means it's not there for
the breath of the wildling
are they gonna like
explain this it's a time travel paradox
oh
or does does paradox create two Master
swords
but then that would imply that during
the time of breath of the Wild
now there will also be two Master swords
that I could possibly find
um
I'm not asking spoiler questions I'm
just terrorizing you know about the
logical
thing yeah okay but okay
I'll ask no further
[Music]
should I go
oh I want to go land here
we're just gonna do whatever floats our
boats today normally I like to oh
what the monsters well well maybe the
last memory will tell me what the master
sword is because it's master sword
shaped
anyway what was this thing yeah whatever
floats about is what we're gonna do
today
who knows I I know
okay I love genius absolute genius
what the lightest
incredible
wow golden hour
[Music]
yeah let's really double master sword
I'm a genius
[Music]
where is the stone
no but these ones there's always Stone
missing see if the girls are connected
yep yep yep yep where is it
better be easy to get
[Music]
um
okay that's not so easy because first I
have to fry them and then I have to
bring it up here okay we'll do it we'll
do it
we shall do it
poppy poopy what comes out of this let's
see maybe something new
oh
Man cards and so my devices
automatically heads for Mark I saw this
used
in something it's going to happen use
button
yeah yeah if you stick this
to like a car with wheels or whatever
oh no even this on its own probably has
wheels
you can use it as a support thing to
fight with you
um
ah shock emitter I've seen this one too
[Music]
I think we got all first try
wow
now
we keep on getting new stuff
defensive roombas
that's what it is
there
okay I guess I fly straight down
sorry I need more chicken legs even
though you're not chicken
close enough
which level is this one
let's see it looks like I don't know ah
since there's platforms there's probably
level two
right yeah
hmm
I'm gonna try shooting a good bone oh
how much damage did that do
wait uh yeah okay
I don't think
yeah we have done some fish officially
arrived yet
oh no way did we kick
I never saw this HP I never saw how much
damage it
oh it was a level one yeah okay
[Music]
it's been do you sign me though
oh sorry it yeah I just did too much
damage
do I have something
um
I only have a donut weapon
I'll have to
fuse it with something else
uh
um I guess this thing
oh that was just a number one core
okay
this one's turning
can you
um
what is that
hmm
Flintstones
oh
yeah
is it because they're turned on
what
a what
four hours
four and a half hours very comfortable
hours
huh
like
what
what can I
well let me go over there first anyway
but no I was far I was right to under it
what about this one this one works okay
um this one already has a rocket on it
and some other tools
oh I want to make oh since there's so
many Rockets here or do I need them
all
I wanna make some rocket Shields I never
did that before really
but it's just so efficient
and they probably work even better with
donut Shields
I won't need all of them okay good
[Music]
what's up here
one rocket but if you fuse it like this
does that even
work
don't they break off when when they're
like
power
when they're
has no free
um space you know
anyway I guess we're using this one
why I don't know it's so far away why am
I doing this
why am I doing this
and how many do we need
um
okay we might need a bunch more though
yeah yeah yeah a bunch more
and then a steering wheel I think will
give us that luxury
right
angle the Rockets
I guess I could do that too but steering
wheel will make things easier
no
you don't think it makes a difference
maybe instead of more Rockets just more
batteries nah although but not with
rockets they just really fall off
after a certain dunno
you'd use angled pockets
he wow a space program
yeah I guess I can leave them oh God
damn it
on the platform on the touch yeah that's
probably the smartest thing to do then
you can also just have better control
over
how
far you're going
yeah okay
okay then let me uh fix this a little
bit
um
I hope they don't fall off
okay but they're pretty heavy so
let's come in the middle
and
you need to attach but then they go up
if I attach them they go off
if it's straight up they don't fall off
you mean if I place these straight up
if you mean do you mean these ones
that will be fine I'll be fine worst
case I maybe have maybe
maybe some
yeah three more Rockets privately
if I start controlling this this thing
does this one automatically go off I
think so
[Music]
oh yeah that's plenty and see how safe
these are positioned
am I going oh
I don't know if I'm going any direction
at all we just gotta go sideways now
like this
trust believe in the process
I think pretty much just straightforward
will be fine
yeah more more more more more more more
more more I guess here's okay
ah that was so I still have some
momentum
[Music]
this is okay I think
I could possibly
you're able to carry it over here
uh Ultra hand let's go
I would just have to carry it for the
rest of the pet and then we get a reward
that was quite
the journey
for this little Stone
more nuts please
[Applause]
[Music]
um
foreign
I really don't like these magic rods
anyway
these pistachios have the perfect amount
of
salt
the perfect yeah they're mad right
they're mid
they're so mid
[Music]
right
um
what I know
and there's a two-handed one and a
single-handed one I don't know which one
this one was but
don't need either I don't need either
there is
this island that I would like to go to
but that is quite far
[Music]
ah it's this one
in the entire in the middle
in the direction of the
maze huh
I won't say it if that cube is the maze
ah there it is I'm not there okay it's
below us so
that should shoot me up quite
well
do I am
wanna check out something else before I
go
I think not
okay and then we check out the four
um riddle thingies
[Music]
you guys gotta help me figure out where
they are but I think one of those that I
showed you a screenshot before is one of
them no
I would personally think that was what
we're looking for because I think I saw
even two of those before
the sword hair glove yeah I mean we can
always go back to it because we have a
shrine kind of above it
that I activated
there's no no need to strap
[Music]
I want to take a photo
wait I'll stay on I can stay on can I or
will it like will I be because I'm
lighter I will like Fly Above It I want
to take a picture
wait it's gonna fall down into the
underground
no
[\h__\h]
it
I thought I was staying on but turns out
I wasn't
chased it use recall yeah
too late for that now right
I guess I'll Chase it
Chase Bank
is it in here huh
it could be straight down
but it felt
it's in the chasm right
how could it like fall diagonally
wind
uh okay
Okay so
[Music]
oh it broke great where's this going
my Royal but I shouldn't be using a
royal ball
uh
sorry I'm confused
there we go
okay there it is
I see it look first let me collect all
these menu
[Music]
felt like a bird POV
jrpg for a moment
I remember when guava said stand back
I'm moving Good Times
I may have indeed said that before yeah
it's a good time because I'm good good
times
is that a yiga camp
I always have very true
I'm redefining the word
following the the yoga Quest actually
that might be something I it's not quite
main quest right and I kind of need to
do that
um trying to find Koga we could continue
that one too
um
so many things to do
so so many things you just finished it
yeah it seems like fun
this
oh there he is there he is I mean that's
not cool guy I think but it's one of his
underlying
oh yeah we are
that that's the one that I fought before
right I don't want to fight it now
though scary scary scary
I'll go over there though
I wanna get kind of higher though
and surprise him from above
um
oh
sick not really a sneak attack but um
Sky attack
you beat that poor Golem before his
recipe yeah it's because yeah when you
start attacking before
um
before uh like actually landing on the
ground
because it won't show the HP uh unless
you land on the ground I think or at
least in the area once I really did so
much damage with that 40. so I think
that's actually like really the best way
to use those materials
these ones the gypto bones
um
don't you agree I agree
nice that helps
that's how I always use them nice nice
Dr Wawa I agree but also do not
understand if you already missed the
castle I'm in the beginning of today's
stream we went I mean through the cave
you know we didn't go to the sky castle
but we went to
the underground of the castle and
whatever is left of it
you know
[Music]
um
okay okay
that's it
damn that's very very little uh HP
cheers
one headshot
and Nicole
said oh wait I thought that was banana
oh my God
bananas
okay so this is actually the first time
that we reached one of these things but
I know that they always bring you
um like guides
another Coliseum ruins on the surface an
imposing buildings similar to that same
Coliseum has been discovered there are
reports that as many as six such
stretches existed
there's six coliseums in the devs
I thought there's only one
I'm not a yika
one in the deepest steps below the cork
Forest near here but there are rumors of
eerie Grouse coming from inside the
courageous team member went to test
their medal I haven't heard from that oh
they're dead they're dead
sorry to say
there's no way a Lionel can fight uh no
uh
a yiga can fight a Lionel
oh nice
and
yeah which one
Ariel Cannon
is that supposed to be for fighting or
forgot
gaining height
banana
can't get the banana
you don't think it was a
um
Liners in them
[Music]
well well well
yeah do I have a shrine anywhere nearby
no
when I activate it and get some light
but
[Music]
um
there was something on top of the
building
oh really
hey I know and I wanna try the Lionel uh
Coliseum once but I I don't feel like
I'm ready yet I will do it though
eventually on stream
I swear if it's just a pole
a five Popo
but it'll be a 10 purple
okay okay
oh fun fun
Germans be like haha purple all right
German word cute word for butt
can I shoot things
wait what is it which door can I live at
you'll have to open it or can I just
ramble
no no space
do I even want the car
where do I want to go anyway I guess we
kind of actually we just went here to
get the photo
then we sidetracked to come here because
it was close by and very visible
but
was I in here before yeah why does it
close but
um then we kind of want to do something
else now right
we need to go okay where where where
where where where did I find
remember
this
[Music]
um
huh
I took a photo
I don't think it was so recently it was
like quite late
thank you welcome to dunk
[Music]
guys know what I mean
ah this one
I'm thinking this is connected with it
right
and then this one where where is this I
forgot spaghetto I'm related
this is main class eh okay
okay
in that case oh wait
um
okay which one should we do first uh
wait
foreign
ruins
display the power of the stage of wind
let's do this first to the owl protected
by many dragons see those are like who's
that screenshot that was owls too
many owls speaking to us oh owls
everywhere's owls
is it the same owl as from uh Ocarina of
Time
okay
uh the owl protected by many dragons oh
God where are what how how do I um I
don't remember where all the dragons are
okay I just know that one dragon is like
here right we saw him recently The Long
Dragon I don't know where all the others
are
um
it's all the same area
in the title
in here
oh it's that simple I thought I had to
travel for the whole world go to each of
the dragons that we see in the sky
find something that I have to use the
powers against
oh okay
hmm
yeah I think there's plenty of dragons
in the sky
okay so within these rooms
I I did see an owl
[Music]
I did I did
which one is this
Soldier free
[Music]
crank it
and I like the music here it's the same
as The Outpost no oh wait this one's a
special one that I have on my stick
right now
very strong is that level four
tomorrow
[Music]
not giving him a break at all
yay
yep okay
I thought it was I thought level three
was Max
moist
[Music]
that's five two oh
is this something
but I I wouldn't know which one it is
[Music]
or are the dragons that are protecting
them supposed to be the soldiers
hmm
no
I can still play quite a while right
no no
[Music]
change oh yeah I should change my armor
again what the hell thank you for always
reminding me guys I always forget
[Music]
which level was this one
also is this supposed to tell me
something that I should fly up
maybe if I Fly Above
and I have a bigger picture
smell here there's an owl hair
but
I don't know
I don't see it being protected by any
dragons oh there's an owl here too
oh nice
Red Bull no I I got I ain't got no more
Red Bull now
what if I just randomly when I like try
all of my
all of my ghosts to use their attack
against the owl
yeah finish the whole thing oh wait okay
uh that could be considered a dragon and
that too so is that two dragons
protecting it wait let me read the
things again
many dragons two dragons
six dragons long dragons
what's many how many is many okay but
this is two I think so fire
it's two right no it says two fire is to
you
and there's a lane for you so we we
bonked the owl
s
huh
what
excuse me
through okay maybe completely from the
very back
okay okay
one more time I mean it's the perfect
bowling alley for you
my friend
[Music]
okay oh
foreign
but
oh okay
complete okay
next
I see a dragon
it is not particularly long
in comparison to the other one
but it's alone
[Music]
um
and there's an owl
see you accidentally used these up
sometimes don't you
need to be like that
okay owl
and it's interesting that there's kind
of a ramp here don't you think oh like a
at least I don't know
is that a dragon
oh there's one what's this what does the
other one say I like this riddle I like
this
um
[Music]
I'll protect it by many dragons
presence of six dragons
and despite the power of the stage of
learning at the end of the lone dragon
that protects the mountain of death
well it's pointing towards a little Hill
where an enemy was on
does that mean it's the mountain of
death maybe it even on the map points
towards the month of death yeah yeah
wait no wait
what it points this way
uh
yeah
kind of points towards the Death
Mountain I don't know is that a stretch
I was lightning at the end and we can
try it is it is this one long
at the end which end this end or I mean
which one is the end
this place
stretch
um
[Music]
it'll be very obvious okay this doesn't
seem quite obvious but I don't know what
else it would be and then there's
him
maybe there's one
owls that you don't use
let's find a different one
another dead owl what wait this one
looks long
oh that's a but wait one wait there's
two maybe a long one and in front of him
is one two three four five six probably
six
water in the presence of six so in front
of the or in the middle in the middle in
the middle water
foreign
here
if you would uh
kindly
brace me no
but there's water here is that not
enough hello
it's like times like this
where I don't understand
why is there only some of them
you know
and why did that not work
[Music]
what do you mean Circle
whoa
sit there
six dragons
maybe it's more than six actually
it might be more than six
hi
a Manny Dragon Manny Man
NY Manny that's what you mean with many
wind okay
[Music]
uh
um
huh
maybe on top of the owl
I mean there's another owl
ah
okay
[Music]
it's it's at least not like a baby
riddle many things in general games are
often too easy
unleash this one makes you think because
it's hard to see now but there is this
long boy wouldn't you agree
there's this long boy
I think it's this direction
very long boy
[Music]
where's the owl
maybe it was the other direction
foreign
[Applause]
but it was a foyer
um
it's a corn dog over there
okay okay okay
the front of the head is here wait
what's with the long one
[Music]
too many quests
despite the power of the stage of
lightning at the end of The Long Dragon
okay
I would say this is the beginning
can you
what are you doing
that is not the longest one
[Music]
this one
is that the end
but like I feel like so far that was
always like some clear like platform to
do
the thing I may be on here
problem is
she's not spawning
yeah part of is this wrong anyway
huh
getting annoyed but hey this is also
sauce what is this
what is all this
[Music]
don't look at me with that creepy face
I am I think in the East now but
can you not
just go
no no
[Music]
no no no
it's not from my point of view
I did
up off everybody [\h__\h] off
let me pick up my items
ah
[Music]
I mean that must mean something
a nerves
[Music]
don't talk to me
okay okay cable I got you I gotcha
John
[Music]
um
East right it better be correct somebody
said East
it better be right
that's where I came from
so what's this one
maybe the other side I don't know this
one's not that long either
last
[Music]
X
wait do all the trees here have eggs
this is because of the owls is it owls
like eggs
one two three four five six
foreign
[Music]
that was not the long one though
oh Helena
[Music]
not them off the rocks oh no
there's lots of gems here from this
Quest
we have one left over
you're right that's actually
exactly what I should be doing
also I love how this is like
it feels like you know one of those
games where you have to move the
pictures around to complete the picture
but there's no horse but
why is there no horse but
I know I already used this didn't I
where is the last one
can't stand
it's
that's why I was trying to go anywhere
and then you guys said West just to get
the other one first even though I was
heading east
[Music]
this better be East okay
yeah
just better be used
this better piece
it's not really
look at there eventually
thank you
[Laughter]
korok Sans
why you why
speaking of the devil
aha
um
your little hands towards that aren't
you
ah okay
but where exactly do they want me to
shoot
towards did you could you maybe come
here
on do we have to do it like in the
middle
and yeah yeah yeah yeah but like where
do I shoot does that matter else can you
your butt your butt's here it probably
matters
I'm gonna have to wait until like the
the face of the dragon is
you know part of it I don't even see it
from here
I swear to God I swear to God
oh it probably matters
Fork
[Music]
okay just shoot my foot okay
see it didn't matter but I think it's
understandable that I would think it
matters was
um kind of
[Music]
um
in this case it was fine but you know
you know who knows who knows really
finish
do I go back to the dude now oh
Shrine underneath
Maybe
foreign
[Music]
I have something about yeah
it did say something about some ruins
[Music]
um
yeah whatever
figure it out as we go where where did
that go
I
wasn't that in the middle
oh you don't want to be spoiled by this
I wonder if it's really a proper spoiler
wait it will take me five minutes to
find it so don't don't go yet also
I'm gonna do this really quickly oopsie
now
I'm not done
I will make it
ah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah no yes
yes down down
no
I'm telling you it's down
I'm so sure nasty
I told you it just didn't let me put it
in
huh
I called
foreign
okay where is
where is
the spawn but am I blind
does it not spawn where I've spotted
spawn
near the long boy okay
ah he's looking at it too probably
he's like oh yeah oh yeah
or maybe oh did it spawn where I was
like
no
[Music]
oh
no
wait wait wait it's like a moment where
you can't find you you cannot find the
forest
because of the amount of trees
I think that's how you say it in German
ah I see it now
I see now
I should heal through that
Mr divorce because of the tree yeah yeah
I mean it's literally a forest yeah with
many trees and many of those old stats
owl statues and many of the dragon
statues it is there we go
oh pretty weapon
a slender claimer thought to have been
headed down to the kingdom of Hyrule
ages ago the blade shines with a holy
luster
is it lusting
for what
why is it so horny
huh
Twilight Princess weapon
wow it's Unique uh I don't want it to
break
up
you can rebuy it
does look like my tepic sword yeah
abrasive is possible to buy from pose oh
oh wait what what else is special about
it just
um did it glows
whoa
why it is so pretty
looks like I can make music with it like
like it's a like a attack stick
Direction thingy stick
um
hey what's up
special because I touched it yeah like
the wind waker yeah yeah I'm surprised
you guys say it's from Twilight Princess
because to me it looks like Wind Waker
conductor when one yeah
um
[Music]
it was a sort of sages
so we just was waiting for us beneath
the ruins
wait you found another bottle left I was
eating the way down here there's almost
certain leaves nothing important working
upon it oh my hardest problem
we dare we allow me
a Monumental loyalty
listen up kfb Hyrule owes its peace
today to the gift that King Lauda gave
unto onto onto on unto us
in his Noble feat of imprisoning the
demon Kings
weight
is named in the legend as the first king
of Hyrule this mention of impersonal
Demon King this monolith is no doubt the
chronicle of the imprisoning war my
heart won't stop going Doki Doki let's
read more
yeah can you stop commenting in the
middle of it
the grand battle ended with an energy
began with support from the Sages
each of them bore a shining secret Stone
the tears of the Kingdom among these
were four hyruleans loyal Warriors all
who hastened to King Laurus Aid as their
Oaths demanded
they
how did I say it they are the pride of
the peoples of Hyrule the stone monument
is dedicated to the Loyalty that will
echo through time
no story story
this Rune is dedicated to the stages who
fought with loud the first king of
Hyrule it was built by Highlands
afterward
oh
wow but why is it all owls
louder is not an owl
um
an owl symbol of symbolism
ah right I heard that he used to be in
like in the form shape of an owl yeah
but that was just kind of like
like a fake shape
I think but was it an owl
that he took shape as
noodle
that explains why there was Hyrule
attacks on the monoliths were found what
a discovery I'm astonished to find such
a profound secret hidden in these long
buried ruins the full misery yeah cool
stuff
mm-hmm oh
I'll turn it into a book nice can't wait
to see the looks on their faces yeah
good for you oh reward
[Music]
okay
oh okay one more meow
yeah you better
that's more like it
ah now if you're not since I'll be
sticking around a while you can come
back if you ever like to talk about the
Bruins and the relics and the birds and
the bees in the meantime happy trails
goodbye thank you
that was a cool uh lore Adventure
I like that the game
you know gives you side quests where you
can learn even more about the Lord
if you want if you're really into it
and I am into it
okay
um
now
oh now
[Music]
I could try to get this
Tower or any of the other Towers
top left what's the top left
no honestly you know what we'll do now
is it an adventure or is it the main
quest
that's another entry right
right this one
you faced master code ahead of the yiga
clan in the great abandoned Central mine
he plans to use the power of the donut
to end the world with the Magnificent
one could they be involved with Zelda's
disappearance Koga went to an abandoned
Garuda mine you can go there by
following a nearby series of statues for
the death wait so the points the golden
point that they're showing me
is already the goal
or not because if they tell me to follow
the statues but they also show me the
Final Destination that's kind of lame
that is where he is okay
um
maybe before I go nah they're weak
anyway
I was gonna say maybe upgrade some more
armor but cool gun is weakest [\h__\h]
anyway
then we'll go from here ah oh I guess I
could go through the transom yeah you're
right there's there's a Chasm here
maybe there's more but that's the only
one I see
could fly from here wait there's another
maze
doesn't look much like a maze though
interesting
okay
um even we go from the Tower or from the
shrine maybe from the shrine
three mazes in total
does that mean there's nine in total
total
hmm Tower would be easier
hello
oh well well I don't mind walking a bit
okay
this way
oh yeah we're not up that high huh oh
but the maze was right there
we're not going there
[Music]
we are going into the deep deep dark
um deep dark deep dark Underground
does link have nipples no
no uh
so I'm so hashtag unrelatable
he would be the perfect hero to me if he
had nipples
haven't
[Music]
I think we'll do
underground mostly until the end
okay depending I mean
depends on how long it takes I want to
look quite a bit because I've been
neglecting down the ground
he ain't no Ichiban
true
yeah
true debt
oh there's a shrine there
then I have to climb back up you know
I don't know about that and there's a
weird statue thingy
we'll go straight down
did I watch so yeah cause I ain't teaser
maybe not I don't know when did it come
out
[Music]
today on the Discovery Channel
King scary I see nothing
but wait on the left side should be a
big flower
um if I can orientate myself
it should be I think there
like I can't
for sure
I want to see it never mind
[\h__\h] ah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
good
I know maybe it wouldn't happen
hurt so much how do you fight things
again
[Music]
um
oh wait wait
I'll do it again
ah
it was too early
so I had a cool down
what he eat it what the [\h__\h]
up
[Music]
I am going some more
thank you
I'll try to go up from the tail maybe
but this is barely coming
good morning
can I please climb up what
I'm mad
huh
can't climb but small fast skin the [\h__\h]
I mean props to your skin care
you just eat one of my buddies
what the [\h__\h] I didn't have so much
trouble fighting him before
hi
what is he eating oh did he eat my my my
paper wait I need a weapon uh did he eat
my bump
yeah we need to go big or go home
then we go big
you little [\h__\h]
how dare you have some respect
eat the Jackal fruits
okay
come on
[Laughter]
I think I stuck less before but I think
that time
um
it had less
of these
gems on him
so that's it's a weaker mop I suppose
less struggle but
it's a blue white one
yay yay no no problem no problem leave
it to me
I need some proper mining hammer
I shouldn't be wasting this on it should
I
I don't know
never found different types of this
really
invited to girls start to learn the
secrets of silky skin so true what a
wasting potential
I do wonder about
my smooth silky skin that's literally
Untouchable yes girl
I want to be so silky smooth that I am
untouchable
sight to behold
[Music]
I need him on glassdock
I'll see what I can do if I see him
again I'll ask him
amakavi's light fruit
I need some lights down here please and
some water
well that's quite a big area because
it's at the
on the bottom of the map so
it's fills out
the rest too and here we have some
statues but we don't even need the
statues because we're following
this
really don't understand why they don't
just make me follow the statues that
would be
more interesting really
like we did before we were forced to do
that before
[Music]
might hit that end without statues
make it so that you don't you won't but
I don't think you will anyway there's
another one
ah
oh it reacted to my light but doesn't
know I'm there yet oh no don't eat it no
um
[Music]
don't eat
wait
oh
nice one
I'm not gonna be mesmerized by your skin
oh boy
he's so cute
wow
too close
hmm
where are all my nice shots
[Music]
ah what happened but it's good I need to
use
some more bows anyway yummy because I
have too many
there you go
a little big mistake buddy your hunger
will be the end of you
for me
already the second one I I hope
there's not
that many more of
him around here
give me some different bosses
not all the same so close to one another
thank you God
that's it
go into the corner
into the corner reveal
uh and you
and you can stay
into the silent corner face the corner
with your face
I guess that's what facing something
implies
usually
okay uh
nope
I am kind of going towards the road the
the light oh wait there's one closer
here
that should be same direction
as the
our Quest goal
and experience that when you were
younger I don't think I ever was put
into a corner but I also don't think
it's really a common practice in
Austrian
schools or generally I guess also not in
families
different cultures different ways of
punishing your kids how would my mom
punish me I don't think she ever really
like had to punish me
no
I mean sometimes I think sometimes she
would threaten with turning off
maybe internet
Maybe
uh
or like make TV or or PC unaccessible by
like cutting off the electricity or
something like that I don't know
oh pretty pink
yeah
no no
spanking nah I think spanking your kids
is
extremely uncommon
in
Austria and like Germany too
[Music]
yeah
there is no such thing as a chancla
here you were spanked
damn I don't know I would never do that
to my kids if I had kids like anything
like I I just don't think
that
that is a good way to
teach your kids they did something wrong
so I'm generally completely against
that type of education
[Music]
I had this discussion like many many
years ago
people that weren't not from my culture
or country and they were like
like portraying me as a completely crazy
person for having this opinion like
oh she's so stupid so so crazy like
don't listen to her like absolutely
bad [\h__\h]
but okay that is
how are you guys been
differently
I don't want I don't want to walk into
the gloomy [\h__\h]
yeah I just think
I mean I I look at me
I never did like crazy [\h__\h] as a child
but I also was never really
um
what's the word again
disciplined
with
physical I mean I don't want to go as
far and call it violence because it
doesn't it doesn't
feel to me like it's the same kind of
violence as you know
but but I turned out great
that turned out great right
and never in my life
took drugs or smoked I ignore alcohol
and I mean I wouldn't say that's because
I I wasn't disciplined
I don't know I think a lot of it is is
my nature too you know just by default I
am just Pleasant
yes
because as I said there was no
discipline necessary so I didn't make
trouble to begin with
so I'm just by Nature Good
but then if I did something bad I don't
think it would have helped if my mom
would have disciplined me with
spanking or whatever I would have
I would have turned that worse I think
to be honest
I would have became a rebel actually
yeah I do think I would have gone the
other way but that's just me personally
because that that would just piss me off
so much
and feel really unfair and and not right
to me
um
is there spanking in the usual room if
you do like it no if you don't like it
maybe
you know whatever makes you unhappy is
what happens in the usual room
personally adjusted very very good
service
don't like it at all you can't lie the
usual room knows what your true feelings
are
what's the sound
can't lie to the usual room
[Music]
almost sounds like I'm making it up have
you not been to the usual room yet
you should know it's real
oh
be close already
I think
it might be another light root
okay A little monster camp on the web
don't really want to be bothered with it
but they I don't know should we
okay nice perfect timing to shoot that
I well that one missed
sometimes they miss when the path is too
obstructed oh
oh wait I should use unable against that
dude
wait
I want to I really want to
so let's second
ly showing new battle skills
honestly it feels like something I
learned in the Wind Waker
[Music]
wait I wanted to switch weapon
look at that nice
can I pick that up no
[Music]
I don't know I know I told I totally
know how I did that oh I don't know
[Music]
thank you but what's what do you mean
there's no effect on you don't don't
spread this propaganda
[Music]
shush now go to sleep
do you want to get spanked
immortal
everybody fears the usual room
even I fear it
I would never anger myself
because I don't want to end up in the
usual room
I will always keep myself happy and
satisfied so that that doesn't happen
foreign
take your own medicine
yo there's a lot of large solenoid here
okay
we need more anyway I have barely been
in the underground
do you guys like the other which which
one do you like more the the sky I mean
it's maybe a unfair uh comparison
because there is less to explore in the
sky somehow although each island is like
more special maybe sky or Underground
the deaths easily on the ground more fun
[Music]
um
kind of I think everybody you know when
they teased
um the fact that you there's a lot of
like Sky action going on
people probably expected a bit more
Islands
so bad but then you compare it to the
huge underground which literally covers
the whole map
now that's so different however I think
like
um
the sky has a lot of special things
going on like the underground you know a
lot of it
yeah it's big but a lot of it is just
like you know running
running running
on well dark ground sure
some enemy camps here and there
but you know all of that there's a lot
of just like
well
you know not so special stuff
well when you do go to Sky Island you
can be pretty sure that it has a shrine
or one of those uh big boss enemies or
it has
uh
uh I don't know the capsules
or it has those monuments that have to
be translated you know every island at
least does have something special
oh the diving quests yeah
there's always something special
it would have been cool though if there
were more a couple maybe at least one or
two more of those big ass islands like
the one that you start off at in the
very beginning that would have been nice
like bigger complexes of islands right
they put too much stuff in the sky then
it's just another ground if they put too
much I'm not saying make it like cover
the full sky
well I think you guys know what I mean
what is that
weird
anyway we were going this way
room for dlcm oh true
they don't have to use the
main grounds that they had in breath of
the Wild
anymore for DLC
true
they could put it like literally
anywhere
I don't know
[Music]
you haven't gotten the
whoa spoiler
oh you little [\h__\h]
whoa
did you do that on purpose like
huh
that's
yeah the thing is okay I already
accidentally read about that
or or maybe saw it in like a cotk video
so I recently did get spoiled about that
let's say I didn't because it was really
recently
after my last tltk stream I think let's
say it didn't then you would have been
the one to follow me
you easily could have been and that is
the thing that is and up until now I'm
so far in the game and I would normally
have no idea about it so it's a very
well protected secret in the game
how can you go into a streamer's chat
and
like oh
mention something like that
oh think
oh no it's a white one
in armor
okay
good start
wait does he even have armor on maybe
not okay yeah
does he see me hello
I'm not sure if he does
I blasted it up nice okay
yeah because it looked like to me like
is he hello
is she like super dizzy
did I bug him
wait Lego no no no no no no no no no no
no
no no
I'm killing you before you're leaving me
no no no hell no ah he realized now
because I got rid of his weapon and
that's probably overriding the bug
she's
[\h__\h] annoying
annoying
yeah get him funeral
finally
that was weird wasn't it
the model fruit Maybe
but already before I hit the Mumford I
think he was already weird
[Music]
take his horse I don't know where it
went
but often I like I really just like even
if it's slow I just like walking I don't
know
gives me more control
horses especially the skeleton horses
because you can't really tame them
properly they're just like doing
whatever
the horse can ride over Gloom I know I
know I know but still
I kind of like walking
[Music]
sending them off
you like walking on the ground too which
is so stupid though because it's so
[\h__\h] big it's literally the whole map
all over again so walking is really
not smart but you know
it's like we're on a hike yeah a big ass
never-ending hike
uh the little frogs are coming
[Music]
I'm a very forgiving person so the
person who spoiled me if you're still
watching I will forgive you but damn
don't ever do that again think about it
if you go into any other totk streamers
chat
better to not ask such a question
I know the good thing with like breath
of the wild is that
you kind of know how far they are in the
game by looking at the top left of the
screen
here you don't really know I have four
sages but depending on who I have I
often I don't people wouldn't have all
of them packed out so
can't really know
for sure but you know
room in the gauntlet what do you mean
room in the gauntlet
see I I have I had no idea that there
would be a fifth one
absolutely no idea
and I don't know who it would be
what did you just tell me it's Zelda but
um can you not
yeah
what the [\h__\h] is going on stop following
me guys
it's Tangled
huh
[Music]
I literally just said I don't know what
okay at least 13 percent
it's beetle
yeah maybe maybe some things well and
let's dance let's hope let's just think
even if it wasn't maybe you guys are
being nice to make me The Gaslight me
positively nicely kindly
yes I will accept the gas lighting
holy [\h__\h] what is this place
that's our goal right
was it
no
I don't say colgar
yeah it's a big fighting arena
and see the statues would have
led me all the way here
don't know why they needed to because
they didn't do it with um
these statues
they didn't show me in the quest that it
would be here
are you
I wonder if I'm close enough I they saw
me huh yeah nice
one also reached nah I can't okay no
problem no problem
um
they did how I found the central one
what they did yeah
Why did no did I really because I like
went out of my way to Mark Ever every
every
single one until I actually saw
the real thing did I just not Mark the
quest or what if I would have marked the
quest would I have seen it is that the
problem
Koka
wait why are you here
this does not bode well
can we talk right now are you in
protective mode you're in protective
mode
can I probably can't I can't really
shoot him can I
okay let's just catch it his other
ninjas
his underlings
haven't been catching it come on do
something
uh
let's explain it to him in easy words
it's the right hand right so why is it
not working I don't know what voice I
did for him
go back there take over
another yiga
if I would take over
um
I would make it work but no
it's you again
so link you just had to follow me here
didn't you
I'm doing what you did exactly but it
refuses to work you tricked me I won't
stand for this
okay you wasted someone I'll battle you
I'll beat you an Australia power
people from you prepare yourself
doya where are you going yeah okay
do I have to go there right away
who can I listen for to the soundtrack
for a while oh
wait I am here
no you're making it too easy no way
[Music]
[Laughter]
still then yeah but I think everybody
has at least some eyeballs with them
right
but without
I wonder
[Music]
loving the soundtrack
right you are huh
oh there's a trampoline there by the way
you went back up there
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
stop right there
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
I love the shamisen in it too damn
um
get up link no time to waste
where is he
oh
oh I
what's that Shield up
no problem eh wait this is a problem
nah
wait that was too much into the middle
of nowhere and
but I fell down too did you get them
yeah okay wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
wait wait when he just when you get him
like too far away then it's too much of
a long ass path
ah
okay please go around it
no
[Music]
I mean okay let's look pretty good
invention a
good aim man but he's got an auto aim
don't doesn't he
foreign
that's not what I wanted
good aim bro
okay that's that's relatively close
oh did he get rid of his no
barriers
[Music]
foreign
I swear
I will I will stay with my strategy this
should work come on
yeah but he improved a lot since last
time we fought him
I'll give him that is
[Music]
different right but it's also really
cool
oh my God it keeps getting in my eyes
so I'm going to let you off easy again
the Hulk of Joe course
you want to watch
I quit you don't want it anymore I found
that power might make things easier but
it's just the icing I'm wrapped a cake
we've been collecting a mighty power
Powers life's charges and we're going to
your weapon for the man himself the mega
never send one Ganon
once we do we'll Grant his wish for the
end of the world no I don't need the
power you stole our collection of
crystallized charges is well underway
and the restoration of the final weapon
is closer turned
so yeah if you want this empty shell you
can have it online
the Eastern abandoned mine
all right buddy
[Music]
is
such a cartoon villain yeah I love it
too he's very likable greetings
thank you for trying out the trespasser
idiot I overheard your conversation you
spoke loudly enough you voiced him
loudly enough that it was difficult not
to the Eastern abandoned mine that man
spoke of is most likely the abandoned
lanaelu mine
it is extremely far from here you will
not find Stone guide posts to it in this
area I suggest ascending to the surface
first you may be able to find a Chasm
leading or Chasm I don't know
leading there in the region to the east
there are two chasms in the region to
the east that contains don't guide those
okay oh [\h__\h] feeling weird recall number
blah blah blah blah blah
there's one more thing
my associate over there at Manchester's
schema Stones you may want to ask for
one
um
will do
no oh no no it's okay 100.
I'm hungry
all this turnover has led to supply
maybe that's my problem too Supply
shortage in the basis do you know how
hard it is to find the banana
the deaths are completely so nothing
around here seems in the least a bit
edible you'd think that every take that
seriously and respect the ingredient and
foods that but no that Red's new recruit
ate a whole shipment of bananas the
moment I took my eyes off of them from
now on I'm keeping my own Supply what if
you what if you shoot an arrow with a
banana attached to it
would that make him happy maybe he would
try to be friends
brilliant
[Music]
authorizer verified
welcome this was once a busy Refinery
where a great deal of the night was
processed my task here is to manage
designs for mining equipment please take
this beautiful schema
don't
oh their own version of a hover
hovercraft hovercraft but mine is much
cheaper probably
try out there's it might be a bit more
stable
I will also prepare the parts required
to test it oh thank you
I don't know where I would be going oh
dad though
I'm curious about one other thing do you
know what other milk will do if you have
oh yeah I know this in you
thank you
have you no stock yet or what
foreign
that one doesn't fly just Glide oh
that one's good for sand oh oh
hovercraft makes me think of that game
that I'm I'm still waiting for
continuation a sequel for
um
was it
well what was it um
yeah Beyond Good and Evil
you know me
what why am I what I already know what
you're doing
oh
I could almost take four hmm
but I might take these all yeah
there's a girl
amazing
charges
oh thank you
yeah 15 years of development
chances are
non-existent
so sad
so sad isn't there a light Road here
look I saw one
there is right yeah
I trust me to open my eyes perhaps also
ah
up there is that the closest one
also what is a sparkly stuff that looks
like a fairy almost
we should go up there
where is the start here
I'll pick up those failed eyeballs
up we go
Duke no new cam forever how long was
that in development
also 15 years or longer
14 feet okay well I mean yeah
never give up
is what we should take from that oh wait
is that just like nothing
that's just the top from the the mine
hmm
this stuff should I is that worth like
climbing up no
where should I go wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait the Lightroom orientation
um
and I just see it
we're gonna go
Maybe
ascending
Blind Boys above me
what can I do wait
normally they're pretty low
but here we go another light root oh
okay also connected
and
we took Colgate down should we go for
the next one too
why are IPO because
it should be easy to find yeah but we
they recommend to leave the underground
ones
and come back
YouTube
it was such an experience but he did
kind of
give me some trouble didn't he
let's be real
we used hovercraft for large crystals
if I just go straight
how do I know where to go
oh wait there's something over there
over hovercraft
[Music]
is it that one there
whoa I mean that's good for traversing
here as well because there's so much
glue
[Music]
ah yeah that's the one okay good
um oh they're connected with tutorials
I'll give you stuff okay maybe we can go
this way before we go
I don't know I kind of want to make use
of this right now
yes
and on the way we can
open
up some light roots
oh no
you want travel make it double no
why are we hello I'm aiming to the left
is it like we're in inverted
don't get it
look no no
oh man
go right side yes okay finally oh
oh it's kind of fast
oh God
well I see a light rude we'll stop there
possibly
oh
or we'll stop earlier
oh no
is this a white one again
I'm not wait they're just
we could take the horse
what was that
was a real ack moment
[Music]
will you please stop annoying me
oh
don't die
[Music]
moving on my battery recharge
welcome snowboarding
ah yeah
my game lagged damn
okay
too much information
for the game
ah oh no
up a mountain seems
very difficult
I'm coming I'll give it a no try more
power
you can know it
memberships blank you again wow
how do you do it
all right I just want to go like little
bits
and then
bring it over
um
and then we can continue moving oh
was I going for this one
oh a cemetery
wait is that a kitto
yeah uh hell no
should I explore maybe maybe there's a
treasure here too that I don't have the
treasure map for yet
oh it's flying ones too
wait what was that that I I like um
I
oh wait elements elements
right these also don't like elements
Mickey
or they don't yeah
was it like I saw some jerk some meme
about ah let's make them fly what no no
they can fly now
something like that
I know a meme guys celebration
yeah they're fine it's a star was
reference right yeah
you will not know how I got it
should I tell you my secret
Star Wars
I watched the teal 2K
[Music]
cutie cake
[\h__\h] I can't reach
um
uh
lore video kind of
[Music]
and it talked a little bit about give
the history and I don't know
and and and the meaning of them whatever
into Decay whatever
and it had this joke
okay if you why were you worried that I
got it from actually Star Wars
what the hell
is that some kind of Shield or something
eat damn
Griffin
oh is it from the sequel Trilogy that
people don't like as much
oh yeah more gito bones give it to me
love I want to use them more oh I know
that so is this possible does anybody
know that this is a treasure
um
yeah
Treasure Chest Treasure no no no map
treasure map treasure no no maybe not
that one usually they're like armor
pieces right
um
not this one really
grape robbing
I think they don't mind also the poles
they're supposed to be brought back
we gotta bring them back
uh is that all here
what are you doing
buddy
[Music]
thank you so much for the pinky
don't worry I mean I I'm kind of feel
the same you know I want to thank you
guys
over and over again but it'll always
like maybe sound repetitive
can't help it
that's how it is
that's why I don't like long Super Chat
readings because then it sounds like I'm
just repeating myself I kind of am
MO
Chad
okay
um this area might be kind of difficult
for Maya
but crap so let me move it a little bit
as we're going I think
for that
oh
root over there
you think so I think I come up with new
ways really
I know I wish I mean I feel like if I
knew if English was my first language
I feel like I would be able to
think of more
sometimes I'm just stuck with the same
vocabulary
over and over and over again
[Music]
oh really you get stuck here no way
ah no way
you're kidding me now what
what
did I break it
no no look online
[Music]
the ground is too solid
s
oh nice
yeah
okay
all right let me um and then we'll move
on I'll just place no hovercraft
somewhere here
oh because it's a sled
oh yeah okay I guess that makes sense
not much hovering going on
should have a fan underneath then it
would be hovering
ah wait
I don't know what's that
a bombs
I've been wasting a lot of bombs today
kind of need them
I can go walking yeah but then my mind
was my hovercraft
we got it so we might as well use it
yay light root
oh it's the bottom left the corner of
the very corner of the map and looks
very interesting
some interesting looking things there
[Music]
um
oh
that's why I'm going
I mark it oh wait it's kind of marked
here I might go on my foot and then we
go leave the hovercraft behind anyway
because after I get the treasure I will
return
to the overground
nice
sorry I accidentally returned
looks like you missed the light root
yeah it's okay
is it at the top
okay
no problem
that's what I got these for today
oh don't tell me it's not at the top
[Music]
is it just that the entrance is on a
different side
um that looks like maybe it's the
entrance over there yeah
I think so
north side yeah I was thinking so too
the bigger
looking gate
that's not like all broken
what
oh
it's [\h__\h] scary it
can I even touch that
safe oh I'm scared it's like a Coliseum
all right instincts no
what what how can I fight what what what
big boss could spawn here when there's
low ceilings
it is a closer
one of the colosseums
ah
no problem
oh but they're white ones we never had
those before I think
[Music]
I currently don't really have
really strong weapons I
guess I'll use this
huh oh wait what
why so nah that's not all right there
will be more
a little bit more
ah wait those were the weakest ones not
the white ones this is where ah
will they get all of them
like I shouldn't give so much
[Music]
oh okay I understand so one of these
colosseums is all lionels and then this
one's this one is all horror blends
and then there's like others with other
types of enemies
come down
wait don't hit me
[Music]
oh
shh you killed or you helped kill your
friends
that one's not bad
um
is that something good to fuse I don't
care whatever whatever it is it will do
uh maybe
that was good that was good
that was good it's got electric slime on
ah
Defying Gravity
[\h__\h] help
okay
[Music]
wait what the [\h__\h] why am I even wearing
this
oh but interestingly I no never mind no
no no no switch right now girls which
[\h__\h] am I wearing here
foreign
[Music]
something that raises attack do I have
something
no
shock resistance cold cold weather
attack speed up ah here
oh
[\h__\h]
but maybe I should get the others out
though
help me a little bit we're in an icky
yucky situation
[Music]
nice
next please oh it's only one it's
getting less and less will the next door
open up zero times whatever the next
color is but this is a white one anyway
oh
[Music]
girls the boys help me out here come on
we're standing in the circle literally
and my stamina can go endlessly
oh it broke though
foreign
I'll take the fire one
oh that's
it okay
uh wait
um please don't come so fast because I
need to
find the right thing to fuse
[Music]
um
uh oh wait those are fused anyway but
they're kind of weak too
let's use the Bratz whatever
um
maybe this
oh
silver horribling horn
looks kind of cool
oh they're still so far
okay let's get them all down at once
shall we
[Music]
are fighting the silver one with his own
horn very effective myself
foreign
[Music]
day today much action
[Applause]
dead
[Music]
that was good yeah
I'm gonna pick up some things that I
want
[Music]
might be
better than what I have because of the
base weapon
oh
they like to use these like Stone like
weapons with stones attached for some
reason why
it drops shield and weapon from uh
which ones is this mine that might be
mine I don't think they would make this
is this mine yep
I totally forgot that thanks for telling
me
yeah because Bach is the coolest NAB not
with the stones that's lame
[Music]
because they're on the ceiling they need
the range if that makes sense oh [\h__\h]
oh my God
is this it's not the same
[Music]
what are you telling me there's a Chic
set
you don't have that one yet it's at the
uh here very bottom left
in the Coliseum
hey yo I just randomly once here okay
right now it doesn't look so cool yet
because I don't I only have the head but
damn
[Music]
oh my God
whoa I need the full outfit is is are
the other ones like Treasures close by
are they
um
like scattered all over but the problem
is they're like there's so many
treasures and so only masks
oh oh I guess so oh and does is it the
same like do I get a bonus from
combining outline this
oh
I mean that makes sense yeah
it kind of belongs together
you only got the head
no sad bonus oh okay so a lot of these
are just basically for you know
you know
feeling cute
feeling cute taking an Instagram pic and
deleting it later
okay did I even check this out yeah
for fashion yeah you know in those
YouTube videos I keep on seeing
um this one clothing set first I thought
it was maybe like a mod
but I see it all the time so I guess you
can actually get it there's one where
your whole head gets replaced
with a cute link
um
I don't know which one it is
kind of cartoony
yeah it doesn't look like it doesn't
look like the Wind Waker Link to me but
it's some cute one
hook
there's nothing here
oh it is marked here though
but maybe at the head there's something
maybe a treasure
[Music]
my my hovercraft would be nice here
um
yeah
no
no no
I have the other things to do anyway
someone
[Music]
if I kill them they're gonna respond
Shadow I don't want to fight them here
no no no no no
bye bye I'll come another time
out
no the problem is here there's so much
ground that I can't walk on the whole
ground was covered
thank you
wait a second you
guys
is this
supposed to look as disgusting as it
looks like to me
this
is like a face a disgusting face of
something I've seen before
ew
it's disgusting
it looks like something
disgusting
okay we are going into uh
[Music]
I mean this is the only one I can really
see
so I suppose this one
there's a chance I'm on the tourism in a
bit hard to find
that's all right then
green
ah wait I already seen it is that the
one I marked
um
maybe maybe
I can go to that Shrine that I see at
the top of some building
might as well
do that
looks like the aliens from those it
reminds me of some kind of yeah some
character some aliens or
something really
creepy I wonder if that's on purpose
anyway
we do the shrine then from the shrine
also we can
jump easily over
to the chasm
um yeah yeah maybe from early Azora
designs they look this creepy
oh there's a glioc there
is it like a the electricity one
well if we ever feel like fighting them
then with the shrine we'll have an easy
path to this one
um
whatever
I just don't want to die will go very
quickly
oh no no no no
no no no
oh there's a cannon there
can we activate it and shoot the Dragon
that must be why it's located like that
hidden item
what in those ruins
a prone pamphlet what does that mean
I know prone to be prone to do something
it's like to be likely to do something
I think
very hidden La silly
ah the old broken Fortress
[Music]
it's like crawling okay
why did they leave me up here
hungry wow
I need to cook today
I'm making sausage something with
sausages
[Music]
oh
sausages I don't know it's like real
sausages
what is that oh
hell no
I am
oh no you I'm getting dizzy and this
feels like it's a breath of the wild uh
thingy
[Music]
oh yeah
can I already open it I'm guessing not
okay but wait
I turn it again
then I can reach it right
oh wait
[Music]
I can't climb them can I
all right
foreign
[Music]
am I supposed to like create a path
to go left
up
well how would I do that
huh
wait I guess I can shoot
things
I want
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
um oh
what what
no it's too big brain for me
what happens when I do this no
no no no no
what's here there's no chest here
that's what I wanted to do first anyway
before I leave you know
thank you
[Music]
now I'm getting so hungry
do I need more nuts I don't think the
nuts will chocolate though
will be more helpful oh
no proper food
oh damn
my taste on
well I can't
I don't understand
I don't got him
[Music]
heck
why
please tell me
oh
[Music]
ah okay
I've done very well today
so far
right
okay now
[Music]
um
I'm eating my Taser
the chocolate balls
um
I figure out the rest
I'll mess it up
um
[Music]
I mean I can't shoot the outside one so
this one but
um
but it will go left
oh
um
[Music]
come on
solve it I didn't solve anything
um
[Music]
oh
yeah
I was like even if I ascend
um
because it like sticks to the ceiling I
won't go out anywhere but okay you want
me to go to the top
um
[Music]
shall we shoot it again
like from here
and jump why don't I do this
[Music]
thank you
that is six shrines today
um
we're not done yet
we're kicking colgar's ass once again
I I wanna cash remember I just you know
I'm busy
oh there's no rain
I thought that was a permanent thing
because of the Dragon
um
there's a hidden treasure here
we might as well try to find it while
we're here
let's see how hidden it is
so stupid to have a stone on them
on the Pokey weapon sometimes
uh
can they go up here
please say no
yeah okay I think no
but do I really want to waste like 20
bombs again
at least we both took damage
wait
it's starting to thunder again I think
is it isn't it
not wait
and they're all sparked nah
no they're not spark these are different
sparkles right
um
okay
it's okay link it's okay you'll be fine
I'll protect you
I'll I'll make sure
and you'll be all right
well just trap them you know
drop them like they're hot
drop them carefully I actually think 10
bombs might be enough right
oh they're done
huh yeah
wait does he not always spawn I want to
fight him
hey
oh no
it doesn't take too long
they're running what
um they were basically dead
all right now
um
I had a lot of confidence now to take
care of them on my own
what is it
huh
so I didn't check here oh my God
okay
where could this treasure be if I were a
game designer
um in here huh
okay because there's a bunny
I think that's all a bunny
no wait
no my oh no scratchy Massacre
whoa I didn't think that would hit us
um
okay
wait before that I just saw that the
light here was on and thought that was
kind of sussy but is it in the cave or
is it in here
[Music]
is that the treasure
I know the hole but you know
that one looks so good and combination
with that silver Hopper probably because
the um the handle
it's pink and purple
okay
okay oh my God I'm addicted ah
[Music]
this is nice too though
even if that's not a treasure
and I probably would have forgotten
about it if I would have gone into you
okay first
can I use my normal weapons again
huh
oh it's one of those okay wow
normally these things are in like pretty
big caves but this is like nothing
wow wow
[Music]
Majora's Mask
um
I know
I just I I just came here randomly
when I get such a nicer one oh wait
continues
yeah because there needs to be
a frog
so you get the coolest thing first
and then you get the Frog
I forgot about the Frog
yeah if you guys didn't
get this armor yet then go get it now
it's over here wait should I just ascend
that was I think the whole cave
we have before
[Music]
I'm sorry but chocolate
is the goat
where am I going
ah green
and it's helping me
stream a little while longer and get
over the pain of having an empty tummy
besides the music video that I mentioned
that came out
um
did you see it
the program that was you know used to
announce it
um
that was fun but um
I think it was
pretty or not not as early as it usually
is when I yeah
[Music]
when I record like Japanese programs
um I don't know of any shrines caused by
yeah I don't know I don't know I don't
even remember the time and let me go to
this route
yeah but it was fun I kind of was mixed
with free council members
but it was a nice
uh recording it was really fun
oh so what am I going don't hurt
yourself what is this
what is this
everything was a mommy question I think
I was pretty good at like you know I
have my own opinion we have our own
opinions about
what we think matches
the
well question
but and usually I would say because we
know each other better our opinion would
be the correct thing the correct answer
but I think I had a good sensor as to
what audience the overall audience would
vote for
um
she's been
Ma I'm seeing moderating these
programs of whole life English Channel
like damn girl
she has
so many jobs to do now
[Music]
as if she's not already plenty busy with
whole life Japan work I feel bad that
she has to do what kind of
hit song
foreign
but still I feel all bad about it about
you know because it takes up a lot of
time recording it and she also like she
must
she can't just go in without like
studying the script a little bit so she
had to
he has to study the script a little bit
too so you know
she can't just walk into the studio and
take notebook
not the script I think she does like
study it a little bit
um
yeah but
she's she's
really fun like she she has quite the
personality it's nice when you know
there's what are we doing here anyway
when there's someone like you know a
staff member who can double as basically
an idol
that's really cool
thank you
like certain staff members
will have like a very special
personality to them
that
following me it was used for content
you know she's been there since the
beginning with soda Senpai so
oh
so that yeah
I think she's just always taking up this
role
there's a lot of white ones
but what is this place
I guess there's there should be a name
to it I feel like but only when I really
enter it
I don't know if I wanted it's not what
we came here for where's the ah over
here
yeah it's like a mine so maybe there's
also a proper treasure there
um
how cute is the IRL
I would say it's just pretty cute
very sweet
I would say her how she looks on the
internet matches
pretty well
this is not completely you know
pulled out of nowhere
um
go back to where I came from
she's found to be around just
understanding
[Music]
and she has you know a good
grasp
of what's going on with in whole life
all the time
no I like she offered to even even
though like you know to be honest it's
um since she's her whole life Japan
she doesn't really have
I would say she doesn't really have much
like power to do things
uh for us in whole life English
oh but she did like
say that we can always go to her if we
have concerns or something like that
I think I did that once yeah
doctor it's a long time ago
would I
opened up my
concerns about some topics there are
ones I don't even remember what it was
about
[Music]
a long time ago
yeah like a counselor yeah yeah
and honestly
I can understand like you know why
people why members would feel like they
want to talk to her I mean I I also
really like you know Gemma but sometimes
you for at least at least for Ian I feel
like maybe there's like certain topics
where we feel like
we want to reach the Japanese side
and
that's not so easy maybe what the [\h__\h]
do I go
should I take that elevator that I saw
try
I haven't meant to go inside of my
direct line manager yeah maybe it's
something like that comparable
[Music]
yeah that's elevator should probably
help me
Pura will give me advice I know what to
do
I'm just saying how do I get to what I
want to do
I'm not out of ideas of what to do
something to do in tutk
I
he died fast
there must be can very much imagine it
must be in Liz Alpha's uh
Coliseum as well right
yeah
oh there's another elevator is that an
elevator
but now I think I can walk around here
maybe
one for each major enemy type
you call it totec
never found it I assume there's none
well
yeah I want more silver monster items a
[\h__\h] hell he's not very good either
should I take make a Hovercraft
I wonder if I can go around the corner
here
[Music]
yeah but normally you know I would
pronounce it in German b-o-tv
this discussion before it just makes
more sense in German
in English b-o-t-w is just too stupid
because you guys
if you're English pronunciations
have
stupid pronunciation for just the letter
w
it's really dumb
it's not even a w if anything it's a
double v
because it's spiky it's edgy
Ryan think about it
there's a lot of the weapon guys here if
I even have a slot
never got it either
Oh Long fro
I can't carry it though
oh yeah I'll take it
what does it mean when when the arrow
goes down does it do less damage than
usual it's kind of lame
damn I've been saying so many white
moblins now
I guess because I did all four dungeons
sheesh okay
ah oh it's just less damage than
whatever I'm carrying now oh
foreign
was used as the letter u
but then the legendary
's gotta go
well at least you didn't refuse to
elaborate you definitely elaborated
before you left yeah
noise
thank you for the knowledge but yeah I
don't know it's just stupid
we also don't say double foul
that's also how it's pronounced I think
always
that's how it's pronounced in like words
also I mean there is
this how you pronounce it in
worldwide you know World Wide Web
that's kind of how you
pronounce it in English too
you guys could have gone the same path
but you refused it
English language
[Applause]
oh he's got armor
got him got him got him
I know I was just a shield
what are you throwing
[Music]
up Lord no instrument and then got along
swimmingly oh
sad
that was such a cool weapon
uh
but now at least I won't feel so bad
about using the the mob the white moblin
attachments because
we're meeting them so often down here
it's a good game you just finished it
well please don't spoil me
[Music]
careful
okay
cleaned
one
up now
that's cat hairs on my nose it's so
itchy
I mean yeah you can spoil me with love
and
sweetness
and maybe with super chats
oh yeah oh yeah
I guess okay don't spoiler me
um
hold on
no don't spoil my little teotic case
only if I
explicitly ask them which I wouldn't do
I know I ask a lot of like theoretical
questions over rhetorical or not really
meant to be answered
all right
let's go which way this way
[Music]
okay
land both landed on some kind of enemy
camp
[Music]
um
and I see no roots at all
what the [\h__\h]
there
uh
[Music]
foreign
okay I'll fight you maybe
laughs
it's just a lot less tiny Camp anyway
no problem
guys take care of them
and I of the real enemies oh my God
useless ah there it goes
foreign
cute boss
[Music]
oh oh that's what that is I saw it and I
was like thinking maybe it's a like a I
don't know it's so nice thingy robot oh
my god well it kind of this what's in
the underground have we seen one in the
underground before
oh
no I guess everything can be found in
the underground
yeah I guess in the Maze yeah but I
thought that would be like a one-time
only thing
that's kind of the opposite direction
though
damn
okay uh it's the smartest way to get
around here without wasting my speed
boost
foreign
okay
why
normal water
so I have heard that
the what like if there is a
Mountain
and the normal world
then there will be the opposite of the
mountain
in the underground
inverted yeah
Maybe
when they created the underground
they took a height map as I've learned
that these things exist
they took a height map
of
the totk world that they created
and then just inverted it
I mean okay it's understandable like not
wanting to
go through all of that work
can I land somewhere thank you
to create all of that
so they found
somewhat of an easy way to do it we're
kind of there
I just need to
orientate myself
um
okay
oh
is it behind this mountain
person just makes it interesting like
the surface
what why because you kind of know what
they're what will be there is that what
you're saying
yeah our nose
places of making Hyrule again at a
similar level of detail manually with
beans and yeah
I feel like
um
it would have been an option to kind of
go the sky island route
[Music]
and just make
like itsy bitsy bits of underground that
are like
like cut off by Big Mountain rocks
that I would say could be in the
underground too of course
[Music]
oh that's in the water
let's have this you guys map right oh
there you are
[Music]
it's like
very very
impressive and overwhelming what why
did I never pick that up before I guess
not so it's behind me but it's
[Music]
what I use that my last
rocket Shield
how'd I
how do I get there from here
it's very high
hot air balloon yeah okay
okay I'll make something
Ariel Cannon
we think but we haven't tried out yet we
think that this one's for
reaching certain Heights I don't know if
it's more reliable than the hot air
balloon
that's what gonna make a hot air balloon
okay it only needs six
wow I know oh no oh no
let's place it somewhere where we have
uh stable ground and nothing above us
standing now
but we need fire right
I love hiero collapses in the
underground which we're just under
underground
no
underground deception
oh a flamework oh a flame sword
lies
I only have three flavors can I use do I
have to make a fire a fireplace
or is only a thigh of fruit enough
let's Place wood
hi okay okay
it's slow but it's working and it's not
using batteries
[Music]
um
isn't it gonna disappear though
like isn't it gonna stop burning
and poof
isn't that what items do
not end time soon okay
yeah it's slowly reaching our cruising
height of
000 meters
for each Dad please stay seated in your
ear
in your seats with your seat belts
and yeah you know closed and don't go to
the toilet now please don't use them
yeah don't don't open up the bins where
your stuff is yet because things may
fall out my experience some turbulences
I will let you know when we reach our
cruising height I think we need to tap
oh did we
oh is there more
a little bit more
I guess I could maybe rewind it or
whatever
[Music]
you should I'll be in another airplane
soon
airplanes airplanes airplanes
more air travel
hopefully this time things will go well
because like recently I've been always
so unlucky of traveling
um like so often my flights are being
canceled and delayed and it was like
fully booked or the flight is not
available or the pilot is not available
whatever it's just ridiculous
wait I have to go even higher
I think I really shouldn't have taken
this path
I thought it was over there over there
yeah it's hard to see you have no idea
usually everything's pretty flat
I know this
ah
is it so high here because there's water
here
holy oof
um
yeah it's like we want to go here
that means it will it will also be at
the top of a mountain
oh
in the summer no I'm talking about like
oh February
and January
I'll have trouble
during my
flights there to like my return flights
um
it was always my return flight but it
was okay it was okay because like that
was a long stay
um I mean I wanted to go home but at
least it wasn't like anything cutting my
stay short
I guess it's summer in Australia
finding the statues
ah oh
wait if I charge it can it go further
or is it just stronger
God damn it
I want to see more
if that goes too high oh
is it that far but wait there's also
something here that's like low so
okay uh
anyway I'm going there
is but it's the opposite direction
but that looks kind of like a path maybe
I don't know
wait let's go here
it's a bit closer
ah
I lit up a lot of the area down here
Ah that's weird
that's weird one that I saw before nah
can't be I saw it at the bottom left of
the map right
but there's never of those like robots
bosses
in the middle of the dark there
yeah then I see it at the in the bottom
left of the map what
um
oh there oh there
hmm okay
well
you know what
[\h__\h] it
[Music]
I'll try I mean it's really hard when
you can't see what the [\h__\h] is that
what the [\h__\h] is that
there's a root
huh
don't go that sir ah
it is it it is
[Music]
because it reminds me of that zooming
cute
no way I didn't know they could be here
what okay they literally put every enemy
down here
is it more challenging
what would I oh yeah
can it save me if I
eat some of this
okay yeah yeah but land I want to Land
once anyway
how do I go down
[Music]
you didn't see me I think it only starts
when you enter the circle
[Music]
oh you don't take damage but it feel I
feel like my hover bike broke
just now
I don't know
ah wait it makes sense
here because that is I guess
where we fought
the boss so there are there are they at
the same locations
as their real counterparts oh
no it didn't break oh did it looks like
it broke like the other fan popped off
looks
yeah what the [\h__\h]
is it difficult should we find it
hey wait it wasn't always like this
right
about the same difficult what do you get
what do you get for a desert chest
oh
I don't know
I had to use some
sit on a lot right
let's turn off
Julian
and maybe unable
or an opal stuff I think I still have
one yeah
all right see them are you ready for a
little deja vu
I did not think this would happen but we
are going to fight your friend again
[Music]
fight it
you're just trying to catch it oh
what
la la la la la la
Maybe
something that makes me stronger but I
don't really have I mean I have the Alex
here I could take
Alex here
oh wait
no I'm already healed oh anyway I guess
okay
um
thank you
for reminding me once again
that was good right oh yeah
um
[Music]
yay
rounds two out of a million
I was hitting
you little [\h__\h]
yo my weapon is so weak uh
I should use this
foreign
[Music]
let this be a lesson to you no more
infiltrating of kfb
no more
messing around with chickens
and I wanna make a weapon I can make one
out of this wait
Taco in the menu no more Taco spies
Allowed no no no
ah
there it is
[Music]
I'll use this
okay
oh no I didn't reach I guess a normal
water splash could work too but
[Music]
okay let's do like a
wait
you
we need more power okay phase two here
we go now I'm just gonna make everything
dirty
it's so like
confused and of course I spawn in the
middle of this [\h__\h]
oh
[\h__\h] hell
you felt real now bro
I don't know
okay okay
oh
boy slime stop go left right okay well
whenever I read this properly wait I
forgot but it's like only has like one
or two more hits this opal scepter
mommy might as well use it
yo thank God
I thought that did the trick where did
it go oh
and it broke mm-hmm
no no no no no no no no no no no you
little [\h__\h] hey you stay here I gotta
use the eye again I've cheese it so
often with the eye but
I don't know what else to do no
no
okay
[Music]
okay I feel like that barely did damage
what a wave is so [\h__\h] too ah
couldn't even free myself from it
[Music]
where is it
I really don't like it
hey
I don't even remember this part
sorry guys this is not an easy fight
we must struggle a little bit for
entertainment's sake
fire hydrants I am
well hmm
well none of provided here but
oh come on
I swear to God
I know I have cats those [\h__\h] there's
so many ways of I'm using so many
already anyway
does that like count as a hit
[Music]
trying to make myself some paths here
but
okay that must have counted
where are you gonna go
[Music]
check out him
okay I tried my best we're almost there
just a little bit
this [\h__\h]
is this does this count into the hundred
percent of the game if he won 100 do you
have to do this
what okay well I'm protected myself
that's fine too no yes I should I feel
like it has to
come on
yeah
[Music]
ah I'm running out of Splash roots
nice one
got it a few times before it flies
[Music]
difficult to reach for me
no not more
well if I run out of Splash fruits then
I'll bring out the fire hydrants
which will be soon
oh
I think you don't even have to hit it
with the
splash fruit but I'm still doing it why
did you deactivate because
I thought they would be in the way
[Music]
all right it might have to be with the
splash fruit
[Music]
[Applause]
I feel like this won't be the last time
either but
foreign
[Music]
I'll I'll use maybe a silver horror
button oh this one
that would look so weird
fuse I'm waiting for now I don't know
what to do with this weapon should I
really use it
I don't want to use it
I'll use this
okay
looks so weird
[Music]
hey oh
did I get it no uh
yes even out of the open yay
[Music]
I wonder what the reward is it better be
so worth it I don't even know what would
be worth it don't give me a sage well
do not dare to give me a sage as well I
haven't talked about balloons
oh God oh God I don't I don't think it
will be worth it
or is it
no
Crystal how Ard Chris okay 100 that
would be maybe okay
oh okay
now that's okay
although I feel like it should have been
200.
oh there's a have here to go I think up
to the mountain
I think that's it yeah okay
bigger batteries
yeah we have to upgrade
we definitely have to
if I I mean we should be able to right
uh in the upcoming Koga mine
normally
you can upgrade no wait no you can buy
but upgrading is only one specific place
right
I think
no I'm not almost there
um
[Music]
upgrade those in the sky yeah okay we'll
go there at the very end
but look at this we can build something
here that maybe helps us
yeah reach our destination
I don't know how high
it will get higher because there is a
water ahead of us
so we should build can we combine a
glider with a hot air balloon
or do we put fans on the hot air balloon
oh my God it's eight hours
what am I doing first of all
oh
yeah I think we got all the parts huh
don't know that
fans won't lift but it will push okay
and that's what I want anyway so we can
hide
oh if you attach and
steering wheel
can I steer it
also this goes
that way right if I place the fans like
this
it goes front right
never tried we're probably there's not
even like really actually space still so
maybe I won't
we'll just try to go in the right
direction by starting it off in the
right direction
okay okay
so we should be rising
and gliding wait
however
wait these things maybe I should set the
hot air balloon on top of one of these
because if it stops it will stay in
place right
I I hope
and how about
we add battery
it won't because it will stop floating
when you run out of the battery
oh okay
so these are not quite like the the big
Bros
there's like a bigger version of them
okay I'll attach one more battery we'll
see how far we get I mean it's not that
far away anymore
we just need some Heights and the hot
air balloon will hopefully slowly give
it to us
although now I'm wondering if we uh end
up we'll we will like probably end up
bunking against
a big wall again because we get more
distance than we get height because the
height is so slow
but oh well
you will
speaking of walls
oh
I think I think there's nothing
obstructing
oh let's go
okay
we got uh
I don't want to go that way
oh
how could I go so wrong
eh
I'm not that
if I stand on the right side we'll maybe
go to the right side
I am on my own
I will never reach this Koga place
well these are just not saved
it's just not safe
these hot air balloons
oh
maybe maybe Landon
[Music]
there's a whole and Zara City
let me know if you I don't need help
finding the entrance this is just so
happened to be like here
I don't know
look what the statue
I should have done so
it's around here a bit east
maybe maybe like here
okay but the entrance will be
significantly lower right
is that
Mountain
high five
been here before wait
have I
I mean wait what
did I plant this yeah I planted this
I'm not giving up
this one's pretty good for distance I
actually will set it as a favorite
uh
maybe another normal hot air balloon
[Music]
thanks
trying
you don't need to go up
and let me try to find statue
he was still about to ask what is that
um
foreign
could do that
true because that's like free you don't
need to pay for
tonight for like an actual
light thingy
yeah yeah I've seen people do that
you can throw I know you can throw them
but I want them to go further more full
time
ah oh no no no
has anyone seen a statue though
we are now here
where where is this entrance
can someone explain it to me
you see a nice figure what
see a nice figure
[Music]
you don't think this is the way
oh
[Music]
ah
from dark yeah the the way into the
deaths from the Zora city that you guys
told me about is kind of hard to find
with that video
easiest way of getting there well
I am I am down here now I'm kind of
committed to it you know
can't help it
the game tells you to go from kakariko
or
real
hello
it's surrounded by rock walls well yeah
I've noticed
what do you mean I activated no Shrine
here
my little Shrine here
I stand up shrine
Nani the fox
oh
yeah it was a really frustrating but no
no I've been way more frustrated before
I know it's just sad that I have to
after so much exploration
undo everything
ah is that so edo-san
you were
you were screaming right
foreign
[Music]
there's a shrine well is the
the
chasm at the front
wait is a chance in there in the water
the whirly swirly
no okay would be cool though why not why
is it not so
a lot of beautiful music here
[Music]
oh it's so relaxing I'm like in a spa
there's a Chasm behind the waterfall I
will remember that is it the big one
where the king is or was
um yeah let's go eight hours let's go
all right next to Shrine uh okay I
thought it was not next to the shrine
the power of water
okay
there's an elevator that leads up
what is this
huh
look at this
it's don't explain it
[Music]
I guess we'll do the other side first
um
well
[Music]
and now I just have to give it a push
yeah
wow still after eight hours has regained
her brain capacity and multiplied it by
300 times x
we'll find out what x is
later
[Music]
um
balls they look just like the maltes of
balls wait they're on chains
oh they can't kiss each other there is
like their lovers and they're so close
to each other
and it's so sad playing good
that brings my heart my cocoa
rocolo
imagine
if this was humans it would be so
heartbreaking what do we do here what
I'm gonna put it here
huh
hey
wait yeah maybe Axel Sarah that was my
point that's kind of the point I was
getting to later as an excuse in case in
case that there wasn't so much brain
there after all I was gonna say well X
was Zero
um
do I need the things from here
uh oh no way this thing maybe I don't
know
maybe it's a connector
I thought maybe you can solve it without
you know
it's nice to have riddles when you
there's separate
hard to reach
wait is this something that always
looks upwards like what
huh
oh wait I don't want you to look up for
it
connected
bastard
foreign
oh there's the water already kind of
connect them do I have to put it here
no
huh
I need to charge it it's a battery
who the [\h__\h] how how was that supposed
to know
oh
I thought that if I I don't know that
this is on the ground connected to over
there and you know
how much better isn't it no
does It Fade with time or refusage
we will see
whoa
reach
okay but
turn it off maybe
huh
I don't I don't know if there's
a better way to do it
and if I'll ever be able to go outside
again after opening this chest
yeah
quick quick okay
oh well I found trash anyway now
clever work around
I don't need another Red Bull the Red
Bull is what's like getting rid of my
brain cells anyway
so now
we needed for the elevator right
lemon Gatorade oh is this what this is
I think with a lemon
it work
oh wait um
with a lemon
you can make electricity right maybe I
don't know some fruit right I think wait
I think of something you can me I put
that was it the potato oh we never did
something like that in science class
oh shh
ah
[Music]
meow hey baby
getting colder better be easy because I
can't handle this much longer baby
awesome
cat picked up
will charge cat energy even if you don't
like it you're so pretty
you're so pretty even when you like warm
out of my hands because you don't want
to be
oh
[Music]
okay bye bye
that's what you get when you come here
should know by now because she's so
Square me squirmy squirmy
myself baby
oh
adios
last Touch of your fluffy tail I I love
to like run
my cat's tails between my fingers
especially when like they're walking
they I always like
you know I pet their
it
I pet their back
and then I run their tail
pull my fingers
my index in my middle finger Edge oh why
so fluffy
so good
it's so soft they're probably like why
does she always
fluff her tails what it was Ken should
live alone our Tails because I don't
think cats really like having their
tails touched normally
oh is it this waterfall
under the bridge waterfall
the one of the chasm
well now the cantarian that's my fault
oh no blood moon
[Music]
ah wait I need to see it on right should
be somewhere but it's a city
okay so I don't need to
go up maybe it's at the very bottom
behind uh-huh I
well what a great timing wait what
is it the cape on the left Bend this
blue yeah yeah yeah
okay
oh wait it wasn't Steve don't know what
makes me
go up waterfalls that's right
it's the armor cave on the Zoras Domain
and let's go
I will explore I don't care if itself if
there's something to explore uh another
time
I wonder where the frog is
okay wait
so I will spawn
um
I'll try to fly directly over there
right
I was towards the
towards the green light
what's that snow what's that
oh
okay easy
laughs
is this it
oh maybe should I do the flower first
it's basically on the same height right
okay good
I I am just like reacting like that
because I want the underground to have
more confidence
so that it thinks it is scarier than it
really is
are you telling me
that this these black parts
are walls that are so tall
that they connect you know up here so
they're literally
oh
not something you can pass okay
okay
um cool here would have been I guess the
One path oh and here oh it was close
that was close
that was cool
can I swim that distance
I was yeah I didn't see the statues
oh man
well
we finally made it it's kind of pretty
here and the water is actually really
clear
but is that bones or it looks like
fossils
I'm guessing it's also bones
kind of terrifying
you
where are we gonna fight dude
wait
let me prepare weapons
um
some weapons here
too I feel like I broke a lot
but okay wait ah
actually I don't
I'm actually
crying about the weapons anything here
uh
electricity helps along here at the
fight
um
should I remove the spiky balls
I could at least
[Music]
um
remove this one
on this one
yeah
so two weapons that should be all right
uh what am I doing
uh
um
foreign
doesn't the base weapon seem kind of
weak
I can't always I'll just do two of these
they're okay
yeah I could I could I know I know why I
know there's many places to get weapons
from
I think this is enough though
flame another club
true true
I could also try to use it but I think
it's kind of difficult to use it right
anyway
why am I doing wrong
wait we want angles off why am I
changing this voice you can no that's
still not working
whoa how long have you been there
[Music]
are you little
oh
[Music]
like I said before my plan has changed
but we already mined up our fingers I'm
around here
tell what you saw was just uh you know
I was killing time
okay okay
yeah because like adding poses to the
random [\h__\h] you say is gonna make a
better
Wawa sweep Wawa sweep that is the case
where it makes it better but but it
doesn't always work you know
persistence little [\h__\h]
in honor of our long-awaited reunion are
graciously allowed you to fight me more
than one before but right now you're the
last thing on my mind because the end is
now why am I not fighting you
okay I've got things to do so let's make
this quick
attack in the water what
oh
uh I wanted to actually hit the other
ones yeah
well I'm all right I'm supposed to take
one of these boats huh
can I shoot no I won't
supposed to
jump on his butt
what
[Music]
ah what I don't get it
ah
okay you know who could be very helpful
hello
oh took you long enough
it was like in the middle of the desk
and it couldn't stop
well now I can use it no
but it's slower Maybe
a cool fight
ER and Wild
levels now
should I practice a marine uh
impersonation
I could do it
no no I think I can do it though with
practice
yeah I heard it when I was just saying
it I felt like wait there's potential
there
anything if I impersonate something
it'll be huge squeaky voices
yeah that's why I panic you bastards
you already disappearing
I'll be controlling it
I keep on using his boats he keeps on
having to make new ones
oh now he's got a shield
does it not work anymore what oh wait it
kind of did
Missy
all good though
hey how do you break it though he just
stops eventually
I'm on your boat
he realized and he was like okay okay
okay new boat
what what
show
s
[Music]
at least I got some unable hits
get in
hi
I really don't remember any of the
any of the wait terms but that's record
pull the horse because it's like two
years ago or so that I recorded that
yeah yeah I know you're gonna leave
because I took too long
but I think we still did some damage
backboard I think was a German term for
something ship related no
you notice how we have like endless
um you know about power right now he
doesn't need to be I guess he never
needs to be charged for
when he's attached to a
something like a cart
as long as he comes back
um
[\h__\h]
it happens so rarely yeah one HP again
but then the unable hitch
to do the trick but now ah now yeah he
sometimes gets gets rid of The Shield
okay okay this was fun
kind of easier than the previous battle
but it was very different and I like
that they they come up with original
ideas for these fights it's very nice
the staring stick got wet so by hand
sleeves don't matter once again you're
too late I've already dug about
crystallized charges this place had to
offer and there's more I just got word
for my underlings they've located the
man himself they found the dude
no I doubt it
just one more step one teeny little step
what do you got class log standing
desire cops to fruition
no rotation I don't know we have more
than enough crystallized charges now and
there's only one more abandoned mine to
ransack Hear Me Now link
time to start the final excavation
the Northwestern abandoned mine and
waits that's where I'll use those
charges to activate the Ultimate Weapon
offered to the demon king and
[Music]
oh
and our next encounter will be your last
me
look at yours just you wait
what you mean the plane yeah I can
easily make my own
well thank you for leaving a present
because I mean isn't that literally left
by him great thanks
because it popped up like that thanks
for eliminating the
to put weirdo once again as listening
closer to the goings on
the Northwestern abandoned mind that man
headed for is likely the embedded Hebrew
mind uh but there are a few chasms in
Hebrew by which to Richard the path
stretching from Hyrule rage that was
previously used is no longer a viable
route
[Music]
though I recall there being a Chasm
somewhere that connects directly to the
abandonment let's this time take the
advice shall we
but another time I hope I remember it
next time you guys gotta remember it
maybe
Root Root Root thank you thank you a
Chasm somewhere that connects directly
to the Panama okay
well maybe I already have it on my map
there is one other thing before you
resume your journey
thank you
well let me see actually
it's here
oh
what I don't remember
Chasm close by
I don't know one here oh this is a
secret
we'll find it at least I can go to the
town easily
that's how I'll do it don't worry don't
worry
I won't try stubbornly
[Music]
the wow away it's not as successful as
the Almond way
fails too often
[Music]
oh you got a hint after you already
found it oh yeah so I should ask some
NPCs when I'm lost okay
[Music]
what do we get
a nice
I think I appreciate that it's the same
kind of boat that I was riding just now
or does it have like a attack thingy oh
it looked like it does
I think I'm aware is only something Amy
can use you know
oh you want me to use again don't you
oh okay I see wait wait wait wait wait
there is
on the ground octovox
I guess
[Music]
wait what camp do you mean
you mean that one or
a different one I I will go over there
first then I guess boat
[Music]
s
let me move it
how do we shoot
how do I do I have to catch it
I don't know if this I mean I guess I
killed them
is this how it works
it just pokes things oh okay
I'll swim back
[Music]
straight from the Philippines
sour bananas are always from the
Philippines
foreign
should I read the diary again
are we kiwis
the only known way to enter the deaths
is for chasms after the upheaval many
times appeared across Hyrule when
navigating the deaths proofs too
treacherous try leaving and returning
for a different Chasm to fully conquer
the deaths we must find every entrance
unfortunately locating jasmus is not
always straightforward it is Roman for
instance that a Chasm has somehow opened
inside a cave
Shirley's is not the only concealed
entrance there may even be holes that do
not seem to be chasms at first cause
look you mean like Wells for example the
tank card the Gloom that leaks from
these pits acts as a beacon yeah and
most can be seen from above glory to
mastercogo yeah no I know that
indeed indeed huh
okay
I can only buy two
and then all of these I think
wait why did I get plus 40
okay
I'm confused uh
oh okay
okay then the last thing I guess that
I'll be doing
ISO
and we're we're gonna go to the sky
to collect some batteries because I
haven't done that in a while I wonder
how much we get
ha oh
Grandpa there's something on the ceiling
no
oh wait that was I think always some
donuts there
no
okay then it is time for me to warp out
of here
that was uh last time I went there I was
like getting so lost
uh
and ran through the cave like several
times
trying to find what I was looking for
but I think generally the thing I'm
looking for
is that the nacho yeah Shrine right
it's it's one and oh
[Music]
really
I forgot those pagato
ah it's okay the air appears nicer
hello
long time no see
how many do I get 635
two full battery
whoa oh
I guess so one thing is 100
oh
better
thank you
that'll be good enough for a while I
think
oh
I know you can double them after you
filled out these ones
living for now now it's pretty decent
I do
while I'm here while I'm still in game
when my throat is exhausted but I wanna
go to the thingies
there's a Beyblade arena is so crazy
people come up with the craziest most
unnecessary [\h__\h] ever
let it rip
maybe another time
um
we did so much stuff today
can't even recount it what we did is
that a class or what is this for you
guys it's a problem
what are they all looking at they sound
so uh oh because they had the music here
ah they're already like in in like this
ending mood like apocalypse once again
let's go
such a weird mood going on here
the music really gives me these Vibes
like
hey
you better do this right because
otherwise we'll all die kind of feeling
I'll get one more heart and then I go
maybe stamina again after that
yeah I think I made a lot of progress no
pressure link yeah no pressure
[Music]
I guess she wants an update about the
Koka stuff
or if she cares about it okay also I
kind of want to watch one memory
I'll I'll see if there's some easily
accessible I'm uh I just uh
yes
hi Sirens we're listening to this I
receive new info about the devs we've
discovered another kind of stats you're
different from those that went to the
Southwest part of the devs yeah yeah
yeah yeah oh should I have taken the
photo
um
one is on land in the London Wet Ones
yeah
they lead towards this after that
investigators continue to follow these
statues
stone statues led directly underneath as
far as the main they discovered the
evidence of civilization there you mean
the yiga
when we dug a little deeper we learned
that the statues oh no maybe they mean
like Civilization has already did
in the southwest land beneath Grove town
so I was thinking does she only tell you
this after you're done with Coca stuff
and maybe a connection between service I
tried investigating the chasms and never
regions to follow my hunch and then we
found a new Chasm on the cliff ah there
we go face sent me to a village in Libra
Cliff face
Cliff face is there a face shaped on a
cliff or is this like some way of saying
something else
I'll remember of course wait we're
playing tltk tomorrow it's hard to
forget
I thought somehow it felt like the next
time it's like in a week or so
oh
okay
next I'm thinking of having them check
whether it's possible to go directly
under the Village from that point
I have a picture for you
do I
no I don't
oh I do
didn't I already show this one
yeah retail Vision oh
took a picture pass wow a good job we
were trying to follow these statues
ourselves but they wrote along the lane
was cut off so I couldn't make it any
further seems impossible to follow
statues at this moment which is why am I
trying to get uh-huh okay
I've been learning one thing after
another about the depths lately it's got
me super motivated motivated I'll keep
Gathering info about the labs
thank you
okay nice
do they have new stuff in the store now
kind of curious
they got the pink
[Music]
same stuff as last American okay
although I have enough to expand
something
maybe my
look at my Shields although they never
break but
so that I don't have to keep on turning
down all the shields
like that I get offered
wow
[Music]
I'm kind of tired
but
I need to cover more knowledge
I need to gather more knowledge
I need to become knowledgeable
I need to become wiser
we saw the sword one and that right the
very red one that we see in this picture
so the next is this tear
plus I need sleep too it's okay maybe it
will be easily accessible I don't
remember where's the tear
oh
that might be rough
I know we could do it more robots
the tear
it's like in the very center on the very
right
ah
must be here
oh
[Music]
no
wait it's best night I have to cook
huh
oh yeah but the memory is short and I
want to watch it
I
cannot sleep otherwise oh do you think
maybe it's on the winter Island can it
be that tiny yeah they're bigger
it must be here
I could probably get rid of these ones
on you any other ones
well here's one
ah I'll leave that one
okay a weird blue purple
let's go to
it we are at the top of a mountain so I
think we shouldn't have too much issue
reaching it
still freezing
oh wait yeah I could have gone out the
tower but I think it's fine
because it looks like it's
the height of the tear is really low
I think and we're on the mountain well
the highest mountains guys
okay
pork Buzz you're getting Blaine you're
ordering it or are you making it Ramen
that sounds like you're ordering it
going to a restaurant
made no I doubt it I see it
foreign
if you guys don't want to be spoiled
then yeah this will be the last thing
I'm doing today
am I like super behind on super chats or
am I like okay
don't remember
oops
I know I read the the members ones
I'm okay
oh why
you're quite okay too guys it's really
pretty cool too
yeah okay we'll see this one's pretty
small it should be easier to see I see
it okay but I don't see it
are you ready
for La Memoria Grande
but I feel like we already saw like the
biggest like bam
story turning point or whatever I see
the quick though I think so
whatever this is I'm ready
I'm just guessing it's easy to Guess
that that's how you would say it memory
what is it what do you mean I'm in the
right order
I have the right order down right I'm in
I'm not skipping anything right okay
well good good
oh wait that's you know is that bigger
plot Place coming let's go
oh
family
foreign
hello
it is
alive
[Music]
can I find the same place somewhere
where are we
it's a door from the beginning
well there's four more
wait do they have their tears already
they do right so wait this is this place
foreign
[Music]
airports
oh no they're getting them just now
ah
so only uh like Zelda had hers
and louder I guess had his and his
sister
and now they're getting theirs I guess
um
yay oh
hot yeah
[Music]
how do they know what to say has this
happened before is their script or
clicker what ritual
yay
my head hurts
okay tomorrow
I think now we are currently very hungry
for story thanks to this memory right
now
and don't worry tomorrow we're getting
sorry I gave you guys for today quite a
bit of you know a head start even more
but I think a lot of you also had plenty
of time right
[Music]
until now the past weeks get ahead of me
tomorrow we'll focus on the story that's
for sure
[Music]
you did the Temple of life oh okay
you finished ages there we go in the
beginning you guys were still like yeah
can't keep up but now we're good
okay ah I sneezed it's sort of cave ah
no it's just a
H okay huh
oh my head is pounding I'll be fine
though once I go away from the PC I
think
thank you guys for watching today
um I'm a bit exhausted now
probably gonna move tomorrow to one hour
later maybe that depends
Maybe not maybe yes
oh I want to do the call talk I want to
do the court look
it could be
and uh I realized too late that the
thumbnail for today was apparently used
before
so I'll make a new one and I'll make one
for tomorrow too
that's a lot of time actually
let's go oh
all the wind oh there is wind here
I'm part six whatever was today part
seven
I don't know I thought oh this canceled
one it was the most recent one but
apparently after the canceled one we did
a number one
I completely forgot about that okay
[Music]
I found the cave guys
God damn it this game oh and there's
doesn't don't these lances kind of mean
like there's something special in this
cave
drown
[Music]
oh yeah he's drowning that's an easy way
to get rid of the silver
horblin
um guys
is cave
help me why is it does it go up and down
up and down
am I gonna drown is this a Titanic
moment
[\h__\h]
Bad Blood Bad
I know I know
but this cave is so interesting
oh spikes
stream spikes
it's blacks can stop me
yeah
I'm not gonna drown I'm not gonna drown
um
uh my head hurts
fun I've got things to do please
[Music]
I cannot stop oh
I
slippery inside
get up there get up there you little
[\h__\h]
what is it
what do we find in this cave
oh
okay that's I think the second piece of
that armor
that I have
I'm only missing the head now I think
so let's go look for a Sean tweet
no just kidding I'm just kidding ah [\h__\h]
my head uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
blah blah
blah blah blah
maybe I have a pizza in my yeah I think
I do have a pizza in my freezer
um
[Music]
thank you guys for nine very nice hours
I enjoy spending this time with you and
Link
ow my head really hurts I
say and in Germany
[Music]
um
bye bye guys
[Music]
foreign