[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
come on
hello hello
everybody it's my birthday
happy
Kiana birthday 2020. oh that's the 2020
free damn I'm gonna turn down my
microphone a little bit I think or
should I
yeah wearing the um kitchen living room
where
we're on my beautiful table
um and so using different microphones
and thus the audio is not a perfect oh
remind me to turn it down when I use the
the mixer the the kitchen machine that
goes
you remind me to turn it down then yeah
literally let me cook no let's really
let me bake I haven't even share here
it's so nice also
a few
um we have Collins pretty soon like okay
there's like two maybe in the beginning
and then later like in the after one
hour there's like a lot of them all at
once so I hope to get a lot of work done
in the beginning we'll see thanks for
the memberships oh my god
um
[Music]
a few things
straight away merchandise because
there's limited uh this time I will tell
you uh the merchandise will be announced
at this at the second hour mark or like
15 minutes before and then it will be
available at two hours it should and
then another thing I I bought
um I mean supposedly I already had one
but I think it missed it was missing the
vinyl piece hi by the way of uh you know
the the thing that makes the camera go
look down directly so I got myself
another new trap now I have like a
million [\h__\h] tripods now
and um I bought a new one that can be
attached to the table and then looks
can't look straight down so we're having
a looking straight down moment finally
yay
and I mean I tested out how far down I
can go and I don't think I would ever go
down that far but just in case let me
show you
that I am wearing
oh look at this
on my head for security
this is so good it's like a shield
there's like no way that you will see
anything of my beautiful gravy heads
I couldn't find my own anymore I don't
know where mine is oh well so we're pink
today
um also gloves I'm using these today
because um I can I have like a whole box
of them and I might need to touch the
the dough and you know we want to we
want to stay clean I'm not gonna use my
my usual pull-ups today the usual gloves
no
um
what are we cooking basically a while
ago I got you know I I have a
subscription with hello beep and um they
sent me food all the time to cook and
sometimes it comes with like little free
extras and they sent me like butter they
said this is not a nothing
uh whatever but they sent me butter and
then there was a recipe for like a a
nice cake yeah a tart a strawberry
[\h__\h] and since then my goal was too
soon
um make it hard so I bought a part form
that I haven't used yet but it looks
like it's been used while I was gone
because it was in the washing machine
so mommy did you make a tart while I was
gone and I didn't get anything of it
what
um but I bought the type one you can
like lift it and it's perfect and I'm
gonna use the oh not I'm not making a
strawberry tart I'm making
I'm only using the base of the of the
cake for it
um the base the base of the yeah you
know what I mean and oh
remember
okay was this my birthday merchandise
from last year
[Music]
starting with I did not starting to eat
as much did it not work
I'm too dude it just probably didn't go
through
did it go through
[\h__\h]
send now
okay
now it's now it's there
um and we pretty soon
oh my mommy did use it what the [\h__\h] you
made a cake without me
I cannot believe it
[Music]
what
she
ah that status status some sad we have
Collins already in a moment I don't even
know if it's if you guys will be able to
hear it at the moment uh how's this
gonna work uh
wait can we test it
uh let me just go in early
[Music]
um
do you want to be my testing object
because I don't I'm on my laptop I don't
even know we should
let me sit down this is nice
um where's how how to dress up on you
audio audio
what was that oh what was that
[Music]
oh okay
that's something else it's like double
microphone oh God I didn't think of this
audio out Scarborough
Hannah
I think that's the one uh
and then
I don't know is it this oh yeah because
now you should be hearing double audio
maybe okay maybe you can come in let me
test this
um but wait oh wait wait wait let me
turn off the BTM first caller
oh yes yes
does it does it go through yes
wow hello you're the first one let's go
happy birthday oh thank you guys can you
hear how well she is she a good volume
or so I think it's working fine my
obsess that's fine yeah in my ears in my
ears you're really loud but I can change
that
okay yes yeah you can turn it up even
more
no I'm gonna break my ears no no don't
do that don't do that what are you
cooking what are you making baking I
wanna make yeah baking I wanna make a um
a cake a tart with um or Mandarin
oranges oranges and maybe peaches Peach
slices so all over the yummy and then
top it with jelly and also in between in
between the the the the
cake base and the fruits will be some
like vanilla pudding I guess
um
why didn't you make one for me because
you know when you were with me how was I
supposed to bake it
I don't know like there are a lot of
places where you can bake I think
yeah
creativity oh my god well there are some
no no bake or no Heat cakes no bake
cakes where you can just make it like I
don't know without the oven I guess I
could have done that excuse me I
dreamed of you I just remembered last
time really yeah
what happened in a dream was I very idly
I don't remember anymore but you wear
this yeah you were there that's the only
thing I remember you you played an
important role
and it was I guess I'll never know I
would I yeah I didn't dream of you
yesterday
I dreamed about adopting a gray cat that
was like a snapback backwards it was
cute I'm sorry I didn't dream of you I
will make it up did you ever dream of me
ever ever
uh let's see I mean I have there has to
be there has to be but I can't remember
I'm sorry hopefully I'll dream of you
soon
I think it's because uh we just met
right we just
we know each other for a long time what
are you talking about I mean we we've
just like met in person
Oh you mean that this sounds like
satisfying your senses so you don't have
to dream about me yeah so I don't have
to dream of you it's like I can just
like recall for like the last like few
days or something I was seeing you for
like so many days I got my dose of
kiwawa
I see I see okay so that's enough for
you yet I dream about you I see how it
is well um
well you can come back well you can come
back here I'm only like uh like I don't
know a few stations away let's go around
here
I'm back but I will be back today
but I'll also be back in Japan soon okay
oh yeah I guess
I can probably see each other and then
you can baby some cake
yes yeah okay okay I I I well if you
come visit me I will try to bake you a
cake or cook yourself okay that's a
that's a promise okay if I visit you
baby cake all right all righty do you
have a request for me
a request what kind of request I can use
my hands for you
oh um you can
um you can you can make like a dog with
your hands can you oh like like yeah
like like a dog like uh like like a
puppet like a puppet thing but with your
hands yeah
that's I don't know then that could also
be like
I guess so it's a dog I guess it's a dog
maybe the nearest thing to be smaller
yeah I guess so it's cute it's okay
[Music]
I can't wait
okay
I can't wait to see you again
I want to do with you and I hope you
have a great birthday and have fun and
good luck with the cake thank you
[Music]
I don't even know who's next I think
there's one more person coming and then
there will be a little break and I I
should get started anyway
how to multitask how do you multitask um
uh okay let me get up
um okay let me read this oh I have to
preheat the oven okay we need cat hello
Cat we need uh 300 gram lights in meal
okay I got the I got the bite to mail
and we need some some butter
I got the butter we need the 120
gramsuka
I got the sugar we need some cold water
uh free free spoons cold water I'll just
take it out of my cup we need I can turn
it
nobody's coming wait who's next let me
check this
I got my list
oh okay
um
what's happening to my list
oh my God Gemma must have changed
something because it's looking very
different from what I know and now I
don't know if I have time to bake at all
okay we need some salt where did I put
my salt out here I have a little little
salt container
and yeah that's that's for the base oh
and some some flour for the for the
ground I I by the way I wiped it of
course so there shouldn't be any sauce
there shouldn't be any um any what was I
gonna say I don't [\h__\h] know okay okay
guys then let's get started let me read
this uh food and move attacks
that's not what I'm using but
um
oh [\h__\h] it's just salted
[\h__\h] it might be salted
I don't know
[Music]
because it says unsalted and this might
be salt I don't know it doesn't say
anything about it is if it's salted
wow
it's not like you is that a big problem
hopefully but
yeah this is a very famous butter I
almost want an autograph anyway okay we
mix
okay okay okay okay I got it I got it I
got it I got it leave it to me I have a
scale
I'm just gonna leave off the music for
now because
uh maybe some people are gonna just jump
into the Discord I'm always open for
Curls by the way somebody is supposed to
be calling right now I think but
um it's it's always open just come
whenever hi I'm just gonna be cooking
Okay so
we need this is in total 250 so we're
using almost all of it
how is there a cat hair on the packaging
how how
I don't get it isn't this better now
because usually my cooking streams were
like always you know tilted angled
and now it's perfectly bird angled do
you like it is it better
open this
great
we need almost all of it so
wait but I think I have to end up
throwing it in small pieces anyway so I
should I should probably you know make
small pieces right my mom told me to
like basically freeze the butter and
then just use a a you know a cheese
grater and grates the butter but I'm not
gonna do that because that's that sounds
like annoying and some I saw other
people just do it with like smaller
pieces of butter and it wasn't fridge it
was in the fridge
Reflections I don't know what you're
supposed to see here just nothing this
doesn't face me at all this doesn't
bother me what bothers me though is I
wonder if there's cat hairs
in there
I said they are
let me
let me watch this oh [\h__\h]
yeah I have to get the cat hair off the
butter
[Music]
at least at least I I I I last minute
decided to see check
I think my mom when she cooks at my
place she doesn't like take it so
seriously with the cat hairs but here
this is proof mom there's like a even
though this was washed
you know it was just standing around so
cat hairs just go in there and do their
thing okay let's okay I'm gonna really
quickly rinse this but that means I have
to take off my headphones real quick and
if somebody's calling in and I will not
be able to hear it once I didn't lose
hmm
alrighty
all right well there's some water in
there I wonder that's probably the
problem let me bring some some kitchen
paper as well okay
here we are is somebody calling hello
no okay
there it is they're coming eventually
here let me throw the pieces of butter
back in there
we show okay here we go we're talking
to kfp please hold the line yesterday I
was on on the line with some like
authentication Service [\h__\h] for like
making a bank account
and oh my God I was in line for
like 40 50 minutes and then I gave up I
had to watch this whole video that's
saying like oh you're you're next yeah
you can you come up really soon but if
you really don't want to wait please
click here to make a an appointment and
then I clicked it and it said it's not
available to make appointments it's it's
not working
it was not scaling it awaying it [\h__\h]
house
restart okay we are
and no it's supposed to be zero now zero
okay zero
back in there
we had yeah okay well 64 gram
I know this if this is gonna work out I
don't know the most I think the easiest
part is uh everything that comes after
um because this is vital the the base of
the cake is vital but even that when my
mom said it's not so difficult
but yeah after that I want to put like
um some pudding
uh vanilla pudding as like a like a
cream you know
um and then we're gonna put the fruit on
top in a nice way and then
ah and then on the top I want to put
jelly I want to put jelly so I have to
make the jelly I have to cook the jelly
unfortunately there's no no camera over
there so you won't be seeing it but you
will hear it maybe
yeah the gelatin gelatin I don't know
it's a really simple tart I would say
my mom was like the moment I told her
mommy I want to make a cake I need to
ask her some questions she was like okay
okay you need to make this cake you have
to get this and this and then you know
you make this kind of cake and I'm like
no no come on wait I wanna I have a
specific image in my head of what I I
want to create you know
so I'm sorry but no
I don't want like your fancy cakes I
just want this I don't know I'm craving
it and the reason I'm using that those
specific fruits because my mom was like
you gotta use berries it's Berry
seasoned right now
how is it only 170 when the total of the
butter is 250 and I need there's only so
little left there is that gonna work out
is my scale wrong
or is the butter wrong no way we're
going up to 200 almost
what was I saying oh yeah my mom said it
was like Berry season
um and I should do something with
berries but
but I don't wanna
I don't wanna because I need something
orange and there's no orange berries
tell me if there's orange berries
200 I've got nothing left
120 what
the scale obviously must be wrong right
what
because I only got this little piece
left
also what's going on with the Collins
why are the people not calling in
is this what happened to the schedule
is supposed to be calling it right now
I don't [\h__\h] know I'm just I cannot
do so many things at once I'm just gonna
mind my own business and be cooking
and what I do about the butter I think
this should be over 200.
wait I'm
wait what what did this
what
but I don't know
ah [\h__\h] I don't know all right okay I
know
this has to be 50. this has to be 50.
um
this is I'm not going for 250 I'm going
for 200 and didn't I go over and over
200. wait why is it only six
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
hello
Muna
[Music]
help me oh okay how how are you doing
hello welcome to kfp
happy birthday
um I have fun watching your stream right
now
around what I want have you ever
how long you're gonna you're gonna
download I swear I'm done I think
the butter is done yeah
um have you ever baked a cake before
Muna
yes I have a disaster
what kind of cake was it
I I kind of like making like um
chocolate cake and a brownies oh yeah
it's it's good at making brownies your
brownies are pretty easy
to make together
I love I love veggies
chocolate cake what was it like like did
you make a chocolate sponge and then top
it off with chocolate more chocolate
chocolate chocolate or what
kind of like that
I love chocolate you know there's a
famous Austrian chocolate cake that's
called
it's so good
oh really yeah it's it's it has like jam
a little bit of apricot gem in between
so
it gives it like a little bit of a
refreshing taste you know
and I really recommend it I don't know
how to make it though but we can we can
try to make it together sometime
[Music]
I mean I don't mind to going into your
place to cook a cake together
sounds good sounds good I'm waiting for
you Muna yeah and more promises to bake
cakes for people I am so happy because I
already had to promise they know that
I'm baking a cake for her
how many cakes will I be baking oh my
God how big you're planning to make the
cake yeah just normal normal tart size
like typical part size but it's it's not
really something I should be eating
alone I guess yeah
but I will eat it all alone because I
haven't had breakfast yet
I'm hungry I am very hungry okay I'm
looking at your stream I'm already
hungry
hey wait what time is it over there is
it look pretty late
so when I mean it's 6 33
oh okay okay
oh no I haven't eat I haven't eaten okay
when I'm looking at your shrimp I'm so
hungry like I can't imagine the the
this makes you hungry it's butter sugar
and and flour this makes you hungry I
don't think it's very appetizing
I mean the smell of it
you smell the burner wow
thank you again because yesterday in my
stream I told the story of um meeting
decoration by the other day and I said
that you wear my rock because I held on
to you because you were my only like
hope at that time on that day I was so
freaking out so awkward so nervous and
then you were just you know chilling so
oh and thank you so much for being there
for me
actually I can say the same to you
because you know I'm not I'm
not I'm not good at talking Japanese
right and and when I know that you're
there I feel so relieved
I I have a healthy yay
[Music]
yay you got that that's good we help
each other we have each other's back
yeah yeah yeah
nice okay I think I have everything for
the base
a little bit of salt okay
okay I'm gonna look at this do you like
salt here I I like salt fresh how many
salts
oh that that is like a small salt I
harvested it what do you mean small
salts always is small oh
I think it's gonna be nice how much is a
pinch of salt is this a pinch of salt
that is that is not a pinch of salt
that is already done I didn't that's
already no I don't know yeah okay I
think so too like a pinch I think so too
yeah there is a reason why it's called a
pinch of salt okay like this is like a
peach she's a cheek yes yes okay yes
okay you just do it like a lot of salt
but that's fine then I think I got it
I'm gonna I'm gonna throw this into the
mixer now and I say goodbye to you Muna
thank you so much for calling it
thank you bye-bye somebody's supposed to
call in after her but I have to throw on
the mixer now wait a second
do you want to see it I think it's kind
of difficult to show you but I could
I could attempt can I move this
I I like um set everything to to stay
where it is you know and the Machine the
cable is a little bit too short I think
let me try to move it explosion time
it's gonna be pretty loud yeah
um okay moving moving moving
here is my
we'll be using that too I'm looking
forward to that
really
but I want you to see what I'm doing
it like sticks to the oh there you go
you can see it it sticks to the
to the surface
okay I think it's locked there it is
I guess that one's no one's calling
right now so let's go
uh and after you can still hear me while
it's actually not that bad that's it
after this is done
um
I have to wrap it in foil and keep it
cold for 30 minutes apparently it's not
sold out huh you want it louder
let me check if my mom had any comments
about
what's going on but she says I'm doing
something wrong
okay oh she used my charge form for
making veggies okay okay but no comments
on my cake so far very good
what is it
mommy should I maybe do it with my hands
because it looks just like crumbled
bread right now
um that doesn't look right to me it
doesn't look like it's
um
should I
when maybe I should it's too dry right
but I put just like it said free free
um spoons of water in there but let me
let me
do it on my own then
I'll try to do it on my own
let's go
oh but mommy says it's okay keep it keep
it going okay okay
see it much hope in this look at that
it looks like parmesan it looks like
cheese
okay we're getting some more we're
giving some more time and more more uh
we trusted okay
we go with it
[Music]
it's very relieving to have my mommy on
standby yes
I think it's becoming bigger clumps of
Parmesan
I just see at the bottom at the very
bottom there's like a little bit that's
just not moving
oh my God okay okay okay
do you guys see this
no it's okay
the grasses
became thing oh it's like ice cream
vanilla ice cream now nice
do you call this in German you call this
moob type by the way and when I looked
it up for English it was like three
words
um some kind of pastry it's a weird why
don't why don't you guys have a better
word for it but look at this
ta-da ice cream vanilla ice cream
let me check with Mommy if this is fine
um
okay okay really
she wrote that one minute ago
[Music]
right it looks like ice cream
a moment ago it looked like uh like the
parmesan cheese I'm watching I'll touch
it what are you making hey I'm making a
Tarts this is a Merck hike uh just just
this specific
um what do you call tyke what's tyke in
English this one
[Music]
I'm making a very specific type of dough
right now and then I'm making a tart
with peaches and mandarins
oh my God that sounds so healthy it's
not healthy though because there will be
a [\h__\h] ton of sugar there's already a
[\h__\h] ton of butter in there
you put the butter in yeah oh this looks
so good I was like yes
[Music]
yeah probably so good right now and you
don't have any egg in this you can
totally yes yes well what do you mean
you mean I could eat it now you could
it's just flour I mean although they say
that flower sometimes you can get
salmonella from Wildflower so maybe not
it's so buttery I don't want to eat it
[Music]
um so it's so buttery yeah
I mean I like butter but this is like
pure butter it's mixed with some flour
you're you're an avid Baker to aren't
you I like baking tell me a bag with
baking did you ever make a tart
okay
[Music]
I really like working at KFC right now
I'm supposed to be the CEO I'm not
supposed to make can I get one size
tutor please
if you pronounce it correctly yes
father's older
but honestly you can get
maybe even in Japan I saw before you
know you know you know those big
department stores in Japan
yes yeah and on the Underground floors
there's like food uh stuff and and and I
saw before one of the famous sakatoa the
brands has uh like but they they are
also in Japan and I tried their soccer
before when I was really craving it and
it did taste quite good so if we're in
Japan again at the same time sometime
then we can try that time
or
or until now I've brought some people uh
sahato to souvenir a couple of times
already
um because at the airport there's this
little
cubes and and big example 22 but I
usually get these little cubes and I
give them a souvenir and it works out
really well it tastes really good
um yeah maybe how do you get that past
airport because you're already in the
airport so oh no this is it's nothing I
think no it's not meat so it's not a big
issue it's got illegal austrians yeah
[Music]
no chickens involved I think I think
yeah what's my next step here
um yeah what are you doing
okay okay one second good I'm gonna take
up my headphones and you're gonna get
the foil so you talk to them okay okay
[Music]
I can I can smell you can you hear me
again please it's about a good book be
quiet
um
asked your Chef this is the chef's
the chef is chefing I'm chefing which
which foil do we want do we want the
see-through foil or do we want the
pretty reflective um cool foil
uh there's two different types of oil
hell yeah there's the seafood the
plastic wrap moving area that's not foil
it's just a cling cling wrap in German
it's also foil
why blasting what's should I do
I like sticky I vote sticky sticky
what's playing clean is this
is this okay
mommy mommy do you think this is okay
it's pretty oh she said don't need she
said don't need it oh my God okay oh no
more kneading no more kneading why not
it doesn't want to be caressed
by the way thank you
your birthday was recently too yeah what
oh could I have one question oh god oh
yes at the concert you performed a new
song I did when are you when are you
releasing the I don't know
the Envy is still being uh worked on so
oh yes that is a
there's a there's a talented
can you can you tell us what kind of MB
it is like animator 3D honestly it's
very colorful I tell I said I asked I
said I wanted to kind of be like a
kaleidoscope and kind of trippy but not
super trippy oh does that make sense I'm
looking forward to it because it that's
like kind of like City pop inspired
right
slap
[Music]
oh it's so soft yeah it's a stuff baby
I'm gonna put it in the fridge so I
think yeah
put it in the fridge wait put it in the
fridge okay
[Music]
wait your pink headphones
oh it's so pink and cute
you're telling me you don't have gamer
girl headphones
no
no what kind of headphones do you have
uh oh they have fabric around the ears
I would take them off but then I can't
hear you
my old headphones electrocute me when I
had them on my head like if I moved so
much they would have liked to keep me
and then I read somewhere that like oh
yeah you could die from that so I said
okay you know what I feel like you
should risk it and then uh Sudan
wait can you sue though if you like are
aware it's like premeditated
I was aware and I did it so that I could
get money
I'm getting fresh gloves right now
and I have the old ones you know if you
want there's butter on it
buttered shark
and do we still have time almost almost
over but could uh wait you you didn't
really I want to hear more about your
baking Adventures because I kind of
caught you off there oh my bacon let's
see what about sometimes I get the
really weird urge to bake like sourdough
bread and a big bread or a banana bread
everybody knows when you have
yeah I've never done that before you've
never made banana bread no how have you
never made banana bread what would you
call that an in German
it was it was similar to English
chocolate chips in it oh it's so good
chocolate chips and banana bread oh yes
and you put peanut butter on top and if
it glues your mouth shut that means you
made a really good batch oh
it gets crunchy with the butter on top
and I don't think that's I don't think I
don't think a fair Exchange
you do you don't I don't why not because
sounds more appealing to me than banana
banana bread
you can't say that because
my friend of peanut butter so you don't
you don't have to put peanut butter on
it it's just banana banana peanut butter
is optional but you know I prefer I kind
of prefer what the [\h__\h]
I kind of prefer more creamy things
you've never had it I want to hear it
you don't get to you don't get to say no
until you've had a taste okay okay
if you eat so many sweet things I'm
honestly surprised I didn't see a single
pimple on your face before
I
I don't know how to answer that because
I don't know
although I had a lot of sugar so maybe
it affects my stomach more than anything
else
I'm okay I'm kind of fun I guess sweaty
uh on my hands a little bit it's just a
tiny bit I don't know
the moistness from the dough that go
through [\h__\h] that's hard work that's
elbow grease that's what I'm thinking I
guess you gotta go I was gonna say I
think I gotta go okay
thank you
[Music]
I miss her she's just like the day I
lost her
what am I saying I don't know I'm so
hungry I can't get into these [\h__\h]
gloves oh oh I'm getting there there we
go you just get stuck somewhere hmm
foreign
can you guys
um count
30 minutes hello hello
hello
hi hello hello who do we have here
introduce yourselves
hello I am here
in uh I'm joining in order to not giving
assistant
I come here solely just to watch oh okay
girls if you're just watching can you
tell me did I put uh by any chance and I
put the disc lock on the wrong way
because I think I did I think
yeah you don't know though
yeah
I have so many I'll try again okay
don't worry I bring I bring assistant oh
assistant
[Music]
yes I I bring two oh
poor assistant though
hello I am the first assistant as
someone who has never baked a cake in my
life before another inspect your cake
okay you know no experience okay no
qualification sounds good you're in
and then one more assistant no
hello I am assistant number two I
provide moral support I would like to
eat your fingers why no no my fingers
you cannot have them I need them to
finish baking this cake
I wanna buy them
please do not okay I finally got in
there was obviously something wrong with
the glove oh
yeah
yeah there's like four gloves on this
wait what the girls what do I do next I
just finished uh the the dough and now
oh I have to okay I have to take the I
think
girls say something to my channel
more entertainment if there's fire we
just expect Mommy
[Music]
tells it
I have an idea what she's talking about
but good luck moral support thank you
I don't think
which one is
I don't I don't speak baking I don't
speak cake have you girls never baked a
cake before ever
no we could
just crazy I mean okay wait have I baked
a cake before
maybe not
what what kind of cake are you baking I
am making a part yeah with um peaches
and mandarins topped all over it oh
you're interested
[Music]
yeah
I've never eaten a peach before
my mom says that wait is that me to the
beach before
never
are you are you okay are they not common
in Indonesia
it's not that common though yeah like
once
wow okay I guess peaches are because you
guys have more like tropical fruits I
guess some peaches are not that tropical
yeah
okay we have bananas too but your
bananas are probably like fresher than
ours because ours are always imported
from other countries
you know we can't grow them here I think
one second girls let me turn on the oven
okay
which one
which one many it's funny how she's
having like trouble when she has like
that big ass cake behind us
well it's okay
let me show you let him send you a
picture mommy
blessed with that cake
which one is she said just go for the
one with that where the fan goes off but
they all I don't know sound the same to
me
hello
can I use your Phoenix powers for what
we're baking the cake
uh I you know I want to as I live in the
human world I don't want to be so
reliant on my Powers so I try to live
like a normal human being and just you
know adjust to the world
stop
YouTube
are the only ideas who keep on evading
me
[Music]
emotionally why do you not want to meet
me
then come over now
[Music]
let's go
can you guys sing me a happy birthday or
something yeah
I actually practice to sing Happy
Birthday in German but I was gonna sing
it with this cake but there's no cake on
the screen right now I'll just sing it
anyway okay oh
thank you good good job
thank you so much thank you and very
cute 10 out of 10. I feel very
celebrated
I got you something but I don't think I
got I drew you something but I don't
think you can show it I can visit with
cake but yeah it's okay I can I I'm I I
think I can wait let me see it
dang it
looks like my children strolling it's so
cute
oh my God wait let me show you
[Music]
it's so childish it's so adorable look
at this
oh my God
is this is this the future of us is this
the day where we will find it this is
the future I was gonna draw a house but
in the valley is there a flying Fried
Chicken
what else to draw
a chicken accompanying us very cute is
that my butler maybe
oh that's so cute and you're wearing
orange you're wearing my hat yeah I'm
wearing the Hat
you like my hat oh
you have two hats I have yes um you
honestly you can have my white hat
though I prefer my my orange hats
okay I'll bring you a hat someday I like
hats
[Music]
okay thank you girls for being here I'll
say goodbye and I have to check the oven
okay
thank you
[Music]
which one
are they gone I think they're gone okay
wait one second before the next person
comes in what did my mommy say about the
oven because I sent her a picture of you
know all the symbols why don't they like
ride I decided
okay okay
[Music]
all righty hopefully that's correct so
that is preheating I should have done
that in the beginning
and the next is I have to put
uh I actually I bought a spray just for
this purpose here back spray black spray
baking spray from Dr Edgar do you know
this guy
he's he's not a real doctor let me tell
you that or is he but he's not the kind
of doctor that you want to get your body
checked out uh with
so I got this to make this um you know
greasy and then tag of Anna with mail to
store them expression I was fun okay
okay so we're still kind of waiting for
the cake for the for the dough actually
it hasn't been it's definitely not been
30 minutes
so we can chill a little bit thank God
okay but I'll open up this thing
I'm hoping for calls by the way if
anybody what is like waiting
[\h__\h] I can't open it
[Music]
uh happy birthday
thank you hello
hi I'm I'm a little late to the party
okay
I'm making a tart with um peaches and
mandarins on it oh [\h__\h] yeah it's gonna
be orange and cute yes it's gonna be
orange maybe orange just like me
you cook a lot but you also bake a lot
uh it depends I mean mostly I just bake
like chocolate chip cookies I don't
really do anything too crazy oh yeah I
love your chocolate chip cookies they're
so good oh thank you I recently
discovered that you can like brown
butter and so I I use that in the cookie
mix and
oh you gotta try it oh it sounds good
and you should also try making a baking
stream
we'll see I'm gonna leave it up to the
experts I can't open this help me I
would I would if I could I'll grab it
with my teeth
oh should I do that uh do you have
strong teeth
um no
um
you could do it here I'll try to help
move
that looks dangerous yeah
yeah for the can it might oh
it's like there's like a line
um it's hard to see
Focus please you gotta you gotta put the
can between your thighs like and then
clench your thighs and then pinch the
tip of the of the can and then then peel
the thing
pinch the yeah so like hold the hold it
in place while it's in between your legs
you saw my legs
yeah yeah I get it
[Applause]
it doesn't work it doesn't work it
doesn't work I don't have enough
strength in any part of my body oh okay
okay actually like because you walk
pretty fast so I thought maybe some
muscular size yeah I do walk pretty fast
like I wanted to talk about that at some
point in my stream like you you girls
when I was like around walking around
I don't know maybe it's because I had a
certain goal in mind and then at what
time we would have to be there because I
knew if we walk slowly we're gonna be
late and then I felt so I feel
like dragging behind is that what how
you say it like 10 minutes behind me and
I feel like I walk pretty fast but I
always do this thing where whoever is
the slowest like I'll match their Pace
subconsciously so glitter is walking
slow as hell so yeah okay I see it yeah
but you do walk fast
and I was leading
jog though it's not even walking it's
like you you're John Jay no
[Music]
trouble we don't want to be late we
don't want to be scolded we did a good
job keeping us in line you made it work
did you tell me people about that that
little cake can that you got
um
[Music]
I ate the can on stream and it was uh it
was bad by the time I ate it because
hey were you supposed to cool it
yeah I was in my bag for like five hours
in the Heat and then I it smelled a
little funky
did you did you show them a picture
uh oh no not yet I got I have it I just
gotta I gotta Photoshop it a little bit
okay okay because I also have a picture
of the machine that was going to show
people eventually oh yeah yeah it's a
really cool machine cake machine it was
really cool it was kind of expensive 10
bucks so I'm sure your cake will turn
out even better of course it will if I
ever get this [\h__\h] open oh no no okay
I'm gonna explain it one more time you
could do it you just hold it like in
between your knees kind of and then you
like hold the cap with one hand and then
peel with the other hand and like kind
of jiggle jiggle I believe okay but I
tried that but I just don't have the
string I feel like maybe okay well I'll
try I'm sitting down goodbye worst case
scenario pierce it was a knife okay
okay bye-bye
I don't see y'all remove the gloves you
think that will give me more grip I'll
try but I tried so hard to get into the
gloves in the first place
maybe just one okay well it gets so
moist in there my my fingertips are
crumbled
okay let me try
ah
[\h__\h] hello
okay you know what I can also just brace
it with normal butter right because I
have still a couple of pieces of butter
that will work right that'll do
hello
who is this
[Music]
time for me attack are you speaking
English I don't understand what you're
saying yeah
wake up
[Music]
[Laughter]
with peaches and mandarins
heart oh now I'm awake
now we're talking right do you like
cakes that sounds so nice sweet so I I
did just wake up how far are you
and I'm currently preheating the oven
but I made the dough the dough is now
being chilled in the fridge and now I'm
trying to grease this stupid
um tart base thingy but I can't open the
can for the greasing spray so I'm just
gonna use it I guess um
I'm incapable of opening it
is that why you're saying but the butter
I can use the butter yes exactly
are you okay
sorry my animal is right next to me
what else have you been doing I've been
asleep for a while
um I did a countdown stream a couple
hours before
um yeah
um and and and just been I I don't know
actually I just woke up and then I
started preparing everything for a whole
hour and and now I'm here so I haven't
done anything besides that I guess
[Music]
um I was impressed only an hour yeah
yeah
well here let's do you want some butter
mummy it's really it's really soft it's
really soft
is this okay can I just do it like this
oh is this okay I think that should be
fine right
it's okay to do
it's spreading really nicely
oh
grease spray yeah this will this will do
fine that grease spray sounds gross
Butter sounds healthier I just thought
it would be easy and helpful but if I
can't even open it
[Music]
yeah that's the worst I'm so much
I feel you I've had a pickle jar for a
while I think I opened it once but I
haven't been able to open it again after
this first time it should be really easy
to do usually but I guess I'm so strong
I posed it really tightly and you're so
strong
and yeah close it in a way that you
can't open it anymore
I'm actually not weak I'm actually very
strong so it's like uh Only One
Direction strength
yes
I'm training do you do you ever like
lift weights or work out or so
weightlifting hmm
I probably should yeah
I can lift later on screen because I
bought weights and and I can lift them
once I'm done with these gloves
you can lift weights
I mean yes as long as they're not too
heavy
oh yeah like a pound
it's I don't know what towns are but
it's like two oh yeah
yeah eight is still
yeah
stone is what they use in the UK or
something yeah why are you speaking in
pounds
pound Stone ah wait what do you use in
America
pound okay okay I thought that was uh UK
this is
wait didn't you okay use pants pop
yeah
wait what didn't you can use pounds
I don't know pounds in your case ah this
is currency and yeah that's what it
sounds so uk-ish to me pounds is the
currency in the UK but in America it's
the weight what does that mean why why
do you do this confusing thing hmm
weird yeah
let's go
but that's not what a word sounds like
but yeah
okay your phone cuts off a lot so I'm
not sure what if you're happy or unhappy
it was an ungodly sound it's for the
best it could happen
Okay Okay I I will prepare the bird
sound just oh
[Music]
yeah I'm so excited
very excited I'm scared to talk about it
because I don't want to spoil stuff oh
I'm I'm just like yes yes better be
careful not to spoil anything
oh you know what I have to do now the
next step is fun I have to
uh put flour all over my working surface
let's go flower flower I think I I got
rid of the hairs once so it's probably
fun I
spread the dog
[Music]
I hope the dough works out fine hmm
let's go
[Music]
I'm so excited to wake up again and see
what the tart looks like yes I will make
I'll take a nice picture and I'll put it
up on Twitter and so on also are you I
know I think you're you can't be in the
deck box right
I don't think I can that's okay that's
okay don't worry about it I'm just
checking my memory if I if I can I can
let you know like
two hours before but I don't think it's
okay because I think actually maximum
participants is eight people I think and
I think we're like pretty much reaching
it anyway oh okay okay don't worry about
it yeah good but I will probably listen
to you guys play it okay
you can give me
if you write me
so I need something give me some good
ideas oh yeah and I'm really bad at that
but okay
I need your help was not cheating it
doesn't matter you're the birthday girl
they don't have to know yeah they don't
have to know don't ever know I never
know
I will help you oh thank you I can use
my foreign
all right remember I'm Gonna Let You Go
thank you for calling in yeah have a
good rest of your stream thank you let's
start super yummy yay
[Music]
thank you
has it been 30 minutes guys for real I
need you to tell me I think it's been at
least 15 minutes
maybe 20. I don't know about 13. hi
how are you doing
I can't hear I can I can't hear anything
okay I can hear I can hear your skin
I'm so good and I saw your good
performance amazing performance
thank you yeah you are amazing and happy
birthday to you yay
I'm sorry yeah in order to eat my cake
[Music]
yeah I definitely wanted to say
congratulations to you because you
always want to dedicate to your whole
life groups yeah in a many ways so thank
you so much
now thank you for you I think your
English is getting better again it keeps
right better yeah damn how about you
Japanese
yeah it's like your summer so summer
live stream yeah it's many yeah
[Music]
I always need to
need some time after not speaking
Japanese for a while to get back into it
because in the beginning it will be a
little bit katakoto right
he's getting ice skating so getting your
Japanese memory channel is getting
after after starting the live stream
right
I don't think you can I can never forget
Japanese but it's just like you know it
gets a bit Rusty sometimes
[Music]
some people actually within actually
within our again members we saw some
pictures of Yago and we were like is he
okay like is he eating fine because he's
so thin everybody's like worried
ah so you you mean the Anime Expo right
yeah like all the pictures we see
recently of yada he's so thin he lost so
much weight we're very concerned
no no no no he wants to keep his feet
don't worry he wants to and I I've heard
he around every every morning every
morning
yeah I see I see and he has been
learning
um every morning for a long time maybe
your rust Hotel crazy ago when when do
you remember and last year
long time ago so yeah a long time right
I told the girls I told them like oh but
he works out he goes running every day
but still he looks so thin do you ever
go eating with Yago do you go without
sleep ah I've heard uh yeah
[Laughter]
um
I've heard he only eats salad or chicken
no not Uber chicken or very healthy
foods
but I I don't I don't know why he wants
to lose weight because he's but he looks
very thin right
exercises
you know when he tried he asked
actually too much weight yeah yeah right
so maybe so he wants to gain a little
bit weight I think now he's thinking I
don't know if he will ever hear this but
yeah
[Laughter]
yeah anyway first happy birthday and I
hope your your maybe birthday cake your
cooking birthday cake birthday cake yeah
good taste thank you so much
[Music]
foreign
bye has it been 30 minutes guys you need
to tell me how many elephants do I need
to I need to do I need to do something
you know I'm actually surprised I can
multitask so well you know I've been
doing so many things while talking to
the girls and so on but
I want to do it is okay okay let me get
the dough let me get the dough let me
get the dough dude
[Music]
let's make let's make a base
bam there it is someone in the call no
okay
here it is it does feel a little bit
different Maybe
but if I understand correctly I just
throw it on there then I roll it out and
then we place it over the tart
um what do you call it
[Music]
thank you wow that surprised me
that was a lot of a lot of passion a lot
of energy
yes of course only to you happy birthday
thank you
bills do you want some of my cake that
I'm making
what her purses are we up to how long
have you been baking this cake oh
something that doesn't look like cake
right now
come on did you shoot you should what
what point what does it look like what
point I am
I mean okay yeah this is actually a
dough that you do use for cookies so oh
not so far off
but I'm making a card
let me let me increase my um my volume
real quick yes wait this is actually a
little bit too lengthy let me can I add
this here
I hear you very nicely and clearly Bales
okay okay
all right sticking
AKA orange fruit AKA mandarins and
peaches
oh this folded this is the tart though
girl
oh you're making it hot oh my God I
don't know why I did not hear that right
right you're making a type oh yeah but I
don't know why it's stinking don't stop
stinking because I'm stinking
onto the boat you can put some flour on
your rolling though yeah
uh I don't know if I'm doing this
correctly have you ever made a tart
before
ah I think I have
um
a long time ago there you're a baker
I tried there was a time where I was
like wait I like cooking therefore I can
bake so I tried once that's all right
only once it was very mediocre
meaty and ocher medium
yeah what kind of tart was it
I think it was also a fruit tart oh
aren't those the best I love
fruity stuff yeah
[Music]
do you want a piece of my tart when it's
done I do I'm actually very intrigued I
love watching people cook I'm very
intrigued right now
streams every once in a while though
this this one has been you know it's
been a while since the last one this is
so long Bales I need to make it I guess
like this
and how fun should it be I wonder
um probably pretty thin I don't really
tell out because yeah don't make it too
thin or else it won't hold up when you
bake it it still seems pretty thick
though
oh I can't really tell them on camera
wait let me see in here oh
I mean it should already fit here on
like the the round oh thing but if it
wasn't good or out all the way on the
sides that is another matter um
I need a little more is that allowed do
you can I separate it doesn't that like
mess up everything no you can just you
can just roll it together roll it
together should I make a ball again it
needs to go up the sizes yeah I know I
know and break it off to make it
um yeah but then it doesn't feel like
it's part of it anymore seeing
no don't worry
okay
yeah it's getting better it's getting
better okay okay let me try to make your
face here
oh my face oh
okay I'll try you
oh okay that's quite thick oh my
goodness okay the fact that you can draw
that's quite thick oh my goodness
oh my God okay let's fix it I'm rolling
over you
your face is being destroyed and deleted
forever
let no are you flat you know I really I
I still I'm kind of like
salty about the fact that you were not
flat
as I expected you to be
I thought you were gonna be the flatty
out of you Jen
so why because you're small and you kind
of from the front I don't know and I
thought you know could be pretty flat
but turns out you're wearing so that's
kind of disappointing yeah be the first
that I'm disappointed with my booba
is there anyone else who's disappointed
by Bubba what is
it because and it's just that that's not
that's not a little pancake you know oh
I see I see
well that's okay there's there's two
admits so you know one's accounted for
yeah I guess so
[Music]
it's nice balance with um with medium
with super super nothing and super big
you know it's it's
a man
medium is premium name is Brandon
honestly I'm just kidding though you
know I also appreciate all all sizes of
course of course you just
it's just me you just Bumpus with me
unexpected
for sure yeah
can you see me can you can you see me
Australian happy birthday before you go
Australian happy birthday what
I don't know this is a Australian accent
really strong accent
all right matey
you were an Australian happy birthday
let's go
you go to the truth it's tradition to
also be holding a beer while you sing it
but also we don't have beer here so
oh I guess multi will have to do all
right Kiara
Kiara
in Australian Australian you tell me
there we go okay
Kiara
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
to you
happy birthday happy birthday
Kiara
[Music]
happy birthday to you
yeah that was marvelous marvelous
thanks man thank you Mike thanks mate
all right done oh see you later
was it good
chocolate
[Laughter]
keep watching your baking Journey yes
thank you very much I'll see you around
Bells
so I think this is a good size now even
though I keep on like making weird like
shapes in in it
what the [\h__\h] and I noticed that some
things are like sticking to the
to the wood and that's why it's doing
that you know this pretty late but is
this okay I think it's big enough now at
least
um more flour one
I think I'm done though
honestly I think it's a good good size
I'm gonna move away in the kitchen
machine because it's like in the way we
have a little window of where we can be
productive right now so
I gotta be productive oh sure
I don't I don't know how how much I can
risk also this is not
this is already too thin
[\h__\h]
the [\h__\h]
that's not good it's not good it's not
good that's not good let me like
[Music]
make it so that it becomes as one
[\h__\h] hell [\h__\h]
sprinkle more flour
come on come on yeah okay
okay and more flour more flour more
flour
all right all right is this okay let me
see what my mom is saying
oh sure
maybe she has some input
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] she said no
it's not well
I don't know I I can't I can't even like
tell you how thin it is
it's definitely big enough
yeah but what happens if it's too thin
but it does like go up it it it it like
you know blows up a little bit I think
as far as I know did the chat just stop
working
as far as I know it it just it blows up
a little bit so maybe
maybe no no not too much of a issue [\h__\h]
I don't even know how to lift it however
you're supposed to lift this
oh my mom says I'm never getting it in
there yeah I don't know how to lift it
[\h__\h] I think we have to redo it because
safe
how are you supposed to do this
[\h__\h]
redo redo
hi hi Chad I see you [\h__\h]
um
why can I not just put it as a ball into
the shape and then
I don't know do it with my hands rip
dough
and ah my mom says use the
there's this yeah really
and then ah okay okay interesting should
I put flour on top of that too
because now it's bothered
and I guess it will lose its effect if
it's
rubber
my mom is giving me life support Live
tech support
uh
picking up the little pieces schneiding
house
right a little bit of flour she says
okay
happy birthday thank you I'm building a
[\h__\h] dressed oh [\h__\h] that was a lot
thank you so much
just a little bit she says
most excellent she says I have to do it
extra really
the the sides but doesn't really like
connect them
hmm
I don't know yeah maybe I should put
some from here too
I'm adding so much flour to it this is
not the original recipe anymore
you've been using very little flowers
with this so that's fine okay okay okay
sure
[Music]
if I no I will I will I think I have an
idea so
I will roll it out a little bit over the
edge
yeah I know how to do it I know how to
do it
do it I have an idea I have a vision
I have been enlightened
surprising how so many of the girls you
know they don't have baking experience
I thought they could help me
but they're not much of Health
man
okay but this actually helps because
then I know at least when I reach the
circumference
of the
of the circle
of the main plate
okay now we're just trying to get
something going
on the on the sides extending it yeah
all right all right okay pretty good I
think now
I'm gonna put this back inside okay so
wait hold this chat hold it for me thank
you
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
it's really fake what's up
okay it didn't go as I thought it would
go
[Music]
okay okay that's fine I'll just have to
do it
we heard there's a crisis going on there
is a crisis going on but I think I'm
fixing it right now it's okay
really have you do you have baking
experience
do I have what baking experience
um I have desserted baking experience
such as
um I like to bake cookies
yeah you've never baked cookies for me
oh I don't know because I feel like I I
uh I feel like you kind of rival me and
experience this no no no no no
better
[Music]
sweet that was baking is I think it's
all about having the right recipe right
I guess so there's a secret ingredient
you're supposed to add a little bit of
mayonnaise to cake if you want it to be
moist that's my tip today it was too
late for that
that's fine
for every cake because I don't know if
that would really fit this cake I mean I
mean if you want like a really moist
cake did your mom tell you that
from now my my childhood friend's mom
loves to bake things for friends and she
made the best cake and she's like my
secret ingredient is just a little bit
of mayonnaise you're not supposed to
tell anyone but it looks like I've just
told
a lot of people now I'm sorry
I wonder if my mom knows about that
oh you should ask her oh she's listening
right now she's protecting me and my
cake
story
hi Mama Tori we meet again it's been a
long time
still enjoying Minecraft
she always enjoys Minecraft if there's a
new update at least how are you doing
I'm good I want to know if you're using
like a fondant is that what you're
making it with
fondant yeah it's kind of like the clay
of the cake baking world
I don't think I'm using that well what
would I what would I use that for
I don't know I thought that like you'd
be making some Cool Shapes or something
wedding cake Vibes oh no what I'm doing
I'm just making a part and then after
this is baked I will put like vanilla
pudding
hmm just as to have something creamy in
between the fruit and the the dough and
then I put the fruit all over and then I
top it with gelatin
wow that sounds like it sounds like
you've thought a lot about it I see that
you have like some beautiful art on the
screen right now
[Laughter]
very good hey it's more than it's more
than I was able to do today
I'm here that's fine don't worry you
gave me
I did I did give you the the Lord of the
Rings dice yeah you'll use them
if I ever get an opportunity where I
need dices yes I will maybe if I play
Monopoly or something right true enough
yeah you know what I also just realized
is that you know I also am very I'm very
sad about the being unable to do live uh
3D thing and whatever live 3D
performance isn't this just truly like
the the most like livest and most 3D
stream that you could yeah yeah I mean
under these circumstances exactly this
is very free this is more freezies than
I could ever be indeed exactly the
truest purest 3D so so don't don't get
down or anything I think it'll be
another great 3D stream this year so
true sis so true true definitely I have
to make holes
what was that
you said Kobo no I have to make holes I
need another scissor oh my God Hey
where's my my headphones are long enough
to reach the drive
I got a book as I saw a video that you
have to make these little holes in the
in the dough right
um are you gonna like put it in the
microwave or something no I'm gonna put
it in an oven I have a normal kitchen
I'm like you know new people in Japan
ah lucky
I love you I think this is fine though
let me see what my mom says
well you gotta brag about how delicious
the cake is to everyone my mom is be is
acting very disgusted about the
mayonnaise thing which I think she maybe
just doesn't like mayonnaise in general
I mean I was disgusted by it too until I
literally like thought about it and then
took a bite of the cake and I was like
wow you know what maybe I can taste a
little mayonnaise now but it's not that
bad
it'll never be worse I just I'll
secretly I'll make a cake and I'll mix
mayonnaise in it and I'll feed it to my
mom and I'll see you know how what her
reaction is if she'll like it if she'll
notice it that's such a good idea it
reminds me of the time that I tried to
bake a cake for my mother's birthday and
instead of using vegetable oil all we
had was olive oil so I used a bunch of
olive oil and it was the worst tasting
thing on the planet Earth
you gotta be careful of that how does
that sound Montessori would you like to
to eat an olive oil cake
that sounds good
I I mean I think she is very fond of
olive oil but not in a cake probably
okay it does not belong in there God I'm
so hungry I have to throw this into the
oven I think I'll do that now and then I
have to announce merchandise
none of you guys can beat my speed let
me check the instructions
okay okay okay well everybody seems
ready this time you know because because
sometimes like during mine for example
it was mid song posted and I didn't even
know oh because I I told also I told
everyone already a million times when
I'm announcing the merchandise so that
everybody is ready
nice wow incredible I expected nothing
less 25 minutes of baking
thank you Kelly for calling in
[Music]
you're welcome you're welcome hell yeah
oh I see somebody else is here someone
else special is waiting really
really yeah oh
come on you little [\h__\h] I don't have
time right now for you
okay okay okay
you come back later right after okay
all the responsibility yeah follow the
schedule okay
all right bye bye
come back you come back after the
merchandise okay
she's gone already okay thanks guys
look at the camera
hold on I'm looking right now are you
gonna flip me off
that's me it's my hat
yeah I'm wearing your hair
I love it I hope that it serves you well
and shields your eyes from the sun no no
that's not what I'm using it for I'm
just protecting it because of the bird's
point of view camera angle you know just
in case I bent down too much it's a
genius move
I get it now thank you for protecting me
challenge thank you
you're welcome have a happy happy
birthday
[Music]
okay
merchandise time baby let me sit down oh
should I throw it in now let me see what
did Mommy say um shouldn't say anything
so I guess I can just throw it in I'm
gonna throw it in I think it said um it
said 25 minutes on on this uh recipe but
this one's a little bit different
because they apparently put some cream
on it before they throw it in but I'm
doing it without but I hope this is fine
it's loud in there
there you go
cute little tart
okay
let me sit down for this everybody you
might want to sit down for this too and
get ready too
uh order my merchandise maybe if you
want no wait my mommy said way too
though
[Music]
um
what could I put
uh
what's what is safe to put in there uh
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't know what I can put on there
what could I put on there my mom's name
uh Drive nuts my mom said nuts I think I
have some nuts
you think it's okay to put some some
cashew nuts on there I'm not that
they're not too too weak
too light weighted nuts
from Halo beep they will burn
[Music]
I'm gonna put
this pizza foil and the nuts on top
Maybe
that's like six nuts no it's a bit more
in six months
you guys
okay perfect size
perfect size
Mmm Yeah the nuts are kind of um
it has almonds but I want to eat the
almonds I'm gonna put some more cashew
nuts
okay maybe even more I have three
packages of cashew nuts
um
but uh what else what else what else
oh hazelnuts I got hazelnuts too
here's some hazelnuts
I hope the nuts don't burn somebody said
they won't burn it really concerns me
okay
I mean
there's a [\h__\h] ton of nuts on there that
will have to do
my mom is like not responding so
no okay okay
time for merchandise guys
Michelle where's my I think they're I
think I have a mouse
nice okay are you guys ready for
me you know normally I always have like
kind of a theme
um last time it was like you know baking
cooking stuff kitchen stuff and and it
was also slippers and blankets you know
like at home chill stuff and so on now
even though the merchandise will
probably arrive in Winter for a lot of
people this time I'm going for a summer
theme and I wasn't able to create
everything that I wanted to know but
it's partially summer themed so here is
a birthday maybe
birthday
celebration 2023 on sale right after
this announcement at the full hour
we have done free birthday party
very big towel
ksb Beach Adventure bag and pouch and in
yo kfb plushie bonus for the birthday
merch complete set limited edition
postcard with a handwritten autograph
and then if you get the full set but you
don't get the limited one then it's a
stamped uh foil uh shiny autograph
instead okay yes in Washington I was
actually gonna do the plushie for my
anniversary but somehow
um it's now wait can you guys look at
the time
it is it's probably already been five so
let's say to intent after I have to take
out the cake probably okay okay
yeah yeah so now instead of anniversary
the plushie is part of this birthday set
and let's take a look what's first ah
take a look one by one okay so here we
have uh the postcard illustration which
is also on the towel
it's very summery very vibrant it's me
on the beach but I thought that maybe
you want a one side that is not so
obviously weeaboo-ish so the other side
is a little bit more normal with the kfb
logo and yeah it's really big so it's a
proper beach towel but you can of also
use it at home
[Music]
it's really
really mean and if you see if you look
closely at the sand I drew a heart for
you guys into the sand mmm cute
yeah the back side I think it will look
really nice uh the back side on on the
beach on the towel because it's you know
this striped
uh pattern with the KFC logo and my name
on it
yeah I think that that part looks more
normal so it depends on what side you
want to show off towel towel towel but
if you don't want to take it outside at
all of course you can just use it as
your shower towel bath towel whatever
yeah
you can go please please because the
next item is a kfvp to Adventure bag and
pouch so it's like I was thinking you
know if you go to the beach for me for
my personal experience I often uh end up
bringing a lot of things like maybe two
bottles of water a big ass towel or two
big as towels
uh a phone maybe a switch Nintendo
switch you know there's many things you
want to bring to the beach maybe uh
maybe a book you know maybe some
um a plastic
a swimming ring thingy that you have to
blow up so yeah you know there's many
things you could bring sunscreen exactly
many things you could bring to the beach
inside there's a nice inner lining and
it's really like it has the fabric of uh
I think fitting to a beach bag it's
pretty big you don't have to use it as a
beach bag you could probably use it for
the things too I saw it in person by the
way and it was like a little bit too big
I thought so I had it sized down a tiny
bit and inside there's also it looks
kind of maybe small on this picture but
it's like a pretty big inside plastic
pouch see-through as well for things
that you don't want uh to get wet uh I
think generally the bag is pretty
protective too but um this is just an
extra protection layer and there's a
front bag as well the there where the
kfb logo is
[Music]
yes it's finally time
there is a KFC chicken
because so far we had Kotori as a place
for the anniversary
um myth anniversary plushies I think but
here it is
oh
let's go
yay can't be you are now really really
cute and big and fluffy
[Music]
I I held this one as well like a sample
I held it in my hands it's very very
soft you can take off the hat I asked
are you requested that specifically
um there's like a little velcro
attachment uh so you can take it off or
whatever you feel like
it's very well made uh it's very chunky
very thick you can move the Flappy flaps
a little bit the feet the feeties are
like you know
like tangly
I don't know how to describe it the feet
are kind of cute I like the feet yeah
it's very
[Music]
you want you right here I want you to
I want to I need you
it's so cute
and it's wearing the uniform it has a
little name tag worth no name on so if
you want I guess you could write your
own name on it
yeah so uh this time it seems like I
didn't make a voice pack that is true
I know I don't feel like it I think I
focused too much on the items the yeah
so I hope you want to get them and I
think in four minutes the sales should
start maybe open the page up already uh
I think somebody will hopefully put it
pin it in my comments in a moment when
it's up and yeah I don't I'm not sure
how much how many
how many limited editions they wear I'm
not sure anymore well how many I have to
sign but okay you're constantly
reloading let's go I'm glad I'm sure
there's enough for everybody who wants
it yeah
we will see hi girls the cake the cake
is fine probably I think it's probably
fine I just want to wait because I hope
the nuts are not burning
ah wait so let me let me let me show
this one because here you see everything
let me just checking the nuts are
burning are you burning
[Music]
no they look fine
they're not even getting Brown
I think we're good I'm just worried
about what comes after this um the the
pudding is fine but I have to make
gelatin right let me put the butter in
the freezer oh my God
[Music]
this butter in the fridge
okay it's gonna start merchandising sold
in a couple of
Eagle does three minutes will geek have
a limited edition otherwise I probably
would have been told that geek Jack
doesn't have it no I'm pretty sure they
have it
um
pretty sure
right
oh can I say
of how many limited ones there are
[Music]
because she told me maybe I don't want
to say it because I would be embarrassed
if I can't sell them all
yeah there's a thousand
um yeah there's a thousands
five thousand
[Music]
um yeah it will probably take maybe five
days to sell out or maybe another
gift check has it too but there's more
quantity available on the official EC
apparently
more quantity
on the official shop but geek Jack has
it too there you go we're almost there
let's go
[Music]
yeah
merchandise which one is your favorite
item what are you looking forward to the
most guys it's probably the the plushie
isn't it
but honestly the towel I guess like you
know you could also just then put it on
the wall like a wall scroll the bag
I'd love to say the plushie
the towel combined with the bag for me
it's a perfect set to go to the beach or
to go hiking I don't know to go for a
picnic I don't know to go you can even
use it as a shopping bag maybe for
Supermarket I don't know
it's it's pretty big
[Music]
there you go it has many uses as does
the towel you gotta wave it like a flag
oh
one minute are you guys ready
merchandise it's going on sale
[Music]
today
simple
oh
[Music]
for me time stop
Don't Panic guys
Panic no Panic
[Music]
also I wanted to
um whip up some whipped cream so let me
let me quickly while you guys are buying
the merch I will be gone for like two
minutes okay I'll just quickly clean the
the bowl so I can mix something
[Music]
soy sauce
all righty
that was not even two minutes
how's it going with the merchandise are
the is it a crash
is it working where did I put my hair
crashed you did it you got it yeah
[Music]
foreign
refresh refresh
and try to get
a piece of yourself
you know I could I was like able to
touch the samples but I wasn't allowed
to keep them you're never allowed to
keep the samples it's so sad but I I
wish I wish
I wish I could keep it but I have to
wait just like you guys it's probably
gonna take like half a year right like
it normally does
[Music]
I spent some time with it then I gave it
a kiss and then I sent him away
what happens with samples anyway do they
get destroyed in front of the trash I
don't want to pick on it what happened
like cutie patooty
sold out no that's that's probably just
um just some error
probably just some everyone
but only gig tag right you can still get
it on the EC
the normal shop
now I'm making some cream now you guys
can't see it right now but don't worry
about it
[Music]
what happened to the sample
moisture and did everybody get it who
wanted it from kick Jack because some
people rely on gig Jack and they have to
use guitar
really
[Music]
um
you got yours it's gone
oh I got yours well even if you don't
get the limited one you know there will
be opportunities in the future I'm sure
um let's get the normal postcard instead
I'll sign it for you someday
yeah I I wish so too that it would ship
to Europe trust me
um
yeah it's still it's still some in stock
in the whole store apparently
how many kids do I have twelve oh I'm
sure it had a bit more
thank you
[Music]
do you want to hear some some loud
wait different different mixer here
there we go
[Music]
so now that we got this beam I wonder
what I'll go for my next birthday would
be myself go for next
but we have lots of time to think about
that
[Music]
beach towel ready
let me put this like up here
the Indian one
for that do we have space you put it
here maybe
[Music]
I love you I love you I love you
thank you
really
oh thank you it was the first time I'm
doing limited merchandise
so I was worried about it thank you and
thank Christian for the support and you
got the problem
it was only fashion yeah but I had to
sign
for you it's Ralph
it takes a long time I'll do it again
for anniversary okay
which is pretty soon after anyway in
September there will be a birthday and
it was pretty much now so
I'll I'll ask to do limited
merchandisers there too with signatures
okay we'll try it again and if the
fountains wasn't so difficult to sign
then maybe I'll request to do 2000. if
you guys really will buy it you have to
promise me to buy it only then I will do
2000.
overnight hello
foreign
[Music]
I don't know when to take it out I think
it's just supposed to be a little bit
brown right but it's so covered so I
can't really see it
I'll give it three more minutes I think
um
ah estimated
schedule around early December 2023 to
early January 2024. the good thing is if
you live in Australia or whenever
wherever maybe the mall of these swords
forever tropical and nice then you can
already use it in December on the beach
but if it's if you live somewhere else
you know where the winter is in December
well then you have to wait a little bit
and just use it in in your bathroom yeah
Brazil as well right it was in Brazil in
summer before
[Music]
okay okay
oh boy did you hear this you can come in
whenever
it will just be a little bit difficult
to talk and have a conversation
and I'm making whipped cream right now
because my mom said I should mix you
know first first I thought I was gonna
make
um I thought it was gonna make vanilla
pudding from scratch but I'm lazy so I
thought okay you know what maybe you
just buy a normal
um pudding vanilla pudding and then my
mom said I should mix it a little bit
with whipped cream then it will be more
fluffy you know did you hear me
it's not even close to being whipped
cream right now
but I'll mix it once it's done and then
we'll put it all over the yeah
I never made this before but uh sugar
okay
did I just feel just has nothing to
prevented
[Music]
uh and cold water
oh my God German people
let me try this
spirit is
here okay
need a bit more really let me see is my
mommy saying something
uh
stressful
oh it my mom ran out of Internet that's
why she's been quiet
if it comes out without crumbles it's
good oh really
that feels good
yeah I think that might be fine
it feels like
texture I think
ah
oh my God I was just like putting my
headphones back on and I'm like why am I
hearing myself a little bit and oh
I wish
I can hear you hello
no problem at all I I was very happy to
have a little bit of time where nobody's
calling in because I was like running
around getting the cake out and
everything
yeah I yeah it's a tart it's a tart
we're making it into what's hard it
could be a pie I guess some Fury
oh
and it's gonna be tough now with um some
vanilla pudding cream and just to have
something like you know creamy in
between and then top the peaches and
um mandarins and then topped with
gelatin jelly yes
I mean normal actually
yeah but she's out of Internet she was
helping me for the first couple like
hour I guess the first hour yeah
oh can I can I tell people about the
fact that we recently finally
found something in common
[Music]
how did we even get to the to the topic
oh my god oh yeah now then now they can
I'm so sorry no what's up what's up they
they you were muted on streams
[Applause]
now no problem no problem nothing
nothing but nothing much of importance
yeah just just saying hello Small Talk
small talk yeah yeah and then where
where
like how did we get to the topic of idol
master I forgot we were talking about
like I think like Idols in general and
then like oh and then something about
like I think
um games and then I was just talking
about like oh yeah like I played like a
lot of a lot of like Idol master and you
were like what do you like Idol Master
better than love live
yes and then I sent you a couple of you
know my favorite Idol Master songs and
videos and dances
yeah because you know all the old ones
you know you also prefer the old
nostalgic ones yeah yeah the uh old Idol
Master 2 game the that game yeah that
specific game had a lot of really nice
songs
[Music]
if we can if we can that that'd be
perfect
weekend covered the hamburger song
before oh yeah I love hamburger yes
ah that would be so cute if we could
yeah for the you know the original 13
girls who do you like the most
[Music]
wait was uh was takane in the 13 girls
yeah attack on it is in the 30th is my
favorite yeah
not your favorite
let's go I used to love yayoi too
yeah yeah he's cute oh
yes yeah yeah
[Laughter]
oh like a feast
I like them all though yeah of course
yeah they're all cute the OG twins you
know they're really cute too yeah but
like if it's besides those girls and I I
really like chicken Nyan yes that is the
girls yeah sexy yeah
hair some like I think I saw some Idol
Master art uh of I think it was like
chicken with
um what's that other girl called that
has like hair like me like orange hair
with the turquoise light highlights or
so in it ah I forgot her name I know who
you're talking about the rock girl yeah
okay what was her name
what does look like you yeah it's like
the cool version of Kiara exactly
at first glance and it was us
literally it's the same hair color yeah
completely different hairstyle yeah very
edgy I aspire to be that edgy one day
we'll might we might get an edgy Kiara
one day outfit I'm sure I'm sure
so I'm glad we could talk about Iron Man
so let's talk about it more soon yeah
that's definitely good luck with your
cake thank you no no tart exactly how
long much longer this seems like you're
you're not super far yeah
I would say I I think there's not much
left the most important part was the
dough and now it's finished and I'm just
you know I'm a little bit slower than I
could be because of all the call-ins you
know okay gotcha but I I'm putting the
cream on now okay the next all you have
to do is just layer everything then yeah
pretty much I I still have to cook the
the gelatin ah can be too difficult is
it like gelatin made from horse
[Music]
um I feel like
I thought it was horse that makes
gelatin I remember when I found that out
I was shocked yeah I heard
once you hear about what what they're
made out of that's what are gummy bears
made out of I think it's from Pig yeah
oh really pigs yeah this is not that
appetizing anymore yeah
gelatin comes with weird stuff yeah oh I
guess anyways maybe some oh yeah
horse feet
oh well oh well I'm making something way
tastier now so yeah let's forget about
the horse yeah all right thank you for
calling
yeah no happy birthday Kiara I forgot to
say the happy birthday
[Music]
okay
um Let Me Take A taste out of this by
the way
[Music]
it's it's Larry like yogurty at this
point I don't know if it's supposed to
be like that okay
um should I make the gelatin first
before putting on the fruit
[Music]
yes maybe maybe yes I just don't know if
I'm fast enough
um but I have to cook it anyway that I
have to uh then it's like 10 minutes of
of cooling it down anyway so here's the
gelatin stuff they said one minute right
one minute of cooking it so that
shouldn't be too long I'm gonna throw it
on the stove really quickly if Cobo
comes in just tell her mommy's not here
right now
here we go
although you guys can probably hear me
from here
[Music]
weekly monthly cooking right said mildly
cooking
a freaking mess right now
mildly cooking and doing stir it too
let's see
um some costumes this doesn't say
anything about stirring only stirring
after Wiseman is cooling down
oh yeah did Colville understand that I
want her to come back I'm not sure she
understood
[Music]
okay
what flavor and mandarins and peaches
[Music]
so yeah
look they look the same they're both
very Orange
[Music]
this is the Mandarin oranges and this is
the peaches ah the ID Girls the ID girls
are cold before they they said they
haven't had peaches before because
they're not so common in Indonesia is it
true
[Music]
girls that called in before you they
said they they haven't had peaches
before because uh uh oh very low okay
okay they haven't had peaches before
it's not so common in Indonesia
apparently yeah it is
[Music]
it's like
like making sparkly sounds
no I guess that's normal
what what oh it's not it's not making
sparkling sounds anymore yeah but I
totally forgot about the gelatin
what happened I'm cooking gelatin right
now
okay you know what that is
jelly jelly making jelly just this way
it only takes one minute
what happened to the live chat hello
chat
wow
yeah yeah it's okay
Dad what happened Dad
[Music]
one minute
I don't know if it's really clicking yet
60 seconds one minute is 60 Seconds
I already turned her to the maximum
she's loud to me hello
sorry I'm going back and forth between
the the gelatin and you it's okay it's
okay it's okay gelatin is important
thank you
I meet you tomorrow
I hope you're not you're eating I hope
you're eating proper food recently and
no cat food yeah
no
um
[Music]
food okay
don't eat dog food my food
[Music]
okay
let me let me drop let me drop some bars
then
okay I have something to say today
when you cook the gelatin then it's like
still very very fluid does it only get
hard after you turn it off because it's
very fluid I don't know how long I
should cook it
yes yes
but my love for you is here to stay okay
okay okay I turn it off now
boom
[Music]
fresh
gelatin let's go okay 10 minute counter
wait Google
do I just let it cool down on but wait I
have to Stir It
oh
[Music]
yes I'll stir it I'll stir it
yo yo yo mommy Kiowa is
right now
okay go one back
[Music]
I just said happy birthday to you thank
you I didn't hear it but I'll have to
watch the archive I guess
it's okay
I was dropping some bars do you wanna
you wanna hear yeah bring it on yo yo
Cabo what do you got bring it down
okay so that was
um
I have something to say today
to Mommy Phoenix Happy Birthday hey
I hope you have an amazing day hey
started putting Harden button that's the
only thing I can say
but my love for you is here to stay
oh
[Music]
you got some
something new you probably got it from
Cali from Daddy Cali
thanks
but maybe stay with singing
I don't know how to make this gelatin I
don't know if I'm doing it right just
cook it just stir it and
uh
[Music]
I don't know I cooked food I cooked it
for one minute and yeah I guess I just
have to
um
it turns out that if it's too stiff you
can still cook it again and then it will
soften again apparently so I can't do
much wrong I guess
you need to pray oh okay I will pray to
the gelatin gods please give me a
successful gelatin Harvest so I can put
it on my cake actually while I'm waiting
I should put the fruit on there anyway
right so let me open
the pizza
there's actually more peaches than
mandarins
for sure
see my breakfast
huh yeah the snake will be your
breakfast yeah
are you [\h__\h] serious
I woke up and I had to prepare for the
stream and then you know there was no
time oh my God that's not really healthy
breakfast there
I think it's somebody else was like oh
that sounds like a healthy cake
for sure but there is gelatin is gelatin
healthy
it's so slippery gelatin is definitely
not healthy and honestly yes a lot about
this cake is not healthy oh I mean
they're they're uh put put many many
fruit and it will be healthy yeah that's
what I'm doing but they're so slippery
oh dear oh dear I'm gonna make one layer
of peaches
maybe I don't have enough fruit actually
and then the inner layout with mandarins
but I'm just realizing yeah this is
no that will ruin the cake no nuts
please
oh God I should have drained them
oh no
they're so slippery
I cannot help from here that would be so
sweet though if we do a cooking stream
together
[Music]
oh true yes okay next time Kelly can
join us too what should we cook cake too
or or some proper food
uh
oh we can cook noodle noodles
I can make some pasta you okay can you
can you bring a noodles from your
country
yeah but so I think they're not so
special
and it but it will be my first time try
it oh
it's more special because
but I want to know what that well how
how does noodles Austria's noodles taste
like
we have a special type of noodles that's
called schwetzle
please bring me ah I I can't I don't
think I can because um they're usually
they're sold like raw so if anything I
would have to make it from scratch in
Japan
huh you're not supposed to bring it
you're not allowed to bring it to Japan
like you know these kind of like raw
foods
they're very strict at the airport
but I can make it from scratch man
expensive
but what it do will took long time to
make noodles
can you make can you make carbonara yes
I can do you prefer it with
um you know there's they say that the
the real way to make uh carbonara is
just with an egg just with the egg yolk
you don't use cream apparently I don't
like York I want cheese
Chase but you're supposed to use egg
yolk huh
no carbonara is uh you you mix with milk
and cheese
no no purple cheese yes before I made
carbonara with milk and cheese well I
guess that's your kind of carbonara
cream you do you mean cream not milk
cream for the cream okay but did you
mean actual actual milk because it's not
supposed to be actual milk I think
um
well that's what I saw in Internet
so that is a weird kind of carbonara the
Italians are gonna absolutely lose their
[\h__\h] over that then
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you that that will be
accepted yeah that's okay
yeah all right note that then and let's
you know and make another cover song
oh yeah Coco this time on your channel
last time I was on my channel let's do
it I'm ready I'm ready
I'm gonna continue making my cake I
think you were the last caller anyway no
there's another one
oh
oh with your cook okay okay thank you
thank you
[Music]
I don't even know see they're the same
color isn't it beautiful I was worried
you know I don't have enough peaches
actually but it'll be fun
at least I'm layering them nicely dude
they there's so much water though I
should have totally
um
trade them but I'm too lazy
so then I have to leave this place and I
try to stay here they're so tired these
mandarins
oh okay I see what's going on it's like
something's happening but it's not too
hard yet
but yeah there's like something going on
there oh
for a moment but it's okay it's not
completely hard yet at all at all it
still needs some time
I want to snack on these little
mandarins
hello hello
oh welcome maybe you're the last
birthday thank you
[Music]
yeah I couldn't pass the opportunity
because I have a perfect trick for your
tattoo
going happy birthday I think I'm almost
done actually I oh wait watch you watch
you baking baking uh a tart with I mean
you can see it no yeah I am I am just
saying it right now oh that looks
delicious Mandarin peaches tart
and very orange that looks so good thank
you do you like are you gonna are you
gonna eat it by yourself yes
[Music]
no I don't want to share it anyway
enough honestly no I could I could call
a friend over
um her birthday was actually just
yesterday
and maybe I should spray
between because I still got so many and
the middle is already full do you like
to bake or cook on you
no I'm I I never really bake or cook
why not do you order Ubers all the time
don't call me out like that please
time and I did that
you know because well you know if you
make it yourself number one you always
know what's in the ingredients so you
can like feel safe when eating it number
two you will have more variety because
you can look at a million recipes and
cook whatever you want at least in my
country the variety of what you can
order home for food is not so big you
know so it's kind of boring I got kind
of tired of it and it's more healthy if
you make it yourself usually the
ingredients are more healthy and it
tastes better and you can decide how
much you want normally when I order food
it's just too much you know there's so
many reasons there's just so many
reasons to do it yourself you know but I
can't cook I can cook as good as you
evidence
true well would you would you teach me
how to cook then
[Music]
okay actually speaking I don't know I
think the only ID the only ID that who
cooks and who I trust like as in their
cooking I trust is probably only to
senpai
[Music]
it also Cooks but then but then
she does stuff like the like the globe
serial gloves and then I fear my life I
do not believe a word when you say Dana
Cooks I visited her before and I do not
believe it no you cannot guess like me
like that you made it does not
cooking she seems to be cooking but then
she does stops like a clove cereal and
like I'm like oh hell no what
and then she wanted to eat cereal I
think and she started putting milk in
inside of a gloves and then she put
cereal as well
to the inside of the clothes wait was it
a plastic glove like I'm wearing
I yeah I think it might be a plastic
gloves okay okay yeah
um
yeah so like why among eight IDs outside
of me there's only one that I can trust
when it comes to cooking yeah yeah I I
would not trust Lena either with that so
yeah I will not trust training
you girls are all hopeless oh I think
I'm out of all the fruit okay I'm
gonna be filled up it's not like
perfectly shaped and all that but it
looks pretty good oh are you done I
think so when am I supposed to pour the
gelatin over it though I think I've said
something here
um
oh at the point where you pour it over
the tart it's not even supposed to be
perfectly hard just yet
it gets hard after you you cool the cake
itself for a while but when do I
know I think this thing
turn it over it's like so pretty pretty
fluid pretty liquid
she was asking the wrong person
bring me back
he's just kidding
yeah I love your merchandising thank you
I really love practical merchandising
yes that's what I always do you know
actually I love to get them but aren't
they sold out already uh no only only
the the signature The Limited uh oh the
limited edition yeah I kind of want the
plushie it's so cute wait I want to show
you where did I put my uh where did I
put my glove
[Music]
wait I want to show you from last year
my
um Merchant maybe it's right here and I
just can't see it my merchandise I had
like a like a baking glove you know an
oven Mitten oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm
sorry sorry so but I'm too blind to see
it right now where did I put it I just
used it that was super cute
okay I can't find it it's gone but it's
okay I'm so hungry for it now and cool
okay we're pouring it we're pouring it
oh you can see it's like yeah it's it's
definitely jelly
it is jelly indeed oh
some of that was a little bit too too
too
[Music]
um hard already
oh
that looks that looks hey can you guys
see that there's a layer of jelly there
now
uh-huh it's hard to see it's so
see-through so clear
some more here it's visible enough
already yeah okay
I don't know where it needs a bit more
maybe here
I love cakes
I'm gonna eat this all alone
let's go
well enjoy enjoy your part thank you
thank you so much
on the next birthday where we talk again
yes
at 2024
okay
enjoy your birthday
[Music]
it's already hard here
it's not covering everything but
whatever
it doesn't matter if it's not covered
doesn't matter doesn't matter right it
doesn't matter just like tiny bits
they're not they're not covered
come on I'm so exhausted I need food in
my system let me put the pudding away
I still have like a lot of pudding here
and I could just eat
but I'm not actually
but we have to put the the cake in the
fridge now right so let me try to make
some space here
um
[Music]
okay that's I think
enough space
say goodbye to the pretty cake we're
gonna put it in the fridge for a while
[Music]
I'm gonna be honest it doesn't look as
as perfect as I like imagined it to be
well no but hopefully it will taste good
and this is only my first part
so who knows maybe my future Tarts any
nuts by the way
and my future Tarts will surely
being another Improvement right
this is only the beginning
of
chihuahuas making new company KBC
and The Taste is different from what it
looks like you think so
oh I'm cleaning up a little bit let me
clean up this middle as well
with uh
[Music]
thank you
how long do I yeah I could eat the nuts
I guess does anyone know how long I
should keep it in the fridge there's a
thing here
no it just says until the the jelly is
hardened so it was pretty hard and after
I poured it
so I think we can taste it very soon
let's go
I'm excited for my breakfast I'm so
excited we're sure
oh
sure
what a mess
oh
okay holy [\h__\h] that's a mess eel
disgusting
I'm gonna turn on BGN again in a second
so it's not too quiet and lonely
some of the dough is
kind of sticking to the
table but I'll fix it
afterwards yeah
oh here it's kind of inside but I have a
toothpick
oh that's just uh-huh some creamy stuff
okay
[Music]
hello
maybe I'll switch gloves too
yeah let me let me get some different
looks like
[Music]
okay I don't know if they're clean but
I'll do
chunky monkey
[Music]
ah
I got some
I love arenas by the way
um after this stream uh like from now
it's like oh five five eight hours
oh death hello eight hours from now uh
there will be another birthday stream on
my channel the jackbox party stream
there's a lot of participants there
Buddha is also participating as far as I
know I mean I don't know if she
remembers because like
she gave me an okay like a long time ago
already
I don't know if she remembers that
yeah but we have fauna uh
uh uh crony
ah
[Music]
um
no Iris no oh Cali
no mermaid
yeah but a lot of other girlyos
I'm so hungry
I don't know this is just
[Music]
vanilla cream mix from some whipped
cream
huh
I don't even like putting that much yeah
she wanted to participate but then it
turns out she didn't have time after all
um
whatever
oh I just gotta wait for the cake
here's new gloves by the way because I
think I'm done cooking
I'm so exhausting like taking calls and
being like high high energy hyped up
while cooking uh making it hard for the
first time yeah these are my eating
gloves yes because I always wear gloves
at any time of the day yes I have gloves
for every occasion
[Music]
yeah we're done we're done
um
let me check
well so exhausting
Mama glove finished don't take
it yeah
[Music]
there's one amazing stream thank you
it's been a while I think since we did
uh like a cooking baking strain
right it's been a while I think
these are so tired
I do like a lot of hand cam streams but
cooking slash baking it's been a while
yeah we did a
we did the gaming stream recently
where we played with ah do
you want
Toto
so happy oh
[Music]
my lips my wings I've seen
two kilogram it's okay
let's go
let's lift guys
[Music]
and I'm even like uh yeah I'm letting my
arms fall down low-key on the table oh
[Music]
oh
yeah well that's rough
together yeah
oh
I'm gonna I'm gonna soon be very buff
trust me
Sun TM
you know how uh Kelly said my arms are
really toned actually this this shirt is
so tight actually
look
and normal
flexing
blessing wow
oh and let's actually that looks way
that looks like way more than it
actually is
oh yeah oh I'm so strong whoa I can lift
everybody I can lift all those chickens
yeah let's go I'm getting swole I should
just do a whole streak where I just live
for an hour
but normally I wouldn't I wouldn't lean
my hands my arms on the table I'm just
doing this so you guys can see it
right
that's my right arm my left arm
[Applause]
ah on my shoulder
let's go
I'm too strong you should be scared of
me don't mess with me I'm small Joe
I'm gonna
punch you in your face and you're gonna
lose all your teeth I mean chickens
probably don't have teeth today then
you're gonna just lose your beak I'm
gonna break you big
part-time work
me right like in the in the in the
summer theme song MV as well
people have this image of me being fit I
think I was portrayed as a very fit
person in the summer Envy Keanu between
songs
yeah
I mean I have I think you know I don't I
really like stamina but
I just have mental stamina
so like even when I'm [\h__\h] exhausted
and I'm like dying I I just I
I I I
absolutely go past the point where other
people would already stop I think
you know what I mean willpower yeah
willpower
I think that's my strong point like my
strong suit
I shouldn't be able to do so much and
yet I do it
like these kind of like strengths
thingies like sports and stuff but also
just in life
like oh this is so heavy
oh
gotta lift
I gotta
I'm gonna do my lips
if we do this
for like a whole stream would that be
entertaining to you we just do small
talk while lifting I was actually
already thinking about this a while ago
oh
do it
yes really we can do Fitness talk oh we
can drink protein shakes together and
drink and eat protein snackles together
I can try to drink uh like an egg Shake
only made out of eggs oh the possible it
is
oh it's it's getting easier I think see
I'm already building muscle
I need to feel a little bit more muscle
because lifting chunkers is really hard
for me chunkers is like legit so heavy
especially you know the problem is when
I carry them in a carrier
[Music]
um you know I want to defend myself
because the thing is like in one of
those carriers like they they're not
necessarily in the middle and they
wobble around so the balance is like off
and that's what makes it much more
difficult to carry than it should be
than just carrying the cat on its own is
so more difficult in in a carrier that's
why I bought myself a backpack carrier
for next time I gotta go to the
to the uh
[Music]
I don't remember her wait next time I go
to the vet I'll I'll try to write it
down how
how heavy they actually are I'm getting
those grades oh
I feel like the cake is already finished
probably
should I should I go get it I feel like
it doesn't take so much time to
oh
all right
go for it yay I need to take a nice
picture though before I I cut it open
[Music]
okay we have a knife
wow
it's so summery
[Music]
like a bit more fruit because there's
still some space where there's no fruit
but I think it's plenty
and also the color I don't know I think
it's because
I've been the reason why it doesn't look
so good is because of the dough on the
sides just not being so pretty yeah
[Music]
well here it is it doesn't look very
different from before I
uh put it in the fridge but
I think it's
yeah it's jelly fine yay
okay let me take a picture
let me take a picture for Twitter
by the way I bought actually I bought
like some lights for this kind of stream
too but turns out it's a USB light and
my laptop only has like three USB slots
and one is for the microphone one is for
the mouse one is for
uh
ah no what is it for there's another one
that I'm using so I could use the light
this time I'll buy like a like a USB
extension like um whatever you call it
glitter
[Music]
and then I can use the lights too but I
mean it's in the middle of the day so
it's pretty bright anyway
okay
[Music]
meet them
I will admit that but
I am proud of it it's my first heart and
I'm lifting it I will lift a lot off
Lift Up Lift Up time perfect
easy
[Music]
no
huh
all right oh but wait that looks good I
think I should take a picture from
this too because the the outside of the
[Music]
um the wall the cake wall
it's pretty nice
yeah because it's got that that typical
pattern you know
[Music]
okay I took some pictures
okay
I'm going in
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
all right uh it's kind of crumbling on
the
on the outside but that's okay we accept
a little crumbling
maybe I should just go up fast
okay
yeah it works out what's that
uh-huh let me get get a plate I guess
chunky wonky don't jump on the table
otherwise you grounded oh right you're a
cat that stays at home
never mind then
that doesn't face you at all
okay I got a plate
what's up
uh one thing I don't have is like a cake
lifter I guess oh wow the pudding is so
yummy
it's running
[Music]
yeah the pudding probably because I left
it outside of the fridge for so long
it's like so liquid it's like running
outside here oh no it stopped I think it
stopped kind of
let me stop and do some cake
yeah perfect
[Music]
um
yeah
vegetable but it will be tasty and sure
here goes my breakfast
um maybe I should watch this
no candle yeah I forgot candles
looks good I think it looks worse in
real life
[Music]
okay
the pudding is just liquid I think it
needs a lot more time in the fridge just
because of the pudding
oh
[Music]
wow that is a
big disappointment
that is
huge disappointment
[Music]
oh my God
oh
I feel like it tastes like nothing
and the dough
I don't know if it's supposed to be like
that I feel like it could have used some
more time in the oven a little bit
and the fruit is kind of underwhelming
too
no I don't know what I expected but
um
[Music]
wait maybe if I get Peaches I didn't get
to the peaches yet maybe the peaches
will will save this experience
[Music]
this is peach
he just peaches peaches peaches peaches
Pages Pages Pages Pages come on let me
lift you that's a lot of jelly yo
oh
um
[Music]
I don't know what's better
maybe the peaches are a bit better than
the mandarins
but in the end it was pretty similar and
yeah I mean canned fruit yeah
but
but wants to go for the trouble
um
yeah doing all this with fresh fruit oh
my God hell no maybe next time
and I wanted an orange cake you know
I wanted an orange tape hold up you know
what the the dough isn't too bad
um
[Music]
oh my God it's exactly like cookie dough
it tastes like Christmas cookies
[Music]
um
yeah fresh fruit will definitely been
better but so much more preparation
involved so
[Music]
think about Christmas cookies while
eating this
I feel better about it a little bit
[Music]
um
there may have been a reflection in the
gelatin
before I poured it
[Music]
really
I doubt that one I have to check the
spoon though
so probably private jingle bot for a
little bit
unfortunately I just gotta check it how
serious it is
spoon you know for my
natties you know no they're not
reflective I have those for a long time
already
didn't even get them for streaming
purpose but um
need to get like a solid color cutlery
[Music]
um
okay the more I eat of it
the I feel like the better it gets just
because I'm accepting it for what it is
now
laughs
and just me being really hungry
[Music]
um
you want some of this cake honestly
especially the sides are pretty good
because I guess the sides are cooked
better
um
foreign
[Music]
okay
no no
the edges of the crust are always my
favorite yeah but the ends it's just
pretty nice because it's like extra
crispy
um
[Music]
almost finished with my big piece here
so at least it's not it's not so bad
that I wouldn't eat it
[Music]
if it's worth inviting my friend
to eat this cake you know
it's not that good
to invite a friend and be like hey
that's okay if you want to come over
[Music]
I got the Browning
but really it should be darker I think
[Music]
it's exhausting to eat while talking
ah
[Music]
the jelly everything is like separating
you know they don't they haven't
accepted
their life together yet they don't want
to be part of each other
[Music]
you want the slimes really
but you love me so much
you would eat things even when you knew
that they were poisoned by me
[Music]
I love you too
really guys I mean okay as I said it's
not like
so bad that you wouldn't want to eat it
but
it didn't live up to that
cake from the supermarket you know the
one I told you about the the um elephant
the children's elephant cake that looks
like Super Mario now because he became
an elephant too
I haven't had that one in a long time
monkey scratching and scratching board
while looking at me
[Music]
huh
she's exploring I think she just woke up
a moment ago
yeah she's jumping around you can even
hear her jumpy sounds it's so cute
[Music]
ah mommy please next time
the pictures actually coming over on
Sunday
for one night
maybe we can bake a tie together and she
can show me how it's done I would be
interested in seeing it and she's she's
been saying the whole time you know that
I should make a cake with a tart with
berries because it's very seasoned right
now remember you don't have to peel them
and everything
that seems much easier to me than you
know making a tart with fresh fruit like
mandarins and peaches
because you have to peel them and I
don't know what else you have to do like
you probably I don't know what you do
so berries would be a beer and would
probably taste better because you can
just get the fresh ones
but you're saying we're talking about
pie
pie is another story
pies are not tarts
that's a whole nother story
[Music]
um
I'll be honest with you guys
I don't know
if I will actually eat this
[Music]
I ate one pretty big piece
but I don't know about the rest
[Music]
I'll ask my friends and tell her that I
have a really mediocre cake
well ask her if she wants to
eat it with me
but I will be honest and then say it's
really mediocre
[Music]
even to poor children I don't know where
they are
I haven't seen a poor child
outside and
forever I only ever see poor adults if
anything but no children where are they
[Music]
is not poor
she's an honest
person I think I wonder if she would eat
this and then tell me honestly
how mid it is or if she
you know it could also be that she would
like it because I don't know who knows
her taste buds are different I I noticed
that depending on where you grow up your
taste buds are used to different things
and then you know maybe I perceive it as
mid and she would perceive it as decent
who knows
but I think she would be generally very
honest about her opinion about the food
even if I cooked it
actually cat food yeah
I mentioned hmm
so you're saying she would enjoy any
kind of food
[Music]
that would be a relief indeed
yeah but it is
[Music]
I'm disappointed in my cooking in my
baking
I'm disappointed but at the same time
I'm motivated to learn oops
to learn what I did what I did wrong and
where I could improve it maybe maybe it
I think the pudding
because it was like literally yogurt uh
texture at this point maybe if I have
something that's more solid
um and then
[Music]
uh hmm
the dough should be in there longer and
fresh fruits if I improve these points
oh my God custard I was thinking about
custard too but I never made custard
before and um I just wanted like a
relatively Simple Solution so my mom
suggested vanilla pudding
and I was like oh that's pretty similar
actually to custard anyway what is
custard anyway it's
with vanilla pudding I don't even know
eggs
more eggs I don't know
but Mayo
yeah it was my first tent yeah
soft pudding
yeah I need something more solid because
it's like you know all running out as
you can see
and practice makes perfect I guess yeah
I need to learn more about how to deal
with the dough apparently this is not
perfect tart dough anyway
but just a tart dough that's easy to
work with and I could have gone the easy
way and just gotten like a finished
dough from the supermarket and just lay
it over and
[Music]
it turned out better
not one to go for easy mode in in any of
any situation that's cheating right I
thought so I thought there's nothing to
do right because like basically all like
most of what I had to do was the dough
and if I take that away then
there's like nothing to do I would have
been finished so fast right
but I I'm curious I I do want to test
the supermarket though sometime if I
just want a quick part
maybe I'll test it out sometime
slicing fruit yeah slicing fruit if I
have to do fresh fruit but if it's
berries you know there's really small
berries so I can just place them I don't
even have to slice them but the
Strawberry Tart would be really awesome
although the strawberries are in the
picture of the of the recipe it wasn't
even sliced it was just like
full strawberries placed all over
um kind of lazy
[Music]
sliced them yeah cut in half at least
stream a new tart
[Music]
[Applause]
s
thank you for bringing up my favorite
jerk
in a star in the start English cards
[Music]
me
freezing hmm
a recipe
that's where I saw it too I love
Arrested Development
and uh one of them has a license plate
that says anus tired but of course
they're making it seem like he tried to
do a new start but that's too many
letters so he shortened it by writing a
and u s t r t a r t e f
ah
it's so funny to me so beyoncia to be us
to be a such a [\h__\h] idiot a new
starter
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay I'm gonna
um end this here
and prepare for the next room we're
gonna make a thumbnail and set up the
stream uh for later
that's in four five six seven seven
hours from now I think a little bit less
than seven hours six hours 40 minutes I
think should be when the next stream is
happening
um
[Music]
and for the last video for standing by
my side while making this mediocre cake
thank you
oh
um
[Music]
meaty meaty core
I want to eat some proper food no I
wanna eat something Savory I'm gonna get
a sandwich I think
I'm gonna get a sandwich
of salami and tomato and lettuce and mmm
to something proper because this I feel
like this just made me sick
I was on time even I it took me one hour
to set up everything
um
but I had fun I hope you guys enjoyed
this stream maybe we can do another
baking stream sometime
soon
this was a ton of fun yeah thanks to all
the girls who called in and kept me
company it was actually quite nice to
have uh first I thought it would be like
distracting me the whole time because
I'm not good at multitasking but a lot
of the time I was just like comfortably
doing my thing while talking to them
so it wasn't so bad actually it was it
was quite nice to have company to talk
to someone while baking
you know with voice you know normally I
just have to chat but it's nice to hear
something coming back you know yeah
Japan Collins don't go well
yeah I sent I told Jenna to send the
managers you know
[Music]
a notification that I'm doing callings
and the managers
sent it to the talents but I guess they
just don't drill in
known I I knew this before
I should have known so this was supposed
to be well I keep on flicking the cake
off this was supposed to be a time for
ID and Japanese members to call in but
you know
it's okay I can only laugh about it
because I know that if I DM the members
directly like hey do you want to call
into my Collins they will try to make
time
but if it goes through management it's
just completely ignored probably they
look at it and they probably think oh
it's not coming from Kiara directly so
she's probably fine she probably already
has a lot of other people calling in so
she doesn't she doesn't need me to call
in Well turns out I didn't have a single
Japanese member calling him
they just don't know hmm
I I I I kind of suspect that this would
happen and
yeah it's okay
bystander effect
I never heard that before but that
sounds about right hmm
I think Chad stopped moving again but
yeah I was in the chat yeah she could
have called if she wanted to but I don't
know if she got the message from her
manager
I don't know if it reached her at all
it is what it is it's fine though like I
can I can talk to them another time and
it's not such a big deal honestly like
some certain person didn't call in
doesn't really it's not a big deal it
really isn't it's all good I'm not
um bothered by it I'm I just think it's
funny
dad unless you DM someone directly you
know the good thing is like for ID and
Ian we have like a server that we share
where I can just throw out this message
and be like hey I'm doing this
and they'll see it and they can react to
it but for Japanese side we don't have
that so I can't go to everyone at once
and be like hi Colin happening no I
would have to go like one by one I just
didn't have time for that this time so I
was just like hoping that maybe they
would react to my
General call well I didn't that's okay
though
um chat is not moving but I imagine you
guys talking to me thank you thank you
for your sweet and kind words
you
thanks cake for nothing
it's like more and more leaking all the
juices the putting juices in the fruit
juices is all leaking
doesn't look so appetizing I can just
maybe I'll just pick off the fruit and
just eat the fruit honestly
I'm gonna pick him up and that's what
I'm in a yogurt
I might do that
trying to salvage the situation I would
like to see what Chad says can I please
refresh it hello
I have no idea what's going on
hello
before I go I would like to see what the
chat says
uh
[Music]
is it like broken for you guys too
stream events up oh
was it broken for you guys too
it wasn't actually that not just on my
side
okay
you were just silently listening to my
speech
well this one's the main birthday stream
I think so um I want to say thank you
guys for spending another birthday with
me
[Music]
it's not as hype as a 3D birthday stream
well I did what I could I tried my best
to make up for the lack of it and
um it doesn't mean that it won't happen
at all it's just it's gonna happen way
way far away
from my actual birthday now
[Music]
and hopefully when it happens it will be
just as hype as if it would have
happened today
yeah instead you get this
relatively normal stream
put some Collins
um yeah hope you enjoyed it
see you again later on in the big
collaboration stream
I'll get a sandwich I'll make stream
reservation on everything and I'll
probably take a nap because once again
it's moving
did not let me sleep
she always lets me sleep during the
dingo stop in the morning
I don't know why happy birthday thank
you
thank you I don't know it doesn't feel
so much like a birthday
uh it just feels like a normal stream to
me
[Music]
but it's my birthday right now
thank you guys I love you guys thank you
for being at my birthday party
before spending time with me thank you
for getting the merchandise
thank you for another lovely birthday in
2023 and yeah I am now officially three
years old free
[Music]
hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
okay guys I'm out see you later when you
say
foreign
[Music]
gotcha