[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
hello
[Music]
hi
welcome welcome everyone yeah it's
growing up we're here we're ready we are
so ready ready
as right as we could be
as ready as possible hey look you know
what let it be said that we tried man I
grinded in this game we've been here
really too we've been practicing as a
team yes I don't know we're doing pretty
good we weren't doing well I don't think
we lost yeah we had some good battles
yeah yeah we were too strong together
I feel like the PC buff
[Music]
let me introduce you to the stream
today's stream if you're not aware is
the free Pokemon world championship even
alive
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah yes thank you huge thank you thank
you very much thank you thank you
exciting the first Pokemon unite World
Championship to be held in Asia we'll
start tomorrow from August 11th to 12th
in Yokohama and in the Pokemon unite
category teams from all around the world
will fight for their championship and we
will also be fighting for championship
against Indonesia and JP
representing team Hollow en and who do
we have it is serious
I have here for our team I am serious
fauna I'll be taking the Pokemon Wiggly
tough as a rule of support we also have
Miss collabi Mori would you like to
introduce yourself hi everybody Morkie
here um I will be playing as uh Garchomp
jungler
um I will be jungler or I uh I will feed
thank you
later I mean mid later mid later sorry
sorry mid laners I will be I will be mid
laner excuse me
and Iris Would you like to introduce
yourself uh hyrus is Iris I will be uh
using glacial and today uh glaceon's
wearing very cute clothes and I will be
bottom today
[Laughter]
all right next up we have takanashi
Kiara
hello
um I am representing every European out
there who is currently awake at 4 5 or 6
a.m I've been staying awake but I'm very
awake still so I think I will be fine
let's come buddy muscle I'm doing alola
nine tails because yeah what else
but it'll be great it'll be great
and we also have Amelia Watson please
introduce yourself hello Emilia Watson
number one detective today I'll be your
tank yes rely on me please
I'm going top with uh Kiara yes yes yay
so it's my bodyguard
well they're it's only a little bit of
time left before the world championship
I'm sure everyone will be a World
Championship oh wait yeah yeah well for
today for two minutes it's happening
right now
left
so how about we watch the PV together
okay I don't do a little countdown and
we can all share it on our streams okay
I hope I don't blast your guys's ears
okay the start one yeah yeah the start
yes yes first one
three two one go
our summer starts now
I love the animation yeah I love Pokemon
animation it's not pretty I broke the
budget for this one
whoa
isn't that a legendary Pokemon
look at that cash money
yeah it kind of looks like
this year I wish I looked this cool when
playing Pokemon I know right we will
we'll look this we're just we're just
holding a switch Pro cons today what you
talking about exactly
hi
I did not recognize that fish Pokemon
just now what is that something new one
of the newer ones
I know which one you mean there's so
many
there's always new fish
cute
[Music]
you guys think wow cooler that was
really cute it's fun to show anime on on
our streams yeah
I know legally permission
uh let's move on over to the event
overview I believe we are ready yup
that's the slides
I'm not I'm not ready
wait the slides uh the the slides right
okay
wait a second wait a second no slides no
slides yeah
[Laughter]
gonna play right now
stop someone can you find out for us if
this is accurate right now and we'll
just talk over it for now
hello I have a Pokemon unite World
Tournament is a promotional event for
the Pokemon u9 category of the world
championship 2023 oh I have a whole live
English and whole life Indonesia will
battle head to head to settle who will
shine on top hopefully it'll be us
the three matches will be JP versus id
id versus Ian and JP versus en and the
match will follow the WCS rules
therefore Mewtwo will be banned oh wait
are you guys showing the slides sorry
yes okay yeah wait wait they're not
they're the shoes like it's like black
wait wait
it's okay for me yeah reopen and in a
case of a three-way tie the team who
scores the most will be crowned the
winner oh so try for points tournaments
go
the winner wins
[Music]
wins and
we all get I think there's there should
be like something right constellation
prizes
mm-hmm
next slide
please okay okay
the MVPs each team will be awarded with
like real physical prizes the WCS
official uniforms which are not for sale
they're very exclusive and a few pushy
wearing the Pokemon United's Hollow air
and other teams will be awarded with 2D
trophies according to their placements
let's go for number one I know which one
we're getting let's go yeah
there's just a different difference in
color that's all you know we yeah
nothing different except for the color
if it's if it's just on the star screen
no one will know yeah they'll think
we're the winners
well speaking of the shirt or characters
in game are also wearing this shirt
which you can also purchase yourself
from the shop the digital version in the
in-game store
it
we are going first seems like it yeah
apparently okay
that's great they did amazing
well trial by fire here we go we were
doing good just remember how we were
playing yeah remember we were winning
okay don't overthink it just because
just because it's the JP okay his JP
team it's fine JB team pick pretty darn
sweaty though yeah no problem we can be
sweaty too it's got to get in the
mindset yeah you know just precipitation
right here in the other participants for
the tournament from JP we have football
[Laughter]
we're a hollow Live ID we have Ali Anya
Renee Kyla and Cobble
[Music]
yo I'll be full but they're cuteness
they're scary
they are scary I mean we're supposed to
be lore-wise you know like God's a myths
we should be pretty darn sure
and including one one one human human
the most mythical of creatures I know in
Halloween I've really been wanting well
I guess we have we got on me we have
British
I just I missed hearing your British
accent you don't bring it out very often
I wish you would let your natural accent
shine sometimes
all right
next one
I think now we wait to do the
introductions no is that all the signs
okay no for now okay okay so these are
our clothes
okay I close it okay
as mentally prepared as we thought
I was still debating on what Pokemon to
choose
yeah
well how do we get into the room
uh they will send a code and we will
input the code make sure not to show it
on stream I love how the order of the
matches it makes it seem like the whole
live JP and ID are like the the finals
yeah and I get to sleep early if yeah I
mean yeah I can sleep nah probably stay
awake anyway though no let's be honest
we gotta fight till the end yeah
three men one we're never gonna win if
we have this kind of attitude yeah we
would do it so well remember
yeah
but he objectified okay and call me if
you need help please just say Maury and
I will
yes we're losing your lane matchup you
know who to call
the code will be provided all the dragon
right
yes I think we're also gonna go into
meet the rest of the
should we do we wait until there oh it
looks like they are they are going okay
okay we go there wait are they is there
a Lobby already the all regions Channel
it looks like okay for introductions oh
so do we move too okay we go we go let's
go
really
is it real
yeah okay
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
please
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
I'm feeling motivated confident and we
need to go into this with optimism
we've been practicing believe in
yourself I'm proud of you you guys have
been climbing the ranks
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm looking forward to seeing your good
fight battle thank you
foreign
[Music]
you can't do that to me
hi sorry
believe yourself
[Music]
thank you
the food you ate no right before nervous
don't be nervous we'll be fine food your
food I ate some food I need some food
foreign
if they screw up big time then we good
oh is that the code okay
did we get it I hope it's over quickly
oh yeah there's your code okay I gotta
hide
okay hi yes hide code Avi search
[Music]
I searched the lobby
I'm in the lobby
oh I think it said something like we are
supposed to be
uh uh like a top
or at bottom like there's a specific
order they want us to be in really
yeah it was in the in the like
explanation thingy but now that the
order has changed I'm confused too but
maybe we're in the right spot because I
think it said for the first one and Ian
down for the second one
[Music]
let's go with that yeah
okay
no panicking allowed okay no panicking
play it safe play cool call for Cali as
usual okay wait so are we gonna go for
top objective first or bottom or are we
not going to decide on that we need to
be aggressive I think
should we decide on that beforehand
it might be situational depending on
where the others are okay
um I should be high enough level at a
certain point where I can kind of guard
the bottom and then also take out the
bottom objective by myself if I do the
jungle correctly
oh there is that it will be good
stay out of my jungle please
if they start to stop us and then get
our first our first uh
goal down and then they also get an
objective we can try to go and steal
their Farm in the jungle okay in the
wilderness we'll wait your command
apparently um struggles against
aggressive players so we really need to
play aggressive okay let's play
aggressive oh it's starting oh shoot not
too early I am
now right yeah yeah yeah
aggressive but safe
[Music]
it'll be fine I wonder how our team comp
is I wonder if it's
can we try to be not like screaming all
the time because it will freak me out
okay okay yeah we'll be calm calm calm
and Collective just like we're playing
against the bots so that we can also
hear fauna clearly when she wants
something from us right oh they have a
Glaceon too okay so Dragon Claw is the
meta but I'm going with earthquake so
that I can take out the bigger Farms of
swablu and alteria so and also attack
from a bit more of a distance who's
going who's going Bottom with me
okay
I think just like I hope I hope my
Gleason's better than their Glacier
we got this no problem here we go have
confidence
let's go just like practice just like we
practiced just slap God my hands are so
sweaty already
so quick we'll use it again later
for the middle go up in the middle I
mean oh gosh darn it oh see they're here
ah they are here of course they're here
what do we do next do we attack them I
am useless until level five well we'll
just poke a little bit okay
let's go and get this they're scared
they're scared
[Music]
they're playing safe they're playing
safe I want to go for the middle
don't let them steal it don't let them
steal it I just stole it did they I
think they did
okay
who needs more help bottom or top
should we go we're doing okay Bob we're
doing fine right now but we haven't
really found them I need to commit
um
their their middle person oh let's go
for the middle hold on
okay
nice nice kiss oh no oh no drift yeah
[Music]
this thing traps you damn okay yeah
we should commit I'm gonna quickly life
steal okay yeah
nice Kelly
okay
nice nice
and I keep already pressing the wrong
button let's take it down here take it
down here yeah let's go
score
steal the farm hold on oh no scissor
dude
okay I need to scissor dude's almost
dead though oh damn it okay okay I'm
lagging pretty bad
oh shoot okay hold on no one's dead
right now right okay I think I'm lagging
I'm gonna go grab Center Farm yeah go
ahead we can hold I should be able to
get some lifesteal as well
should I join down there
[Music]
um
don't worry completely like stuck on
this I think it's my internet
oh yours oh no yeah oh they're umbreon's
here umbreon's here I still see you
moving okay again I'm safe I'm safe okay
hopefully it passed and it doesn't come
back
yeah
should we go top should we wait wait
yeah I don't attack yet
I think they're gonna go for bottom yeah
they're going for bottom should we
should we interrupt I think we should
try to steal it seven okay let's try
steal it okay
you guys can go top you guys can go for
it okay good okay we'll just oh they're
coming by but like distract them
don't die don't die don't die God damn
it that's the most important
okay
um
nice nice nice
let's go
okay let's not play too impressive yeah
I mean I'm bad play safe play safe okay
welcome back go back if you have to
go back oops oops
all right that's fine
shaking I know me too my heart's
thumping if I had my heart rate monitor
now I'd be dying right now oh God we got
it ah there's nothing I'm missing you
can score maybe I don't want to grab
Center form again hold on oh actually
yeah I need to score
you think they're gonna steal it they
might but we could grab it we could grab
it
we got it you got it nice nice but we
have to protect it uh they're all right
I'm coming let's go coming let's go top
maybe I shouldn't have I broke their
thing sorry no no no no
that's okay okay we're coming we're
coming we're coming we're coming
it's okay no problem all day yummy
where's Umbreon
it's fine it's fine don't worry don't
worry
I can't really fight uh um
it's okay just uh be the bouncy person
okay
just be bouncy I'm gonna back up
yeah ideally we don't want to fight on
there yeah if we can I'm gonna get out
but I'm lagging oh no I'm sorry it's
okay we'll be fine
oh God I can't I can't get out of here
all right I'm coming I'm coming
oh they're scissors real quick hold on
can't do anything hold on okay
nice oh no I'm so sorry oh did one die
did someone die all right
sorry they also died too we're good
they also died one of them died I got
greedy I got really greedy I think that
was my okay let's see let's be
oh yeah run back my game is updating
I will be back okay let me get over here
and help
nice
actually
hold on let me grab a bottom glaceon's
green bottom okay hold on um I think
it's gonna go bottom should we should we
go back someone should go brought him
anyway
sound is pretty darn scary oh god oh
okay I committed too much
I think I think we need to farm a little
I think we're focusing too we're trying
to fight them yeah okay uh he's
background
all right hold on yeah we can try to get
the
you can try to hold bottom yeah wait
what level are we is everyone higher
than us no they're Nine and Nine yeah
oh shoot okay I got surprised
if I snuggle behind me
be nice we got it we got it we got it
keep it up I'm gonna go back to the
bottom
okay
Hyun is good
I don't know who's who who's what I know
I know I can't pop a speed
I have really nice just dropped my and
my scores though yeah we shouldn't get
greedy because we have an advantage
right now okay let's go bottom oh they
just got they just got ready guys okay
let me uh okay hold on no worries we're
coming here
no I should have known they were down
there I was not paying attention to the
map
thanks guys I will be there in a second
oh I need to be a higher level
no worries it's crazy okay
[Music]
shoot they're totally ah I'm dead okay
hold on
I'm not high enough level yet yeah we
should be careful about team fights I
think I think we need to they choose
there's only two minutes left actually
we should oh God okay we're ready we
should defend I think okay should we go
down or up
already
is going so fast stay safe
okay
we're all here we're all here let's go
let's go okay
I have something to score uh we should
defend if we can't okay okay oh they're
they're totally they're they're scoring
like crazy over there um
I know
plus 100. why am I scoring here I don't
know
it works no it doesn't work
ah
um
from
okay
we're really struggling
you didn't have to tell me oh no oh no
there's like three of them oh God I'm
dead I'm dead I'm dead oh damn it
[Music]
I don't know we just have to stop them
from uh depositing points and we can
still put in we might be even right now
um
it's true I'll defend I'll stay and
defend if you guys go okay I have no
points to put I don't know if that's
enough to go over I was willing to risk
it for a biscuit what the hell got me at
least they hey I distracted them where
are they right now I think I'm out of
this air are they at the bottom uh no
they were all the way to the right at
their home bases at their home base okay
they're probably in defense
[Music]
they know what they want already
[Laughter]
[Music]
but uh I uh was lagging really really
really bad yeah
it's not that bad
next match
we'll get them next time good job
good job
I'm proud of you guys I thought that was
pretty good yeah if only we got if we
got the recoils I'll requests yeah and
it was closed it was close because
so
[Music]
it's kind of rough yeah anyway
let's try it yeah maybe maybe check chat
for one second yeah I I needed far more
let me just accept my presence right now
the Ambush
um
so we're leaving the lobby right
are we playing again immediately
yeah immediately yeah we're warmed up
it's true but my hands are shaking I
know it's my controllers controller is
sweaty Chad I'm sorry oh is there
already a room is there a room
another one
what about now Chad
I thought it was just super quiet champ
okay okay wait do we still have a chance
right yeah okay well wait yeah we do we
do we're only behind 200 points as long
as we'll see how ideas uh yeah but they
saw us fight
you know they know our cards
it's true they watched that is true they
have that
they had a fun time watching damn it I
think I know and I thought we'd be in
that position for this next one yeah
yeah I think in that one team fights
were our weakness
because we weren't arriving all at the
same time yeah yeah gotta make sure not
to start and I was doing not to be
honest before everyone arrived oh whoops
I'm sorry wait hold on is this the wrong
but they went to the wrong one
um yeah I will try and help if I can but
I really need to try to focus more on
farming yeah yeah you're a late game mom
so you can focus on farms and we can
just try in the
try to defend yourself I'll try to help
if I can though yeah yeah
Kiara since you're looking at the time a
lot um oh yeah we just need to remember
so seven minutes the first subjective
unlocks and then at two minutes Rayquaza
so around like 30 seconds or a minute
before that we got to be prepared yeah
like at at three years at 3 30 don't use
your old I think for Rayquaza when
there's yeah 3 30 left okay
how do I move my position wait
I'll be here are we supposed to be
bottom this time I think so yeah they
were all on top so
it seems like it but I don't know
[Music]
missing fauna
here oh yeah
okay
um
yeah I I get so tunnel visioned and I
don't really get what was like after I
get to a certain level I'm just like
what should I do now yeah I think just
stay with the team or yeah
group up
I have to also focus on leveling in the
beginning because Evie is weak as hell
in the beginning and yeah I have to wait
until I get to like at least level six
or seven to get ice shard
yeah I think it too
we were focusing a lot on fighting them
and we probably should have just been
staying back and farming yeah yeah
we can try that too
okay okay okay
I think Reyna was using that bear thing
um I forgot there there's a bear yeah
there's a bear maybe she was only using
it for that stream I don't know but
they were going with like a pretty
pretty
meta-ish I think I forgot
I've got your back so let's show the
screen I forgot about that okay okay
I've gone to your back so cute I'm going
to focus on being the strongest
good buff buff
whoa
good work no laughs keep it up no I gave
up on lapis
also we need ours is doing really well
with glazing we need more we needed more
um Power anyways I think Lapras is too
too weak for this
comp
and also also because Lapras did not
have much outfits yes that is
a really cute outfit yeah if you really
don't like Zoroark
[Music]
I think she's juggler yeah I think she
is oh God we're gonna have such a bad
time
confidence up
okay okay all right all right
I believe all right I'm gonna be the
strongest right now
10 minutes and three minutes be aware
all right yes
three minutes what happens in three
minutes
you should be ready yeah what 3 30.
don't use your how long does it take for
the ultimate it depends on the character
I think yeah it depends but how many
you'll be safe if you win 3 30.
oh arranged
dang it
I want to get that form
steal it okay I think I stole it nice
I'm scared
we'll be fine uh I'm going back to heal
oh okay
they're being very aggressive
[Music]
hey I'll come down to grab well you guys
what do we do
here comes the Cali nice
[Music]
okay
I need to actually get some Buffs go
back don't make the middle middle spun
right yeah
[Music]
I'm good now
it's okay it's okay we're done we're
doing okay in the middle so yeah just
try to play safe don't die and farm as
much as you come in a pop
okay
speed up I need to keep farming actually
I need to focus on being the strongest
I'm gonna go for Middle Farm
yeah
I think they're all going for top is it
just me I think I feel like yeah
Iris do you think you can hold your own
down here
I could I could I'll try I'll try you
can you can go up I'll I'll try to just
hold the back I don't know if I could
die
okay
Kyle and bought
run go down don't fight right now come
come
oh that was close that was close yeah
you got the we got the words can I help
them I was gonna help them but never
mind oh okay
I'm lagging again oh no oh gosh man yeah
yeah just try to hold them off and just
try not to die yeah I want to score I'm
gonna score I'm gonna score this I can
solo this
I wonder if I should break it or not
um should we go down are we gonna are we
gonna try here they're all here all of
them oh nice oh we should go okay I
think all right they're gonna they're
gonna take the objection maybe we should
leave one person bottom should I say
should I stay bottom oh no okay okay
yeah and I'll try and farm at the same
time
points
[Music]
yeah we should try to defend
um but we'll have extra Farm after this
oh God I died
I shouldn't have sandwiched okay Kyle
nice nice
yeah they're really coordinated and they
are it's okay we still have the Rayquaza
I'm gonna go Center Farm two more
minutes left till Rayquaza yeah we can
take it yeah make sure to farm the
Pokemon in this Lane in the Top Lane
there will be bonus mons of uh spawn oh
because they took a farm yeah because
they took arms oh they're getting their
Farm they're getting out of here
yeah they're on the top Lane I'm also
top but all of them yeah they're all in
Top Lane it's scary
okay I think I saw at least three of
them on top we can group up let's group
up yeah okay uh what should we where
should we go just keep on top I guess
let's stay on top we should we should
Farm probably I'm gonna farm so they're
gonna come in and try to kill like
anyone
okay
should we go
oh no they're they're trying to kill me
they're oh they killed me
I look Kyla's near me
right now this is scary
how are their levels doing right now
uh let me see uh I'm still up a level
above we're in it I'm gonna go bottom
I think we should all just group up in
bottom right now
let me know if you need me somewhere I'm
farming come down with us okay yeah
that's fine
I think it's fine okay uh we should
probably go top okay
I'll wait for you oh wait they're all
down in the bottom Lane are they oh okay
we can just go top though Kyle is bottom
Lane wait did they leave they left she
can solo everything yeah
okay
I topped my score okay yeah okay
do we want to go aggressively for once
maybe maybe how fast we can get it so
here comes this little bro here they
come
oh oh no
try to last hit it again
HP HP is back now that was a party yeah
oh run run are you kidding me I love
being useless to my team all right
Rayquaza Rayquaza yeah okay that was
because of the leg let it be known let
it be known that was because of the
[\h__\h] lag baby
and see if we can make it count okay
okay yeah
thank God I didn't die
everyone should have been saving all
their stuff so we can try to win I'm
saving yes
oh okay um
oh we're really struggling yay I'm
really struggling actually hold on oh
here comes
oh
okay yep wait
yep dang it
um right just get ready for Rayquaza
okay yeah yeah I still have my old
thankfully
we do have a lot of points we could put
in yeah you might need someone to stay
and defend I'm not sure
I don't know I feel like all of us can
just go Rayquaza I think they're all
gonna go I think they're all gonna go
Rayquaza oh they're probably getting the
bottom objective yeah I can't get that
in time
they're definitely down there oh oh yeah
no no
no no yeah okay okay
get him get him get him right nice nice
you don't lose all your HP to the
Rayquaza yeah because they're gonna show
up really soon
um
drop your holds if you have them
yes okay we got it we got it got it we
got it oh my God just run run and don't
die
[Applause]
do your best try to score
I'm so sorry they're so strong lagging
so bad oh God they killed me
yeah
here I got I'm gonna pick up the points
yeah yeah
thank you
I need help Callie um I'm coming
oh they're all they're guarding the
middle they're all guarding the middle
maybe you can go top top is empty the
topper the one is yeah
fantastic I'm coming to the top too
yeah
okay okay defend defend we're in the
lead we just if they don't score they
then we win okay I'm going back yes yes
really we're in the lead how do you know
lead okay we have two pads Defenders
um I'm staying in the middle pad is that
fine go up okay I need help on this pad
I need help bottom is the bottom bottom
just don't let them score interrupt them
all right I'm coming
has nobody on it we got a guard top pad
too okay okay I'll stay on bottom though
because there's so many yeah
all right
just one person on top is enough
leave there's no way there's no way nice
yeah oh okay
[Music]
okay let's see let's see
there's no way did we
I don't believe it
did we actually I didn't wasn't able to
get turned in oh yeah
we were doing really well that's because
you died a lot doesn't mean that yeah we
died a lot we did that basically I was
the the victim for them to all you know
jump on so that they were pretty great
[Music]
another day
I'm totally sweet how are you guys I'm
so proud of everyone you're teaching us
so much
[Music]
is it for every match I think it's for
every match right for every MVP yeah
let's go yay
happy
proud of you guys
I think we did really well in the first
one
yeah
do you guys know if they sell this shirt
or not yeah and don't say no
Iris
I was gonna buy it yesterday you're like
hey I got this shirt guys I was MVP yeah
oh thank you
let's go
yeah
I'm too excited
I'm so sorry
if we maybe got in second place
hopefully we'll see after the next match
if they tally up all the points how does
that work so like if and if
if ID loses then we're first I don't get
away how does it work you would have to
get less than like 300 points which is
unlikely unless JP is
we'll see okay
it's some of the points oh
I want to spectate are we able to do
that yeah I'm gonna set up once Fonda
makes the room we just join us
Spectators first okey-dokey
on me
too much excitement
well we did good night yeah we won a
match yeah I'm proud of it I know okay
we did so well
I practice paid off oh yeah I'm glad
that we practiced a lot yeah I'm glad I
grinded like like 10 11 hours yesterday
hard
you too afana thanks for helping us
learn the game yeah I hope I wouldn't
have been able to do without you
thanks for playing
also thanks for the the tips uh chat as
well to improve my jungle game I feel
like that second that second game was
much better
yeah yeah good good strong mid lane game
let's go Ian strong man um Kyla was
scary as hell yes yes she is scary she
just comes out of nowhere and then bam
bam bam bam
so scary can we get a run back with JP
now can we try it again yeah
I know kiwawa you you want to sleep no
it's not because of that I'm not even
tired even though I've been awake since
I don't know what's adrenaline I know
adrenaline rush is real yeah
now we get to sit back and watch yeah
and no matter what happens we've already
done so
I know it's on our part we've done our
part yeah I'm really curious to see how
these aggressive teams play against each
other so for us to first place if it
were to happen
um then
what wait wait so if JP wins then we def
then JP definitely gets first place
right
um so if ID wins then there might be a
chance depending on point difference it
might be but they could get like 800
points yeah I don't know it could be a
close match with these two teams
yeah I think because I don't know I
don't know if we'll amount to uh Mike at
third place because of our yeah yeah it
was pretty close yeah third place or
maybe
yeah oh it is
we still we still
we fought we won one weekend
yeah and then the JP match was closed it
was pretty close we just kind of slipped
up at the end and yeah I should have
been stronger
the pain was holding me back
it's the bang
yeah hey the lag really got me the last
map okay we're starting
oh we're starting okay game's starting
okay I wonder how spectator looks yeah
do we get to fly around probably ah wait
I need to show oh that'll be kind of
cool I think that you I think that you
can I think we get to just fly around
the camera did you guys know that like
on the edges
edges of the what you may call it the
the map there's like this Magnemite
holding a camera yeah it's so cute this
is cute you noticed it yesterday it's
adorable
cameraman
thank you
so who do you guys who are you betting
on
um
was very aggressive yeah
we will see though
because they're both pretty strong
it will be exciting I know I can't focus
though my adrenaline's too high today
need to chill
chat who do you want me to to focus on I
can follow someone specific
yeah yeah Kyla
Kyla was it was Middle Lane right yeah
okay yeah
because JP got a break between maybe
they've you know recovered
yes you can scroll around yeah
I want to see what she does is this this
is Jason okay I know this is ID team
yeah true
so cute
the baby baby is so cute
do you feel like so efficient I didn't
know the flower was like a starfish
looking thing in the beginning
a starfish it looks like a starfish you
know the red the red yeah you're right
with the flower or like a star fruit
yeah oh yeah I could see that yeah they
seem so determined I know oh my God
I hope anyway you're really going on my
beloveds go for it
you can do it yeah they are they're
playing aggressively well yeah
the most important when is the level
going oh okay there is right now higher
level than Kayla right now
oh
man
and they're gonna shut her down yeah
it was ready for that yeah
the JP is using the grass a lot they're
like hiding in the grass most of the
time yeah did push pretty hard to get in
there no so safe
she's back in the rotation to get the
Buffs again
she's level six so is Glaceon who's
playing glacy one uh
okay
they're oh they're killing Kobo yeah
Japan yeah winning right now right now
okay
um
they're strong
Anya's chilling Anya no yeah
Anya come back there
two versus three on the top
[Music]
okay I believe in your bottom instead
is she gonna dump okay and they got one
uh
yeah let's see what they do for choosing
yeah
resolved prioritizing oh Kyla's low
again
they did push them back
we can see the point difference it's
it's interesting how they don't show the
point difference when you're actually
playing it yeah
I'm glad they didn't honestly I think I
would have choked yeah
oh yeah he's going for regular oh
they're going for the top yeah
it's gonna be a fight is there who gets
the veggies
Retreats oh oh Japan salad
you got it yeah
[Music]
I feel like yeah JP put in most of the
work but you got the fight let's go all
about the final hit
yeah everyone's on top right now yeah
everyone's ignoring the bottom yeah I
guess is much more important we defended
really well though
this is exciting I like spectating I
know me too I wish I could zoom out
zooming let's go Cobo where's she going
it's dangerous cool but there's three
there's three enemies coming
[Music]
I know right that's so weird it seems
like JP is winning but no idea is
winning oh yeah he's been picking them
off getting some kills yeah some they've
been able to get glass
okay right now JP got that oh
gosh that was a good move
are joining
oh they're scoring a lot here yeah yeah
[Music]
hey farmy always picking up the forest
Lawns yeah
[Music]
four up top
yeah it is well Cooper's going for the
bottom they're going there yeah get rid
of it uh ID has a plan for Rayquaza yes
oh they got Ollie
I feel like they would be very good
communicators the ID girl so they're
gonna yeah that's true if their
Minecraft server is anything to go by
oh they're going forward everybody in
the top is I got it they got it
that's gonna be it raining
here
oh no
so
the point difference we need you I'm not
too big still yeah the Rayquaza can
still turn it around but us being third
place has probably already set in stone
and 200 we or less like 100 we might get
second place
is it by points or is it by games one
I mean I mean one if there's not a tie
okay okay I think I think yeah if I mean
if JP wins this then I think by points
we'd be okay but if they get Rayquaza
what is what I mean
um
she's alone
one versus three oh here they come here
comes the rescue plan this was the bait
JP sniper coordinated as well
there she is oh they got it
if you got it
one minute
yeah we'll see how Rayquaza goes and
stuffy that's the main place yeah we're
all cheering for ID for a lot of reasons
[Music]
I see how coordinated JP is I'm feeling
like proud that we held them I know
we've got it together pretty good
against them to be honest yeah I feel
like I died Too Much I Feel So Close it
was close if only I didn't die that much
I'm just like ah if you've got any
questions dang it uh I should have aimed
my old better
[Music]
our grind was I think we did pretty good
yeah
[Music]
20. it's only in our practices our
enemies weren't so good so so
I know a lot of them
oh no wow they're really they're really
going for Reggie Reggie like you when
Rayquaza is gonna yeah they respond
really soon interesting yeah yeah
they're just gonna go for an afternoon
but yeah Randy's already starting
Rayquaza yeah
here they come here comes everyone
who's gonna get it oh oh they took they
took that one in Japan the other three
they're three oh okay then it's just out
they took down the energy too oh which
one
you got it
oh
yeah
that's a lot let's go oh they're they're
done
it's over yeah they come back oh wait
there's a hundred points up up top tech
oh yeah for 100 points she is
gonna be so close foreign
I think and everyone else is going
offensive
what is the right answer for this one
be careful I don't know
ID defend Maybe
I don't know what the points are yeah
they don't know the point that it's a
close man yeah they have no idea
keep running
yo oh my God
they got the points in yeah
he's gonna try and score these points
yeah let's go
nice the clothes that was awesome that
was so clutch
wow what a gamer
I know it's good imagine a really good
match yeah yeah great it's like clothes
for everyone that was amazing whoa wait
so everybody won one match yeah yeah now
it's all according to points oh [\h__\h]
well guys we did our best yeah
me too we did well
I mean look at how scary and chaotic and
crazy that battle was like yeah
going up against these girls is quite a
challenge it is huge that was huge
for that mvp good job Japanese sign
Ed only were the MVPs yeah
everybody did well
I am I'm proud of everyone I'm proud
yeah everyone knew what to do pretty
much yeah there was nobody that was like
fumbling around like I didn't practice
yeah yeah
I can confirm I did practice a lot
that was fun that was really fun it was
fun that was really fun yeah I think I
might try to play more this season to
hopefully get to Ultra
I'm playing
so this is this is
this is a closer
[Music]
like it feels like sports like the team
camaraderie yeah I want to play games
together too like I don't know yeah yeah
fun collab game I think it's a good
satsu game too yeah in general yeah once
you know what to do you just kind of
yeah if you're not too sweaty
foreign
[Music]
I just need to
prepare
yeah for the chat asking we don't know
the final tally yet we don't know yet we
do not know did you know man then you
may know
cameras don't tell us we don't want to
know we want to stay oblivious
Nomads yeah if you can do math your band
smarter than the fifth grade a first
grader
will at least be in the top three I
think so
videos
[Music]
if you think about it like the Olympic
bronze medal is something very something
very proud
as big of an honor as that
I'm proud that we won a game I saw so
many people saying hey we are not gonna
win it destroyed
[Music]
I thought they're gonna walk all over us
yeah
we've been training we've been working
but I was ready to be the most beautiful
carpets there to be no no wrong I have
an orange carpet right you have to be a
flying carpet Yara you have to be a
flying one where am I flying to Flying
to Victory
pad
for a dump Underdog prevailed
well chat did you guys enjoy watching
that did you know what was going on all
the time it was at least fun to watch
yeah I never knew this could be so
sweaty like these kind games yeah yeah
yes yes whenever I saw like games like
this like you know and I see like
tournaments going on and whatnot I look
at it and I always like oh they're just
spamming skills it's just like an MMORPG
was it that I was like oh that was fun
but I don't why is this so competitive
now I get it yeah we put it all into it
almost the end when we like joined this
in kikaku I don't think we any of us
expected it to be dead serious I didn't
I didn't I thought it would be more it
would just be a fun
just a fun fact
friendly yeah friendly competition
but I'm really proud because I think we
trained enough to make it like
interesting matches yeah definitely
it wasn't too one-sided in any of the
matches yeah the thing is like a lot of
Japanese and ID members were already
like really well practiced in this game
and I've seen a lot of master
um ranks
so you know yeah we just started playing
a lot of us just started playing yeah
like four days ago yeah
but we put in the work feels good I was
playing in my dreams like last night
you were playing pretty late last night
yeah yeah did you win in your dream or
did you lose uh well I was just like
attacking stuff in my dream but then
when I was trying to fall asleep I was
like running around in the game and I
kept running into walls and it was
really frustrating it's like it's like
nightmares
oh yeah
I get chased a lot in my nightmares just
like here in Pokemon United
so it was a nightmare no no not at all
just play more
yeah yeah it'd be kind of fun great
match remix
I don't know I'm kind of scared to
rematch
have you used all your power I know yeah
I'm happy with the way we've performed
yeah
[Music]
it's so much more fun to like play with
like friends and like VC than one year
it was so frustrating yesterday when I
was like you know queuing by myself and
then like oh yeah the random would like
you know leave me in the in in the area
alone and I'm just like why and
everyone's at the top in the beginning
I'm like what the why do you do that I'm
like I'm Central
I'm Central I'm jungle and then I wait
like five seconds and then right before
the match starts somebody else says I'm
jungle and I'm like are you kidding me I
might as well not even do it
yeah I also had troubles playing alone
soloing regileki so many times why I was
like why don't you girls wanna go up
there and get that objective why not
[Music]
they were just there to steal it after I
already got it yeah
it feels bad man feels bad but this
feels good man yeah I like playing with
the five stack yum yeah I'm still I
still don't know if the held items I
chose was the correct answer though I
didn't go with like the most standard
build I went with
I chose something else for the because I
wanted to make myself less squishy but I
was still very good I was still really
squishy so I'm just like maybe I should
have gone all offensive I don't know oh
they're going up now yeah I think it's
time okay the final result
we gotta go check it out let's go I
gotta set up the window though so hold
on
okay
[Music]
wait a sec
one moment and gotta set up the slides I
I slide slide again
[Music]
hold on hold on hold on guys excuse me
I got it thank you I got it I got it
I got it size wise it looks a little
awkward
sorry I'm sorry this wasn't supposed to
play this I'm sorry uh I'm sorry how do
I turn it off
oh my gosh sorry
[Music]
thank you for your good bottle arigato
yay
[Music]
I don't know
are you ready for it
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
there we go
it's a big team ID team and third place
is in team so you come today
yeah everybody good job good job
everyone yay
[Music]
amazing
let me know you were sold
um as a leader in leader please hear you
are sold
I'm really proud of everyone many people
doubted the ENT but I hope that we
showed we showed our abilities today I
think we did I'm proud of everybody
we did our best
thank you thank you for your team it was
really amazing amazing match yeah
as a leader only time please say
yourself hi
um we we all worked really hard like all
of us really strategized a lot do you
guys have anything that you guys would
like to say ID team
um
[Music]
thank you yeah
where's already aggressive and we never
never give up right
we can see a very good teamwork
communication thank you so much
thank you so much
I'm really glad you enjoyed this much
it is
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Applause]
only jump
thank you and not only this so I don't
know anybody
it is
MVP is
oh my God
[Music]
um
founder is MVP yeah
[Music]
congratulations
she taught us the way
but on a soul great leader you go to MVP
in the first match and you're really
supportive
[Music]
yes
in the idea region Ollie you are MVP
yeah you go to MVP and you contribute to
the uh comeback comeback Victory bye
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's not the concert birth
foreign
[Music]
thank you
ugh
oh so we on the stream now or something
I think the last video we showed the
last video yeah just give me a second
hold on
because when we left the slide thing you
played it can I play it yeah one more
slide we need to show one more slide
one more slides really oh okay okay okay
okay okay one second
let me pull up the slide
it's my time
oh is it slides it's not not the video
oh okay okay okay
if this
is deciding a man and I'm deciding the
actual one movie I know right
you can also do predictions right now
it's true you can do predictions in the
in the game you can get predictions
right you get prizes I heard personally
that the team uh Peru is absolutely
cracked really really yes okay no no I
don't know
I predicted also on orangutan
let's go
wait is there European oh yeah there are
European teams I should probably cheer
for them
go Europe go Europe let's go man let me
let me remind everybody and did the
Pokemon unite category of WCS will
happen tomorrow and here is a slide of
all the participating team members uh
the Pokemon category will be streamed on
the channel listed in the description
tomorrow 9pm November 11th jst tomorrow
and of course you can predict in the
game we're just talking about something
for it right you will win prizes if you
guess correctly so please check it out
please watch the stream and cheer for
your favorite team
and we'll see you all tomorrow
yeah yeah and with that I think that
wraps everything up I'm really proud of
you guys I think we did really well yeah
considering considering like you know
how much we didn't really know yeah much
in the beginning
yeah that's why Yeah final MVP really it
makes a lot of sense thank you thank you
I want everyone to get MVP though
[Music]
yes I think I'm really proud of us
genuinely we might have got third but
they were close matches they were good
matches yeah it wasn't a huge Point yep
it was totally exactly it was it's
pretty close I feel good about it
with Matt shall we play the ending PV
okay there are streams yes then jump
away yeah all right thank you everyone
for watching thank you thank you guys
thank you thank you so much for the
support it was really fun we're not
where are we are we muting during the
video
okay okay okay
let's do three two wait wait wait wait
wait I'm not ready
all right we're good okay I'm ready I'm
ready okay
three two one go Pokemon unite recently
celebrated its second anniversary allow
us to introduce
yeah congrats oh this map
yeah
this looks fun oh cool I didn't even try
that yeah I wonder if it'll be a just as
sweaty
the extra strong YouTube
too strong is not allowed strong you too
via an event happening now and starting
August 17th you'll also you could get
your Mewtwo today
um
why Mewtwo was this like tiny unite will
continue
[Music]
in Pokemon Unite plus we're also holding
healer holaware for Pokemon like huge
stylish please join us
second anniversary
cute
[Music]
yeah
yeah thanks so much for everything you
guys that was fun yeah that was fun
thanks
for inviting us for this thank you very
much a lot of fun yeah I'm really glad I
was able to take part in this and
experience this type of game yeah yeah
fun training with everyone I'm glad we
were able to train in the morning
[Applause]
first type of this genre game yes it was
fun thank you soon
I'm so tired
[Laughter]
well I believe that's all we have for
today we can let everybody get some rest
yeah we tried our hardest
thank you thank you thank you very much
thank you very much
later thank you very much thank you for
cheering us on
us thank you for believing in us thanks
thanks
have a great day bye
I've been down here before
[Music]
do you do you see the lighter does it
ever been oh
[Music]
thank you
ah
that was sweaty that was fun though
I really enjoyed the grind yesterday
and
I don't know if we have if we will be
able to stream this again but I think
I'll probably keep continue playing it
was fun and uh I am I'm gonna be very
very very busy on this upcoming
this upcoming week
yes um
like extremely busy uh I also have to go
out today after this I have to shower
and go out and
yes do some learn some stuff do some
stuff uh
but I will try to stream as much as I
can in between there's gonna be days
where I'm just gonna be out like the
whole whole day
like from morning to night
um starting yeah around next week so
just a heads up but but I'll try to you
know I'll try to sneak in like at least
a space or something if I can at some
point yes
thank you very much for coming it was a
lot of fun and thank you once again
thank you very much
um okay man united for inviting us it
was a lot of fun I'm really glad I was
able to experience this it was a lot of
fun playing with with other young
members alrighty then thank you guys so
much
I might have screwed up but but I tried
my best
thank you bye virus