[Music]
la
a
[Music]
no no
la
[Music]
I spilled so
much
[Music]
uh not hot
chocolate [\h__\h] on my chair on my table
on my shirt on my
pants what is this fancy mechanism of
double lid where the lid underneath is
just like transparent
and like you can't tell where the hole
is supposed to be
[Music]
oh oh oh I am
stiff from all the dancing
[Music]
wait stiff CH K oh my
God sorry I woke up like an hour ago but
I slept so much I slept like
probably 10
hours thank God but all of it I swear
all of it even though I woke up several
times in between all of it was one
nightmare one big
nightmare so that's what I get in
exchange for a long
sleep yeah yeah and no no I already
cleaned up like most of it like there's
a few like drops on the table that I'm
licking M iron metal
M uh it's
okay no I'm like I'm not licking the
table I'm licking my finger after I
picked up the
[Music]
drop anyway
um beware of cat hairs my cats are not
with me can you be a little bit more
sensitive right now my cats are in
Austria and I am still in
Japan
but
uh not much longer and I can finally go
home uh oh how the turbo stain how the
turo stain that sounds
correct yeah uh the past three days is I
have missed playing with
everybody because day one and two I had
like 10
hours of recording each day which was
fun and
exhausting and then yesterday I also had
some more work to
do uh in the studio
so I missed free dungeons free
dungeons I missed ena's dungeon I missed
my own dungeon and I missed amma's
dungeon and I missed I guess a lot of
like role play
lore stuff
incidents I was like thinking is there
even a point of me still coming back is
there a point I don't
know partially I feel like no but I'm
here
now I asked
around if someone can join me um do
dungeons uh ketchup and well of course
Raa has been
saying at any time that she'll help me
what a [\h__\h]
angel um but she won't join until an
hour in I think I was hoping to do at
least one dungeon a bit a bit earlier
but I'm not
sure U if there is anybody willing to do
anything with me besides
laa um so we'll see let let me huh
didn't I already I opened the game
already where did it
go yeah I know fauna I think fauna is
the only one online right now
uh oh yeah Amit yeah cuz like nobody
nobody in myth uh did the Amit dungeon
yet I think so I asked myth like hey but
I didn't get replies they probably
didn't all see it and cie cie saw it but
she's sick uh and she's she can't play
until like after her outfit reveal she
has an outfit reveal today yippe I think
I already saw it it's really really cool
M well get well soon
Al there it is there it
is had it open already I guess I closed
it
accidentally yeah Ena starts in 4 hours
yeah that's like pretty late like that's
when wait is there another dungeon
opening today no right is there like cuz
all the myth dungeons are open now so I
wonder if the last two days is just
like like for everybody to do like side
quests and and whatever like role play
and maybe catch up on Dungeons and stuff
yeah today and tomorrow I guess would be
a free day
Nissa Nissa are you busy you you don't
want to like log in and help me redo a
[Music]
dungeon yes I want you please I love
you let's do like one Dan in like maybe
the Ena
dungeon I want you so bad let me grab R
okay y I was actually like really like
hoping to play more with narissa because
so far I only participated in two days
uh the first two days and like I I I
just couldn't end up with a in a group
with her
somehow because of fate I
suppose so maybe today is the day
finally also I keep on seeing everybody
having backpacks how the hell do you get
a backpack maybe narissa will tell me
maybe she can help me get a
backpack yeah I heard that at least my
dungeon cannot be
soloed uh so I'll definitely have to do
that with somebody but I think when
we're done with ena's dungeon let's say
me and Thea do ena's dungeon wait where
is
and then me and la and maybe Nissa if
she wants to still be with us could do
my dungeon and then and then am is
dungeon so I don't know if I should
still wait
for No am d a lot of people haven't done
amed's dungeon yet I guess so could wait
but uh
yeah I wouldn't mind soloing something
too like early on but we have Nissa now
it seems any a lot of things happen here
can people
enjoy explain this to
me never I joined again Yi wait up audio
turn that on thanks for the membership
welcome this is f not
here hi finally wait I now I have to
close your stream unfortunate you look
so powerful with that purple
Sparkle thank you okay how can I carry
you today Miss
Takashi I remember you because I did I
did your dungeon you remember
me but you don't remember yourself huh
uh actually I don't know what's wrong
with all of you guys for me I I just
like I'm a phoenix and me dying is kind
of like normal and then Reviving is
normal so I always lose my memories for
like a short time and then it comes back
to me pretty soon so I pretty much
remember like everything already like
mostly all right
well W yes should we just do it
ourselves or should we find and ask FAA
too uh fauna is building the library she
so she's busy yeah she's busy but we can
we can solo it just the two of us okay
just the two of I don't know I want to
just ask just in case although I don't
want to press her but just ask so is she
in there is that the library she's in
the tall building that's being built
she's
she there she is yeah big chandelier
hello greetings to you fair
lady
greetings um I I I don't want to
pressure you uh what you're building is
beautiful I just wanted to ask if you
want to take a break and do uh the ENA
dungeon one more time with me and Nara
but you don't have to I I just want to
like lay out the
offer um I think I'll pass if that's
okay it's just it's just puzzles anyway
so if I come along I'll just be spoiling
it I'll I'll bury you anyway on accident
no no no no don't tell me anything okay
okay then have fun building
Library it's already looking so good I
can't wait to see it later what books do
you have we've got at least four books
yeah with actual
books um
no we've got yahi we've got Yuri we've
hey hello those books didn't exist in
the medieval fantasy roleplay times I'm
sure they
did definitely did but they were
forbidden some way they were
forbidden forbidden scriptures no no B
they're going to be on the top level
Library yeah exactly yeah forbidden
scriptures they must be burnt I must
burn this library with my Phoenix Fire
come on come on Phoenix you can't burn
down the library of scarlet wand well I
I well it's not even finished yet so
maybe after it's finished just kidding
good luck good luck thank you good luck
you
too okay wait my quest currently says
speak to the Cerulean uh cup Guild
Master wait should we get into a group
and a call uh yes we should do that good
thinking moyy oh one second
okay
oh ah hello hello all right I do you
know where she is or should I lead you
uh I will just follow my
map uh unless you know it by heart I do
okay wow I shall lead you sasuka my my
beloved
yippe what my horse is
jumping oh yeah they do that it needs an
apple
or or put here she is
ooh oh best scores of what I have no
idea what this is
interesting okay all right Celesta ah
was was this the French one this was the
French one is she French can you do a
French accent yeah for me she's oh Al
okay I don't want to make any claims but
um uh wait uh uh the ancestors blessings
upon you kind
EO it's
perfect thank you uh wait this is so
difficult okay uh as you may have heard
our Scouts cited the same light coming
from the forest that lies past the
Mountain
Road we lost access to that region when
the Calamity overtook it but it seems
the Calamity has withdrawn for the
moment
uh Mays The Growing Power of uh
Revelation within you has given
s
sore uh to this uh blighted land I must
warn you even before the Calamity uh
that forest was known as an aured Place
indeed I am love love to send you into
such
danger guil Master what of our sister
who are stationed near the forest oh
that was someone else well they all have
the same voice and same accent they know
the region well and can surely guide the
hero
safely uh quite very well no wait that's
quite so very well kindo seek our
Sisters of the seruan cup coup upon uh
your
arrival as to reach the cursed Forest
you must cross the Plains and follow the
Mountain Road your path will be FR but
we will provide uh what a we can May the
ancestor protect you and may your heart
art be your
compass all
right woohoo so French so beautiful okay
all right follow me yes you know we got
to go to the Mountain Road and speak
with Cassandra
Cassandra do you like to say Cassandra
or Cassandra Oh well Cassandra Cassandra
cassand I think I would go for
Cassandra yeah yeah you like surprised
Cassandra I do like
Cassandra because it sounds more British
because you're secretly into uh
Elizabeth where did you go uh where did
you go oh did you go left oh there you
go okay
this is the way oh wait it sounds like
quas okay I'll call her
quandra
quas hello
qura because French mhm makes sensey
Wy we we bugget we bugget how you doing
tell me oh I'm doing good I've gotten
back a lot of memories about uh this
group called myth oh yeah yeah yeah very
important group mhm very very important
it seems they seem to be very
influential yeah mhm very cool so
amazing so cool so go oopsie freaking
horse talk to me
oh
you're you're one of the heroes it's an
honor to meet you that's right I'm one
of the San C Coupe members stationed in
this region
but um I'm afraid I cannot assist you
right now you see when I was scouting
the forest I found some animals who were
a badly who o ooh o o were a badly
Hur they were attacked by the stains and
they barely escaped with their lives I
came to the road to see if anyone could
help but that's uh when you arrived I I
have
tell of your kindness and
benevolence EO won't you help help me
save
um all I need is some nourishing soup s
to give them one spoonful and they'll be
feeling better in no time at at least I
hope soup soup you got to cook soup wait
I have the perfect super person Wait no
that's outside of this world I know of
nothing I don't know your soup Endeavors
I don't know of any of that or you don't
know but I know yeah what soup what
let's see for nourishing soup we need a
carrot potato sweet berries and a water
bucket damn she already knows it all I
have it in a book oh but do you have the
ingredients for it we can find them come
with me all right
yippee yippee I love soup me too wait
where the hell am I
um huh um where did we just go I thought
you were quite experienced with uh
traveling these lands what the hell
what's happening I thought you would be
a great
companion I'm sorry where does this lead
we will find
[Music]
out looks yes right yeah yes okay okay
sorry now I now I know why I was
confused towards the sun or moon or
whatever that is that is the
Sun a it is the and Juliet is the
son what Juliet is the son it's it's I
thought she was a
daughter
no okay wait wait wait wait wait stop
stop stop okay so here's the
shopkeeper so you can buy things off him
you you need to buy a carrot potato and
sweet berries carrot potato and sweet
berries and we need a bucket right yes a
bucket filled with water do you have a
bucket okay I have iron I shall make the
bucket well let's go across the street
mhm I actually also have a cooking pot I
made I did the side quest like on day
two oh
nice well here's the nearest crafting
table
ah wait don't can you
when you use the cooking pot do
you uh do you just do you still need the
bucket in the cooking pot yeah because
you need water the bucket the the bucket
will uh yeah it's interesting I I
thought the same thing I was like why
can't I just put water in the
pot what's the shape of a bug head oh oh
I think it's a V shape I'm not sure okay
what that's a mine cart like a
V like middle far left and far right in
the bottom oh okay I got it I was making
it way bigger than it needed to be okay
yeah I I kept doing that too and then
there's water right here oh
oh
magnificent
Divine
mhm okay and now I use my cooking pot
yeah wait can you only do this with a
cooking pot yes oh so you had to do this
side quest anyway eventually yeah
exactly okay it doesn't matter how I put
them in there no you just put them in
and then you click click the cook icon
oh
wonderful oh oh how beautiful
ooh Divine I made it they only need one
right all right yes um let's quick do
you have any food on you I have four
bread and five
steaks uh so we're going to you're going
to buy some bread before we go actually
purchase bread when I still have meat
that I could
cook
yes no trust me just okay I'll I'll cook
a little bit of U meat over there and
I'll buy a few breads oh okay okay okay
okay okay
okay from FAA Mar no no no we're not
buying buy anything from
fart no no oh what was that no no
purchasing from funart no this is not
funart right it's not secretly connected
with
oneart I mean uh you could he he's
wearing blue so probably not good good
good okay I have a total of 34 bread now
does that Delight you uh I'm more
delighted than I was
okay very well very well let's see okay
my my stained meat is almost done uh
being blessed by the holy coal to return
to normal edible steak
meat
yes the soup oh I that's what happened I
ate the soup by
accident I right clicked it oh well you
have to make another soup
then Mama
Mia Mama Mia no
M okay I'll make another oh wait the
bucket's still okay the bucket's still
there that's how they get
you they convince you they convince you
to accidentally eat your own soup the
smell is too enticing to resist
M yeah taste test it was a taste test so
I'm not like accidentally uh poisoning
anybody you got to make sure that the
soup is nourishing right yes it wasn't
indeed nourishing did it give me a buff
or
something uh I think some food just give
you a buff I don't know I never I've
never made nourishing soup I only make
potato salad M yum yum I tried that once
but it didn't really increase my uh
jumps that
much uh I don't make it for that reason
oh well what reason just
for uh I'm I'm I I'm on the black market
of potato salad
money exploit oh yeah
wait you broke the economy says the
voice is in my
head yeah I have 47,000 nervous
[Laughter]
laughter okay he don't eat the
nourishing soup yeah I'll try not this
time let me rearrange this okay we shall
return
okay this way
okay wait you have
47,000 gold are you a rich lady I am a
rich
lady who are you very rich are you beted
to somebody I've heard there have been
many bet tring in my absence well h i
the the voices in my head have said that
me and you are are married actually you
you said you you have your memories is
is that true yeah I don't want to spoil
you but it is true and it has been
breaking my heart to see you with other
ladies well um there's lots of marriage
happening in the land of
lestel uh Irish has five wives keki viu
who is the princess and daughter of
Queen Mario Mario also known as adada
um she she has three three wives me and
Shor and Iris are some of them I I'm not
really sure what's going on
anymore
okay this ISC Cassandra yeah it's it's
it's complicated it's okay
though okay I I just uh skipa skipa and
gave her oh no did I did I did I give it
to her yet yeah okay we are ready to go
into the eldrid dungeon while you tell
me more about what happened in my
absence yeah uh generally uh Scarlet
wand has with their uh store been
gaining funds for the library which we
are finally building it is not a dream o
anymore but a reality uh the Scarlet
wand Library so are
you with them I am a member of scarlet
wand yes and and a employee at fom Mar I
thought so because of your tall Red Hat
usually as sense danger in the Pres
presence of a red hat
but with you I shall be certain of your
goodness in your
heart it is no
worry would you like to ready up I have
indeed then we shall enter
enter HRA dungeon I am I have sanity in
this dungeon well look over here there's
a story or something all right it's
started out it started out as any
afternoon like any other the girl was on
her way to the library oh the library
that
Library same
Library I don't think so sadly enjoying
the pleasant warmth of the sun when
suddenly a clap of
as a clap of Thunder shook the
clown she flinched in Surprise and when
she looked down she found an ancient to
in her
okay okay those ass cheeks be clapping
that happens lead the way oh okay looks
like we're coming upon some sort of
shrine don't you think oh wow it looks
like from a completely different world
one I have never seen before right oh
what are these shapes what is this
architecture that is so unfamiliar to
me but it is beautiful I sense
some mystical power here mhm
wow oh wa what is this hey Miss nice to
meet you who are you have you seen my
friends I've been waiting for them but
now that you're here you can play with
me instead a the first game is smashing
pots oh let's go sounds fun sounds like
a children game the last time I played I
smashed five pots without getting
caught good for you I had to be really
sneaky it was so exciting
okay you should try it's really fun okay
where the pots let me smash
them smash
them well let's oh cool it looks like
they all have symbols on them and
there's these books here oh indeed okay
let me let's see the cool thing is I am
now unless you spoil me forced to figure
this out on my own without any party
members using their brain cells
save me well I I could help you but okay
now I'll try to figure it out first uh
let's see do these books say something
creepy to creepy to yes or no would you
like to read the creepy to no oh they're
all creepy TOS mhm oh read
them okay I read this red creepy tomb
the man raising both arms may be broken
ah okay
that already sounds great yeah right do
I break it with my sword yeah okay won't
it be too much of I lost the sanity
point oh no arms up potery shirt do I
take
it oh no it says Ah it asks me would I
like to smash yes smash all right smash
well good you found one I guess we
should read the rest of the books then
yes uh this one says oh creepy to again
but kind of in a why is it
gray I'm not sure that which is only a
face must not be broken okay
cool the cracked heart may be
broken oh interesting cracked heart may
be broken oh well done break the broken
heart
done this is not too difficult the
turtle may be broken cool
turtle turtle ah cute turtle turtle more
toed
house I just so basically I just have to
do this before my sanity is done for
oh oh I get like a black like my eyes my
eyes turn black every once in a while
it's weird
[Music]
happen are these the same books old of
those used in battle only one may be
broken M okay that's a that's a little
bit more of a ridddle that which is
already broken may be broken
H is there broken heart I think that is
maybe another hint towards the broken
heart oh okay okay
okay then so only one weapon may be
broken we have two we have an arrow and
a sword wait of those who which relate
to liquid only one may be broken that's
again kind of vague uh that which is
small may be broken small one liquid
related thing and a small thing and one
of the
weapons wait do we still have we only
have one liquid thing now I think a
strange potion may be
broken strange potion may be
broken is it strange though I'm not sure
if it's
strange oh God but there's only there's
only one so we might as well break it
right okay was there something else of
liquid that I already broke no I don't
think so okay
that which is made with string must not
be broken
so the diamond may be
broken wait wait wait wait wait wait
that was just made for string I would
think that's either the bow or the the
bow cannot be broken so I think the bow
and fishing rod probably know but you
can break the
diamond how did you come to that
conclusion because the book said that
you can break the diamond oh I didn't
see that one okay it says the diamond
may be broken okay
destroy okay oh look our is only at 38
let's go oh let's go that was it
yippee smashing PO is
fun yeah let's play some
more cute it just wants to play yeah you
know I once got lost in this funny old
house mhm no matter how many doors I
went through I couldn't find my way out
it was like a maze ah that kind of a
maze I see I wanted and wanted for so
long it was really
scary oh don't worry it's not scary
anymore recover 20 sanity points yippee
I feel so much more sa story oh ever
since that day the girl was accompanied
by a cluster of enormous wriggling
tentacles
M maybe cut them off strangely enough
they didn't seem to bother her at all in
fact she appeared to have complete
control over them oh how
fun weird though that sounds dangerous I
would want to stay away from someone who
has huge wriggling tentacles around
them and so she continued reading her
books as though nothing had
changed a okay that's good follow
me through the
cobwebs oh somebody needs to clean up
here
oh what what what is this oh no don't
don't no no follow me don't worry okay
don't worry about it wait you're not
really supposed to spoiler me for it
though no no no no trust me where you go
trust me where'd you go I lost you no no
no here no go go backward
backward uh I unlocked the checkpoint
hey nice I just went for a random one
hoping to trigger
you you did you triggered me I don't
know where you are I lost you is there
hints as to like how to know which one's
the right one um I don't think so uh I
need to let you know uh pay attention to
the pathway if you see one leading into
a wall you might want to follow
it
ahuh uh into the wall
ahuh
oh
well into the wall
where
[Music]
oh ah it's it's did you find
it um I can't walk through the wall it
seems e you should be able to if if the
path leads into the wall ah
uh oh the door stays open interesting ah
um what's this one oh okay that doesn't
do anything I see your
name I think
yeah oh here it is ah come here here
here
here aha look walk follow the path
oh
mysterious what's that
what is that the end of the
dungeon no okay so oh ah that's Ah
that's where that's just like where you
get the secret chest to get the CD uhhuh
the the not the CD
um what's it called a v vinyl vanill
yeah vinyl
yippee do you have the first one
yes I do I saw you found it and so they
were very kind and walked me through
getting
it thank you for finding that there's
one more game I want to play can you go
find a lily of the valley oh I've heard
of that before bring it here and plant
it in this flower pot near me a lily of
the valley there should be flowers and
stuff and chest all around the
shrine oo there are lots of different
kinds but I'm only interested in ladies
of the valley could you get one for me
please sus I don't know this thing is
kind of
weird be oh there's another story Over
Yonder Over Yonder
mhm interesting choice of words it
started out as an evening like any other
the girl was on her way back from the
library when she
suddenly what when suddenly she stopped
and turned around what is it no one else
was there and yet she clearly was wasn't
talking to herself do you want to play
some more with a soft smile she started
climbing the stairs to the shrine with
those
legs none of the ones over here have it
so you can skip the three chests over
this way okay okay well let me let me
Che them all let me look yes through the
others I see a
chest peekaboo
azour I found it it's up here no I will
I'm sorry I look for it it's in a random
place every time I didn't find it on
purpose I swear well I'll still look
around as if I you know as if you don't
know that it's uh near me
yeah I want to these chests yeah they
they just got little flowers in them
cute perhaps I shall take one and gift
it to you me lady so kind and
considerate very very very uh mindful
very
Demir so Demir Demir how do you say that
de deir de another weird word that has
popped up from the
future yeah mysterious
future what does it
mean
deir like well I know
but I don't know but I know oh I it's
it's just a meme it's just it's just Tik
Tok thing I know oh I didn't know it
came from Tik Tok yeah someone just
being weird being like very Demir very
mindful so mindful so Demir and then and
then everyone just started saying it cuz
it was an unhinged thing to
say unhinged I think it is very demure
not unhinged hey come check this chest
by
me our sanity is lowering I don't know
where you are are I'm up near the top H
okay I found something that looked
similar to a lily but I guess that's not
it it was is aily's purple no no this
way this way am I going the right
way you
were here see me ah I see you thanks to
your huge red hat
thank thank go God for the hat right mhm
oh wow look at this chest right here I
can't throw it away
oh oh this chest yeah looks promising
[Music]
right why thank you thank you for the
flower M lady a poy a poy a poy a poy in
these trying
times a lily of the
valley
yippe let's
go well I saw a lot of beautiful flowers
but you are the most beautiful of them
all Nissa ravencraft if that is your
actual name in this world I yeah it is
okay it is people have different names
unexpected ones yeah Tam Gander I'm
Shakira by the way oh Shakira yes
Shakira Shakira if you say my name twice
I shall come by summoned from uh the
desert oh it seems I have done it
yes well then I shall play the video
[Music]
Yeah Shira of the oranges
yes dungon finito oh let me play let me
play I downloaded the video Let me let
me look at my
Memoirs wa wait wait wait
wait full
screen
Ena I know her I remember her okay here
we go
um monitor only
let's
go I'm watching how many have visited
this place by
now at least two or three whenever the
book shows me someone new I always feel
a little
sad some say I'm acting as a GU to help
them move on but to me I'm just keeping
them company I asked them what they were
good at what they were bad at what they
never got to
do each answer is a
[Music]
surprise they all had more potential
than they ever could have
known or each and every one of those
moments is precious to me she drew a
huge version of it
amazing oh big
octopus
oh so we basically did what she's been
doing we played with the
ghosts yeah damn how's she doing
that I don't
[Music]
know
bye-bye
bye-bye oh there goes the
leaf why why leave take care out there
why why did you leave me leave
okay that was
the thank you for helping me with this
one yeah do you need help with your
Onsen too my
my it seems you have observed my
Diaries I've become quite the pro at at
the onen
Yen
MH really um can we wait 15 minutes so
that L joins us Queen Tim tender you you
have to you have to do the uh prep
preparations R is Queen Mario EXC oh
[\h__\h]
oops do not Mi up your Queens you get my
my the queen I follow is Tim
tender you follow Tim Tander yeah
because I believe in her and like I I
need to be loyal to her otherwise why is
what am I I need to follow my duties as
a knight of
hers well as long as you're
happy thank
you don't you like the queen Tim tender
just because of her absence now
everybody decides you
tender uh
Tam Ginder Tam like
Tammy Tam gander
t t
t Tam t a m Tam T ch ch ch
Chandler no no no no Tam like
Tammy T
CH
Chandler you're you're too ESL I can't
with you yeah excuse me excuse me I'm
sorry I Gander I as far as I can tell
I'm saying it
correctly no I I regret to inform you
turn your quest I've got to I've got to
kill some cows so I will follow all
right all right I'm going to go back to
the we we buet Lady Tim Taylor She's to
the left to the left oh amazing that is
a really um valuable hint that you have
given me yes you are welcome mhm
okay Celesta it is me again I have done
the thing welcome back kind EO I see the
ancestor has returned you to us safely I
understand you must be Ti from your qu
[Music]
qu but uh police spare a moment to share
with us what you have learned Within the
Ruins
yeah sure yappa yappa yappa yappa oh
mercy Buu kind EO so as we other ruins
you recovered some of your memories and
with them some of your power of
revolation uh persevere along this path
and you may soon recover enough memories
uh to face sustain King sustain King oh
I forgot about that oh okay we we
thank you
uh okay and the coin oh welcome
wait oh wait a
moment it
is no there's only four kills so it
doesn't make sense does it I just
thought like because I'm in the
ambercoin guild if they purposefully put
us into the guild that will like or or
the other way around the Guild Master
they might have to an extent
yeah I'm not sure though because it
seems we're going to my dungeon
next yes it is this way oo I have heard
that many people have suffered by the
hands of my dungeon uh it is the hardest
one without without a question I shall
test everybody in in their qualities of
a hero if they withstand and the hot
flames of the Phoenix then they shall
pass and if not then they shall pass
away in a different
way let's see uh hello it's been a while
my Amber corn Guild
Master what if it ain't one of them
arrows you pick the right time to stop
by just got work from one of the guards
on the Mountain Road says they seen more
of that mysterious light what's got
every want saw it isn't it isn't this
great how I'm saying things it's it's
perfect thank you Cockney
English yes Scottish yes all of the
above the problem is down down that ways
and active volcano you're like to get
your plates bought off just going there
there but the way we say it ain't no
doubt that's where the next ruins are I
ain't going to beat round the
bush
bsh bush would like to join uh uh would
like you to join our I'm already in your
guild would like you to join our Guild
in investigating the
area oh oh I thought I thought you were
the who are you talking
to I I was giving leather to the Scarlet
wand oh that's why you were fighting the
cow
H I see okay you know how it goes by now
we got a scout on the ground already so
have a word with him when your wife
arrive so both you and the celes lady
can't pronounce hes huh you have a
problem there blind May nearly forgot to
tell you how to get
here H you all the passed a fork in the
road when you traveled to the C Forest
eh well take the same Mountain rout and
just go the other
way and out whenever you're ready
remember fortune favors the
Bold yes that's that's your your
catchphrase fortune favors the Bold yeah
I've been saying that my whole life okay
so we need to trade real quick and then
we will go oh what might you have for
me I presume you might be broke so oh
excuse me maybe broke in comparison to
you how much money do you have uh 800
900 891 bucks yeah yeah yeah take take
take take my
coin well in this economy I suppose I
might beef just broke yeah
mhm I guess I I wonder whose fault that
is not mine no all right surely it is
yours no how could it possibly be you're
sharing the influences of your stalks
your riches with me I I share my riches
with all yesterday I paid off my lawsuit
with
mococo I by giving her 10,000
coin because she sued you yes oh yes
follow me again I thought her lawsuit
wasn't very rightful anyway but I I
wanted I wanted I wanted to be friendly
and since I have coin I allowed her to
extort me of even moreone yeah aren't
you in the end just supporting her
addiction though H I don't think she put
it back into the lottery this time so I
actually I think it's I think we might
be
good okay we'll see if she still has
that money
later yeah we will
see were you did you have a a lawyer
or no she did but oh see that's the
problem you should have lawyered up
settle outside of Court
a oh this guy right here Felix of the
Amber coin a feel Felix the yeah hello
Felix long time
no burn burn into the ashes you shall
never revive again and see the light of
day okay a blind mate nearly burnt my
body BL come off guess there's no
getting P sorry I'm doing my best can
you please I I'm talking to this
guy ow too
close oh you're one of the arrows sorry
about all the first yeah that's right
I'm the Scout from the Amber corn uh-oh
uh fre I ain't done much scouting though
the lava's too bleed bleeding ot to even
get H yeah he said BL it h yeah why does
it say blot it BL
we' be Ash before we got anywhere near
them ruins oh did I mention a trinket
well all right there's one way into the
volcano but you wouldn't mind keeping
mom about it would you mom say the or is
around here fet a penny so I've been
mining them for profit on the
slide that was possible thanks
facts t a nks s she says that with an F
just they're writing out the accent yeah
wow wow w
wow as I hear Mario Mario Queen Mario
Mario
Mario so a little trinket I had called
the fireproof
Talisman just uh one a little problem
who what do you mean
who I thought she would react to that oh
you ah she's so cocky now yeah I know
we're in the same Guild my
lady we have an appointment as I
remember yeah yeah yeah shall we invite
her yeah she has to get over here first
oh okay
okay uh blah blah blah blah blah if I
just add the coin I could pay off me de
get the Talisman back and You' have a
way into the
volcano uh about 500 oh she wants a call
but we're both in a call yeah 500 coins
ow oh he wants 500
coins money from me I'm from the same
Guild all right take take it
then speak speak to
me I'm speaking to you there you go fly
me look at all that corn did did you
earn all of this to help me cor I don't
know how to thank you
I'll go pay off me deths right away be
back in a
snap minus 500 he took all my money that
I got from you narissa uh I told you
aren't you glad you accepted it now I
thought it was a personal gift from you
now I'm kind of disappointed cuz it's
gone
already uh you'll get it back later well
thank you thank you so much I'm in your
depth I
suppose no problem Bob
[Music]
uh you can hang on to that for as long
as you need it will let you explore this
volcano without failing a little heart a
lick of heart
ow whoa I
am the owner of sa fire now okay can I
throw away some things here yeah might
be a good idea your waistband so you put
it in your usable inventory and then you
click on it and then you can fill up the
um
ah yeah and then and then you click on
the waist bin to empty it so anything
you don't want you can just put there
and be like get out here yeah okay um I
probably don't really need these
things I'm going to go kill a cow be
right back oh More Cows it's it's
important you know books you need three
books to make a bookshelf and you you
know it cost one letter per book oh yeah
one of my regain memories is like
reminding me of how hard it is to build
a library yeah yeah yeah so we're uh
we're suffering that's why we needed so
many donations understandable donations
or you mean more like um Lottery
exploitations it's not lottery
exploitations I don't want to hear this
of slander it's not a scam
wow wow wow we bomart are committed to
your
satisfaction you when did they get you
into it when did they like take over
Scarlet one your mind they brainwashed
you no I'm not brainwashed
help
help they are too
powerful okay oh
there you already have a diamond
Enchanted is that enant enchant it yeah
you you can enchant yourself things
so I heard there's a boss fight in this
one yes
so if your diamond sword is too powerful
maybe hold back a little bit on your you
can't use you can't use your or weapon
they provide you one oh I see I see okay
let's end the call I need you to call
Queen
Mario all right I'm scared um but I
shall do
[Music]
what is there something specific you
want me to tell her uh just see just
checking where she is seeing how she's
doing one I missed
you okay thank God I miss you
too yeah W or back into the kingdom of
Lies oh welcome back
come here to uh the entrance of the
dungeon coming wonderful we are awaiting
you I was actually I think I'm lost no I
will lay out the the red carpet for you
no I don't need it you are member of
member Co oh special treatment I see
special treatment
I appreciate it I think I'm almost there
I don't remember where is the dungeon
follow the lava well there's no Lava
really on the way
but yes yes I smell you oh no wait
that's wrong dungeon smell you it's a
good smell smell me yes sniff Sni
me sniff snier sniffer sniffer
[Music]
my wait can my mom my mom she um cleaned
my uh my house and like she uh she
brushed my cats and she said she got so
much hair out of my cat said she's
making a pillow out of it and I asked
her are you serious and she said yeah
so all
crazy I think I'm here join the party
call okay yeah
uh uh we're waiting you and then we'll
invite you to our
party I'm next to Cassandra ah
Cassandra Cassandra she's next to
Cassandra Cassandra wrong one wrong
wrong Temple K the Kata the fire temple
the fire
temple Fire yeah Amber coin Fire
temple
lava across the bridge
are you are
youu I think so I'm looking for
[Music]
it let me go for the portal and await
you in front of the
portal oh you have fast
travel yeah woo you have fast travel I
don't know no can that bring you to the
temple wait is she is she I was looking
for still uh where are you now I'm next
to the Cassandra no okay from Cassandra
go to what was his name we'll we'll pick
we'll pick her up it's okay okay we'll
pick you up just stay back thank you oh
no way I see the bridge now I think ah
you see the bridge she sees the bridge
this
one oh if she sees the bridge did she go
through okay now I'm next to Felix FedEx
felex fromin oh sorry I have FedEx on my
mind
aha oh yeah over there ah yes yes yes oh
Cassandra is over there huh okay very
close by okay I come to Cassandra back
okay no no no what not to Cassandra no
no no uh no you went too far Amber corn
Amber corn okay wait wait me next to
felex okay
uh no it's um yeah FedEx is FedEx is
kind of stressing the [\h__\h] out of
me
so on the day I return I must accept a
FedEx package hello hello oh nice
hat oh oh wow wow you look like a wizard
when you have that hat and you fly
around above me yeah hey come here I
have something for you oh oh
gift ouch oh no a hat oh you're enough
room in the in your inventory I don't
know I don't even have a
bag a I can give it later if you want
okay maybe I don't deserve the Hat
yet oh my God it and don't use it it's
fine this is
ridiculous let's go hello beautiful lady
hello beautiful lady invite the cat Okay
join our party
call no the queen I'm here like a fanny
resurrect what why how did she do that
you're not supposed to have that power
okay into the dungeon uh uh okay H okay
okay wait I have to kill this
cow uh by the way uh uh oh she's oh
she's not in the party call Queen Mario
join the party call no she already went
into the dungeon did she am disapp enter
enter as well oh yeah one second we go
I'm
here
ah wait
wait I'm fighting for my
life oh and another one I guess I'll go
just just just yeah just come through
don't worry about it okay all
right follow me
ladies let's go
yes cute lady party
woo by the way we got orange pink and
blue girls try to not spoil me about the
dungeon um I want to F figure things out
I will be always is behind you okay I I
will go ahead but I won't get the
checkpoints okay okay okay
okay okay ready up let's
go get up let me throw wait I need to
throw something away again oh yeah I
don't need the stained bones do I uh I
would save
those they're you need them for building
diamond stuff oh wait I never actually
successfully uh recycled when I tried
you have to hit the recycling bin when
you put everything in it
okay recycle okay now I have
space
okay you want to give me the Hat away oh
yes please do you want it
yes one I give I give her I give her a
hat I shall also be hambur Co in
possession of the Hat
yeah woo put it on on put it on put it
on put it on okay so yeah yeah yeah yeah
hat party hat party wait it's in my hand
uh there we go right click when oh wait
no right click you right click when it's
on your
cute oh
fancy I look so
Irish I love it it's so pretty Irish
it's Irish
lead the way Miss Irish okay um I am
Billy Irish and I shall lead the way
wait where the where do we hey Shakira
Shakira hi have you seen the castle we
buildt for Amber coin and the kingdom of
Queen Mario I have uh uh uh seen a
little snippet of it
indeed but oh oh I see this is how it is
I told you I'll I'll build a castle okay
I need to get a closer look you have to
give me a
tour oh checkpoint yeah sure wait are we
trying to get closer to this Castle over
there yeah you're running where are you
running to cuz I follow you so I don't
need the path good good good oh there's
another just don't just I am invisible
here
just just follow you uhoh I follow you
into the lava too you follow me too
a a
wow I'll die too in solidity let's
go it doesn't hurt at all yeah just bre
used to it no no don't no louder no
that's
broken oh we jump over
it Oh I thought there would be one not
broken
one okay this needs some maintenance I I
shall take care of it another day is is
this dungeon familiar to
you um it must be don't skip your story
oh it must be built by my old ancestors
yes yeah yeah when I found out about
them it changed my life forever they
just felt so right for me you
know I bet it was fate I think about
them all the time maybe there's one in
this town too what what are we talking
about wao there is okay I'm checking out
this fast food place right
now wait why is my Lord book like the
only one which is like kind of out of
this world there's no fast food places
here don't worry I think it will make
sense at some point okay for sure all
right and I I love fast food let's
go me too I suppose my senses are
tingling is this
platforming seems like it okay so far so
good oh easy oh this is like one of
those like you know on TV
like uh well I mean we have phones so we
maybe also have TV uh those like
challenges where people like run really
fast over the parkour and then they fall
into water sometimes yeah yeah yeah yeah
like American Ninja Warrior whatever
that is nin I always wanted to
participate in
oh oh maybe maybe one day for your 3D
debut that's what you can
do you can do anything in you Frey deut
make it make ah
no what I
do you have to go back over here over
here oh like how not here
oh she just laughs she dies and just
laughs I like the spirit she
has what if I just go this way you keep
doing your
best all right that's that's a good
restart we just like do it all over
again
parkour par are you already at the end H
yeah she's a
pro but don't worry I I didn't I didn't
get the things she opened it I
see okay and
now up
here
parkour no
W hey did you fall down why why was that
your early conclusion
of me not making it I can make it back I
can make it back
La it's just so hard
no wait where are you going wait I
thought this is the path I need to take
to go back but no oh you were just
telling me to fall
down
no I don't know what I was doing come
here oh is it the other side come back
come back mhm okay oh well let's do it
together
yeah o
yay yay yay
easy Sor you fell okay let's go what no
wait I found a way to go back actually
ah okay well well it doesn't I found a
way now not before though I show you
later
okay okay okay calmly but surely will'll
make
it oh no I fell again
how did she do it so fast oh oh okay
okay I'd like a checkpoint here why is
there no checkpoint
here I need a checkpoint did you miss a
checkpoint back behind you no but there
should be one here in the middle no it's
back here God damn it is there a path
that's better than the other
here no
okay you guys go ahead don't worry about
me oh
okay
M the orange juice down there looks so
tasty
no oh make it am I supposed to not step
on the Soul
Sand
e oh because I'm supposed to jump over
it huh yeah I mean I I step on it I
don't think it
matters
no no no help me uhoh give me your hand
there is a I I'm sorry uh go behind you
you have such a long
Fork I can't help you you you have to
you have to jump across look easy no no
no hey come back where you were you can
just jump up on the Soul Sand oh you
don't have to go all the way back see
just right here really Oh I thought it
was over we're so
back all right get that checkpoint all
right and now you can just die no she
has to do it that's quite real to say
yeah no she has to no I didn't made it
like
that okay we should have forced her to
do it without the checkpoint nah it's
fine
wish I come over
here
no yeah
okay okay is there more
lore uh where is the L door here yet but
there will be more lore the lore door
wow Mission
Impossible whoa whoa SC
whoa oh God they just zoomed through
that one
okay
okay okay I live I live another day
don't die uh I'll think about it I'll
think about oh you're still following me
you're like a
cat you're so
cute very cute how okay let's let's
follow follow me again after this laser
goes back again okay okay go go go go go
go what if you just run by the sides ah
[\h__\h] I see I see
no now you know what to
do what I going to do oh come back die
okay oh right I
uh there you go guys
bgm did I no you got to you got to turn
I'm waiting for you both at the end
you're just flexing
girl I told you I'm a pro it's okay I
skipped I skipped all the things so you
can you can fulfill it yourself okay I
get it now are you are you okay I'm okay
no go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go ah no
ah what I
thought what no
no I thought if you're on the platform
you'll be safe no
[Music]
lies I
see come on yes yes yes yes yes yes
yeah okay ah maybe maybe I shouldn't run
on the side because then I have a a
quicker way to the
platform no no no no no no
okay okay I made
it you
go oh
it's okay it's okay you got the
checkpoint okay okay okay here we go
again you over here yeah why you're so
fast uh oh here
oh she is
[Music]
flexing uh why did I do that why did I
why well I guess you can just run
through it as long as your health is
full ew wa what is this
is that the next uh oh you already went
through that too
narissa yeah it's
easy well someone like Mario should be
really good at
platforming yeah right I'm Queen Mario
okay so different Mario I
see
oh I a break at the middle of the M's
going to catch
you meanwhile
[Laughter]
L okay are you ready L go go go go go
run run run run run
run H
okay we were we were way faster than the
laser yippe did we miss a
lore did we miss a lore I don't think so
I think there's there's more coming up
soon
okay okay do you know where the secret
Wawa CD is I do we will get it no
worries okay
okay remember narissa yeah
she okay why didn't you press some of
these
buttons I hate you always so funny it
is it's okay I'm sure the next won't do
anything like that what the [\h__\h] did you
just activate that no you just playing
with me no no mama you this will not
disappear right no okay where' you press
that oh look there's a button back
here well maybe you should press
it okay
go come here no okay
bye-bye fell I tried my best I did not
succeed yeah yeah yeah what are these
black doors here or not really doors oh
well there's a new pathway behind you
why don't you check it out why don't you
check it out this is this is your D
we've already done this go on exp you
said you didn't want any spoilers okay
oh no I'm but
[Laughter]
no not all
[Music]
bad that almost made it who was
that what is going on this place is
cursed very cursed oh there remains but
one path
why you peeking there so suspiciously
there's another one here another
one I mean at this
point L yeah I got some snackies for
cats come over here come over here come
thank you there letter
want well that was UNS unexpected hm
a cute cat would would would oh sorry
never going to trust you ever again of
course you will of course you will wait
so where did the stairs go come here
come over ladder okay there's another
another puff why don't you try it no no
that's
sus is it well why didn't you try it
it's see it's the only option
left you're got to push something for
sure
oh
no oh he
didn't but was there
like no what happened
no I see she went over the wrong side
yeah isn't there like I saw in the
middle of the ladders there there
something that looked like a button
perhaps did you touch that no no
okay I'll wait
I look back and she's just
gone no no no I'm here okay here go
run run wo who was
that just the floor the floor does have
sometimes oh really maybe I should run
on the side
yeah Mama
Mia Mama Mia pizzeria
wait so what why did she fall into lava
is it this spot
here let's not no I think she jumped
over the wrong side directly on the
other side of that there's lava
ah oh no you made it I made it I thought
you were going to follow me
no okay know I'll come with
you if that always happens oh oh I guess
I got to jump there you go oh thank you
so sweet so so
deir deir what de very mindful aren't
you what de Mir means mindful I don't
know don't worry about it the brain
Rock stop dying this is your home I'm
just enjoying my a sin stop stop dying
oh my
God I want to test
something no
okay all right all right all right no
more no more no more ow no more holes
right why why why no more messing no no
why what why why don't I didn't I
haven't seen that
one just focus on on getting
through maybe
left yeah I jumped just in
case you can come now yeah yeah yeah
yeah I shall Contin
continue There You
Go were you pressing this button all
long way so no this button uh turns off
the thing so I've only just pressed it
now oh but when I pressed it it didn't
do anything yeah that's because when I
pressed it it turned off these which was
its only
purpose
weird suspicious things
happening all right onward I am very
paranoid onward onward to where onward
oh
straight
oh oh
okay lead the
way lead the way she
says no you're a [\h__\h]
comedian thank God you're in all
[Laughter]
alive why is this here I think we have
to press these buttons together are you
ready um
sure all right
one on on three okay one 2
three nothing
happened one more time why did you run
away
narissa I don't
know okay 1 2
3 well that was high you're comedian
ah
instincts okay wait so what what you
supposed to do not push
it you can't just not push it right oh
it's gone now okay um where did she
go what the
huh something just f it hurts it hurt
[Music]
help help help oh I go there I go there
okay
okay some kind of like iron fell from
the sky oh my
God I I wonder
why yeah that's not very de miror of the
iron what now do I go down here
there's some stairs up oh yeah those I
already took oh
we I died
H oh what is that crying obsidian why
are you
crying what
happened I don't know what's wrong with
that cute
sounds it does truly
maybe I should go on your side oh that
looks suspicious that floor yeah w
w
yeah what happened where I I I died wait
we I also died why I didn't see it the
floor became lava I need to catch it in
4k you can't just do it off camera I
didn't try to I thought you were
watching me a
h this doesn't do
anything walk back this
way I saw
coming what come on well at some point
it just gets
old really this is yours F yeah this is
you built it this is me and my family
taking Revenge at
everybody for their crimes against
us and their misdeeds okay all right
come on not going that way anymore you
mm oh all right come here oh there's a
story oh
okay a story wow M now this is what I'm
talking about it's a shame they didn't
have fast food back in the age of
Legends because a good hamburger would
have motivated me to fight even
harder
[Music]
yummy so simple so food so
deir but now we've got this whole range
of burgers to choose from so how cool is
that yeah like the Yago
burger and the Phoenix Burger
M good stuff okay checkpoint so get the
checkpoint but then come with me
oh it's about the vinyl ven isn't it oh
I see it already see that over there
yeah so it's kind of hard to nail it but
if you come here and then you have to
double jump double space bar to try and
reach this low Point
here
mhm double jump yeah could just hit the
space bar twice and it'll make you Glide
a little bit oh it's kind it's kind of
difficult you don't want to hit it
immediately so like do it like bump bump
o yeah you got to time it
right oh I I have to
like have to like stay checkpoint yeah
oh cuz I like press it once and then let
go immediately okay okay I press
longer w w w also enduring the same fate
as me oh no I never I never succeed on
that I thought you did I did once
never
again I don't know how I keep making it
honestly I think it's dumb
luck every time I try to tell someone
how to do it I I successfully do
it okay nice
Flex hey I can't do
it you can do it takes a very many many
many tries don't
worry to me it took like 30 minutes the
first time yeah
I try again and again and again this is
very Phoenix like is this really like
the only way to do it though I feel like
that would be a different
way oh see now even I can't get it again
H okay no there's another way oh really
oh what the way what's the other way ask
them now cuz it doesn't really seem like
something to me that the the creators
would force us to
do I feel like my RPG senses oh the
potato salad yeah well but well that
relies on you having potato salad
yeah oh okay so the moment you exactly
at the edge of it hit hit the space bar
for the first time let me try it one
more time maybe I can get it down to a
science so the moment you're right
here hit and then H I didn't
get look up I feel like I look up Edge
maxing what yeah get get all the way
close to the
[Laughter]
edge you got to get as far to the edge
as you can without falling then jump and
then when you're kind of nearing The
Edge like hit the space bar again
okay but wait you always try it from up
here maybe it's okay to do it from the
way left you could
try because like at least you can Sprint
properly
there okay right I don't
know uh the reason I do it that way is
because
um
this I'm I'm like too stupid still to
use the the
the flying
jump yeah it's it's difficult
[Music]
okay well okay I used the potato salad
and with it is pretty easy though you
have another potato salad yeah I do if
you want oh give me tra it to yeah okay
trade it to the
Phoenix yeah cuz WIA can just make it
without
come
back no
no no
yeah
accept I accept your potato salad thank
you now is this get your track is this
cheating I don't know maybe yeah I don't
think it's cheating like it's something
in game like there must be utility for
this potato salad no yeah yeah wait how
do I eat it oh I'm not I'm full you need
to be a little
hungry so take some fall damage from
here and then he going to consume your
bread
okay yum yum yum yum yum I am so
hungry yummy yummy in my tummy I'm still
not hungry though I know
okay ooh I actually really love potatoes
Sal it okay here we go here we go you
can do it almost almost almost
almost maybe maybe try it it takes a
little bit but you can do it it def it
gives you a little more area to fall
okay yeah a easy see you made it maybe
they expect you at this point to have
potato salad with you because you're
already in the fourth dungeon I mean
this potato salad has only Don oh good
job
yay oh it's already the buff is already
gone yeah it's already
[Music]
gone okay now we shall proceed perhaps
to the
end it keeps on talking to me the the
the L door
yeah all right oh it looks like we have
two little things things that are not
lit up
no she's
dead okay two things not lit up and then
this little block here okay wait wait
wait wait wait wait
wait let's explore the room it must be a
puzzle what is this will you lead the
way yeah I will attempt uh how
about this looks
interesting I can go up
and down again
oh and then what's over
here I
[Music]
see nothing except a
trapo oh there's another one over here
too oh how to open the trap door why
don't we check the one that's open
first there's an open one yeah right
hey hey you don't have to
die I wasn't hoping to oh I can jump
down from here
perhaps yeah okay I'm going down
bye-bye wao what is
this it's it's a
secret ow [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] no no no no no
no
I see so if you touch the floor girls
you will be poisoned so don't touch the
floor okay okay for
shame no no no no no no no no okay okay
oh that works brute forcing
it sometimes that's the way the game's
got to be played you know the floor is
poison
froggy wa room oh interesting indeed
that's where I keep her that's where my
family has kept her for thousands of
years R ravencraft has once again
discovered the floor was lava and I
think I saw it was here right
there NADA would you like to check if
it's if it you can just jump over here
okay can jump over here oh guys one of
the things has lit up oh
oh that's wonderful is the other trapo
open yet no probably not yes that's
where you came out of
a okay yeah one LD up so ah maybe
upstairs there's some
stuff well let's go up shall we
yes yeah
[Music]
M can I reach can you give me
appies no
no
[Music]
appies
oh interesting so
unfair wait I saw you
oh nice platforming once again mhm
showing us how it's done and me just
continuing to fail oh ah y
what's out
[Music]
here why don't you try that weird ladder
you saw again maybe something's
changed weird ladder
yeah did you change the one you saw that
only just led to a dead end that went
with another ladder
down I already forgot about its
existence
[Applause]
[Music]
oh um I still want to attempt this
ladder
again that's what my mind my brain my
desire is telling me
okay well I I se this ladder but this is
uh is there something different there
oh was this did I not see that oh okay I
found something
interesting oh what have you found uh
zoom zoom fire with the Zoomies
fire in the Z
why um okay oh oh
oh oh what are you
doing what are you doing up there I'm
speed
running okay let me try to speedrun it
too zoom
zoom okay is there a way to do it
without getting
burnt yeah
carefully
[Music]
carefully no no no don't take my
life I'm here
welcome like so but not
quite I see not just running through but
like going step by step
yeah oh no go
die fight fight fight okay okay you can
do it believe close
call
wait mama
M I'm coming up again uh no worries take
your time you got
this got
[Music]
this it's too fast to think oh
what no no
[Music]
yeah
b i i maybe I'll just go the fast route
again like just run through
it
uh but I have to heal back up again I
think for that
mhm
wait okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay Zoom wait where do I go I here
oh okay I'm up again M good work good
work now I need to jump over there I
suppose or walk can I walk over there
you got to jump I guess you could
walk what why was I
burnt why what I did not see there's
fire that shoots across the way huh H hi
don't pick you up
okay you want come here come here okay
ah
ah I might
[Music]
die you get close
up what the going to do if you die
Al don't die okay I'm okay uh I'll
come speed
running a speed running you've got this
you know it is a difficult D you need I
was like talking to a senpai
yes you stand in the way of the fire the
fire is only on one
side am
I I was talking to to a Japan Senpai
yesterday and she was like asking oh
what what are you guys doing with this
like Minecraft thing these days and like
explained everything to her and she was
like oh I want to play too it it's so
cool oh yeah it's so cool I said sorry
it's like Ian only and it's like a long
running project and sorry but I know
it's really cool it is okay now you got
to jump over here go yeah come on ah
wait over there let me eat a bit before
I fall oh there's fire here okay
wait it's oh
you have to time it one two 3 one two
three
one okay yeah yippe and then over
here I made it I
survived Y and then and then over there
fireproof Phoenix ow no
what was I
[Music]
saying you can do it you can do don't
die don't die don't
die okay be careful now wait come down
the stairs Elizabeth is in my
head wait I'm too scared to move is
there so fire here no there stairs no
there's no fire down here
Mama Mia this is a difficult
dungeon it is ice
ice
what
no wait nobody warned me about this did
you not see it well I saw snow but I
thought well what can happen wa how do
you do that without dying uh double
jump you hold you hold hold down the
thing La is is so so mindful so
considerate very Demir yeah very deow
meow well L you can lead the way again
I'm coming or say you
too
skill
skill oh no damage run yeah let's go I'm
gaming oh [\h__\h] oh I got I got stuck okay
that's not
fair not not not fair not you got it
you've got
it
okay careful
hi
hello hello
hello okay yeah how what lead the
way I'm just going to fall
again oh you jump over it hold down
space
bar hold down space bar
oh
this there she goes where is why am I
alone where are you
girls quickly go you got to press the
button press the button well this is
certainly not
safe
oh yippe woo did that turn on the
light I think it might have that sounded
like a turn on the light sound why don't
you come on out of there
okay uh what's the best way to just die
right there no right right
right no behind you behind you yeah
right there it opened up a
path K come
here what's wrong with you I don't know
I think you're watching what I'm doing
in delay and oh no no no no
no that works too yeah that's what I
thought oh we all died well thank God
that at least one of us is always alive
otherwise this might end in a full party
wipe that would be fun if that was a
thing ooh what's cooking here hey stop
dying wo
wo that is so fun want to fly that is
amazing Yes again again
aies
[Music]
up oh
oh
a okay that's so fun made it you learned
how to fly girls we did flying cat right
I want to
explore oh okay run around yeah yeah
this is a very big castle Yeah better
bigger than your Castle H yeah way
bigger than my castle so maybe I should
be Queen
H aren't you guys in the same Guild you
can't fight like
this I hear no objection queen of this
Castle okay well I
am okay is this lore l door no l door is
over here
oh over there mhm but it's not
orange it it's past here I want to look
for the windows W
Windows you're spying on people
like literally yesterday I walked like
past some like guy who had like uh these
like goggles with which you look far
away ohuh uh-huh binoculars yeah and it
looked like he was staring into windows
from buildings like way past the
street I was thinking like maybe benefit
of the doubt but I don't know what else
he would be looking at weird mhm
but that's not what I'm doing there
weird people around there's nothing here
to look at so I'm I'm just like thinking
of how to decorate this place how
to make
it it's nice do you want to move
in no I don't know well there's so much
fun things to do in a private
on it'sit hot but it's great
yeah okay
the lower door lower door ler door's
over to the left lower
door more door hold
door okay
man why are all my Lors just food
reviews it's ony what is this
Burg maybe you have to gain your
memories you have to gain your clearly
you don't remember this I thought you
said you didn't lose your memory I want
to see like the reactions from other
girls who read this stuff for the first
time were you girls like eh burger what
burger
burger I like pork ma'am this is a
kfp man that burger was perfect juicy
meat crispy veggies fluffy buns it's
exactly when I want it I wasn't
expecting that from a small place in
some back alley but you know what this
is now my new favorite
restaurant okay good for you uh Lor good
for you what's going on these stairs are
disappearing and yeah appearing where
are you you got this I'm I'm up high
look
up now waits for
me okay I'm trying very hard to not get
the checkpoints
go
good you got this you got this good job
good job let's go together together um I
was so scared yeah that really counted
that one
moment I got stuck
okay okay come on come on Kitty come on
Kitty okay three 2
1 okay take a point take the point let's
go does this disappear too yes oh no can
you not hear the the timer oh God oh God
oh God oh God
God tick tock tick tock I did in fact in
the lava so you can uh respawn yeah no
okay oh maybe
yes man that was perfect we good
together now come here okay I press okay
oh okay three 2 one go go go go
go almost
[Applause]
there okay three two 1 go go away
oh his R is difficult yeah no
no I'm
swimming comfy just floating again you
did it too let's go okay 3 2 one go wait
I look so magnific
ah I died really oh wait for me you here
too for me wait let's go back come here
come here
yes but look at this beautiful woman up
there oh ah oh you're actually like
walking over here
okay how de miror of
you a mirror very much okay I click
three two one go
I
sorry can do it there's this big Phoenix
presence up at the top which you know
makes me
nervous you made it now H yeah yes it's
all up to you now okay ah easy H
oh oh yeah you built this almost
there okay this time this time for sure
yeah surely
mhm take your time no I
cannot and done let me out let me out
let me out trying to go there you to go
this way I want I was out of time so I
better just jumped to the side
no okay
[Music]
[Applause]
it's making me nervous you got
this you built it after all so no no my
family built it how do you
what you you can do it
I need to yeah it's about you got to do
very very very fast yeah I thought I had
more time I thought that's where it was
over
okay here we
go a queen
Mario are you are you trying to take me
in as as your
consort private watch this don't no
no do you are you already married with
uh some lucky ladies I I am I'm married
to quite a few lucky ladies
actually uh firstly shiori then uh
princess Vu your daughter and then
Iris oh wait if you already Mar my
daughter you're did
it oh wait uh if you have Boss music you
might want to turn it on now yeah I have
an even more bossy music um I have like
two okay there you go what's happening
lady Nera if you're already married with
my daughter I see a little difficult to
make it oh I think we can make it work
statue
breaker we can't use our swords or what
nope cool we got to use these pickaxes
and do uh and and pick at her okay why
would you pick at me why is everybody
picking on me you I suppose it's a
future me it's like you know how in
Legend of Zelda there's like so many
zeldas and so many links there were waas
in the past and this is you know one one
of them and it just represents all the
waas I
suppose what if I
die well youa the beginning
okay wait for me I want to pick on
myself I am the greatest enemy of myself
after
all stop burning I totally believe that
oh
okay are you
picking wait let me do some picking
too I won't I won't finish him off I'm
just helping it's a boss fight after all
we have to work together where is it
where do I go anywhere okay get it very
close and then you just ding okay I
think I'm close enough come come come
here yeah right there's good too I I
like going right here and doing it a oh
cool wa that's really cool ah no I shall
pick before I die I shall pick before I
die you did the last one okay it's up to
you oh okay sh you have to finish it off
just give me like 2 minutes please f it
time we can't beat it without your
power I see the laser means that the
fire is going there
soon moment I thought you'd be more more
fire resistant than that
um ask my uh I I I I pleas the
fifth you sure you no sorry I'm too I'm
too excited I'm too excited
no I'll make it this time I'll make it
this time but it's so beautiful why
would we why would we destroy
it I'm sorry it has to be done I worked
so hard to build this or my I thought
you said you didn't build it I I means
me and everybody who represents
me my
family they're an extension of me I see
yes okay I am so
back
uh stop burning yeah oh sh oh oh is this
going to burn
yeah no no no
Mama did you
fall
yes come on like an angel from the sky
wow oh oh no oh no oh no it's
okay I have escaped on the last very
last moment
no oh
hello I don't know your onen huh it I
have have to make the most out of it it
is you know time limited I cannot spend
too much time here or I will become
fried
Phoenix oh god oh oh oh
God okay
okay okay hi very Demir very no I died
for you
okay okay there is no rush it's actually
pretty
hard yeah
honestly
uh I'll take the same path as before
when it stops there you
go
okay I am so close
oh oh okay I think this is enough is it
yeah ah no no no no no no I shall I
shall take it down with me I shall take
it
oh my God so good the of me is the
demise of all of
me thank you for your support
conations
Revelations and now you have a memory
back yay let's see what all these
burgers are about
one moment
please of course of course that's that
egg looks
familiar a little bit
[Music]
H monitor only okay here we go free two
1 a phoenix has countless lives
true sometimes a symbol of Hope
true sometimes a port of prosperity I
don't know that means Port sometimes an
avatar of
rebirth for Ian I've used my power to
help people there's not a problem I so
or so I thought it all started one day
when I decided to drop byy my favorite
fast food place for one of their
delicious burgers I found out that they
were almost broke and would have to
close if they couldn't pay back their
debts Yak no problem we're just got to
make this thing called profit right
right should be a piece of cake but it
wasn't once I became a part-time my fate
was sealed it was work work and more
work I used to Le armies now I'm working
for minimum wage money is hard I can't
just beat up bad guys instead I got to
keep the Restaurant Cle good food and
make customers want to come again and
keep doing it day after day after day
I'm going to die and I'm supposed to be
immortal that's okay just die the same
time it was also a lot of fun
I don't think that's so many new things
I'm happy and everyone else is happy too
they all tell me how good the food is
booming and the deps
allg even the dep collectors are now
regular customers money was overjoyed
I'd call that a happy ending a happy
ending
[Applause]
yeah
waset well guys if you want to watch
that without the yappa yappa it's up on
YouTube on the whole life English
Channel go give it a a peekaboo for me
thank you leave a like subscribe comment
everything turn on your
notifications yeah thank you for leading
me through this I only have the am
dungeon left now yeah you're doing that
with with the myth members the fellow
myth members right no probably not
because only Cali
replied oh m when did she when was she
going to pop on cie well she has the
thing is she has her outfit reveal but
she's also sick so I don't know she said
if she plays she will just like log in
and not talk and just like write in the
chat so but I could wait for Amy at
least because I'm sure she's logging in
and doing it but maybe I don't know if
she has an appointment with someone else
to do it so well I'm sure she wouldn't
mind I'm sure they have room in their
party for sure cuz pretty much everyone
who was on yesterday which was a lot of
people did the dungeon so okay if she I
don't think she's done it so I'm pretty
sure she has room it's still early does
she have a stream reservation up I don't
know let's check H lia's coming in 2
hours apparently
O Let's
see
I'm I see
no stream reservation
so who knows when she will
[Laughter]
stream well
so uh I can I can do some Side Quests
for now Oho you can always like if you
cannot find any party oh did B not do it
yet M just we're going to come with you
did B not do she down to do it with you
oh okay okay well shall we shall we go
back to the
city uh yeah
yeah yeah yeah I need to jum for the
time being okay wait where did you go oh
just follow in the
path the path the path follow the path
sorry it's so beautiful
I'm it's where did you go oh I'm already
in the city oh ah you're fast fast
travel yeah fast travel because I got
lost before so I F can you teach me how
to get a
bag yes yeah okay cuz everybody talks
about backpacks and I don't have one
they're helpful you just got to buy it I
think right
oh you got to build it but you need a
few things go go through the teleporter
Tak no look at these beautiful pure Al
Waters I know that's
beautiful it's so
clear mhm so bright this are this are
really Alps aren't they Alps and
volcanoes like wow they know crazy did
they know that I come from the
Alps they
must wow the deaths are calling
me I need to go and throw all my rings
into the
volcano oh
no wait Nissa do you watch rings of
power I haven't watched the new season
nether but you watched the first one
right yes and you were also like pretty
like okay with it right yeah it was it
was do I think it was a masterpiece no
do I think it was as bad as people make
it out to be
no get on your horse and just ride
ignore them ride no I'm a hero I must
fight I do not run from a battle I die
on the battlefield ah good
thinking yes yes
yes victory
honor okay wait yeah so I'm waiting um
because keep following I got to kill
some cow okay there's not all episodes
out yet anyway so I'm waiting to go back
to Austria and then I'm watching uh all
of it yeah I feel like it's better to
wait anyway just Ser are you talking
about uh rings of power rings of power
it's like a Lord of the Rings uh prequel
it's an adap it's an adaptation of the
sil marilan which comes before events in
Lord of the Ring you sound
so is it good yeah uh do I think it's as
good as the movies no no but considering
the S melon wasn't even finished by
tolken himself and had to be finished by
his son oh do I think do I think that
like girl obviously it's still good but
it's it's not really it's not really
written in the same way that like the
Lord of the Rings or The Hobbit is
written to my knowledge
in the chat already yeah so it's it's
it's and it it does change a lot of like
Lord things but if you just want to
enjoy something that's Lord of the Rings
and uh that's kind of world like yeah
yeah yeah then then I think it's fun but
I think if you go into it with the
expectation for it to be as amazing as
the movies I feel like then you'll be
disappointed but it's still it's still
it's a fun watch like I'm going to watch
it when it's finished uh coming out too
but like I'm not going to be like oh
yeah it's token so therefore it'll be
amazing because I mean the sil melan
isn't really even 100% tolken so oh my
God nous
Shez were
like I like this like yapping nerd uh
sry nerd
Vera all right finish your quest
mayhaps wait I wanted to ask the chat
like don't spoil me but for the people
who are watching the second season would
you say it's better than the first
season not not if it's good at all cuz
you guys are just going to say no it
sucks but is it better than the
first no yeah same hello would you join
our party uh we're not ready yet uh she
she needs to run around and do some
other stuff but it says you're already
in another
party okay not a whole door better than
the first strong opinions I'll be quiet
okay
hey
Revelation yeah yappa yappa okay we're
in a party call so you can join right
now kiata is over at Ain she's doing the
uh rest of the quest she's going to king
liel oh I am indeed it is
time so feel free to join the party call
when youd
like hello there she is
B is B I am
Princess um blood flame panthera
Evergreen oh yeah yeah yeah yeah so
sorry Princess it's a you're are
forgiven daughter of Queen Mario I'm so
sorry yes I am I am daughter of Queen
Mario nice to meet you how come I have
never heard of like your royalty
we we have recently discovered it
because you know we have lost our
memories so the memories took a while to
back yes so wait you are the
daughter yes I am the daughter of Queen
Mario the king who the Father the King
was conspiring actually and that's why
he took our memories away so that they
would
forget the who I am now going to was
conspiring yes yes should I not go to
him then no you may still go to him but
we just need to keep in mind that he's a
dirty filthy
liar okay is he
really yes oh is that the plot
twist yeah yes that is that is the plot
twist okay let's see let's see uh ooh
wait this looks so like Super Mario like
cute
cute very de
miror yeah very mindful very modest very
mindful
yeah oh this place looks uh familiar by
the way
um uh and Nissa are currently not
sharing their and yeah not streaming
right and but bi right okay yes I see I
see princess beu uh uh yes princess
beu
sure I
am she's she's my daughter so she's the
princess so I I request you to be kind
and polite and respect her names
thanks yes you must respect you must
respect the heir to the throne princess
I believe that you are her
daughter I will not share my other
political views for the meantime for my
own
safety I know your political views
Shakira Shakira
Shakira I know it already don't worry
okay and you know what it's my duty as a
as a nice and kind Queen to respect
thank you forgive you thank you not all
[Music]
you as whatever you would
like okay no then uh the king says our
battle grows ever fiercer be vigilant
hero and ready yourself
for what well man
earthquake are you okay Nissa it was a
strong earthquake right yeah it's really
strong really crazy oh never in my life
have I felt the Earth Tremor so
violently I British accent he oh he's
British of course oh I think I used to
read him like I fear this B ill for one
is to
come your majesty urgent report most of
stains is gathered near St wait this
feels
[Music]
like this feels like I'm reliving
things
Rel yeah stain stains at the
[Music]
gate to Calamity began spreading stains
would of emerge from the seers so the
entrance was sealed shut but if the
light of Revelation also stirs in those
watery corridors then we cannot but
investigate oh investigate let's
go
what voices in my head are confusing
me here I'm going to temporarily leave
the group call it might end the whole
group call for everyone so just as a
warning so everyone might need to rejoin
the the party call but I I'm going to
Quick talk to gathan okay gathan okay
gathan
again um ah
gigy
right all right and now there's nobody
to answer me yeah it's giggy okay thanks
for Super
Chat thanks for the
donation okay I got a key K KY
key well I already regained my memory so
I know things that you don't
perhaps what's
this what's what's this
Castle I want to talk to gathan
too go back to the king ah oh oopsy oh
we're not done talking
oh oh oh I can talk from afar oh yeah uh
speak to the Jade sword Guild Master on
my way
where is the real exit of this beautiful
castle
here map would you mind
updating
okay
V the green
one join part oh should I join
[Music]
again
uh ah no welcome back meow oh that's a
fun tree that looks like
a that looks like
two Pokemon
combined it looks like the bunny and
like the
tree I
think do you see the same things as I it
looks like
several but only from this angle
okay so in German
M oh I wonder in Italian and what the
Pokemon names are are the same in
English oh what we have different names
in uh German I know even in French but
in Italian they say they say as in
English version he yo oh my God for some
reason wait the embercoin logo is really
cool you like it yeah want to but the
does make a fair point we need we need
your
your my my you need my ah I see wait you
see by carrier pigeon let me quick share
an image with you that Gigi has sent or
excuse me Jonathan has sent to me
Jonathan I you mean on Discord hi
carrier Pig car pigeon
Mario carrier pigeon my carrier pigeon
kchen name the Discord look at the
Statue currently that is fixed of Tam
Gander yes queen as in is married to the
king now if you check if you check the
message I have sent you via carrier
pigeon you can see how it was defaced it
is so lwd I can barely even bear to look
at it yes I can bear I cannot even eyes
on such a thing I have taking it down
because I was fixing her but when I
logged on when I arrived in the kingdom
and I saw it I was so full of shock I I
wanted to throw up wait and who who
which is the queen that you are
supporting the I support Queen Tam
ganner the one and only me too yes yes
to think that someone would do such a
terrible disgusting thing we have
estimated that you can only build within
your own your own boundaries meaning
that it had to have been someone on the
team Cerulean cup huh interesting
obviously either the princess or the hot
pink one also known as Iris
the hot pink one well she's not speaking
right now the princess I just want to
mention that yesterday the hot pink one
uh admit that I am the first queen and
she time B is the second so just let you
know do we have a proof of that think
you do it yeah you actually have proof
of that it happen you think the hot pink
one would do it it has been recorded in
the arive should we take this mayhaps we
should put both of them on trial both
the princess and the hot pink one to
determine their in have to I agree child
mother I don't think so you you are not
allowed to touch or talk to my um
daughter she should prove her innoc
again exactly she should prove her
innocent I do not the no she doesn't
have to prove anything yes she needs to
prove her innocence completely I cannot
accept this I cannot just let it
go uh we were going to go and do and do
a
dungeon's dungeon to be exact my
sweet has not had the
opportunity give me perhaps 6 minutes to
craft a what one would call a
thumbnail Shakira needs needs to go
herself and actually finish the rest of
the quest so why don't you do so yes yes
I will I will get you the backpack right
oh yeah backpack and U the rest of the
quest yes that would be can you keep
talking so I can equalize the voices in
my head
um
um um yes how is the equalization going
uh sweet little princess who has put
okay should be good now thank you
shameful things onto my
queen oh I would like to show you
something your hat is nice I will give
you that this moai this moai amidst
[Music]
sound it's quite impressive hold on I
will show you stay stay in front of the
mo with
me
oh I need to
investigate
oh I see what kind of sounds can it play
Princess yes wait outside while I I show
you okay in front of the muai it will
sounds
okay please play the Beautiful music so
my ears may be
delighted you
should oh my gosh I love this song
[Music]
la oh oh hi oh hi
oh H
ha hi
[Music]
live to fighting to the
D hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi
[Music]
alone alone alone alone
alone he he hi hi hi hi hi
hi
[Music]
s and TR come the break up
day wow
[Music]
me a
stray if I go wrong what awaits me in
the oh be beautiful
KET where are
need hi hi hi hi
hi get getch round two
[Music]
hi s hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi
and in the next life too I will find
you all bless the moai statue which
Project Music Godly
music very
deible that that was magnificent that
was divine yay you have a gift it seems
to be able to control
this mysterious mythical
statue
uh Vu would you like to join the party
call oh yes oh oh this whole time L was
sorry sorry for making noise
l no way I was enjoying it I was spring
uh K why don't you now go and finish the
rest of the preparations for your quest
okay I'm on my
way thank you for doing this for me I
appreciate oh we read gathan isn't in
this did you def face the statue
princess pishu huh I did not you def
face do you know who
did I I don't know
it had to have been something I locked
off kind of early last night yeah I mean
you were you weren't doing so today were
you oh I only logged on like 30 minutes
ago oh that's true I suppose then I
wonder who else was on today maybe we
will be able to find some sort of
archive yes I wonder well it certainly
wasn't me do you think gathan might be
making it up and have defaced it him
himself that would be a plot twist what
if is not as righteous of a hero as we
thought I think there may be a
potential there may be a potential that
maybe some of the one of the lesbi
leeston bloggers may have captured it in
one of their
Vlogs yes
mayhaps may maybe the voices in in
takanashi Kyra's heads will know or
Tanisha Kyra's head excuse me well no
they're saying it was the hot pink one
oh yes
yeah but who knows if my voices can be
trusted yeah because you know the voices
in my head told me that apparently Moko
had put a bounty over my head but it
turns out that that was not true ah well
it seems like they are there to start
trouble those
voices the voices they would lie to us
yes I know they they caused a whole lot
of drama over
nothing maybe we should put the voices
on trial maybe we should they're not to
be
trusted okay I'm talking to skullet one
Guild Master here have the
key the stormgate
key okay seruan cup
master I'm
proceeding to where is
it it's uh yeah your headed Jonathan
with a
G still observing my
Vlog I
am oh so beautiful when the Sun is
setting this is so
gorgeous wow I am so blessed to be
living in this wonderful
Kingdom of lesbians
lesbian
leest what
wonderful wonderful indeed
I go grab a drink I'll be back very
quickly okay you know I'm surprised at
how flat Tam gander is where is her
ass ass ex oh I that yesterday when this
was being built Queen Tam Gander where
is your ass you mean her
butto yes her
butto please be respectful of my Queen's
butto in fact it is not only just flat
but it is inverted
what what wait what come look it is
inverted oh oh my inverted ass T Gander
correct have you done something with it
also I am very very sensitive when it
comes to inverted buttocks because I
myself has suffered this illness before
please do not make fun of it look at her
backside yes but it it looks quite
cursed I think that they need to correct
this this mistake immediately
unacceptable There is almost no cure to
an inverted ass it is difficult to
undo maybe how does one get Afflicted
with inverted butes it is possibly by
birth the only thing that can save you
is something called a
BBB no BBL B BBL
yes it stands
for benevolent
buttock lamp
ification you know I've heard that word
that acronym before but I don't think
I've ever known what it meant that's
what it means h i see I've tried it but
um on me it has only partially worked so
I I don't know if it's like really safe
to recommend to the queen Tim tender I
would not want her to suffer the same
pain as me so let's just ignore her
inverted butt otherwise she might feel
very sad about it let's be sensitive
let's be mindful and demate yes very
mindful very demure modest very demure
Very
cutesy Yes where do you learn such words
my ladies
it's I don't
know it's just the memories in my
head sometimes I hear a a clock ticking
and talking
sometimes tick tock tick tock when I
think of a clock taking I think of
something else than you
perhaps it's like we come from different
worlds and different perhaps even
different times of birth
I cannot follow you with your new
futuristic yes we we we must be from
different timelines yeah
MH um I'm going back to the
king so is the king your father
beu I I do not I have just um been aware
of my familiar line I just know the king
of lielle as far as I understand seems
to to be the situation that he is
married to Tam Gander however him and
Tam Gander are usurpers to the throne
that is rightfully Queen maros and uh
princess kosek
IBU I see so therefore they are not she
she is not the King's Daughter however
the king is not the rightful Heir or or
leader of the throne he has simply
usurped it from the rightful Queen whom
he stole the memories of wait if the k
is not the
rightful uh uh King then does that mean
that Tim tender would not be the
rightful Queen yes oh
exactly I need to find proof for this I
still believe in my
queen even if her King by her side is
not the rightful one I still believe she
has the destiny and the Fate on her side
to be the rightful Queen right all right
well that's on you that's on you and in
the end we are saving the Les leeston
and I think what they really want is a
queen oh
kiaii Kia pimi and what queen do you
believe in h yeah kimori what queen do
you believe in do you believe in Queen
Tam gan or queen
Mario is there any other queens I don't
know about yeah no I think those are the
only two B fish IDK well she has spoken
D has
spoken maybe the real King was the Dad
we met along the way yeah maybe the real
King was the friends we made along the
way and the king the Dad should
choose his rightful Queen the gardens
are full today this makes me happy you
have been taking care of the
plots I'm
glad oh I'm ready to investigate the
sewers dungeon but first I want a bag
Jonathan a Gucci bag
please uh well that that'll be uh Ra's
responsibility but you what you're going
to do is you're going to have you done
the quest to unlock the
bag no uh
KIU yes do you remember what quest it is
unlock the
bag
cake
chicken I am back whenever you guys
ready waa can uh Mario can you help me
with the bag one of the blacksmith
appren Sor I believe could you assist me
with the uh with with the bag the act of
getting a bag oh yeah yeah I already
make the materials for you come come
over yeah oh I'm coming coming to you
now hello greetings
salutations
Sal okay so I give you now mhm uh accept
the
trade accept you
need five Ingot I give you
10 oh I have enough oh you have
it do you have stain hide M well
15 I think that's enough okay then we
just got to go to the black black well
she needs to finish a quest first is
that not true oh you need to finish a
quest okay let's see what what kind of
quests I have up
here uh ah looking for five gold ingots
should I continue this
one uh no uh uh voices in I see it I see
it oh yes yes accepted the
quest okay okay I talk
to I talk to the
guy
probably yes oops see somehow I
accidentally keep on mounting my horse I
do not know why H we are almost ready
for the dungeon I I found Jonathan D
tell him to join the party call pray
tell uh pray tell join the party
call okay
[Music]
I don't know why I said capable of
buying the backpack welcome gathan we
are gathan I I am on my way what do you
mean we will wait for you fair
hero I will make haste I have the
backpack thank you oh you got it yes
good
job let me put some stuff in
there I am finally Gucci
up I will make haste towards the
blacksmith
yes ah some things seem to be unmovable
from my
hands it's okay yeah yeah any any any
like uh critical game items you are not
able to move so like the fire the thing
that makes you live in Fire and so on
and so forth I
understand
uh oh this shall
suffice I am ready whenever to
strike all right yes yes let's go then
we must wait for I see gathan in the
distance go on my way where is Queen
Mario ready right behind you my lady
wonderful one second my
dears
yes this looks like the kind of hat I
would wear but just way
smaller all right I am I am ready I am
also
the let's Embark let us go park
onward ride we ride
I'm we are all such sophisticated head
wearers yes yes a wonderful wonderful
hat without hat M I love hats I remember
and now you have a hat yes I am one of
you
now beautiful I do not know how I feel
about an Amber coin but that's that if
you if you support Queen Tam Gander I
speak a truth with my life I support
herion and empathy we compassion and
empathy ah yes I will open My Heart To
Thee thank you for your
kindness I knew I could expect it from
remain ever loyal to Queen Tam
Gander she's my everything I I have a
complaint to make however with the Tam
Gander statue what uh can you please
fill out her ass it is currently
inverted I need you to make it uh real
true to life give her a b please Fallen
I am attempting she's still a work in
progress she needs am I the only one who
hasn't done it yet yes has has everyone
here finished the dungeon yes yes okay
can you try to not spoil me yes thank
you please read
uh okay we find ourselves in a white
empty space it's so vast that the very
concept of distance seems to lose
meaning why is this not about Burgers
huh why was m about
burgers in the midst of that space we
see an atique desk and a lever chair and
on that chair sits a girl sipping tea
okay okay okay close enough tick tock
tick tock tick tock tick Tok TI tock
tick tock tick tock peu what do you say
about this does it sound familiar we
hear a clock perhaps Sparks something
within my mind yes Sparks Tik Tok Tik
Tok Tik Tok
as more and more clocks join the chorus
the girl closes her
eyes take talk Tick Tock talk tick tock
tick tock tick
tock I shall close my eyes too
m i can sense it more
words okay okay o it's a quiz cannot
believe they are floating which source
of energy did a certain Reaper discover
ah Soul energy Soul energy oh no uh oh
sorry never mind people's strong
emotions people no people Souls no uh uh
both well we'll vote on whatever one you
want so one of this one strong emotions
strong emotions there's a third one you
do not think the eating lots of sushi oh
there's
a no no this one it's it's this one I am
sure
trust me okay right oh
yeah so smart so
intelligent well I have paid close
attention to what I have learned so far
what is this book oh souls are not a
zero sum game that's what the reaper
realized for if she could stir the
hearts of her audience the power of
their emotions were energy enough yawn
Crimson bows bows a treasure lies in
wait the Gaze of orus will point you
straight I do not understand does
somebody understand
this uh it sounds like a a hint to where
her thing was in the last dungeon no yes
doesn't that sound familiar remember
remember when we when you the trees went
across the C the trees branches yes yes
the trees the trees I remember well
a checkpoint a checkpoint huzzah H oh
it's just a hint if you haven't gotten
the thing yet yes yes we are making
great progress and you are learning so
quick you're are so intelligent oh yes
indeed because I don't need these hints
it seems I have already found them all
collected yes
well yes I'm slow because I'm
starving do you need food would you like
would you like some bread mother if you
have some bread I I have some bread
mother for starvation in Medieval ages
who would have thought it is quite
common who would have would have known
thank you so much that's very generous
thank you all right what is the answer
thank you so much which of these guards
the force field around Atlantis shark
statues electric jellyfish a dignified
man with a beard H I have collected some
sewer water oh no
delicious uh please do not touch me I
collected
water SE keep that keep that away from
us it seems like would you like a drink
no I do not drink dirty sewer water no
surely it is a dignified man with a
beard surely okay if that's what you
want we'll vote for it it must be oh I'm
I'm on my way I'm coming are you in or
what yes okay there we dedication I want
to see it wait how do I get
in oh right click oh oh no was it the WR
wrong answer
reel
re
[Music]
reation I honestly didn't know but be
you princess no even if you're not my
princess I shall protect you cuz it is
my honor they hurt me oh you saved me
thank
you a princess must not find the need to
fight she must be protected thank you
for protecting me by a night mhm mhm H
all right what is your second choice
after a dignified man with a beard let
me try to recall my Adventures from a
long time
ago um L were you part of my
Adventures yeah what do you say what it
was no no no you can't ask her no yes
you cannot ask her um it is so long ago
it is hard to recall but perhaps um the
shark
statues could
be yeah
yeah uh one more person oh sorry
princess princess princess thank you oh
I almost went to the
jellyfish thank goodness thank the le le
best the Le best
yes in the depths the kingdom of
Atlantis sits safe within its force
field Mighty Stone sharks stand guard to
defend it and yet rumor has it that one
girl slipped through those defenses the
ancient doll meanders in its maze reward
awaits who out the boundaries St I
already have this one in my
possession you're so smart to have found
all of them onward I am grateful for
your
Praises on
to the checkpoint huz thank goodness
huz I wish I had a glass that I could
throw on the ground while yelling
huz yes if
only feels wrong oh question number
three come on this one is must be more
closer in my memory because I have done
it today a mysterious boy appeared at a
certain Shrine what is he particularly
good at
folding
origami a word that is unfamiliar to me
unfamiliar to me as well from a
different
Takaki that is also
unfamiliar what is that what is soccer I
only know football right football
football what is that I do not know any
of those things um it is when it's it's
an illness when your feet are in the
shape of balls illness oh no terrifying
is really hard to walk it is so hard to
walk that you must do a thing called
dribbling in order to move ahead
dribling uh okay to her she was merely
keeping them company but to the souls it
was what they needed to move on one boy
left his Fs in origami before departing
for the other side a laborin fiend
passage passage test the eyes proceed
Beyond the Wall to claim a prize
interesting
interesting very interesting a a really
smart tall uh soup lady taught me how to
get that one n or Mario Mother drinking
some cat oh it's
okay mother must stay
hydrated as you should checka
checka check the
checkpoint huzzah we have forgotten our
huzzah huzzah huzzah we We Are One Step
Closer to solving this
dungeon wait a minute bgm was missing
okay so what is the grand achievement of
a certain excuse me Oddball Phoenix
hello
Oddball talking about oh how dare this
dungeon qu a cruel
place ball helping a fast food
restaurant repay its de taking first
place in Hamburg eating contest or
saving a k lettuce on the brink of
collaps I say this looks good because
that sounds way more like something I
would
do yes
yes we will follow along
huz
WR it was we're just proving our
strength once again yes it is necessary
our strin princess do not touch the
princess ever
again oh help all they H
Revelation okay well you know there's
the my family consist of many phoenixes
and maybe one Phoenix made a fast food
restaurant certainly not me because I
saved kingdoms yes but I guess never
your memor so that is true oh we went
the wrong way yeah yeah yeah
wait come over here me ladies
my honorable
ladies we got the wrong way wait we got
little my goodess
oopsies we
have food restaurant to repay deps
mhm onward
reel where are we now oh reation liary
reation a SW fast restaurant finally saw
success and prosperity some say the
hardw workking new parttime is as fiery
as a phoenix a crumbling crack and fiery
Fortress wall the brave may claim reward
where others fall
oh ooh see you have to jump to it ah n
oh wait come this
way come this way enemy he's back back
you come here there's a
door wait wait what was I the girl
stands on the roadside looking dazed as
though she just woke up from a dream the
picture in her hand soon jogs her memory
however all right I need to find this
dog help Papa help I kill I kill I shall
kill protect the is expecting a call
from her soon so she'll need to be quick
thank you mother this detective has a
reputation to uphold after un little guy
I'll find you a promise hey what do you
want Jord for leading me to the L door
my name it's Jonathan
no no no here here
here down here hey water watch out
goodbye he to the
yo wow do not
touch nice where are the
rats thank
you yes Crow Raven lady
beautiful we had to we had to do it
multiple times cuz we couldn't find
it yeah that's hard to find yeah right
damn especially in
[Music]
reation tacle has to be earned except
for I don't need to earn it you earned
it I have earned it long time ago in
other ways yes
yes I have a right to listen to
it h
huz huz a checkpoint once again for the
kingdom or the
quom yes the Queen the queen queen
sleigh yeah what did a certain detective
invent for The Travelers who made it
this far is it a teleportation thing no
a golden axe oh is a oh wait but that's
like we wouldn't really know this would
we no what do you think she would create
for us oh definitely a warp Crystal
because she's a Time TR I don't know
this but um I have a feeling have a
feeling you are corrupt
wow I am just really good with my
intuition what's that over there ah that
looks suspiciously
placed suspiciously you should open it
oh it really is it just there like that
oh there's another book over here too
maybe I read the book
first I leave this for the heroes who
will one day visit this place may it
serve you well each chamber past has
offered you a rhyme revealing Secrets
where you've gone before there's one
last thing to find ear out you climb
what British and therefore I present to
you one more The Haunting grounds of
creatures of the night within its depths
you'll find a hidden light what ah see
I see
yeah W Crystal are you girls already in
the possession of it yes yeah it is in
our pockets amazing now I own it too I
shall use it proceed to the
final
ration back into the sewers are they
ever ending
are we stuck here for that's an endless
loop we leave here now that's our house
it is quite a large sewer system
mhm Another Story scary and stinky okay
we find ourselves in a white empty space
the girl still sipping her tea opens her
locket to reveal a number of pictures
each of them shows a girl who looks
exactly like herself one is searching
for a lost dog another is buing bu some
sort of machine yet another is playing a
video game video game what is that she
gazes at the photos with a warm smile
let's see where should I go
today I do
Wonder
okay are you having a
memory flashback
I'm having a
migraine I feel the migraine ah it STS
you feel it it's St do you remember yeah
wait a second I think the pictures in my
head are coming together in memories in
60 frames per second
oh
wait you girls are probably already have
seen
it but I shall play it for me and the
voices in my head three 2 recount your
lost memories yes wait bgm is not on
okay 3 2 1
go what's with all these cases my dog's
missing my husband's cheating and to top
it all off now I'm getting buy me some
iced tea and make me some pasta that's
not even detective work I want to work
on something big the case of the century
yeah something like the strange creature
lurking around the coast or that demon
carrying a cursed object or that weirdo
walking around town with a huge sharp
weapon or the words out on the street so
why is no one hiring me i' be perfect
for the job that's why I decided to take
matters into my own
hands she forgot about me I figur I'd
Crack the Case and become a hero she
hurtes
me no way but when I dug deep found out
that the rumors were only half the story
my investigation concluded that they're
actually pretty nice people and also
that this is a damn good burger we're
all out there bringing SM to people can
I do the same about
myself time to do something about after
that whether it was missing dogs no case
was too small while I was at it I also
invented an automatic ice tea mixer
pasta maker and teeth brushing machine
soon the whole town will be smiling then
the whole country then all of
humanity okay maybe I won't go that far
but I can at least start with the people
around me like my
clients of course I've still got my eyes
out for that case of the
century a detective's curiosity is Never
Satisfied there's one that just doesn't
fit in there's one that's just weird I
am finished watching it but I am
confused
you're the CEO of kfp you run an amazing
restaurant it seems I am not as mythical
as I thought I
was my good you are but you are not
known for your mythical you are known
for your amazing restaurant and amazing
food you should build one to rival that
of a divorc diner by
kiaii maybe maybe I should or maybe I
should prove my mythical
no no I do not want to be known as the
burger lady oh you are more than that
you are beautiful exactly beautiful and
mythical and demure and mindful Demir
and mind very mindful
indeed well thank you for accompanying
me in this adventure of course of it's
fun thank you for having us I am finally
caught up with all of
you you are you
your pocket you the war cryst K don't
you oh warp to the king you say let's
see how to war towards
[Music]
him am I in no need of my horse
anymore you will need your horse it is a
big Kingdom oh there is so many
choices uh Which choice shall I make the
best castle that is a great choice me
lady
[Music]
ah I
am suddenly in a completely different
world
no different place where am I I'm
confused this is too much for me as as I
am not streaming and have simply come to
help the fair Maiden uh complete I I am
going to sign off
will you wait before you go Nissa
ravencraft will you mayhaps help me with
my trial tomorrow
trial I yes I will have a trial I will
try if iine I will be your witness you
will stay as my witness yes yes of
course thank you need to put princess
koseki beu in the hot pink one stand no
thank
you stand
the oh shameful display I may not be uh
oh you will not be oh then we will hold
a trial another time it is fine I will
find who did
it I shall leave as well because I have
my queen duties to do accomplish so I'm
sorry I got
to thank you so much for your support of
course it was nice to play with go to
adventures with you thank you so
wonderful to see everyone farewell
farewell Mario Mario see you soon see
you
soon byebye bye
bye oh oh there goes the whole uh
party I really quickly need to for like
a
minute leave you guys and then I'll be
right back and we'll think about uh
maybe doing some side quests or so BRB
BR R BRB B
RB let me give you bgm at least
here oh
[Music]
for
huzzah I like that they say huzzah like
especially gathan seems to like to say
huzzah because I like huzzah from a
certain show that I
watched
ham okay so I'm
back Yum Yum
Yum let's see nobody like tried to call
me or talk to me right in the time I was
gone good good good um what time oh it's
it's the usual dungeon opening time but
there's no more dungeon
opening why why don't they just make the
finale like tomorrow I could come
tomorrow if there's no more dungeons
just do it
tomorrow
man Mama
Mia yeah oh well yeah let's talk to the
king ow ow ow my neck is so
[\h__\h] like I think yesterday I like uh
pull a muscle or something and then it
it's mostly
gone it still kind of
hurts I think I'll get a massage
tomorrow that massage was so good
there's like sometimes when I get
massages there's like some good moves
that they do and then some moves are
like kind of like uh me but this lady
she every every cuz every time she
touched I get this feeling that every
touch was you know good like every
single
move had a meaning and the
[Music]
purpose yeah she was so good man I need
to go back to
her very experienced massage
lady she had the this mommy like not
like Mommy sorry Mommy but like real mom
aura about her too so I felt very
protected and taken care
of I'm glad I went back because the
first time this is so weird the first
time I went to this place to get a
massage I thought oh this massage is
really great that I was a different
person though but uh even though the
massage was so great I
noticed something was off cuz I think
that
time I could be wrong but I had this
feeling that my my massage therapist at
that time was picking their nose all the
time I just like sometimes it would like
like I would notice that one hand was
like not on me anymore and like some I
don't know why I didn't see it but it
felt like they were just picking their
nose all the time I don't know and then
I felt like they were just like not
putting everything into the massage
anymore I don't know it was so weird so
I felt kind of um annoyed by
that yeah I I think um maybe like
allergies or
something scratching their face no
because it was like constant
secret booger technique and then I was
like should I go back because like
surely it won't happen again right
generally it was so comfortable because
some Massa massage places they have
really
uncomfortable like chairs SL
beds um but some are
like decent mid but this one is was
incredible like they had these cushions
that are like lifting your upper body up
really comfortable really soft cushions
and they're just like in the perfect
shape and then and then there's a like
separate cushion for the head and it was
just like the most comfortable massage
uh chair I've ever been
in
oh wait are they in a party
[Music]
call no I wonder are they doing
separately right now those
two sir gathan has taken notice of
others talking to themselves and finding
it
strange well
well talking to the voices in my head we
all have
them oh I see okay wait no I want to I I
don't mind being alone a little bit I
want to chitchat with you guys a little
bit
[Music]
B
yeah maybe I should read this let's read
it because I have time to read it my
keyboard is doing weird
[Music]
things ah ah hero I see you I returned
safely pray tell what transpired in the
seers below I see as with the ruins
before memories were regained and
Revelation awakened a predictable
outcome mayhaps but nevertheless a
welcome one your Revelation ought to be
greatly empowered by now you have done
well hero we can all breathe a sigh of
relief for now at least but what with
the quake and increase in stain activity
the end of the world seems to be seems
to loom ever closer would that uh we
could do more to stay it what would that
we could do more to stay in atas since
the earthquake there have been no
further reports of unusual activity from
anywhere in the Kingdom
I fear to SP to come before the storm
and something yet more terrible is
brewing as we
speak it always do be burrowing it
always be cooking as such I ask you that
you take this time to prepare train your
comat skills and stock up on any items
you might need this may be your last
chance to make the most of it please
lend us your power for just a while
longer hero for peace and the future of
Le besto
yippee H GA your strength to prepare for
all this to
come I want to rate the
dungeons let me rate the dungeons for
you guys
because I want to talk about them let me
get rid of this in my
Ops okay now I'm starting in 15 minutes
now she has a stream
up
M the timing
literally could not be worse I just
finished it if I knew if she had the
reservation up earlier I would have
waited for her I did not see her
reservation up a moment
ago
brah okay so I want to say uh H I think
the first dungeon the Cali dungeon was
fine but uh I really liked the
intuitiveness of the uh secret hidden ch
chest right and how difficult it it was
like uh like a good difficulty to get to
it but it was like very visible and to
me intuitive so I liked that the laser
Skool was really cool yeah but um I wish
I wish that all of these dungeons had a
boss fight that would be sick which
gives my dungeon and the extra Edge the
extra coolness about it yeah so best
ending of a dungeon I say must go to me
best secret hidden chest
M to yeah the tree the Cali one because
it made me so
happy and I was the first one to find it
and then I did I did really like uh the
whole procedure like the riddles of like
moving around the the things in the
Atlantis
dungeon uh moving the little little
zombie Trident guy
around that was good puzzles and uh in
that one still the treasure was like
visible and you knew that you had to do
something at least now I was kind of LED
through the other ones narissa showed me
where the treasure is but but I think
they didn't look very intuitive to me
the one in the lava dungeon you could
see it if you turn around and you see oh
there is one there m but still kind of
hard to
find and the sewer one was definitely
like yeah not
intuitive and the the ENA
one was like
through yeah that one through a just
walk through a freaking wall H difficult
I don't think I would have found that uh
under normal circumstances
H when they found these they weren't
being given directions so they probably
looked around a lot yeah yeah I'm sure
they did
[Music]
oh that's
weird it looks like I got a DM from Amed
but now it's gone she must have deleted
it right when when someone's at the top
of your DMs
but it's just there's nothing there
she's she deleted
it a
man maybe she was asking about the
dungeon uh wait a
second Kiki says someone has def face
the statue of the queen team G Tam Tim G
Tim yeah I'm looking for a detective to
find out who is done such terrible deed
and I demand a
[Music]
trial now hold up ghost
GM weird Tim time Tim time temp Tams
yeah um overall dungeon design Ena was
really
[Music]
beautiful maybe enas enas and guras
maybe f
favorite
maybe and favorite
cutscene I think
goodas yeah may maybe yeah or gas had a
lot of like movement which was
really
exciting but am am kind of like you know
brings everything back together so
that's nice what the hell why am I
like I thought I was being investigated
by her too why am I just the burger lady
guys I don't
understand so
rude just accept it I
can't my wings were badass yeah like
seeing me seeing me that on the
battlefield that was pretty
epic h
let's do side quests but I'm available
if like Amy says oh I want to do a
dungeon on her stream and she's like I
don't know with who like tell her oh
maybe ask kiata cuz I wouldn't mind
doing it again with her for the side
quest that says do it
again I'm available I'm available I
still got a time I'm going to uh go out
and record uh a
video for
anniversary yeah I would do it with her
I'm just going out later but I still
have a lot of time until I go
out yeah I'm going to make a video from
MOS
anniversario yeah I don't know I I
almost like was going to uh say [\h__\h] it
I'm not doing it um but like a few few
days before I asked around if anybody
has a like camera that I can borrow like
a GoPro or something similar because I
have something similar but I for like I
didn't think I would need it when I left
to go to Japan one and a half months ago
so I didn't bring it even though I have
something perfect for it and then
um like one of the
managers said I could borrow their
camera
which isn't a GoPro but something
similar so I was like okay
um
now I feel kind of obligated to do
it even though
I uh I don't know I I was about to like
say whatever I'm not going to do it but
then I got the camera so I'm like okay I
guess I'll do it
yeah so now I'm doing it even though I
don't have much
time left pretty gidy gidy
I will do my best to get some good
footage let's
see oopsie I did not activate to eat
that bread must have been
[Music]
natural um moving to a new house but I
have far too much stuff to carry all by
myself could someone help me out
a e is that just like a moving things
Quest putting it in my bag and then
carrying it somewhere
[Music]
what oh let's do this one because maybe
they'll teach me how to
enchant lais
Luli I'm guessing I can get them at the
Ocean Temple
right
clast where am I oh yeah over there cuz
there was so many gems over over
there let me I want to hear the bgm too
let me put it on
the monitor only
[Music]
beautiful oh my God I'm in an
RPG hey Ma l l l l give
me give me hey
Ma yeah I've been playing in silence I
knew that you guys were here hearing it
though
but I wasn't listening to it
myself e it's so dark I can't
see it's not here I guess
wait where was it
[Music]
again further further ahead I
guess fart also she sells more than just
uh lottery tickets now
amazing what
progress uh where is the entrance over
there do I have a pickaxe oh yeah but
oh not much
left there we go this is so
nice I wish in real Minecraft there was
like there was places like these where
you could get all kinds of gems
[Music]
in a place like this so
beautiful wait do I need an an iron
pickaxe do I need an iron
pickaxe cuz this is a stone one I
think Oh no I got
eight uh
mus oh I can just mine this top one
again
there's an air bubble I don't need air
[Music]
bubble there we
go all right should I take more just in
case because maybe I need more for
enchanting my stuff I do have diamonds
so I can make some diamond weapons
probably yeah it's a it's a
okay full of materials I need yeah but I
should probably come back once I have a
iron pickaxe
again come on come on one more one more
for now we now I can teleport so I can
come here way
faster but can I get some can I get an
uh can I get a uh
get a it's so
dark it's so
dark how many diamonds
per
mining wait I'm not going to get this
because I have a stone pickaxe never
mind okay I'll be
back
yes
oh wait can I teleport in the water
wow okay
cool yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah SOLO playing we all be solo playing
now gold ingots
Diamonds oh wait what how do
I let's go to green green is where it is
right
right who needs
it ah ah in
there of course it all comes down to the
blacksmith people oops it
ah sorry I'm so
confused okay 200 coins
huz and then
that's it is the quest Fino I think so
can you sell
me iron pickaxe
H
Sticks no
problem there we
go yeah that's all I want for
[Music]
now okay let's see is there a
continuation of that
Quest
bito this is so calming oh my God I'm so
relaxed after all those stressful days
man I'm so
glad you
know I worked my ass off for you guys I
hope you going guys are all going to be
there when the result is going to be
ready to
show enchant research we've been
researching the properties of Enchanted
tools but we're out of specimens to
study could you bring dot dot dot dot
dot bring bring what let me see my book
will tell me
more wouldn't miss
it damn skippy we will does that mean no
Skippy I mean Shakira Shakira
Shakira when will we know the date you
will know it when you will know
it uh obtain a gold shovel enchanted
with efficiency free or
higher
where make it myself or
what what
what what narrator narrates all hello M
narrator Nar chat Mumy uh no what's your
name
[Music]
today I see you have no name so maybe
we're back to M then because m means no
name wow genius genius oh
yeah you have no voice today
[Music]
huh hello oh she's talking to
me I
see
so for another five minutes okay okay I
hope then afterwards you can tell me
your name cuz I want to address
you okay I want to address you correctly
uh wait so what I guess I make the ah
yeah I just make it myself a golden
shovel I make I make shovel myself I
don't have any gold right now so I'm
going to go and obtain some
gold hey I need to do the gold Quest
first oh
[Music]
you guys know everything even though you
can't play the game
yourself you're playing through US
you're
living uh
vicariously through is that how you say
that from
me
living vicariously right I was almost
going to say
viciously okay let's do this
one um uh deliver but I don't have it
yet
right collect five gold inot
okay um which I suppose I can also get
[Music]
underwater now it's better to
see living viciously through me that
sounds yeah just like what a hater would
do but you guys are living
vicariously have you guys seen not just
my
um like Ian Reco memory video on YouTube
have you also seen on the Japanese
official Channel they uploaded a little
meme short meme Recreation with me and
Callie on the on the shorts
page it's quite
funny is put if
F they asked me to record uh just like
a that's all I needed to
record I gave him like free takes of
that is is there gold here I see iron
and copper and Diamond there should be
gold too right oh there it
is faster to mind than the entrance on
it's
[Music]
okay it's still so
slow did they change the time it takes
to mine or is it because I'm on the
water oh it's probably because I'm on
the water CH okay I get it I get it
now oh 5 years
[Music]
later okay okay oh look at that that's a
good spot wait this is still on the
water it looks like I'm not on the
water h
[Music]
okay gold is up there
though is there anything that I can
reach
easier let me get this
diamond you shall be mine I have nothing
now okay let's see how many do I get oh
way faster one
Diamond wow
wow another one I think I saw some gold
on the right side but is there a bigger
[Music]
one
okay how much for one
Ingot wait or do I get an Ingot out I
forgot Minecraft okay yeah this is a raw
gold how many for one
Ingot I know it respawns but I don't
want to wait forever maybe over here and
I can mine the diamond and the two Golds
and then go back and
forth one to one oh
okay well that is very
generous Diamond not back yet
[Music]
lame hard to
reach maybe some more of
you I had Fortune well maybe I will get
myself some Fortune
but tomorrow will be the last day I'm
playing this so it's like how hard do I
want to
go well might as well go hard even if
it's my last
day because
otherwise otherwise what's the point in
playing it all got to take it seriously
[Music]
make the most out of it and crony went
so hard to is she not coming back
anymore I know she's like on a break but
is she not coming back
[Music]
anymore so sad because it's hard to
support a queen whom is
absent just like in House of the Dragon
like you want to stand your ground but
there's others like man it's the reality
of medieval
kings and queens you got to be there
your your
presence motivates your
kingdom for real for real yeah but I
want to I want to stand strong and stand
by my
morals can I mine this because it's in
the way oh well yeah but it only gives
me a
stone okay
did you see the haard the dragon drama
what
drama I
saw I mean I saw the second
season what drama is
there you mean
because um it was supposed to be 10
episodes but they could only make eight
because of uh budget
cuts gr R RM wrote a post about h o t d
doesn't like the writing what recently I
know like he made some comments in
between here and
there uh like something about I think he
didn't like the change
with make uh the the Sheep
stealer being somewhere else not where
sheep seal is supposed to be I
[Music]
guess he sold it and his rich now he can
deal yeah I mean especially after Game
of Thrones he should expect that there
will be changes maybe not as bad maybe
like maybe that was one of his
conditions or so but if he didn't put up
a condition that nothing will be changed
then well expect there to be
changes you know and I think the Sheep
stealer thing isn't even like that bad
like I like
that uh I don't I mean I don't see it as
such a dramatic
[Music]
change you
know like there's other things that
could have more impact this kind of
works in my
opinion think changes will make the
later Seasons worse well he's in luck
there will only be
four maybe maybe um am I happy with this
now do I have enough well uh I have some
gold what else will be asked of me what
was the other Quest that I didn't accept
yet uh probably diamond right diamond
ingots let me get let me get a bit more
diamond
in
thanks they wrote off an important
character yeah the one that's supposed
to ride sheep stealer right no I like it
this
way I mean maybe I wouldn't like it if I
knew like that character
really but even Al shift is fine with it
seemingly well I mean he doesn't really
share personal opinions much but um he
seems fine with
[Music]
it yeah I know I have the other diamonds
but I'm thinking maybe I need more I
don't
know I won't need Redstone will
I is there a quest that asks for
Redstone
if Redstone is completely useless in
this world then I wonder ah but for
potions right there's a
potion stand to make potions with thank
you for the gifts by the way the 20 now
and also there were 20 before thank you
so
much oh look at this nice
spot and the orange juice surrounding it
oh I can't go there a what a
tease what a tease
is am in like is everybody just doing
things alone right
now Raisa isn't streaming right m is
about like starting now be is doing
things along gigy
still they're having a
drama they're role playing
H well I think I'm happy with all the
gems I have let's go no not that she
is she not streaming at all
today she had something about 2 minutes
minutes where are
they maybe in front of all the
buildings are they talking about who did
the
[Music]
nipples oh or the problem is is uh we
are to be married right now uh already
surpr wow I came at the right time I say
no I say no I
sayate she yeah we we now we are
married not how marriage works yes the
Phoenix has witnessed it so therefore it
is true Mighty Phoenix it is not true um
right I came at a very confusing no
context timing so all I all I saw was
the kiss and now all I see is your sword
well do you not love
[Music]
her that is a very strong word
slow I mean she hates me I don't hate
you I don't I could never hate you why
would you even say such a thing banish
the thought from your
mind I don't okay M I am not thinking of
you anymore haha easy banished you are
banished I see from my
mind well time to kill myself I do think
you two compliment each
other
you oh romantic is this Ro Romeo and
just gamble instead just gamble instead
that's what I
did woman will you control your feelings
get off your horse uh uh no why why
should I give me one good reason H get
off that high horse me lady yes get off
your high horse my high
horse you know what you know what maybe
no that's you have multiple wives why do
you want me as a wife um because then I
have another wife maybe leave some wives
for the wifeless ones huh you already
also have a wife no I I actually
actually since I am night I am not to be
wet and I'm not to be enjoying the
company of any woman at night in my bed
don't say that in of night lady
bloodflame I am a KN she probably
follows the same morals you have to take
responsibility as a knight what are you
pregnant
no yes I am pregnant you are not I'm
pregnant and it's
yours what is this witchcraft prove
it okay hey is that how witches work
there are some medieval techniques to
find out if a woman is pregnant or not
you shall pee on top of this red
stone what and if the red stone turns
green then that means you are
prante no that's not how it work here
let me trade to you my Redstone hey hey
you just don't want to because you're
not pregnant then yeah she's not
pregnant I can tell thank you mighty
Phoenix you're welcome we nights we must
we must stay on our own to protect true
our whoever we're protecting yes yes
everyone we protect we must Focus
especially the king exactly the king
whom they have been saying is a traitor
and is leading us all to our demise but
I cannot believe it yet he is not he is
not he's not that way he is a great king
I agree I believe in the king and the
queen tim tams Tim tender okay ah okay
that's why I the line oh stop trying to
make there's the baby and it's yours
looks more like
Minea it looks more like the Phoenix it
looks more like mine no it it doesn't
look at that red look at that redness on
it it has wings though and the white
look we both have red and white on us
somewhere no she's orange not red this
is your
son that is
will you truly abandon your son and
wife because you you do not want
responsibility what son there never
was the sun is gone it is back Dr just
murdered my child no no if you watched
my lore video it says I am the owner of
a fast food restaurant I am just
creating Fried Chicken this I am just
creating Fried Chicken to sell where she
go this a mighty Phoenix you listen to
The Mighty Phoenix yes I hope I hope you
learned from recovering your memory how
Mighty you are oh um honestly I it
started off pretty Mighty but then it
seems like I have been degraded to just
uh a fast food restaurant owner so I
don't know anymore how dare you you
brought uh you brought a a plot of land
back from its ashes oh thank you that is
very Mighty not anyone could do that I
am doubting myself very highly now I
don't know who I am anymore even more
than before yourself anymore and stop
gring to that Queen well she's not
around
anymore well I would have thought that
after watching you know seeing your
memory that you would have knocked some
sense into you well I will say that even
if we are rooting for different Queens
we are still um United in our love for
the king so yes true that shall be our
bond No Matter
What well what has
happened
what has my child no no no you have
presented a chicken in front of me I am
I am the owner of kfp as you have all
seen in my video I must make chicken
into Fried Chicken that is just how it
goes she killed my child and ate him
even worse video it is a strange slang I
think strange slang from her lands
wow excuse me the M Phoenix has
different wording yes I I came up with
it it's easier to say I see is quite
good I see we we shall learn from this
myen you can call it a
video or you can call
it child can we not forget that she
murdered my child no it was never your
child you just pretending to get
Elizabeth into a spond that she is not
willing to enter freely of course I lay
eggs what oh that's wait what you lay
eggs what I
lay going to lie my lady that is a turn
off oh my goodness you seem to have
given her the
EG I only l i i i only lay egg here I
only lay eggs here I don't actually lay
in wait how could it be her child would
it not be the your own child that's what
I was saying
no it was my child with Lady BL where
was the human in this bird that we saw
it should have been grotesque and
disgusting when did you guys consummate
your marriage yes I did not know that
you guys yesterday I was caught in a
tree Earth came and trapped me and while
we were trapped while we were trapped in
the tree we consummated our our love for
each other no we did not I trapped her
in the tree I mean
the troll came around and chapped her in
the um um excuse me the usual incub
incubation time for a bird is about 21
days so if it happened yesterday you
could have not possibly already laid the
egg time Trav my time traveled time it
must have been someone from 21 days ago
time travel time I'm beginning to think
you are a
witch I'm not a witch how can you time
travel if you're a WI
attempted murder attemped murder
Mur what you were saying she's a witch
Mur bit because she's a witch doesn't
mean she deserves to be murdered she
deserves to be burned if she I'll pull
it out no no not murdered burnt I
believe you should be to The
Gallows must put to trial trial you must
be put trial what else would you be
doing with a witch on a we question her
and we show her compassion that's not
how you do it in my L you're supposed to
put her on her shake and burn her I'll
rub this medicine that sounds barbaric
crispy she shall
become she shall turn to crispy to the
Galler no no I refuse how kind also
she's fine can refuse she's not dead
she's
dead killed her no no she's alive she's
also uh um ladies uh did you uh did you
uh uh uh see the uh the the the notice
board
with there is a tournament today to
tournament a grand tournament will be
held 10 minutes at the uh the
arena honor join us and show voice
coming from to test your mind I did not
to know that they had there is no m
listen the kingdom it's honor but money
I love honor no money we will watch the
show yes no you must join in you must
join in it is my hobby partially
training you must my hobby hobby it is
training as well for the fight ahead
indeed do not worry Jonathan everybody
gets a wooden sword it is a fair fight
my daily
training I was worried I might kill my
opponents but if I would maybe not I
hope you do Jonathan I mean not kill but
uh bludgeon them and
win um anyway uh yes that will be held
in an hour and 10 minutes an hour and 10
minutes oh okay uh yes yes yes yes okay
okay so it's on the hour and hopefully
there'll be more uh participants by then
maybe I shall prend the princess
girl the princess I was questioning her
yes where did she go she disappeared so
quickly
my fellow Jade member yes I believe it
it might be good if we build it if we
buil a courthouse I believe you were
working on a bunker no oh yes I mean yes
I mean you can add a courtroom if you
wish yes yes to trial yes decided they
must use the Gallows we must use the
Gallows on them yes what yes
what what is this bias against Amber
corn members that you have
since the very beginning I know I did
not know you were
money oh yes you didn't know oh I didn't
look at my hat I think they were there
she's wearing a hat for no reason just
for fun all SE guy ever very SC what are
these biases empor I have only served my
honorable king and queen stand away from
her the eye of ambercoin stares into my
wallet please please I do not care for
your
coins I do not care for your coins at
all the gamble house says differently
she eats money what I have never made
use of the gamble house
before Oh I have it's quite fun if any
perhaps I am the only one who has not
gambled yet oops sorry that was an
accident that was an accident are you
are you my are you my my goodness no why
you trying to hurt her why you trying to
Hur my girl
it wasn't sorry I cannot control my
Phoenix fire it seems okay I shall I
shall remove myself from any people
because it seems like my fire hurts
people without my will mayhaps you you I
like
fire you cured you're cured you are
cured yes you are cured I don't know
from what exactly
from your misuse of your Revelation okay
thank you control it better now oh that
is so nice of
[Applause]
you
huzzah question what a joyous day yes
what a joyous day Wonder but if you can
cure me of that can you cure uh Tim
tender of her uh negative ass buttock
what she's being worked on okay she is
not a finished she not finished statue
she has a negative but
she's she's under construction she does
anyway I must observees abide by the
code she is under construction she's
being she looks like she is doing a a
certain run style what is
that what is
uh oh I see done can you wait but um are
you if you're adding the buttock are you
also adding the what's a medieval word
to say
boobies bz buz buom the
buzzom awesome she was not made for
objectification you look at her and you
look at her with awe and wonder not
to
but her beautiful shape of her body is
also something to be honored she looks
like a worm right it is a shape that I
cannot achieve in any world that I live
in a little she's she's almost she's
getting arms soon it's nothing to be
ashamed of her sh going okay I must
honor her shape honor her shape we're
adding some more Dimension here yes she
is getting some she will soon be
breaking Dimensions what does that what
exactly is why is her front more
threedimensional than her
back she is not finished okay it is just
here for you to look at her you seen the
queen back is it quite prous I am not
aware covered by a cap it is covered by
a cape you will not look she has a cape
on you don't need to look there's
nothing yes yes I see I
see well it's quite accurate
no yes it is very accurate liestal
wasn't built in a day so she shall also
not buil be built in a day she's she's
not built in a day she will be built
over 2 days mayhaps okay I shall observe
her tomorrow again her beauty I hope to
be impressed by her beauty yes when you
observe her tomorrow she may have a
backside looking for to
it I love her
body but I love her for more than that
of
course I am a knight but I am also a
protector of the queen and it is not uh
shame
to you
know positively be impressed by every
side of
her I am not lusting over
her volumptuous
shapes I'm not lusting I'm a
knight and I shall spend my bedtime with
no one but
myself just like an idol
[Music]
same thing uh okay they they said 1 hour
approximately so I wouldn't mind going
there and testing my
sword on the others you know I have to
sharpen my
edges but for now I shall finish some
side quests M can you use a shield no I
don't think
so it's just for show
dearest uh lady of my guild what is your
name today hello today as every day my
name is fra Adams anet Senor what
Creator Adams antonet Senor Freda Freda
Freda Freda Adams antoinet Senor
antonet beautiful name been my name
beautiful remember thank you
magnificent thank you thank you very
much okay accept oh dear guild member
yes I have a plan oh what is wait let me
raise your beautiful voice in my head
let me clean my ear really quickly let
me turn off my Fleetwood Mac hold on you
you don't worry about it okay hello once
again what is your plan once again the
plan is to open arriv rival Mark to the
the
F uh it will be called Nana 11 Nana 11
yes and we will have competitive prices
that will ensure everybody in the
Kingdom only comes to our Mart we will
we also have our own Lottery which will
be free to enter oh M another Lottery H
free to enter wait free free free to
free to enter I love these morals that
you are protecting
if if I can be of any assistance please
notify me I let you know for now I'm I'm
uh grinding I'm getting a bunch of money
and I'm going creative mod yes and then
I will build it
understood yes do your best we must fix
this economy we we very very much need
to yes what are you doing H I have
finally caught up on all the dungeons uh
that I had uh and now I'm doing some
Side Quests for like all the Ingot stuff
all the all the uh gem stones and then I
forgot ah ah in 1 hour I will partake in
a tournament in the
arena oh I saw a flyer for this
tournament but did not read it I only
read the words tournament perhaps I will
check it out and see if it's you should
it will be a great joyful day and
occasion okay I shall check it out out
we shall prove caught up in the grind
yes we shall prove Amber coin's power we
still have a pretty bad reputation but
we shall improve it together but
remember I'm a spy yes so so we like
pretend that I betrayed you and you're
like oh my gosh that Freda Freda I hate
her Antoinette senior how could she do
this to her own Guild but I I oh my main
goal is to benefit our Guild do not okay
okay so by the at the end of the day you
will be wearing the same hat as I I do
not have that hat but not at the end of
this day but at the end of a day in the
near future yes yes
yes okay okay okay okay I I will keep it
in mind okay I hope that that all you
said to me is truthful and it will not
end up in me being Bamboozled it is not
it is the truthest of truths okay I rely
on you my lady of the Amber corn got
I got you girl farewell
farewell app Coin App Coin App
coin that would be nice if it all ends
in a big haha
bamboozle but I won't be there for that
big finale probably I'll be there in
spirit uh okay got to go in
here I have some stuff to report
T
to uh you again or
yeah okay five diamondo did you take
them away from me or what sorry that's
not enough gold ingots cuz you're BL ah
wait you want uh it to be turned into
five can I do that uh on the crafting
table wait she was so quiet even at
maximum I couldn't hear her well but I
raised her a little bit on OBS now we
can have our bgm
again okay um
ingots what you said it's one to
one do I burn it probably it's been a
while that I have done it like
this
okay is she
streaming she sounds a little bit like
sickly another vow voice back coming oh
my God see like I I told you like a
while ago that I took so many voice
packs wait which one is it this time
she's not streaming okay
which voice Pi is it this time the Y one
ah I see I see I
see yeah they like gave us choices what
we wanted to be like C did it did it
yand did it and there was another
one and I chose yand cuz I wanted to
scream loudly and be
angry yeah but there's like several
voice packs right now so if you want to
support me
like you know with a a small sum of gold
coins um while receiving a nice little
uh voice pack tangent
toino make sure to get these voice packs
uh it's it's a lot so maybe I'll make
like a post about it or so or I'll
combine them all the images of it and
put it as my ending screen or something
one of these days so that we all know
what we have cuz I honestly lost track
of it too how many voice packs of me are
on sale right now one of the most recent
ones was the back to school one where
I'm also on the
cover next to Gigi and bi Boo and
O M very
cute yeah I stopped for a while and then
like they sent so many things to sign up
for and I'm like okay I'll sign up for
this oh this one too I guess I'm not
setting up for everything but you know I
think there was like
uh uh yeah recently there was also a
sports one
right where I was playing
football and I was like running in the
spot I tweeted about that when I
recorded it I think as was running in
the like in the
spot uh while recording it I was like I
hope I hope this will sound like I'm
actually running on the soccer
field and yeah then there was the one
where I was on the water talking to you
guys I don't know how I did that the
island
one talking to you guys on the water cuz
it's apparently a thing called Sea
underwater walking sea walking I don't
know basically like I said oh I like
snorkeling so or diving and I wouldn't
mind like teaching the list nerd uh how
to do that but then they made me walk on
the water really
interesting okay gold ingots done
Diamond uh also Done Right both of
them uh could you bring me a gold shovel
enchanted with efficiency free okay now
we make the gold shovel with
these things see this is really like for
me this is
actually the ideal event
cuz you guys know I love Minecraft uh
mostly for its adventures and all that
and not like building
things and for me this is
amazing what is this butter block how do
I make a shovel like can they teach do I
buy there's quests there's dungeons it's
amazing oh I
bye I wish
I wish
I I wish this was like a thing
constantly I actually really like it you
know I was like really worried when
people were um like after the trailer
you guys were like expecting for us to
have like an original game and it made
me feel so like pressured like oh God
when they find out that it's so to say
just
Minecraft I was trying to lower your
expectations
but you know the presentation like if if
the presentation wasn't so like high
quality then you guys would be excited
about this to but I think you guys are
all very excited about how this has been
going and it has brought us many fun
interactive streams where everybody's
like having
fun so it's great right and then it
comes with such high quality
presentation with like um music the song
is really cool that they made and you
know this will continue and with more
chapters and more cool stuff so I
think I think we'll have a lot of fun I
hope next time when this continues cuz
it ends for now uh on Sunday I think it
will take a
while until the next chapter starts
because I haven't heard anything about
it yet um it will happen but I have no
idea when so I think it will still be
quite a
while yeah it will take them a while to
build it and like shape it and write L
lore and this and
that I don't think it would be next
month cuz I would know about it if it
was next
month no I think it will take a long
time um certainly maybe not too long
maybe not a year but maybe like I don't
know couple months I don't know I I
really don't know I haven't been
told but I hope then I would be more
available for
it yeah it's unfortunate I was really
busy during this time but honestly like
with so many members it's hard to find a
time frame where no one is busy there
will always be someone who's busy if not
several people who are
busy yeah we all have our individual
projects
too like my birthday thing birthday that
became anniversary that became later
than anniversary
we all have these kind of things oh it
can't be helped we can't like make it
perfect for
everybody
right aborn had a hard time this chapter
yeah I agree like
it's a weird coincidence it's not on
purpose it's a we coincidence that the
members uh the the smallest group the
smallest Guild is the one where two of
them me and Bae are kind of inactive
H and M also missed like one or two days
I think did she and she's sick yeah so
do I just get both of these help
me cuz they said free right but I need
uh uh I need threee and this is 2 two so
if I do 2 two I get four
no Amber corn the underdog
[Music]
I can't combine it oh oh wait for wait
was it Fortune free or efficiency free I
thought it was efficiency
free what uh what do I do
then I could ask someone let's let's see
if it's written in the side quest
otherwise
H okay let me call someone for a
hint Who would know oh you know's online
let's ask
[Music]
gathan hello hello gathan I am calling
you Jonathan in the request for Aid uh
just in the just in the form of your
voice perhaps but uh could you please
share with me the information of how to
create a a golden shovel with efficiency
free I am in the possession of a golden
shovel but I do not know how to make it
efficienc are you of um if you look at
the bar of um look within and you will
see a bar and what number do you see
upon within that bar does it just cost a
lot wait M I'm in a call right now I'll
talk to you in a moment uh
21 I'm on you must reach once you reach
the age of 30 on that bar you will be
able to use it to enchant your shovel
and you have to obtain some lapis lazuli
to enchant it but it says like the the
the table says Fortune free is what I
will be getting not efficiency free perh
there's another one when you try
crafting a stone shovel and then putting
an enchantment on it to cycle it you
will want to uh you have to gacha it and
if you want new choosing you will need
to place an enchant on a different item
before you can enchant it once more okay
it so first I shall level and then I
shall uh try putting in different
tools to see the result M so check the
tool again once you've Enchanted another
item and if efficiency 3 is not there
you will need to enchant another tool oh
oh I appreciate your
assistance it is no problem Tanashi
karia Shakira yes for sure Shakir thank
you Shakira for
short well please call upon me if you
need my assistance again
congratulations okay I think we're doing
the same
thing are you trying to get an enchanted
golden shovel yeah how do how do you do
it first we must reach level 30 it seems
do we have 30 yeah free zero all right
time to go grind grind what level are
you uh 21 and you
22 oh close we are of close age what's
the fastest way to kill the kill the
thingies M I would perhaps just go to a
place like the first
dungeons the F why are you taking a bath
right now in front of my eyes it is l
mean too I'm so sorry I didn't know you
were
looking yeah I would probably just go to
the like where the stains are at the
like there were so many at the portal to
the underworld I think oh for example I
need it I was wanting to go to the
Atlantis dungeon
oh why because I want I need to get
diamond
diamonds H for the Diamond
Quest I just want oh you just
oh it's okay I shall accompany you would
you like to I need to empty out I have
so much stuff I'm going to buy a
[Music]
backpack I have
sewers once but not twice what are the
sewers you speak of you didn't go yet
either what are the
sewers is that the dungeon is that a
dungeon of sew
oh egads what does that mean I I
e
gets e
gets
OTS let me yet I have
not
ah backpack
please Oh I thought you were going to
start singing have not gone yet a
okay uh uh you you should probably go
with the
detective if you haven't gone yet all
right I shall okay but I have not
perhaps you will gain some age levels in
there as well oh very true if I don't
die I will not die I will not die good
luck I will I will come back to
alive I hope so I'll carry a photo of
you in
my oh my God what's the word what's the
word sword uh lock it lock it pocket I
pocket my yeah I am flattered and
flustered yes and if I am about to die
I'll look at it goodbye okay goodbye wow
I'm in her
locket Jord them no she literally says
with them free who didn't go yet she
even wants to go alone or people who
haven't gone
yet I'm a hates
mey Noy
it's okay I I I'm just going to you know
do the things I've been trying to work
on they want to do it without spoilers
yeah right I mean I could just shut up
but like the others the others were like
not saying
anything it's
okay yeah yeah yeah no I get it I wanted
people to not spoil me either I'm not
saying that I would spoil anyone
[Music]
oh well what was I doing ah gain
levels you you should shout that when
you go into the dungeon as your like uh
your your Mighty catchphrase I am so
Irish I'll do it now I am the danger
[Music]
Str hey what's up doc are you Irish nice
to make your acquaintance
because you're wearing a a green hat and
your red
head what is
Irish Irish is
Irish oh yes I am I see interesting
right company into the source yes I I
swear I remember licking your wife the
other day do you not have her around
anymore lick licking yes have you
forgotten my wife did not notify me of
this
it was it was in front of you comrade
was it
what my name yeah hold on it's written
down H did you say turned down it is it
is written down written in my pocket it
is fra Adams anet
Senor wait what was the first what wait
say that again Freda Freda okay Freda
nice to meet you Freda hello detective I
am lady bloodflame me lady bloodflame
I'm a detective I assume you forgot
again I already talked to you about
detective things before assumed you were
a lady I guess I'm a detective may
iomp you while shutting my mouth and
doing my quest for the second run I
guess that makes sense um for what
purpose are you getting coin for this
Quest yes and I also need to gain age
levels and will I be receiving a percent
of the coin you received from this Quest
are you asking coin from the others who
were accompanying
you well it is their first time the
experience with them is uh
[Music]
Priceless how much coin do you
want well how much coin will you be
receiving from the quest uh let me check
if we are you are not oh I believe
thank you
man
[Music]
scam why not I'm going to shut up
anyway where is where's the
quest uh Temple alwi
volcano ancient
sewers how much
[Music]
oh it doesn't
say it doesn't say how much coin I will
receive well then I will require a fee
how
much I believe five coins will suffice
five
coins fine I will give you
50 oh what a deal he h yes all right I
will accept your offer
y 55
fine I'll give you
500 oh for free not to flex or anything
uh I give you 500 for the return
of uh
445 what which I think comes down to 55
then right math genius I demand 55 coin
I shall give you 56
wonderful
wonderful can you break a
200 yes I I I do have oh wait you want
it up
front yes I require it up front uh let
me see I've never done this before
[Music]
Oh 50 is this pardon me I must go behind
this tree for 2 minutes you are not
taking a leak in the public area are you
okay I think I did
it
meat oh thank you thank you wow that is
a fair exchange yes very high quality
meat m i required that anyway I
appreciate
it I've invited you to my party as per
the terms of our contract oh do I need
to read theine print have you got enough
food thank you I I might need some some
more here I will help thee a knight will
help a fellow
Knight it is so it is
true I know I know of it first
experience firsthand experience here I
shall trade with a
stick thank you for your
[Laughter]
stick I I'll use it well d
d maybe you can use it in the arena ah
yes I
mean if if it wasn't part of the rules
to have just a wooden sword I would use
a stick just to show off with the stick
you can make a
sword that is true sticks are
important we using our Revelations no
only Uh Wood no you only use a wooden
sword in a wooden Revelation perhaps you
magically get a wooden sword no arrive
back in time uh the dungeon is quick
you'll be it's pretty fast
okay I believe we are just missing um
hero Nino Ina n she may be but first I
will look for this mad person who I you
could call her defecating on the public
property oh she's still oh my
[Music]
God now did I look we do not need to
witness such things my eyes I need to
wash
them perhaps with sewer water where the
hero n in a
frequence I am uncertain you made you
might want to give her a
call would you perhaps make the phone
call for okay are you
shy oh no yes you
are mushh oh hello hello I have been
requested to uh call you um to inquire
where you might be uh to soon depart for
our quest to the dungeon uh I was
talking to the king oh and now I got to
go to these sewers I don't know where
the sewers are okay so you are more or
less ready for it okay have I met you
before I mean I mean at least
lightly I was in the vicinity of
you I have
you have forgotten that was harsh
punishment that's I seem to have very
bad memor oh I see the party is here
well yeah the party is here hello let me
get out of this call hello party let's
do a party
callot
hello ra the
roof fra you must accept our invitation
who's Freda oh thanks okay
okay
H it has been accepted do I oh and then
I partyle yes we are here okay I will
indeed shut my mouth so you guys will
have to find the dungeon yourself it's
not like I remember I I do not I really
do not remember how to get there oh well
they said the king said it was the uh oh
shoot you guys visited the king already
tell go the king he has a very strong
Scottish I don't know what Scottish
actually means but Scottish action
according to the voices in my head is it
Scotland Scot Scottish from Scotland
scsh Scotland yeah if you if you could
change your fate would you I don't
know I don't he talks like very I think
he talks like this
or yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah make
cas yes Mye Mye
M A Rose
Mye I can't believe Scottish is
real what for lands do you speak of
Irish is real
too lands I read in a book not heard
of oh I'm reading the things he says oh
yes oh yes I see
uh-huh such a small King reached
a yep uhhuh
ah the witch has
returned oh dear an omen oh no that's
not
good are you Skipper
Skipper I know I I have incredible
reading abilities I had forgotten how to
read and then when it all came back it
came back even better than before
ooh I wonder why you have this ability
I think I'm special it's quite rare in
these times in these trying times here
want to hear how fast I can read
yeah
oh
impressive she's absorbing the the text
go to the castle and speak to king libus
oh I did that speak to the Jade sword
Guild Master is that what you all have
do got make the rounds the green one you
haven't done this yet oh no you have
done this wait you've all done this oh
no oh no I just finished it's okay King
onward apologies if you can hear me
munching on the minest of Wheats oh the
minest of
wheat is it the one with the magical
white sauce on
it
what what are you eating yes something
something like that that yeah mini
miniest of Wheats Min of Wheats Min I
think it is called
icing
Icing sugar o icing I am very aware of
sug
sug I might be going here icing is
something I have previously feasted on
on top of a cinnamon
tornado the cinnamon tornado yes it's
real it is so I've seen them when those
I thought it was just the food of the
Legends it is realer than anything I
have ever
witnessed here oh
okay yes the the green ones like to hide
in the in the little cave
cowards yum yum
yum I gave very oh shoot
okay oh yeah
shoot are you reading super speedy
again is inde
fascinating is a skill I wish to
acquire you see
it wand Master okay all
right follow
a perfect Scarlet again
um the other way I'm not sure oh you're
right I think it is the other
way oopy doopy okay let me know when you
girls are ready to go I will go slay
some stains I am ready I am waiting in
the king's chair for
a oh no worries did not realize you all
did this already
are they this way ah they're right here
oh oh that is them wait my GPS they have
the same hat as you you should you
should
know I I know many
things no no matter what I click
on there we
go oh my gosh I have to speak to
everybody
okay too much socialization for one day
M social B batteries oh no my goodness
social going to be drained batteries
what are
batteries what are
batter I'll show she has finally done
it I'll talked about it the first day we
were here how's she do
it I didn't get up
there I have accomplished the feet which
now names me as the new king wait potato
salad
perhaps potato salad is that the trick
salad no potato salad was not involved
in my coming to
King any other food that has boosted
your
abilities in an unnatural
[Music]
way
hey
what
what was I too close to
uh her Secret
H I thought it was no comment but no it
was just the call that was
over yeah but like it what was it
because I was too close to the
solution oh someone called in private
ah someone was called or I guess Amit
was called in
private makes
sense are you with the others right now
what yes I am oh I
see it's quite comfy here I should say
are you also on the chair I am indeed
H well somewhat of a royalty
myself aren't we all
okay has this not already been
[Music]
10 I mean I am quite related to a
princess which kind of makes me royalty
which makes me qualified to be on the
throne I
believe are you guys fighting over that
right
now
perhaps don't fight share
[Music]
it can I count to
10 maybe I should
have
oh what was that oh level
up we are all ready to Traverse
[Music]
H okay he can't even get up by
[Laughter]
himself
oh pryal all right I believe we are
ready for the sewers so we we are ready
for the sew the sewer dungeon and meet
you at your Arena oh
wait one second okay uh at the sewer
dungeon yes to the Sewer dungeon to the
to the sewers huz
huz oh it's
foggy wait a minute these these lanterns
look very familiar just like the ones in
the
dungeons huh the one that castle know
the entrance no I don't think this is
the entrance I think the entrance is uh
the purple marker on the magical map
that was given to us by the higher power
I'm on my
way I must find the bridge here we go
OHA you must join our per party
call party
call that so beautiful no it sounds so
medieval I like it hi I I just lost oh I
found
[Music]
her
oh oh I
see are you in front of the sewers turn
your lights on lady my goodness I put my
turn signal on I did not see
that sounds like a you
issue I don't believe so I think you
have an issue with lying
luckily I have a dash
cam in my in my
brain are you still I know you are crazy
are you vloging sometimes it I did know
such thing yeah right sorry of course
you don't not as that is not a
technology that is available to us yet
oh yes I I've done absolutely
nothing anything you name it it was not
me
strong wait I should have made oh you
know what I'll be right back is it is is
it is is it interesting I do not hear
sound of this
world I shall receive a diamond
sword wait is this the right way I do
not know huh I'm following
you um St
I I'm
the marker
doesn't I don't think I right
away everything else is working so I am
[Music]
unsure are you girls
lost okay that
works I see I see this what was your
name your name your name your name oh I
am John Watson with a
Y John Watson with the
Y yes Wason with the Y oh
yeah look at us we all wear different
hats are we one from every single
different Guild like the Power Rangers
yes because uh Freda has betrayed the
Amber coin
Guild oh yes I see yes we are not
getting along you and I we hate each
other oh yes but we will get along for
the purpose of the of succeeding in the
dungeon oh how I love you so oh how I
hate you so
more oh oh oh oh no fighting yet but the
moment I enter this dungeon my feelings
for you shall poof Into Thin Air perhaps
into something beautiful I will become
neutral and we'll see where it goes from
there oh W suddenly I feel this love
form this bird Freda graffiti upon the I
still feel neutral
then I shall feel neutral
too but perhaps if I feel enough love I
will return it h I will work hard for it
the memory Shard one
moment Oh I thought we received those
after we clear ha if you know oh yes yes
I am preparing mentally okay I see I
see
meditating she's meditating wow
diamond sword you have wow thank you I
have but a pickaxe for this dungeon it's
all right I shall protect you all I am a
hero from another world if you if you
didn't know thank you for your your
protection all right I'm ready are we
ready ready Freddy The Gift of the
Night o ready I am ready more than I
ever was before ready
[Music]
oh here we go
whoa oh my what is this place I've never
seen it before it's so dark and so deep
my goodness we find ourselves in the
white empty space it's so vast that the
very concept of distant distance seemed
to lose
meaning in the midst of the space we see
an antique desk in a leather chair and
on that chair sits a girl sipping tea
tick tock tick tock we hear a clock but
from where
tick tock tick tock as more and more
clocks join the chorus the girl closes
her
eyes oh I finished reading that way
before you she's too fast for us just
letting you
know not only is she fast but also
humble wow seers we're going to see
some seat a lantern
May prepared perhap some mutant turtle
of teenage age
ah perhaps a type of lizard that lives
on the coast oh there's letters where
did you obtain a lantern if I may ask
from the store the shopkeep yes I did
not which source of energy did a certain
offbeat Reaper discover people's strong
emotions consuming people people Souls I
know which one it is I believe it eating
lots of sushi wait wait oh there's
another oh what's Sushi sounds
reasonable
[Music]
Sushi sure she love sushi should we it
say it's eating lots and lots of sus I
think that's pretty sus maybe we should
someone should try for science to select
the the wrong one okay is the wrong one
consuming people's
Souls I believe so or perhaps sushi that
sounds sweet we all have to if I die do
I lose all of my XP no oh are you
telling the truth will you die she is
she is you will not become
younger unfortunately oh dear it's
attached my name to my I don't know if I
feel comfortable about that oh it's it's
a majority
vote I split the V vote into the third
party let's go and what will happen if
we oh I think we must I guess everyone
has to vot the same oh I see I'm curious
what happens if we pick the wrong answer
oh oh oh we battle we
battle that's good I need to grow older
ow I appreciate this challenge I don't
have a
shield don't we all ah oh that was fast
oh oh we went
back oh it's it's the beginning did yeah
now let's answer it correctly shall
we okay I guess we must a pretty place
to farm the
stains yeah yeah that would be good
brain power does not you don't have to
run so
far so this is some type of exam huh mhm
everyone taking
notes back to the school that I have not
been
to a
librarys a
a book here souls are not a zero sum
game that's what the reaper realized for
if she could stir the hearts of her
audience the power of their emotion were
energy enough yond the Crimson bows a
treasure lies in waight the Gaze of orus
will point you Street The Gaze of
Orphus oh oh what oh is this a puzzle
perhaps is there a secret is this book
case move or something perhaps of orus I
think it's just through here
ah orus what if there's a secret oh a
secret a secret you
say oh secret I don't know it could
possibly be there has been secrets in
the other
one but I guess we'll uh we'll go
ahead we can always come back yes yes
okay we
could let them
cook they're cook
why does orus sound so
familiar
orus or are you think the Morpheus
movie morus orus that why it's familiar
a movie I mean tail tail tails of the
Morpheus of morbius
morbius of that's the name okay which of
these
guard the force around Atlantis Stark
shark statues electric jellyfish do you
remember signified man with the
beard oh you remember it I remember
dolphin statues the dignified man with
the
beard is it not Santa
Claus no no no not Santa Claus it's like
the fish version of Santa Claus oh so a
shark
then perhaps
mayhaps sounds
reasonable
okay
marvelous
Divine de miror another
book in the depth the kingdom of
Atlantis sits safe within its force
field Mighty Stone sharks stand guard to
defend it and yet rumor has it that one
girl slipped through those
defenses the ancient doll meanders and
its maze reward awaits who out boundary
strays
[Music]
so we oh doesn't that
sound like how One achieves The Treasure
of the second dungeon because the
ancient doll sounds like the zombie or
whatever that was the thing with the
Trident if you if you did it did you do
it did you get the secret treasure yes
yes I did it oh did yeah so I did it I
guess this is probably for those people
who didn't do it
yet oh
I we don't to read it's a hint I see
wink screw them book ready to proceed so
generous proceed
huzzah huzzah huzzah
checkpoint okay wow they're asking so
many questions why do they want to know
all these
things maybe they're all related somehow
perhaps mysterious boy appeared at a
certain shine what is he particularly
good at oh you remember do the thing
with the leaf the thing with the leaf oh
wait the thing with the leaf is in here
folding orami they made something that
looked like
a uh an octopus what it called octopus
that's what it is oh so would it be the
takoyaki oh oh it was not
takak
octopus what is
takoyaki I believe I've heard this
phrase used before to refer to octopus
oh to her she was merely keeping them
company but to the souls it was what
they needed to move on one boy left his
things and Orab me before departing for
the other side elaborate passage tests
the eye proceed Beyond the Wall to claim
a priz oh okay okay h M see must have
traveled far if you heard of the word
takoyaki before oh that sounds like I
want to touch it I want to touch
it she touched it I touched it I'm going
to lick it
too oh oh we're in the sour you don't
know what kind of BAC those are some uh
not so F
Waters what is the ground achievement of
a certain phoen OD ball OD the grand
achievement I mean would you rather be
an even
balling a fast food restaurant repay its
debt saving a kingdom that was on the
brink of collapse oh I hope not taking
first place in a hamburger is that what
we're doing right
now I would say wouldn't it be this one
yeah thank you you are so smart I agree
it is this one from the fragment we we
it was this one no no no I saved the
kingdom that was on the brink of
collapse if you did that I'm going to
have to push you off the edge what the
the council will now decide your
fate who is the
council uh me me I'm in I'm was in a
council oh so Council decides that you
closest are you doubting my abilities to
save a kingdom that is on the brink of
the collapse
perhaps well where's the proof of this
achievement then surely they would have
given you a coin or something Have you
traversed have you traversed through my
dungeons yes I did have you seen the
visions of the past yes I did but have
you seen me on top of a cliff where I
looked upon an
army and and what of it it means that I
have saved the kingdom that was on the
brink of collapse I feel like I've seen
a picture where Kiara was you know how
they take a picture after you win an
eating contest like oh you're one of the
people that did it I swear I've seen one
of Kiara on our
website but that is just what I do as a
hobby my my real duty is to save
kingdoms that are on the brink of the
collapse
oh all right all right find in but this
is not the true
me I think this is the true you no it is
not I do
more I do more honorable things than
that it I don't only eat burgers I save
kingdoms the struggling fast food
restaurant finally saw success and
prosperity some say the hardworking new
part Tower is as fire Fury as a phoenix
a crumbling crack in the fury Port fall
a pre may claim reward where others
fall that one was very difficult for me
I remember ni S I
remember it was good for us all H except
for
me oh o a friend not oh goodbye oh
you're so powerful hero I have just sne
I have wait there's another story
here please read it to us wait what was
I the girl stands on the roadside
looking dazed as though she woke up from
a dream the picture in her hand soon
jogs her memory however all right I need
to find this dog the owner is expecting
a call from her soon so she'll need to
be quick this detective has a reputation
to uphold after all don't worry little
guy I'll find you I promise he's finding
a
dog oh how sweet I do love puppies I
must say wow the sewers it's so deep oh
yeah it's pretty big wow what creatures
lay
here what creatures Slumber in these
stain
stain I got to get him I have the oxy
clean was it also being sold at the
shopkeeper was it I made it myself oh
it's interesting wow so many
pathway
o i dable i i dble Freda
The
Alchemist oh afid of The Alchemist I
[Music]
see I hate
stairs I thep stairs I see more
letters my legs are burning what did a
certain detective invent for The
Travelers who made it this this far an
axe oh invented she invented
Crystal an iron pickaxe didn't you say
all you have is an iron pickaxe I I I
did say that oh wait a minute but did
she invent
it invented was there a need for it to
be invented maybe it's a typo maybe it's
what did she bring it but they
accidentally put what did she
invent no I don't think there would be a
typo in the dungeon mhm you never
know well I I I I don't know if this
detective was around to invent an iron
pickaxe or a golden
axe I mean this sounds the most
inventable the most creative perhaps
yeah the most interesting what should I
say interesting it stands out never
heard of it so it's probably this like
the other two get then it says Amelia
Watson what what try to rearrange the
letters it says Amelia Watson
I already do not
CM oh if you try hard enough it works oh
put
the okay and then what do we do about
the E about the Y don't question
it what's that a chest oh so suspicious
hold on there's a book here first wait a
moment I leave this for the hero who
will one day visit this place may it
serve you well each chamber past has
offered you a rhyme revealing ing
Secrets where you've gone before there's
one last thing to find here out you
climb and therefore I present you one
more a haunting grounds of creatures of
night within its depths you'll find the
hidden light hidden light oh hidden
light War Crystal this be the hint are
we supposed to use the warp
Crystal it do have swe we T the war
Crystal allow you to teleport to select
the warart
[Music]
interesting think you're on some onto
something should we use it I'm going to
use it oh it says it can't be used here
oh just
kidding well there's another place here
we can
proceed oh would this would this be the
end of the dungeon I think
so I think that what about the secret
treasure the secret yes yes we must
investigate to find the secret treasure
okay
we have the hint there was a secret
treasure in every dungeon there must be
one in here investigation begins no I
don't think there's one in here H sure
oh theygot about creatures of the night
must be the stains no or we were
fighting the stains perhaps oh yeah
smart with then it's so we got to answer
one of the questions
wrong does it work like that can we even
go back and do that we can try let's
just go back for once
backtracking I can't use the warst ah
it's still here will let us and uh it
not let us undo it oh it won't let me
pick seems that hot air balloon is
filled with hot
air oh can we not go
back we can there's a crystal there is
that just a checkpoint and we can't go
back yeah I mean there were stains in
like the the hallways if we can get
there
again true
true what is this
hole seems but a mouse hole
perhaps oh can something be observed
with this mouse hole no
interesting interest
no dingon can be perfect there must just
be no treasure
today
no no I do not believe such
hery they must have forgotten
it such a thing cannot be forgotten if
only we had hero with us oh you want uh
my advice now I can give but I was
waiting for you to request it
oopy oh the party feels shall we request
advice hero a hint would be nice no
advice but a hint is welcome indeed you
must return to where the stains
were as uh the one with the Y was
saying I'm I'm going to die I'm oh no
I'm not which I I'm not sure I think you
should be able to return from here I I
did it like right away
so maybe if is perhaps broken
no wait how do you
uh much walking somebody carry me oh I
think I have returned to
it I yeah if you just go back back back
you can go to every question
room and it was before the questions I
think if I recall
correctly H oh no wait oh yeah over here
I guess it was was it here where are you
was here
um uh wait let me try to find you have
we gone too
far the first question almost yeah we're
at the uh we at ena's
it's here is that is it before in's
question it's uh when you let me let me
track
back there is I don't think went ahead
of us I think that it's back here oh
okay
wa I'm getting lost went past
us I'm
lost wa I found another new
checkpoint I see no
names but okay there I see a question
again did you girls pass the question of
oh yeah the
detective yeah we went we went to Ena
so mhm guess way it is between question
five and question
four between question five okay this is
now where we are entering okay
ah
M okay it should be should be should be
oh I remember I remember yeah I see your
names yeah hello wonderful we have
reunited I'm looking in every corner
don't follow me that's not a good
idea I'll go down this way
yes it must be where she was before no
where she came
from yeah around here
where uh notify me when you are in the
need of another hint oh am I too far
okay I'm too
far don't follow me don't follow
me I'm doing suspicious things
watch
[Music]
me wait where did you girls go we're
here where did you go that's the
question it's getting should I say hot
and cold
perhaps that seems good hot hot hot hot
me hot hot you're so hot I'm hot hot oh
thank you
hot oh
I'm hot hot
hot cold
cold hot hot that's a very
H did you hear my
we that's the
hint ah
hot what I'm
smoking oh treasure hidden l oh I've LED
for
the what treasure have you
found it is but the disc what does it
say it
says it says not you didn't pick it up
no thank God I
asked Tick
Tock what does this have to do with the
hidden light though
there's light down
there I think maybe I was wondering if
what I honestly don't know but I think
for one of these windows where you can
look into the sewers you might be able
to see a
light like oh yeah actually I can see it
from
here ah and maybe you can see it from
other directions too
oh is this the right way uh yeah yeah
yeah yeah return We Shall
yeah that one difficult to
find no I bet I could have found it
myself I think so I bet you could have I
bet a hefty
amount we shall uh leave this dungeon as
soon as possible to partake in the
tournament oh yes I need my honor I ran
out my honor I also need honor
but I think that is the door that will
Mark the exit ah okay will you all fight
in the tournament I shall for
Honor for honor I'm may all right yippe
are we going to
remember oh for sure oh I wonder if we
will unlock another Crystal core
memory where is that from hippity hop
hippity hop hop pry Hop look at this
maybe maybe Amy wants to read
it find ourselves in a white empty
space girl still sipping tea opens her
locket and reveals a number of pictures
each of them shows a girl who looks
exactly like herself one is searching
for a lost dog another is building some
sort of machine yet another is playing a
video game she gazes at the photos with
a a video game what is
that the photos with a warm smile let's
see where should I go today
all
right very
informative you shall witness the
memory completed objective investigate
the ancient sewer dungeon your power of
Revelation has grown stronger oh my
goodness it's so recovered a portion of
your memory sound I'm
I'm the m
[Music]
Thanks for the Memories even though they
just weren't so
great all
[Music]
alone you and Ena should
know oh they muted okay okay I I didn't
okay I'll stay
quiet I
will how is it how's the
movie it was good I already watched it
oh you already watched it yeah I really
I thought it was kind of rude in how it
represented me unlike the others I was
not a mythical being man what the hell
there was no reward for you
yeah you simply
I'm just the burger lady you're just the
burger that's where I saw the
picture that's that's why I I
went I read ahead I read too fast but
food is
important f is important I still want a
burger me too your your dungeon really
made me want a
burger maybe this is all bur Burba
Burger propaganda because on in am's
memory there's also big ass
burger I think so so many burgers are we
selling burgers Burger
sponsorship burger burger
burger was your favorite
dungeon wow I remember you remember
detective detective why she still
muted a m what yeah
mil she likes
Burgers who
doesn't psychopath wait what's wrong
with mine oh hello friends she has
returned Amelia Watson I'm back I know
who I am now you know do you remember
she knows oh my goodness I am I am not
Jonathan Watson I Amelia Watson Amilia
was right you
are I'm a a detective
not just the detective you're the number
one
detective oh I am number one detective
at least of
bestl I'm one detective of Livy maybe I
should offer my
services you
could wasn't there a case of uh
someone ruining the face of the queen or
something there was an inquiry about
that
detective the graffiti I believe yeah
oh I will investigate this
okay all right is it time to trot back
home yes let's go back to the arena
Arena I Will Follow You Ena is it
happening I think it is it shall be at
half past half past
Crystal wonderful wait
what we can go to different places at
the warp Crystal yippee
we oh should we warp home then where
should we go to theal Castle let's warp
all the way home oh yes we must talk to
the king hello prin
okay oh yeah talk to him ah King wait
what goodbye
princess there we
goit wait a
minute could have taken the crystal
again detective I think the crystals
broke oh dear the crystal you you really
goofed this Crystal up I I was promised
fast travel to the
castle I did not I don't have any memory
of making this Crystal maybe perhaps
when my memory was
uh I want a refund of my time wait is
this the right way I think this is the
wrong way no refunds oh I follow
you oh the horse girl is back no that
was just my horse oh ah the horse speaks
oh am I fine the horse does
speak I'm
fine it speaks whenever it hits somebody
oh thank God I was ready to go back
inside oh yippe Quest is
Fin and now the stairs I'm still not age
for not either I didn't I barely I see
you return saely PR tell front by and
the SE
below I see as the rues before memories
were regained and Revelations aw in a
predictable outcome mayhaps but never
less welome I've never heard you
speaking such an acent before the
Revelation are to greatly Empower but
now beautiful stand to well
here you breathe the S relief for now at
least what with the quck and the angry
since St
activity and the world seem to live
closer we thought we could do more to
stay here alas since the earthquake
there have been no further reports of
unusual activity from anywhere in the
game a feel this but CL Cal before the
storm and some something yet more
terrible is
that you take this time to prepare train
the combat skills and stock up any items
you might need may be your last chance
to make the
most please land of your PA just a w
longer here for peace and the future of
the
best the
king sounds
amazing we did it we're ready for the
last battle
oh sounds perilous I can't I run anymore
I'm going to try to get to level 30
before the arena thing happens it's in
like at half past so I'm going to leave
the party so I can enter the dungeon
again to find some stains ah okay good
luck thank you for your
assistance uh do the same I think oh
okay maybe we make this part you hero
okay goodbye all right thank you see you
thank you heroes and villains see you
next hero and and the one that I hate
again now that I'm out of the dungeon
but I don't hate her it's just us acting
because we're role playing within the
role play you know no no
exp
oh if uh I hope uh when she said she
will do the same she didn't mean she
will cuz I was where the hell can I find
stains they weren't there where they
usually were like like flocking around
where should I go if they don't give XP
in
there maybe the
coast mining is fast ah okay yeah maybe
I'll
mine let me tell her
that hello fellow Ember corn member
hello I was just about to call you once
I figured out how to call people I shall
share with you an important
knowledge the stains in the dungeons do
not give H increase but the fastest way
to increase your H in a quick time frame
might just be going to the uh underwater
dungeon and Mining crystals and gems oh
I see I was trying to oh I have the warp
thingy so I can EAS get there now
oh I'm on my way beautiful I think I
shall see you there all right see you
there actually we can stay in the call I
guess okay I am do you want me to wait
for you by the coast or do you want me
to go oh I'm already diving on the water
oh okay I'm going to go do
that okay which gem brings the most XP
maybe damond wait a minute I need my
thingy my thingy oh I got my thingy okay
Rec confirm are you currently
vlogging I am not I see how come Vlog
because I didn't know when the Vlog
could begin and I was not home so I
couldn't set anything up ah I see I
see yes it's okay I am vlogging for you
now that is fine I'm also going to be
building stuff I oh feel like I'm very
slow at if oh yeah right you want to
build your own like uh Nana 11 was it
yes theana 11 I like the idea of that I
will invest the wa coin into the Shakira
coin yes the Shakira Shakira Shakira
Shakira
Shakira oh my oh baby when you talk like
that it makes a woman go
mad yes so be wise oh and do what and
shoot I don't remember be calm no some
and something about the size of my body
ah I know that these uh poems are very
very
wise whoever wrote them must have had a
great talent in the English language is
iron pickaxe not enough to mine gold uh
I think it should be why is it in
working I'm going to hey are you on the
water try to go out of the water into
the big hole where you can breathe
properly then it works better okay yes
yes y oh you're right yay cuz I heard
that uh little bit out of uh rooll play
right now but I heard that Shakira's
lyrics from back then the whole album
was this isn't out of role play there's
Shakira in this universe yeah wa was
machine translated right which is so
funny
I didn't know that what yeah like all
the English lyrics All the English
versions of her songs were I heard
so we machine
translated did you hear from a from a
reliable source source reliable
source
beautiful or maybe partially where did I
hear
this who has told me such
rumors talk
Shakira songs translated by
machine
[Music]
no now I can't find anything about it
maybe I have been
bamboozled Bamboozled have you but I
like this version of the reality cuz
it's
funny it is that would be W believe it a
a WKA w a away yeah damn you got it you
got it uh Freda antonet I forgot the
third name Adam Adams anet I Adams an
anet
senor senor senior oh senior wow who's
your
Junior I don't have one
yet I've been looking for
one and I felt that none have fit the
junior
title I must I would offer myself but I
don't think I quite fit it either no I
am no one's Junior you do not fit yes
not my
junior even this feels kind of slow
should I only be mining this does feel
kind of SL
or what's the best one I mean I think
diamonds might be the oh yeah diamonds
pretty
big I just comparing that is definitely
the best one M okay but I want a little
bit of everything true all the shiny
stones bird love Shiny
Stone are you a bird in this
universe um
I yes yeah what the probably
that's why I feel like you're so
familiar eat carrots perhaps that's why
we are in the same
Guild but I've seen birds in other
guilds as well they're not real birds
they're
robots I could agree with that because
narissa didn't know about the incubation
period of a bird's
egg oh yeah which bird but she might she
might know and just you know like try to
she might be embarrassed yeah she was
trying to say that she like just got a
child by uh Elizabeth which was like
consumated yesterday and then I I told
her well the incubation period is 21
days or so and then she was like this is
not
true perhaps she had a
premature that is very premature I think
then it shouldn't have looked the way it
looked because she literally birthed a
chicken in front of my eyes and I said
well wouldn't that be for
me for you she birth the chicken for you
from me oh from
you like you hire as a surrogate what no
I don't yeah perhaps I I just think it
doesn't look like
she consumated it with Elizabeth oh
seems highly
doubtful yeah and Elizabeth was saying
it isn't true either so
what if she is insecure because she is
incapable of having chicken
Offspring uh Elizabeth or
Nissa who's insecure wait who who who
who claims that they birth the chicken
Elizabeth wait a minute oh I'm so lost
Elizabeth bed a chicken yeah no uh no
sorry narissa bed a chicken and claimed
it was by Elizabeth wait a minute a she
live bed the chicken in front
wait a minute there's a few things not
adding up here right
exactly she gave life birth to a chicken
yeah
afterwards is she what did she nurse it
um no there was no need of nursing
because I just followed my duty as a
fast food restaurant owner as given to
me by the lower memories uh bur to
question I'm questioning if it was a
chicken at all it was a chicken
certainly it tasted like chicken after
all you atat it well you've seen you've
seen my memory haven't you I have so I
made it in I fried it I I just did the
thing that felt right according to my
lore no I don't blame you at all thank
you I I was just confirming yeah okay
good good good they said I was a witch
and I said I'm just doing my my lore
Duty I think she's more of a witch the
fact that she didn't lay that she gave
birth to a live chicken within one day
too she claims yes no it's I think she's
projecting projecting
yes see I I knew it I knew there was
something with you you you just you get
it I get it completely now that no one
is here we can talk freely and admire
one another wonderful finally I've been
waiting for this
day we' been so what admiration I hold
I've been so I just I've been feeling so
held back these past days because we
were being torn apart we were torn
apart but in our hearts we're always
together yes I thought of you quite
often thank you every
ad I I will remind you um that I am a
phoenix but it's okay well I remember
that you you cooked chicken yeah oh yeah
wonderful she gets it and you kind of
look like
one okay that's fine in a certain light
yeah just a certain very a very very
specific light a very unflattering light
like yes it's a very rare one I'm almost
age uh 30 which is in demand um once I
am done here here you can take over this
perfect strip of diamond that I have
found oh I'm I am about to be almost in
demand one year away from being in
demand oh
same I'm so excited to be finally in
demand
again it's been a while since I've been
in demand go oh this makes
[Music]
sense it's
coming 1
2 3 oh my goodness you're already that
close to being in demand I am being
demanded as of now oh my goodness
[Music]
yippee I'm getting a workout here I will
wait for
you I'm going to be a fit
30-year-old let's
go all right I'm about halfway through
my 29th Year huzzah Goodbye 29 fre zero
is the number
now almost my
gosh now I know why she had so many
diamonds back so many
diamonds I mean I have so many yeah I'm
rich nice I'm almost oh my gosh I'm
about to be in demand perhaps you can
use these diamonds to make your nana 11
better oh congratulations to us
definitely well yippe all this will go
towards the Nana with us being in demand
in terms of our age perhaps the Nana 11
will also be in demand I can feel it I
think
so okay then we shall teleport back into
the city shall
we yes I'm just I'm just a little greedy
and I'm
getting go for it whatever your hard
desires I want just little
[Music]
we will have the superior cheesecake no
not cheesecake uh the Strawberry
Shortcake better even better mhm I'm not
the biggest fan of Cheesecake yeah no no
no I mean the Strawberry Shortcake good
good okay was
I wait so I be I wanted to become level
30 so I could do this here but I need a
different shovel because this is I also
to
be I'm doing the same thing you but it's
just giving me it's just giving me
Fortune free I need efficiency free so I
need to like do something else first
like a
different this doesn't work
right I need a different enchantment
what do you I don't know how to enchant
stuff I'm going to learn
today oh I made lasagna and fish and
chips when did I do that oh yeah yeah I
think that I also was like surprised
when I saw that it came like out of
nowhere
huh I have no
space
let's burn this
iron oh hello hello oops hello I don't
know how to do this should I look it
up in my head uh wait basically well you
put the lpes that's iant
uh Golden Spoon into the book thing but
if it doesn't say efficiency free there
then you have to like refresh it by
putting a different tool there and
enchanting that first which I guess I
could put my diamond sword in there well
I don't know how to do any of this I put
lapis and then I put I put what else a
book uh no uh like a a tool like first
see if you put in the golden shovel what
does it give you as the third
enchantment oh it gives Unbreaking three
not oh yeah you don't want that not so
for example put a different tool in that
you wouldn't mind
enchanting and reset it basically like
give it a different well but now we need
a level again but I would get Unbreaking
next oh my efficiency free though wait I
can get it oh it doesn't even take 30
levels this
time wait did I mess this
up what did you do I messed it up I
selected the third one I to I must
return to the I must return to the coast
I've lost I've lost years of my life oh
no oh no I've lost three years too we're
not in Demand anymore oh dear all right
I messed it up I must I will return okay
just go to the diamonds I messed it up I
messed it up I ruined it boiled it I
foiled it how could
you rich what did you mess up she uh put
the wrong enchantment on her shovel and
now she's down in her age
again Ah that's so it soiled it sorry
we're on the call uh but uh can can you
tell her I meant to say I soiled it I
soiled it she soiled it she says I
soiled it soiled it soiled it soiled
it but I was able to get the right
enchantment in the end even without
level 30
surprisingly so maybe you don't need it
either I
do all
right a witch cast a spell on me I
cannot
speak poor poor
cie
copine is it already time for the
tournament tournament oh shoot I don't
think I can do this in time I'll just go
to the tournament IR
sword uh wait what was I doing oh yeah
where is
it uh the arena the big big big arena
yes of
course um let's see over
there well now I have a cool diamond
sword too I want can I get a second
backpack for sure I can
right I shall buy another one
okay good cuz it's getting too packed in
this
backpack
um this enough for
you oh
[Music]
perfect can't put this can't put this
this
stuff
oh okay
um oh see I'm right nobody's here nobody
there nobody's here I'm coming
soon oh let kill
me uh
[Music]
okay toon toon on my high horse I'm
coming
over is there a certain entrance oh
there we are hello salutation sal sal
salutations
salutations okay let me ring everybody
else to see if they're on their way yes
yes and hello
copine I hope the curse will soon be
lifted from you I know how rough it is
when you have a curse on
you you notice now that I have been
calling you this all
along because it says Mor
kop the curse you have the curse
[Music]
[Laughter]
not the curse oh do not fret the curse
should hopefully we're off within two to
three weeks good
luck get well
soon you're rocking that outfit
though ha
rocking I don't get it please explain
explain the joke um you must witness our
outfit to understand
I get it you do yes I went behind that
tree to take a a look see at the
outfit good day to you princess
boo I feel like every time I do that I
take your nose oh I and then I put it
back I'm behind you yes I'm here
don't
wor scam
Co scam call scam call you know that
forart just keeps calling everyone yeah
I believe it yes
yes K butts you
say oh wait I'm going to leave this call
because this is this is byebye
we were never in a call we hate each
other excuse me I am your princess I
hate you I will fight you I will kill
you yes I will fight you and I will kill
you you have betrayed the
GU I have I have betrayed you what you
going to do about it do about it I will
kill you an enemy no you
won't I will bet I will show you is it
the the winner unfortunately it is not
five potato salads as well as honor
o
Su party okay
mag but the first match shall be
Jonathan and Freda it's best of
three Jonathan and fra let me
think Jonathan is here really you guys
will have to set it up yourself so one
of you clicks this guy well pokes this
guy and then
ask him to duel and then whoever does it
first needs to click Start once the
other person's
in okay I'm automatically give us wooden
swords yes yes yes it will it will even
out our inventory so it's his sword nice
yes
even is it the KN Jonathan or or is it
it is you Jonathan oh me ah you are
against Freda
[Music]
we can wait until Gan is here we can
wait a minute or so they said they'll be
here in a moment wait I'm still lost but
I'm wait it's is us we're fighting yes
yeah so the first first match shall be
Jonathan and Frida and then it shall be
beu and Shakira and then it
shall and a princess
how' you do that it is not a secret no
it's not it's not a secret I'm not Le
secret secret will there be a second
round
Elizabeth uh there'll be three rounds so
it's best of three oh best of and then
the winner goes on to the next part of
the tournament I must proceed so that I
can fight uh Freda because she has
betrayed my guilt do you know how to get
up there you
trying must bring my sister back was
Thea that is uh the brown haired one
here the one with the horse inside the
she's Hing around away dang
it but I needed
it
oh yes I got up here fa and square oh oh
that's how you trying to get up there oh
I see oh that's how you got onto the
throne no it's
not yes hello welcome welcome we waited
cuz your your beloved is going to fight
first against in the closet I'm going to
kill your
beloved I do have a beloved I'm now
going to come out of the
closet do you make come with me I'm
going to kill your ex beloved I'm going
to kill them what what do they mean what
what do they mean by that I wonder if
the night is
about me so if you
could continue yes as if she does not
know
me just play
along uh
sure okay you okay bro I'm I'm fine
go is it
happening and and Jonathan why don't you
click this guy first and then the other
one also joins clicked it clicked it I
clicked it I clicked it I am ready to
duel not you I will not Jan Jonathan
first her name is not a Jonathan it is
Amelia Watson I believe I used to go by
Jonathan oh yeah she remembered she
remembered wait why does it say dual
canel should I remember that I'm not
Shakura minutes I like being minutes
have not
passed
yeah he is gatekeeping
any rules we cannot use our Revelation
correct I don't think you can
yes away from you this did not your
Revelation yes I I am not able to it
says the arena is currently in use try
again H that's strange let me try it
says I've joined the red team oh
ah
H it does not let me join the duel for
some reason
are you in a party I I'm not in a party
now I left it I disbanded the party it
says we're in a party
together
J
sword
sword CH sword user it says I joined it
says that sword okay I left I left the
game
so I'll just I will wait for moment and
come back CH
sword it seems it worked when I when I
left my party there so maybe it has to
do with parties no don't
leave where are you
going
no dear J sword
user go hey some people are just like
bullying me some people have not been
educated on how to use the futuristic
keyboard okay do not bully my J
futuristic exactly no bu she's wearing a
red hat oh she's wearing a red hat how
are you the Jade sword if you are
wearing a red hat wait no it it didn't
work this is dual cancelled cuz the
opponent has left uh you got to you got
to stay in it and one of you clicks okay
I joined you joined oh yes it says I the
pinky gnome hat it's a red velvet
cake yummy red B
cake do you
have it says can yeah just eat it it's
uh emergency rations start
R rations I
joined all right looking yummy the
game begin yes they will fight onward
fight fight fight fight fight they're
fighting fight
I can't here come closer to us
wi they're fighting goodness oh they're
fighting I want I want M to win so I can
fight
her come on Freda Adams oh we
can't oh no I wish she would die well
then she will die by my
hands congratulations on
win oh she
disappeared as well
magic y okay now I must okay best of
three ah best of three best of three
okay okay okay best of three best of
three oh no
oh I see how it
is the wind is not certain yet
again only are circling each other
what does the winner win all they are
backing away potato salad salad salad
and H your touch her oh she ran forward
fting nothing exceeds the volue of Honor
exchanging blows this could be
anyone's anyone's
match so many
hits once again she has done it she's
too powerful she so powerful
got someone who comes from Amber coin
originally my
headed very well I hit my head really
hard oh I'm sorry that was not very
Sportsman as I watch the rest of the
[Music]
tournament okay next up is beu and
Shakira oh no I'm nervous and
Shakira Shakira Shakira Shakira how do
we do this onward Shakira I'm a
gamer duel click the guy and join the
duel and one of you will have a start
what happened oh I see okay are you
ready uh very ready okay let's go for
Honor oh no
that's she's a gamer
too she's a Souls player for
[Music]
Honor oh princess I sorry for what I
must do to
you easy
actually well she is nothing but a
princess she has not been taught in the
ways of
battle it is only
natural you are a princess after all not
a fighter yes I am I am a princess not
we shall try again though try yes round
two I shall train you my princess so
that you can protect yourself from
evil ways of the fight excuse me please
ignore my trade request way to prepare
for what is yet to come once again
says oh oh again oops oh again oh it
says 5 minutes have passed since first
participant joined try try again
okay I've joined the blue
team begin da d da da
there we go dub and D dub and die dub
and D dub and
[Music]
die oh oh did I do it again oh my god
let's go my God that would have been
embarrassing if I didn't I'm I'm a hero
I'm a warrior I'm a warrior
she's it's because I must avenge I must
avenge
for
ambercoin no for Amber coin not
ambercoin no yes yes
no not know if I can
hurt okay it shall be your name for
tomorrow it is good
name you and one of you will have I just
felt it she's a Vivan
desk I have Vivan Margarita what
happened we are
starting VI and Margarita
Marcus how's that sound oh it's
happening sounds like I'd pay like $10
for
it my sister oh that's a lot of breed
she seems so strong
oh KN has won the Knight has won Miss
ninoa had almost slayed
me round be careful be careful with my
orange
Knight I must eat some meat you have
taken a lot out of
me yes you are a good a good you're a
good opponent you are also a good oppon
CL game indeed close game gathan with
the G
do we go again yes the best of three
onwards
onwards oh I'll join again okay oh yes
yes I really love the way she talks let
us fight till the end fight
again oh here we go
again here we go
again away
fight Orange let's go
change
blows orange why they tied they are tied
TI gathan what happened I do not know
she is just such a good sword woman she
so good at fighting what I believed in
your or make sure we're full full HP
first though I feel like that was not a
fair fight make yes
yes it's anyone's game now is is
anyone's game okay let us go good luck
Knight hold on I'm still not full oh yes
yes you who
slander yes
you I am
not I have no more horse girl than you
or her or her or her or
them I forgive you
you're
forgiven
fuus what's happening ah they exchanging
cloes go go orange be careful or will it
be oh no I lost count I lost
count
yes woohoo Orange has congratulations
Knight thank you y w that was high
you fellow
KN thank you that was a great fight G
yes it was a great fight you were Wonder
close it was a close fight I almost I
almost fell the future of Cilan is
bright it is bright very
bright
bright mother I believe in you mother
G I mean I'm not
mother good good good luck mother mother
mother mother they all is she
mothering she oh she's
mothering and the other one is
fing that was she too powerful she is
very very
powerful you were
Ming
mothering I shall also eat
wow that was that was quite something
that a great fight yes mother we are
proud of you I've never seen anything
like this mother daughters I mean you're
both not my daughters
daughters are they they're not my
daughters don't believe them yes we are
siblings siblings although we haven't
done much to make her
proud what it's okay mother will show us
how it's done yes the side chicks I
don't see a start button do you see a
start Buton so many side chicks what is
a side chick a there we go ah they are
it's a chick on your side relationship
with one another through their side
chicks oh you have many huh are you sure
I have many side chicks you guys you
have side oh they're keeping their
distance yeah the voices in my head are
my side chicks what the seems like we
have different understandings of it not
me got a hits mother no that oh mother
get
mother
no mother and
father is she a father oh no is she
ising mothering so hard let's
go I don't know who I'm rooting
for We are rooting for both mother and
father of course family TI how are they
family what a Twist one what a twist
what a
Twist how
exciting this is
entertainment owners are excellent
fighters in the final battle the final
last final battle B the final battle the
family fun this
time I have
joined do it do it again I want to see
you do it again oh oh they are drooling
once more drooling why are they drooling
they are drooling drooling what are they
drooling over themselves themselves may
have they're drooling over the victory
that would bring them honor yes I would
too who's winning it's so close but it's
so far is this a custody
battle I think so the pink one the pink
one
she
back she has one the pink one has
won power ofat congratulations
88888 ate she ate she that ate at at she
ate ate it all we have been Train by the
same lenia I see
well done
call the next ones to fight is Freda and
Shakira let's go revenge on the traitor
the Revenge oh the traitor of ambercoin
this will prove
everybody of what is the truth where is
the traitor oh there she
is oh
my oh and who do I who am I facing now
it is me your biggest eny Shakira
Shakira Shakir do not lie mhm her hips
does not lie so does my
honor oh once again yes I I'm just not
going okay you do it first do it
again go in go
in all right I want to spill your blood
does anybody want to place
BSS do not have any Co
with once again we shall
trying one Bread
on I press join I
now I wonder what is wrong with it oh I
oh I
see it should work could it's happening
it's
happening
okay this is it guys
we love but we hate each other I love
you I love you people can't hear us I
love you ha you I love you and I hate
you I love you and I I love you and I
hate you I love you and I hate you I
love you and I hate you for
aor under
restored
you excuse me excuse me typical what did
I hear so stronger AB what look at your
typical amorn Behavior it is my honor
again again okay I shall be having my
honor once
again my hands are
bloody oh wait wait wait wait need to
eat y do you not get like healed back up
before the fight I'm ready oh okay all
right let's go let's go one more time
and go
are they still so despised may
[Laughter]
have all the
slander for the reputation of EMP coin
let's fix it together let's fix it fix
it the way to fix it is letting me win
just kidding just kidding I don't think
I can you're going to I'm going to die
no you're going to die
you're oh my God I am a warrior not just
about Burger
my lore is wrong too
good defeated you fought well
undefeated I will never ever return to
ambercoin I detest it we will see about
that I detested I will do everything in
my power to see it fall
uh Freeda they burned me my gooda I will
give you a booby prize oh what I want
the booby prize what the
hell what is the booby priz what priz a
booby prize booby
prize Say booby
prize hey yo what do you mean by that I
want to trade with
you oh she's shy
see are you dead did you just my big
brain cannot comprehend what this priz
is yes it is about a booby
prize Well I I shall take it instead
have you never heard the term booby
prize I have not
prize it is uh so if you are doing a
like uh a pub quiz whoever is the the
last one gets a booby prize which is
something is that what they say in your
lands that you are
from I'm not sure it just comes to mind
whenever I think of a booby
PR makes sense reap when I am sad I
would like to have a booby prize indeed
oh Reaper are you there well you have to
lose
but I would like to give you I would
like to give
you mother I am such a loser May I have
a booby prize please take it represent
the Jade sword I lost I would like a
booby prize as well heart you wanted my
heart I'm such a
loser my my goodness I don't know what
happened to her I guess I killed her
completely surprised by
accident you oh she's leave me
to the booie prize my good the boie
prize let me TR that's what the queen
statue is missing why won't you tell us
prize what
that's why she has leave her alone she's
being worked
on I was just I was just
thinking missing I see
I I will on the booby prize this is so
complicated on the booby prize put on
the booby prize what is the booby prize
what is the booby prize may we see the
booby
prize we burn this boy Burn It To The
Ground first I will dis the booty wait
the booty it's booty is it our
hat I cannot display the booty it's
them we are the same after
all an Amber coin I spit on
it I know I know it belongs to you
wonderous boobie prize I will make a
public display of my my this taste my
next is
against
oh fight Jade so makes Ruan proud I will
do my best but it seems that the reaper
is quite Adept at
fighting I believe in you show her some
empathy I will show her some
empathy empathy empathy King Kelly fight
for k please sword let me fight she
wishes for your wife's where what hat is
people wearing anyway what is that
aren't there just four
hats so
confused here we
go oh here we go I wonder or I have no
idea who to bet on a St for empathy a
you can do
it oh she's got
aggressive hard to tell o I do not know
who is it she's running the KN is
running she's
running
you're you should be what the CH the
bravest of them all you got it does this
mean Orange versus
orange is it going to be orange oh God I
didn't believed in you one more
one more one more fight shall be had I
saw that it was the same Strat he used
against me it was very orange dominance
I believe in you just one more for your
I think that that will be the outcome I
will fight in her in her honor so that
memory may be your memory will be proud
of me my dearly departed
wife you run with the cattle you run
with the Sheep we are the wolves
oh wait where where where did the other
wolf go dang it she's a sheep now I got
poofed back
then oh you got poed oh it was not your
it was not your fault then this is
important to me personally I've got
a g
of I like them both but I must cheer for
orange because I want to see the orange
battle is
Freda I believe Adams Come Back infin
she's using the G let's
go for
empathy is there number one or is orange
next what why what were you saying on
the battlefield to nothing
nothing she just showing some empathetic
words to her you know showering her with
empath you
fought vant all right the the last match
the final match even shall be Shakira
against gathan all right
Gan know you're exhausted but
showed true empathy I will do my best
though she is a murderer I will say this
is the Battle of the oranges so if you
shall win I shall lose my title of
tanaki shakar of the oranges and you
shall be of the oranges you will lose
your
title if I win you will go to court and
trial wait wait that's both just like
bad for me though what what what oh
shouldn't it be something else well if
you win I
will die if you win you will go to court
E I don't know about this deal that's
kind of like oh you no so if I die you
get my title of the oranges if you die
what do I I
get do you have a title will I will I
will stab myself oh H what about
something like she says ARA ARA or some
strange curse words I do not care for
those words she does not care well then
something may I take your may I take i h
i know since you will be getting the
orange title how about since you have no
title to give me I shall take your last
name and make you my wedded person you
you force me to marry you I shall
request you kindly only if I happen to
win this
battle fine let it be off onto the
battlefield I have secretly always feed
my eyes on this orange the stakes are
high let's go let yipp real
love I shall
prove I always had fondness for her I
will not be your wife you are wrong you
must you must I love you actually but as
I am a KN I could never I had to pretend
that was
[Laughter]
easy one
round it's just one round so fast no
that was so fast okay it's just one
round oh no I'm going to have to be her
wife my life is pull yourself back
together so fast I didn't understand
what was
happening going to come back
toan we revealed oh no but it's okay I
get one more uh battle let's see if we
can win with a handicap I have forgotten
I have forgotten to heal up but it is
okay going to
be I canot no I have forgotten to my
heart only begins to hand My Heart
Belongs to one
[Applause]
no it's okay it's okay the next
fight it's okay it's okay we will take
those I accept I accept it because I
will win the next
fight snap it together one more left I
scw this one to give you oh okay
you can you can do it your pear Waits
you my dearly departed wife this is for
you she's still alive she's literally
right behind
youen Okay okay now I'm nervous
[\h__\h] you will not take me as your
wife you will not be W you will face
trial for your murders you you murdered
no a raven cop I seen it I even seen it
with my own eyes you killed her child
the chicken that she laid cuz she laid
IDs you've killed her you will not take
me too you I would rather die
I
what what what just happened that was
weird
no
no no there is no wedding
Noy I do not want your title I only want
you to to go to trial you may keep the
to of the oranges
trian it is a trial tomorrow will the
trial be held it will be held at the
Gallows I suppose sorry how about we
have the trial the day after
tomorrow after proposal because I still
have many things to do uh that I want to
do before I go to prison in case I go TR
to get out of this no are you trying to
get out of this you would not have such
knowledge of me not being available on
the last day so um how about tomorrow I
uh get a few more quests done and then
we have the trial the day after
tomorrow how about you finish your quest
and then we have the
trial a well on the day after tomorrow
of course proposal we have the trial
right now on the bulletin board I still
many to a also get married and have the
trial you can have
why
suspicious she she will not marry I if
you're going to courts anyway true but
if you're there anyway might as well get
married now true I like this logic know
who was she married to to you to
you at the
court belongs to my de departed
wife I
over I know that your wife left
you she did I am here spot I am here for
you I have always admired you I am going
become a sensitive spot and remind you
you are now single and that at this
court you can I will become a none you
can hit two birds with one stone I will
hit me hit this bird with your
stone to the Sewer dungeon please I
offer my love to you and my eternal
protection if you can prove yourself
innocent in the trial I will I will
consider my past murder come you your
potato salads thank you need a little
bunk on your head a potato salad will
you will you bunk you got five okay oh
five potato salads that is 1,000 gold
500 gold Maiden lless do you
remember thank you happen oh yes no
worries Well Done You Are Victorious
remember a diamond if you you are a
skilled Warrior thank you I appreciate
it could be a knight I am a knight I am
the knight to queen Tam Gander but see
we are of the same morals I also stand
for team Gander you are of Team Gander
all along and we are both orange don't
you think this is meant to be I have no
Revelations I cannot be with a Criminal
so you must Pro I am not a criminal I am
not also you were told by a ghost that
you killed
Isa yes better yes I have I have not
done any such thing she is still alive
she's just not uh currently with us but
she is still very much alive isai or
what is an
isekai but if you are so innocent then
you will have no problem to face trial
well under one uh condition what is the
condition that n shows up to the trial
about
you because she's
alive I will tomorrow it seems I I have
a right to a lawyer right yes you have a
right to a lawyer then narissa
ravencraft shall be my lawyer she will
but she is the victim of the crime but I
demand her to be my lawyer I think you
will have to contact the thing is this
is likeing cat or something because she
can be my lawyer if she's alive right
and if she's alive that means I haven't
killed her so then then is's no need for
uh a a court thing in the first place
glorious symbol I think we will just
have to see tomorrow and then then I
will make my decision on how I feel of
your then keep an eye if you see her
running around that would mean I have
not killed her and then she you know yes
that is true then all of this is
resolved this will be resolved and I
will deeply consider your proposition
keep in mind I will consider it keep in
mind she is known to be a witch and she
she claims she has birthed a child but
it was just about a chicken which she
cannot birth in reality a glorious
glorious tourn my your evidence into
head into my head I will keep it in mind
I would like to see both sides I do see
your side that she could not have
possibly given birth to an egg also see
my side that I am orange and then I am
team Gander she is not she is not team
Gander side of the queen that I serve
that is she serves a different Queen we
not holding hands she is just speaking
to me very
closely she is not we are not holding
hands
would you trust someone who served the
wrong Queen wait before you leave wait
Miss n before you leave I would like to
have a conversation with you and Tanashi
karia Shakira of the oranges what is
it I shall go to the gardens goodbye
thank you so much for this entertaining
event the arena thank you thank you for
joining it was nice make use of the
Arena good job BR thank you thank you
thank you all very strong Warriors thank
you
farewell for the the queen
well yes what I wanted to speak with you
about we are we all still loyal to Queen
Tam Gander much yes of course yes well I
know that you are siblings with one
princess kosaku but I believe that she
is possessed by a
stain it seems so it is true and I swore
to slay her myself if it need be oh you
you know then you know of have you seen
the corruption that has fell our our
lands I have I believe that it is her
that is doing this that she is
corrupting our
land I know
but what should we do it's a good view I
must strike her down
she I know she cannot suffer like this
yes we have to put her out of her Misery
we will have to put her down I have
exper
magical down because I that could maybe
bring her back
I will I will rest until tomorrow and I
will shall see you then okay yes fairly
well Watson oh thank you Jonathan G
congratulations on your win thank you I
appreciate it this is so
heartbreaking I will I will see you guys
what is the matter no no it's it's
nothing it's nothing it's nothing a
really want oh all right I farewell
that's fair have a great great night's
rest have a great night I will see you
yes goodbye farewell
goodbye
farewell are you are you okay Don
gathan it hurts this hurt but I respect
her I always knew that this would
potentially be an outcome so I have it
doesn't have to be like this she has
forgotten me and it is fine no our she
can remember we have our path have you
guys up considered the option that we
don't have to kill her we just have to
take off the
hat oh I have considered that but it
seems that the um the stain hat has
taken root and possessed her within she
has shown her head a few times but then
she has put it back onely after you
tried okay have you tried beheading
her what I guess that ends up in killing
her H it does end in killing her damn it
well we can behead her and try to put it
back on no no no no there there there's
a tail of magical Golden Apple that can
cure perhaps cure oh her but she refuses
to consume it I don't it's because she
knows she's possessed we her her head I
don't know we must try how will we try
what what do you propose we do I'm not
sure where to get this magical golden
apple as well I I I know I can get a
normal Golden Apple but this seems to be
a more special magical Golden Apple
maybe we can hide the golden apple in an
apple pie
yes yes oh baby we hide it and we blend
it with another meal oh yeah like a
smoothie oh that's true a special
smoovie perhaps maybe if we look at
mayhaps once the library is open we'll
find the library on how to obtain it
your hats are really that I've
heard they're large they are girthy hats
yes they're very girthy are very girthy
hats they they're they
GI brain a very large Brain full of
empathy EMP empathy hat that is why we
must put her down yeah yes yes yes yes
all right shall we convene tomorrow
maybe I can find a book tomorrow I that
will us wait so you want me to help with
this and yet you want to put me on
trial if you help us maybe this is the
trial yes this is the trial to prove
your innocence is by doing this for
Queen team by showing empathy okay I
shall take this because I am a hero and
I like to do things with honor so I
shall help for the queen Gander okay for
the queen for the queen ask FAA faart if
she has any books that relate to this
possession but be very quiet we do not
know who to trust in this Kingdom that
is true there is many safe everyone
there are very few people to be trusted
there are very few people that we can
trust yes so please please message me
through carrier pigeon you mean Discord
no yes the carrier pigeon named Discord
okay that's a weird that's a weird name
for a bird yes because he when he flies
there is quite a bit of distance in his
in his um in his wings so that's why he
is called Discord I see I pigon all
right that's making it clear thank you
yes yes well we cannot be seen together
too long otherwise people will
know yes I will go another way we will
split up I will go this way split up all
right bye farewell
farewell does this mean they're ending
their streams cuz I already streamed for
like six hour over six hours so I was
going to like go around this time anyway
uh but that's a great ending actually we
did actually a lot we did free dungeons
I did some side quests H and we did the
arena fight I got pretty far maybe if I
wouldn't have um but if I would have
healed up I wouldn't have gotten so
nervous and messed up the second fight I
was definitely uh in a disadvantage
but I'm fine with this outcome although
any other outcome would have been funny
too cuz I really like her and she's
orange and she's currently apparently
Maiden so you know it would have been
perfect but I'll get
her I'll get her for a different way for
a more honorable way I'll make her fall
in love with me um you know with honor
with proving myself to her cuz she's
currently still in doubt over me and you
know I can't force her to do anything
against her will right oh yeah but for
now she knows my my interests and my
desires and maybe that will flatter her
greatly yeah I have one day to get her
heart a she's
orange and we we fight for the same
Queen yes
might need to send a pigeon about
what about what exactly tell me help
me one day is enough yeah how fast
people have hitched
up
Discord she just needs to see that I'm
not evil
yeah no no no she just didn't seem happy
with the prospect of marriage with me
for
now she shall Swoon over my chivalry
yes I am nothing but chivalry
is was just 15
minutes she literally sends a picture of
a pigeon and a
note oh wait maybe I have seen
that I mean I've seen like several like
well-crafted notes but not from her so
I'm like I was only asking if she means
Discord because I was really not
sure
oh ah H
oh apparently there's like mockup images
of the merch things
now oh no oh I thought it was I thought
it meant real life images of these merch
items no that's not what they
meant okay never mind then well well
well well this has become a little bit
long
but uh maybe I can read super chats for
minutes I was really eventful I'm glad I
was worried about it but I was eventful
and I had
fun and I I implemented myself well
M okay so let's go to uh I don't know
what is this again ah
wonderful I shall remain
here I'm really stuck with like English
roleplay though I wish I could like
throw out all these cool big terms I
think I can do more so in German I'm
surprised like I always pick up words so
easily right but and I watch so many of
these like medieval shows how come I I'm
not able to pick up those
words the same way I pick up other words
like
demure maybe because they're too
difficult and you just can't you can't
just throw out one word it has to be
like this whole way of speaking but I
love it so much I think maybe I would do
better if before each stream I would
watch one episode of like Game of
Thrones or House of the Dragons or Lord
of the Rings or whatever because like I
swear every time I watch something like
that I I feel so epic
afterwards I feel so like I'm in the
world but it's already too late yeah the
tutos the tutors as
well hang around Liz for a bit you'll
get it no honestly I think giggy does it
the best if I'm around her I might learn
I really love the way she's doing it
she's so
[Music]
dramatic it is difficult to grasp the
difficulty she has not broken character
the entire time
amazing she's so
committed uh she should she should play
a ttrpg with somebody like with Callie
Callie would be delighted I think about
gig's role playing oh my God she's like
the
perfect yeah her like if Callie does a
ttrpg with gigy and Elizabeth and maybe
like crony oh my God that'll be
marvelous oh my God she mentioned a
ttrpg s session soon I'm probably not
part of that but but I don't think I
signed up for anything like
that so before I start like uh Tangen
thing all over
again uh let's try to get some super
chats done cuz I'm still pretty far back
uh so before I go and do my other
duties um tomorrow I shall like adjust
my streaming time to whenever geeky
starts I think because she wants me to
be uh part of the trial and stuff or
maybe I start 1 hour I'm not sure but
something around that not as early as
today for
sure
um where do I continue reading I
[Music]
wonder oh I hope M makes some progress
with her thing uh because I won't be
there in the last day so I I hope
there's something
tomorrow that's the problem like she
wants to out herself right and like
Bamboozled them but like is she planning
to do that on the final day because then
I won't be
there I'll be really
sad I want to see that
outcome I want to see it all right I
don't know where do we H which spring
I'm grown I'm a grown ass woman now very
good I am in
demand there we
[Music]
go which bring
our yeah so many character arcs it's so
it's so Twisted I saw I saw those like
uh
charts um and uh like I was uh I had a
as my cat but besides that uh I think
there wasn't much I think that it said
something about me and crony too like it
showed that I liked her
uh you the subway maps now maybe maybe
it will be a bit more difficult H
different now maybe they'll update it
and my my stance will be a little bit
different I'm yeah I'm her
protector sworn to yeah that's
right indeed I am
forever I shall not betray her just
because of her
absence that would be the act of a
coward yeah I even did one dungeon twice
so good
stuff I caught up fast really honestly
what dungeon do you guys think is the
best like my lava dance and it had a
great boss and it was just overall so
funny I feel like it probably created
the most laughs didn't
it and like the they were actually like
really challenging things with all the
fire and the lasers it was really good
right holy [\h__\h] and in contrast to that
my lore is like freaking fast food and
so like so ridiculous that even uh am in
her lore does not consider me a mythical
being me the one with the most amazing
dungeon it just doesn't match up guys it
just doesn't
match a bit the traps a bit too
much no I think it was really funny
especially I would it would probably be
even more funny if everybody who
participates is like in there for the
first time like narissa knew what she
was doing uh la la la is amazing she
just like kept on falling down with me
sometimes on purpose sometimes not on
purpose LA's a paid actor I was honestly
thinking today that we are all paid
actors in whole life
aren't we
all that one is so
funny she was such a good wing woman
yeah I it was so sweet of her to like
kind of always stay behind with me and
like fall down whenever I died and I I
felt like she was very Demir and
[Music]
mindful yeah love her I love
her yeah she's she her Giggles are so
[Music]
cute she sounds like her giggle it
doesn't sound like it but like it has
the same effect as when a baby giggles
and like she laughs at the same times as
when a baby would
giggle like something bad happens to her
and other people are laughing so for
like that's when she starts laughing
just like a baby like it falls and it's
like what the [\h__\h] how do I process
this and then it will start laughing
like if the people around the baby are
then like oh are you okay then the baby
will cry but if the people around the
baby are like then the baby will often
laugh as well
right such a genius technique
brainwashing the baby into thinking that
everything's okay that's so
cute baby's brains are too mushy to
understand okay it doesn't always work
I'm sure
but yeah babies look for
reactions oopsie super
chats red D wait one thing let me just
charge the camera cuz I think I forgot
and I'm not sure how much batteries are
in there
[Music]
where
so cute it has like a little case that
looks like a
suitcase so
[Music]
cute USBC oh my God this is the the edgy
USBC that's not called USBC
probably oh does one ch watch
this it seems to be
encased where
is where is it how do I charge this how
is this supposed to be in the
case oh what is
this this is um interesting I don't know
how this
works I don't
know H I guess it is is in the
waterproof
case how does one charge it ah maybe
here
open open open
[Music]
what how can I charge it when I don't
know how to open
it yeah I have the micro USB cable but I
I don't know where I can put it
in oh
[Music]
H I shall ask
yeah okay
ah okay well hopefully hopefully it is
already somewhat charged can I see can I
[Music]
tell
oh ah oh it's fully
charged then never mind although I have
no idea how to use this
[Music]
let's
go okay okay okay uh let's read super
chats I think I already read a few but
let's start from the beginning
uh
Cru stud Ro for a
pinky and those were all nice so
[Music]
far by a few you mean one
oh to
you it was kind of um not so hot anymore
yes today but I heard it's like getting
hotter again these days like today
tomorrow and so on we'll see I hope not
cuz now I have to go outside and film a
video
[Music]
video the natu is reducing that's what I
thought it was like really um
[Music]
bearable I'm sure in Austria it's
reducing at least compared to
here
yeah it's still like a little bit human
and hot but not too
[Music]
crazy here it got so nice at night time
yeah night time evening is nice not too
bad it's been reducing in the
States oh that's good summer man summer
can just be over summer can kiss my
ass okay I don't know what 109 means
means because that's probably Fahrenheit
and I don't speak Fahrenheit even though
that seems to be a pretty German word I
speak
Celsius I do not speak your
[Music]
language yeah I'm excited for autumn and
winter thank you Studio ra for the
pinky H
Kim you
Chong you your uh one one one
one come Sanita thank you happy
birthday well okay it's late I'm sorry
me naan coton thanks for the pinky I
have to come in here and chime in while
on my break that uh that forehead and
freckles T is super cute that's all
oh was that like the stream before or
so thank you thank you forehead and
freckles
t
h that is a reality I can give you in my
fever knite outfit only for
now it was quite cute huh R so free
thanks for the pinky this mom paycheck
is in my is in memory of our lost oi
small chef hat May her rest in may she
rest in peace in W's closet well the
small chef hat has become really big and
is now being worn by a certain Guild in
our Minecraft
Adventures why am I not in that Guild
you may wonder if they have that hat
maybe we just don't belong together guys
maybe we're just not meant to be me and
that
hat you yeah ever thought about
that if if I was meant to be an Amber
corn maybe I'm not supposed to wear that
hat but and doule Jones thanks for the
pinky I would like to express my full
support for what Nathan cotton has
stated
for paying respects to the uh Che chef
hat well then I guess all your money
goes as donations to that Guild that I
forgot its name Cerulean probably
Cerulean
[Music]
right you should be donating your money
to
ambercoin bro we're already a small
Guild with less earnings than other
guilds because we are small and inactive
okay you have to help us out
guys Kazu
D you are thank you for the red super
chat hi there wa it's my birthday today
oh and I just want to say it's been
amazing for years in kfp I started
watching you when I was 24 and now I'm
going to be 28 oh almost in demand so
it's been quite an experience and I
thank you for keeping it interesting
good luck in the spelling be ah thank
you
you thank you sh well thank you first of
all for being part of kfb for so long
and second of all happy
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday in your shoe happy birthday in
your pants too happy birthday to
you yeah and I think I did pretty
decently in the spelling me sorry for
being so late on the birthday message
though m
kisses to make up for it they're not
ancient okay maybe a little bit cuz this
was yeah it's over a month ago but okay
I'm trying my best y'all I'm trying my
best the speech
[Music]
Dan
Kim
maybe three times
H oh you watched the Fire Emblem free
hous stream so long ago oh my God
come
[Music]
just
or the gamer Austin y d unknown D
skeptical Panda D ghost of mint DS of
fancy dun and death Rex thank you very
much
pineapple pineapple I've been eating
like pineapples and Kiwis like for
breakfast almost every day or like even
if it's not for breakfast like for lunch
as a snack or so in between because they
have all these cut fruits in the
convenience stores and you know what's
weird so there's like three main
convenience stores here one's family mod
one is is lawon and one is
7-Eleven
and
um the other day I bought
pineapples from Lawson I think and then
I didn't eat it immediately they're in
like this plastic
package and
then I like put it in my fridge and then
the next day when I open it I see that
the plastic package is like a bag it has
like kind of B
up like a
balloon and when I open it and I tasted
the pineapples they tasted a little bit
off to me and they they were like
carbonated so I'm like
M this is so weird like did they go bad
what the [\h__\h] they didn't taste like
rotten though and their color was still
perfectly Yellow Nice
yellow and they shouldn't have expired
yet but then I buy them again and they
did the same thing again like
twice but they never do that when I buy
them at 7-Eleven like they have like
really similar products these
convenience stores
sometimes they have very similar
products must have been like a bad batch
or so I don't know so now I'm like okay
I'm I'm I'm just going to buy my
pineapples elsewhere now my pineapple
business I'm taking it elsewhere
pineapple and then I was thinking to
myself H carbonated pineapple it's like
when you put iris's song carbonated love
was it together with pineapple and make
a remix out of it and I honestly think
that would sound really
good and that makes that makes
carbonated
pineapple somebody do it get to it
[Music]
cooking it inspired me it may not have
tasted very well but it's it inspired me
so yeah sounds interesting
[Music]
right trust
me mash up yeah let's
go I'm hungry I have a little another
like piece of my breakfast cuz I had a
dut for breakfast and I have
little
thing
here how small is
it oh cute
oh interesting what is this a
paper oh wow this is very
moist
oh oh that's not what I
expected h a little
cake m
[Music]
interesting not
bad could be better but not
[Music]
bad what but
maybe I should eat it off
[Music]
stream I'm actually meeting
with assistant manager
Chan but she has not been
replying is she
okay she's assisting me in my endeavors
[Music]
yeah I'm going to end soon guess I'll
just end
[Music]
now um
okay censored assistant manager hands
again no no no um it will be my hands
cuz I'll be wearing gloves and I'm
mounting the camera on my body so um cow
carat will not have to do as much uh
like censoring so to
say h it would look
weird
but it will be easier for
editing well my hands don't have to be
censored but I guess every like person
that is in the video will have to be
censored that'll be fun
yeah and it'll be a little bit hot I
guess when I'm wearing gloves
[Music]
outside manager Chan yeah this assistant
manager Chan is different from previous
assistant manager CHS because so you
know JMA is like manager of the
managers and she's managing me as her
only child but recently you know every
once in a while we get a new manager and
then somehow it often overlaps with me
being in Japan and being in the middle
of a big project so then the assistant
manager will be kind of like trained
through
me like which is actually perfect
training because it's just always a lot
of things to do and it also takes off a
little bit of work off with
jenma and so like I always meet the new
managers and now I've been working with
one of this these new
managers and she's really sweet really
cute and we we we get along and now I'm
making her help
me but she might just like
become one of my managers for long term
because jenma has said she's like you
know generally very overloaded and she
wants assistant manager John to kind of
take over mostly and I was like what are
you are you abandoning me we have this
promise between us you can't do this to
me I was like really dramatic and she
was like no no I'm not letting you go
and I'm like but like how much percent
do you want her to take over me and and
and then she was like like and I was
like what how much like 80 and she's
like yeah 80 and I'm like what you'd
only be like doing stuff with me
20% bro you can't do this to me I don't
know I'm I I'm sad
but like 80% is like pretty much
abandoning me
oh
Jamba I was like okay well maybe maybe
you you you're going to like take me
back once it's less busy and then you
don't maybe not 80% but like 5050 or so
and she's
like doubtful of
it Jemma please JMA no no JMA but it's
okay I'll be a good Wawa and I'll I'll
accept my fate
[Music]
you had a pack well we still have the
Pack she says the pack still um is
like there happy birthday Arie oh my
God happy
birthday for now I shall say this and
more later
at least make it 69 hey
no I don't like
[Music]
that so yeah um new manager Chanel I
have to think of a name for her I'll
check with her what name she would like
to
have I'm not
sure I I'll I'll I'll check with her
don't forget
design oh yeah well I don't know I I I
don't think we need like designs for
every manager because that will be like
a million managers
now replace
ma no she's so funny though because like
she gets so
lost she's quite pko too in terms of
like
directions and
yeah finding the right
way she's pretty PA
PMA I don't know if she would appreciate
that having that as her name then she'll
never get rid of it no don't call her
upon my head no no no no no yeah let's
run it by her first
[Music]
she's cute though and I like her fashion
sense we have some very fashionable
[Music]
managers let's get to know her better
first I feel like I know her quite well
[Music]
already yeah she also came with us to
America which I'm sure was already like
a great adventure considering she was
still very
new to the
company like not not every manager
joined us but a
[Music]
couple okay so I'll go now I'll see you
tomorrow for more Minecraft
uh tomorrow will be the last Minecraft
stream for me so apparently we're having
a trial uh but not not really no the
trial is taking the hat off of beu and
and then I don't know what else it will
surely all like resolve itself or create
more
drama
around like whatever time gigy will
stream or maybe plus minus more like
minus an
hour drama craft
yeah I hope I can wait yeah perhaps I
may marry maybe we will have another
happy couple on the server
after after that but I will I be Maiden
l no I will be the opposite of mless and
then when I marry her however I feel
like maybe I have to put down salt and
be fendly no my my night duties I cannot
fulfill them anymore I cannot be I can
not be the Queen's guard
[Music]
anymore so I guess
I'll I guess I'll work at a fast food
restaurant
works works out yeah I have a night
quote and I will follow
it but for my fast food restaurant I
will support the queen
nonetheless yeah and full circle
[Music]
uh yeah I mean apparently I own one I
just uh I'm I'm not going to have time
to build it so I'm just going to take
over Callie's to no
so I'll tell her I'll tell her I I'm
your boss
now the Lord tells us
so she cannot say
no I don't want to take it away from her
only if she finds it funny but I
wouldn't take it away from her I just on
on the scriptures I would be the boss
but she would still be operating
everything just like with kfp I'm just
the boss on the scriptures I'm not I'm
not working
there I'll Fe us in
[Music]