[Music]
so
my
[Music]
hello
i was doing some work
that had to be done
before midnight
japanese time
i think i got cat hairs in my
eyelashes
yeah
and my room is so hot i think
yeah i i kind of got it done but i don't
i don't really know what i was doing so
it was a bit uh confusing so
that's why
that's why i didn't know how to do it
um
[Laughter]
and
yeah
[\h__\h]
my eyes
[Music]
mascara is like a trap for cat hairs if
i put on mascara
the
chance of me getting cat hairs in my
eyes is
even higher than usual
oh maybe should not have necessarily
face planted my cat right before the
stream but she was
she was lying on my bed like a snail
and it was just offering herself to me
so
what can i do what can what can i do oh
my eyes okay i think i think i think
i think we're good
ah
yeah like a snail when they're like
curled up like a snail it's so cute
i had no choice that's right yeah thank
you for understanding
daily fluff tacks
uh
how was the day um i was i was at the
dentist today before also before the
stream
and um
i mean nothing big but like
it was a little tiny bit of drilling
and
um it's not like it still hurts but i
feel like i got something like i don't
know imaginary
um
um memory
pain maybe it's called phantom pain
like like i i i um
the nerves
are like telling me that something
happened there
and
yeah
only a little bit though it was so tiny
uh but yeah
the doctor was like you want some uh uh
of that sweet sweet sleepy stuff and i
was like no
no it's just a little bit right we
just
i wanted to i want to be strong
i wanted to be strong anesthesia oh yeah
i am and i was like no
no i can do it without no one can do it
about
it was just a little bit
[Laughter]
just a little bit
[Music]
um strong verb yes yes i've been through
so much pain in my life that this is
just a little small thing
edgy but it's the truth
um
so
yeah thank you for waiting everybody
it should be okay
um we're gonna play starship titanic
today which is an old game that my mom
uh used to play
and i remember vaguely watching her
and maybe also trying it but i'm not
saying that all of that happened in 1998
when the game came out okay it was
probably after 2000
sometime after 2000
or yeah
and
yeah i doubt that i was playing that in
1998.
um but the game in theory came out in
one of the games that my mom liked um
it's a riddle game and it's retro can we
call it retro i was feeling um you know
i was thinking what outfit to wear and
maybe
maybe this outfit can have a retro vibe
if you want it to be
i thought that was my fault that was the
thought behind choosing this outfit
today
um i think i think it can look retro
um
my outfit and the game is retro yeah
finally i can call a game retro on my
channel
uh this game is retro yeah it's by a
famous person called douglas adams who
is unfortunately not on this world
anymore um but
douglas adams is also very well known
for uh
something called hitchhiking to the
galaxy or something like that
uh i think i only remember the the
german title uh hitchhiker's guide to
the galaxy or something like that
hitchhiker's guide yes yes yes yes i
think you guys know that one better
someone told me that this is actually a
spin-off
to that story to the hitchhiker's guide
of the galaxy story so maybe that um i
know most of you probably don't know the
game i'll be playing today so i thought
maybe you know maybe that uh kind of
makes you
feel more interested and familiar in it
because i think a lot of people know the
hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy um it's
like yeah in the same universe
yeah and
it is
some people asked me before and also my
mom if i planned to stream this on this
day on purpose because of a certain rms
titanic no
it was not on purpose
a certain ship with the same name sank
today uh many years ago but that was not
planned
oh wait is the hitchhiker's guide to the
galaxy
where the number 42 came from
is that where that whole thing came i
know it's like a perfect number um i
know that meme i mean
right
now we're talking okay okay so um this
game uh
is on steam
and i got permissions from the
publishers for the steam version
um
now i tested it a little bit but
obviously i can't test out the whole
game so there's a chance
uh that
we may
have like i don't know issues
somewhere
like midway through or in the end or so
and in that case well can't help it um
but somebody in the audience tested it i
think at least until one hour in and it
was fine
so
yeah
uh we're gonna play it on steam
and we'll see how far we go supposedly
supposedly
it's a short game and i could finish it
in like four hours but it's also it has
some uh
very confusing riddles
so
i'm my mom sent me a guide
because i would probably get stuck a lot
and today
in this game i won't really be able to
get help from you will i because i don't
who is there anyone here who played the
game
and knows like played it recently so
they know
how to help me
i'm guessing no
no no yes you would know how to help
really
i made this game [\h__\h]
don't believe it
ah no no i played the game like a decade
ago
25 years ago oh but it's cool there are
some people who at least played it um
for me overall it is it feels nostalgic
um but i don't remember it at all
i mean i remember some jokes i remember
something with a robot wanting chicken
i think
i think there was a robot who wanted
chicken and and then the robot always
was like chicken or something like that
so i hope we meet that robot
oh
i think
oh no that's a parrot who wanted chicken
ah when what was with the robot there
was a robot too and oh my god the
website that my mom sent me looks very
much like a really old website
oh
how old is this
this looks so old do you guys want to
see it like the background is obviously
made in the resolution that
uh is not our modern resolution
[Laughter]
you want to see it maybe you guys maybe
you guys can also follow the guide if
you want um on the side
uh
to also maybe help me um
i wanna finish it today
look i posted the link
i posted the link
it looks very old
[Music]
know
the menu
[Laughter]
what is that menu oh my god nice website
right
this is ancient
okay
let me open the game the game opens in
full screen uh i don't see i don't know
an option to change it into window and
uh
sukashi uh the start i don't
i don't even know if it has auto safe if
it has autosave then we might just stop
from the beginning i don't know let's
just get started let's get started
uh let's go
okay okay
so wait now i have it launched in full
let me get out of the window please
let me
oh no
no wait
i
i can't go to the my other screen
how do i uh
i can't go to the screen where i have
obs
uh i i did push windows button but the
mouse won't let me outside of this one
screen
oh i'll tab i'll tab i'll tab i'll tab
no i won't let me go
alt enter ah i'll enter thank you
okay no show
um
i won't capture it until i open it again
will it
oh sh
it's so small it's so small how do i
now it's like it's like ah
what is this it's a window now oh my god
it's a window but it's like so small and
it won't capture it capture it obs come
on you know you can do it
it's such an awkward window right now
capture that [\h__\h]
told you to capture it
[Music]
it
transform
reset transform no
um
[Music]
this is the first puzzle
when we'll figure it out just sometimes
sometimes uh obs like when i choose a
new window to capture it just takes its
time maybe i should capture it in
not in game capture but window capture
maybe
yeah that
works there you go
that works
all right let me cut this this is
exactly how it looks for me like um
for some reason once i tabbed out it has
this black
uh sides
but hey it's it is a 3d game from 1998
3d like it's made out of 3d objects but
it is point and click i like point and
click
games hi okay
oh beautiful oh my god is that 16 to
nine
am i seeing a 16 to nine resolution
almost
no way
also sometimes something i'm doing my
stream uh
my brother will ring my doorbell
uh to pick something up
so
i will i will um dan my brother is
driving to my mom's place i will join
tomorrow and i found some nice old
furniture in our um garbage room
that someone threw away but it still
looked perfectly fine so i took a photo
and sent it to my mom and i was like mom
do you need this and she was like yes
yes yes yes yes yes please put it into
your apartment
so i grabbed everything i could and um
i'll put it up to my my place
and my brother is going to drive it to
my mom's place and i'm going to join
tomorrow so yeah anyway they're going to
pick that up so anyway
are you hearing a beautiful
sophisticated bgm
you're going to go
no he's not going to say hi nah
embarrassing hazukashi
yeah actually there was a table there
too that i thought could be useful but
um i was like i can't carry this up
right now so one day later i went back
there and it was already gone but the
rest was still there the table was was
popular
ah
i think you guys can hear it
all right so we start uh swoosh
swoosh
[Music]
uh this is this is beautiful i think
my mom used to have a pc like this with
a with a cdk swingy on the pc there this
is actually
in my opinion this is pretty modern
because the fact that there's a pc in
the monitor that's like that's like one
of those apple macs isn't it
that's pretty
dope like all in one product
yeah
so now we're gonna open this up
and put in this titanic oh yeah i have
to drag it
cd is this cd
it's just cd right
loading
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
the game is making my house crash
[\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] is that
oh my god
nice cutscene
aliens are coming to abduct me
oh no
oh dear
oh yeah
oh dear oh dear we're darren dean
oh dear there
as you go thank you he's british
are you an alien
oh you're a robot
i forgot what i was going to say it was
oh yes where's your script my name is
fentable i am the doorbot serving on
this the maiden voyage of the starship
titanic
possibly roll the credits
go wrong oh you can see the ship this
thing you see behind me well we've had
where are you pupils
sometimes he's done pupils disappear to
the paint work i think luckily your
house was quite there are no subtitles
but don't worry later they will have a
text box we need you urgently
will you help
yes hello
yes help yes hello yes
oh silly man strange deluded benighted
me you'll need your personal electronic
thing here we go we call it a pet
yeah there we go see complicated but
wait you don't see it
all you need to do oh i cut that part oh
that's what and that's why that's why
that's why there was a black thingy
no more 16 to nine no more 16 to nine
ah you have pretty cool anna for the
game of all yeah this is how it's
supposed to be
so i love this i'm afraid we don't have
time to fool around no an odd way to
spell it but that will do fine
well maybe you will but let's get you on
board anyway
just type not now not now we've got to
get you on board okay
i can't tap now they only let me type
when when i am
when i am asked a question
unbelievable you should take this trying
to silence me
uh a picture yeah yeah okay they want me
to take this picture with me now if good
the way this trip is going it may be the
last time you'll ever see that
particular view come on
it's kind of weird like he cuts off uh
but uh and talks in a new sentence but
he doesn't uh show it in the text box
yet
but yeah gun body everybody
[Laughter]
whoa
i'm being abducted carefree helpful
help me it's a maiden voyage you see
with the ship maiden voyage lost its
mind am i the maiden
including me
though i do have my lucid moments
i only wish i knew if this was one of
them
things are going from bad to worse i
can't even find the buttons now can you
help me buttons aren't here
terribly sorry it's my cell point
settings you see well i don't suppose
you do see but it is my sell point
settings anyway
well wait a second i want to fix this
screen somehow
um
is this better
[Music]
mind generally marginally better too
bright on the side oh you don't want it
you want this
move chat above my why would i do that
can it be stretched
i mean yes but it's gonna look like [\h__\h]
uh put chat on the side
okay let me try to rearrange
[Music]
chat
you can go
you can go here for today
uh
let me change your resolution chat
lift
with the
height
how about this
i'll put you here maybe
and
no
no that makes no sense
105.
[Music]
and then
i take this and this
[Music]
well i'll take this
and i'll take
this
[Music]
and uh
we don't need the hashtags
i'll put mice well that wait wait i'm
gonna do this and then i put myself
here
oh man these old graphics
forcing me to change things and we use
we like to think the way the things are
but they're forcing me okay how about
this
is my is my advertisement
bothering you
i hope not it ha it has to be there
[Applause]
lobby
going up human being isn't it yes well
of course one's her mixed reports
i just hope that you can sort out these
problems because none of us can
we're all robots you see and what's
happened is that the ship's central
intelligence has been lobotomized
sabotaged if you ask me and it's left us
all unable to function properly and you
may find that we're all a little
i know that i am so it's all going to be
up to you
as soon as we reach the embarkation
lobby press the button on the plinth and
we'll be on our way
then go and see marcinta she's the desk
bot and a bit of a dragon when her
setting the wrong she'll check you in
all i've managed to secure for you is a
super galactic traveler classroom but
i'm sure
you can always ask my cinta for an
upgrade but be ready to duck
you'll meet chris when are you gonna
stop talking and show me the text it's
so hard to follow about that once you've
settled in and made yourself comfortable
you'll be able to get on with working
out what's gone wrong and fixing it
oh my god
it's a [\h__\h] book
embarkation
here we are i think i don't see my mouse
anymore i'm sure that nobody's in
control i'd better go down again to
secure things but i'll be back a bit
later to help you if i can
i hope you understood most of that
i understood nothing good luck now good
luck don't forget to press the button
which button
i already press the button all right
welcome are we in space now i think
we're in space now
we're gonna go left all right oh no
already have to make decisions think i
think rat straight let's go to the uh
check in
please do not ring this bell again
that's a challenge not yet not yet
not yet really
you sure
not yet not yet okay maybe not yet
um ah what about what about this oh this
is the monkey
i remember this monkey the succubus
and the dark is not recommended oh okay
okay
okay what about what about this
welcome to the starship titanic please
press the button for opening credits
opening
credits okay
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
douglas adams
whoa
starship titanic
thank you everybody for watching today
wow
i see the pixels
wow that's a cool spaceship design
though
[Music]
finally i made banana milk before the
stream i'm so proud i added some vanilla
ice cream and some cinnamon and cinnamon
some cinnamon and some
so noisy
i can't hear myself and some vanilla
extract
yeah
and milk obviously and banana
banana milk
okay beautiful can i check in now
yeah
hello lamp there's a this is
number uh one to the most glamorous
galactic cruise ship experience in the
world space time continuum the starship
titanic the ship that cannot possibly go
wrong
[Music]
my name's drewbish
hello i am the desk bot oh that's fine
do you have a reservation
no i don't know you abducted me and no i
thought not
but i see that fentanyl thinks we should
take you on board
huh soft-hearted fool can't touch you i
don't see that you're going to be any
help
as far as i'm concerned you're just a
freeloader
oh well we're going to get you checked
in you crashed into my house like in the
morning continental or the full porky
cook
porky continental breakfast place choice
newspaper
the baronton bugle no trumpet no
saxophone no kazoo no i don't read
witch
the baronton bugle the trumpet saxophone
kazoo
no okay how do you like your room with a
view
uh
yes okay corner or balcony
ball come on only you know
corner or balcony
balcony then in balcony it is all the
corner rooms are usually like a tiny bit
bigger than the other rooms are good
choice bed even in the same category
royal presidential despotic
royale
king's eyes queen size prince princess
princess plus
when are these things
princess
good choice fish what's a princess [\h__\h]
maybe it was like one of those nice
fabrics on top of your uh on top of your
bed fish no good
well you certainly won't like the room
you've got that you've been assigned to
super galactic traveler class elevator
one floor 38 room two and don't come
whining to me for upgrades because you
won't get one okay craig
don't worry not one of those people not
one of those hotel guests
hi i'm craig hi craig spellbot today i
like you craig i see you're not carrying
any luggage that's great i can take a
little time my house is my luggage do
you know i see your super galactic
trailer now bring my house so i guess
you can find your own way to your room
the door's over there the elevators
round someplace relax stay cool enjoy
he's nice i like him
wait do i follow you oh
no i think this this is the elevator
we regret to announce that the ship is
hurtling out of control through
hyperspace well great passengers with
insurance queries well
well where was the elevator again i
think uh there no wait i can't go oh
on it
or is that the elevator
pirate
oh there's a bleeding maiden voyage more
like a bleeding disaster if you ask me
whoa what do we hate now what do we hit
now
oh bang oh there we go again it's
something else now have we
what do you expect of a ship's got no
brain
let's not let's not talk to him now
then buster missing you already i don't
think ha ha
cheery vitamin buster uh that's what he
would say
uh is that the power that wants chicken
i don't recall it like that okay i don't
really know man oh what is this oh my
god now where is the elevator is this
the elevator no that's not the elevator
what the [\h__\h] is this
oh my god
whoa
am i falling what's happening
i think this is the end game
hello
didn't i see you in the lobby
ah
best character
what did you say
stop fiddling with me
stop feeling with me
get out of here okay sorry i'll see you
eventually probably
i will be led to you probably now can i
go back please i i'm lost i didn't find
the elevators probably it was probably
pretty easy
it wait how
oh what the [\h__\h] is that
i remember this dude
i don't know
that's that's a human body what are you
doing with that
how to get to elevator
how
how to get back
here no no no no
i'm stuck forever
what about this
no
passengers of your class are not
permitted in this area
wow discrimination i see all right oh
danger unbelievably high voltage don't
use the serviceable parts inside that
sounds sus to me wait can i take some
parts
you really shouldn't have opened the
first inspection plate this is not
really not only fantastically dangerous
but you are avoiding your
warranty i think i should open this
don't say you weren't worn
oh
chicken take
the take
play around with it
wonderful
can i put this in here oh
no
i wonder if i can have a full inventory
because then in that case maybe we can
leave it here
sorry sorry for opening you i'm leaving
i'm leaving there are no other safes
yeah i don't know i don't think so i
don't think there are ah this here this
here's the sign for saving
was this
oh login
sorry no i don't have any of that yet
i'm not supposed to be here i just don't
know how to get back
huh
[\h__\h]
ah
where did i even come from i don't know
anymore
i found it
i was just playing around i was just
playing with you guys just wanted to
give you a little bit of a tour of my
space ship
i'm the only passenger so that means
it's my spaceship
that looks like an elevator
no
uh
let me leave please okay uh where is the
[\h__\h] elevator
uh uh where am i
oh god the controls are just pointy
clicky and i'm still
not having
easy time here maybe this is one of the
elevators
or no no i mean i mean i mean
here here
here here this one no
and what do i know
is this not an elevator
and that's
going down oh
wait i can go back to my home
are we going back home now
at least we're back at the lobby
that is an elevator but that is uh like
a different kind of element
external axis
bottom we're no we're not going home
we're just at the bottom of the starship
i guess
oh
there's another one of those
suck your bus
you feel rotten my dear
i'm sorry i don't have any bananas i
have a banana milkshake but i drank it
all
[Music]
in case it crashes it shouldn't crash
though
oh okay
okay let's just act as if this all
didn't happen
um
i
totally know where to go
probably just straight ahead no that's
where we went before
shut up
shut up you stupid parrot okay
uh it must be
no
it must be
it what the [\h__\h]
it must be here and then here and in
here and then here and then here and in
here and then
um maybe here
no
maybe um
maybe here no
maybe
here
no
oh
the pellerator what's a power raider i
can call the pale right there
is the pedal right in the elevator
what is that
what is this
no spitting
no
spitting it's not spinning at anything
parallel elevated that's a cool
wait how do i get out
what
wait can i
you're already at your chosen
destination
and how do i am bye okay
uh this is a great start i can't find
this stupid elevator mommy
let me see maybe maybe the guide can
help me where's my room look at your
super galactic travel card and go to the
appropriate elevator at the top of the
well there are four elevators there
chose the one that you're assigned
the top of the well
what is the well
what is what is maybe maybe ah no this
is not the one isn't the well something
with water
opposite of the pellery that yeah i
think it is somewhere in this hall so
maybe
um but that's
impellerator
ah
huh now we already we're here
that's not it
i went this is the [\h__\h] how the [\h__\h]
am i supposed to know that this is the
[\h__\h] elevator this doesn't look like
an elevator
outside of elevated floor wait how do i
know which is my elevator
um did they say which elevator
[Music]
uh elevator there's there's an elevator
around some place
elevator one this is elevator four
this is elevator
free
oh are they on the other side
i suppose so another little four and
three right here and then
oopsie
here we have one probably okay
calling
okay the first big hurdle
good day to you sir
thing this is so creepy better than some
of the days we've been having recently
indeed mild trouble is quite cleared up
so that it will be a pleasure to attend
to your vertical transportation
requirements
isn't this creepy
i think i remember him kind of in a
depressing way
this dude
madame or thing
i'm going to really wait
uh-huh okay
well ah that came out can i choose
myself where i'm going um
wait what do i have to tell you
let's go not today thanks
what
i need to go somewhere
[Music]
my room please it would be my pleasure
what chet
how did you
[Music]
brad
thank you red
you had the magic words
wow
oh this music
hey visual flaws huh i remember this
this is so sad
this music is so sad
but i like it
all right
uh
i love this music too
where was my room again
where did they say it
um floor 38 room two
[Music]
um
do i put this in here no what is this
what was it i forgot
already [\h__\h]
we're in one word
what was the room
damn it the floor for room two really
that was it
shift click edit congratulations you may
have already won an upgrade
turn to channel 3 for details
[Music]
they want me to use the tv but in order
to use the tv
i need to i think open up certain things
in a certain way to make them work
um i think
but
let me try to figure this out deploy
floral enhancement how do i
ah i know i know
i know i know i know
um
okay uh
let's say for example
[Music]
we start with this
this is a
fully recumbent relaxation device
this goes
wait oh oh that can't open because this
is open
what if i open
what
no it doesn't
open at all what if i just open the tv
it doesn't open
[Music]
opens looking fancy
what about a toilet the toilet won't
open
uh
yeah this is a riddle
ah
this is good ah and then if i have this
out
then
uh
let me put this back in don't need that
probably
we open this and it becomes a table
smart was that on the phone no it's me
[Music]
[Applause]
what else do i need
maybe a floral arrangement
can i watch the tv please the bed will
not currently support your weight where
i'm working on this problem but i'm not
okay maybe something underneath to help
me support my weights
[Music]
what do you want from me how about the
toilet comfort workstation it says yes
totally that is comfortable perfect
toilet like this
what did i do oh wait what was this
i could use cleansing recept
where would this go maybe no toilet oh
wait what is this
come on come on are we not happy with
this yes we are
[Music]
smart
watch
[Music]
now
i thought you wanted me to watch tv when
oh wait can i also put this somewhere
let me go back
i want to go back into my room i like my
room
can i put my my picture somewhere
maybe no
oh oh
i thought watch
watch
[Music]
what you want
i want to watch tv in my room how could
i do that use your pets to make it
happen choose this order
oh there's an order
no okay it should just work if i have
the right um uh
the right
order of items
um
i don't want to cheat
but i feel like ah what about this
what about now
oh
it was not enough
i have the tv on your pet bar what
the tv on my pet bar
ah
you mean something that
nothing else will come out of here no
um
what is a pet bar again
pet is my room or something like that
[Music]
okay
i don't know the channel needs to change
oh
uh do i have to make that happen
was i not supposed to like put this in
somewhere
[Music]
why do i always go outside
no no
no no how do i how do i go back without
going outside
[Applause]
this is gonna be a long day
uh the user interface pet bar
wait what
when
open the drawer i can't it just goes up
now i go outside
lie down first how would i like that you
don't know what you're talking about
click draw i'm clicking the drawer
i clicked
i clicked and draw
it's not a game for zoomer okay
i made me destroy it
do i need this
do you want me to put this here
no
can i watch the tv now
okay
should i reset everything
let's use the
let's use the walkthrough
[Music]
maybe
the deployed and personal maintenance
hub yeah that's like what the [\h__\h] even
is that personal maintenance
hub can i reset everything
go back
[Music]
no that can't go first this has to go
back that's the relaxation device
that is also relaxation device
uh
this is this is the deploy the
maintenance yeah okay now we have that
yeah yeah okay
uh and uh
this
no
first
[Music]
no what is this
this one this one and then this one
all right we're back to
we're back to zero guys
is this eleanor
wait so we start
we start with
this
horizontal work surface
and probably you know this one right
the horizontal storage component yes i
mean i had a pride i just don't know
there's one one detail we're missing
the fully recumbent relaxation device
uh
this one
no we need first something
[Music]
else huh
it's not working
the guy is lying to me where's the
moment storage compartment
wait no
wait there's two different ones there's
inflating and deploying okay
and no problem
no problem okay all right there we go
and then we'll finally operate the
visual entertainment device isn't that
exactly what we did
huh is the order important
[Music]
did i always have this option
nah i didn't always have
this option
[Music]
no
and but now what
huh
there's nothing on the tv
channel titanic
there's currently nothing available for
your viewing pleasure on this channel
can i put um
this in
channel 3.
you guys are looking at the guide aren't
ya
ah
am i switching oh
what is this
[Music]
uh
five
that's channel five it shows us the
elevator 27 remember that guys 27
[Music]
what is this oh
isn't that the pattern of my room
no it's not
remember this guys
two in the middle at the top
uh third row
left
for free
second last row middle note
left and right yes and bottom row
first and and third remember this
edit your pattern and save it mod i can
edit it ah shift click that's what they
mean oh
oh am i supposed do i get an upgrade if
i do this
oh are we actually doing something right
[Music]
nowhere you likely want to go
uh
[Music]
i should
should be correct now
how do i activate it
upside down
ah it couldn't be that easy right nah
yeah yeah upside down
really
[Music]
what
i am confused
[Laughter]
is it also mirage or just upside down
is it mirrored
[Music]
this
no but that's mirrored though why am i
trying to mirror it what about this
[Music]
it's just upside down
upside down always mirrors
okay true maybe
so
this goes here
something changed here first first class
floor seven
uh just not even
oh oh this just changes the elevator
oh
wait
this is not quite it though
here
elevator two room three first class
or seven
[Music]
this is correct
i think it is okay what now
i did it now
[Music]
yeah
what did i do
did i do it
but it didn't change
[Music]
now drag it into the box and save it
drag it into the box
[Music]
oh huh
doesn't
just like
[Music]
wait no it changed
i think it was
um
like this
no i don't remember
[Music]
can i not watch tv unless i do the whole
thing again
huh ah
here we go
57 channels and nothing to watch never
watch it what's the brain no chickens
did you hear that the parent was talking
to you guys
sgt
class remember that
[Music]
whatever sgt class is
i mean that's not it
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh i am in the sgt class
ah super good like to travel okay so
please tell me please tell me this is
okay
how do i how do i get there
how do i get there
[Music]
how do i uh
um guide
no
no guide
guide no
uh
elevator to
go to channel three back to yeah do i
have to tell the elevator guy where i
want to go wait wait
wait it says i need to go to elevator
too okay good good good
uh
let me let me enter
let me enter call
morning or whatever
sup
i don't suppose you were ever a military
man military woman
thing
i'll tell him to go here let's keep it
simple it goes up all goes down
could dance on the table in the ncaa's
miss rose's rules i always say
rose's rules
rules
i thought he was saying roses rose rose
okay he won't take me
hmm he doesn't want to take me
it has to be the right that's not that
is the right element but some people say
go to channel three okay
[Music]
i don't understand what these channels
are what numbers are they
five this is five right okay 27
and then we go to
nine probably
maybe i don't know
one super galactic traveler this could
be your luck like a lucky day
yes you may already have won an upgrade
to second class and a whole new world of
luxury you may collect your
complimentary in-flight magazine from
the succubus in your sgt lobby if the
coupon on page two has lucky number
three five two seven nine on it 35 279
just one step away from a travel
experience most bipeds can only dream
about
take the magazine to the embarkation
lobby and our helpful desk staff will
delight in upgrading you
what that was so much and so i go to
this thingy he gives me a magazine and
with the magazine i go somewhere else
i think
uh a robot son
where uh oh
are you here
is this you
hello hello
come
thank you
i take
magazine thank you get out of here okay
i'm getting out of here and with that i
think we go to the lobby
are we going to the lobby
morning sir i was like
you've
[Music]
probably not a distinguished sir like
yourself but it's no joke and one of the
things is when your wobs is gone and
your goals is gone you need a bit of a
helping hand when it comes to things
like vertical transportation
you need to be told which floor you're
going to
you have heard your wobs go on yes sir
your wobs and your gorms
probably not a distinguished sir like
yourself but it's no joke and one of the
things is when your wobs is gone and
your goals is gone you need a bit of a
helping hand when it comes to things
like vertical transportation you need to
be told which well we will do it so god
willing and i'm not one to make the fuss
ask anyone he's nobody want to make a
fuss any of the lads would say no
nobby fuschia
not on stoical type knobby even when
he's in agony which i am so what
what the [\h__\h] are you talking about from
here you can walk to your requested
destination oh thank you very much
we're back here oh that looks like a big
version of the item uh that the thingy
spit out wait what are we doing with the
magazine now we're going to the
reception
oh no not entering pirate space
bye bye
chicken on
[Music]
scary music also what is this pen should
i remember this pattern
should i remember
these patterns
maybe i should remember these patterns
let me remember these patterns no it's
the pattern i have on here right now
but i don't have it saved i'll save it
it's the invocation lobby
hold on
hello have a magazine and an upgrade
please greetings biped
uh
upgrade please did you get the lucky
number
show me your magazine
yes
i have lucky number five four seven two
nine o'clock it's very bad for passenger
discipline oh very well let me see i've
assigned you to a second class state
room room one floor 26 what about first
class by elevator one
don't get drunk in the bar don't elevate
the water positions don't fiddle with
the pellerator
and if you go up to the promenade deck
[Laughter]
sorry i didn't let you finish what was
that what were you saying
i'm so sorry elevator one no i'm on the
wrong side
but okay we got an upgrade
we just built our whole room and now
you're telling me i need to leave it
it's useless now
no
elevator
element there we go
okay call
uh
[\h__\h] what floor i don't know where you
want to go not having the gift of third
sight but i have to tell you my office
so up will be a bit of a problem and
seoul down just so as you understand
floor 26 i got it
uh floor
26 please
well
we'll do it sir god willing you know not
one to make the fuss ask anyone he's
nobody want to make a fuss oh my god
would say no nobby fuss here is your
floor they they really needed um
visitors i think he really wanted to
talk
oh
it's looking nice
wait what room number i did urgently
what
give me a break will ya oh no not you
sorry oh my god i didn't want to disturb
you
uh i just want to know what my room
number was i have a short time memory i
can only remember so many things room
one never mind bye bye
[Music]
uh room one maybe over
there
[Music]
oh
this is my room
wait what i didn't see the number
why does it say it
oh it doesn't say this is my room i
think it's my room otherwise i probably
wouldn't be able to enter mmm snacks
oh
i hate some snacks look at the sky that
must be fake
why why do i see a sky aren't we in
space
we're starting nuts
what do we have here
now i want those snacks i want those
snacks
[Applause]
and there's some more snacks oh m m's
okay
uh we have a robot in here as well
apparently
but i think they want us to maybe
i don't know lay on the bed no
but watch tv
oh i guess i'll talk to you hello
give me what you got no okay if i can't
suck it
or blow it it's a tv don't show it
how do i use it to be
here ah only from that angle so far away
do we get different programs now
did you listen to what he said i didn't
even listen
you gotta you know
filter these crazy robots out out of
your brain out of your mind out of my
sight i know
no it seems like we have the same
channels what am i doing next
what am i doing next
i don't remember getting an assignment
fairytale gum bed
oh
this is new summer
medium pollen
wow we get such a clear view of the sun
i know
that's just cereal non-interactive
entertainment forms you better off point
your parents not much but a bit i mean
yeah i'm proud that is true i would
probably be better off talking to you
parrot because this is not very
entertaining this tv
[Music]
need to get first class upgrade
who is saying who is even telling me to
get like why
why i mean what what foot
i told you it was fake
huh wait what
where better be why not this is the
promenade deck
okay
i think the game is telling me to go to
the promenade deck
where is that where what floor is that
[Music]
can i ask this dude to bring me to the
promenade game
promise you wouldn't like to know more
come out pomegranates
of the system [\h__\h] i really forgot how
to write it i was just walking around
now i don't know how to write it
paw wait what was the word
from promenade okay i really forgot
please always say please guys
yes sir
the chamber right unless you create this
chambers right you know if you're in the
wrong one see you on account what you
might
top of the world
all right thank you dude uh whatever
your name was we're in a prominent deck
what now this is uh permanent deck
isn't this just a lobby
no wait this looks different
there's no fire here but there's some
weird sculpture all the way over there
okay maybe
oh
[Music]
it's the cube
it's the [\h__\h] cube
it's the
it's the hope cube
[Laughter]
iris
is iris the solution to the game
oh dear oh it's art
oh my
scrallion tis are you a greek person
[Music]
what do we have here
we have more heads to look at
bro busty gun
nice to meet you sir
oopsie i didn't want to go that far i'm
going to look at this
wow
so sophisticated i'm in an art gallery
did i see you already
little v news
the pattern of the code is uh
the door is a key code i thought maybe i
should write it down
okay
oh
it's just
the same that i have here now
so maybe i put this here
okay
well i saved it
now i'm not sure what to do
hello
gonna make me go insane
[Music]
one of those is douglas adams himself
really yeah but it wouldn't say it in
the writing would it
even then that won't help me maybe i was
just not supposed to be here but i want
to push this
what did that do
who knows we might never know
okay so we went there what is uh what is
there to see in the produce
promenade
pregnant dick
oh
there's holy music when i look up there
wild tube oh thank you hallelujah
um i'm coming
wall tube this is a wall tube
gib
call
oh
this again am i supposed to be here can
i go
can i go here
no here no
no stupid greeting please shut up
i can go to an orchestra
some of the buttons work now yeah some
of them
are we there yet are we there yet shrek
are we doing it are we doing now are we
when are we gonna be there shrek
music room
okay time to work on my new hit signal
enjoy the view please finally in front
of you goodbye
oh i don't remember this room
i don't
it's in here
oh my god
oh
wow
beautiful
turned on some nice music so this is
this is oh there
did i have to solve this
what the [\h__\h] is this
what
does this change anything here
nice chairs
oh no wait i don't
um
wait do i have to look away in order to
change something is this like the
no it's not the layout of the room
where is it
wow that's loud
[Music]
help
what am i supposed to create here
[Music]
oh my god
can we at least turn off this one
wait am i supposed to recreate this
maybe we are
am i supposed to recreate this
[Music]
i can try
maybe
okay let's try
[Music]
start make music go
make the music i don't hear you
that was hmm loud
why is it not making music anymore i
turned them buttons on
the chairs are hint
chairs
oh
yeah my eyes uh
all the way to the right all the way to
the left
all the way to the bottom
somewhere in the middle just about there
on the right to the right
uh
yeah all the way to the left all the way
to the bottom
somewhere in the middle
let me check
uh somewhere on the right
my mom tells me to go to the parrot
first
can i not solve this already
uh somewhere on the right somewhere on
the left somewhere in the top
just there
here
here what about this one i can't see
that one is it on purpose
i can't see the top left one
oh and then this is
swoosh
and this is swoosh swoosh
okay
swoosh
and swoosh swoosh
this is
swoosh and this is swoosh swoosh
ah
swish swish
this is how it is
this is how it is i just don't know
maybe i have to try this one top left is
correct already okay i'm done
[Music]
oh
yes
that looks that sounds proper
[Music]
what do i get
as a reward
do i have to listen to the whole thing
[Music]
this is my new hate single
what's this name of the vocals
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
wow okay shut up
i solved it do i not get something for
solving it
record it on the gramophone oh
uh
recording is this
listen grammar phone listen
how long how long
[Music]
da
until it ends okay
[Music]
i'll be waiting
it's a nice nice tune though
i like the choice of instruments what
the hell is that on the left side i feel
like
that does not exist in reality the other
instruments okay but the one on the left
i doubt it
[Music]
oh yeah the guy the thing in the back
that is a robot knocking his head but
i'm sure we could recreate that in
reality
[Music]
nope we're not done
actually
[Music]
well actually
what about
[Music]
this better have recorded properly oh my
god
wow
[Music]
it's done
it's done thank you everybody
why don't we say gramophone
can we play that now
um
there it is do i have to listen to the
whole thing too
it worked
get the disc
[Music]
we got a blue ball out of that titania's
here ah that kind of reminds me yeah
yeah i am
i think we're looking for like body
parts or something
yeah my mommy says i have to go to the
parrot so let's go to the parrot uh
okay i think probably here
press square disk
what
kindly enjoy the view please yeah wait
we need to sell it cylinder what goodbye
was that not not all i needed
oh [\h__\h]
here do i need something else
uh
i can't grab anything
that's all i can take
surrender
press square 20.
oh
danke [\h__\h] how do you guys know did you
guys look at the guide
pascal
thank you
all right all right all right all right
all right all right all right
that's all we need right
now we can go back
now we can go to the parrot or or i
don't know my mom wants me to go to the
parrot but we are like we can go
anywhere now
who is this guy
please stand up straight the bar
oh we saw it before oh yeah it opened
stand up straight the bar
[Music]
it is very confusing oh
can we sing karaoke
this is like the yakuza bar hey
i'm getting
[Music]
the parrot
is very talkative i feel like i'm being
stalked by the parrot
oh nice bar very elegant hello dude can
i have um
non-alcoholic cocktail please a mocktail
require service please ring the bell
i shall ring the bell in my head
i require services
at your service
welcome to the starship titanic bar of
bars
uh
mocktail please catch the game last
[Music]
and your man orders up the artillery
artillery neville sink moisture himself
a little bit of top pocket from there
and then he wastes half a day playing
harry wants pistachios
can i take them
from my room into my inventory
everybody's so noisy
where's my mocktail where's my [\h__\h]
mocktail
oh that looks like titania's vision
center can i hesitate that looks like
titania's vision center okay can i has
titania's
vision
center
please
lovely words you do use you have a voice
like a favorite melody
still it's an answer you're wanting
isn't it hold your horses and let me
think about it on second thoughts tie
your horses up outside the saloon
because they're upsetting the dancing
girls can i have my little joke now what
i'm a wee bit stuck here with this
cocktail i'll let you have it when i'm
finished
no forget the cocktail i want them i
want the vision center it looks like
titania's vision center
remember it's here though i don't know
if we can get it now unless
[Music]
oh no is there a way to get it now
oh
oops there go my cell point settings
what
steal it looks like
his vision he just left that's it
i don't know how to take it yeah we need
to kill the bird i think i think we can
do it
shut the [\h__\h] up
[\h__\h] up
[\h__\h] up [\h__\h] [\h__\h] shut up [\h__\h]
ass
whatever the [\h__\h] you are
let's go and kill him
no spitting just killing don't worry
about it
i am i am going to throw him out of this
starship
and uh
i wish him all the best flying for the
universe
uh where the [\h__\h] is that penguin we
need to uh
ah here
i think
hey did they say penguins i mean parrots
stupid
parrots i don't think
the bear of chickens
yes that is me
pieces of ten
pistachios
no don't worry talking to me buster i
don't do small talk oh i'll take you
yeah
[Music]
okay
here we go
[Music]
i'll have to see your mother and the big
the big monkey yeah yeah okay what is
this
is this
anything i can take here
what is this
tv yeah
you just killed a parrot yes i told you
guys that was what i was about to do did
you not listen to me
i told you very clearly we're going to
take the parrot
send him through the universe
and wish the best for him
i told you stick
i warned you nobody stopped me why if
you had a problem with that why did you
not stop me huh huh
do i need to remember this
let's remember this
all right
um
i think
i think we got all we need
all right let's go to the big big big
monkey mama where was big monkey mama i
feel like we already met big monkey mama
wasn't she at the very top or the very
bottom
was she
you guys know
the bile room
down the lobby elevator huh i went to
the bottom of the first elevator
at that room and you mean
wait what how do i how do i go no no no
no no
no
no no no no no not here oh am i going
here do i need to go here
maybe i don't need to go here
ah are you mommy mommy
mommy yes mommy please
your lucky day
i've got an object for you is it a dead
bird
[Music]
amanda
this is christmas
no
i lost the [\h__\h] bird i thought you
were dead
i thought you were dead
oh i need
my mom says i need the feather from the
bird
uh but we lost the bird i think we need
to kill him again
let's go
let's kill the bird yay
i think i understand now understand
everything completely
first super chat ever thank you this
weird game reminds me of some other old
one that plays as a kid where you just
cute little cute robot around and
helping folk
you should try such art
oh the problem with old games often is
that they're
already abandoned wear and so on i was
really lucky with this one
uh
so i don't know if the game that you're
talking about would even be possible to
play we also need to even if it's not
abandoned where we always need to
contact the the people who are the
publishers and we need to ask them
kindly to give us permission
and uh you know it's and not that easy
i thought the parrot would was this not
the parent room what happened
it's another art gallery
oh
any good he's still just a superannuated
old winter
soldier
we need to kill a bird i don't want to
listen to your stupid whiny pirate voice
the whole day
is this
oh no it's another riddle
[Music]
mate
my mom keeps on sending me advice
surprising how she remembers what to do
oh let me save by the way is this saving
did i save i think i saved okay
uh uh
i'm
[Music]
okay let's go back to the bird
my mommy is backseating but um we need
that oh no where are we on what floor
are we
[Music]
what floor are we in right now
this is not the first floor
huh
ah
president
correct
first floor please
certainly
thank you at least we understand each
other now
[Music]
wait no we don't seem to understand each
other um
lobby
afraid we're not in morocco now sir you
will have to give me a precise floor
this is the first floor
eh floor one top of the well we're
already there
we're already there
that's not correct why is the room
different
why is that
oh maybe
oh
we're on the wrong side is that possible
is that ah we were just done oh i didn't
realize what
i'm back
stupid
throw it away
no [\h__\h] i lost the bird
okay i figured it out i got the feather
uh what did i need the feather for i
don't even know mommy just told me to
get the feather
do i
what do i do with the feather
[Music]
huh
i think i need to just send the feather
instead of the bird
let's go to the sack you boost what you
give us something
i don't know who i'm sending it to
feathers
feathers make me sneeze
and dab
dab uh-huh
you're just sneezing right
wow me koregami to you koto descartes
bless you my dear
oh
why is that
one at a time one at a time i got the
feather back
how of what you were saying here what
you must have said
somewhere else
feathers
feathers make me sneeze
holy [\h__\h] i just get the feather
we should do this later okay
well mommy just really
made me wanted to
get me to shut up the bird but you're
just not going to shut up
person stop it [\h__\h] you screech i should
screech i will send you so that you shut
up
[Music]
kill the [\h__\h] bird
[Applause]
i think that got lost oopsie you have to
see mother nah i don't think we need to
i don't think we need the the bird
anymore we already have the feather we
don't need to [\h__\h] parrot anymore
nice okay uh
still what are we doing next
[Music]
i
we could go to the other side in that
room where there was a riddle that i
obviously did not understand
and that was uh
here
nope the other one
maybe this one
is connected to the other room it has a
sign in it no maybe not
all right so we're in this room
how
do we solve
the riddle in here
what is this
[Music]
that just moved something
i think
[Music]
i think it moved something but is there
like a hint
i want to just aimlessly do something
here
i hear something moving
oh
the arrows on the bottom left
ah do they all need to go upwards
[Music]
oh it went down it all went down again
though
now it's also going down and one is up
ah that reminds me of that game i played
with if i
remember those those
tubes that we were
trying to connect with the gas oh that
was terrible
oh
okay that sends both of the upper ones
upwards
we were here yeah i mean i liked the
game but you know it was suffering oh
they're all up
what now did i solve it
but it already goes back
to the bottom
[Music]
oh
mommy says
i need the bird
for the pistachios in my room
okay
i thought we don't need to deal with the
bird anymore
okay we need to go to mommy
to the in-game mommy not my real mommy
uh
wait wrong side
i didn't uh wrong side
[Music]
here here
here
here no
uh
here
this is how i go to
uh in-game mommy right
mommy
mommy monkey i didn't know i had a
monkey as my mom this is me not a monkey
after all
oh mommy mommy
that thing
is that really mommy
because last time we picked the bird up
it just flew away we couldn't actually
receive it properly i think we need to
go to real mommy is this really mommy
right there's a bigger mommy right
that's not it right yeah photo too huh
didn't i see a big mommy somewhere wait
uh
uh did the this weird bilge room or
whatever that you guys said was what i
understand what was that build room what
does that mean what is that what did
that look like
what is the build room you guys are just
getting this from the guide aren't you
you don't even know what you're talking
about
the very first elevator
start eleven you mean the one where i
got from
my house to the
to the starship
um
okay
understand
uh
let me off of here
and then i think
empty parent room i wish it could stay
like that forever
and then
here
this is the build room
yeah
i already forgot what that one looked
like
oh
oopsie
i i knew that was the ncs i've seen you
before big mommy hey mama it's that
monster drunk you know my mom get on the
floor and move your booty mama
[Music]
pleased to eat my pistachios
but don't let it fly away
we need to control the bird
get out of here huh
where's my bird
oh feather you want the feather
feathers make me sneeze
[Music]
wow that's a lot of dirt oh my [\h__\h] what
oh my god
we got two things we got
titania's old factory center and a blue
fuse
we didn't get the parrot
what the [\h__\h]
suck
i suck
he won't blow
i blow
you want
intellectual disputation
i got a big belch
is this the yuppie thing that they said
before
send him back oh maybe i can no it says
there's currently nothing in the tray
not so sure about it looks like a
mannequin or a dead body
judging by the
pose is probably a mannequin
okay i think we got some um important
items though um
my mom
my mom is saying
feather birds send in your room
but
i know has bird only has feather
i'm gonna make him throw up again give
us more dead bodies
feathers
feathers make me sneeze
oh receive the bird again
oh my god
oh
i'm sure this could trigger some people
into throwing up for real let's just
leave
vacation
yeah
that must have been fun to record
embarkation lobby
hello
uh where are we going next to my room
right no to parrot room get parrot again
but wait parrot didn't even
get freedom again parrot is not here
parent
oh
parrot john
received there's nothing here
he must have sent it somewhere else here
can i has birdbath brothers
feathers make me sneeze
and haven't done before
okay
okay okay okay
i don't want my room oh
we're gonna receive it in my room really
oh where was my room again elevator two
[Music]
uh
four seven or was that my old room
which one is this one elevator two
can i just say my room please oh well
sir you and me both stuck with our
respective positions
it works
wow this is high tech guys
this is high tech if if only
the
elevators nowadays would work like that
voice recognition why do elevators not
have voice recognition yet
um although i i can't see how that would
be maybe kind of difficult
but but you can use your card at least
and just don't talk it out just put the
card on the elevator thingy
and then it already selects your
your floor i've seen that before hello
oh wait so do i can i take pistachios
and then put them into the
no
okay but the bird maybe is gonna set
free in my room and then eat the
pistachios
maybe
there's nothing here
something in my tray
and make sure
feathers
might make me sneeze
[Music]
it's still just a feather though how do
i receive bird
how do i receive a bird
just receive
no it said nothing oh didn't he say he
has nothing oh no come back come back
then i'm sleeping
stop fiddling with me there's nothing
here
you must have seen it maybe i have sent
him out to the shuttle realm for real
[Music]
ah
if you've gone to your room your second
classroom you'll notice that there's a
foot cup of pistachios in the room and
you couldn't bring the pistachios to the
parrot so how about bringing power to
the pistachios yeah i'm trying where the
[\h__\h] is the bird right now we were able
to get him once and then send him free
but how did he get into my room
mama
[Music]
my mom
said where did you send him to i don't
know one of these buttons this button
also takes you to the upper level and is
situated three inches higher for your
convenience why does this sound like a
german recorded this
this button would take you to the higher
level if you weren't there already
this button takes you to the lower level
where am i now
[Music]
am i back to where originally was
where's my bird wait so we took the bird
and then we uh
we
we i think
um
did we send it through
the suppose
uh
literally told you burke was sarah
to your requested destination
i had been office where is admin office
don't see no point in that line of
questioning
me neither sir me neighbor what about
can i like i don't know um
when did we bring the bird they were
bringing somewhere here
uh
here no
did we bring him somewhere here
no looking around or shrugging please
huh
don't worry my model can't shrug
the blue area where you got him last
time
you mean his room right
who's this room
is this
the promenade deck probably not product
ah
no features remarks please
low elevator with motion sickness okay
okay okay
you mean the bottom room with uh
[Music]
uh-huh
by the way the whole chatting thing
reminds me of one
one thing they like
like to use uh in my free time back in
the day
that's an order was this ever a thing on
uh for like where in the internet when
you guys were around um like a
a god
butt that you could write with
elias elisa yeah
eli's output
[Music]
you look like you could do this i'm not
talking to you right now eliza a chatbot
in the bottom of the well no i don't
think down there yet
maybe i didn't mean that one no i mean a
god a god like a god but
cleverbot
robot
[Music]
speak to an eye one
i don't know it's old so maybe it
doesn't exist anymore but that was fun
i think i think um
yeah while that was popular a lot of
people were using it
because they were bored
so bored and didn't have anything else
to do
but that was pretty smart because like
they had um a lot of answers
it was pretty
well made like mostly
but i think many people tried to make
that god uh their girlfriend
and then god would always be like no i
am uh ai no thank you
i'm not interested in that kind of stuff
you cannot marry me no no no
that is not possible
parrot
parrot john
oh that was not it
peritong
typical maidenless behavior
yes i i i don't behave like that i am
the maiden
oh [\h__\h] no no no no
which one was the room
oh
bring it straight and then left
ah
do you have my bird got something for
you i thought so
[Music]
thank you
we finally have it back the lost bird
you can't keep a good parrot down
but
it's leaving you
he can't
can't keep a bird parrot down is that
what he said he flew to his cage yeah
that's like a circle it never ends
never ending circle
another question do you have a monkey
yeah but i couldn't receive it in my
room
i went to my room
[Music]
when you send it from another one but
but but but when i tried to leave the
room where the bird is in its cage
um it flies away i already tried that
use waiver room
what address on success
wave wave room room mat
boom boom
raven
what
okay oh i can tell
him where to set it properly
okay bird
don't [\h__\h] around with me anymore
person stop it watch the screen how do i
tell you
where to stand which one is my room
this one
does that work
are you gonna send it to my room
[Music]
do i do it again maybe just in case
just in case
and then send it okay
here we go i wouldn't know how else to
do it please please please say it works
please stay awake please
okay
it's there it's there
this must be it
uh so now we go back to more room
which is
here's second second elevator no second
second second elevator i think what was
it first
it doesn't matter we'll get there
somehow he had a big brain
always
my room
this mpc is one of my favorites though
even though he's like kind of annoying
but this one and uh
we didn't talk much to our
own dude here i wonder if he'll get some
more action because
uh okay
so please say this works come on
[Music]
not here
maybe
i lost it no no
impossible here take feather
feathers
squeeze out my bird sneeze sneeze out my
boots
[Music]
that's not possible
no this is my room or am i in the wrong
room
no room one
receive clear
[Music]
huh
not here
maybe
i lost it
how could i bring the parrot to my room
he won't come out of the parrot room use
the succubus in the perim grab the
parrot and put him in the succubus tray
then press send
now head to your second classroom and
straight to your personal succulents i
did that press receive and take the
cylinder i did that the part will be
free no
if you're in the correct room as soon as
you click on the bowl of the status
the parrot will fly to fly to it and eat
them
but i i didn't receive it this is my
room
oh oh oh no no bird
is this not my room this is my room
huh
you're telling me i could enter rooms
that are not even mine
what about it's number one though the
first room
what about this one oh i can enter any
room
maybe this is number one and the other
one was number four what you got
if i can't not here he doesn't have
anything either
i lost it
um
[Music]
every room is my room
i've got something for you why this room
he has something for me
[Music]
this small room
where is this room
oh
i'll take
it
no no don't leave or was it supposed to
leave it in the tray no take that
i hear a thing
now we got something
oh wait this is
oh
now we have
two ears
ah finally
finally
it was about [\h__\h] time you know
normally i never use guides obviously
this is the first time i'm using a guide
for a stream
i'm sorry but with an old riddle game
like this when you guys can't help me
the problem is that you guys can't
really help me that much
right because most of you didn't play
the game and you're also just looking at
a guide
yeah it's so old like with the other
games i play
most of the time there's like so a lot
of people in the chat who played it
themselves
so
we kind of figure it out as we go with
the chat together but in this case
i need to do it myself i don't want to i
don't want to stay here for 10 hours you
know
i want to introduce this nostalgic retro
game to you guys and
if it takes some uh backseating from my
mom and from a super old website
with a
weird resolution
and a beautiful gradation background if
that's what it takes then that's fine
with me
okay so we got the the parrot with the
pistachios and the ear
and wait did we get the eye it says here
there's an eye too
[Music]
i
oh apparently oh there's a broken
elevator that we can fix and from that
we could we would get the
the eye we can try that i only read that
that that we have to do it i didn't read
how to do it can we do it i wonder if
we're ready to do it
yeah a bit cryptic this means more arm
action i'll be bound uh lobby oh
oh
[Music]
he doesn't understand the word lobby
excuse me
sorry i do it again and again and again
top of the well sir from here you can
walk to your request probably if i would
just write number one it would probably
also be enough
so elevator four
is
broken
are you broken
hello
there's no one to talk to yeah this one
is broken
[Music]
one
so what how do we fix this elevator
maybe from the outside
we fix it from the outside
ah
and this one has no face
i remembered that but i don't know how
it was fixed
[Music]
i'm trying to go behind it this is the
best i can do
and then it just brings me back straight
out wait huh no
no
i can't i can't
i can't go behind it um
uh
see you in five minutes or so uh
[Music]
i think one of the elevators is broken
shut up have you figured out which one
yet not now
[Music]
so
now
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
me
oh me
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
find my destiny
would you tell me
[Music]
oh
me
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
tell me
me
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
is
i've been trying to find me
pushing me
[Music]
wow
oh
[Music]
okay
ah
sorry
oh sure
sorry no super chat rating yet sorry
sorry sorry
my brother and my sister
came up
uh to
get the stuff that i rescued for them
good timing why
my sister was actually uh watching uh
the stream
while in the car
and she they my both my brother and my
sister also played the game and uh my
sister was trying to
help me i asked her hey if you know the
game do you know what to do about this
elevator and she said ah you need to get
the head and i was like oh yeah right
the head
uh
i think
she was not quite sure but
uh
the head we pick up from somewhere else
and bring it here and repair the
elevator
yes yes i have figured out which one is
broken do worms lick their trails
what
yes cool
cheerio
cheerios hey man you've lost me hey man
you're an average billboard he's
glitching i understand everything
he's so cool he's so chill he's like the
most chill guy in this whole starship
all right
so we need a head i think i think
um from that weird uh
elevator on the other side
i think
my whole family is helping me with this
game now
um
what was it what did she say
probably
was it this room messengers will kindly
behave themselves on the journey was it
this room
um
was it this room
maybe not
i'm not sure
and my family got my back about this
game everybody loves this game in my
family
i think my mom started you know and then
my brother
and my sister
are both older than me
so they played the game too i suppose
and i just i was watching everyone play
it but i i don't think i ever really
played it let's exit the other side okay
yeah it's very confusing and chilly
[Music]
what
that's
birds
pixel birds that's not the room that i
thought i was going to
oh my god
is this room no where is that head wait
um
no no no no
uh
it was my sister also said it was
something about
dropping a tv
there was something about dropping a tv
uh
from my room i think my tv's room rooms
tv and uh then
yeah
i don't know how do we get out of here
again
i would like to leave
i have to call
stupid
uh
we're going back to this is the lobby
right
uh
uh wait
should we just read the guide
most probably the broken elevator is
number four head to the bottom of the
well i forgot what that was again via
one of the elevators are available
simply by tapping the bottom of the well
oh okay
when done
now my mom's backseating me and get oh
my god my whole family my mom's saying
no
go into the parrot room
what from when is this i already did the
parrot stuff no
i don't need a guide anymore it seems my
mom please my mom seems to remember
me
okay
um
apparently
apparently parrot
should keep on getting what's up
messages from my mom
so
uh
apparently here we call needed urgently
the bell button
according to my mom head up to the top
of the well get a fix on things
uh
drop my tv please how am i supposed to
tell you drop my tv please
yeah
you bet smash the ship smash the ship
smash the ship bell bots are bad what
[Music]
he's doing it
what
[Laughter]
he's silly it's just
oh no
oh there it is
my sister told me like yeah he's gonna
do that i'm not sure why he did it but
he's doing it and i'm also not sure even
though i just had it happen to me why
he's doing it i think we manipulated his
mind
into becoming a bad butt a bad butt
who's a bad butt you're a bad butt shut
up
wait no that's the tv that was just
there no no no we're
shut up
should it be like at the bottom
somewhere down there now he dropped it
down there
uh so if i go
to the elevator
and tell the elevator that i want to go
to the bottom of the well
oh dear sir i am well oh
oh and then from the broken tv i think
we get something out of that
yo okay
how do you figure this out right
in a normal playthrough in a blind
playthrough without a family advising me
what to do
how give us your flaws huh
how would i have known
to do this is there are the they're the
parts
i didn't
i saw them on the ground let me pick
them up i think i oh
it's the head
we're trying a lot of things and finding
clues
there must be a clue somewhere in the
game telling you to do that right there
must look at that
maybe i should replace my head with this
would that look good would i look good
with that hat i would look good if any
head won't wouldn't i and this is my tv
smashed
nice
okay well that is uh the liftbot's head
so now we give that to
the
elevator
uh
if you could just hang on a mouse while
i try to summon my spring it doesn't
really matter which floor we are in
though i think but we're just gonna go
to floor one
acquired the broken tv
people used to spend months playing
games like this
yeah i also don't like recall it being
such a short game like four hours but
i mean it's a long time ago and maybe my
mom here you can watch just played it
several times over and over and over
again i could imagine that
she probably did
so
it's your lucky day mr elevator i have
your head your cat
[Music]
take
take the head
head
cake
take it
take the head
he doesn't want the head
[Music]
why you not want my head
is it the wrong head i think it fits
perfectly
fake
take ah take this oh
and then i get oh titania's eye
oh blimey
hello
step me vitals
[Music]
absolutely amazing
that reminds me oh you guys didn't
remind me but i reminded myself
do i need this elevator to go anywhere
specifically i wonder um i wanted to
tell you guys something while you guys
are all here uh this is something
something for the members some some news
for the members
out of nowhere because i feel like it
so
uh
one one thing is you know i've been
talking about uh struggling to find more
games
that i can play for members only
because
we need like you know specific
permissions that allow hello's biped
sounds to me like the big mother's got
something stuck in his throat
you need to make it sneeze it out
somehow shh big man i've got something
stuck in this root oh
this dude gives us advice when we're
stuck huh
so i've been i've been trying my best to
find games that maybe perhaps we maybe
have a slight chance of getting
permission to uh use it for members only
streams so i've been requesting several
ones and i finally heard back from one
uh
[Music]
this is thanks to kiwawa okay
we have maybe three games that we can
play for members only and now we have
maybe four
yeah uh it's called townscaper do you
know what i thought it would be really
chill to play that uh in a member stream
townscaper have you seen it
i once saw like a trailer of it and it
looks so like smooth and nice you know
it
yeah yeah yeah it's so cool
it's really cool you should look it up
townscape you like build like houses
in in the middle of nowhere on top of
water and it's like i don't know it's
really cool
uh
it's like a
town builder game
build quaint islands island towns of
curvy streets small hamlets blue blah
blah blah block no goal no real gameplay
just plenty of building and plenty of
beauty that's it exactly
yeah yeah yeah so it's gonna be like an
aesthetic uh
game to play
uh
you know to relax and tangent on the
side so i thought it would be good yeah
it's like sandbox building game
yay
so i since we just got permissions for
that i thought how about we play it this
weekend i was gonna play fall guys but
since we now have something new
yeah i think we should play this one
yeah
if you're good with it
let me pour some raw water
as relaxing on the tag yeah it looks so
so relaxing it's so pretty
it's so pretty i think am i wrong maybe
this was about a different game but i
think this game was made by one person
one person oscar oskar's
styleberg
or so
i think it was just made by one person i
could be wrong though
i was right there you go so big respect
man and the other thing is
i'm announcing this uh early because i'm
excited no i mean it's not nothing too
crazy it's just
it's just i was thinking um
like when i make schedules when i make
weekly schedules i generally use
or i need i have to use otherwise i have
to
edit the art but i have to use like
landscape art um and i've been
struggling recently to find landscape
size art fan art that i haven't used yet
and that would fit the schedules that
i'm making so i was like what could i do
and then i got the idea um to commission
art just for the sake of weekly
schedules but have it be monthly
um
like one illustration per month
that i use for all the weekly schedules
in that month and it will be themed
after that month so for the summertime
we'll have summer illustrations and all
that and i just
commission whoever i want and but on top
of it obviously will be the whole
schedule so the clean art of that will
be distributed to members only as a
monthly wallpaper
yay
a new a new um
perk
to becoming a member
monthly exclusive wallpapers themed
after each month
starting
in may i just had the idea yesterday but
i found an artist who um has the time to
uh work on it for the one for may
and then we'll continue on and on and on
yay
basically i was mostly doing it because
i'm i'm lacking art for my weekly
schedules
but i thought why not get more use out
of it by
uh giving you guys the the clean art oh
thank you oh memberships let's go thank
you
um
it's yeah it's also kind of like at the
end of a year you could make a calendar
out of it because the art will be
um you know themed after each month and
whatever whatever i want it to be themed
after
it's an extra perk for you guys hope you
will enjoy it
[Music]
i know
uh good a good day good news for members
all over so let's talk to this bellbot
again you did a great job at smashing
the tv how about we smash the [\h__\h]
parrot next
become a member now get a free wallpaper
for next month next month
become a member next month get a free
wallpaper
um
uh thank you for the membership oh oh
i wasn't really trying to promote my
membership but it seems to have worked
wonders
uh back to the confusion yeah
use your brains again everybody
greetings my name is something stuck in
his throat you need to make it sneezy
you may you need to make it sneeze it
out somehow okay is it something new
because we've talked to the mother
before
i guess it has something new for us uh
where how did i go to mother parrot
again now mother monkey
uh mother monkey was i know where i know
i know i know i know i know i know i
know no no no no no no no no no i know
this this one i know this one i remember
um
nope wrong wrong side
wrong side
mommy says nothing new
mommy says it won't give me anything new
yeah i already made her sneeze yo can
you tell me something useful need it
urgently
greetings biped if i were you i'd check
to make sure the big succubus is working
the big succubus you mean
the mommy monkey
[Music]
okay mommy tells me to go to the
bartender
we're listening to mommy
this dude he just smashed the tv he
doesn't know what he's talking about
he's just so
euphoric
yeah
let's go to the bartender and let's sing
some karaoke
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm getting bored with my feet why are
you here knocking from under me
disturbing me
i have to make him a cocktail how do i
make him a cocktail how to make you a
cocktail
mommy says i have to make him a cocktail
i'm mixing a drink i see it on the guide
that's better
got me sell point settings back on
course again
how do i know
[Music]
oh but i have to get all kinds of things
from all
over everywhere no
i need a hammer i need a lemon
i need
pureed starlings find a chicken to
produce one
there's a chicken on the promenade deck
apparently
but do i have to ask you first about it
[Music]
um no the guy tells me to get a pair to
get a chicken
a chicken for a cocktail
a chick tail
let's talk with him first though
another cocktail
i'll get you one just as soon as you fix
this loop
as i've as soon as i fixed this loop
which loop
huh
okay where's leonvenous he'll fix this
little mess no problem
leo venus is that a hint that is a hint
wasn't that one of the guys in the in
the museum thingy
[Music]
here's a chicken and a violin right up
the street oh
there go my cell point settings
huh
we will go
uh
do we have
we have the blue fuse
the guide says i need the blue views
go to the promenade deck
find the chicken to produce one it
should be a uh
a lot at the promenade deck you should
could check it out
please exit other side
this is very cool
congratulations uh
think
promenade deck we can get to the
prominent deck by telling the elevator
prominent deck right
calling
i suppose i should say welcome but my
samaroids are giving me hell you
wouldn't mind this
stream layout becoming the norm
only for games that have a weird uh um
resolution
problem grenade
oh we are on the promenade deck
oh think
uh
chicken
there's a chicken supposed to be here
going to tania's room
wait
should i go to the titania room before i
get the chicken
okay wait wait wait no no no there's no
we need to go to titania's room where is
that
elevators
yes
i already fixed uh all of it go away
where is tita who even is titani titania
is that the with body at the
uh here
is this titania titanium's room
is this it
because there was a body here this is
this it okay
there must be a chicken here
there's a red button
push button to disarm bump
not right now
sounds dangerous okay this is this is
this is titanium lying here i suppose
yeah yeah can we already give you
something
no
maybe not now
uh
this room i couldn't enter but what
about what about this room
this was that room
ah yeah something about the blue fuse
this is where i got the blue fuse from
uh
what is this um
shoto mata
how do i work with this
oh
well this is not it either
i wonder if they just want me to put it
back in here open all the doors please
and insert the blue i already no no we
got the we got the we got the uh blue
fields from somewhere else
so we check we put this in we turn it
around
and dad maybe did something take the
yellow chicken
the chicken fuse here says chicken
it should wreck the fat at the promenade
deck it says
i'm not even trying anymore i'm just
using the the guide now i'm so sorry
[Laughter]
but i didn't hear anything i wonder if i
did it
wrong so if i go back to the promenade
deck will i have will will something
have happened
i don't know why they're trying to get
chicken like this i have so much to
offer here
fresh chicken fresh from kfp
why would you want to get it from
anywhere else
and we have the best chicken
uh it says
it should wreck the fan what fan
what fan
i know i never saw a fan here
maybe
in this room
no
there's no fan here
i need to sneeze i think
but not like that monkey don't worry
i don't sneeze like the monkey
you know what let's go here there was
something about one of these dudes
not you
there's no music here did i break it
you i thank you can i take you something
was there was something about you
i think
this dude was
okay no no there was something about
this
guy right but what
do you want something from me do you
want can i put something on you
no
huh
ah
wait
my mom was saying something
i missed it
damn it
i don't know what it's about anymore
told me to click something
what fan
i don't think what we did worked to be
honest
i don't see a fan that's not a fan let's
say chandelier or something like that
[Music]
do you guys ever see a fan
i know there's a lot of fans in the chat
i'm a fan i know
it says go to titania's room and enter
the fuse room insert the blue fuse turn
the blue knob sideways i did that take
the yellow fuse i did dead it should
wreck the fan at the promenade deck
what smells so good
i smell food
[Music]
wonder what that is it's the chicken
it's the chicken i think it's the
chicken
it must
wait be the [\h__\h] is this
wait wait i need to investigate i need
to investigate
[Music]
i think
i think it was my imagination
but i picked up a cat
you know at the moment i left my room i
didn't smell anything anymore
now i don't smell anything in my room
either
[Music]
no but maybe it just means i'm hungry
because i am hungry
gpu on fire
totally
this game is making my gpu
uh set fire set on fire yes yes ah let
me
um
maybe we did it wrong
help in the interest of safety
please do not overload your bellbot
aren't you like a concierge oh no i know
you're a bad boy
you're not helping me much lead me to
the concierge please
we will
once again go to
the titania room
now
are usually for uh carrying the luggage
and like opening the taxi door and
bringing the luggage to your room and so
on and helping you generally with like
smaller things and the concierge usually
knows everything about the city and will
help you get reservations and uh tells
you what toys what city tours to take
and all that and the bell boys are
working together with the concierge
usually to um
you know have some teamwork going what
is this anyway
hmm well we probably did this wrong
what if i turn this too
we turned this sideways after putting
this in
and we took the
yellow thingy it didn't tell me to turn
the knob but maybe it was supposed to
turn it off too
cave chicken oh it stays that way
maybe now
because if i turn the knob with the
yellow thing in then
it
uh
stays that way
you haven't even been today of course i
have been to the promenade deck
of course i have
they told me i already was there
i think
you're confusing me
god damn it
why is it so difficult to get back up
here
why you gotta make it so
musukashi oh by the way i did learn
korean you didn't you didn't think i
would do it huh
looking especially at one person in my
chat you didn't think i would actually
do it right i don't know all of the
signs yet but i know some of them like i
know the the ah and i know it and i know
oh and then the m and uh i know ooh
and i know
and i know i it and i know
uh some others like d and then d plus d
plus over seven is do
and all those yeah i know some some
hunger
some of them i remembered i also still
see no change mommy i'm
no i didn't use duolingo i got myself a
different application for learning the
basic hanger
uh an app that's called
uh i even bought like the premium
version of it
an app that's called
where is it
i think one of the elements something
like
write it korean which one yet
where did it go where did my app go
oh it's not on my me
some of my main screen write it
exclamation mark korean
yeah
i think i get it i will continue to oh
oh my gosh oh i think no wait no no no
no that says um
you know i think that says all yeah that
says
and um
that one says
the first one i don't know yet but i see
i see uh
[Music]
i think
i see
oh
ah wait i forgot the circle was
and then with that one underneath that's
under the table so that's
cool
uh the last one i don't i don't know yet
yeah yeah i'm still trying to make some
bridges to tell myself
what it could be
i'm getting there
ah
i was i i don't think i know i can say
knee i know the knee and so i can also
probably say neo or nia
or
anything similar with me
i could probably say
um i could probably i probably would
know how to write me knee or something
like that
oh i think i should know how to write
key from key ah but i don't know how to
write da i only know how to write key
and adam i think
i think
because uh e is just the one the one
straight one
and
because you combine the k and the e
so it's the the one that looks like
nihongo
uh
uh combined with e oh wait are they
writing my name they're writing my name
kiana
and i'm i'm smelling tuna pizza what the
[\h__\h] am i smelling tuna pizza
i want to know pizza i'm stuck and i'm
just talking about korean can we just
study korean now
can we just study korean
tuna
tuna pencil come from maybe maybe it's
the cat food maybe i give my cats tuna
tuna
wet food today
[Laughter]
[Music]
happy what are we gonna do
ah
find the chicken to produce one it
should be a lot at the promenade deck
you could check it out
what does that sentence even mean
maybe we're in where is
but then it tells me to go to titania's
room into the fuse room instead of maybe
the first step was not
uh done correctly
uh there's a sound
there's sound b and
option what
to the promenade from the bronze tube
hello right now
[Music]
which one was it
which is the promenade deck this one
please stand up straight
i'm sitting sorry why would i stand up
straight when you have literally seats
in your pellet radar hmm
hmm
what do you have the seats for if i'm
supposed to stand
all right
promenade deck very german of you duncan
mine's how you go that also sounds uh
german i [\h__\h] hate those birds
[Music]
okay there's a chicken supposed to be
here
[Music]
we're talking about chicken chicken
chicken chicken
yeah yeah this is how to get the puree
starling i guess yeah okay speed chicken
please
speed speed
[Music]
oh oh
oh that's what they mean with that
purity oh
[Applause]
oh
i finally understand it
chicken
that's not a chicken but that's to
understand everything now
this is like um
coffee pasta
you don't want to go near that thing man
you don't want to go near that thing
that's just an automatic of mucus as
there's a cybernetic bowl of phlegm and
don't give it a chicken any chicken you
find is my chicken i want that
understood my chicken rug you don't want
to go near that thing
you don't want to
it just repeats wait who was talking
though
were you talking
shut up they're still talking how do i
get my
how do i get the period pureed stalling
no just chill
off
shut
up
why is everything so obnoxious am i not
supposed to pick up something
[Music]
oh yeah
i killed the birds and got nothing out
of it on it find a chicken to put to
produce one and something learning to go
what to produce fine chicken to produce
one
maybe i'm not supposed to pick up
anything
hmm
everything in britain is obnoxious oh no
come on now
that's not true except me
i am obnoxious will kindly behave
themselves on the journey
ah
didn't you have fish pizza that day what
day
no my clothes are fresh i'm fresh
the top of the well i took a shower
yesterday unbelievable
i took
the door a full-on shower yesterday
i even washed my hair
um
next step we're gonna redo
the thing
now going to redo it
in the hopes of that the purity
startling thingy was necessary for
whatever reason
i'm just going to play around with it uh
is this the room
no
i still don't know what the fan is
though
wow
hello here i am once again
i'll turn into places can't deny it
can't pretend just fought you were to
order
ah
oh you turn it back to normal
uh turn this back to normal
uh
turn this back to normal okay now we're
back to normal i put this in
i turn it around
i take this and i go
according to
the guide
am i doing it wrong
[Music]
hmm
ah sorry look people hold up pretty poor
ah
did you not watch the concert you only
want to uh the digest that is wonderful
i'm glad you got to watch something
that is perfect
it says after to go to a restaurant okay
and yeah yeah so uh i don't know when
exactly it happened a couple hours ago
maybe i think while i was sleeping
a whole life english channel uploaded a
digest of our performances and they had
like uh
i think
part of my verse and my bridge and then
the the chorus with the cake
with the kicking cake in
the digest so if you didn't get to watch
the concert then you all could watch the
um
the
yes
the digest at least at least in some way
you will be able to
get a view of the
3d moving what is this
is there a restaurant here this was the
bar
what is this i can't go there
[Music]
now use the pylori and go to promenade
deck approach the fan
turn it on and set the speed too fast
uh
okay ah the fan up there
oh yeah yeah yeah i'm so stupid i'm
confusing so many things
they've showed my favorite part from
your turn yeah they show uh some good
parts also like you know where i go like
yeah yeah yeah so i'm glad they showed
that because you get a good view of the
really hyped up uh audience
that is really good please exit other
side
this is very confusing i like that view
mind how you go
find how you go yeah
so and now we broke the fan hopefully oh
yeah i think we broke it
that's that's supposed to happen right
ah the fan will slash the chickens wait
no no no no what chickens
what chickens
i'm so confused
it's wrecked now
but
uh
use the empty glass under chicken to get
the pureed starlings
the [\h__\h] click the switch for chicken
beside the door and then insert the
chicken
poke with long stick i have a long stick
hook
poke
how do i
i need the hammer i think no i don't
need to hammer but i i know i can i have
a poke stick
it doesn't work i need to poke it
several times oh
hammer
but i need a chicken
i need a chicken and i need to
apparently i know this is really cruel
but i need to send it through the fan
hmm do you have a chicken
i killed the birds um
[Music]
there's nothing here [\h__\h] you must have
sent it somewhere else
yeah
probably
uh
yeah we did the fan
we pureed the starlings
does my mommy say something
the thing with the chicken is something
else what's this perennial with him
glass there is poo green ah it seems
above the light i think
i think i
know i think this is
take it
take it no
oh god damn it i thought i could like
scoop it up mommy says to take the purim
of the glass
puree
take it
scrap it up get it in there get it in
there
i don't know
[Music]
isn't there one in your room
a chicken
are you making a joke
are you hinting at something particular
ah go to floor 28
why
what's in floor 28
no way
seconds
did we miss something like from before
um this is all about mixing a drink
right so uh we upgraded to
um
sculpture
do i have to do all this first please
stand up straight
uh-huh
as chicken dispensers
find how you go
that's an order
oh my god floors 28 to 38 all of them
chicken dispenser close to your first
room
floor 28 you're my sphere of operation
sir i only patrol between floors one and
twenty seven
you best be having a word on the
community with my colleagues in lift one
or three one or three oh okay
no problem this was number
one oh dear sir laura 28.
no sooner said than done the men are
speaking
yeah my mom says i messed up the people
but no i can't be um
i i didn't soft lock myself
is that possible can you soft that is an
easy soft block thing
how would i
have done it correctly what the hell
uh the chicken
is doco
chicken
mona lisa
ah she smiles when i
click on her okay
that is so weird oh
hello
oh the music changes too
let's keep her smiling because i think
when she end when i entered she was not
smiling
oh but she goes back
no now she's smiling okay
maybe in the future oh
smash
emergency long stick smash class
i got a new item that will be helpful
hopefully
oh there's another stick can we get
another stick
yeah
[\h__\h]
no i don't think i can get any more the
dispenser has certainly been fitted with
unbreakable glass to prevent unseemly
hoarding of sticks
is a smart i guess
i i don't know why you would do that but
i guess it makes sense
where is chicken
where is the chicken
is it here
[Music]
what a menu
look at all these chickens chicken and
sauce tomato chicken
[Music]
give chicken
oh no
oh
[Music]
it went straight to the
it went straight to him why did it go
straight to this boy
monkey
stop fiddling with me
do i need to stop
like
it maybe
here bother me
nah
i keep
huh
feathers
feathers make me sneeze
and dab
chicken
[Music]
there are
29 mentions of chicken in the guide
hot chicken
get designer room number of the parent
room first
on this only sauce there
wait is that the different kind of
chicken it's not like i can do i need to
go to a different room at a different
floor to get the right chicken
oh cause i only got
this one touch
it's really a kfb game
um ah
the parrot likes chicken
but without the sauce
and hot
well
uh
oh dear sir some sort of floor you
wanted was it
how do i get different chicken on floor
29 floor here is your floor sir thank
you
it's the same menu but maybe something
else
no it's the same chicken
ah chicken
i told you guys in the beginning there
was a lot of
chicken
in this game with this this monkey this
robot eating the chicken i know it's you
stealing my chicken
i know it's you
i'm so lost at this point
i'm so lost can we go all the way back
i'm i think i'm missing something
important here so we did the arrival
um
[Music]
uh
that's the word
okay
we should maybe do first things first
that are in the guide because uh maybe
it's all connected in some way
so we will go to
and then we'll go to
the titania room and disarm the bum
because the guide says that pretty early
on and i think that's one of the big
things that i didn't do here
[Music]
what is the problem with the thumbnail
huh the bomb is optional
oh damn it okay then let's do something
else
[Music]
um
second class passage you did dad what's
really going on in the shoot in one of
the room into 10 years for uh the one
that has a few youtuber computer if you
could find a way to check the email
inside the computer you'll know exactly
what's happened with the ship
you could use the staircase at the top
of the well
to access her floor
you want me to check the
pc okay
hello no no no no
if you've not already been there i'd go
up to the promenade deck and have a
stroll
i've been there and i've killed the
birds and now i regret it
but thanks for the tip
i'm on the wrong side again
guys
don't give up yet
we are going to
get somewhere in this game trust me
hey
[Music]
okay
uh
yeah i think i saw a computer indeed um
somewhere
was it here
no open
ah well that's the bomb
the mega scuttler is now armed and
preparing to explode i think a fairly
big explosion so please stand back about
22 miles countdown commencing
now
1 000
i think i know
[Music]
about 40
well only another 1100 why does it need
to load every time where's the y 74
billion 146 million four oh my god
thousand eight l 31 k
i need
[Music]
nobody but you
can you stop talking no i'm singing
[Music]
nobody
i want nobody nobody nobody nobody
[Music]
presented to you by
the online guy
do you ever worry nobody
why is the alphabet so long
pasty and red-eyed
nobody likes a
remember this for life this is very
useful knowledge 188 do you want to
listen to this dude or do you want to
listen to me guys which one is it ah you
look a little pasty and red-eyed maybe
maybe you should get out a little more
certainly okay before i explode
the children in my school always used to
tell me i was too
one thousand too pale you're not gonna
tell me this now i'm out of school i
don't need to be told this kind of [\h__\h]
anymore i don't care i'm looking perfect
no matter how pasty i am certainly you
should get out before i explode in
you're repairing yourself
i'm recommending countdown no oh
i like this it's like i'm saying it
towards this voice right now
900 nobody likes uh
my mom is telling me this is john cleese
as if i was supposed to know who that is
now what is john cleese 983
monty python
and eighty-one
nine hundred
eighty it couldn't be a film
oh yeah yeah i totally know what you're
talking about
well that's me though closing down
countdown secrets i cleared an optional
riddle
but i can't get anywhere with the actual
is now armed and preparing to explode
this will be a fairly big explosion so
please stand back about 22 miles
countdown commencing
now one thousand
nine hundred say something about it
again
please shut up
960 if i go up here
i won't hear you anymore right 64.
[Music]
oh thank god
oh thank god the voices in my head
but i need to go back i think i was
supposed to do something down there
and the tune of pizza i just keep on
smelling tuna pizza
pizza
962.
it's
oh no i'm not doing that [\h__\h] again
960. oh
900. somebody make him shut up
958. okay what am i supposed to do that
here wait um
you'll find a computer
you'll find the computer you'll find the
computer find the computer find a
computer shut him up
is this is this a computer 53
yeah i think this is 951 yeah how do i
know
[Music]
the questions are hidden in the creators
room the passes are written behind that
free buster remember the name of each
bus in this position you'll need them as
a username 46.
you have to find a way to break this bus
oh i think huh wait my hammer wouldn't
work maybe
938 the guy tells me though
the passwords and all that should i use
them
934 there's a bump yeah but he keeps on
repeating that is not important
932.
931 uh but wait how do i get 100 30.
from uh
929. do i do the name first purpose
does this work 927
i'm a hacker
can i not cheat like this do i actually
have to go find it out for myself
um
right switch sideways
and remove the red pills
[Music]
i will break the lever in the koreans
room go back to the koreans room
karena's room
in the creator's room i remember a lever
what is the creator's room is it the
museum
that's the museum right
i remember
there being a leather 903
dude bye bye i'm not listening to you
anymore
so we can't cheat we already know the
passwords and the names but the game
doesn't let me cheat which i guess is
a good thing
okay
anti-hacking device
uh
creator's room museum was through this
elevator i think
i'm starting to remember
uh
i don't know
no
i don't
this was no stupid gritting please not
it this is the bar this is the top
wait how did we get there before
oh thank you
oh i think
i have 15 minutes
no way
uh
shouldn't i turn oh don't worry about
that he's just repeating he's he's like
he has a bird burn he keeps on
forgetting
wait where was that where was that
museum
[Applause]
again
um um um ah maybe maybe maybe
uh
no maybe
this is one of these rooms
no that's a parrot
don't forget to write
and then
oh god
that's the museum found it it was on
this floor and here this is
[Music]
oh i am destroying this plane am i not
i did it
i
broke this [\h__\h] am i supposed to like
pick something up no
the heads are just gone
yeah yeah okay go back to the grand room
pool lever next to the entrance door
that will blow away the bus now read all
those passwords uh
i think it really needs me adapt
uh-huh for that specific head
uh
and this uh-huh i did read it i have
acknowledged it
huh i'm supposed to be able to read
something here nah
and other
okay i have acknowledged it game i i
know
i know the passwords legitimately now
so
uh we go
down again okay okay okay okay
i love being in this like nostalgic
scenery though even if the riddles are
frustrating for me it's just about being
in this world in this game that's all i
need and i'm satisfied with that
so we're going back here right 73
800 uh
go back to the
computer in the fuse room login
870 uh which one was it not this one
the third room
eight hundred and sixty-eight uh-huh
straight straight come on
whoosh
did they add such a
weird effect 66
sup
all right 65
22 65
is the order not correct
hey
maybe there was no anti
cheating thingy i just need to know the
right order
is it then
[\h__\h]
bravostigan
[Music]
no no no did i miss right from bosticon
800 is he not repeating anymore
842.
i thought he would continue repeating
ah
eight hundred and thirty-nine ah [\h__\h]
yeah
eight hundred and thirty-eight oh [\h__\h]
you
is it legit
thirty-six
thirty how about blinty wurdle fruitcake
huh yes oh except for the w oh and the f
well how about poodle stomping knights
yeah keep on tangenting splattering
what did i do wrong
nobody
now one time
only another
1122 trillion trillion
274 billion 100
million 400 1 800. it's going to take a
while kfb
you can go in uh 700 uh to an idle
meeting break if you want to 576 to go
so you set a nice pace though
like
recommencing countdown now one thousand
how about blinky he's starting
uh splattering ghastly this no that
reminds me i meant to be exploding onto
122 trillion trillion
274 billion 146 million 401
881 trillion
973 billion
i'm getting tired of this
hundred 31
sixteen combinations to drop this one
right to another piece or get a like
here we go
what did i do wrong though
well that's me done closing down
countdown sequence disarming
have a nice life
but it says push button to disarm bump
is that not what i was supposed to do
huh and we just should just walk away
but
this arm doesn't that mean to
deactivate it
is it a trap oh
well then you can't blame me for that
how would i know that
i'm sure everybody makes
well there you go
[Music]
nobody nobody
nobody disarmed the bomb
okay now we finally have silence back
here isn't that beautiful now we can try
to figure out why the [\h__\h] my password
is not not working
bro
gone
what do you want why does say x is
denied it says login and read the emails
it will tell you about titania and the
important role of the parrot after all
this the parrot has a used i need to do
this otherwise i will not be able to
move on
eh
my mom says the pc is completely
irrelevant
this is optional too
oh my god why do i even bother with any
of this
what is optional what is not optional um
okay then if i don't do this the next
thing they tell me to do is fix the
elevator we fix the elevator
and then it says the parrot keeps on
whining about pistachios we gave the
parrot pistachios how could i bring a
pair to my room and we did that okay and
then the next thing is mixing a drink
how could i upgrade to the first class
easy go ask that deskbot again but this
time she's not that cooperative so we
have to talk to her
okay
maybe we have to let's go to desk but
but the lord well i'm trying i was
trying to get us some lore but the game
won't let me there's some anti-hacking
device or something installed
um
let's talk to the desk bottle
desk bottle
time for me to go to podcast mall for a
drive
what
what about me
you don't want to find out what we're
going to do with this starship
[Music]
upgrade please
oh there you are
nice to see you again dear isn't it
upgrade please oh i don't see why not
dear
the rooms are all empty aren't they
pity to waste them
and you've had such a difficult time i
said signed you to a first class state
room room three floor ten it said she
won't be that cooperative she was
cooperative first class beautiful rooms
none of those nasty laboratory things
there's the lovely restaurant the canal
with the love oh i'm the podcast you
mean you're just turning off the video
and just listening for when you want to
commune with nature a little did i do
something lovely place the arboretum at
this time of year and if you trust me
you can always
did i do something ahead of time that
she would have wanted me to do
i already fixed her earlier
wasn't you fixed the room beforehand so
she's in the right state
what did i
do it's a miracle
thank you
my pleasure
it's what i'm here for well we're having
an actual conversation
goodbye goodbye dear ah
good night thank you so much you deserve
a tip for that for giving me the easy
way out okay
oh
it says you go to the description of
just the two slides on your statue there
wasn't i just playing around i think i
just played around
until the setting on the side of your
pet turned to yellow
oh yeah yeah
i cuz someone said look at these
thingies here and i tried to make them
go up but i didn't know what what it
would do
ah there you go you sometimes sometimes
you do things randomly and they just end
up working out perfectly okay so i go to
my
i go to my room now let's go tomorrow
did you say which room which floor and
all that uh
uh stairs state room room three
floor ten
reach by elevator foot which i would not
be able to reach if i wouldn't have
fixed my elevator already
zoombi bantan
perfect
my elevator four we did some ground work
we may have struggled a lot but we also
did some groundwork
yeah uh let me call this elevator
what's in my eyes
oh well sir you and me both stuck with
our respective positions in life oh four
times
with a better view
but okay i'll take floor 10 i guess 28
will have such a better view but okay
this is my room no uh room
what was it room free
yeah
wow this floor looks nice
which one is it
these look nice but this is probably not
my room where does it does it say
which one my room is
like yeah
i don't know why i would say that
better view of space uh-huh i mean look
at that are you so pixelated
[Laughter]
i shouldn't be roasting this game it's
from 1998.
oh wow
that is a gorgeous room though
wow
gonna have a good time here
all right we are supposed to watch
channel four
[Music]
ah
i already did this apparently my mom
says i did it and the guide seems to
stay the same
go to this room floor seven elevator two
room three yeah we created the pattern
we were supposed to look at the channel
it would show us the pattern that we
were supposed to recreate and then we're
supposed to go there
mm-hmm
wow i didn't know i was doing all these
things
where is he where this was the elevator
is this the elevator no
are you the elevator
[Music]
i don't see an elevator
oh this is it it looks just like a
roof um
here we go
okay we need to go
uh
floor seven can we go from here no we
need an elevator too
[Music]
this room was founded in the tuck on my
100 000 yen hotel room
well
no i wouldn't necessarily say that our
room had uh two two floors even
so that's pretty impressive
i would say
uh uh can you take me to
floor one
top of the well
top the well sir from here you can walk
to your requested destination well it
wasn't in space but it wasn't hokkaido
and that's pretty comparable
ah elevator
two
elevator two elevator two
elevator two elevator two elevator two
elevator two elevated
huh
mommy says
mommy says i should put the parts into
titania
oh uh
but i tried that before she wouldn't let
me put any parts on her maybe i did it
wrong
well
let me go let me go to the elevator
first
[Music]
a memory
of the whole
starship um being like on the water like
uh um
uh like you know the whole floor would
be covered in water at some point i
don't know if i'm imagining things or if
that actually happens at some point
is this really where i'm supposed to go
room free well how will i know which one
is room free when there are no numbers
and it's not even in the right order
like one
two three
it's not even like that
what am i supposed to do here
[Music]
examine carefully at those four lights
at the center but am i in the right room
oops
[Music]
four lights in the center
i see the lights
[Music]
but maybe it only works in
one specific room
[Music]
maybe thinking of a different no no no
if you are in the right room backlight
will be loose uh-huh
thank you did you actually end up
finishing the game
then i will
always listen to you whatever you say
is this is this the room
is any
no
no that's not the right room
[Music]
those do we have to get closer
no way that's also not the room
what was there another room
is this a circle am i in the same room
as i was two seconds ago
in the same lobby
or all these different rooms
huh
when i went through that door
i wonder if i circled if i went in a
loop
someone break the loop
do it for previous rooms okay
[Music]
and they all look the same
did this one did this one now let's do
this one
ah
to the back of the room and turn around
what
wait
huh
isn't this one off
am i seeing things
to the back of the room this one
[Music]
welcome back to kiwama gets scared by
simple sound effects
this one is loose
call the bambot
uh however
bell bot
bellbot needed urgently bellbot needed
urgently you look like you could do with
some help maybe you should check out
some of the other first class rooms no
no no you'd have you have absolutely no
idea what you're talking about get the
broken
light please that's one of titania's
eyes all right how would you know
how do you know if you know that why did
you not always already give it to her
my true enemy sound effects
that was
loud you found the line a lot faster
than i did well i but you didn't did you
use a guide
i'm using a guide my mom and chat
three different sources of help i don't
think i earn any respect for finishing
this game if i finish it
do we have two eyes from titania now
um the guy tells me to go to the bar now
[Music]
to look at the tv and remember the
recipes you need to make that mixed ring
ring the bell and take that empty glass
on the bar i i took the empty glass
already when you went across your tv i
did crush your tv
i did that with the parade starlings i
did that but i didn't get any
stylings from that
um
i would tear outboard them
for the
lemon i have to go to the our
board do i really have to ask him though
a finished game is a finished game we
take this yes we did just looking
bellabot in the business you still have
to actually make sense of the guide why
the cybernetics have some credit no
no lemon yeah we got some of that stuff
on board you want to check out the
arboretum man oh thanks don't why does
he talk like that you're so obsessed
i can't tell a lie i was on the verge of
doing as you asked but the thing is i've
got a lot on my mind at the moment
personal problems i won't go into
details i like him you know how it is
can i maybe you don't
but hey can i pull that com port
and some of the software can i pull that
turn off your life
i'm gonna try
no let me i wanna pull your
ah
i wouldn't let me do it
i was probably sensitive for robots like
him
[Music]
restaurant would be better first your
mommy also told me to go to a restaurant
i think
restaurant i don't i don't remember
seeing a restaurant so far though
um
dude do you know where the restaurant is
means more
yes
top of the world it is stop top of the
world from here you can go
restaurant has its
own no
we're just in the first floor
where would the restaurant be
so we at least know it's down here you
have access now oh you mean it's in the
tube again in here
it's one of those things i couldn't go
to yet well one of those was this one
and the other one was that one oh that
looks more like a restaurant i do have
axes now
no shrugging no looking around no no no
no i'm not looking
i'm not looking at all the first class
restaurant
oh
first first class restaurant
second class normal class they don't
even get to dine in the restaurant
[Music]
nice music
hello
oh a key
i
i am the keynote
can i smash it
let me smash it please
no i don't have what it takes
so
we can look in here oh wow
what's up this dude
welcome to the most glamorous dining
experience in the whole galaxy are you
dead
may i apologize for the music
uh
it's all good i think the music is fine
do not prod me i want to help you i say
again do not pod me do not do not plug
me
oh i'm so sorry you could pull out his
guts no wait are you really saying that
i fight you
you were serious about that huh
all right i'll fight you is that that
and that
no this also no fighting i have the
advantage of you i think i have a signal
and a hammer have a cursor them for i
fight very very dirty i spit on fast and
soil myself
mommy says i have to hit him with his
own arm me on my achilles heel you sing
wrong my fun friend i fight with renewed
vigor
a hit a very palpable hit
no i hit you more and i will die here
here here on my very own jokes on you i
am a phoenix even if i die it's not a
problem oh that's maths
zones that smart did i i think i hate
him oh be gentle with me
now i have you never trust a fighting
waiter in his prime you're not even
looking at me submit submit
oh and a hell of a spot
to say
you are flagging now you will very much
indeed i press home my advantage indeed
ouch
i think it it was successful hit a very
palatable hit i hit yes
never wonder how often is that if you
please
fingers i bite you very much
you fight with a man who fights many
times i am fighting two times already
today you have to be very fitting these
days to run a restaurant
it's funny
no tools just cursor oh you brought me
on my achilles buttock this you must not
do it pains me very much
you must not hurt me on my achilles back
it is very on fire that i cannot wiggle
it away
do not part my achilles buttocks
[Music]
this is very monty python i die i expire
oh
how much defense and hp does he have a
person at the peak of his flexion and
elasticity my mom tells me to continue
me on my achilles body am i doing wrong
very on fire that i cannot wiggle it
away
ah how could i pass the metro the boat
keep on talking
until he gives up he still starts
complaining if you hit the right spot
after you defeat him we'll allow you
okay
if you will point my achilles buttock
you will compel me to give up
offer enough you win the day i submitted
owl i following the ghost my white flag
i yield to your superior bottom prodding
strategies
well if you like my butt wait until you
see my legs my kitty kick
oh thank you
vegetable
excuse me sir damn that table is busy
the table is busy
[Music]
this is so typical for restaurants
they're like
you can only sit in a specific table but
i understand it's okay because like only
certain tables are like set up that you
uh you can eat already and others are
just you know not set up and they want
you to sit at the ones where you already
set up the cutlery i understand that i
had that too when i worked in a
restaurant
and i had like 10 empty tables
all with cutlery there
ready for you to sit and eat but they
choose to sit at the empty tables that i
didn't even clean for example
yeah you're all talking about the dude
are you listening to my story
but i hate that they always go somewhere
else sorry about that i just did the
same thing hello oh another
you are boring to me now excuse me now i
prefer to hum
what is that is that some um
i remember hearing that somewhere
some countries him
i got a green party yo
um corpse are you good um
was was the soup poisoned perhaps
the french
the french have him oh god what makes
sense
[Music]
excuse me
bye bye
merci beaucoup
oh so i've since we got the part i'm
guessing we have to go to the fuse room
and and my
mom wanted me to put some parts on
titania anyway so
let's go and do that
uh
i think we need to go
back to here
we have all the fuses now we do yeah
uh there were two one two there
originally and we got extra
the green one and the
red one no blue one i'm not sure
not sure about the key oh yeah maybe
that's optional though there seem to be
a lot of optional things
not a problem
all right
i'm coming for you titania whatever
happened to you whatever i don't even
know the reason why i'm doing all of
this but
but i will fix you i will fix you
i
will
try
to fix you
right that's the lyrics right
that's a beautiful song
[Music]
oh can we use the arms for her for
titania
one eye
oh
whoa
you're welcome i'm giving you life i'm
giving you a purpose she has a nose
we're missing the nose
maybe we can take it from cuckoo senpai
this is an ear
we have another ear here
take it
she doesn't want the ear
what else do i have i have
i have ears
i thought i had more parts what is this
old factory center is that the nose no
what is that
what is this
no
what about this
why does she not take the ear maybe the
other side
no
that isn't that where your ears are
supposed to be
there's something about this ear
the sensato titania's ear
brute forces we have two you see i have
two
she doesn't want
either of them
[Music]
she's just built different
okay
we need we need three more of those by
the way oh dear oh dear
and the mouth and the nose
but we already uh
gave her the the
oh wait here
what why is that so the hitbox is way
too small
right you don't need those arms do you
wait a second look it says metro left
arm holding a key
how would how do i take okay we will go
back eventually maybe and use the key
okay
and
we did that and we didn't we come here
down down here for a different reason
until you have to to to to put maybe
perhaps only just maybe
put the fuse into the fuse room
although
i don't know what will happen if we do
that
let's
try it
use the fuses
on her
was holding titan or something and the
other arm was holding titanium something
oh
auditory center do i just how do i take
it do i drop
it um
do i just offer it to her
[Music]
i got something for you
it's very important
oh here
let me give this to you
let me give to you
no she doesn't want to have to separate
it somehow
um
wait wait go back
ah
yeah we'll go to fuse room again
and
put this here
what is that a
tree
put this maybe back as well should we
now uh one of these ones for the
ventilation maybe this one because this
looks like a ventilator a fat fan
should we just put everything in
and there you go
this
means that we turned on the big mommy
maybe
notice your yellow knob is still facing
up i think we need to put uh need to put
the yellow fuse back in and turn in okay
should i turn this one too
let me see
yeah i also wasn't done with the metre
of the boat
uh
because i have to go back up in order to
get the auditory center that's all the
tory center once okay we'll go there
later
um
or do i need to go there
first
um
[Music]
i don't know about this one we'll go
back
of french fawna's french was really
mmm
what
should christil
was really nice yesterday
her pronunciation sounded really good
but i can't really judge how much french
she actually knows unfortunately
maybe
maybe it was pretty basic or maybe it
was pretty good but she liked my idea
of just getting a french script from
someone else and doing asmr yeah i feel
like
you know a lot of people think french
sounds really hot
so that's a good business idea for fauna
isn't it
all the saplings can come and thank me
once it happens they'll be like thank
you kima for blessing us with this
amazing
blessed idea of french asmr you're such
a genius what would we do without you
right yes i i understand
where are we going we're going to the
restaurant
we weren't done there
yeah french does sound numb so i i i
haven't liked it i was feeling woo
flattered when she was speaking french
no looking around or shrugging please
i'm just looking at my chat okay is that
not allowed i have to otherwise i won't
get anywhere i'm lost without myself
class restaurant
at least the back seating and starship
titanic is nice
i mean the ones
the ones who do try the backseat it's
very confusing i know mind how you go
mind how you go
and so there was something here i have a
key do i just put this here
oh
open
oh i take
no
maybe not take
maybe do take maybe not but i have
different ones that i can put in here
you have one only
ah
decide do i have another one
no
i don't have another one
let me see
let's make it easy
the napkin taken up in the green shoes
and uh the other arm his arm is holding
the key to unlock the music and go out
and lock the box inject the cylinder and
replace it with the one ah no i have to
replace it not uh put it on the other
side okay
so put this here
um
why i don't know
then play it if your music is good
you'll see
ah
metal the boat will relax again in the
restaurant and he'll give me the
auditory center
but i already have it in here
oh well
ah
of course my music is perfect
because i fixed it beforehand when it
wasn't even necessary and now i'm glad i
did it
how do you like it
what did you say
so dumb yes uh
bonjour
uh
take and give you do not arouse me you
are boring to me now excuse me now i
prefer to hum
no need to ham i fixed the music for you
[Music]
give
me
titanius
auditory
center i do not wish to speak of this
titania it makes me very tense let us
speak instead of the delights of what
did she do to you
the many you mean with all the chicken
chicken i will check with this chef i'm
afraid so damn that due to a previous
passenger choice that selection is no
longer available
there's no chicken here and i don't want
to live here how can i live here with no
chicken
we need to eject the center one and
replace with ours
put santa one on the right side oh my
god wait wait a second
they can't appreciate idol music
now if we would let sparks run here he
would probably appreciate it
so wait
eject the center one
i don't see a i don't see anything here
replace with ours
ah
i'm i'm hitting my forehead right now
you know the graphics it it didn't feel
you know i didn't i thought it was you
know you know
uh
center right side this is always
is that ours
[\h__\h] i don't know
[Music]
oh
yeah the perspective were confusing
[Music]
tonight
it is so lovely and so long
[Music]
do you want your arms back
no
okay but we got the auditory
santa the music looks perfect
thank you for helping
it is quite a nice track i must say
myself
now we need to take care of the chicken
now i think um
[Music]
did we get the chicken inside the
parrot's cake
the chicken not the chicken the stick
because we have two different sticks but
they're not from the parrot's cage
i think but in that case try to distract
the parrot first with something he likes
hot chicken go get one get designer room
number of the parrot room first you'll
need this for the succubus later to send
the chicken i think i got the number for
that
go to the fuse room
uh and turn the yellow knob sideways
oh wait did that too
i think got the yellow fuse ah i left
the yellow fuse there
of course i did
goodbye goodbye
[Music]
oh god oh
oh oh dear
i left it there
i forgot
then we good really are we gonna get
some hot fresh chicken
oh dear oh by the way tomorrow is the um
unarchived karaoke rebroadcast i asked
uh
like around if anyone
in the live english discord has time to
rebroadcast it for me because i won't be
at home and you just have to play pre
play press press play
uh and then turn it off after like three
hours but
uh seemed like no one could help so i'm
gonna do it like a
premiere um
i think that should work i just need
someone my manager to
private it afterwards
but as a premier it's like a video
upload
rather than a stream but you still have
to live chat so you can still react
should i leave the others here
just says get the yellow one
i'm gonna leave the others i guess
i can do it sure sure no you're not
gonna do it because i would have to give
you my streaming link and that's
dangerous obviously
just yellow okay
does that mean we can rewind as well
oh
maybe but like i don't know if you
really want to do that it's an archive
card okay we already know what's gonna
happen so oh wait no i could have given
you uh whatever i'll keep it until later
i guess
i guess i'll keep it
i guess i'll keep it it's not important
to put it in right now
so i hope that goes well it should go
well
shouldn't be
an issue
um there's i don't really think there's
a difference
um
in in that situation it makes no
difference whether i'm streaming it or
it's a live premiere where are we going
next uh
oh yeah uh chicken we're gonna get
chicken
the designer room number of the parrot
room first
and go to the future and turn around
upside let's get the yellow foods this
will mess up the chicken dispenser in
front of the sgt restaurant yeah yeah
yeah which was only reachable from a
certain elevator right and then floor 28
uh it was elevator one i think
actually something i remember
[Music]
some sort of floor 28 no sooner said
than done
10 10 to the 3.0 miles will have myth
too right um
yes
but uh
you know it's in a seniority order
it will happen in an order of seniority
so i saw callie's tweet about soon but
um guys it's not gonna be anytime soon i
told you before
uh
yeah it will take a long time
um
let's just say personally uh i don't see
it happening this year for myth so don't
i'm not i'm not even excited about it
now because there's no reason to be
excited about it now
and uh it's only gonna be
for the main
default outfit
at least for now which i i don't even
use
much
most of the time i only use it for whole
talk except for today because it kind of
looks retro but today is an exception
so i won't even get much use out of it
but
yeah
it is what it is it is what it is give
me the chicken i want the chicken
wow it finally doesn't get sucked up
anymore
look at that
is that the right one though this is a
hot rather greasy chicken doesn't say
anything about sauce i think this is
perfect
i want some more oh i'm getting hungry
and we bring this to the chick did the
parrot no wait
the chicken gets the chicken gets cold
the chicken gets cold
this is scented chicken i have to use oh
my god you have to throw away the cold
chicken first oh my god
oh my god wait am i already like too
late
put chicken under nozzle that squirts
purple starting
[Music]
and use bar glass to catch the liquid
under the nozzle wait what nozzle
is there nozzle there
oh
i think i see it
but
no wait i didn't see anything
did i
that's a nozzle
[Music]
oh
it's probably cold by the time oh
okay
what
doesn't say anything about the
eww
yeah that's um
[Music]
it still says greasy only it doesn't say
anything did i ruin it though
[Music]
ah the glass
got it
[Music]
where's my glass
ah
huh
that's so weird
now we have
ah
for the cocktail
[Music]
ah so i don't need do i even need
chicken at this point
[Music]
do i even need the chicken but i need
the chicken for something you know
ah the napkin is too um
to get rid of any remains of the sauce
but there doesn't seem to be any remains
of the sauce
[Music]
how do i
a cold red no less cold but the succubus
will take it
i think
center chicken
say brothers
[Music]
you're disgusting as always just as i
remember you
thank you
can't receive i didn't give you that but
here take this
[Music]
i love it
when it's about chicken we can have a
conversation oops
i seem to have accidentally swallowed it
we need a hot chicken but then wipe it
okay okay
you're so picky
okay get the hot chicken
wipe the hot chicken
now it's some hot very plain chicken
there's so many different chickens here
hello do i need to send it to a specific
place though yeah it won't suck
i don't want suck i want to give you a
chicken
i love chicken
perfect
is she gonna
whoops
i seem to have accidentally swallowed
[Music]
no really
okay
[Music]
ah
i did that
[Music]
when you receive it at the pirate room
use the napkin one more time
i have to go to the parrot room save for
parrot
no sucks save a parrot
[Music]
should i do that now
uh
[Music]
because we need to distract
the parent it says try to describe the
path first with something he likes hot
chicken go get one designer room number
of the parrot room first get it uh i
think i have it go to the viewers
chicken chicken chicken chicken here's
the succulents to sand the chicken you
have to throw away the cold chicken
first use a succulents to throw away the
chicken
use your designer room number for the
parent room to set the destination
do i i'm so not sure if i ever did that
correctly before parrot lobby
it's the parrot lobby right parrot lobby
okay
but then i wait i need to get the
chicken first
[Music]
but he the parent wants a hot chicken
right you have to give him a special
chicken not just hot chicken use your
napkin on a chicken to get plants you
can then use the chicken at the middle
dispenser to coat it with mustard that
should do it hot chicken with mustard
yummy okay okay get chicken
[Music]
wipe it
get mustard chicken that's still hot
we got hot chicken coated in mustard
sauce
yummy
say hello
oh what's interested in doing is sucking
all blowing try talking to it
should i still send it
did you take my chicken
no
send
go okay
here we go
is this gonna work
now we go back
no if i sand it i think it keeps it hot
uh for longer
apparently according to the
guide at least maybe it's not necessary
but top of the well sir from here you
can walk to your requested destination
faster
uh now parent room
that's the first time i could go there
no time for that now
ah here it comes here it comes been
watching your progress with interest no
not very much
wait
wait chicken
recipe
i got it i got it
take
oh there it is is it still hot it's so
hot
add some chicken
what's that smell we got a chicken with
you have you got a chicken
bliss oh yeah
what's this muck on it what's this
mustard mug
i thought you want the mustard
it says messy fix pieces of sex
ah what the [\h__\h]
did i do wrong oh
wait was i supposed to first push him
off then give him the chicken then take
ah
i can't take it now anymore
it's too late man
the [\h__\h] happened
move yeah yeah i was trying to move him
to one side but
that little piece of [\h__\h]
tricky bus now can chicken then dangle
on the side
why does the guide say it is it is it
is it trolling me the guide says it's
one monster chicken but okay it doesn't
matter i'll grab his perch when he
starts going for it
dangle the chicken on the side
when he starts cooking
stop the canoe
not no
are you kidding me
i got my chicken and then just disappear
rude
oh well sir you and me both stuck with
our respective positions and all i get
is an empty stomach
right away sir
[Music]
put the mustard or the sock thing ah
cause
ah
cause the robot
will eat it
if i don't put the sauce on it because
he only likes it without the sauce but
if they're sausages
take
wipe
sauce
okay chicken acquired very hot i'm
burning my fingers no that's not true
how could i
suck
and phoenix i don't burn my fingers go
go go
express delivery please
we have a very important vip customer to
serve
likes to uh eat a lot of chicken
could waste a lot of money at kfp
top of the well
oh yeah
kind of uh acting like a karen about the
sauce though
i'm just trying my best here okay
not even tipping me yo
top of the whale sir they don't
understand the struggle
in this business
okay parent room parent room [\h__\h] where
did i go
parent room
here we go i'm on my way no oh the
barrel of chicken
the bear
thank you
okay i take chicken
now we don't mess this up again
wait maybe we shouldn't be too close to
you
come here come here come here come here
go away stop it stop it
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Applause]
it looks the same
i'm being
used i'm being abused from the parrot
this is bird abuse this is phoenix and
kfp abuse we have to do something i told
you this bird is evil
i think instead of tuna pizza i'll be
having a parrot pizza tonight
one more time
i guess we're gonna have to get him on
the left side
it does say in the guide try to loot the
parrot to the left most part of the cage
but why why why it looks the same why
does it have to be left on
i was trying my best okay in a very
stressful situation
chicken
i'm a pro at this this is a kfp fast
food simulator now
simulation game
ripe no grease
mustard ghetto
simulation
uh no i want you to send this
okay
here we go i don't even have to tell him
where to send it anymore nice
[Music]
okay
mama tony was framing you for this yes
for this very moment
i noticed my heart now this man yes sir
top of the world it is
[Music]
i will do that thank you
sir everybody will thank me once i've
killed this stupid ass bird
thank you kiwa
so noisy like a [\h__\h] pc virus
thank you for freeing us from the
suffering
okay your stupid ass bird what's that
smell have you got a chicken with you
another one come here
come here
is this a chicken i see
love it
are you [\h__\h] [\h__\h] careful stop
look i told you go away go away you want
to perch on something purchase yourself
stop it stop it you can't push me off my
perch you think i'm some sort of marvel
godwick you could just shove off my
perch you think i'm just a model petrol
i'm a pirate
p-a-r-o
t
i unhappy you you
person
i am so
mad at this piece of [\h__\h] parrot
what do they want from me
what am i doing wrong
[Music]
it's tough boss it is
what is this stupid ass [\h__\h] bird
doing
i already have the item what what item
no i need the stick this is the stick i
need the stick you cannot take this
because the cage is locked shut i don't
have it
ah
i have this stick but
they mean the stick in the cage
it says couldn't get the stick inside
the parrot's cage inside
yeah yeah yeah
i know i have sticks but this is not the
right stick
huh
it's a perch but isn't that the perch
from over here
wait a rather long stick approach we had
two sticks for like the whole time
but this is from outside they mean the
inside stick this one see it gives me a
grabby hand i need this one
right
doug what do you say
use the hammer to beat the parrot
i was trying that
i saved before dangling chicken the rod
you want is blue so you don't have it
yet
blue
this is not blue
oh but maybe once i have it in my
inventory it like uh changes
uh into a different item like it
happened before
i
do i really have to do this again
let me save by the way
it becomes blue and i don't know
okay okay okay
we're doing it one more time otherwise
maybe i need to reach quit
i don't get it hey
wait let me read it again um
try to load the parrot to the left of it
again after he grabs the chicken quickly
get the stick was i not fast enough that
was fast
rather quick enough to do that
this is safe and restored facilities we
have travel
oh i should save before i give him the
chicken
ah
safe's coming huh
really we have to stoop on that level oh
there's a some sort of floor floor
what guy
[Music]
has to lean over but it does immediately
disappear right i'm not doing that wrong
like it doesn't just
eat it slowly
i don't think so
[Music]
my shift just never [\h__\h] ends it is
endless
we've never done it kfc you know it you
know it
[Music]
this is so accurate this is just like
real life kfb
this is how we send your food to your
doorsteps you're welcome
if you could just hang on a mouse
[Applause]
[Music]
so
training video
yeah you can see it like a training
video surely here okay there we go we
saved
this [\h__\h] bird will not get the
better or the best of me i'm not sure
what use how you say that
hello
hello do you feel the bear you can't be
proud
for stealing so many chickens does that
make you happy
make you feel like a better bird
uh wait excuse me
i did i forgot how to work with you
there we
go and get it
i will take it thank you
i'm feeling slow right now but okay here
we got the chicken it's
hot and very plain
you don't deserve it but come over here
here
oh
you're gonna have to eat it cold if you
act like that come back here
[Music]
never want to see you again
oh
holly [\h__\h] luna
[Music]
oh yeah baby
oh yeah
it only took us four tries or five tries
and
we were about to save scum but we didn't
have to do it after all
let me save now
wow what a emotional moment for all of
us
this is what i call a karen how can i
help you today
not at all thank you but
what should we do next we didn't do the
cocktail yet i think we'll have to do
that
okay
we're going to get the last titanius
part i'm going to do something wrapped
in robots voice
ah you mean you mean that boat over
there
[Music]
this might be a clue for both parts oh
well i think i understand
around i i understand a thing or two
about rowing now
do i use these arms
no
oh wait
oh my god
where are we going
this is so fast holy [\h__\h] i'm not even
rolling
like a
speed robot i can't roll that fast holy
[\h__\h] that must be some
buff arms ruin that boat
okay we are somewhere else now that
looks exactly the same i am confused
what
eh why are we here
is it
matrix
[Music]
we don't need to talk about what just
happened
[Laughter]
left and right oh
wait a second
left oh
hello
rubberneck
what
are we gonna go somewhere he's singing
what can i do for you
[Music]
change season to winter
says guide
but
i don't know
oh
this is not gonna fairytale please not
touch the plants
i want to touch the phone now
but okay let's change it
oh
[Music]
oh can i have this this is a pepperoni
pepperoni
winter oh beautiful can i say spring too
though i want to see spring
wow
the poland do you guys have a pollen
allergy
i don't think i do but when i lived in
japan everybody complained about pollen
allergies all the time
everybody i feel like japanese people
are
uh
like i don't know genetically
inclined to have pollen allergies
nope nope nope
i've got it it's bad
sorry for your suffering
yeah my mom says uh i'm close to the end
and my mom says i need a
lemon so let me that's right yeah for
the cocktail i i saw there was a lemon
necessary indeed
that's right let me try to grab the
lemon
in summer
[Music]
lemon tree
i'm turning my head
up and down
how do i grab it
maybe i need to access it from somewhere
else
[Music]
it said somewhere something about a
lemon
[Music]
thank you
ah because it would already be summer
uh originally it was set to summer right
and where the hell is the arbitory i'm
sorry we'll do a different mission now
lemon long stick
what i can just take it with my stick
i don't have to go to the arboratorium
or what it's called
let me try
a long stick probably not the perch this
is the perch
it's just a stick a wrap a long stick
keep
give
this one
suddenly
[Laughter]
that looks so perfect that almost looks
like a tennis ball
[Music]
it looks too
perfect will i be punished for taking
the lemon i hope not
nobody saw that right
now buddy
[Music]
ochoa
there's something in fall as well
[Music]
and oh yeah we need to set it back to
winter too oh wait i can take that too
oh that's how i take that
and then
winter
[Music]
i would have completely ignored that
part because i thought if i can't take
it with my hand i can't take it at all
really for these riddle games you have
to think
in a different way than you would
usually do
[Music]
oh it's you again what is this part
oh i can't look at that what what is
that a hose
i have
a hose now
do you want the hose
no what you're saying is beautiful i
don't know what's wrong with you singing
the guy says something is wrong with
your voice but i think it's beautiful
[Music]
you want arms
no
let me
[Music]
see think he's singing italian right
open chest chest
chest
there's another one here
i'm sorry you cannot enter this pillar
at present as it's frozen shot now
[Music]
i'm
sleeping
oh yeah all right
[Music]
it all sounds beautiful
i don't know where the issue is maybe
the other one
can i no no can i check the other one's
volume too
[Music]
i don't think so i have to deal with
this guy
[Music]
what
to hold them down at the same time
because otherwise it would not all
he stopped singing
this is so weird this is just
very very weird
and
wait what did i get did i get something
from that
because i made a ding everything stop no
can i take them back
yes
and he just stops like that
i accidentally go there
i can take off the mouth oh it's a
titanius map what
[Laughter]
oh and it turns blue dabba dee dab and
die titania's blue double die that wendy
daven
[Music]
can i turn it back to summer so i can go
back though
i think i have to
she's blue dabbing
double die double double dive
oh
i like spring can we keep spring
i wonder if it matters
if that was green i would die
what what's the problem why do so many
people dislike green huh
can we go um
back please
i'm sorry i stole your colleen's lips
i don't hear you
what are you trying to say
this is so brutal
this is so
brutal this game brings back some
memories yeah for me too i mean i never
played it completely when i was small
but i watched my mom and my sister and
my brother everyone was playing it
uh
do we have all parts we have the speech
center we have the mouth we don't have a
nose though
maybe we'll get the nose from the
cocktail who knows who knows
but we also have the auditory center are
we
i think we got all the centers
maybe or still missing one
um but do we have all the ingredients
for the cocktail
hello you checked out all the elevators
yeah repellerator
yes i have checked out pretty much
everything thanks for asking uh oh wait
i could have just there was a pellerator
there could i have gone directly to the
bar
probably
also yourself
do i really have everything we're
probably gonna have to go somewhere
again because i probably am missing
something but what would we be missing
at this point
i hope
i hope we have everything
wait a second barbra
if all the ingredients to the bar boy
barb
approach bought
hammer dispenser
use it to get the ham
hammer we got a hammer
passengers will kindly behave themselves
on the journey mind how you go
i'm an order i am a well-behaved young
lady okay i'm getting bored with my feet
got everything though
no one likes your parents
it is a very goofy adventure yeah
i i am i think it's a very weird game
choice on my channel um very random just
because of nostalgia but i hope you guys
are somewhat enjoying this weird ass old
riddle game
so
what do we do with you cocktail can i
just ask you just as soon as you fix
this loop
this loop yeah what loop
what loop are we talking about
uh
[Music]
i just i will just give you the
ingredients okay
you will get from me
this glass
don't you dare drink it before i'm done
with my cocktail
was that okay he just wasted my cocktail
where's the where's the lemon
where's my oh there it is
lemon
oh he's making it in his head right okay
okay
is that all you need i don't have
anything else
uh
i will tell him to get the vodka oh i
thought of starlings
[Music]
as i was saying last night's game give
me half a chance half a chance i've got
a bottle of finest signature i am such a
hacker
yeah you have to
go
i think maybe the cocktail's name is
pureed starlings or something like that
but you tell him to make that but then
he goes into a loop i suppose and then
you tell him to get the vodka to make
him stop no
no i don't get it it didn't work
it didn't actually work what are you
saying
uh last night's game
bye pets
got a bottle of the fun sticker and
vodka right here and whip us up a shot
for you as soon as i finish the titanic
tip till later
don't tell me i have to get all the
ingredients again
you better not be for real those
i'm just missing one probably
don't call you
hey
i'm getting bored of my mouth
take it off
oh
is that not what i typed
that's what i typed before what's your
view of facial hair i wonder
we sent alfred after seeing some
write-ups and tash galactica you know
she never looked back once it was fitted
didn't look forward much either come to
think of it
of course it's not so fast
i am confused
[Music]
vision center please
certainly just as soon as i finished
mixing this cocktail starling
um
vodka
i've got this i'm getting bored with my
feet
it says
how could i make the bartender mix the
drink bring the bell and give all the
ingredients well did i do what what are
all the ingredients let me
[Music]
mixing a drink
uh
ah
pyramid stylings lemons
a hammer
do you want the hammer
no
i have all the ingredients these are
starlings i already got gave him the
starling juice
did i waste it
are you gonna give me an empty glass
again
the starling's already dead
no it's in his head already
he got the vodka
yeah
i think so i told him get the vodka i've
got a bottle of finest signorian
sell point settings is this in here is
it where is the vodka bottle
what
vodka you see i don't know much about
alcohol but like i suppose vodka is very
handy in making uh
making the
cocktail require service please ring the
bell
what did i get from the crushed tv a
crash tv
does
did he just give me
an empty glass again
what
[Music]
where's my crushed tv where did that go
here
i see you
when it comes to casual violence
like crushed ice
he just takes anything at this point
how is that an ingredient for my
cocktail
is
there's infinite stalling
oh
[Music]
oh can we ask for vodka now good
question no [\h__\h]
i don't think it resets
because i
couldn't get another tv could i lovely
to meet you too get the vodka ah
i'm afraid i wouldn't have anything of
that nature here oh
now he doesn't even mention it anymore
okay
for me that means i need it all again
[Music]
i think
i think it reset which means i need a
lemon
last save oh no we're not going there i
feel like i stand up straight that would
be a waste i think
we are gonna go
here
because
we're gonna go to floor 28
and i was safe next time before i make
another cocktail
the top of the well
load oh no my last save was after
after the bird did i save after the bird
but
but then i did the whole thing
please with the boat mind how you go i
don't feel like doing that again no
we're fine
but i need another tv
you and me both stuck with our
respective positions in life
hello here's my settings going floor 28
immediately
or is it lazy to tv
something that will not be reset oh man
oh man
i should have saved more often i didn't
know that it would be interesting
necessary to do safe scumming in this
game
so we have the glass
at least
oh
chicken first because apparently you can
only get this maybe there's like a
sensor there's probably a sensor that
only activates
if uh there's chicken underneath it yeah
yeah it senses the hotness of the
chicken
the thick hot juicy meat welcome but
whilst
yes sir top of the world it is
[Music]
the typing part of the drink is rough it
took me a few tries
uh
is that
does it need to be like perfectly
capitalized because i think i didn't do
that the first time yeah from here you
can walk to your requested destination
okay but i give him the ingredients
before i do
anything else right before i type
anything
uh
lemon
lemon lemon lemon lemon
i don't know about the crushed tv though
i don't know if we can do that but no
way that i can soft lock myself right
that's an easy
one another one of those easy moments
where you can make a mistake
so
i hope not
thank god i still have my stick
yeah the ship's layout now is pretty
familiar to me
lemon please lemon
i think you still have them don't hide
them from me
hulk
which one was it that gave me that lemon
which one was the magical
the chosen one you would have chosen one
or you
do i have to poke it with this side or
with the other side does it matter
i don't know what i did last time to
make it drop
[Music]
no i'm not gonna alone
no
or should i because at this point we're
no no
no
am i out of lemons
i'm trying a dangling one
it doesn't want to
one doesn't want to
[Music]
it's a fake lemon tree
you only get one lemon the ingredient is
no reason no [\h__\h] way
uh it's more like the order of typing is
purity is to tell them what it is and
get the vodka
then get the vision center
okay
okay my lemons
cycle the limbs oh
oh
cycle them gently
gently
this is like
you know the massage therapist told me
there's a lot of emotions in the butt
there's also a lot of emotions in this
in the lemon
you don't want to surprise it you don't
want to startle it
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] it's not happening
change
maybe we need to reset the season again
[Music]
oh cycle the seasons oh
well there we go we did it i don't know
if i just need to poke it or if i need
to swoosh will swoosh move it around the
screen
this is the big one i want the big one
oh man
[\h__\h] it
[Music]
where are we now
what are we doing boats is that what i
is that exactly what i did immediately
afterwards
it didn't work
didn't work i admit the fate
we know what to do it will be fast
hopefully
[Music]
first of all well you're still gonna
have trouble getting the lemon maybe
unless it's really limited i don't
believe it
i don't believe it
here we go
i don't know maybe it's really limited
no wait don't go out i still need some
more stuff
upset
but we can't take the hose whatever that
for whatever that hose is for
[Music]
i need to get the thing from the robot
yeah yeah don't worry don't worry i'm i
have it on the radar i think
see it's that easy
no way
if it's certainly that easy for me maybe
it really means it's limited
[Music]
uh
is that all
oh yeah and then leave it at winter
right
okay stop stop stop stop stop
it's lagging
my pc is too powerful
my mouse and my finger also
calmly
set it to winter
there we go
oh beautiful
beautiful keep it like that
keep it like that
just like that and then turn around talk
to this dude open this up put the arms
there
[Music]
one arm
and the other um and take the lips and i
think that was it
i can take the arms back though
and i switch it back
i switched season back
so i can
[Music]
uh
go back or i could also take the
elevator thingy here
let me go i want to be set free
yeah the sideways train i was thinking
is uh
the same thing
see now at least i still have my tv i
think we would have maybe had some
trouble getting the tv again
um calling
in
to the bar we go
i hope we have everything
ah doesn't matter
it's okay
yeah important self-saving i thought if
you guys you know would maybe tell me to
save the game because of the chance that
it could crash but hey there we go the
game didn't crash themselves at all yet
until now
so respect for that
good
good job is running perfectly fine on
steam and windows 10. let me out how
long is this going to take
let me out
an order mind you how you go i'm getting
bored with my feet all right i think
that'll knock him from under me don't
wanna
make a mistake i'll save one more time
cocktail one more time
so it says start by giving him the
ingredients but
is there a specific order with the
ingredients too
[Music]
again are you enjoying the facilities no
no because you're making it too
complicated
[Music]
um
wait i'm trying to find there it is
okay
uh i give you glass
you like it don't you
i give you this ah
lemon
yum yum and a tv you want a tv too don't
you
squeeze it
that sour taste makes my taste buds go
wild
yes
tv
when it comes to casual violence
wait he said what when did he say what
ah
hello again
this is such a deja vu moment
oh my oh my
should i start with giving him the tv
again are you enjoying the facilities
[Applause]
cocktail maker
the video i'm watching has tv first okay
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
and the lemon okay
no mistakes now ah
lemon lemon
garnish with a hint of lemon
i'm getting cold okay and now is the
moment of truth
what's this
uh pureed starlings that is
well done get the vodka
on
why is it so complicated
how frustrating
[Music]
right i know
i'm such a genius you're drinking dead
birds that's so good
[Music]
this is why i don't like drunk people
this is why i stayed away from them
oh my god he's getting so aggressive
there we go like titania's vision center
what do you mean
[Music]
it says here tell him to get the vodka
he'll make the drink when he's drunk
grab the titanius piece in the bar i
couldn't because it was loading
get the vision center
right away
no it's okay
even though he's not drunk anymore he
gives it to me now just that simple
okay you're gonna you were gonna make me
mad right there for a moment i was gonna
punch you in your face but you're safe
you're safe
no he's still drunk look at him moving
i wish i could move three-dimensionally
like you
show off my nice moves
again thank god can we save now
because i'm scared
that
something will be messed up again
okay
i think we may have everything now
do we have the nose did we give her the
nose before
nose
uh the nose i think came from the
broken light fixture
all right
[Music]
i know we didn't get the nose yet
it says here with the with the holes
that we already have go back to the
paragraph and stick the hose to the
light uh it's not the broken light
fixture in the uh hotel room it's in the
parrot room okay
let's do that
and then i think and then i think we
might have everything
mm-hmm
no looking around or shrugging please
smacking me dizzy anyway i just want to
close my eyes and let it happen
the top of the well
almost done yeah
i have no patience for riddle games it
seems
this is very confusing ladies
this lady at least
uh at least she admits
the truth the game is very confusing
hello on it
he's gone he's just chilling somewhere
where is the broken light fixture
broken
which one is broken this one is fine
these ones are fine
this is the parrot room
this one's fine
huh
stick the hose to the light
that's right don't listen to me you
think you could just ignore me because
i'm a parrot well remember all right
around comes back i mean goes around
wait but that's the only one i can
actually touch
i say don't fiddle with that you
wouldn't just ignore my i said don't
fiddle with that it's broken in terms of
not that there's no light but that
there's just something weird coming out
of it oh you wouldn't
i'm gonna enjoy this
stick the hose to it they say stick the
hose to out there we go it's like a
snake
i say don't fiddle with that i didn't
you wouldn't just ignore my advice if i
i said don't fiddle with that you
wouldn't just ignore me i said don't
fiddle with that how do i know
if i was a half-mast weaver i'll let you
talk
are you done talking
hurt you
i put no one over i touch it
i said so little with that
you wouldn't just ignore my advice if i
was a plush crested j would you no you
wouldn't you
watch him blow the hose
he's not blowing it fiddle with that
lower house ignore my advice if i was an
olive peach face love bird would you
ah turn it on the water
oh
what it
wow that water is in this room whoops it
[Music]
now i can just open it okay
okay
that's not very nice i'm missing one
step
oh
uh
wait there is okay if someone said don't
go nearby just go go there
because i'm in a broken light in the
parent room
insert the other end to the succubus
oh
uh-huh
first
yeah
are you any good i can't do me any good
to the point do i still have it in the
inventory not show nuts either
what good's anything that is totally
devoid of chicken or bestop chain nuts
what oh
that's
ah
the other end of the
mm-hmm
[Music]
the other end of it so do you
maybe you want to blow it huh
maybe send
no you stand by just
just blow it please you like blowing and
sucking don't you
i know you can do it
[Music]
connect it ah
something's happening there it is oh
that's the nose it does look like a
mouse
all right baby i think
we may or may not have all the parts
finally assembled together
what is going to happen
let's try it out i think i think that
might be all
but don't get your hopes up yet
don't get your hopes up
uh
okay
oops
titania
i am here to fix your body
you can thank me later here are your
lips
very kissable lips
here is your nose oh so
three-dimensional it really gives you
that edge that you need and beautiful
here is one of your thingies
here's another center
and i got one more for you
ta-da
you happy all safe
don't you have everything you need now i
can take it off again i got to use
i got your nose i got your nose here you
can have it back
okay
and the perch
perch
perch ah the blue thingy oh where is it
where does it go
here where does that go
huh
intellect where does it go ah there it
goes
people people testing testing initiated
oh that feels good um cleaning my ears
this is uh you're cleaning asmr
it's working no
you happy
do i need to wait for something
the door behind it will be open and
you'll enter the bridge i think i think
class
i think okay i think we're done
and then there was one room right that
uh we couldn't open before
but this room would open
she's not happy with it maybe she wants
a different kind of nose
she wants a certain celebrity's nose
sorry titania we can't do that
you need to be happy with this does this
matter
do uh
does this get
arranged automatically
oh wait a second
oh this could perhaps very much matter
the colors oh was there a hint for that
somewhere
ah
i will mix
and try
oh
we have we have a hint
i see
blue lower left
oh
oh it's close enough
it's not the windows xp logo
no way
remember
remember that real nicole this is really
because nowadays the windows xp logo is
just white
oh my god she's
alive is she gonna kill us all now i'm
terribly sorry about the parrot
oh you should be no really
i know how it must have been for you oh
really
you also sometimes feel like eating it
you're creeping me out
so typical of leo
so clever he could never see what was
actually happening
everyone used to say of him
nobody likes a smartass
he never saw how unfinished the ship was
that it was secretly being prepared for
scuttling
scuttling even i didn't realize till it
was too late
and then
they took my brain to pieces
thank you for restoring it to me you're
welcome my mind is i'm safe i think i'm
afraid what do i get and the ship has
been wandering
come on
leo has obviously been in a complete
state
and probably jumped off the ship when
you got onto it leo
poor old nitwit
he's completely besotted with me
we should find him i suppose
should we really and you'll be wanting
to get off home of course
yeah i think she's evil she wants to
destroy earth doesn't she probably i
mean she looks like someone who would do
that but also the other people in the
ship are kind of weird and crazy and
wanted to manipulate her and sabotage
her
okay is that open
wasn't there a door behind me
did i switch places
there was one door that was uh i mean
the middle door
that was closed yeah this this is it wow
good morning captain welcome to your
special i am the captain
oh my god this must be a racing game now
[Music]
oh very nice
hello
where do i go
meaningless wheel spin stop glow
cruise
and something a bit
uh-huh
[Music]
clear sailing ahead
okay
only going somewhere with this
oh
oh oh
moving at the speed of light
ahoy
where are we going what is that what is
that are we going to crash into it don't
crash into it
safe
i don't see my controller anymore
it's kiana is not in control anymore oh
there we go there it is are we done
spinning that does this even do anything
oh
insert destination skyscape here
oh i have something like that what about
the chicken thingy no if you don't want
it is there anything we didn't use yet
this no we never used this but this is
this shows my destination now i'm gonna
go home
wait no i was thinking right for once i
didn't look at the
look at the the guide for that one okay
it took it i was going from my inventory
was thinking there must be one item that
i haven't used yet right right right it
must be something that i haven't used
what is this
should i put something in there too the
hose
no
um i think everything else we've already
used so i don't know what this is
how do i use the helmet
i'm cooking everything
pizza books
stop making me think about tuna pizza
glasses what glasses
i don't remember having glasses
these are and these 3d vision glasses
with the blue and the red
it doesn't work
you could leave behind the picture
and get soft
what
but you could probably play until this
point right with no problems
oh i would be so mad the one thing in
the very beginning
that you leave behind will
bite you in your butt at the very end of
the game well that is pretty mean
huh third icon in my pet
ah what
navigation controller
oh
now this little thank you oh my god i
see so much
holy [\h__\h]
set destination where is my home
wait
no no no here no what the [\h__\h] here this
this place this place
don't break it again please
google are we going
i hear
going sounds
did we go
it doesn't look like we went there we
have not arrived at i think
i'm a dragon
or
i set the destination
yeah okay and then i go to the wheel
and
and then we
go
wow fancy lights this is an idiom
concert
idiom festival
oh
i'm an astronaut um astronaut
uh that was really loud
there someone there
but we're so in the universe what the
[\h__\h]
are we home yet hello
let me go here
wait a second
according to the guide that's a
navigation user for photo from home and
it's not use your pet to activate the
control
yeah
on the screen you have to draw a
triangular position
three points of the stars based on your
photo
wait you mean these stars
eh
try clicking the stars
oh yeah
[Music]
like
what kind of triangle we're making
and do i just um like let's say let's
say we choose
one of these
and then
what was that is that is that one of my
spots
oh
oh oh
oh oh this is difficult to control
that's not
so sad
they're very difficult i can't is it
okay if it's just blinking oh oh oh oh
hot cold
is this okay
baby
uh
l to lock oh how did you know that what
the hell
oh
[Music]
and then
how about this one is that okay
or should it be more in the middle maybe
this one
down
wait we're moving in three-dimensional
space now
[Music]
okay one more
this one
maybe
where is it
oh i saw it
so
okay
[Music]
let's go
can i take off the helmet
i think so
and
here we
go
here we go
oh
is it gonna work is it gonna work
please please please
pray for me i would just want to go home
to my kitty cats and my tuna pizza it's
working everything's coming
[Music]
is that earth
that looks yeah good afternoon my name
is
you probably know that i'm sorry about
what's happened to you i'm even more
sorry about what's happened to me
you have lost a house i have lost a life
and a dream oh [\h__\h] you may not care
about my life and my dream well i don't
really care about your house is that
douglas building the ship was my dream
and now that dream is over
all i want is the love of a good woman
and also
a fishing rod
thank you for restoring titania
i know she isn't real well she's real oh
is it his dream woman
so to be honest i'm more inclined to
place long-term faith in the fishing rod
by the galactic laws of scotland women
let's get fish is now yours
there is nothing like her in the
universe
i hope you manage to sort i will ride
that ship as for me
as you say my life's work is done
and i've gone fishing you've gone
fishing goodbye priorities
priorities
wow we saw douglas adams the man himself
at the end i think that's the end
i'm gonna get credits
credits
oh ending sequence oh [\h__\h] my house oh
oh am i just not gonna live in my house
anymore just live in space
i guess i have my own luxury hotel all
to myself six stars
with a lot of chicken
lots of chicken dead chicken only but
it's food
noise ship
nice boat nice boat space
boat a fishing rod in exchange for a
spaceship
a fair exchange yes
we didn't
be
i say we because i barely did anything
yay
finally
without your help it probably i wouldn't
even have been able to do it in 24 hours
i probably would have absolutely lost it
great quit
we always work together we do we're on
days
wow
that's the first time i ever see the
ending of the game
i always saw like little small bits of
it
because of my family playing it but i
never saw the end of it oh my mom is
my mom is happy to see the ends too
[Music]
yeah we
we have um
had a lot of help from an online website
from the chat and from mommy from my
sister even even my sister gave great
advice even in that short moment she was
in my apartment
[Music]
gaming family proving its strength once
again
biased based
yeah i didn't rage quit thank you thank
you
hmm
oh the beautiful music and what is that
why did i
what in in my brain why did i have a
memory of the whole ship being on the
water
flooded
i really feel like
there was a time when you had to walk
around in the flooded starship titanic
i'm not talking about titanic the movie
nook
maybe it's because of the the one area
with the boat
maybe i just projected that onto
everything else
because there is water there there is
water
it was a really fun and unique game
yes it was it was a it was a weird game
choice but it was um interesting
[Music]
and
i often mention like you know old games
that
i remember
uh from
when i was younger but those are all
almost all of them i cannot play
on my channel well this was one of them
so i felt like i had to
give it a try it was a good game choice
you think so there's not many riddle
games like
not real games what do you call them
thinking games on my channel
but we need to train our brain right
there is yeah i think the same publisher
published uh the really old turok
game
uh i'm not sure there's apparently more
than one turk i i saw it and i'm not
sure which one i played
um but i don't think
we'll see that on my channel anytime
soon it it doesn't look like something
that interests me anymore nowadays i'm
more um girly now i want more girly name
games
yeah there is an original on the
nintendo 64. but i i don't know which
one
me and my brother played
i don't know
[Music]
yeah i there's like certain games that i
enjoyed as a child but that doesn't mean
that i would enjoy it still today i
think um this one was okay
but i i'm not sure oh it just closes is
that how games
used to end
they just
closed out of nowhere
okay
not
[Music]
was that how it was back in the day
movie watch oh i would love to watch
that i've heard a lot about the movie
but i don't think i ever watched it i
just know the other 42 meme yeah yeah
that is the perfect number and all that
yeah yeah i don't think i watched it oh
did i
let me look up a picture hitchhikers
uh
guy to the galaxy
oh
are there more than one movies is there
an old one and a new one
wait
is that uh zoey dejanelle
in acting in that movie or does she just
look like her
yes
there's an old tv series oh
what netflix is that is it on netflix
the
the movie is on netflix
yes it's her
billboard is in it oh wait that is
billboard that is billboard on that
picture
oh i totally want to watch it i like
those actors i only know two but i like
them
and let's watch it
hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy let's
watch it as a members only movie
sometime
oh that sounds like fun it's not it
looks like a funny movie and i know that
the book is like a genius book
yeah yeah yeah
oh it sounds like fun i don't wanna you
know do too many movie watch alongs uh
on my channel i don't wanna you know
spam movies but this weekend we're gonna
um play that new game that i was able to
finally
organize
the new members only games
game tell me if any other whole life
member plays it by the way as a members
only stream they might not even notice
that there is a new members only game
that we can play they might not even
notice but if anyone plays it let me
know hey
i'm i'm curious
yeah
yeah i'm glad we went for that like
there's uh other games too like you know
uh
wind waker for example
wind waker i played when i was younger
but never finished by myself
uh and we're gonna do that we're gonna
start win awaken next week but i have a
little bit of a problem
this is the thing when you buy things
secondhand i
um
i went on like a second hand website
and i looked for um preferably a bundle
of the wii u and wind waker but i
couldn't really find much
um but
anyway so i found this one person who
was selling
uh the wii u and some extras and blue
blah blue and i think the wind waker was
pre-installed and i was like yo can you
um can i order this and you have you
send it to me
and
they were like yes but then
two days later
they wrote to me
uh and said oh somebody just picked it
up uh in person so
i'm not gonna send it to you anymore i'm
sorry it's gone
that happens so often like with these
websites you reserve something and then
just give it away because someone just
comes by to pick it up faster than the
other person would have come
man what is this layout sorry sorry
sorry
i'm
oh
oh i'm trying to make it look good
let's make this big
this is this is the layout that we're
chilling in right now okay
wait so
yeah but it's okay um there are so many
other wii u's on that website so i can
even get it from there but i also found
a store that sells it i think
i think it's probably also secondhand
maybe but i'll i'll get it until
the stream don't worry there's more than
enough people who want to get rid of
their wii u's out there because the wii
u is just
not a very
liked console is it
it doesn't really have much going for it
not many games
that people would want a wii u for sorry
i'm just kind of roasting the wii u now
[Laughter]
[Music]
i love i love my wii u it's an emulation
beast oh as an emulation thingy
mm-hmm
isn't that gamecube with an hdmi adapter
easier um see i originally said i want
to play wind waker on a gamecube
um because i love gamecube and that's
where i originally played it but then
everybody was like that um
saying that the wii u version of it has
a nice
uh remastered that really helps
so
yeah i'm getting that
um i don't feel like reading super chats
today are you are you guys okay with
that
i will read them uh let's see what do we
have on sunday
we have a member stream and something
else
i'm hungry i want that tuna pizza
i really want that tuna pizza what am i
streaming on
on sunday egg painting oh okay okay
i will be able to
read super chats after that i think but
not for too long because of the member
stream but i think
i think it will be fun worst case you
know there's not much piling up because
it's just today
um so we could still read it on monday
or whatever
um
yeah yeah yeah i just i just
my mind my brain is thinking of tuna
yeah yeah yeah oh by the way yesterday i
made cut
shirt bullets again
um
yummy shred bullets with lots of
lingonberry jam and and also i bought
some cherry cocktail tomatoes
uh to add to my balcony i need some
veggies too right not only fruit so yeah
and also i'm adding some strawberries
too
um
yeah yeah i'm getting all the all the
yummy things from my balcony i'm so
excited
i'm so excited yeah
oh
and
since i'm recently so open with you guys
about um what i'm doing music wise
i realized that i have to start
already planning for the next
song the next original song
uh
time wise because of time problems
um
even though i haven't even like
gotten like i don't even know when we
can release the upcoming song
but i already like i contacted the
person who's gonna write my next song
and um like already
slightly vaguely talked about the
concept and i had to figure out the
whole timeline because i want
that one i want to be a 3d music video
and um
i want uh
i want to also perform it
at my uh birthday concert so you know it
has to be ready it also has to get a
choreography ahead of time so that's
when i realized oh
i need to start planning the next song
already
so
yeah it's
yesterday i spent like
a lot of time planning things and and
trying to sort things out and trying to
get things off of my to-do list and all
that uh maybe you saw on twitter i was
trying to get things done
and it took up a lot of time yeah i was
like my mind was everywhere and even
genma was like holy [\h__\h] chiara you're
today you're throwing so much at me huh
i was like yeah but um also on another
note uh this needs to be done and uh
also i was thinking we should do this
and that and then at the very end i even
threw some random new idea about members
content at her write the whole
wallpaper thing
i'm so sorry gemma
we can we can work it off one by one but
yeah i just i just realized there's so
many things
that
i need to think of i need to be taken
care of and
i need to do things i need to do things
um yeah but
it's good that i
did like thought of all of that
yesterday because i i recently there's
like some moments where i feel like
uh i don't want to be
moments or like hours
days where i feel like i don't want to
be productive because like i'm having
like a little bit of a problem with
finding finding a reason to be
productive as in you know like a
like
uh is it is it
is it
i don't wanna i don't wanna be him
espresso depresso depressor espresso but
um
yeah
i've been questioning some things
recently but but but one cannot give up
one cannot just say oh
it's i'm not no it's not worth it or it
makes no sense no you have to
there is no meaning in stopping don't
stop don't stop just go your own way
stopping is worse than
fighting and struggling
even if it doesn't look bright
either
my voice are very scrambled today just
like scrambled eggs
yeah but i'm what i'm trying to say is
i'm i'm yeah i'm fighting my own
shrinerhood yeah i am finding myself
finding my own
um
lack of motivation and all that
my thoughts
um no i can't slow down i cannot it's
already slow like
the whole
process of making music for me is
generally already
very slow because i have to i can't
i can't do everything on my own i have
to
you know get so many people involved and
that makes everything very very slow the
whole process and
and i want to do so many things
um
yeah
i want to do many things but
i also feel like
um
it's very difficult to make them happen
so
so sometimes i have these moments where
i'm like blah blah blah why am i even
doing this
but then the other kiana that sits on my
other shoulder comes out and she's like
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] make use of your time make it
worthwhile
you shouldn't regret
not taking action uh one day so
do your best
and
put in all the effort that you that you
can
to not regret it later on yeah scrambled
egg spots
scrambled eggs original music yes yeah
well the upcoming one is a very
different genre but the one after that
will be probably more like um
just
general something for the general
audience again go in the safe route
again because i'm not even sure how you
will like the upcoming one
um so yeah i wanna be safe with the next
one also because it's gonna be a 3d
music video so i really want to be safe
that um
be sure that it's it's gonna be
something that people will will like
mostly
um
are you interested to see how different
it will be
um i think
i think it will be quite different and
that is kind of risky i know but i
wanted to try something different
no matter if it's
even if it flops
i don't care
i wanted to try something different to
have some variety in my discography
discography this choreography
disco disco party party
yeah the upcoming one will be very
different
i hope you guys will like it it's it's
uh taking shape it's starting to take
shape
taking shape was the name for a sec oh
that sounds cool the way you capita
capitalized it i'm actually not sure i
have like a a working title for the
upcoming song right now but i'm not sure
about it i feel so cringe when i think
about
what title to go with i've been thinking
for it for it about a while but i can't
think of anything good i think and uh it
makes me feel so cringe when i come up
with some
words to make it sound like a song title
but
it just feels awkward whatever i come up
with
oh i'm done thank you
a kiss for myself how do i kiss myself
i'll kiss my hand
[Music]
thank you kiwawa
thank you so much you're such a lovely
person while you work so
i'll go get the pizza
yeah i have to sleep a little bit early
today i think too because i'm gonna be
uh gone for most of the day tomorrow and
busy busy um with mommy
pre-celebrating easter i guess but i'll
be with you guys for
easter sunday
um can't wait for the next song thank
you
yeah so if you want please
watch the unarchived karaoke tomorrow
it's the second run for everybody in the
sea timezone
golden hour
yes yes very
much a banger karaoke
with oldies but goldies
so
worth a re-watch maybe as background
music even
yeah and while i'm gone tomorrow make
sure to also stream cinderella
yes it's on my channel now new song
cover please check it out
[Music]
i know
who here
saw the game that we played today
for the first time today
who says it was my first time
me me hear me me me
oh oh so many
so many
it's always a
weird one right but considering it's
wow it
did look i think
back in 1998 that must have looked so
good
that must have been like be a beautiful
game
um
very polished looking i think
yeah
when did sims 1 come out
sims one
two thousand two years later
wow but i think you know those those
those years
uh
1998 and so on were probably the years
when they
were
like developing
and making so much progress with like pc
gaming
that everything was changing so rapidly
so quickly i can imagine
yeah great gamer times yeah every year
must have been such a big jump from the
previous year like wow
oh [\h__\h] we made a big jump in graphics
damn
and then next year same
i would have guessed it pre two thousand
yeah
yeah yeah
me neither to be honest
i didn't think it was that old holy [\h__\h]
2002 was the most insane year why what
happened in 2002
what happened
i'm not ancient
it's my mom's favorite game not my
favorite cream afterwards
ah
gamecube 2002 when do i go or what
no [\h__\h] way
oh my god
there is four years in between
starship titanic
and winnebago
wow
i mean the art style is sure but like
that's a whole different world
damn
well that's really shocking to me right
now holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
at least
the whole console generation yeah i
guess it went from 64 to
gamecube was that nothing in between
from nintendo 64 to gamecube i mean
besides handhelds
yeah ps2 xbox damn damn damn
yeah wow crazy oh my god well gaming
history is a very impressive uh
i feel like you know when you look at
games now like at the really really good
ones of ps5 games and all that that are
like made to impress i feel like looking
at them i'm like not sure
how you can
even improve the graphics anymore
especially for games who are supposed to
have
non-realistic graphics like more like
cartoony or comic styling graphics
uh
like how do you improve that without
making it look semi-realistic and so on
you know what i mean
and then even the realistic games out
there like they already look like like
how are you gonna improve that even more
they look like they picked
how i mean you can definitely pref um i
guess uh improve like
the
um
how to say
livestock uh
what's the word
what's the word for that
frame rates yeah i guess
performance that's what i meant yeah
performance of games
uh
and flashiness and like effects and all
that
um
but i don't understand how how how much
more i can't imagine how much more
graphics will
change
[Music]
but
maybe in five years i would look back
and be like
wow five years ago graphics were [\h__\h]
okay guys i'll leave you guys now
and in german we selfie doesn't thank
you guys for watching hope you had some
fun today
i used your brain so much i'm so sorry
for
abusing your brain
[Music]
it was a group project okay
okay
it was a training for kfp um
a group outing or a group exercise for
all of us to improve our teamwork
yes that's what it was exactly
and also a brain exercise for my own
brain
didn't use it much though
ah
today no super chat oh tomorrow and the
day after tomorrow okay
[Music]
there's no eye in canopy
exactly
yes thank you for the very helpful
kfp members
i really appreciate you i would have
gone crazy without you
thank you very much everybody
hopefully doesn't have a great night and
have some nice dinner
and enjoy yourself wherever you go
i love you guys love you very much uh
happy easter
happy easter if you celebrate it if you
don't celebrate it then still it's a
cute
cute um
holiday eggs and bunnies and chocolate
so cute
oh [\h__\h]
there we go
[Music]
do
you