[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
kick it again
hello
nice video thank you
indeed it is cute yes I must agree
title on a guy I don't know what's the
title for today
[Music]
see I'm not even 100 sure what we're
doing today there's a bunch of things I
want to do but I'm not sure what exactly
we're doing so it's difficult to uh
decide
welcome everyone though
the block game
yes I'm playing the ball game
I am still at the exact same point where
I left off last time
uh I have yet to clean out my apartment
as well in my apartment my am I
inventory
um uh also my mind is a little bit
preoccupied because
um there is oh you know what I want to
do right away I want to find bills uh uh
uh I can't put a gunpowder farm so I was
saying I was saying uh I'm getting a
um
at my door in somewhere in between the
next five to ten minutes
yes
it's ironic that I said I've yet to
clean out my apartment
um because yesterday I actually did
clean a lot of my apartment but anyway
no yes
[Music]
so where is tell me roughly where is
Bales uh gunpowder farm that would
really help me out here
okay
oh you guys know everything do you guys
do anything besides watching all of the
whole live English members Minecraft
streams
do you do anything besides that is it
easy to see is it small is it big
like this is a trail Farm is that the
Gunther the farm
is that what a gunpowder Farm looks like
I saw this a while ago I was like I
don't know what this is being built into
and that's it
or are you answering to yes I don't do
anything else besides watching Minecraft
streams
is that it
is
[Music]
creeper farm
this is a creeper funnel this is the
creeper what exactly is the creeper
phone how do I get the gunpowder
oh do I go down here oh
more please
foreign
[Music]
I
hope it's okay to take
it's okay right I can take it right
she can have my paper from my paper Farm
in exchange
I have a lot of paper
[Music]
foreign
AFK at the top for more okay okay after
my stream
uh I will gladly AFK
but now we gotta do stuff I'm gonna go
to my place and make some more fireworks
I still have to figure out like I tried
the other day
even looking at a tutorial
I tried how to uh make the more fancy
slash longer lasting or stronger fire
looks but I failed
uh I think it was like put more
gunpowder in there for you know
different effect
but it didn't work I just I don't know
what I did wrong I don't know oh there's
the cards I have too many things in my
inventory uh
[Music]
I'm not wearing my armor
there we go there we go now we have
space
sun is already setting longer fireworks
is a waste
okay but I still like uh a million years
ago okay not even that long ago I was
told I told Callie I'm gonna make fancy
fireworks for her uh Carnival
um
so I want to figure out how to do that
too not because when I use my fireworks
literally nothing comes out of it just a
few like white sparkles there's nothing
Amelia years ago
Express oh Muna you look beautiful in
the Moonlight
there's no moon only a sun
okay never mind you look beautiful in
the sunlight but Moonlight would have I
don't know been kind of like kind of a
cooler thing
fix the damages what what do you mean
damage
what do you mean damage where has there
been damage
[Music]
there it is
guys tell me when you get sick of this
song I have a different one as well
I'm home
[Music]
I should get my yes Infinity
one question uh because I have mending
on this one was it that mending cannot
be combined with infinity and that's why
I don't have mending on here
it's about to die
I don't want to die
how to repair what do you need wood what
does it need
what because it's made out of wood no
how do I repair it
use I never bow you're right I have this
useless bow I'm just useless Bowl yeah
let's clean it up let's clean up
now so now so
oh nice oh nice oh
why am I recently always on zero levels
or maybe now because I had something on
I had the The Mending Hot Wings on
all right makes sense you can put this
here we gotta clean up
we have to clean up
uh oh
[Music]
I don't want so many things
but this is my stone box maybe I should
put it in the stones into my stone box
let's see if I have space we're starting
slowly right now but we'll do some cool
stuff later I think I hope
I reckon
hmm
urata
did you guys see her summer
um thingy stream that was so
so funny
that was such a good stream
amazing no what was it she had like over
the summer
she had her fans send in all kinds of
random fan-made things related to her
but it was not like fan art but like
really really all kinds of random things
like it literally could be anything like
um there was someone who
uh made a famicon
um
what am I doing I just want to level
famicon game with pecula Senpai in like
two weeks and then there was someone who
remade her opening in Excel sheet yes I
know that sounds like her but she did
the person who made it did like an
amazing job
uh I want to kill something to get exp
maybe what if I kill squids does that
work
um in Excel Abby made it an Excel like
and then there was one who was uh just
driving a motorbike
and
dressed kind of like pickles and stuff
do I go to PPP again God damn it I don't
see anything
oh wow
so pretty thank you now I see you do I
got exp from you
did I get exp
I don't think I did
and then there was this one
there was this one video where
um that a fan sent into her which I
don't know why that was so funny to me
but
um
this dude he made like a water bazooka
or something
and he was wearing bunny ears to make it
somewhat pecula related I guess
and he had like different strengths for
that bazooka
yeah what a rocket launcher and then he
launched it and the first time it was
okay but then the second time he
launched it the water was like blasting
all over his face and his his bunny ears
fell off because of the pressure the
force of the water and and he played
replayed that in slow motion many many
times and I don't know why but that was
so funny to me I peed a little
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm sorry
that's a joke of course because
Idols don't pee right so that's that's
not true obviously there is no
no expression that makes you understand
how funny it was
hey I didn't pee at all I don't pee
peeing is something that humans do not
Phoenix's what am I doing I just want
exp like a little bit come on give me a
little bit exp someone somewhere but
what if I maybe if I mine some wait that
don't work I'm not wearing gold what if
I mine some some
points
or if I've I have two five wait let me
make fireworks first and then I fly over
to PVP
okay okay go get some paper why do you
never go to the Japan zoo what kind of
question is that why do I need to go to
the Japan server I don't need to go
there at the moment
I don't have the need for it excuse me
[Music]
paper
what would I get banned on Twitch if I
were on Twitch if I said that that I
a little
would I get banned for that
[Music]
no I don't know
I don't know why you guys are
overreacting so much
[Music]
okay fire works now how many do we want
oops I want to make some fancy ones
how does it work again to make the fancy
ones
[Music]
I don't know we'll look at that later
let's one of our missions today is to
make fancy fireworks all right
I I I I oh there we had papers didn't
even need to
[Music]
BRB one second
oh
[Music]
foreign
oh oh
I'm back
I didn't die
I'm alive
believe me
don't underestimate me I don't die that
easily
I'm talking so much that I keep losing
track on what I wanted to do so if if if
the subway
goes down here and then turns around
immediately so the track starts here
then goes that direction
at some point
it goes even right your left I don't
know let's find uh PPP go flat ah
left okay thank you you guys are smart
every time I'm not sure like where to go
it is however somewhere in the snowy
area like very close to the snowy area
so is it somewhere here
okay
a bit more a bit more
[Music]
oh and there's a village I I know
there's a village there
am I already off track
hold it
what is this Ah that's the village I
think
yeah
I found it
now we gotta go to the top right
this is so difficult
nice I'm here
now there it's not night yet though so I
can't sleep
[Music]
anyways
this means she's on the en server right
now right I greeted her in the beginning
but I don't think she saw it or she's
AFK
foreign
[Music]
oh I did think that it only shows the
people who are like on the same
um server at the moment oh okay okay
yeah so she was at least streaming
before I started I don't know about no
am I good to jump down already also is
what is this oh
it looked like a bunny from up here
people
[Music]
should I should I go
I was still thinking about going Google
I hear zombies
I hear them
[Music]
monsters I'm on my way Sasuke I'll be
okay
apparently later today Ina is gonna be
streaming live foreign
[Music]
Minecraft
yes I don't know if I'll still be
streaming by the time she joins in I
might be reading super chats I don't
know we'll see how it how it goes
give me some levels I don't have
anything
uh they're both mending I want
levels though how do I
ah
I need a weapon without mending
um
ah
weapon without mending a punch
oh There She Goes
uh weapon without mending
[Music]
crafted iron swords
one one iron I'll punch
Falcon Punch
Phoenix punch
nice yes give me speed please give me
level one
come on come on come on
I'll gently gently kill you killing me
softly with your Phoenix punch Kill Me
Softly I don't know how the song really
goes
and okay oh I'm already level four let's
do one more
that wasn't too bad and my ax has
bending two I can't use my ax
but but if The Mending weapon is already
full does it then go
oh wait oh yeah wait when it's full it
would at least go to me now
let me see let me see if I'm if the
sword is full on mending it should go to
me come here yeah
yes okay
okay
I learned something
[Music]
so should we use this or go home I'll go
home
that's all I really wanted a few levels
to fix my bow
[Music]
how to get home this way
this way
my what
I don't understand you
thank you for the Super Chat though uh
I'm lost I don't know where to go
[Music]
this area is weird why is it shaved so
weirdly
water wow fascinated verb this is
okay so pretty did you just see how my
shadow was on that mountain but let me
show you
from far away
see look at the mountain did you see my
shadow there did you see
did you see my shadow I'm lost where is
home home
uh what's the coordinates for home again
300 or something like that and minus 400
or the other way around
uh
what is that
does this ever happen naturally
this
300 350. I'll have 300 300 300
[Music]
Sky Road
take me home
grass old Trident fun
new Trident form
oh
I feel like I'm close somewhat closer
yet so far away
Sky fruit
no I'm not just building something like
that I'm like far off again why did I do
that
this way what what did I get oh my
fireworks
I'm violence
[Music]
okay we gotta chillax for a moment
oh oh what is that ah
here I could go to the end right now get
a new elytra let's go uh
oh oh oh
yes I've been here before
I'm surprised they're still alive here
wait 300 okay wait but the other way
this one
how come I'm so
I'm sorry
oh I see something familiar
now we're talking
hello
oh
see last time we built this with with
ninity doesn't it look beautiful with
shaders at night
[Music]
looks good guys dancing
beautiful
[Music]
blursed
have you you don't know what's beautiful
apparently the standards of beauty of
your culture are just completely messed
up if you don't think that that's
beautiful
then what is what about me huh you think
I'm beautiful
yes you do don't you
then something's wrong something's
messed up in your head
more fireworks
[Music]
um
how much
this much okay
so now we're gonna repair the boat
wow already so productive
um so I've been thinking about today uh
we could either work on Phoenix then but
that's boring for me right now
well we could
fly to go to the Mesa by Omi
I think that's what we wanna do right
[Music]
now I don't know where exactly it is
people have offered to tell me
I do however know the direction and I
think it's okay for me to know that
actually you know what I'm not even that
sure anymore I think it was when someone
told me on Twitter
that if I go from the spawn point
only self
[Music]
that I would find it eventually maybe I
hope that's correct and I hope my my
memory is correct
um
[Music]
I'll need yeah I will indeed need more
fireworks maybe even more than all of
that if I use it up but yes to correct
with that that is true it could be
extremely far away I don't know how far
where is it no
fireworks
wouldn't it be nice if you oh that's a
lot of if you could find biomes in there
[Laughter]
and Japanese Mesa no no no no no how
many times do I have to tell you guys my
mind
what's the word bye
principles my principal
anything that can be accessed in the end
server will be accessed through the en
server I will find us our own mess up
Road our own by wrestle by All Me
it's been a long time gold from me yes
should we bring we should bring shelter
boxes right so that we can like
um bring a lot of materials back already
correct yes correct okay so we take this
orange chocolate box what's in here
not so much okay we'll empty this one
too then
[Music]
um
so two maybe two should we bring a third
one
foreign
[Music]
but today we're just gonna try to find
it and let's see how long that takes us
and how many how many times I'm gonna be
distracted Midway through and do
something else
uh I'll try to not have that happen too
often
not too often but it will definitely
happen sometimes
a bed yeah yeah well we're in the middle
of uh preparing right now
um let's bring some extra gunpowder and
food I have do I need more food
here more food
um not the bowl
stone color can go somewhere else
how about here
and did I not already have one or is
this from my I think it used to be there
trade melons for something yeah probably
I should I should get proper a little
bit better food
uh
um
I could get some more
uh oh
potatoes but I I think and in the spawn
area there's more potatoes more baked
potatoes
meat would be better here but I don't
really have oh wait there's a couple
more I don't really have
proper access to
that meat currently you know I don't I I
might I may have a lot of chickens but
that doesn't really mean I mean anything
ah we should take one in the chest right
uh
um
should we bring some blood I don't know
why
I probably don't need wood
if we need wood we can get wood but we
could bring a boat
[Music]
smart you are smart where's my
self-touch pickaxe
wait this this one is silk touch oh yeah
Ryan I don't need to use my iron silk
touch pickaxe anymore should I bring on
like a normal not yes yes I should bring
a normal pickaxe as well where's my
other normal is this my other good
pickaxe I think I had one that's even
better than that
[Music]
where's my other
bring more you think that's not enough
maybe it is not enough might never write
one yet where is my never ride pickaxe
maybe in my house my other house
[Music]
uh oh ah there it is panic attacks
okay
bring a bed yes yes yes chill chill one
moment one one after another
let's bring this
crafting table
um should we bring a saddle maybe later
we want to like I don't know if we don't
want to use too much of our
um elytra we could go get a horse right
um
golden helmet for a five minute should I
bring something to make a Nether Portal
but should I make the Nether Portal
there right away and then search for get
the coordinates and then um already have
the coordinates from the Nether and like
later on I can just make the yes yes
smart but obsidian obsidian obsidian
obsidian uh and and the thingy that
makes the fire yes yes so we can we can
put the obsidian in the uh never an end
never entered and I I was energized and
sometimes I don't know anymore I think I
had obsidian yes I have oh I have 61
crying and 12 normal that's enough right
how many do you need
how many
[Music]
what bring more shocker boxes more
shelter boxes more at least eight ten
ten is minimum
I'll just bring it all and put it in
there in the chest okay
um
so let's put obsidian here
[Music]
um
we don't
need this if I have a look for glowstone
remember I have glowstone here
[Music]
um
I don't need both of those shovels and
put one in here
[Music]
we have to prepare everything properly
bring the gold handle yeah it's a good
idea right
it's a good idea to bring something
that's gold
to survive in the never later on we can
bring the bootsies
and a bed a bad bad bad bad
foreign
take the bend
should I put the bed in for now it's
fine to just carry around normally I
guess
okay then put these here
I'll just leave this stuff here it
doesn't really matter torches lights
torches in a bucket torches torches and
a bucket torches and a bucket
set the spawn here yeah for now but I'll
definitely later on change the spawn oh
well
and do I have Twitches here no
which is here no I did have some calls
somewhere
I think in the other apartment torches
no no torches
let me get
some wood shots
[Music]
just a reminder that we love you I love
you too please one and after one after
another guys one after another there's
so much to prepare so much to do we can
make uh two more shulka boxes
um perfect
what do you guys say I forgot already
torches torches I know I have enough
water buckets here there we go
yes
oh that's all my dark oak I prepared so
much dark oak for that uh Shrine built
[Music]
had to find that biomi first
okay shulka box
and one
and two and then
stink
why oh
thick
and then torches
okay okay
looking good
then we put a store shovels and entrance
yes yes wait if it would open all it was
not opening
okay ah it's not open because of the
shulker Box above
did I not open it before
I feel like I opened it before stick
I dropped some torches
did I really I did
[Music]
my dad
no that's not what I wanted I one
uega
foreign
just because I don't wanna get rid of
the shulker Box above
okay so the empty sugar boxes four at
least for now should be enough we can go
back there anytime once we know where it
is
and
[Music]
um we kinda needs
probably even low Rockets according to
you guys
now what do you mean what do you think
guys let's put a saddle here
and
and some torches
here that's probably too many torches
too like we only needed to Mark like the
Ariel I think oh well
some of that here
Elite
a lead I don't think we're gonna bring
anything home
did you get online do I have flint and
steel somewhere flint and steel
[Music]
no no
flint and stale nope do I have Flint
somewhere
do I have Flint do I have Flint
uh
I need to organize my stuff a little bit
better
I feel like it's already so well
organized up there it is but still it's
never enough anything useful here
maybe some iron
should I bring some iron
just in case I need to build something
out of iron
[Music]
handle bring an anvil name tag why what
four what four
no no I'm not gonna waste my totem on
that
[Music]
although if I'm flying
with my if I'm flying with my Elijah and
I you know because of the area that
we're not loading in too fast I bunk
into something and I die in the middle
of nowhere I lose all my things of
course that would be
messed up so yeah I guess I have to hold
it
hold it inventory which one was it
[Music]
hold it in the left hand okay
I have a feeling I have a bad feeling
about it somehow don't know why
uh so flint and steel we have bucket we
have
Zelda's protection prevention
foreign
let's put this somewhere else
although
I don't know
let's put this stuff somewhere else
so we have more space later in case we
need it oh no this one stays this one
goes
um
wet and steel
why
okay whatever whatever you say guys
where is she going I'm going I'm going
to find search Mesa
by Oh Me by all means I will find it
always bring a book
just just bring a bucket just when in
doubt bring a bucket or add alright
alright should I fill it with water more
food yeah that's right okay let's go get
food
foreign
lots of food could be a long trip
uh let's use the spawn food there's so
much food there I don't want to really
use the Watermelons though because it
doesn't fill up at all
let's maybe get into the
[Music]
I mean there's baked potatoes over there
right
foreign
[Music]
what's what's I always wonder
um how do you like pick up like what
what is the combination of keys to pick
up like everything here
what was that again I want to learn it
shift
no
double click
[Music]
oh can I take it off
I'll share my um
my findings later on oh what what's this
no no
no don't want to waste
I can't open it oh wait it's not it's
not a box it's not a box that was
Bamboozled I was betrayed
okay I understand
let's see maybe we have some more good
food here
baked potatoes here too no
[Music]
oh no no oh
I didn't see anything
pumpkin pie is good right I think
pumpkin pie
does oh
fill up all good bunch of Health
I'll get that is this enough
we can always Midway through I don't
know kill some animals
foreign
if you find the title somewhere please
report it
and then we can call out for the title's
mother to pick the title up at the
reception please help
food and energies yes yes yes yes
[Music]
[Applause]
I love that so much
anything useful here
I don't know what I'm looking for
there's a bed random bed in there bucket
of water here let's switch
uh
[Music]
-huh I need to fill up the food chest
again sometime but now we have all that
food at the spawn point so maybe it's
not even necessary
anything else wait let me fill up my
current hunger with the Watermelons that
we have
should I bring water milk
if something curses me
is that smart
no need yes milk no no ah thank you
[Music]
oh thank you
why not
[Music]
okay
okay what else what else did I forget
something
did I forget something
a little bit more fireworks would be
nice though but I'll try and do not
waste too much oh thank you for the red
super chat uh Stephen W hunt thank you
it's a promise right promise
promise me promise me
I have my second pickaxes it's here
and I have my ax and I have my dick on
me and I have a good bonus with infinity
so we don't need too many arrows
actually only one let me put back the
sticks
I think that's everything milk in the
show girl no no milk is now just for now
in the in the end of chest
lock your door check if the gas is off
sleep by the way
if Santa's Imma die of laughter if you
if you laugh at me if I send us
you will indeed die because I will kill
you
just kidding I love you don't don't
laugh at me though
don't laugh at me
what is that one torch doing there
you haven't
okay I think we are prepared
I think
I think we are prepared
um
wait let me make one more tiny bit of
fireworks
as much as I can a keto docket
school okay now we got one two three
four five Stacks five Stacks come on
now I hope I actually remember that
correctly though with go south from
Spawn
I hope my memory doesn't uh play tricks
on me
does anyone know
why the original one I don't know people
say that's fine
foreign
[Music]
I don't think a map can have all of that
on its on its um
oh my God don't don't tell me the exact
coordinates and not that I could
remember but uh so where is South though
where where does it show again facing
north east south
so we should go this way
is this this is the spawn point this
wait wait wait
from
is that from the spawn point that's
somewhere like here
South
follow the Blue Line how do I follow the
blue line
oh
oh oh
[Music]
follow Blue Line oh
I don't know how that works
[Music]
if I look on the ground it's easy to
understand
[Laughter]
okay let's go
this could take a while guys let's go
[Music]
do we need rules like
um how many times am I allowed to stop
in between if I find something
interesting what's the maximum of stops
that I'm allowed to make
[Music]
what no give me a few more times three
times let's do three times but but if I
stop for you know other reasons not for
exploration
um that will not count for example I
would like to uh land now in order to
change the music to be honest
let's land on the mountain
[Music]
oh hello
hello
wait I want to take a picture
[Music]
Hawaiian uncle
come closer you were all so close just
now why are you like no
cute uh wait I wanted to change the
video
[Music]
okay for a little while let's play some
Lo-Fi
some real low low fat
the headquarters of the resistance
trying to take over the city this
is always the sheep and the chickens
guys it's always them
who planned their resistance we've seen
it in Chicken Run
simply
[Laughter]
where is South
here is south
is the bgm so loud I think it's a bit
too loud no what do you what do you
think
I know
[Music]
it's a bit loud
I'm flying right now
wait uh uh I need to Tab out in order to
change it
now will you have to deal with it for a
little while
[Music]
it's not gonna be anytime soon
we're so far away already
Uncharted lands are ahead of us guys
as always I like to be
oh
pumpkins I like to be the first one to
find new things on our server like the
Elijah
but that was um kind of painful
no don't look don't look Kiana
don't look whoa big ocean we could go on
a boat for a little while
should we
let's see how big the ocean is
I'll go
[Music]
save my uh Elijah
how to place boats there we go
yeah I'm gonna save some fireworks and I
mean we have mending on on the hot wings
but yeah
[Music]
oh
isn't this nice now I can't lower the
volume a tiny bit
[Music]
okay I lowered it by five percent
yeah this is a graphic bug from my uh
shaders
[Music]
right there
should I like take screenshots for the
coordinates
I won't know unless I uh what it is
though later on let me uh
uh
wait
[Music]
that's a looks kind of small
okay I took the I took the coordinates
this does not count as a stop because
[Laughter]
it's the range
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
come down
I need to make a curve around and I
think I'm scared I feel like I just I
just I just it kept me in because
[Music]
drink milk
now I have to drink milk I'm not going
to the wrong direction
do I have to drink milk now oh my God my
arm hurts because of that scream
oh mine's lower okay we'll we'll drink
milk once we're off the
uh water this is where
[Music]
this is this is south
right
is itself okay oh my God it gave me a
heart attack
[Music]
my hot right arm
hurts
am I going around how is that possible
[Music]
it's facing south
we should be fine
I don't I don't know honestly though if
me going south will really eventually
lead me to
uh the message
what is that
is that ice thingy
it'll wipe out eventually okay okay
I'm going diagonal now
Loop Too Short all right I'll change it
one second
my audience is not happy with my uh bgm
all right all right
[Music]
no that's
I put the wrong name on this one this
was supposed to be Rick Roll City pop
what
where's my Rickroll City Pub
that's not it
well this is kind of fitting for
the travel
[Music]
s
laughs
[Music]
I could write lyrics to this about
finding the myths of iomi
yeah yeah
I will find a mess I'll buy on me today
[Music]
no matter how far it is I will not stop
I am motivated and nothing can stop me
no no no no no even though some things
jump scare me easily
I am the Phoenix
who will make hollow Ian succeed
and together we're strong
yeah
I don't know what I'm singing
[Music]
succeeded and I'm gonna find the Mesa by
Omi and with that we're all gonna be 5
million
Bill entire
understand
it's night time should I sleep oh
is that a temple
if it's a temple I want to check it out
[Music]
if it's a city I don't care if it's a
temple I want to check on it oh God I
really mind slowly huh how long does it
take to
it
give me my bed
[Music]
the boat I was able to mine so fast
I really need to drink my milk now well
there you go it was worth it bringing
the milk
but now it's gone
[Music]
never mind
this is The Mending right okay
she's so close so close it's a silk
touch
okay
let me just quickly check
I just want to see
if that's a temple
if it's a temple then I I might want to
you know infiltrate it I know it's not
it's not
[Music]
and ladies
um I'm infiltrating it anyway
bamboozle you thought I wouldn't look
inside haha what the hell is this
okay I will go then I'll go about my day
this is like literally only one house
what the hell
uh-huh
nah
Okay so
for yourself facing south
mouth
bow straight only takanasi Kiara wow
[Music]
wow
I don't know how to restrain myself but
like everything's so beautiful is that
enough there's another Temple here
okay here another Temple
temples are really not that rare huh
water temples
like it's like
um what Mansions are they much rarer
than temples because like I see temples
like water temples everywhere but what
Mansions I see like nowhere
South South
[Music]
they are around just lucky the water
temples they are right really
[Music]
I'm so curious I want to look around
how far are we now
uh
thousand on that
six thousand we are now
oh thank you thank you for the pinky
what do you think about me doing Tai Chi
did you hear me talking about that the
other day
[Music]
I've been recommended doing kaiti has
huh what the
just happened
has anyone ever
done tai chi in the chat
what what what is with my body I can't
control my body
lag
this island is dangerous
never pretty relaxing
maybe use bulge yeah the ocean is big oh
no there we go I guess it ends here
no
okay
um
both times oh no there's the land
[Music]
let's see maybe it's a small island then
we can go around now
Tai Chi makes me so sore every time but
it's great for my body oh makes you sore
[Music]
why is it so exhausting
oh we can still go with the boat for a
little while nice the gym suits you well
all right it's the last one time that
was a short Boat Trip
[Music]
coming here
these sheeps they don't know only
Harmony and peace
they're so far away from the horror
elevates them in the hollow Ian and Hall
of Japan so though
[Music]
should go higher I know I know
I'm so scared of the lag though because
remember that one time when I went to a
wood mansion Jungle by Omi
whoa wow
uh that I like I laughed so bad at the
end remember that
uh am I going south yes
and I kind of lagged into the wood
Mansions area out of nowhere it was so
weird I was so scared but at least now
we have the
whoa whoa they're on the water
now we have the the the the thing oh
Landing Landing Landing Landing out what
what how would
that help
how no no no no that was lag no
it takes so much HP from me
your golden apple to make up for it
Unbreaking golden boots
we could uh exchange for the other gold
boots
crying obsidian is that usually more
than one chest
I should have brought my fennel falling
boots huh oh damn I do have feather
falling boots
foreign
I need to land a little bit softer
I have a lot of crying opportunity but
okay I'll go I'll get it wait let me let
me place my Ender Chest
and get this one
and
I guess I'll put that in there anyway
yeah
oh my God all right
um wait uh
get the obsidian
CA
yeah nice golden block always golden
block
who is cutting onions I'll be cutting
onions this week with public
ly
nice advertisement right am I right is
there anything else down here
foreign
[Music]
maybe she'll be cutting onions maybe
she'll be crying because of sentimental
questions or something like that no but
um I put out my weekly schedule
yesterday
and you guys were all freaking surprised
that whole talk this week is with aqua
Senpai
bamboozle I got her to uh go for a whole
lot a whole talk yay
I'm takana I can do anything
Unstoppable Force
takanashi Kiana
how did you manage it I mean what what
do you mean why is that such a miracle
I know she doesn't like I know she's
like shy and all that but like
um I don't think it's such a insane
surprise that she went for it
but
um I was like looking on Twitter and
like Aqua senpai's fans reactions were
also funny they were also very very
surprised about it oh I should have put
the gold in there oh well
later
she did to let me see yeah but that is
like management
um doing stuff
and I don't see why why would you turn
that down if that comes with like an
original song and a merchandise and all
that that's that's
something it wouldn't turn down either
okay
we're going south baby and I'm gonna go
higher
we were so close to losing our uh told
him
but that that didn't happen
slowly slowly slowly
but to be honest I'm also
a little bit nervous about
the collaboration what is that
and because I know she'll be shy I hope
I can make her feel comfortable
foreign
I did not stop
oh portal again can I stop to pick up
the gold it doesn't count as a real stop
okay oh this is a nice cool location
though
okay safe landing
wow
let's sleep though
uh
[Music]
go into the portal wait is it full I
didn't look closely
it's like almost almost completed
should I complete it actually
I don't know what what good that would
do to me but
uh
[Music]
obsidian oh it even has obsidians and
complete and flint and steel yo what
what is
why I charge for again just to make fire
right
just a quick peek yeah let's just take a
quick peek
maybe maybe this will be like a Midway
stop in our uh Mesa never Road
that's really convenient here
this is I think the first time I am
making a portal on my own
[Music]
laughs
and how did I do that wrong
[Music]
how
do you do it
I have to replace the crying obsidian oh
that doesn't work
hold on this is the exact amount that
you need there were two obsidians in the
box and there's another extra obsidian
here
yo
very nice of them
that could have been lava
okay uh
I
I guess I'll just use this
Appleton so yes I'm careful careful is
my second name Kiara photo
I'm gonna take the crying obsidian and
Shaboom
oh I was like why is this gonna failing
fail again why would it fail again yo
[Music]
uh crying obsidian
um gold and black
I I'm scared
[Music]
said spawn
is there ever like can it ever happen
that you go into a random nether portal
and you're in the never and you
immediately die because you get spawned
in the middle of I don't know lava or
something
is that a thing can that happen
oh
no yes yes yes what no which one
[Music]
I'm so scared
hello
am I fine to go in I'm so scared why am
I so scared
what if the could it be that the portal
is broken once I go inside
[Laughter]
go go
oh dear
oh my God
so dark
[Music]
okay it's so dark I don't see
what's that
I don't wanna I don't wanna I wanna
let's go back Cairo Carlo
the void the void is scary I don't like
it
all right
okay we still have a lot of fireworks
we're good we're good
um okay
[Music]
give me back my bed
and we can put the flint and steel back
uh I got it
[Music]
okay
this one has soft touch okay always
gonna check twice because I'm really
scared to
uh mess it up
okay we're good continuing
but if we really go straight South and
just by going straight South eventually
reach the mess up by only wouldn't that
mean that if I make a straight South
Railway through the
um never I could kind of like use this
as a station in between though
[Music]
help me think about this guys
red yes right yeah
like I don't know for what reason you
would
[Music]
what
[Laughter]
[Music]
is that
whoa whoa
whoa
I found
oh yeah
that was way faster than I thought it
would be where are we
ten thousand
wait is that concrete powder
there's a red sand can I if I add water
to that does it work like concrete and
it turns into this terracotta what's
this
wow they were called am I this is so
dark
[Music]
um
oh it's a mine shaft
whoa whoa
right here cool
well it's so pretty it looks like a
burger
whoa
this is this is it right
now
next up I always known for mine just oh
yeah I heard that I heard that like a
lot of gold and stuff
all right I want to go on top let's go
on top wow wow wow
wow oh my God I'm gonna mind it should I
mine it with silk touch
this makes no difference with this one
right
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah it's not even that far away
honestly but then like even with a road
above ground
that wouldn't even beat out much that
long of a road
oh is that white terracotta
wow I hear I hear a dog me
mine shaft underneath
wow oh how big how big is it let me fly
it
way
wow
oh it's so big that's the first time I
ever seen
Little Joe by only oh my god wow
there's concrete for days
you're telling me that all over that
area there's gonna be like a million
Treasures like mine shafts
[Music]
this also Fancy by Omi with the trees
don't load it all
for later
I set the spun I did I did
[Music]
it's never ending yeah
no concrete system yeah that's what I
mean
wow this looks like pink is that pink
looks like pink
pink it's not pink though
[Music]
I don't even know where I come
it's a mess of paradise
[Music]
well what is that what's that what's
that
[Music]
calm calm Landing
okay
this is like mine shops everywhere
there's so many like spider webs
and I saw something here there we go I
think I guess that's nothing
special oh spider is that a spider spawn
that's a spider I don't know I'm so
excited
wow
what is that what is that oh is that a
behind mine shaft mine Shuffle
[Music]
cool cool cool oh my God I'm so excited
hello
mine shop though I've yet to find a
treasure though
oh
oh I'm gonna load it out
Jesus thank you
game tag
oh
I don't know if I really want all of
this right now I'm fine I'm fine I want
to find like gold give me gold
this is exciting
oh wait I still have my crazy eyes I'm
calming down I'm calming down
yeah now it's turning night and I don't
know where my bed is well I need to find
my first screenshot yeah a bit
love it where was my where was my where
was my where was my bed
app data Minecraft screenshots
[Music]
you know what we found it so much
earlier than I thought we would so we're
gonna explore
um
[Music]
wait I didn't take a screenshot yet of
ah I know I have a screenshot of the
coordinates of the portal yeah
I mean I'm scared
mine shaft
[Music]
wait ah if I just go
opposite direction of of South would I
find it
uh it's too dark to find it
oh yeah I'm scared uh
no yes probably
wait
I was at thousand five five two
and and 270.
200 2017 200 200 when is it going down
is it going down here okay
all the enemies are waiting for me
no no no
no no I'll deal with you a little bit
later oh
[Music]
America
some places in America 270
217 and then 1500.
you're the Grand Canyon you have never
been there I want to see it
somewhere there I think
[Music]
I was so excited I flew away so far
portal
God damn it
portal the portal the portal uh
do you guys see it have I missed it
isn't it somewhere here my bed
wasn't it here
I just play Roblox
wait I need a clear view I just flew
over it
better
we'll find it by the time it's already
daytime
and I place it on high ground though I'm
pretty low ground there it is there ah
oh yeah but there's so many zombies here
though
all right I'll take care of them Hello
friends
um I'm taking over this by Omi now thank
you
oh my God
I'm taking over I'm the mayor now I'm
the oh my God I can't hit them what is
this
okay
[Music]
calm down
part-time Warrior my shift has only just
begun
yeah
the lag man what do you want what do you
want what do you want what do you want
[Music]
no by the time I clear this place it's
gonna be
I can't go down
it's gonna be daytime hi speeda
oh the creeper is following me too yeah
[Music]
hahaha
[Applause]
okay spider is down
I'll take care of you guys
[Music]
oh they're not coming after me
who knows what happens if I go to sleep
there we go
can I sleep no yeah
I don't know
[Music]
yes this is the sign for you that the
Phoenix has arrived
you want more here eat this
Okay so
um I'm gonna keep my bed here
we're gonna place the under chest
we're going to put my uh Electro in
there we're gonna take out choker boxes
and
we're gonna
mine
for torches Aya and mark the place
that's right that's right we should Mark
the place
uh-huh
lucky to Boosie
honestly now I just really I can really
directly just use that never portal that
we saw over there
don't even have to make my own one so
easy
make a house okay
um out of these materials all of the
terracana it would be nice to have a
different material to make it stand out
more and we have some Oak planks
you could even make it out of obsidian
we have too much obsidians all right
let's make a safe house it'll be easy to
find oh that's a powder
okay house
Kiana house
[Music]
could have brought a little bit more oh
well there is more wood uh somewhere
I've seen trees there
on a vacation spot right I can advertise
it as a visit to the Grand Canyons oh
oh we'll get the tourism going but we'll
charge uh we'll charge a city tax
of
one Diamond per day
I want to go get some trees
one second
I don't have any more I think so one
second one second oh
[Music]
my hot wings
uh trees over there
why so pretty looks like ketchup and
mustard
and cocktail sauce
let's go see high again
yeah I gotta be careful that's right I I
am careful as much as I can be well
at least we didn't like die on the way
to here dying now is somewhat okay
because we have a spawn point
and the coordinates
not belitra you know
[Music]
there you go
okay that is uh
more than enough okay where which
direction did I come from
[Music]
there
and land in the water whoa
let's finish Kiana how soon
with those old planks
I need a door as well
and I can place my crafting table
yes
[Music]
yes wait wait first house then pillar
house kind of serves as a pillar as well
[Music]
okay
should we make a proper roof
or just a flat roof
it would be nice to have a proper roof
can I make
[Music]
a
flat roof no I don't I want a proper
roof now
[Music]
I need to practice how to build roofs
20 20.
24.
I need to get up here
how to build a roof with takanashi Kiara
like this like this maybe
uh like this like this like this and
then
uh we put these here yes yes so far so
good
oh it's already looking gorgeous
is this gonna be enough
hi
okay
[Music]
my little cape of happiness
he
[Applause]
X
[Music]
what do you mean only needs blocks on
the ends
wait how much blocks is there in between
I need a few more
stairs only a couple or a few of my
stairs and a few slams maybe perhaps
yes and then slap
oh no okay we don't have enough for that
that's okay
no come back to me
okay
[Music]
I don't know how to place this correctly
without having to place something
underneath
uh for now let's just Place terracotta
and then get rid of it and well once
it's done
[Music]
uh-huh
I didn't wait oh
oh that's already it
I thought there were two blocks in
between I looked at it wrongly
hmm all right let's just keep it like
that
whoa
beautiful put a slab on top one
I should put torches on top though
huh
and a door will be here
and now I'm lacking all the materials
again though I need I need more wood you
know what never mind how much do I need
for a door
[Music]
okay
my dog go on top
no built I'll put the Torches
[Music]
so no zombie will try to get close to my
house
known zombie
and no other monsters
now what would we build a pillar out of
though
remove the wood Under the Stairs oh yeah
right oh oh smart
thank you I wanted to do that anyway I
forgot about it though
now I can make Le door
[Music]
and a voila
our house
is pretty much done
[Music]
here we go
okay you know what I think I'm gonna go
over to the portal and
although there was like only Soul Sand
around me right when I spawned in there
I was thinking I should make the the
tower out of something that stands out
because
I don't know like a different color
different approaches inside oh yeah
but I guess I'll just make it out of
dirt or something
okay that's enough
let me get that dirt then
a Black Tower glowstone I should have
brought my glowstone
some yellow terracotta okay
yellow mustards mustard no that was more
like mayonnaise terracotta
it's got getting dark again though
should I sleep first
Chloe has a native call
[Music]
oh I can't sleep yet
there's some yellow stuff here now
[Music]
what the hell is mayonnaise Tara call
that
as if it's such a
weird idea here this is maybe no not
really I guess that yellow one is
mustard is this the yellow one I don't
see it properly yellow okay
uh
[Music]
uh wow
you're gonna make a big tower maybe
maybe I'll put torches on each or every
second block or so
to make it light up nicely
also I probably don't have enough space
yet
[Music]
okay 40 40 blocks high is that enough
I say yes
wow now it's so easy to see
swim swim
hey Chad the Moon is beautiful tonight
why are you flirting with the chat flirt
with me
wow
I wanna if Ina if she hears that I found
the Mesa by Omi here if she's gonna go
come and see it immediately
she I wonder what her plans are for
today
maybe she wants to come here and get
terracotta
okay how are we gonna do this we're
gonna build we're gonna build a tower
where do we build right here
maybe sorry I can jump into water to
fall down okay one two
free four
porch
yes
one
two
three
four
torch yes
one
two
three
four
yes one
two three four
yes
one
two
[Music]
three
four
yes wait no
was that really for
[Music]
yes one
two
three
mommy I'm scared this is so high
[Music]
bye
fear even my totem is shaking when I
jump
look at the totem he's shaking
shivering he's so scared
he's like this gonna get me killed
and it's literally literally your
purpose though
okay oh my God
[Music]
it's fine
oh there we go
and it is done
um
okay
nice towel maybe I should have put the
torches on the whole sides oh well
it's fine
now let's look at some of the shafts
and get a lot of concrete material
um wow I still have so many left over
fireworks
I guess we don't need that
[Music]
um
um how am I gonna do this
we should not bring the elytra
um
no need for the boat
no need for sticks
should I bring the totem
I don't really need it anymore right
because I mean I have my safe Point here
I'm gonna leave it here
more food um I'll keep on coming back
though to bring back my stuff when one
choker box is filled I guess I'll just
or or into shulker boxes are filled
I'll come back here
[Music]
you know what let's put let's put the
what is this is the sand uh worth
keeping what do you think guys
lots of spiders in the shafts keep the
totem on
yeah
for decoration not really it's just sand
for glass yeah
sand but it's red hmm
um it's not even a much different color
[Music]
Ed everything this is Minecraft
I guess I'll take a little bit but
mostly we'll bring the Terracotta and we
have orange terracotta oh this is just
normal terracotta the whole Brown
terracotta white terracotta okay
[Music]
okay
no need for a light trap
can I bring torches
yeah I'll bring torches
and now I'll bring my water bucket
and you guys say I should really bring
the toenail
but I want to hold my Shields
and wait for that we can just respawn
here
fine
[Music]
silk touch
yeah I don't want to waste my totem
don't need it okay okay okay
thank you for coming
when you cook terracotta it turns into
glaze and has Anita I need pattern whoa
oh those are those those fancy
terracottas that I see sometimes in
villages
no no
silk touch no need for silk touch
oh that's cool
I'm excited to like use a lot of those
fancy terracottas and then build stuff
with that
we can't use it for Phoenix don't even
I know there's like a lot of different
patterns yeah exciting
okay I think I'm I'm ready to go
uh eat eat
[Music]
spawn point okay
the night is gonna come sooner I think
all right let's climb up
we should build a path that's like easy
to climb but I'm just gonna try to climb
up
here
okay
wow
I thought I would be flying for hours
today to be honest
oh
what's the most special thing you can
find in um
in a mine shaft
is there something super super super
rare that you can find
[Music]
me
did you really just say me
glowberries oh yeah right I still don't
really know what those blueberries do
I know that there's no glowberries
and that the girls have already like
planted a lot of them
named Alia name tags are pretty dope
um
to get for free
[Music]
ah source of light ah okay okay
wait maybe here mark this path a little
bit at least
we'll find the mine shaft but honestly
it's like which is the crutus I would
probably find some as well right it's
like underneath
everywhere
[Music]
I know I know I have a I have a
librarian that sells uh name tags but
it's so much nicer to get it for free
here
congratulations on the final
Naomi thank you
should I go down here
flying over everything made it much
easier to find anything but okay we'll
walk now to be safe
extra safe
free stuff always nice
give me those freebies here
now that I don't go outside anymore the
fact of missing so many freebies that
are being giving out outside unlike
train stations and all that makes me
really sad
when I used to have a normal job and I
used the the train or like whatever
traffic means of getting to my job every
now and then I would find
uh like I would find people giving out
freebies like like energy drinks and
sometimes snacks wow
the feeling of
this just made my day
just forgetting one free can of an
energy drink
I don't know why but it's just
overwhelming
one free can of energy drink can
literally make my day although I mean my
my first choice would usually not be an
energy drink but
it is what it is I wanna go over there
is it connected somewhere
come on give me my traps give me mine
shaft come on
I wanna go over there
without jumping up and down oh
[Music]
no
I want the station closer to my house
oh
sharpness five wow but it's all gold
it's crap
I leave this for someone else to be
happy about finding
well there's I think
it looks like there could be a shaft
there
I want to go back to sleep now though
damn it I should have built a second bed
I know that would kind of destroy my my
spawn though right
oh well
oh oh my God they're like everywhere so
obviously and no one named
Angel
um oh torches actually
you know what
that's pretty cool I need torches
[Music]
is there more to this like should I go
deeper is that water
are they all just like these teeny tiny
bits
get the bread yeah okay
free rails
[Music]
I guess so
they're normally big right so is this
just should I dig deeper to find the
rest of this mine shaft or is this it
you got chokers take everything yeah
true true
the mobs are here now yeah Emma loves
three rails I'll donate some rails to
her although I I will I will need rails
to build no I want to make it out of ice
right
never mind then I'll make it out of ice
all right I don't care about the mobs
I'm just gonna go over the flow
I'll try
yeah
wants to fight
one hit how did I do that
that was a headshot if I've ever seen
one
get it missed
ah who kills who first huh
haha now leave me alone
[Music]
I don't want to go to sleep
why can I not go on the water grapple
anymore there we go
it's too shallow
but I don't want to go back to sleep
single time I'm here to collect stuff
okay I'll go up here
not so many enemies here
kind of want a torch here
am I okay am I safe
I think I am
is this red concrete
uh terracotta so I keep on saying
concrete
[Music]
yummy yummy
the same color yeah
what eh that's not a single that's brown
isn't it
[Music]
Brown
Brown and red
[Music]
cobweb mine Chef oh every every cobweb
equals mine shaft
all right
let's go look for those they do stand
out
what
[Music]
okay okay
is that oh that's just a skeleton
I'm gonna change the bgm now I think
ah you say you love the video I'm sorry
but
um I've heard this for too long now it
was very fitting for the travel part
let's see what do we have what do we
have
[Music]
oh
nah
[Music]
no
that's my loading bgm that's that
that's this that's the city pop thing
that I was looking for I think I sent
AMA the wrong track because I named the
city pop brick roll thingy for amen
didn't I intend to send her a different
one
I think I didn't intend to send her a
different one I
was like yo this is really nice but I
said this made me think of you now this
does not make me think of Amit
that other one made me think about me
oh I think I messed up
but this kind of gives me a Rick Roll
City pop Vibes I don't know
what
you get sticks from these
I know
yeah
I mean I wanted to go up but there's
nothing really up there
go down again
I'm it has been request
low-key yes
I'm glad she liked it anyway
another one
no he's not coming
yet
yes stop bugging around like that I
don't have time for it
[Music]
I think you sent the right song she used
it on the master oh she did
then I guess I just named it incorrectly
but sent her to correct one okay I'm I'm
relieved then she is
that means she liked it all right
uh should we check out this area
way go away I don't want to fall down
because of you
wait let me go up here first
what do we have here
hello monsters
okay I'm slowly going down
slowly descending
out
food
uh
I almost don't see you in that Moonlight
damn
okay now where's the Minecraft I saw so
many when I was flying around come on
there's spiders here
could be a sign
of it
foreign
what a nice greeting thank you so polite
you guys are
no wonder no one lives here besides
monsters you guys are not very nice
well what's that
oh no I
can't shops anymore
instead of title doco it should be
Manchester
foreign
day
we got through the night
should I have brought my
Elijah with me what what is this what's
this
is it raining
I've never seen this weather before
it
not do I see the weather here
oh fat
fancy clouds no
this is so weird
that is so weird
I just gets cloudy it doesn't rain here
ah that makes sense
oh
I see
but it is daytime now wait so do they
burn do the enemies burn when it's like
cloudy like this
oh the creeper is still alive
wait the Creeper's burned I forgot
I don't right they don't care about the
sunlight
[Music]
oh yesterday guys did you see on my
Twitter I uh I went to get some Japanese
food unagidon unadon
it was really spontaneous I originally
wanted to cook yesterday but at the same
time when I was about to go outside
so oh he's not burning when I wanted to
go outside to buy ingredients my friend
called me and she was like yeah
Kiana
I'm I'm right now I'm uh out with my
friends eating
what
uh you want to join
so no normally I'm not like the
spontaneous type to go out for dinner so
spontaneously
but I was hungry I was hella hungry
and then even though that's usually
always quite an expensive food even in
Japan
uh it was actually not that pricey
oh no
oh
you changed your mind
we love it
there we go
I wanna go
what happened here
I want to go over to that portal that I
just saw leave me alone what is this leg
I can barely hit it
loud
lag really strong yeah is it because I'm
so far away from the headphone there's
no way right
oh
now you're done was really really yummy
my friends had Ramen dough
bad connection to the server
all over there even though that's not
the Mesa by Omi anymore but we have
another portal more gold
[Music]
uh
wait I know I want to get rid of those
first uh
before they pushed me into the lava
open it
what is that buff that I have right now
does it go away
all right let me take it
no
try try to get closer
oh that's just a lava okay all right all
right all right all right are we done
now
can I
I don't really know these things are not
even that cool though mending golden
legging leggings okay
um I don't need it but I want those two
gold blocks
okay okay
here we go however maybe there's lava
underneath
nope nice
huh give me
thank you okay that's all I want I'll
need the obsidian
I'll put a torch it out to know that
someone has been here before
oh hello friend
oh now now he starts burning
is it clearing up I don't see it
clearing up
oh by the way speaking of food oh now
it's raining speaking of food I didn't
show you guys yet a picture of the curry
that I made right you want to see
you want to see the carrying that I made
the other day Japanese Curry
yes I'll show you hopefully nothing
attacks me
oh uh
my mom I got a Discord message from my
mom
telling me about the mess of Wyoming I
know I know hello Mom everyone say hi
Mommy
hi Mama Tony
foreign
Big Image incoming guys
there you go
um
[Music]
Japanese Curry
it was very yummy but it's not that
difficult if you have the the curry
um block
then it's so easy you just I said it
last time but you just cut the veggies
and put it in there in the into the pot
you cook it for a little bit then you
add a water
and then you add the curry
block thingy
um
the rice the rice is not very good
though
um this time it's not as watery as last
time
oh
but it's still not perfect I for some
reason
forgot or unlearned how to make rice
properly
should ask mumei about it maybe
but I bought a rice cooker because it
made me so mad I decided okay I'm gonna
buy a rice cooker now
so it arrived today so next time I'm
gonna make rice it's gonna be perfect
again
foreign
what do I have here
far easier to use a rice cocoa yeah
I've never used a rice cooker for
anything besides rice though
and apparently you can make so many
things
the rice cooker fascinating
I feel like I'm barely Wing from where I
came from where are the shafts
I need to find the shafts
also give me some of that white terrible
yeah do you have like the same thing
that you like buy products like machines
or whatever that like they say they can
do so much more than what you would
usually buy them for and you're like wow
I have the choice between
this thing that does exactly what it's
normally used for or this thing that
does that and so much more so you buy
the one that can do so much more but you
never use it for anything besides the
main reason
right
wow this has so many functions so it's
way more worth my money I'm gonna buy
this one but then you never use it for
any of the other functions
ah
dark so hard to see what all this is
like it's all this darker concrete still
terracotta terracotta terracotta
[Music]
have you tried any Indian food
uh yeah I'm pretty sure I have
well uh my mom definitely made Indian
curry for me before and I have just
eaten it in an Indian restaurant as well
I suppose what else is Indian food why
is it so junk I don't know I asked I'm
asking you guys why the hell is it so
dark here
Sun is going down and it's cloudy
thank you for doing now
spice little oh I I uh I really can't
take spiciness unfortunately
oh I'm pretty sure I ate that before
on it
that's where it ends
at least for a while
now it's raining
let's go up here
did I just hear a spider
please have mercy on me
chicken Tandoori oh yeah definitely
definitely had that
but but if I say that I don't know I
feel so shallow I'm sure that it's so so
so so so much more Indian food that's
really good but that
um most people just don't usually think
of when they think of
um Indian food so I don't want to be so
superficial and say these she's super
famous foods that everyone
has definitely tried before
I saw you creeper nah no oh
is the bread right
foreign
I'm gonna mark my territory at least now
I should Mark it sometimes so I have an
idea where I was
[Music]
What if I find right here like through
the mountain
oh it's raining again
terrible weather
gonna go up here
the shafts don't open on the top usually
oh but I saw like so many when I was
flying above
oh
well at least we're getting materials
have we tried Lassie I have
I was at uh I I
I had food takeout I took out food
before in an Indian uh
uh rest restaurant thingy
and they were like yo you wanna Lassie
that's a drink right
oh kind of like a yogurty drink
yeah it looked yummy so I did I did take
it I drank it for the first time not so
long ago
it was okay it wasn't bad
oh
mm-hmm
all the colors all those beautiful
colors oh yeah oh no no no no no
no
why is it always so dark can't we have
good weather again it's been like a
million years since we had good weather
blah blah
hi Enderman help me
help me
[Music]
I'm running out of food
am I running out of food
yeah
bury yourself in a hole and just what
wait until the weather is better
ah I see something there
ain't seen something oh actually there's
a lot here I see a lot of spider webs
okay
okie dokie
oops
I really ran out of food though maybe we
we should find bread and stuff right in
in those in these shafts yeah
so when I get rid of the blocks all
right let's I guess start here
I'm scared I don't have much experience
with mine shafts
I'm honestly just gonna look for the
um
for the chest still I think got it dead
end okay there's a lot of gold
oh my God I'll take the gold too
we can play gacha
oh where do you ride there's really a
lot of gold in in the Mesa by Omi this
is like
not uh
brand not like a coincidence right
now
whoa
oh my God if I ever need gold again I'm
just gonna come to the Mesa by Omi
it's a gold mine literal gold mine
oh I should fill up my sugar boxes one
second
uh I have one here
okay
terracotta terracotta terracotta
Mercado
red sand
golden block
terracotta
and a full stack of raw gold
silk touch
on it but I think I left my silk touch
at the at the base
right I think I left it there
oh wow
next time
I think no I thought I just saw a chest
but nope give me more chests
I love buying some gold
we'll find more than enough
whoa
oh this is so cool the way these are
built
generate it really cool
get some spiders okay okay yeah
somewhere Japanese bro just said
um I can get I can make a bed out of
spider webs what
really
I've never I don't think I've ever heard
of that before
what
you can make wool of that what
SI oh hello
wait wait wait wait
okay okay
first Target taken down oh he's smart
he's a smart cookie
what you gonna do though when Kiana
comes for you huh
all right
look at all that gold
serious latency ah where can I see like
um the
what's it called again
wasn't there a button to look at the the
what's it called what's it called
inventory full it messy
the pain yeah why do I see my ping
not inventory for what are you talking
about
[Music]
F free oh wait is it written here
where's my ping
where is it
tap
what
tap I'm pushing the top
three bars what
oh that's a pink ah
ah is it bad seems normal
and come a friend
oh
strong sometimes I kill them with one
Arrow only oh copper
do I need copper
oh my God dangerous
almost suffocated me
dead end
damn gravel
freaking unravel
which one have we not been to is there
something here
oh
we're out of the
hour
desired biome does that mean no gold
here
yeah discuss
ing
oh it's pretty huge
but no chests
more chests
I'm a little bit disappointed in the
amount of chests I'm finding
gold yes but still
oops
no gravel please
I am gonna
be hesitant about mining from the
ceiling now
hmm
it's fine now
where does that lead oh it's outside oh
second level
yeah but there's nothing here but hey
it's again oh and you can like see
way better now
dead end
I want to hold on no problem what about
here
oh nice
yes
[Music]
can I take now I'm gonna leave those
there
a golden apple
gold
enemy enemies no
yeah
you're paid for this
I would have left your life if you don't
attack me is that not an option to you
peace you know what that word means
yes it's also what the tourists say
every time they come here and take
pictures
that's so scary you want being up there
oh my God Kawaii
foreign
what's gold in Spanish guys
average Australian spider
yum
oh it's like ore whoa which is over
you know so many people who can speak
Spanish
or is that the only word that you can
say
that you learned in Spanish class and
you can barely remember
um
which way do we go now
I feel like The Mineshaft is still not
completely
uh
done
interesting
very interesting path
I'm stupid
nothing here but gold
[Music]
what does that mean do I need to learn
Spanish
for you guys
Heart of Gold that means I have a heart
of gold whoa
ah
and let's get some of this too
[Music]
oh placing some things
we still have so much place so much
space for all of our terracotta
we can give some to Ina if she wants
foreign
[Music]
's new outfit today
oh
it looks so cute and she had like so
many options she could like have the
white dress or the darker dress
which combination did you guys like more
I think I like the white one more
because I'm used to seeing her in Darker
clothes
and seeing her in a like in a brighter
style was nice for a change
white jacket of the dark dress and that
was really nice too I like that one a
lot too
but you know just for a change
kind of liked uh the light version it
looks so cute she looks she looks very
Cecil
foreign
ah I can stack them oh
oh I didn't realize I never had
somebody's name tags at once
should I go which hole did I not enter
yet did I answer here
there's nothing here
am I gonna run out of torches no
and then not only suicide samples but
have you seen
Indonesia first gen is getting new
outfits
like very soon too
wasn't it like what what day is it oh
aren't they starting tomorrow
I think I saw the date 20th if I'm not
imagining things
like one per day I think it was
foreign
I had no idea that they were getting a
new outfit I was so surprised and they
seem kind of Halloween themed because of
that witch hat I mean it looks like a
witch hat
or they're even Halloween themed or just
like costume party
or like magic something magical themes
yeah
exciting
scared me
KFC is getting abused
I'll only kill that zombie I'll try
not are you okay I kept it alive though
chicken is still alive what
we are
that's probably the the kfb member who
gave me like the the hint of where the
Mesa by Omi is in the first place
huh
he was waiting for me
thank you
employee
you want to be the branch manager of kfp
Mesa kfp
you can be anything if you want to
pirate
what what are you talking about the
Swift Code isn't that something from
Star Wars is this ZIP code from Star
Wars
so by the way what what is this
dark oak oh this is dark oak
guys turning tonight again I hate it
it's so hard to see stuff should I make
a bed
I could probably make one by now
but I would have to make also a crafting
table uh
nah no thank you let's go up
I think I looked through most of this
mineshaft
um this place seems kind of safe though
I could chill here 12 strings
never mind I'll just continue mining as
if it's uh not nighttime outside I'll
just ignore the fact
and chill here as long as I can
look into this one I think I did yeah
give me your dolls thank you
again
every time
it
um
chop the wood around I guess so
all right let's do it let's take uh this
Woods
and make a crafting table
oopsie there we go
and get some more wood
and whoa
what
what honey I need more I need three was
it I think three
oh
there we go
we can sleep now
oh monsters nearby all right never mind
then
one second
wrong way
I don't see any monsters what are you
talking about
huh
[Music]
Papa
can I make this into like blocks or do I
need a do I need to cook it first
what if I do this
oh you can make it into block of ruggle
should I do that
safe space
it's not it's not irreversible right
it's not a loss is it yes okay one
second
around gold
Shield
I can do the same with the copper huh
copper block oh
it looks like food that has gone off
like weeks ago
disgusting
but it Blends in nicely with these
colors
all right
I do hear those monsters hmm
Noah please let me sleep come on
I want to sleep
please
maybe in the shafts where there's more
light here yes
oh ouch
eat it
but it's daytime okay
so I think we're gonna continue to see
if we find it if I explored here
oh wait there's a little bit of
unexplored territory now not much
and I look for a different mine shaft
oh yeah I was speaking of the new
outfits
is that Muna who's gonna get a shortcut
yo
yo that's gonna be hype I'm so excited
for the new outfit to hot new outfit's
always so exciting everyone's gonna
just recently Aki Senpai got one too
when is when is Hollow myth new outfit
doka
is that gray terracotta
I feel like I didn't really mind any
gray tarot card I should go up there
Aki's Empire was killed too yeah
also who else I think wait someone else
also got one uh
[Music]
yeah I just mentioned suicide but
someone else also got new outfits very
recently
no not Luna but she got cat years yeah
but I mean like
more than that
as well did we ever talk about that
I'm fine yeah yeah yeah
yes I think that's who I was thinking of
the season of new outfits
but pretty much everyone is going for
like a casual outfit
these days
a light gray
yeah no assistant but I got some kind of
like Oktoberfest outfit I was so
surprised about that
um I was like
she's wearing
she's wearing the clothes of the country
of my people
how come looked very cute but um from
the point of view of someone from well
that country
it's like it looks more like a cosplay
of
um that traditional
clothing Denzel
then like a like a real proper proper
proper one it still is like hella cute
but it's definitely more like cosplay
oriented
yeah because it's like super short like
normally and you you don't get such
extremely short dandels
like the shortest Dental that you would
get normally
like a proper one would be like until
the knees or like a little bit above the
knees and even that is called a fashion
dandel
rather than a traditional gender like
the the proper ones are apparently they
go over the knees
but I understand why she went for this
this is pink what the hell
it looks so pink
I already have a lot of those don't I
um
but the braids they look so cute on her
apparently she took inspiration from me
like she mentioned me
in regards to the brain stitchy
mine shaft below
what
I don't see much out here
meow
believe I'm sorry damn it one second
[Music]
Oh I thought it was a gold Block it's
just a light source
no no mine shaft but definitely a shaft
but
um I I personally like one of my dream
outfits for the future would also be at
the end also
when when I get that too we can have a
dental dental collaboration
um
but I think it'll take a lot of time
until that happens
no clam yeah
she's such a sweet sweet girl
I never really had a proper conversation
with her but I love for Jen with all my
heart
so
I'm all up for it
yeah someone requested bgm change I am
fired
[Music]
you ask and you receive
going for a little bit of a Japanese
style here now
[Music]
um
nice PGM right thank you audio stock is
like my favorite place to go these days
is it is it not too loud
I don't know what else to put in here
I'm running out of food though for real
now I need some chests with food please
[Music]
audio stack
audio stock
audio song
the song Oh by the way yes it ends today
I did recording for my new song cover
it's coming
out Halloween Halloween
yeah very fun song to record
I still need to record the harmonies
doll I think I'm gonna do that tomorrow
because tomorrow my stream starts
late I think am I streaming Mario wear
tomorrow
foreign
for Halloween
just to cover
I send this tomorrow
where do I go
those colors look to me like Burger King
Burger King eight o'clock my time all
right
all right but I I am by the way not very
sure about what I want to do
for tomorrow
I just felt like uh playing Sims again
for the first time in a while
um but we still like Clara is still like
a baby I think or like a toddler no wait
did we already have a grow up
I think we did isn't she a child now
shout down
we could continue raising her or we
could create a separate family that's
like maybe Council
and play around with Council
but that's like starting from zero again
I would have to create so many new girls
wow
five new characters in a separate family
maybe with Iris as well
what was the maximum again for Sims
Family
what was it again because I was able to
make us five and then two cats
and one child
so that's eight I think
wait I think eight is the maximum yeah
booba had to be sacrificed
would you create Olive whole life nope
no someone else can do that for me
I am not interested
I can't find myself
maybe I should get my elytra
[Music]
I don't I don't know where I've been
already and where I haven't been
[Music]
what about this area have I been here
yes there's torches all over
over there
eyes getting dark again
Sims 4 collab of gouda Sims is not not
something you can collab with
unfortunately
or maybe it is fortunate actually
because
I wonder what people would do with with
Sims 4 if they could
like use an online mode I feel like only
bad things would happen with that
[Music]
where's my tower by the way
multiplayer Sims yeah sounds sounds uh
sounds curse
like GTA
but like oh no imagine it being online
and then the cringe of like
strangers like it's like an mmrpg where
you can get married and can get children
like normally with mmrpgs it stops at
getting married but with this you would
be able to have intercourse
uh I don't trust the children
on that one nope nope
nah that's that's probably why it hasn't
been done yet
that might be the reason it's too cursed
no one wants that
or or all the children wanted but we
can't give it to them
[Music]
it's not safe
this is Mesa by Omi yes I am planning to
build a whole
Road and Ice Road
to get here
maybe in my next Minecraft stream but
the next one is actually gonna be with
Kelly so the next solo Minecraft stream
[Music]
ing
let me up
[Music]
what
why am I doing this like that
I could also just
use some of my terracotta
there's more than enough
I swear to Cali no this that's gonna be
a really long
process that's probably gonna also be
really boring
I'm not gonna Force Cali to help me with
that no no no we're gonna do something
like
I think I really decided
that we're gonna go for the Elantra I
think I'm happy with that
that's the portal that I checked out
before
I'm gonna go this way
oh
I feel like I keep on going around the
same area
don't know
[Music]
hunting will be fun yeah she's gonna be
so excited getting that Elijah
[Music]
but now that I'm running out of food I'm
thinking maybe it's time to go back
I didn't even get all my Shockers full
though like I could do that quickly
you could quickly fill them up with like
a mountain of that
um foreign
somewhere there in that direction
[Music]
yeah yeah don't worry she won't lose it
we gotta believe in her
if we believe in her then no you know
what she might take it too lightly
[Music]
she might be like oh they think I can
handle it that easily all right then
no need to be too worried about it I
guess
[Music]
where am I
also I've noticed there's like no
animals here I thought maybe at least
like uh
like a desert bunny
nothing
or am I just unlucky
is there usually animals in a Mesa by
all means
am I just unlock
animals don't spawn in the Mesa yet or
have there been uh reports of possible
animals in the future
yeah it was one chicken well then there
must be why why did the chicken spawn
there was that because it was like close
to a desert by Omi or so I don't know
like any other biomi was close by so
there was a chicken there
that was weird
Chosen One
kfp one single chaos theme
[Music]
was looking for me
chicken jockey
kill fish yes probably the last
last um Resort
[Music]
he got lost
canopy is bad with directions
nah you guys are good
you guys are fine you helped me find
this place
[Music]
you helped me not get off track
so was I hand before yes I was I can't
please
[Music]
why this was much bigger when I flew
above it
how how is this possible
am I cursed
[Music]
there's even still the blocks that I
mined because I keep on bumping against
the different biomes and I feel like
okay that's where it ends but maybe if I
walk up for a meet a few meters it's
Mesa again
[Music]
where does it tell you by all me again
uh
ah Badlands
this doesn't even say missile
is Badlands the same as Mesa
yes okay
out
[Music]
what's another uh biome that I haven't
seen yet by the way
[Music]
I feel like recently someone mentioned
some that I haven't seen yet
and I didn't even know about it
[Music]
mushroom place
that's even rarer than Amazon
[Music]
Island ah it's always an island
what if I randomly find it around here
shattered Savannah what
bamboo forest
that's right you know is that where the
pandas are
I haven't seen that one yet no
all right
go north go north why I'm facing off
right now
why are you like playing the game on the
same uh
seed right now and telling me where to
go because something's over there
bamboo is always in the jungle oh didn't
we fly past uh a jungle
I even took the coordinates I think oh
North is the portal direction oh
[Music]
that's out the floor
and just chose to not take it
Maybe
[Music]
hmm
well
[Music]
take the cards no I refuse
spider spawner
[Music]
nothing
yeah that might be the first one that I
opened
all right let's go let's try to go back
is is North really where I uh
where I built my portal oh look at that
foreign
[Music]
yeah that's right
I think I can follow
but I don't see anything here
I am going to look at my coordinates
there it is 300
and a thousand
okay so just X needs to be corrected
800 no 300 300 300
this way
[Music]
and there's a spider spawner wait have I
been here before
probably
oh
that's in a weird spot
[Music]
one bread
food thank you
[Music]
um
wait let's let's check this place out
let me put down
both of my orange choco boxes
[Music]
yellow red
red Brown
yellow and the name tag goes here
[Music]
I can't place it wait can you not place
a shotgun box in a shulker box
[Music]
it
I don't know
I did not know that
[Music]
oops that would be broken in
I guess so
so uh infinite storage ah
yeah right true
all right
[Music]
oops
is there something nice here for me yeah
oh dear
okay I'll get out of there for one
moment get out of there for one moment
what the hell was that
why did that poison me poison spider
oh my God what was that that was huge in
there
big
I don't have food though
I need to
go get fish
there are no fish there's one fish or
two fish
I'll eat your raw thank you
uh more fish
I can't eat the squid unfortunately
no no need for you I need fish
I have a golden apple though
something
[Music]
food
oops
okay one and two
need some air
and then we go back in there because
that looked really interesting
[Music]
I'm really bad at uh
killing fish in the middle of water
[Music]
or we can partially blame the lag though
what are they doing why are they
swimming like that
[Music]
Titan
come on
offer your body to me
can't be wouldn't you do the same
this is this is why we don't sell fish
at KFC because they don't offer their
body to me
ridiculous
that's a waste
see these fish I have to force but you
guys you don't have to be forced
you guys offer yourselves a voluntarily
that's why I love you guys so much
I left food at my house though didn't I
at that uh
at that base right
[Music]
damn it
okay oh no
no that's not good
that's not good
I did uh should I go there first
I want to look at that mine
[Music]
yeah no
no no no can do what
[Music]
pick up your boxes yeah I know I know I
know I know
I know I know I know
I'm coming back
[Music]
that place looks so scary though I don't
wanna I Don't Wanna Die in there
we can we can have a
my bed right here
how did I
where should I enter Ah that's that's my
card over there
okay
foreign you don't need anything from the
mines and I need I need it I need it all
[Music]
it looked exciting
oh dear
okay okay okay
eat a bit more
maybe even take my golden apple
[Music]
where is it I hear
and
all right
I'm going in guys I'm going in
[Music]
Hawaii
okay with barely any torches and barely
any food
I am going in
go go go
Don't Panic Don't Panic it's fine
no problem
oh my God oh my God
oh my God
safely
one down
speed up come on
you're not gonna poison me again
eat your own poison
okay it's still very dark and what's oh
oh my God oh my God good thing I didn't
I didn't fall down oh
I shouldn't be too close to the edge
[Music]
get those EXP
nothing
wait this place wasn't even that sugary
Pokemon
images
[Music]
no I'm fine I'm fine
it's gone
I guess I'll eat the apple
[Music]
um
is there something
we're going down
[Music]
calm down calm down calm down calm down
oh my God
oh my God oh my God oh my God okay
[Music]
lava
that's good
[Music]
okay I'm I'm leaving
hi Dimas
[Music]
I'll be out here another spider
also I just realized oh no not another
one
I just realized the Minecraft audio is
really quiet isn't it
stank
do they drop something special no huh
[Music]
is that the spawner
that is funny
yeah
it's fine okay
okay I'm sick of that music now though
this sounds like
um
Animal Crossing don't you agree
oh my God
[Music]
Vibe chili
let's just relax lay back
yeah
what was that was that my bgm
no there's a witch that isn't it
there's a witch what
a bit of it
[Music]
ah
is he dead is the witch dead
he's not following me anymore
did you drop something no nothing
up a stick a stick
that's all you drop
it
[Music]
the witch is dead though a magic wand oh
that's supposed to be her magic wand
[Music]
ER
freaking one dollar store magic wand
cheap ass witch man
[Music]
all right I'm gonna look for my home huh
wait my smoker boxes
I forgot my chocolate boxes
[Music]
almost forgore
don't worry I've got it on the radar
don't look into this yes I did
huh
to help out which still is the more
where that came from
came from here right
yeah
there's nothing here she was just
chilling there which is like do they not
need a house to spawn oh my god do they
just spawn in the Mesa as well
[Music]
I hear another spider
where are my boxes
I gotta put my boxes wasn't it here
it's here and then left
left left
here here here
ah
okay
okay okay safe oh my bed is there
sleep they don't only spawn at a witch
hut ah okay hmm
[Music]
I know a spider is coming at me
five
I got no food but I got zombie meat
wait I wanna I wanna one this this one
did I check this one yes that's the one
I just checked I'm so confused
everything looks the same
but wasn't there something else here
oh oh
hello hello
we can be friends you know
if you if you let me through thank you
we're friends now
wonderful was you were protecting like
nothing though hmm
don't be greedy
but but
I have to come back with
hands full of gold
[Music]
it's a creeper
you're a strong boy wow
was that another spawner
foreign
nothing okay
[Music]
what was that what was that what was
that what was that
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
[Music]
hello
yeah
I got Infinity though my friend
we can battle forever
but I don't think are you gonna win this
battle hey
nothing okay
[Music]
okay I'm gonna try it for real to look
for my little house now unless
what did I say it's 300X
300 300.
gotta go down this way
no this one this one
this way
white bed cocoa
don't you worry I got it all now I went
back to collect everything properly
no missing objects now
guys I I bought a new plant
do you want to see it it's really pretty
yesterday I bought it
I was actually going outside to buy some
groceries
but the store there was a specific store
that I wanted to go to and I guess that
was too late but like on Google Maps it
said it was still open I hate it when
it's like different from what Google
Maps says like change your times
on Google Maps please
[Music]
so but on the way to go there I was
walking by a flower store flower slash
plant store
so I was like okay
I wanted to get more plants anyway
and in order to not go back home
empty-handed
I'm gonna go buy a plant
so I went in there and I bought a big
big plant
I bought one that
um I could put on my on my shelf
eat I don't have food man I would eat if
I had food
I'll be careful though
uh Direction Google
uh yeah yeah I bought a big one and I
can put on my shelf that like my my
vision was to have one plant at the very
top
seeds you can eat a seat Farm no I'm not
gonna Farm here now
um yeah my basement wants to put one at
the very very top that like grows
downwards
and has like leaves long leaves hanging
down that was my vision and that's
exactly what I got I'm going to show you
a picture in a moment when I reach the
my home if I'll ever reach it with this
insanely slow speed
oh I could I could eat the zombie meat
wait a second maybe something is here
is there a fish
no I even slim slim swim so much slower
I can't speak
cooked kelp I'm not gonna start cooking
now
I'll eat the zombie meat
that does it
I've done it before and I was I stayed
alive
[Music]
okay Heal Me Up yeah baby please
300 306.
[Music]
we're on our way
going to Iris lay
has a very unhealthy diet doesn't she
ew This is disgusting
disgusting
I have been eating so good yesterday and
this is what I eat today
well you gotta balance it right
I'll balance your diet
[Music]
hi this is
foreign
noise
holy
can I imagine something but I don't know
if I can say it now
[Music]
do you guys know what Ollie is planning
she's always planning something but you
guys know what she's planning related to
something with me
has she talked about it on her stream
Maybe
where the hell am I
no oh
oh
chest
chest just oh she didn't mention it oh
yeah okay okay yeah just watch along she
contacted me yesterday
she was like yo Kiara just want to ask
for permission if I can do a chess watch
along of your yours and Amelia's chest
just play chess match
and I'm like well I mean sure if you
want to suffer
it's not gonna be a lot of fun
but only is not a professional in
Minecraft ever though right I I remember
she learned how to play chess for this
tournament from some professional girl
but it's not like she's like super
Superior now is she
where is she
she's not right so I wonder how she's
gonna judge our session
we're proudly worse than her though I
guess by now
[Music]
I don't know why she wants to watch us
play chess I mean I I always thought
that me and Alma playing chess was a
wonderful wonderful
thing and that we did a great job
and that you guys are just being over
dramatic about it
yes
[Music]
it's been a long time too so I guess
like there's a lot of newcomers as well
who don't know
what happened back then and what's so
bad about I mean there's nothing bad
about it but what's so bad about the
chess match that we had
[Music]
Chad has seen mine and Amelia's chess
match
well I've seen it
[Music]
they're not leave food here
oh
okay that was the wrong question who has
not seen it
who has not seen it I'm it was a little
salty oh yes she was
[Music]
I saw the summary
I have not seen have not seen it haven't
seen me me me oh oh okay see that's also
a lot now the question is do you want to
watch the archive do you want to do that
to yourself can I recommend it can other
people recommend it
um
[Music]
let's see
oh I could put the
chests and the energies in the end oh
I kind of want to go to the idol meeting
though and then decide what to do
we should
we could already start building the path
but oh that's gonna
okay I guess we could start yeah why not
I hope but it's already been how long
[Music]
only three hours
we'll start building the path then I
think uh what am I doing here like this
like that
only free always for attacking us stream
no no no no no no no no no no no no
no wait out we're gonna end it here
but so I I have received the advice to
if I were to build something like that
in the in the never in the end no in the
never
um I should build it like at the very
top at the ceiling because that would be
the safest way to build it is that true
and also a quick answer please because I
really need to go to the Iowa meeting
is that true yes
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I'm all good I'm always the same I'm the
same as before
[Music]
no wait you want to see the plant
one second let me I need to send the
picture
from my phone
to
jenma
yes
Jenna are you up
[Music]
it's probably fun
cook
[Music]
I think Jenna is sleeping what
what
I am so proud of you Grandma for
sleeping
at a good time
[Music]
I got it it was this photo
should be all that job
yeah all right
save image
now look at this beauty
[Music]
big
very very big Beauty look at that hair
[Music]
whoa I mean to be honest it was kind of
like not in the most perfect shape
like if you look closer at it like you
would see or like from a different angle
you would see like some some not so nice
parts
but all in all like it has a really
really long
um I don't know what to call it
schlepe
um really really long so
oh you see the alpaca
and and Beyond the stage DVD
out of the vines yeah
[Music]
it's pretty nice now that the Shelf
looks so nice with that little green on
top did the cats find an interesting
yeah I'm chonkers yesterday when I
placed it there chonkers played with it
for a while
um but uh I think she already lost
interest check she stopped touching it
so I think we're good we're good about
that I looked it up that plant is fine
for like cats can even like munch on it
a little bit and they're supposedly fine
no problem
so yes oh 64 whole stack we got the
whole stack man
[Music]
um
it's a safe plant for cats all good
divine
portal well should we just make use of
the portal that we have like somewhere
over there it's really close
[Music]
I think can we see it from here
if I jump over there it was right over
there
might as well
I couldn't like build a path then
um on uh on top of the
the water
[Music]
a new one would be easier bridge too far
I guess we can build a new one okay all
right I'll build a new one
because we have enough obsidian 25 and
we have plenty of Steel
okay how to build a portal how many on
the bottom I think two and then you can
build one like diagonal to it right like
this and then like that
foreign
or is that too narrow
yes okay point and then one more I think
one more
and then in between
this this
is correct
[Music]
easy
all right all right this might be pretty
maybe I should have built it up there so
that we would have been spawned up
higher
I guess we can rebuild it if we need to
oh man I'm so scared about building this
tunnel though
I'm not very confident about it
anyway we need we need my pickaxe what
do we need in order to build it nothing
really
just a pickaxe
what else do we need are the golden
boots
real true
I'm breaking
[Music]
tornado today
I got food now as well all right
you can glitch up to the roof what
right now I can't do that
I should die
um should I bring one shulker box in
case I I've mined a lot of cords Maybe
yes okay
I don't need these blocks but I'll throw
them away once I have a full inventory
um
[Music]
I'm scared
all right
I'm I'm I'm I'm I guess I'm gonna go I'm
gonna go let's go I'm scared oh let's go
let's see where we where we uh
let's see where we land
so dark again
what wait this looks like the same place
where
all right because it was so close it
turned into the same portal
ah
oh
no
[Music]
oh God okay oh God
um
the ocean
a second I want to see
[Music]
uh video settings or in a distance
oh my God
this is
very unclear to see what's going on
and let me see how about more brightness
uh
I don't know that didn't really make it
much brighter that's the song
like should I turn the Shadows off for
this yeah in the in the never the
shaders are
not really helping
and still off
[Music]
his father was in the middle of like no
where
which I am but okay this is at least
kind of better
yeah yeah I have better Vision now way
better is this Soul Sand
Soul soil and this is so sand
or you go really slowly on this one here
bone block
[Music]
hello skeleton
wait skeletons yeah skeletons
that's lava
[Music]
we're uh well wait I don't even know
which direction ah I would need to know
the direction of of like like the the
the coordinates from our portal huh
turn off fog
.com
North ah that makes sense
straighten off
um okay uh
opposite of Blue Line okay but where do
I turn off the
fog
on the chunks maybe a little bit less
[Music]
chunks higher
should I make it higher
[Music]
quality
oh
Lucy fog
details fog fancy off
okay well the little brown color here
oh it was done okay North is
here
this this is the exact
opposite right yeah this green line okay
but I want to get to the very top
if I dig up to the top is there a danger
like awaiting me
like I don't know lava falling yeah
definitely level falling down how do we
do this stairs up first okay
okay let's make a stair
[Music]
single lava blocks yeah oh God
ah
building stuff like this in the nether
it is kind of scary
oh God and the sounds
like a horror movie
uh speaking of horror movies
I actually like next week I am planning
to do like all kinds of like Halloween
related things
I'm planning to play
um little nightmare
nightmare nightmares
foreign
by the way when do I know that I'm at
the top
is there like a maximum height in the
Never
and
[Music]
Bedrock okay
I'm scared and I'm gonna also play a big
surprise did I mention this already I
wonder
did I mention
that I am going to play most likely if I
don't change my mind and I think Alice
madness Returns
which is kind of a request from my BFF
because she loves that game and I have
some
uh connection with it too because my mom
used to play uh either that one or Alice
my G I'm not sure which one it actually
was
when I was younger and I saw her playing
it and it looked interesting back then
and I think it fits the Halloween week
pretty well
and
has anyone in the whole life even ever
played that
because I wouldn't remember
anyone from Whole Life playing a game of
herself it would be a first time nope
you'll be you'd be the first I'm
actually surprised like it's a pretty
cool game though
[Music]
I wonder why no one has picked it up
before
yeah
and I like I like Alice
until Halloween time
it's a little dark but awesome yeah
hey
Halloween Halloween
[Music]
foreign hahaha
how did you help why are you here why
are you here
I got a heart attack
don't do this to me how did he know I'm
inside
[Music]
oh my God chill
and you think torches are gonna help
if there's torches you think he he won't
split just like wander in here okay
okay
let's give it a try and maybe not so
many
there you go
[Music]
like I I almost feel like in the in the
never it just doesn't make a difference
but I could be wrong I could definitely
be wrong
[Music]
[Laughter]
maybe like
build up the stair this way and then
this way and then this one like like a
like a circle circle thingy
[Music]
make a turn okay
I'm super slow at this because I'm so
scared uh and I I gotta be careful I'm
sorry guys
so anyway besides that I guess if we
could also watch a horror movie
um even with members only or publicly
but I usually don't do watch-alongs
publicly just because I don't know I
feel like it's not the most riveting
content
um
for like public streams I I do always
enjoy it a lot to do it with my with my
members though it feels kind of special
like we're on a little date
hehehe
but for my normal Channel content I
prefer to have
like games or or anything else like
karaoke or whatever
oh yeah and one other thing was famous
games that I'm doing for Halloween is my
new song cover so that's something
that's something special right
[Music]
what horror movies
I don't know about horror movies man
you know how I feel about the horror
genre guys
I'm I'm less against playing an FPS game
than I am against
playing a horror game
horror game is like my least favorite
thing ever
if I had to choose I would definitely
choose FPS and that said something
[Music]
you know I know you know
does that mean you will play Apex Ollie
shut up get out of my chat just kidding
that wasn't even Ollie that's why I'm
talking my dad normally I would not talk
like this too Ollie okay
[Music]
freaking addicted
Apex intervention with Ollie
the panel from that um I think it's a
Expo in Canada where I'm a good idea
at least some of the girls except me
will be at they kind of move to the time
slot so there will be no delay
for the Halloween Among Us collaboration
no delay like originally it was like
there might be a delay
because it it's like very close to the
ending time of their panel because there
could be some issues
[Music]
but they kind of changed the time not
because of the mangas just because of
their own things but this is better for
me because the
the earlier we start the better and
honestly like they pushed it so far
behind that I could we could even start
it like an hour or two earlier
an hour actually an hour earlier would
even work but we already I already
announced the time and even though it
would be a million times better for me
to start it one hour earlier
um we're not doing it I don't want to
change the time anymore now that we
announced it so and it's in such a big
collab so
I don't want to make too many changes
but it's starting at 3am for me and it's
probably not gonna end until 5am
I do have kind of a time limit in my
head though so not longer than two hours
because it's a huge collab
so I would be done at 5 00 am
[Music]
5 00 am
um
[Music]
foreign
let's go this way
how high do we need to go like we want
to build right under the Bedrock right
if I build right on the Bedrock do I
still have the chance of running into
lava I guess yes right
we Europeans will sacrifice ourselves
with a greater good exactly
oh gold nice
European Sasuke
[Music]
that is a source of love
no no my friend
no Lava allowed here
[Music]
all right let's continue oops
yeah yeah
it is what it is I'm okay with it like
this this is a big thing and I'm happy
to organize it so as one of the
like or the only person in Europe and in
that kind of time zone
I feel like it's the the least amount of
people
suffer from it if I take the fall
and I said that it was really well
falling
[Music]
so it just makes sense that it's me
it just makes sense guys although I did
I know I did say that I will
like
try to
not do collabs at those kind of times
anymore or like at least no more
sponsored streams and stuff
besides ttlpg
but
well for this one since it's my thing
and I want everyone who participates to
be happy
I decided I'll I'll just
take the fall
I'll take the bad time slot no problem
well Bedrock Nicole
[Music]
bedrock and Soul Sand
confusing
but should we start building like here
uh on this level
[Music]
here foreign
yes are we going the right direction yes
we are okay
but we're still gonna be careful there
could still be Lava here I think
so anyway maybe you
did Callie post her
schedule only for members yet or for
public people as well I can't even make
sentences anymore I apologize
did she make her a schedule public
she realized it okay then you probably
saw that I'm gonna collab with her and
fun on bells and that one starts for me
at I think one or two am
which again is for me
a little bit unfortunate
but
um I don't know I don't it's difficult
because like if I would really say no to
all of these collabs and I wouldn't be
in any collabs you know
and and I don't wanna I don't want that
I don't wanna I don't want it to be like
that like I'm already like
not part of a lot of collaborations
so I I feel like I I need to take what I
what I get
or what I'm invited to even if it's a
shitty time slot
if it was like with Cali only or so then
we can get a
we can stream during her evening my
afternoon that that's a good time for me
like 3 P.M for me is like uh
10 p.m for her
yeah but since fauna and Bales aren't no
Bales isn't really matter that much in
that case I guess but fauna yeah
[Music]
most ian-based YouTubers are not EU
friendly but I I would say that
we generally know
oh like I remember getting a lot of
complaints in the beginning so that I'm
not you know friendly but hey by now I
should be your friend like I stream from
the EU
am I not your friend I'm the only one
like I stream
usually between 3 P.M to midnight
that's it can't
get it in that I don't know why anyone
would complain if anyone complains I
don't know why you would complain where
are we by the way oh
okay okay okay the x is like close to
zero
[Music]
and just said it's changing that's good
okay
foreign
a friendly okay I'm happy about that I
am I'm just kind of sad that I had to
leave
my sea Bros behind a little bit
um like especially this week I tried to
have a few more streams
um from in my evening time
partially because I saw that the slot
was free in this in the calendar I was
like okay I'm gonna take it my slot now
but usually I always try to mix it up
there there should always every week
there should be some streams that are
good for SCA and some streams that are
good for Na and generally every stream
should be good for Europe yes
[Music]
4 AM gang what do you mean right now
it's 4am
oh dear
hey where are you at
thank you guys for still trying to catch
my streams and if your archive game
hello Minecraft games hello hello future
this is the past how you go how are you
doing how's it going
thank you for taking time to watch my
archive
I appreciate it
and thank you to the live people as well
you all are fabulous gorgeous Divine
Exquisite Majestic beings
Sasuke
ah which makes me think of that clip
that has been going around
I got so many replies yesterday like out
of nowhere like I didn't even like this
just because of the clip like out of
nowhere literally they're like yeah
don't feel so bad about it blah blah and
um that's very sweet and all I
appreciate it but I literally only
replied to a Super Chat
and now everyone's like so worried about
me
there's no need to be so worried about
me I'm all good
I'm okay
I just realized
this should have been
three blocks tall
[Music]
because of the ice like it can't
yeah one second I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll
I'll I'll I'll fix it
it should be free at least at least
three
[Music]
no no no no the Clipper is not at fault
the Clipper also Clips other things of
me not only like
sad moments although that does seem to
be a popular popular choice of moments
that people like the clip of me
where I say some sad things
but most of the time it's just me
replying to Super chatters
it's not like I constantly bring up
these sad topics on my own
but no I'm not mad at the Clipper at all
it's just I was I was kind of like
after getting so many replies yesterday
that like everyone's like almost babying
me
oh man and then then I then I even got
some replies from people that are like
you know that yeah you're doing great
who don't even follow me so I'm like
yeah you're trying to be supportive here
by tell writing me this nice message but
you don't even follow me so you're not
really
[Music]
how the hell did they date
spawn in here
how do I prevent that
so yeah I wanted to say you're not even
like you could help but I don't know
following me you're not even doing that
so
because of the line okay damn it is it
too late now are they gonna leave if I
put the lights down
[Music]
what what's about the eyes
when you build the ice Road put buttons
on the ice I saw the trick
they'll do spawn eventually okay but I'm
kind of scared about hitting them right
now when I mine the blocks
[Music]
yeah so anyway I just wanted to say I'm
fine
um
I I appreciate that many people are so
worried about me but I'm actually fine
[Music]
yeah I have a very loving and caring
Community called kfp
and they're the best fans that I could
ever ask for
of course like
it can always be it could always be
better
in some way but
it's not like I'm crying every day in
bed because of a lack of viewership
that's not it
[Music]
guys I love you I love
and to everyone who did worry about me
also I'm not mad at you guys either
because it's it's sweet I appreciate it
I appreciate the thought
and some people said they will try to
catch my streams again like they
they're gonna try to catch my streams
this week
because of that clip
well well okay
see the clip did have some positive
effect then as well so don't be mad at
the clipper
he had no bad intentions I'm sure of it
I don't want any like
bad feelings
here
let's just
live in peace and Harmony huh how about
that
[Music]
sounds good right
good words
everyone
is just trying to okay maybe not
everyone but everyone who's here I hope
it's just trying to do their part to
support
me
and even if you're not trying just you
being here is already a support so
doesn't matter if you send Super Chat so
you're just watching my stream or if
you're watching an archive
if you're watching an archive or
what
or life it doesn't matter it all helps
me
you're part of the community you're part
of kfp
yes
[Music]
are there people tuning in asking what
we're doing in another uh we just
um found and looted a messed up by Omi
but I mean we're far from completely
looting it thank you for the pink y
and now we're starting to the path
from the headquarters to the Mesa by Omi
which I didn't think I would do it all
in one stream but here we are
foreign
guys being being
[Music]
helpful doing stuff
what do you mean when the firebird
attacked you mean me
some Harmony yes
yes I looted
yeah
you're loading me by saying that I
looted a biome not the type of person to
lose something
at all except baby for myself if you
look at Twitter you know what I mean
I have to say
when it comes to squishing fines it
feels much nicer to squish them on the
inside than on the outside
if you know what I mean like the inside
of the fine
but um and I tried that I tried it on
that picture for Twitter
but it didn't
um because the hand is so short
the hand PNG is so short I couldn't
do it that way
squeezed on the outside I squished and I
squeezed on the outside
[Music]
Still Still I must say quality
squishiness
over nine thousand
both
out of on both yes yes indeed we will be
using boats here you know
[Music]
I hope there's not gonna be an issue
with like you know lag like some people
said there might be an issue
with like if you have a
uh if you don't if you're PC or your
internet connection is not so good then
you might have a problem loading in if
you go so fast like I don't know if
that's really gonna cause issues I hope
not
I hope I don't crash anyone's games with
my blah blah blah
that's a good name
I will remember that
speed limit maybe in between I could
like have some spots without ice to slow
them down
does that work or will you get stopped
completely if there's like one one row
of blocks without ice
do you continue sliding
[Music]
yeah if it's a German Autobahn there
should be no speed limits foreign
to help people with bad internet it
Cactus at the end would that help
[Music]
a checker pattern oh for the eyes
but I mean the whole reason why we're
doing this in the Nether and with eyes
is because we're gonna We want to be as
fast as possible right it doesn't make
sense to speed everyone down then does
it hmm
hi
[Music]
what do we do what do we do well first
of all we just built a tunnel I don't
even know if we can start building the
ice today
I didn't expect us to be so fast wait
thousand
that was only a hundred blocks from the
last time I checked oh my God
it does take a little while but way less
time than it took an energy she took
three months for her Mesa wrote Because
she built it outside not in the never
she built it in the Overworld
maybe Ina would like to help well I have
no idea what she's planning for today
but once she knows that I found the mess
of Wyoming and it's not that far away
you might want to join yeah
oh wait my chat crashed
[Music]
my chat crashed
I have to reload
I see it on lbs but I don't my normal
window crashed
are you okay Chad breathe come on
breathe
don't die on me now
you're back welcome back Dad how are you
doing
[Music]
how you doing Chad
oh I missed you can I have a snack
it's the first time I'm eating I'm
eating a snack I think
hmm
okay
you guys know
um
a beefy roll do you guys know that
yes
is that like a German Australian thing
a b-i-f-i
I know it's very common here
ah yeah she's probably gonna prepare
something for Lami that's right because
she has a collab with Mommy
I yeah not today but like she's probably
preparing something solo for it today um
I ate it in Belgium oh
yeah I don't know I thought it was a
good snap snack for the middle of a
stream
because it's like it's a it's a long
Slim
salami roll
um
inside of a long
bread roll
very simple
very very simple indeed
[Music]
salami sausage it's like a hot dog but
not as fancy and not as good because
there's no sauce
like a corn dog oh
yes where the corn dog is much better
oh no look at my pickaxe by the way I
need to go get some exp man oh no
oh no
I keep on picking up new habits because
of good uh
[Music]
900.
it should shut down
spawn be somewhere around zero is that
is that really it
that's gonna take a while
maybe Ina can dig from the other side
[Music]
foreign
on all axes like okay except except y
oof
yeah Ina could tell me the chords I mean
I'm sure somewhere
maybe that's maybe I have a screenshot
with coordinates
somewhere maybe
I'm not sure though
Ena definitely told me those coordinates
before remember that one time where she
rescued me off screen
and uh I think we got attacked by this
pig and then Ina killed the pig for me
oh yeah good times good times
on that one block path
yeah yeah yeah I remember well
oh yeah and one uh probably a different
topic that we had before but we got in
the Halloween wink one more thing now
we're doing is outlast
I bought the heart rate monitor it's
coming sometime soon
I'll do my best to set it up even
without the heart rate monitor we're
doing it there's no Escape for me
anymore
and what else am I doing for Halloween
wait let me see it
Alice little nightmares ah out west end
and uh the song cover release and
Minecraft with Cali in the end which I
guess is also kind of fitting and I'm
gonna do a cooking stream for a car for
pumpkin and make pumpkin soup with the
rest with the remains of it yeah
that's basically our Halloween week oh
and and then the Halloween
collaboration with uh the myth girls or
I think it might be
all of Holland English I'm not sure
[Music]
I feel like it was supposed to be all of
us
oh hello
[Music]
but no details about that yet because I
don't even know any details that's a lie
I know some details but I cannot share
however that might be for me already on
on the 1st of October I think
um
what's down here I'm curious
nothing
oh what a view
foreign
okay I am done looking I'll go back to
my tunnel and be quiet
ly build my tunnel
[Music]
years later
she was still building her tunnel
but it was definitely a good idea to
build it uh
up at the very top huh
oh it's already time she
stream now huh
she's starting right now
[Music]
she is
Early Access you know my stream
[Music]
mean
and I
what are you doing today
tell me
share with me your plans for today
[Music]
Taco Tony
didn't realize there's already 10 Pizza
time goes by so fast man
10 p.m finding a path a path
finding a path to a yard
you are quite the slimy slime ball oh
slimy tentacles
she has
[Music]
I'm about to slip y'all there
no my question was serious though I
really want to know people like to call
me limodo
I don't get the joke what's what's
really matter
and
[Music]
Ah that's slime anime oh
um
[Music]
maybe she has no plan
foreign
[Music]
she's explaining her accent ah oh that
accident where she slipped
oh yeah I read about that
gotta be careful when you're so slimy
you
enough ocean stairs stairs are evil doll
I don't like stairs either
I don't like going upstairs I do I do
enjoy going downstairs
uh oh she doesn't know
does she not know
oh
uh-huh
[Music]
she's not gonna share any details with
me
[Music]
I guess she's not available though
sounds like she's busy that's okay
works alone most of the time anyway
now that Mama takanashi Mama cannot join
the server anymore
which just reminds me I had some kind of
dream I think that someone else
some Randall wasn't our server I don't
know why I dreamed that
on our Minecraft server
don't don't ask me
[Music]
sometimes you just have weird dreams
random fact number one today I finally
found my uh
thingy
[Music]
seller room
colors
bass yeah well I mean yeah my my
particular basement thingy
[Music]
my my basement because there's a lot of
basements
I they showed it to me when I moved in
but I haven't used it since then so I
completely forgot I didn't know where it
is
so I couldn't store anything down there
but today in combination of something
else I asked for them to show me again
where my basement is
there's a lot of
little basement cells
now I know where it is now I can store
stuff there finally
yeah like a science storage yeah yeah
yeah there's a lot of like small little
rooms basically
[Music]
and one of them is mine
this is just normal I'm keeping track
don't worry about my pickups
although I don't know what I do when
I run out of it we have a silk touch
pickaxe
oh we could just I guess kill some mobs
to mend it there's there's more than
enough mobs over there in the Mesa
it what do you mean where's the rest of
them
no not really
I can give coordinates
coordinates
now she wants to come we have a first
a city attacks is one diamond
per day
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
cook
we gotta think of it in a business angle
you know
unless you pay two diamonds per day
[Music]
nice you're not exactly as if she
doesn't have any diamonds to share you
know is I think one of the richest
players on our server now
shipping
[Music]
she's hiding her stash of diamonds
she bawling
[Music]
no diamonds chuckle
no diamond taco
oh definitely hoarder Taco yes yes
hahaha
you must have some diamonds lying around
come on
oh wait I haven't placed a torch in a
while
[Music]
she's not gonna is she gonna get the
chords from the chat
ignore the coins for free
what why
we gotta make pancakes we think about
all the diamonds we could be swimming in
think about it
[Music]
don't mess it up Kathy
she's been real quiet now though
I'll tell her
I'll tell her the coordinates but I
expect some souvenirs
um
63 1000
1080 822.
that's my house
[Music]
that's where my house is
we're on stage oh you went far oh
it was surprisingly
[Music]
close to be honest
no
did it did it even take me maybe one
stack of uh
I forgot what it's called to someone who
can find circles oh yes are they you
know
what happened to
she has it she has a little extra
can fly too though
[Music]
my pickaxe
is almost done for
how far are we oh 700
we have like 400 blocks behind us
nice
[Music]
and no Lava is getting in our way that's
also very reassuring
toscato
[Music]
durability I know no chill
an eye on a chill chill
[Music]
it's a little bit more come on
let's all go a bit further
do you guys remember when your only real
remedies if you watch the collab from me
and amen the other day
you guys remember when I said that I was
watching these like uh crime related
videos on YouTube
[Music]
I watched so many I kind of got sick of
it already
[Music]
like now I'm just
I'm like worn out by
these crazy people and they're crazy
actions
have you watched the scama ones Oh you
mean you mean like the the scamming
calls ones oh I'm way past that I've
that was like my thing
three years ago four years ago
I was like really into that I was
addicted
I watched hours and hours of scammers
getting baited
yeah that was fun
now it's like boring because I've seen
too much of it
so unfortunately when you watch like too
much of something and you're sick of it
I'm going back
[Music]
yeah kid boba
um
my friend
I know it's almost broken that's why I'm
going back
[Music]
yum yum
I watch way too many cast streams and I
don't get bored
really
I'm happy to hear that I hope I hope you
never get bored
I really hope you do not
lock picking videos
no I have yet to follow into that rabbit
hole
I don't think I ever will
doesn't sound particularly interesting
oh yeah I was talking about my micellar
right
um
the other thing that
I've had uh someone take a look at was
my heating I think my heating is broken
like
um it's constantly heating I can't turn
it off
that's why
um I've been sleeping with open windows
every night and had my windows open also
during the day all the time this room is
fine but in my in my bedroom I think
it's only really in my bedroom
that my heating is broken
the window opened constantly because
it's really cold outside
I would be burning alive which is I
guess fine because I'm a phoenix but
still it's not very comfortable anyway
yes
[Music]
oh my God can you not
yeah could have at least given me those
EXP
[Music]
no
oh my God
[Music]
what the what the
oh yeah
well well will that thing forget that
the gas will he forget that I'm in here
oh will he like like Camp right in front
of it
[Music]
wait a second
oh thank God oh my God
oh
[Music]
you're gone
I think
uh-huh
foreign
still around somewhere
[Music]
thank God I brought flint and steel
I was probably close to not even taking
it with me
no one's here
[Music]
oh we spawn here
oh that's annoying
ah but I can destroy this one then we
would spawn in the other one
[Music]
I don't know
gotta destroy this one
[Music]
come on wait where it's over there right
okay
so far away
should I just right now
careful probably not
you have to build a new in never portal
for it to link properly destroying this
one won't help
but ah
if I build an extra portal in the nether
like right next to the other one that
one will connect to to the one close to
my house
[Music]
no and what how would I do it then
just destroy this one
[Music]
uh-huh ask enough destroy destroy this
one
need to destroy this one
okay okay okay wait wait wait I just
wanna do something about my pickaxe
ask Ina she helped crony
I mean is he not like coming right now
or is did she decide to not come at
least not right now
you guys know
maybe she's already here
she's AFK at the Trident fun aha
Hoy she's still that was uh scary
incident I thought I was gonna tell you
also let me check out
that
[Music]
maybe I can kill one or two spiders uh
if I put this on my right hand
it will mend it I think right
that was a close one yeah
oh didn't have time to stand to eat
so I decided to
Corner myself
damn and I should have brought the
second one
there's nothing here
nothing
um
I guess I'll go I'll go up here
[Music]
no I hear some skeleton inside though
mine calling ah
mine calling calling mine mine coin mine
and cold
now I got it I got it down
[Music]
damn it
go away
foreign
[Music]
the skeleton I heard was you crying
oh why are you crying what happened hmm
[Music]
what happened what can Mommy Kiara do
for you to make you
happy again
I'll do anything
no not anything I'll take that back
[Music]
those trees still haven't you spawned I
thought I got rid of them completely
they took a long time
no no
no not anything no no no no no no no no
no no no you guys started reacting like
this uh to that that kind of sentence
the way that Japanese audience usually
reacts then
foreign
[Music]
I can't find enemies I need to find coal
then but wait and in order to mine coal
I need to use my pickaxe
uh
[Music]
ah
kill enemies in the nether
I guess that works too but like uh the
the place where I spawned is like kind
of an awkward place
uh
skull
I couldn't mind that gold but do you
think in the process of mining it my
pickaxe will die nah
now
oh there's gold here too all right let's
try it out yes no
you're fine
like by mining one
I'll get already EXP
[Music]
oh I have to
that didn't give me expedo what
wait gold doesn't give exp when being
mined
what why does Cole give exp and gold
doesn't
what is that
it's ridiculous
I need coal
[Music]
Shield my Phoenix Shield
oh wait is there coal here maybe
I get my Shields Shields Shields
Shield
[Music]
my Phoenix Shield
special limited edition
[Music]
is there a new coal
wow
nothing
only items you don't have to smell like
cold diamonds Redstone quartz lapis oh
damn and now I'm in this huge puddle
do I have
yeah I could make
[Music]
I need to get back up again
and also build up like this
[Music]
I hate when it bugs around like that so
laggy
[Music]
now for once I would appreciate it being
Knights and enemies running around for
once
[Music]
like I can't just aimlessly mine into
the ground now because of the lack of uh
Health durability
on my pickaxe
smelled never rat yeah but then I know I
don't have a I don't have a furnace
right now
[Music]
wait
foreign
ers
and now I need I need wood though
you can smelt never Rock
also what I don't have anything to smell
it with there's some trees over there
[Music]
wait what do you get out of Netherrack
if you smelt it
never breaks ah
wait I don't think I've ever made those
before
[Music]
that would be a first
excuse me I'll just take some of those
although the Sun is going down so we'll
probably meet some enemies soon
okay
[Music]
foreign
bus would give us success right yeah
oh well well
so
[Music]
and this gives me EXP
when I take it I guess so
[Music]
it didn't give me XP
at least I didn't hear cling cling
I don't know
yeah okay you know what
it's gonna
kill that dude
oh hello
fight
[Music]
yeah
let's see if I have it in my right hand
it should be mending itself right do I
have anything else with mints my sword
meant but but it should go to the to my
pickaxe
[Music]
yes I think I think I think it's only XP
thank you
[Music]
I do be gaming
there's a lot of Speedos
not you stupid little kid
ah this kid needs a leash
I'm usually not one for leashes on
children
but this child deserves it
you cannot let a child like that run
around freely
good
[Music]
yes exp can I also shoot
glibery you were
that's not very much an expedo
I need more
[Music]
what the hell
it's gonna take a while yeah oh I see a
bunch over there
my bow doesn't have mending right
yes okay let's let's snipe them
foreign
cat hair trying to kill me
[Music]
strong
takanashikiana what is this
barely doing something for my pickaxe
I'm gonna be fighting for centuries is
that an Enderman and the man give pretty
good experience
[Music]
foreign
and is it just me or is it lagging like
I don't I don't know man I don't know
I'm gonna die
[Music]
come on heel back up
this would be so much more dramatic if I
was playing oh if I was playing my
battle my dramatic battle music that I
was playing during the Woodland Mansion
takeover
[Music]
hello he got the drip
oh you think you're cool of that trip
show me your golden teeth come on
yeah
those golden teeth ain't gonna get you
nowhere
who's shooting at me now
you
[Music]
Have Eyes everywhere
good
nice
this will take too long yeah
should I just take my silk touch pickaxe
because I I got an extra I got a backup
pickaxe
[Music]
or I guess I could go coal mining now
because now I got at least enough to
[Music]
kind of just mine normally
little you little
[Music]
who is it now
I feel like I'm playing some kind of
zombie apocalypse game
[Music]
exp bars but you're not going up I don't
mean my only experience I mean mending
the the pickaxe and yes this one is
going up
oh that barely that didn't do anything
whoever told me to do that
that takes me probably a million
years
[Music]
now now it's getting down
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my God oh my God
let me let me go
I can't I can't take care of so many
people
I can do it I can do it I can do it I
can do it I can do it I can do it I can
do it
leave me alone they don't do much damage
today
nice
I thought I was on my boat what the hell
come back where's your friend did I
already kill your friend
yeah give me XP on it
and the night is over
[Music]
oh oh you got some Fancy Pants Mr fancy
fans
glowing pants you're trying to
make something stand out a bit more than
it usually would do
my headshot
flexing
[Music]
now our brakes are pretty though so I am
going to make use of them eventually and
where is that exp from that other
Phantom hat
it didn't drop any didn't drop anything
all right okay
this is okay give me that
um
foreign
wait a second let me throw some things
away here
have these have those
bye bye
and I'm gonna take
this back
[Music]
and I guess
speed
do they give more exp than those other
enemies probably not right I kill him
though
I want to kill them
[Music]
what's for
oh
speeder no
sleep
snip snap oh
they're like what is going on hit one oh
I hit another one oh there's mommy
they're coming for me
oh God oh God oh God
[Music]
ah it's coming fast
oh dear
oh dear oh there we go
[Music]
oh they give good exp they do a little
bit of it went uh into the wrong place
that's unfortunate but oh well
on it wait now I got the curse on me
though
do you have any more milk but
um
I'm gonna go into Phoenix
maybe if Ina comes over anytime soon she
could bring me milk but
I might just camp
um because I'm not gonna finish building
a tunnel Brown I might just camp
and
in my in my Mesa by Omi home
um
in a milk delivery you think she got
some milk
ingredients
oh
you think she can uh provide me with
some precious milk
almond seems to think so oh what does
that mean what does that mean
is Amit taking milk from Ina
and I don't know anything about it
[Music]
there's a vending
I had a vending machine
[Music]
what is she currently doing still at PPP
or TTT
[Music]
um
hunting Any Man Creeper oh is she ah
creeper from base creeper from oh the
the one where I took everything haha I'm
so sorry
I'm sorry
I took everything
[Laughter]
[Music]
is
cat ears
oh my God you know it's cat years I just
realized imagine her with cat ears
although it would look maybe a little
bit weird in combination with the
flip-flops that she has the flaps
they're flaps on top of her head
[Music]
she does have her flaps yeah but imagine
cat ears oh that would be so that would
look so cute on her
it's kind of difficult to pronounce
though but I'm sure she would say it
so often
I don't think she could hold back on
constantly using that
ah fishies
I just want some coal can we get another
mind going yo Maybe
that is mine in here
foreign
[Music]
into the mountains ah
that was probably somewhere where I've
already been to before ah
oh there must be some coal in there I
wasn't here before and I probably left
some coal
I probably did
Cole
called Uncle
please I'm desperate for some yummy exp
what is this place that's weird foreign
still no call
[Music]
maybe here
come on
[Music]
I see I see it
how much does it give me though
[Music]
um
not that much evil but at least we get
like some chunks of it
foreign
okay
we're back in the game
oh gold as well but I don't want any
more gold I'm actually declining it
thank you
[Music]
oh my god did I I set my spawn Ryan I'm
fine I'm good I set my spawn
[Music]
dig while I'm being smothered by it I
don't know if I can do that I think it
will fail but I try my best I think I
have it in my hot bar I have the I think
it's one to the right or one to the left
[Music]
oh my god oh
you gravel oh it literally like all fell
down when I was logged out
hello
I escaped yeah
tell me
uh milk indeed if you plan on coming
here anytime soon would be nice to have
milk
is she planning to come now anyway I'm
glad I'm glad I'm alive
oh oh she wants to choose
[Music]
instead of bringing me diamonds she
wants to bring me milk now
having a special milk oh
oh
is it milk made of out of diamonds
Diamond milk
oh my God that's a lot of coal
what about it you know
is she gonna tell me more about it or is
that it
milk made out of diamonds
[Music]
low price of uh entrance to the mess of
iomi could it be could it be could it be
[Music]
unlimited yeah I'm living it for one
milk
and drink a drink
that's all
foreign
[Music]
if you call within ah
The Next Movement I should call
is she asking me to call on Discord
buy one get one free
so two milks for unlimited
hahaha
well customer series really slow here
she doesn't pick up
customer service slow AF uh
why hello there
you took a long time to pick up there
what the hell oh it's called it's called
a streamer mode on Discord
you didn't notice uh-huh okay I didn't
yeah um yeah uh this is a Taco uh are
you calling uh in regards to the uh the
milk deal we have going on right now
could I um get a like do you have like
what's what's the milk made out of
can I get like a list of numbers get one
free on it one one get one free wow are
you robot
what a deal
um
I'm only uh allowed to say the uh things
on the manual sorry I'm just I'm just a
lovely uh worker here supervisor
uh yeah give me a second yeah I'm
waiting I'll be waiting I don't have
much time though so you better hurry up
give me your supervisor hello
are you not like a child you sound like
a child you don't sound like a
supervisor well that's real it's a saint
I come on you I want you Mickey Mouse
oh
I just found out
oh no oh my God no no no no that's not
the name I go by here well so um I
wanted to know a little bit more about
the milk that you're selling
milkyness
can you tell me like what's what the
milk is made out of like where does it
come from which animal or which human
being or so
oh it's a it's not human milk it's uh
milk made out of hopes and dreams
okay is there any diamonds in that
um
let me check what the Nutrition
department okay thank you wow there's
even the supervisor doesn't know what
they're selling like what are they doing
unbelievable they're only a distributor
not the uh
not the uh actual Farm you know
let me uh okay interview the providers
of this
this milk and it kind of sounds
suspicious that you can't give me much
information about this milk that is
supposedly so much worth that you would
get access to unlimited missile biome I
don't know seems kind of iffy you know
well
it seems like it's not Diamond milk it's
not that it is this Emerald milk what
what milk
Emerald Emerald milk oh that sounds
better at least
yes it's it's a favorited by the uh
members of Phoenix town
oh well well if it's if that's the case
then I guess I must make a little
exception
can only be given to one person
all right who should I make it out for
the axis pass
ah make it out into uh uh Nino Nino me
Nino
Ina nice
uh-huh okay never heard of that girl
before do you mean uh someone called
Nino Maya inanis
uh I think that's what she calls that
yes okay okay yeah I I know her I know
her yeah yeah she wanted three axes
originally but okay good good so you
will deliver the emerald milk
ah yes please tell me the coordinates
and the uh I already wrote them in the
chat
oh you're still at that location yes oh
oh I'm not exactly but I can go back
there immediately
all right are you we will be there
sometime okay you probably need like
about one stack of fireworks in order to
get here
oh that's no problem
almost dead anymore
are you still where are you at right now
milky Mouse
I'm uh over
uh at the uh
at the uh the hiring Farm
how are you laughing at my voicemail
no why would I laugh at your voice is it
beautiful I got that a lot I feel like
you could probably also do an impression
of Elmo
what's the whole impression uh
wow I will I'll keep that in mind
I'll request it next time
I I'll I will practice man I'm looking
forward to it okay
do you mean anything else
I found an interesting zombie villager
I'll kill it
I don't know my with my experience what
the hell you scare me
the Villager no
because of how much I worked with
Phoenix Suns
I can't kill him
darf Mouser
oh no she's found out
wait I gotta stop it
okay and it turned on the chord 306.
okay you basically actually it's really
easy you just from um you don't even
have to look at coordinates it just go
south from the spawn point
um last time I just went South I ended
up north no
uh yeah and people make fun of my
direction sense
I think you've got I think you've got a
better Direction sense than most of
Halloween
I'll be honest with you I'm not sure
um uh mine is not really good either oh
my God north south is towards uh okay
South is South South is when you open uh
F3 F free and you
um you gotta look at the the Blue Line
the blue line has to look straight ahead
the blue line in the middle
oh my God okay
oh
we're on our way ma'am oh are you sure
you don't want anything on the way oh my
God that would be amazing although I
actually kfp is better and um I hope
okay if he's close right now they don't
know it was always open somewhere yeah
but oh I'm getting hunted down by oh no
okay getting hunted down I've been I've
been in a pickle for a while here
um oh
are you almost ready
what
you said you're in a pickle you're gonna
be a pickle ah I'm not trying to become
a pickle oh yeah
I thought I thought chicken pickle was a
new thing is there such thing as chicken
pickle chicken pickle
what what I have experienced recently is
uh uh popcorn chicken
it's my first ever had popcorn chicken
before no until like last week but I
have to say I'm not impressed because
it's literally just tiny chicken nuggets
it's literally
sorry
um I'm trying to kill some all kinds of
mobs here
I'm like desperately trying to get exp
to mend my to mend my pickaxe because
I've been um I've been digging a tunnel
in the nether to make a tunnel from the
uh sorry to
oh my God from from headquarters to uh
uh the the mess up Miami
yes yes uh and I'm pretty far already
pretty far but like ah all right all
right
[Music]
well uh seems like I didn't even have to
wait did you send your uh spawn to
yeah yeah and spawned I have to have
like a little house here but no
no wait okay just come uh explosive my
things my things my face well now I
don't need the milk anymore so
um I need the diamonds now
are we is that I'm sorry dear the
transaction has already gone across
I'm afraid there's no refunds I no it
hasn't come across because I don't have
the milk yet I would like diamonds now
I'm sorry but it's not refundable
then I will now just destroy
the Mesa biomi so that there will be no
more mess up iomi that's a lot of work
where is where did I die where did I die
where did I die
wow wow wow
it's okay I'm looking forward to meeting
you milky Mouse
all right
I had one more milk in my chest really
I thought I drank it already no I didn't
right
I didn't
swim that I had ah oh wait I really
could have just asked for diamonds then
oh my God I'm not gonna find my things
I know this place are you already here
oh I'm at the um
I'm at the Copper Express
that's it
I was like this looks familiar
it's like exactly South
uh South what's that okay
[Music]
it's not here
it was somewhere on a higher level
did you lose all your tools elytra
my my never right pickaxe not not it
would be my never ride pickaxe the the
wasting tools uh if I don't find it but
my elytra I'm wearing right now because
I had it in the chest and I'm using it
to look for f what F3 and B what what is
that F free and B what is that
what is that at the same time
what what is F3 and B
it doesn't do anything oh
B is that um what's it
look the uh
hitbox yeah
shown it hasn't been it hasn't been five
minutes yet I don't think
yeah yeah wait what does that do
what does that do show hitbox of items
what does that mean
show the grip yeah okay how far away do
I see that
okay okay
nice Chad holy holy macaroni chat
did you find it
Genie no I didn't but okay we still have
time stop time
I didn't go that far did I
wait
wasn't that around this area
I was pretty far away
if I needed a stack of fireworks to get
there means I need a stack of fireworks
to get back oh yeah I'm probably unless
about to finish my tunnel and another
you'll be also it's a one-way trip
now um is this
the area I was that
did you make like a tower in the ocean
this was like
this was this was this nothing
you can walk home
oh no no no no no no no no no no no my
never mind pickaxe no and my animal and
my my Diggy call me
oh I don't know where it was
was it up up upstairs above ground below
the ground it's above ground
[Music]
um did you put the Torches around there
anywhere or two two thousand there's no
way it would be like around two thousand
what do you think or 200 did you say 200
is it 200
201 200 and what
log out and check default can I is that
is a smart thing to do
yeah because the chunk isn't loaded then
it won't disappear I think
I can't check the water though because I
would have to end the stream oh that's
true
[Music]
is anyone recording it's not I'm still
far off so
what's that is that a village before
made me well it's a desert temple
wait have I been here is this the one I
looted
how how far away do you see those items
do I have to be pretty close to ground
chat
or because I didn't see anything when I
was like further away it's not gone
don't
save minutes yet
fly high up really
are you okay no
no I'm not okay
find it no
wants your sticks on the ground
I don't know where the hell I am and
where I was
it's not there it must be in that
direction I think
I'm trying not to load drunk
not sidetracked no you're probably so
far away
look for a creeper hole
um
I think it's gone don't give up yet
too early to give up I don't have
anything left to live for
oh my diamond armor and my my beautiful
beautiful weapons
my tall
two
did you get it
too early to give up
I feel like some things may be missing
but they might have broken in the expl
where's my pickaxe no it is there okay
but like I have no helmet and those
shoes but that's okay but my pickaxe is
there Kiana X is there Diggy call me is
there my shield is there
[Laughter]
ah
oh look at the the cries of the Phoenix
is a
we're filming something I was so scared
oh it's okay important thing is to not
panic okay
I was so scared to lose my favorite my
favorite sucking hey Birds hey hey Brent
sword the one I got from pick one on
seven five
hey what she was is written
looked
thank God I didn't lose that hey pretty
on stream spots even my stream Sparks is
still there nice Sparks
okay no no more danger now
okay I will I will now go back to the
safe Zone to welcome you with open arms
okay will you catch me
about what
oh no I said are you gonna catch me oh
I'll catch I've heard I heard Trust
oh well honestly now now is that a
motion volume
yeah there there's like I've also met
two emotional monuments on the way
what's the uh I'm gonna make uh what's
my call it because it's on the way back
right I wanna make a
the the fragment form thing my cheek
one day oh the lanterns oh
about to say oh yeah oh yeah thank you
chat for telling me that trick without
you guys I would have been I wouldn't I
would not have found it
thank you thank you chat
Minecraft sensei
arigato
now I can't find my base and yeah there
it is
you have the coordinates
foreign
[Music]
this ground looks like it's made out of
carrots I was so when I first found this
biome that looked so so amazing to see
it for the first time with my own eyes
I was actually watching your stream when
you first discovered it oh you were
watching
I thought you went to the GPS
oh Kiana has a principal and that is I
will not use resources from the Japan
server unless I'm building something
into Japan server
wow so I wanna I wanted to find the Mesa
by Omi on our server so that we don't
have to go over there and we can use our
own resources yeah
and now we have it and it's not even
that far away and I'm currently building
the the never tunnel it's quite far away
no no fed like nothing to me
Island rare
sorry
all the way
yeah what the hell are your coordinates
I need to know
well let's put the Mushroom Island that
is one of the rarest ones that I just
flew over it oh really you just went
straight South did you I think so where
are you whoa where are you
three five six
oh my God oh my God so excited six six
three two nine three five six two six
three two nine thank you
you don't you can log out and I sleep
here okay okay oh my God I wanna see
excuse me
um in order to access the Mushroom
Island you better I'll pay you up you're
diving done for us one one for the other
you you now let me know where that is
and I'll let you know where to mess up I
always go
but uh the it's just really really rare
but I think there's actually no
specifically
special thing about it this Vlog why
should I take more oh it's just dirt oh
that's some weird looking dirt
what if I get rid of all the mushrooms
before she comes ah red cows and mobs no
no there's only red cones it's weird oh
I see them oh I see the red cows
oh
you look awfully familiar
familiar with a certain Halloween member
it no I understand what
oh
doesn't the color remind you of me
red red equals Bay
Molly come look come look you literally
if you look you'll know you'll know okay
please wait for me I'm I'm trying to
figure out what I'm doing here uh okay
wait is there milk red
Google
I'm having studying studying problems
okay well glad to know that uh red cow
milk is still milk oh you can take milk
from them too yeah they are cows
thousand
that's like halfway through yeah
no I said I should make like a like a
like a stop in between for that by only
as well
man it's pretty big because like it's a
small island I'm building a straight
road so if you really only went straight
then well you can get soup
you mean mushrooms we're making a soup
you can get soup from the the cows if
you make a bowl with that I don't have a
what you look
I don't know craft I don't know what
wait I think we'll get wood
what
beef in it
oh it's what is that
I look like a bee cute is that a witch
house
who who are you talking to I'm gonna
uh everyone
okay
I heard her she said
oh yummy oh
no not the pigs no
[Music]
not the base the poor cat I took her own
I could have brought my uh
sugar
well that was worth it
yeah I want to get rid of is there
anything special here
so sorry
there's nothing here like witch's houses
are so useless like what do you get
there nothing
you get a witch
es
wait North North
to make a face here
what do you need to make up oh on it
okay
you'll find the jungle on the way too by
the way this is this this is gonna be a
really great uh road if I make a stop at
the jungle and stop at the mushroom
Naomi and the stuff that the mess will
buy on me you get everything
all in one line
yeah you get a soup supply wait can you
like
can you like bring a horse or
like one of these back and then they
infinitely provide soup
uh I wonder
I wonder I don't I want to yes
but apparently you can get infinite
mushrooms too
can you
if you have two of them
are they gonna make babies
I'm not gonna be that far anymore once
we have the The Ice Road in the nether
which direction am I going what the hell
yes apparently they can three five six
six thousand well I wanna bring them
back once we have the uh pathway
now an infinite soup
yummy
but I don't really like soups in
Minecraft because you'll have to have
the bowls and you can't even stack the
bowls right
yeah I don't think so but but they're
good for good for some menu oh it does
look different than like the mushroom
Forest oh oh are you here
well I'm here where are you
I'm kind of in the back of the uh
oh the island
well I'm trying to find you
I wanted to see this one and has never
seen it before right didn't she say that
to me last time she hasn't seen it
really
sure I can show you the mushroom
world
you can make a mini biome just to spawn
them back at HQ what what how
silk touch
stop touching get a whole bunch of
mushrooms maybe no of those blocks these
dirt blocks
oh cute
oh
they have mushrooms on top of them oh
yeah wait I'm gonna bring some of this
dirt back then pan again I do
I'm not no I don't have a shovel but I
have a pickaxe it's so weird
oh I need more inventory do you have an
Ender Chest on you by chance uh there's
any chance in the
um okay Safe House
with me
how big does it have to beat the spawn a
horse or a horse cow though
where are you
no firework
uh wait let me
did you hear that no
I think if you can't you see me in the
middle there's like a there's a
oh no there's like a lake kind of thing
in the middle of the island yeah
I'm I'm there
shoot one more
no I think I'm in a different part
where where exactly what are your exact
coordinates
uh uh four four one six four nine seven
uh
what 400 x is that it yeah four four
eight four four eight four four eight
four four four four
before
yours probably just beyond the little
Hill over there I'm thinking
because I thought I thought it was a
small uh Island but like
you go over the hill and there's a whole
bunch
yeah probably
four for eight and and uh
six four five six
I'm very close
very very close you
are you up on the hill on top of it well
I'm by the lake in the middle yeah
yeah I'm by the lake too
well I guess I guess there's a lot of
lakes but
wait stay where you are don't walk stop
walking you know
I'm walking
they stopped yeah
I just heard the sound of someone
milking a cow I think that was not me
really
what was that sound
are you here
you said by a lake
okay it's so hard to find you
it was right over the hill
over the hill firework please
did you hear that no
oh what about here
oh there you are hello
oh he came out of the ground hello I
haven't seen you in a while
so oh yeah
I was telling you oh this is like the
mushroom spores on the ground on the
dirt
oh
I don't have a bed
oh oh
do you want to like stay here or come
with me to the metal place I I wasn't oh
yeah I was gonna give you milk yeah but
now I don't have your space
[Music]
said I don't have the curse anymore
because I died once and I had milk
anyway actually
well wait I have a bed oh I have a bed
oh I have one too made out of
super special spider silk
um
that is extra soft and extra disgusting
is it itchy when you sleep
no it's just slimy and disgusting and I
feel eyes looking at me
hmm
all right you want to come with me to
Mesa
all right let's go
I wanna I just did you try to maybe put
them in a boat is that possible I wonder
and it's still I'm sure it's possible
but still quite a long ways back
we could get something for another
portal right yeah I think so so if we
get them for the nether portal and then
on the ice Road it's a really safe road
because it's a tunnel yeah at the very
top so they wouldn't be attacked by
anything evil or run into lava it's just
a one-way Road simulation fly what you
can fly no that's that's your chat lying
at you
oh no way
no way although I don't want to see what
I get if I do this just normal dirt
uh-huh
I see okay when it sucks touch for that
I didn't bring so much
okay well we'll get some of the dirt
here but I'll get more just in case look
at them eventually
those beautiful red cows oh my God
hey look at them don't they remind you
of they yeah yeah they do they look
exactly
you should put a mushroom on base head
can you take like the mushrooms off on
the of their back I think so what's
cheers I don't want to hurt them do they
attack you when you hurt them oh they're
just a cow but I can't really hurt it
at least use shears and then you take
the uh the mushroom don't you no
alternate normal cows oh
also what what if you bring a cow
here will they get infected oh
and become red cows or am I because
someone in the chat said that if you you
can like recreate the bio biome right no
oh
but if you break the only place on here
I guess they they're only useful for
getting infinite mushroom soup
which is not really that worth it
because the balls are
um
it spreads oh the mushrooms corrupt
everything is that true
hey
soup machine cool we should get at least
one of them somehow over to our house
yeah I want infinite soup all right now
you follow me
okay uh
South South is This Way South
all right you ready to go you need
yourself
I got I got my stuff the stuff that I
needed the stuff there's that's good
[Music]
we need to go until like around 1 100 or
something like that
ten thousand uh yes
yes
I keep on getting distracted but there's
a ship here right now in the oh that's
like Titanic in the water
where where it's a stone oh oh where did
you fly past me
you're still behind I don't know
if you keep on flying straight and then
look right
at 7100
14th what's that is that copper oh
that's called
what seven thousand okay I'm not there
yet oh okay
now I'm allowed to make stops right
before I was literally slow because uh
I'd like to enjoy the view you know I
get that
free
worlds
whoa
let's are you getting the ship yes good
is there treasure no not anymore no not
anymore no I meant treasure uh map oh
not not yet uh yes now I have one oh
oh are you here
oh yeah yeah I'm right here you want to
go look for the treasure map quickly
I found nearby yeah I have the treasure
map but let's see
where is it dokodoko
oh
oh uh chat help me out where do I have
to go when I look at this
uh
which way do I go oh I need some paper
actually
good south east Southeast
Shelf
this way wait was that Oliver just
like I took the rest oh
I mean there's sometimes like multiple
like more than two yeah I saw two I
don't think there's more than two in
this one
Southeast
there's super ship okay
okay where are we going
try to go try to follow me I'm on the
top of the ship
I'm doing a a Titanic moment here
[Music]
why are you like one up here okay oh
there you go okay
well self
IES
Southeast myself this way
[Music]
did you watch that
yes
right here
my fireworks isn't working I think
itself
your fireworks are not working oh copper
yeah I can't fly on water darn it
Adorn it
is
oh it's a
drowned
coming down here I got it I got it it's
another
Go Get It Go Get a trident go go go Gina
I don't think they have tried and Sear
s
what is the trick again to getting the
the treasure well there's like four of
them
it was a trick again
chunk nine nine
nine nine nine nine nine nine nine
nine
nine nine nine oh it's just uh it's not
a temple but
oh my no it's a trident oh it's a
fishing rod
there's so many ground here
you thought you thought you found the
Trident but it was a fishing rod yeah oh
no disappointing I don't want to get
suffocated again here
I'm disappointed
there's a lot of John I wish there was
just the Drone for me
I'm at nine nine and just eat the
mushroom I can't it will not be under
sandstone
well let's find it no I'm very very
close to finding it
South South Southeast
I don't know where you are
never understand
oh
weird
was that not nine nine yeah
I'm everywhere
okay
guess it means I just you turn and go
back home no no wait wait wait
I almost have it
uh
uh you could just if you wanna you could
also go ahead to the Mesa biome if you
if you want to see it but I'm almost
done why can I not find it
in there
85 588 7385.
7385 something around that
annoying this way
five eighty six nine
why can I not find it
[Music]
here oh there you are
where is my Chester
where is my chest doll
if it if it's not at 99 goats what oh my
God you gave me a shock enough
look down
I'm looking down
hook chunk
nine
oh
it's not this you found a chest
no
nine nine
apparently not uh
I think I was a little bit off there
nine maybe not
I thought this was nine
wow what about you
wrong chunk apparently
wait I gotta understand I wasn't I guess
I was not standing exactly
at the right spot on this is zero
no it has to be on the sand
14 13.
why is this one so difficult to find for
me
10.
are you on the edge uh
I I am
I am
I am now now this would be a x but this
is not 99 this is like 13.
that here here it is there it is
n't that what you need
I already have a couple of those I don't
really need it oh can I have one yes
what else is in there
um golden Emerald do you want it
I'll take the emerald
okay
if I if I don't die in the water first
I'll take them gold and TNT
it's getting dark enough
grab the emerald you didn't really pick
up the gold still
I picked them up the nuggets are stuff I
threw away
because I don't have space ah okay oh
yes and then
sleep yes
oops
and then we go to the Mesa by Omi and we
will not let anything stop us anymore
of course of course
of course
should you usually like put the map back
into the chest like in order to I don't
know not make it spawn anymore
because I have this issue before like I
found the same treasure maps over and
over and over again
where's the chest
oh yeah
break the chest apparently destroy the
chest ah
uh-huh will do
uh-huh
okay special
okay
okay we're a South
South
uh West a little bit
she already leaves okay
are you sure you're going the right way
yeah we just have to turn a little to
the right a little bit that's about it
for this 306 10 822 so
final's pretty big you'll hit it just
going south yeah yeah yeah
we'll see it eventually
wow we need to repair my elytra sometime
how's your durability
I'm around halfway so I'm gonna have to
kill some mobs to repair my Elijah good
luck before I go back
good luck with that
that took me a million years that's why
I died because I was trying to get exp
[Music]
wait I'm totally is this the jungle bio
yes Stellan are you saying another one
on the way so make a we should make a
stop here too yeah yeah that's what I
was uh trying or like planning to do
like make a stop at the oh
at the jungle behind me and the mushroom
by Omi and at the last stop would be uh
the the mess up oh apparently there's
jungle temples
oh yeah I think I've never seen one of
those treasure I haven't seen one either
I haven't been to a jungle I think
also pandas oh yeah yeah
[Music]
and birds
parents how do you tame the birds
let's see I don't know but
um
hmm ah
let me
are you okay
you didn't scream so you're not dying
it was
oh I was unable to breathe
um
I was one hide away from dying thanks to
Lava
yeah foreign
[Music]
there's there's a lot of stuff I want to
mine here
um
damn it I just remember the coordinates
we'll be back we'll be back yeah
remember no tangents
yeah supposedly
but you know how it is when you see
something that was interesting was that
nice
at least there's ice here we can mine
real
fast or close by is it blue eyes so
packed eyes
it looks like blue eyes
and then look at the Block and on the
right side you will see the block that
you're looking at on on F3
wait why is there a hole in the wall
why wouldn't there be a hole oh never
mind
you're scolding me he's school he's here
information all packed ice
ah I have a lot of packed eyes but it's
okay I already I already have a
different
um ice by all me well blue lights is at
the bottom oh is this blue I also have
blue eyes already
but I might need more probably is it
pretty fast to do like alternating
blocks
ah oh I don't know about alternating but
blue eyes is kind of the fastest one
yeah so I saw something where instead of
putting like all the blocks they took
the like alternating blocks let's save
some blocks
oh yeah why not
doesn't need to be all blue eyes it's
too fast honestly someone says yeah it
could be
um unnecessarily faster like so fast
that it crashes someone's game
yeah people warned me about that if I
make that Highway in the nether then
it's gonna be too much for some people's
PC
oh yeah
well
we gotta be fast though
gotta be speed
and then she's done that a couple times
oh is there another chance not another
gate that's another gate here already
yeah you mean the one in the in the
water basically yeah yeah that's the one
uh that connects
I made another one that's even closer
but that one is already very close to my
my my headquarters you will find certain
blocks that I need
if you go straight from there you'll
immediately see my tower
uh-huh
wait no oh no it's not the kfb hates me
no I don't have
don't worry can't see we're gonna end
soon
um
I'm gonna have the one I need I thought
it was supposed to make my block what
did you want
uh some crying obsidian oh I have I have
a lot a lot a lot oh how much you need
oh as many as you can spare
as many as I can spare
I have a lot of holes I think I see it a
little bit over there well you saw it
the trunk oh no I meant that messed up
item it kind of loaded in halfway yes
yes
you found it
I see the giant column of light
yes giant column of light
the Phoenix light
let yourself be enlightened by it oh
there's the uh
now I've I've already
um uh looted a couple of mine shafts
there but it's a pretty huge mess I'll
buy on me so if you go a little bit
further then I'm sure you'll find uh
other shops that I haven't looted yet
and okay I think it's more about the
endless amount of concrete blocks anyway
I do want to go see if there's any
chests with moss in it oh I haven't
found anything
some some rare stuff you know
um I think mosses sunken ships are
there's a lot of uh gold to mine a lot
of gold like a crazy amount of gold
an article oh you got a lot of
terracotta and uh yes you saw my my
Shockers yes
oh I guess change of plans we're
exploring the uh
blue I flew all the way here you know
yeah I knew that if you would see it
that you wouldn't be able to hold back
I need to fix uh cutting Corners anyways
oh oh she carry some milk
but Thor would be good I'll just I'll
just I'll just take a photo
okay
we can make
um
[Music]
Whatchamacallit uh what should I call I
like how you guys say that yes I do have
are you saying that we're looking at the
coal in my focal boxes oh I just looked
at it now
wait a second self
yeah I helped myself too so
okay it's Christmas
uh oh yeah
now I don't need it anymore but I still
want my Emerald milk
oh do you want some I guess so
well I can leave it in the shulker Box
okay well wait for me I want to at least
say goodbye boy okay I'm in the I'm in
the Box
sorry not the Box the uh the thing yeah
my house built you call it a box
it's not a box
it's a Happy Meal box
hungry
some McDonald's
oh oh yeah right I wanted to take a
photo as well for my
goodbye
um
tweet yes here I am turn around
yay
[Music]
picture I hope you have oh yeah yeah
yeah
I hope you have a lot of fun if you if
you uh you're welcome to use my bed if
you want oh thank you at the Ender Chest
if you want
many things enjoy yourself get a lot of
thank you concrete uh no not concrete
I always say concrete it is terracotta
yeah the the bed might smell a little
bit like gravy but a what gravy you
don't have problems oh okay gravy right
I thought you meant something else I was
like oh
what would that be
I don't know I want to turn my shaders
back on
um
these ones so next time I'll continue
building the tunnel and finish it
hopefully
yeah oh I want it to be daytime sleep
oh
tell me to sleep outside okay I'll sleep
outside
there's no ruins I mean I woke up in
space next to me I think yeah but I want
to smell like gravy
oh with this light it's beautiful oh I
wanna get up here
oh it's so pretty have you looked up
here
no
you should you can there's a lot of
enemies burning right now though
my Electro and I was like why can't I
fly
of course you know you don't have your
wings of course you can't
I'm walking
I'm assuming the stairs is what you made
on the way up stairs it's conveniently
uh yeah
let's take photo
oh my God it's so difficult to walk like
this
wait no this way follow follow
[Music]
okay
somewhere here I hear lava
look there's a spider don't worry don't
worry it's safe
do they bite
who
the spider yes they do
oh
cute
by the way life hack
uh-huh we destroyed his bushes you get
sticks
oh did you know
yes
they're the same as the desert by I'm
also there's a spider I never tried
destroying nothing I was really
surprised
oh hell yesterday
I've had some fights today also with
poisonous spiders that was fun those are
always exciting mm-hmm
anyway spiders don't attack during the
day oh I can't wait to see you just
killed them in the shadow
oh
shooting
do you shoot
no there's a there's a
skeleton oh the ultimate yeah be careful
too you might get lost because
everything looks the same and uh
yeah there's a lot of enemies at night
be careful enough I'll be fine
all right I'll leave you to it then
bye
have fun
no it was that was wet
what what did she say at the end okay
chat wait no don't say goodbye we're
gonna Read Super chattels
oh oh my God I wanted to jump into the
water I'm getting a little bit
um
two callous
it's time to
it's time to end it
so fast
she said that was wet ew not my fault
Ina
all right so we'll go to my office guys
and we'll read some super Shadows from
this stream we're caught up so we only
have to read the ones from today
um
so give me maybe two minutes
and then I'll see you in the office okay
I think I'll make some tea yeah don't
give me three minutes because I gotta
make my teeth
so far
and I hope you had fun in today's
Minecraft stream tomorrow is Sims and
the day after that is Warrior look at my
schedule and we have a lot of exciting
things today so in case you can't watch
the Super Chat reading today
um you're welcome to come to any of the
other streams this week it's an exciting
week yeah gotta love watching this at
school oh you're watching this at school
so that should I teach you some things
I'll be your teacher I'll tell you how
to say something in German I'll tell you
how to say I love takanasukiyana
there you go it's as easy as that
so okay office in uh three minutes Raja
um
intermission
[Music]
foreign
who waited for me huh
I'm still here
hello
for waiting
just one moment
myself
[Music]
how's the office looking you gotta go to
the Halloween office
is everything fun here oh my God
what
I'm all good surprise surprise
Casper is here too
my baby
[Music]
and there is chat there you go
nice to see you all again happy happy
spoopy month
everyone
[Music]
omata says Halloween
I covered him up yeah I don't know I
don't have a better space
I don't wanna yeah
let me let me put it like here
yeah yeah here is good okay
got a seat cast but you're right you're
right Casper is very important
[Music]
please don't vent in view of others
honestly if I become the Imposter
um because of my lack of experience I'm
pretty sure I'll either be too scared to
vent or I'll carelessly Bend
and accidentally get immediately seen
while doing it
both situations are very highly likely
however
um on my schedule it does say that
members only stream it will be um fall
guys but I change I'm changing it to
among us because
I was like yo I can still play that with
you guys you can play together with me
and I at the same time can get in some
practice because it's been a little
while since the last time I played Among
Us
yeah let's get in some practice to be
confident The Confident leader
well I'm not sitting correctly on on
this chair and also not on my actual
chair I guess
a little bit too big
there we go
okay
[Music]
huh
sounds like a plan yeah
so members are welcome to participate
what was it was it on Friday I think
it's on Friday yeah
I'm having like practice sessions
actually testing sessions with
um with the other Ian girls to make sure
on the technical side everything is
working fine
and I'm having a member stream on Friday
as well yeah having two members only
streams this week
where are my members at are you excited
two memories to make up for the lack of
a member stream last week
[Music]
nice happy chickens happy eggs
means happy Tanto
um
okay my tea is gonna take a while until
I can actually drink it so
[Music]
you spoil us no I don't I should scream
even more I should do like weekly
members streams to be honest
like I feel like I know a lot of or most
of the people who join the membership
as far as from what I read from your
guys's opinions
most people join really not really
because of the benefits but just because
wanting to support more which is
extremely generous and sweet
um
so that makes me think okay
um I don't need to stress myself too
much about it but still I want to give
you guys some good quality content
even non-members are excited
sweet
I joined what I missed it where did the
comment go
and Joint membership to support your
member streams are just a bonus yeah
there's a lot of people who kind of have
that attitude
hmm
great content already thank you
love this bgm I hope you don't get sick
of it I think if you listen to it for
too long you might get crazy
you might become insane
[Music]
ah yeah I guess
the the biggest reason to join
membership is really just using the
emotes
is in the hollow Birds picture yeah
of course
let's open Super chattels
am I my thing my problem is still not
fixed I think I don't I don't know
I think it's so I think I need to
reinstall Chrome or something but what
the hell
what the hell man
um
[Music]
I honestly don't remember because I'm
ready sent to credit cards oh
I don't know what that word means but I
guess you just don't want to like get a
credit card I understand that I still
don't have a credit card
hmm
is the Google Sheets at least working uh
probably also not because like last time
it also didn't work properly
no matter what I did
no matter what it's weird it's okay well
it's not that much I'll try to be
careful to not miss anything but you
guys let me know
if I missed something although the
sheets would be nice to have again
I didn't save it
la la la
foreign
you should have known what would happen
to you the moment you joined
[Music]
okay have fun at work the thing I sent
last time yes please
yes please
oh don't worry about it you don't need
like just because you're not a member
doesn't mean that you're not cool
you just ask cool
[Music]
not revealing one spots or feelings
readily ah okay
yeah there's like I uh some people who
just don't want to have stuff like that
yeah I understand that's okay
no problem Bee Movie
[Music]
you gotta premal of the Bee Movie
God damn it that's these chickens are so
hard to please
oh what is that that's cute
and I just went on Twitter and the first
thing I'm seeing is a really cute fan
art with me and the chicken a kfp member
adorable
and I'mma tweeted two minutes ago that
she's gonna have a cookie around Kingdom
collab of gouda on her Channel I think
that has been scheduled incorrectly
she this is not the first time she does
that
oh I got it thank you booshan
thank you
okay I'll save it this time
[Music]
traveling gone wrong
okay let's go Canadian cats bigs oh it's
an imposter
you see that Canadians he's trying to
impo imposter you
oh thank you girls
you made multiple book
thank you that's very sweet of you so
Canadian Mr caspick says I cannot
believe you said that you hate it
angry Canadian noises it's a it's the
superior topping for any pancake
no
Superior topping is Nutella with whipped
cream and like strawberries and more
berries and uh ice cream
that's that is the superior topping or
like bananas chocolate banana things
oh God
foreign
yeah this time you're around
Yokai Watch
it does give Yokai Watch but yeah oh
American beings right now I'm with you
hot wings maple syrup is overrated the
only topping I put on my pancake is
freedom USA USA
oh wait Australian pigs
I have nothing to add I just love this
account I thought you would write that
you add you put Vegemite on your pancake
come on Australian bigs you disappoint
me
I thought you would say oh wait is it
with a wink though it's with a wink
never mind this is the the the the real
Australia
oh yeah right we don't put Vegemite on
our pancakes
[Laughter]
don't taste Vegemite I'm not this thing
though where do those Australians really
put Vegemite on their pancakes
oh my God don't tell me you do that
Vegemite on your pancakes no that goes
too far right no no okay good man I hope
not nope
seen some do it
[Music]
wouldn't put it faster
now
[Music]
ask bae
correction might own pizza
but I have actually never tasted
Vegemite
I just heard it's uh it's not very good
foreign
I have a very picky
taste
#cluck oh we got a new hashtag
captivating lovable upbeat and
charismatic piano
I think hashtag Vulcan hashtag yolk is
already enough but thank you for that
that is a cute hashtag
oon
for the pinky
sorry boss I shouldn't have made fun of
your super weak kikiriki your very own
Phoenix after all is normal
then you don't have the strength anymore
I should be more considerate of the
elderly though I may oversleep a little
since I can't hear you
I don't know
well yeah good that he's already in the
usual room
calling me old
wow the nerve
[Music]
what do you mean Ina just finished a
tunnel
is basically done the tunnel what's that
mean
is she finishing my Tunnel right now
foreign
she's she's continuing my tunnel
okay wow
she's trying to get a quartz there's no
quartz up there on that level
she broke through to a forest eh
[Music]
oh
there's a tunnel there's a forest on the
way of the tunnel
oh dear she's looking for EXP
o
just gotta get home somehow oh she'll
she'll find you could be somewhere there
she should just fly
anyway
s
magical
hold it
is
[Music]
it's eroding apparently hours I said
Sarah didn't but you corrected me here
to say Sir Rodin you know what I should
just the way how I say uh that fire I
should continue saying Sarah Sarah then
the way I don't even know how I used to
say it anymore
it's supposed to be so rodent but I I'll
continue saying Sarah din
Sarah then Sarah didn't I'll say it in
different ways
just not the actual way
thank you
I am independent in this case I would
say yeah
Joseph what the hell is that a rainbow
it is
it's a rainbow
[Music]
um
Boss's Day boss's day was on Saturday
like what International Bus day
what
is that so
it was a special day of your boss guys
[Music]
oh there you are in the chat
um
[Music]
why did you guys not spam me about it on
Twitter
I should have tweeted something about it
damn it
well it says here's a hard-working cave
potential Awards and the most creative
Phoenix award and the squishiest Phoenix
wise onward oh and the cutest Phoenix
Olaf award
and the kfb Employee Retirement donation
for your Associates what I'll just put
that in my pocket is that okay
how dare you break my combo oh yeah
Elvis Elvis broke the combo with a
cuckoo combo breakup
that's very sweet of you so many awards
I don't even know where to put them all
never mind I'm actually gonna put them
put them on the Shelf where I put the
the plants on yesterday
so proud like I have three plants now
and they're all alive
oh it's alive for so long before it's a
miracle my mom must be so proud
[Music]
hmm
cut no not cacti no prep of plants I
showed you the picture of one today
should I show you again my new plant
I'll show you again
in case you missed it why did I save it
there
oopsie
there you go
my new plant
with a little bit of a advertisement
cook cook
I don't the Shelf is not quite filled up
yet there's still a lot of space without
plan for that shelf are there real plans
yes they are they are
yes of course they are hey
I hope this one will not die because
it's so big I had to carry it like
I have to carry it like with both hands
I had to like kind of princess carry it
home
[Music]
tunneled by myself
whoa okay how much is it only one please
tell me it's only one
otherwise I will receive the tunnel tax
it's my tunnel
okay she can have it
if she wants it
she may have it
[Music]
oh
she's way lower she's in a different
tunnel
[Music]
but I don't understand oh my God I'm
feeling dizzy
the thought of of me losing out on
neverend made me feel dizzy
she's she's continuing it's not my
tunnel it is the same tunnel why do
people say different things
it is the same tunnel
aha
she went quartz hunting she is not in
your tunnel uh um
um
one second guys
[Music]
you guys don't know what you're talking
about do you
hey
everyone says something else
oh man
your channel no she's not in your town
she's gonna tell no she's so completely
different she is literally in your
tunnel now she's somewhere else
flying to make you feel better
she made it back to I don't believe
anything that you guys say
I don't even know what the cop is that
the thing that they were building in
like like with crony and fauna
[Music]
she's in another same tunnel
tunnel section that's that's where she
is
real to the new chunk oh
my God
it doesn't even matter it doesn't even
matter
just kidding
I want to put my team
schroding is enough
she killed him
you are going too far
it's a joke for you
guys are killing me I'm scared of you
guys
foreign
[Music]
stop no point
Saucy Baka
[Music]
okay let's get serious
never say that again why not this is
like the third time I said it in my life
mom's trying to sound cool shut up
shut up you're the you're the right
person to say that
[Music]
I can't keep up with my chat today
it's like it's like the Zoomer is
ganging up on me the Boomer
even though I'm sure you guys are
boomers just as well just like I am
it's cute when Boomers try to stay with
the memes
not going to the usual room you're
getting a fast pass to the usual room
we boom together
sounds weird for shizzle
I got the hippest slang on the Block on
here
[Music]
Express ice road to the usual room yeah
that's where that road really goes to
and I'm just taking you guys along with
me and you guys don't even know where
it's really good
foreign
anyway Elvis thank you for a red Super
Chat as well
was it worth breaking a combo
definitely right it was worth it must
have been worth it
okay so let me open
um
translate Korean into English
[Music]
I need to sneeze I think
I always
for the red super chat
attention today is my birthday oh
finally this is it's been a long time
since I uh wished someone in the uh wish
someone a happy birthday not belated
um
and I heard you were into pancake
recently and my nickname in the 3 000
canopy Discord crew is exactly pancake
wait why is it on pancake here
you want to have a bite of me also can I
get a head pet and some pocket money as
a v-day prison I'm not giving out pocket
money
you're the money that you gave me for
the Super Chat could have been your
pocket money
but you decided to give it to me so
there it goes
[Music]
for your love and your support
and also I wish you a lovely lovely
happy birthday I hope you stay very
healthy and you reach your goals that
you dream of always dream big badly
very important don't dream to smile
because
you gotta aim for the big stuff
and on the way to the big stop you can
still go get the small stuff as well
so happy birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday
[Music]
day to you
congratulations
thank you for spending your birthday
with me
and now I cannot read this one even
that's Russian
universe
foreign
can you change your ways a little bit I
I recognize that immediately
you think I'm stupid
now it says
cheat
you changed it up I respect that
[Music]
but no I will not be
why does it say why are you the way you
are Kiana why are you a hater now all
right
just because I don't read your name
properly anymore you're salty I'm just
salty salty little chicken
you're missing some pepper though
and all the other spices you're only
salty
go go go go now jump into the spice
bucket Coco
[Music]
foreign
let's say if I want to do something like
what pecula's fan did should I make
rockets that use fire instead of water
as a fuel to make it phoenixly oh my God
we're talking about that water rocket
launcher that I that I talked about in
the beginning of the screen
I think that might be a bad idea if you
make a rocket launcher yourself that
instead of blasting out water would
blast out fire I think that might be a
bad idea I think that will literally
backfire
in your face and burn your face off
do not start a little chill fire today
no no no no streams box yes start a real
fire no
yeah that's just a flamethrower
hmm
[Music]
you are however all welcome to create
any kind of takanasikiara related
content
just like they know sakis did
and by the way that once again inspired
me to do something like a like a room uh
room room rating stream or like a pet
rating stream or anything like that but
I kind of want to go for some more
original idea like all of those have
been done before and I just can't think
of something really original
maybe you know what no I should ah I
have an idea
remember that one time when um I first
like created the menu for kfp
and people started making those burgers
maybe I should make like a KFC menu
Recreation uh
uh challenge
so you can not only make the burgers but
like anything that's on the menu
we can also
overhaul the menu
to get uh more stuff on there maybe
that's good and it will look we'll look
at good food for the whole stream
because like back then those burgers
that people made they look so good I
participate yeah really
I would maybe participate too make my
own Burger because
um I always want to try them I always
wanted to try to make my own Burger
I didn't do that before
you're assuming people won't make some
real gross stuff just for fun
yeah actually I I have a uh a hunch that
that will happen
because it happened for the chocolate
challenge as well the Valentine's Day
chocolate challenge
I remember there was a lot of cursed
stuff
I remember
I wish for this not to happen again
[Music]
with corn yeah yeah
challenging
oh yeah
middle
to you
Indiana
yeah sounds like a good idea put it on
my on my notes on my on my sticky notes
please care of me
[Music]
hot wings
although I will I think I'll put up a
rule that likes too simple stuff like
chicken nuggets
if you really only put some chicken
nuggets there and take a photo it's not
gonna be
it's not
allowed not gonna be entering the
challenge
there has to be a bit more effort in it
I'm like okay I mean it's funny if you
put like chicken nuggets there and put
chocolate sauce over it or whatever but
but
um I don't know chicken nuggets easy
you guys go all out on it
our spiders are loud I guess so
if you really need to put I don't know I
don't know where in the kfb menu it says
spider burger or something like that if
you look at all the ingredients I don't
think you see a single trace of spiders
in there so I don't know what would need
to happen for you to put a spider in
there
unless you troll me is unless that is
the goal
hmm
Australian Cafe menu
how come I don't know anything about it
hot to my burger wait is that in my menu
really
[Music]
that
what the hell
[Music]
um
please play me Danke Schoen
was that the red superche
yes it is
thank you thank you once again
for your sweet kind and generous support
I appreciate it thank you so much
hope you enjoyed the Stream
Stephen W hunt thank you also for the
red super chat
don't ever worry about us we are loyal
to you and will stick
stick with you forever love from the
community thank you
thank you so much
so we made a promise you and me right
Stephen
I I don't think we can speak for all of
the people but you can at least speak
for yourself
so I'll take that as a promise that
you're sticking with me forever and ever
and ever and ever and ever
I'm late to the end already yeah
basically but we're reading super chats
right now and
after that you're welcome to watch the
archive
we went on an adventure today
[Music]
this stream's title
sure dedicated an entire stream to
finding the message by Omi what about me
huh shouldn't you be looking for me
instead
I should honestly change the title now
though because now it's literally really
about finding the mess of iomi and I
think I'll change the thumbnail later on
too
[Music]
I think I'll change it
let me change the title already
we could just change it to Mesa by Omi
me
doco
there it is I found it spoiler I should
write in the title
spoiler we found it
and we found even more
it's incredible we're fought we found a
jungle on the way and we found
um the
the mushroom the super rare extremely
rare mushroom by Omi it's literally on
the way
I can't believe that we found that and
we found Ina yeah
I like the formula as it is I would keep
the the the Arts but the background I
would change that
Sasuke Explorer Bob yeah this is what I
like the most about Minecraft but
there's only so much you can find
in Minecraft on until you're like until
you run out of content unfortunately
oh
that's why a lot of us install mods
I think like we can't really do much of
that kind of stuff
yeah because well we need permissions
even for the mods and even if like I use
the mods
like I I you know it doesn't work in an
online server like that I guess
[Music]
there's a mod which brings about 50 plus
biomies that sounds so cool that sounds
amazing
thing
oh yeah sandals it was really close this
is this is the first time that I've been
so close to zendosu
contenders
with some monuments but the thing is
like I don't really like building that
much in Minecraft
at least not on stream I like I think
privately I wouldn't mind building
but during the stream I just don't enjoy
it that much
[Music]
um
unless it's something smaller
what I also enjoy is that the whole
Phoenix and Arc though I mean that also
we're currently involves a lot of
building but the whole like
um
um raising those villagers and and make
them useful I like that part
adventure map mods Terraria
I remember
uh
a long time ago a certain Senpai I'm not
gonna say who but a certain Senpai
wanted to start like a Terraria arc
including me and some like Japanese
members and maybe one more em member
and was like you want to test out with
me if you if we like the game and and so
on and then I did
um not Coco said but no no I did that
buy and download the game
and we tested it out a little bit but I
don't know after that it just kind of
didn't happen because I guess I'm not
sure what the reason was but
I also honestly didn't like it that much
like
for me I'm sorry but
like for a game that I can really get
into I need I need a like on a long time
at least I don't know usually I prefer
it with better graphics
terraria's Graphics I don't I'm not such
a huge fan of
those tiny pixel graphics
especially in 2D
[Music]
I think even with pixel Graphics you can
make something look amazing for example
that game that
um Sana played Delta Rune or not not
Delta was it the other game
it's on platformer 2D or something like
that
that looked really really pretty
um
Celeste oh yeah Celeste
Celeste I looked uh at her stream when
she was playing that and I thought it
looked really pretty
yeah so generally I'm uh I know that
there's like
games that could look really really good
and I mean Terraria looks good for what
it is but my personal taste
is a bit different
[Music]
yeah she was really good at it I wonder
if Sana would ever play Jump King she
would probably be really good at it too
hey
foreign
world I've seen a little bit of that
but also again like visually not
appealing to me
anyway Skye thank you for the pinky
Kiana I want to ask for a normal request
I love how you talk like a valley girl
and how you sing believe it so can you
try to sing that song repellent girl
style
[Music]
oh oh that's quite the challenge
well I can't play the bgm right now
because this is an archive stream
uh
oh my God
how would I do that
I'm not I'm not that good with valley
girl that I could like improvise a whole
song
okay so there's if you believe it now
we're done already believe it believe it
here I am with my ninja Clan ninja Clan
Here We Stand number two I'm on my way
now which I'll be okay getting ready to
fight on set come on best friends
beautiful
like if you believe it
Naruto Naruto like just believe it
believe it I'm telling you like totally
here I am with my girl's Clan girls Clan
you here we freaking stand uh-huh yes
Naruto I am on my way okay stop
stop bothering me Naruto I'll be okay uh
getting ready right now doing my nails
on set come on besties by my side Sasuke
he's like so cool and Sakura she's a
okay
all right then all right then Skye hope
you're happy
Thanksgiving cats
CEO
oh my God
what does it say Kiana For the Love of
kfb if you're flying towards the sun
you're not going south if you are
looking towards the sun while it's
setting go left to go south if the sun
is rising go right
the problem I was flying in the right
direction what's the problem
I found it easily I don't know what he's
talking about
Israel Hernandez gender Ranger 13
Ezekiel Ramos thank you for the red
super chat
timing you have one lucky Phoenix or was
that the moment when I found it yeah
I was surprised so early Adventure Akita
opening the way for the rest of Hawaiian
now to explore and make the world yeah
then I can probably once again stay done
um I have helped the server just like
with Phoenix then he yay I'm proud
so I'll do my best to make an ice Road
out of it if Enoch starts doing that
please tell her to not do it I want to
do it I want to do it
I'll gladly accept the help to like dig
the tunnel but I'll make the I'll make
the ice
I'll build my ice Road
my my tongue
and producer
[Music]
stop she's back home oh did she take
some terracotta back home though
[Music]
for some reason my stomach
hurts me because of my my posture
[Music]
there's a lot of work
maybe share the work seeing then it
almost took forever but she built it
outside my tunnel
it's not gonna it's not that long it's
not also she the reason why I took her
even longer is like instead of digging a
tunnel
she like
uh always like built a huge layer of
Glass on top of it extra I feel like
that takes much more time than just
digging straight through something
hmm
yeah the tunnel is basically done now
we're almost done this needs to be
filled with ice on the bottom layer and
that's it
although
I might um just use a mixture of blue
eyes and tactiles
depending on how much I have
[Music]
should we post a check yet during stream
Canada I don't think it will help that
much
but I'm sitting somewhat okay like
somewhat properly right now
anyway
uh
thank you also foreign
baked chicken new KFC menu item
what
chicken baked and clay
isn't that toxic why would you eat clay
Jesus I don't think that's a good idea
I think I have to deny that
that sounds crazy
thank you though
Clay Oven
or just like as a decoration you mean uh
ah Clay Oven
it's a way of cooking
clay baked chicken okay you made me
curious I'm Googling Clay Pot ah uh uh
and I understand
wait what the
clay it's a chicken shaped clay
pot
[Music]
never seen this before
makes it very moist the chicken
do you guys want to be prepared in a way
that makes you very moist
but all the nun buckets out there
because for the buckets is already too
late
[Laughter]
what I'm asking a normal question do you
want to be baked in clay or not
[Music]
this looks crazy you crack it up like
you crack it open like that that's
interesting
that looks like a lot of work though
clay roasted chicken
come on
I'm being baked in clay what
well welcome new member
um is that a sign that you want to be
baked and clay
the fact that you join now
well very interesting thank you for that
I feel like Jesus always gives me this
interesting info thank you downstairs
Kiana Canyon oh I should call the Mesa
by Omi over there I should name it Kiara
Canyon Kiana
[Music]
can
canara
[Music]
Canyon he had a canyon wolf K oh that's
cute I like that
piano Canyon
the grand the the grand piano Canyon
oh no the the
um no the grand the grand
Kiana
The Majestic the divine
Kiana can you
the great Phoenix Canyon oh
oh I'll think about the name all of
these sound amazing piano rocks
yes that's right I agree yeah rocks and
names
[Music]
USA this stream's title dangashion in
Congress on finding the mass of Miami
now please find me I'm just a title I
can't even walk I need help I'm lost
but basically we found you now because I
changed the title
I guess this is the title now
[Music]
stream rocks
Evan Duncan
skill page donation Jebediah tweet.com
[Music]
oh
now
[Music]
small navidation
yeah
maybe Ina can bring some abstract ideas
or you can help stay concrete otherwise
it will be a mess off ideas
oh the takodachis
all the Taco dots
Mrs dankerson
your hair is like the prettiest
terracotta except it doesn't smell like
dirt
your eyes are like gleaming amethysts
except they aren't rocks
your voice is like a soothing Songbird
except I want to hear you in the morning
I want to hear anyone okay
Miss twist
that is a weird way of flirting but
I guess it's pretty Charming foreign
the end of it was better than the
beginning
[Music]
of flight to fancy donkey
zero zero remnants bendy with a pinky
oh dear
in regards to your question on how
viewers are seemingly losing interest I
personally never have time to watch your
streams due to work and personal life
but I just really want you to know that
you're on my mind every day so truly
thank you every day
am I living rent free in your head
[Music]
very sweet of you thank you for living
letting me live in your head I
appreciate it
thank you well I hope you at least have
some time to watch my archives sometimes
thank you so much please keep on
enjoying KFC and Kiana
Don kitchen
my blackened heart ever Bears a
phoenix-shaped scar where you have
pierced it Kiara as a Blazing Arrow
pierces tonight never a day passes
without parts of your beauty and how
wonderful it would be to make you smile
[Music]
thank you
Sarah
Johansson thank you
[Music]
thank you for your support I'm glad you
enjoyed the stream Patrick
no I've never tried that
no alcohol
big sweet donation
for the pinky Pinky
Kiana has a lot of students today I
wonder why
[Music]
I should try you really should it's
really exclamation mark
Shawarma is amazing what is that now now
I need to look that up too
uh-huh oh it's like a tortilla
[Music]
oh it's like a like a camera
close
pretty close to it
doing that
do not like a donut
a wrap made with pita bread it looks
yummy
but I've never heard of it before so I
highly doubt that I can get all anywhere
anywhere here
so peace is a lie there is only passion
for passion I gain strength for strength
I gain power for power I gain victory
for victory my chains are broken the
force shall free me the Sith code
I like how Chad recognizes it neither
Reverb for that too late
we should have been like a robot though
who says that
does Darth Vader say that
probably not right
[Music]
who says that
from sandwiches to Star Wars sandwich
was
[Music]
Gandalf said it no way he would never
say such a thing
it's not in the movies oh
the older Star Wars game oh Knights of
the Old Republic
you guys are well informed
Anonymous
276.
are these flash chats
oh it's these chats or something like
that beyond the Stitch book the animals
like the fancy Doncaster skipping those
flush chats
opportunity
oh that's fine cute you named your dog
go Tori that's cute
I like it Jim Tracy Duncan planet
thank you
right so foreign
for the pink
y your laugh always makes me smile
remember the Phoenix Rises From the
Ashes were born Anew I love you
I love you I love you too thank you
Poseidon
very very kind of you thank you for
being so generous
my love makes you smile really I love
some more for you
hmm
foreign
[Music]
I'm glad you like my love
oh no actually it was
cheaper and Doug
Josephine for the pinky biggest advice I
can give to anyone who came up to you
after watching the clip is watch streams
exactly yeah
if you want a support stand once my
streams
yes
you're right black Richard you get it
you get it you get it because you're
always here
you're always here
if the Checker pattern is ice and
nothing instead of ice and another block
you lose no speed
and get to spread your eyes over twice
oh what
I'll do it that way then
oh my
[Music]
is that the smartest idea
to do it
I think so we'll save like half of the
ice and we'll still be the same speed
[Music]
oh stream streams
Twice the Ice
that sounds nice
thank you
maybe fear
in it for today reporting I know you
don't want to use the Japan resources
but if a single person used then his
eyes or that veggie would have been so
happy
using it I will use it then
I want to see her mess up by Omi then
wanna make Nana happy
sure someone will use it though if
that's like the the only and the first
access to a Mesa by Omi on the Japanese
server why did they not why would they
not use it they did already
they should use my mess around
she used it with me
together okay that makes sense
oh most of them can fly now uh on the
Japan server yeah that makes sense
well who knows maybe maybe one day there
will be newbies who don't have a elytra
yeah and they can walk Slash use
um
a boat right he bought it did she use
ice
she used she used eyes right
[Music]
yes okay
or I mean even if they don't use the
road on the ground they can still fly
alongside the road like to see like
where they have to go I think it's very
useful
even if you fly
huh
uh yeah maybe in the future someday I'll
get a European coal High I doubt it
chocolate Insomniac thank you also for
the pinky oh my God so many pinkies
thanks for making my days better KSP is
always here to support you thank you
thank you guys for making my life better
chocolate insomnia
thank you really really really
thanks to her life and thanks to kfp my
life has
changed so much and I I lost so many
worries that were on my shoulders
for years I mean now some newer is on my
shoulders but
I have a lot to compensate for that
um
it just feels nice to have
like an audience that
enjoy seeing what I do
and I actually I
get something back from my hard work
yeah feels nice
to feel appreciated
love you guys
get ready to be stuck with us forever
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
easy I'm the Eternal one between us
remember
Nick s thank you also for Pinky all the
pinkies today hey can I work across the
street at Deadbeat Records we keep
hearing chicken screams and chanting
when we are locking up at night
it's something like hashtag yoga not
quite not quite but close if you would
like uh we can come in and sell some
sound proofing for you you have a
problem with our chanting
they have a ritual to go through every
day foreign
[Music]
must hear it it's good that it reaches
other people it must reach other people
we cannot build a soundproof wall around
my chickens now
share the hashtag vote hashtag yolk
ritual all over the world
go chickens go Cafe
[Music]
thank you
a Poseidon X20 Duncan thank you
yeah yeah I remember that but I don't
know what what in what context that was
uh applicable in that moment
of the sea thank you soon
oh
oh thank you
Mr ector
thank you for the pinky Mr actors sweet
sweet awaits you are doing great piano
and I'm proud of you good enough thank
you I hope you will come again sometime
soon
[Music]
foreign
I'm just assuming that you speak German
because it's a URL donation and you said
good enough so
and you slept at a time that's kind of
like
normal for it German speaking people to
sleep at
[Music]
I'm almost done by the way Super Chat
reading almost done
Kevin
longitude and crypto Max 8536 Foundation
[Music]
excellent safe knew you could do it
thankful thank you for the pinky ah that
was uh when I avoided the channels yeah
thank God oh my God I would have been so
sad
[Music]
I was being attacked by so many and that
was probably also a little bit
distracted by the cutest Taco on Earth
um Jen Lawson no no
[Music]
foreign foreign
but I did apparently lose my helmet in
my boots but I I guess that's just the
creeper damage right
um
please be more careful yes
then found
everything was found no not not quite
anything
[Music]
oh okay
my helmet broke earlier ah okay I guess
so okay
[Music]
foreign
pickaxe my only never right item
my armor
all kinds of things
Diggy call me
[Music]
good
thank you welcome welcome
yeah I guess it's content
it was very sad so thank God it didn't
happen
yes
thank y'all
is that gorilla Ramos thank you for the
pinky Phoenix luck knows no bounds to
shift from sadness to Joy was great glad
you got your things back thank you I was
legit sad
because Chad was already all right also
already giving up you guys need to have
a bit more hope
maybe you guys need to watch Iris
streams
where is the Hope guys
have you lost Hope by joining kfp
I hope that's not the truth the fact I
hope
[Music]
hmm
opens in the fryer now
[Music]
not everyone is as lucky as me
um
I hope my hope isn't gone
seven hours how do I always do this
tomorrow should be shorter though
I think gameplay tomorrow maybe three
hours free maybe
yeah
and Jacob Gonzalez thank you
coordinates hot above your health bar
what
that's cool
and while we overdose thank you soon
I know
I know it's pronounced biome but
I want to stay with my original
pronunciation it's cute
I like it
[Music]
okay
by all means Cannon
by only
bankishing thank you crime on Danke
Schoen
well oh I recently made a DND DT based
off of you she's overwhelmingly powerful
and the pattern DT of my world's
Penfield whatever that means a shame
though she's not as cool as you couldn't
make that happen oh thank you for
including me
[Music]
and refresh time we're almost done
a group of thoughts oh
thank you
I made multiple accounts and joined them
to membership so that I could have a
chance to avoid being fried
that actually
comes out as the opposite you just get
fried more often
the chicken cannot think logically
fighting
Mr
Mr MX
ipltk thank you thank you for watching
my Vlogs and clips thank you for the
support
[Music]
I'm only just now solved and joined and
I'm sorry but I love your new content I
just got overwhelmed because when I got
into Whole Life Council then we did it
right after
ah when I got into Whole Life Council
David right after and I forgot to sub to
the rest of myth
oh wow you're very recent newcomer then
welcome to the fandom
foreign
[Music]
well then have a good time here at kfp I
hope I'll see you more often
I'm only human also worth 55 hours a
week oh damn
yeah no any anytime you have time I
would be glad to have you
55 hour week is tough
yeah thank you for thinking of me bartek
Dakshin boohoo 723 donation
[Music]
sorry for not liking the seafood I like
tuna dude
Doug Joseph and
XXVI Amelia thank you for the pinky I
was about to give you a kiss a lot of
reflex
no case for pinkies
being a light at the end of the pitch
black tunnel of endless University in
midterms on you I have a lot of archives
to catch up on but for missing three
weeks of work at kfv I will gladly take
a nap in the usual room first see you
next stream oh is it over now
you did it oh
[Music]
yeah
thank you for coming back not forgetting
about me thank you
welcome back
I'm proud of you for making it through
that
[Music]
why is there so many Koreans now two
pumpings
thank you thank you Korean Bros thank
you
I keep on getting Korean Clips in my
recommendations they're so good
thank you for the pinky can you do the
Chiara field Live for us I thought it
was hilarious or at least to the Chiara
field yeah also finish Tales of arise
and end game tales of Celia too is still
my favorite though oh we have the same
favorite
yeah good taste
[Music]
um
Kiara film
I don't remember the script did I write
it down somewhere I think I did I think
I did write it down
I don't know which one was it not this
one not this one not this one
not this one or was it this one no
was it this one no
was it the sun now
was this one no
I never read I don't have it written
down
I don't have it
oh I don't have it
[Music]
foreign
off the table and then eat her
yummy I'm a flesh
um
good good food
yeah you're safe
I don't give a do I look like I
give a ask me what happened to the
three cheese pizzas
as we as we chat what I what I did to
all those Foods
what happened to the food I ate those
food
what happened to the takoyaki I ate
those food
what happened to the taco shells I ate
those Foods
what happened to all the free cheese
pizzas I ate those Foods
what happened to Kiana I ate those Foods
what happened to the Hamburger Helper I
don't even know what that means but I
have I ate those Foods
I ate those Vines
what happened to the diamond milk I
drank those wolves
what happened to what about the mask I
hate those sheeps
what happened to all the maple syrup
pancakes
I came into the Canadians
what happened to chunkers I gave
chunkers lava
what happened
so this oh God
what happened today what happened to
Casper
Casper is down here on the bottom right
I poisoned
Casper
what happened to employee
I fried those Foods
what happened to Yango's dream
[Music]
I ate those dreams
what happened to German fairy tale
videos
I ditched that because no one was
watching it
what happened yesterday
I had a day off black she gave me some
privacy for God's sake
[Music]
no I'm not gonna say that the one with
the nuts no
I think I'll stop it
I was watching them I miss them so much
you guys
listen listen listen up okay listen up
right now
listen up listen listen listen
you guys are the bestest
cutest
adorable is this
sweetest
chickens for supporting me like that
okay I love you okay you understand you
understand are you listening
[Music]
oh my God
pick up that music now
you're also the most delicious yes
if I could do if I could do my my tongue
thing around the mouth
I will do it but you gotta deal with the
sound only
slip slurping that that gravy off of you
okay shut up I didn't want it to be like
that I wanted to be wholesome
should it was supposed to be wholesome
God damn it I was just trying to thank
you for being so kind-hearted okay don't
make it don't make it weird
[Music]
uh where was I here
I'll see you guys tomorrow for steps for
I'm not sure what to do yet you're
welcome to send me recommendations on
Twitter
doesn't meet the seven hour streak
yeah
it's too short no just kidding it's
actually
maybe one day I'll bring it back thank
you yesmir
Simpson
it's been a while
kind of felt like playing it so don't
worry about the whole pressure thing
[Music]
like part of me is like wanting to do it
over by
um not cheating at least not that much
money like giving them a normal house
but not like a freaking Mansion
so maybe we should do console
but without cheats having five sims
is difficult
um well let's let's try no I just don't
I don't know I know I can cheat I I I I
I'm not feeling like I I'm like the chat
doesn't want me to cheat or whatever no
no no it's my choice like I just feel
like
um
the whole mansion for the myth grills
which is too much like because it's I
need it all to be on one floor just in
order to have a proper overview of where
everyone is I actually really it made it
a bit a bit more difficult challenging
to have everyone spread over two huge
floors
so one floor house apartment whatever
it was very difficult to keep up with
everyone
so we'll make Council
I don't know about adding Iris because
the more I add in there it's so hard to
keep up with them
we'll see I'll probably only make
Council and and put them in a new house
and we'll see we'll see what happens
we'll see who has the best uh harmony
with who who works well with who we'll
see we'll see who we can marry to one
another
and who chooses what kind of job
actually I feel like I have way more
freedom with counsel than I have with
myth
playing with a dollhouse
[Music]
I wonder if there's already like
pre-created Council Sims in in the in
the library
maybe Iris because she's been around a
little bit longer I'm gonna check
but I'm gonna do my best to recreate
them
do they have any Halloween type events
in Sims see I was thinking a little bit
about that if I could do like a
Halloween themed stream uh like with
Sims
I'm sure they have some kind of content
or like you could even just do like uh
like they have this vampire world I
think you can become a vampire so that's
kind of Halloweenish
there's a vampire thingy
right you can't become a vampire I I
usually don't like those expansion packs
from Sims
but I guess it would it wouldn't Theory
work well for a Halloween stream
[Music]
um
I Was Bitten yeah
Halloween costume contest
is it a little bit too late to start
that also like my my next week is
already pretty much planned out
the big big big event is the new song
cover and the the pumpkin carving
China
foreign
hmm spooky games yeah yeah I mentioned
it today I'll be um
I'll be uh doing some spoopy-ish games I
guess not too spoopy the most spoopy is
that this is outlast
and that's the one I'm looking forward
to the least
for now guys
I hope you enjoyed this during my I
enjoyed spending time with you guys
um thank you for finding new lands of me
yeah
yeah it was nice going on a trip with
you
thank you
I'll see you on Twitter
[Music]
and in German we saying
bye
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]