[Music]
do
hi we're back here again
[Music]
do
this
[Music]
do
crazy
[Music]
yeah and um
you know i think
[Music]
there's one reason why i want to do this
a lot of people say that it's a very
painful match
[Music]
as a member of your zombie would you
like me to make you a sauce card
fermented cabbage and chocolate cake if
you lose a bet no thank you i'm not i'm
not doing any more bets but anyways yeah
um
i don't i don't think it'll be that bad
you know like how bad can a chess match
be among
they're better than i am see so someone
said that
right we were there it was horrible i'm
i'm sure you guys are just over
exaggerating because like um
[Music]
i wish it was an ex exaggeration i mean
like first of all kira senpai uh didn't
know how chess
uh how chess goes right
[Music]
like during the stream garrison i had no
idea how to play chess and amelia senpai
she she she knows the basics but it's
just that she never really learned the
openings and techniques
[Music]
so i kind of want to explain to you guys
from the beginner's point of view
[Music]
i want to give them justification i i
wanna i want you guys to be like oh
right
well they are new at chess so this is
probably what they were going for but
you know right
hmm
kiddo was in the test club
keras and bios in the what
here
exactly i don't was she really in the
chess club i i i
see
yes they are new exactly which is why i
want to convince you guys today that
it's probably not
as painful as everybody says it would be
and anyways uh we're going to
i'm not going to show you guys the
stream
so we'll only be doing a watch along
while we do a watch along i'll give you
guys explanations on maybe what best
moves that they should have played for
and maybe what blenders
and why they did that blenders
[Music]
hmm
everybody ready
we're starting in
did everybody already got there um
you guys have the stream ready it is
we're going to start
and count down five
four
three
two
one start
yes
i mean he can you can never go wrong
with chess
[Music]
wait she really wasn't a test club
uh-huh
wait
wait see she literally wasn't it says
tournament
see
literally
[Music]
there we go
i hope this is better
you know the rules and so do i
you guys should be able to do it so
anyways the one who's white is kiara
senpai and the black one is uh ammunia
senpai so let's
get it
okay let's go
uh
so what keras invited is that she
brought the pawn in front of her
a queen side bishop out
it's it's it's um i think she's going
for the quick check i think she's
planning on doing this like maybe she's
wishing for uh amelia senpai to do the
same thing like maybe she
wants amelia's invite to like push her
pawn also over here and get for a quick
check
this is also something that i first
learned when i started tess
maybe who knows it's not the most ideal
as we know
um
[Music]
e4 is the superior opening as we all
know but but you know again garrison pie
is a
isn't very custom with yes so
this this is one way of doing it you
know
oh wait right uh amelia senpai kind of
pushed oh i know ah
all right amelia's invite pushed her
pawn over here
which um to be honest
i i don't know what this does maybe
maybe she's planning on like pushing all
of her side pawns and getting all of her
rooks out
i i think that's amelia senpai's plan
for now
for now she's going to get her big big
um pieces out you know maybe i don't
know and harrison is also doing the same
thing
it's uh
oh your memories run with says club sent
by uh
i i i
i see
wha what a wonderful
chess club
[Music]
um
see see amelia's in fire is getting her
rooks out it's it's her plan she's
planning on um
going on a massacre with her rook
cursing by what did the chest pop taught
you
here why are you pushing off the pawns
like this sweet
i'm i'm i'm glad you're activating your
pawns but here caressing pi i think it
again uh one thing that i learned from
anna it's good to push your pawns it's
good to activate your pawns they are
very useful but
but uh
you know
pushing
maybe maybe she'd want to like activate
her horse or maybe her bishop
like this is actually a very good trade
uh
right oh but then okay she went here and
then they went here yeah amelia is
anybody's planning on a mascara but i
don't know where maybe
she's going to go here is that what
she's going for i'm not sure
ah
garrison bye
wait so so
why wait okay uh one one thing that anna
always told me um always
move
your pieces to the middle of the board
to the center of the board you don't
you don't
why did you move it here
the horse is looking at a wall senpai
wait
wait wait wait wait
hmm
the tower is called a rock senpai
rock
no not not fortnight sent by it's not
fortnite rock is rock standby
oh the tower okay
with the tower awesome see is she he's
starting to activate her
um
[Music]
oh okay um
and amelia senpai decided to guard her
two pieces which is not the best move
but well i i see what she's going for
wait what what happened wait which which
piece did uh it goes here
and this goes uh
in front of the king
i see
ah so so uh amelia senpai is going to go
here i'm guessing
because this is
kind of like a free pawn
but this isn't something that
i mean you get this
uh
ah
okay okay okay okay okay kirsten by is
finally activating her bishop which i
really really like activating your piece
is important but i don't what i don't
like is that he's activating it to this
size instead of going to the center
because you know again center
is a very
it's important you know the center why
can't i make more red
oh
wait what happened
oh you ate this okay good good job
amelia senpai you did something
what are you talking about
well we'll see
she did something so so so i'm proud
it's our very first
capture
and i'm really glad
um
nintendo games are fun yeah
and
oh oh
it's called the bishop senpai
yes it goes diagonal senpai
uh-huh
are you going to put are you going to
put it there
not bad you're threatening your
the bishop
the bishop's thick then the queen can
also take so and not to mention
you oh
ah
why are they confused
she moved back and she opened the check
for the king
[Music]
no no no no no kirsten by amelia
somebody's checking you
ah so emilia senbai wanted to get
out from this situation so she moved
back
basically she's keeping an eye on the
pond but i don't know why she'd do that
because the only thing she's keeping an
eye on is the night
and the night the night doesn't really
have a bright future
anyway so like
um
like maybe i'd move the the bishop
somewhere elsewhere
ah and see
she moved uh you see it's us she moved
her king no this is no no no no no okay
and then
this is a
blunder wait is scared with scares and
by really in a chess club i i i would
like
i beg to differ
did you just take it standby it's a rock
it's a rupture you'll get eaten by the
bishop but
why did you go here
and that's a free wreck you could have
you could have you guys could have had
an exchange you know it would have been
better
what bugs me is that c
did this
this bugged me a lot
quite a lot because she could have just
blocked it with the with the bishop it
would be a lot more efficient the king
would have to move and then maybe she'd
have a chance to actually castle over
here if she moves her queen in the night
no wait
wait senpai's
don't worry i look at the chat too
sometimes senpai but please please
no now you see it
now you see it wait wait wait you dated
this and then this
not yet senpai
right i forgot to do that
yeah
yeah your smarts empire
puss your pawn please
right there
push your pawn yes and bye
yeah so so
uh-huh
yeah you can stop here by pushing your
pawn
push
push the pawn senpai
it it's that
no the pawn cannot move in any direction
senpai
senpai this is basically a free pawn
and amelia senpai doesn't see it either
[Music]
yeah
but i thought he wanted to tell everyone
that you're actually smart
also i'm noticing some stuff sorry
let's uh
so uh
i don't know what this position is
uh
there's also there's also this
this is like a free knight right here
and uh
oh oh oh you don't know how to play
poker
you know if if if like
she could go for his there obviously
garrison pie and maybe maybe amelia's
invite wouldn't notice you know like a
stair is good
yeah that goes up oh oh she's taking it
she's looking she's looking at it she's
looking at it she's looking at it
everybody
looking at the evil pegasus from america
sin by side
yeah why are you laughing senpai
are you taking a senpai it's it's safe
yeah yeah that was
uh exactly she was uh
yeah finally and and now uh amelia sent
by is finally looking at the pond the
free pawn
like it's nothing big but
uh with this the the enemy horse is
finally in the enemy's territory
stepped into the kyra senpai's
border
no no no no no not yet not yet well i
mean it can go here and then it can take
your queen but you can actually prevent
it you know
and you know you can always activate
your queen you can go here or you can
maybe threaten the horse to go back
except here the queen cannot go here
anywhere else other than the border like
i really wanted to activate activator
queen
or maybe use the horse in the middle
as for amelia senpai amelia simba should
really start activating her other pieces
as well like
but that would be a sacrifice
[Music]
she could start with her queen she can
like uh i don't know bring this thing
out
and she could start going here and then
she could start planning something from
here
oh what happened
oh oh she's checking
ah
good job big brain
big brain
and uh you can she can she can block it
with her pawn
yeah this will be idle amelia's invite
could block the detect with the
with the pawn
good good good good good
but then you can always take it again
and that's wanted to become serious
business
because then you'll have to block with
the queen
now you can't jump over but you can take
the pawn
one kill
yeah you can get one kill
yes you can use the horse you can go
here and then she can get the stare
the
this is the king the king always has a
cross on his head
yeah yeah if you go here then the queen
will have to block
she's starting to believe
yeah but it's not a checkmate yet
yeah you have to
um
i'm getting proud here because she's
actually thinking five not five actually
but she's thinking about the
about future moves that's possible
like you can go with the horse to be
honest the horse is a lot more
ah
i mean it's it's it's it's
it's good too and then you can do this
and then you can get the queen
awesome take the queen
awesome
don't hesitate
the the the king can go diagonal senpai
it can go to any boxes
but only one step at a time
so basically the king can still take it
yeah it's a good trade i'd say on your
side
buy clean
and then have no choice but to take it
oh very much worth it i'm proud of you
senpai
oh she knows
she knows
and then you can just take your queen
over here
and it'll be a quick check
senpai what are you planning with that
bishop plea please
yeah
yes you do so it would be good if you
bring your queen out and go for a go for
a quick check you know
senpai
yeah yeah yeah with that queen no no no
no not there here here's the boy here
i mean he you can threaten the horse
here but you can you can get it you can
get a check yes a quick check let's go
no no no no she can't do that she can't
do that she she can't
the only way is to do this
this is the best no no no no
no this is the you're gonna push this
one and then it'll be protected no
somebody not this one i mean this one is
also protected but like with this you
can actually turn the queen you know
oh senpai
this this is good but this is better you
know
ah
okay good
she's threatening to open it up
it is what i feel
okay
oh oh what happened
wait what did you move oh she moved this
so i'm guessing that she's looking at
the horse
but it's not very
beneficial
i'd say
they can do this and it'll be a check
and uh the king had
yeah
this can go here
but then amina's invite would do this
and then oh and then you can come and
then the king can't get it because
there's a
horse guarding
it good job kirsten pie
good job
wait are you really running away
well i guess running away would be a
good option because if if you take then
garrison bay will take
wait no not not now with the knight but
with the queen
meow senpai decided to move her king
oh it is
actually it makes sense because taking
taking wouldn't be very beneficial right
oh and she's checking again
awesome
so now you're limiting the king from
going here
and here and here but king can still go
here here here here
hmm
good job
and so i'm here since i moved to the
side
no she could she could just do this this
is basically a free pawn and she could
limit the king from going anywhere
like the king will be trapped in a
little box
oh but then
but then the knight will be guarding
itself
a free horse oh you're right it is a
free horse
yeah diagonally it can move forward but
it can only kill diagonally
no no you have to kill if you want to
move diagonally so you can go here it'll
be a check
um
you want to go for this
i mean
sex are never
it's never a bad thing checking that is
and you can just go here and it'll be
another check or you can go here and
it'll be another check but then this
will happen
[Music]
yeah you know what i think it is better
for kiara senpai to get rid of uh amelia
sinbad's force if she wants to win as
for amelia senpai she doesn't have that
many
pieces
she's kind of at this advantage here her
position also so one thing that i do if
i was there i'd start activating either
the bishop or the rook
[Music]
maybe you want to activate your horse
you can bait uh amnesia and vice versa
and then you can just take it with your
king
we're close to the end game anyways
sacrifices are necessary
well i mean
[Music]
so
ah you're that check no no no no not
there no no kerosene but this is no not
here
anywhere but here you can go here you
can go here okay but not here no why did
you do that yeah
no
oh you forgot that
[Music]
garrison fight things can eat too
oh my
[Music]
here
oh my god
i'm
why do you throw your queen like that
it hurts me so much
that was a thick blender
[Laughter]
and focus please
focus
yeah let's be smart
okay you're you're push what are you
something that you can do maybe you can
start by
you know i don't know
maybe you can move it here
try getting your workout
or maybe you can just move it here and
it'll be like a little check
you can go here
or she can go here but this isn't really
recommended because there's a rook
she can go here a check oh but then
there's this oh but then oh there's also
that so it'll be like an exchange
and you'll be you you'll be at an
advantage
right
right here sitting by come on come on
you got this you are in the chess club
you're in the chess club
make those people who didn't choose you
to the tournament three great
come on
send by
it's it's just like this
it's okay
it should be
oh but she did send five
yeah good you should have you should
have done this earlier though
you should have done this earlier
uh
oh my god
okay so um
so far it's only the queen blender and
also this truck right here is what
frustrates me the most so far okay cool
a free pawn you can take it it's okay
but wait no no no no no no it's not free
anyways
i forgot yeah it's not enough i'm very
sorry
then is he got this
but hey yeah if you have you have two
pegasuses on your side senpai
right
uh
it's not free i'm very sorry i apologize
it's not free
i forgot to look at the board
well i am also a beginner so hey
the horse will only look at a wall you
don't want the horse to look at a wall
okay
okay come on come on the horse wants to
fly free the horse wants to be freezing
by it wants to
fly it wasn't flying but
it doesn't want to be in a castle they
don't like being caged
i'll work on it oh oh oh
how dare you
it just is not boring
senpai i'll make her a chest a reality
and it will be awesome
it will be awesome i promise you
because now the only thing she could do
is that she could
you know
she gotta get rid of this somehow
is this horse
this horse can't go anywhere but either
back here
like again
she should have gone here
because
now she can't go here nor here because
there's twisting
wait the king went here and then she
went
she did what okay the king's here
hmm
oh is he is he trying to bait
is she trying to beat if she does this
and maybe
yes
like
all right
all right this is in this isn't this
part i'm sorry
i'm sorry
i'm sorry i wasn't
but but that was that was a very nice
plan harrison by was
planning on going here
maybe to bait the horse and then she can
take it
exactly you cannot set it free which is
why you see see
which is why i freaked out why did you
do this
it does absolutely nothing we're just
castling the tower
wait what'd she do she did this
okay she's starting to set
she's starting to set this free
okay
maybe ah
is she aiming for this and then this
i mean emilia senpai has a has a
promising move here
only if here senpai doesn't see it
though
oh oh i mean you could but like uh
remember yelly's gotta aim
it's just like fps i know you don't play
fps garrison pi but
you gotta gotta aim
like if we go here then what then
we're here like nothing happens here
knight on d4 the knight on d4
this
i mean it'll be an exchange right
it's an open check an open check
open check it
where
i mean if you move here
it'll be cool if you move here it'll be
another exchange because then you'll eat
but you can take again with your horse
but then you can think again with your
horse this is okay
definitely okay you're a weakening here
sacrifices are necessary senpai
c3 can't move c3 can't move uh
yeah this can't move but but the horse
can right so like
this is okay
a given date
you know
aussie actually went here
wait no no no no no no no she's just
pinning
all right there's also this i didn't
realize right right right right this is
being
oh she can just pull down right she can
just pull down
it'll be a check and the king will have
to run yeah exactly exactly
but you can't eat it kiera senpai you
don't get it you can't you can't eat the
rook
we can't you can't eat the rook senpai
yeah you gotta you gotta run
smart indeed
see well
you gotta go maybe maybe to the to the
ah no senpai because you can do this
or that
but oh no but if you if you do this then
then she can she can take this so you
can do this if you go here
you you should have played this amelia
senpai no no no
and then what is this
and there's also this it's free oh but
amelia senpai is running away i feel
now she's planning on doing a massacre a
bloodbath
yeah she should have taken the tower set
by
you
well well
yes
i mean i i'd go here i i'd want i'd want
to get closer you know
so now she's spending the night the
night can't go anywhere
no no
you gotta
yeah yeah they gotta
what sacrifice your what
you're sacrificing
yeah the thing is this is pinned you
can't move it anymore
no but if you pull here then you just go
here
no
no no no right now i want you to focus
on maybe maybe eliminating these pawns
and maybe promoting your own pawns that
that that's that's an idea you know
wait does she know about promotion
the the senior promotions
or like you know
she can
she should know about promotions right
there's she wasn't she was in the chess
club or you know she could maybe move
her kings over here
i mean her king over here and then she'd
be
she'd be doing it she'd be uh
what does this do exactly i'm very sorry
stand by what does this do
what does this do
and so the the amelias and my skin is
starting to run up
oh
no no no this is pinned you can't do
anything what i do is that i definitely
do this i do this i protect my knight
while also threatening their work
or maybe i could go for a quick check
maybe the horse will then cover or maybe
the king will start running away
so it's either this or this from me
yeah you can't go
forward anymore the thing is this is
pinned
no no no no curiosity
there's there's
oh
why though
no no no but but you can you can always
check but but he can check he stand by
over here
all the way right here
we're here
i mean this is this is also an option
um
to be honest this is this is actually
good for you
or like if they do this and they do this
then maybe you can just start moving
your own king somewhere else so that
your horse won't be pinned we want to
free your horse the horse the horse
wants to fly by a dozen try getting them
why is it here
are you planning on doing this
and then moving your pawns forward
is that
she went here ah
let's check
or this
that's also good
okay okay
okay
oh
she she's going there senpai
yeah now now your horse is finally free
it can finally move
yes yes ma'am
you shall
you shall what shall you do
all right
and that's the check
you'd want to go up
you'd wanna oh wait wait it's a fork
it's a it's a it's a fork
it's a fork oh my god amelia sent my big
brain move
[Laughter]
oh my god
my god
that was
which is why you gotta stop the pawns
from promotion
from promoting
yeah this
that that's that's the best move i mean
she can run away
like if you go here then the horse will
either go here
or here
here
so so it won't be a check
doors can only run away again here here
here here here
here here
how long has it been it's been uh it's
been
a it's been 40 minutes i think
40 minutes
you can't you can get a stalemate and
it'll be a draw or if it's like a
repetitive
thing then that's also a draw
a draw by repetitive
oh wait i'm sorry i forgot to move this
i forgot to move to sorry
hi
she's looking at another check for a
share amelia senpai
he's looking at another check
but again what i really want them to do
is that
when you only have this many pieces what
you'd want to do is that you'd want to
promote your pawns as endgame
yeah you're going here
oh are you are you ah
so so she's also planning on a chick
yeah
see another check by amelia senpai
looking at the king respectfully
uh-huh and you gotta move
going up is always an option
because if you go up we can maybe
get the pond
all right because they're not using
assist
they're they're like playing
like normally like you know in chess.com
where like
do we have like assists like these
[Music]
very helpful
and so she decided to move back she is
in the protection the king is protecting
his minions
quite nicely
harrison by is planning on doing a check
over here but then again the the king
can also
escape but that makes the
the little castle over here a little
protection over here by the king
and off
defense but defenseless exactly
my goodness my pcc from this match is
getting triggered i'm very sorry
okay so uh
i really
want them to start working on their you
know this is this is good if only if
only amelia's in by
like an edge
an edge pawn right here
a check is good it's like it's good
because then
because then the the king will have to
run either here
here
or here
the king will have to run and and if the
king runs you can actually run too
how do you check with yourself
wait how
what
tech meeting i i don't think that's
possible
no
no no no that's not that's
no no no
that's not possible
it's not possible at all
like a king's always has this one gap
i guess like what is it called kalyan
limit
the cat making the cat
yes good start developing your pawns
good job senpai
no no no you really can't do you can't
do that
yeah
every every single game it won't let you
checkmate yourself
like if you're getting pinned you can't
move your pieces
so you gotta
you know right now kira's invite is in a
good position because she is actually
limiting the king from moving too much
like bullets bullet games are actually
really fast because you don't really
think about your pieces too much blood
games is more like haha speedy you know
yeah make it end please
why did i decide to do this why did i
decided to do this
so you decided to move here
because right now emilia sitting by is a
tiny box
a very tiny box i'd say
a checkmate is near i believe oh she's
starting to move her pawn good good keep
going keep going amelia senpai
make him a queen
wait what did what did what happened
ah
oh
garrison but you gotta run kirsten but
you gotta no you gotta you gotta start
running harrison bye it's a race between
you and amelia senpai erase again let me
say this
you guys gotta mario kart each other
get the blue shell don't don't move the
other stuffs you gotta you gotta move
first karen's in my no this no not the
cake why
why though
why is that
come on
millie isn't by
now amelia's invite just needs to move
she has two pawns and they're moving
forward it's not looking good for kara
senpai at all this is this is not good
at all no oh oh oh oh kirsten bye you
got it
no garrison but you're so close you're
so close look she's she's really
developing
kara's and bye
you're going to be toast
and it wouldn't be fun
you can't promote your kickstarter you
gotta
yeah promotion wait
what they don't know
[Music]
let's go
okay
yeah
yes
yes you can you can't turn it into
anything you can turn it into
yeah queen definitely
no it exists for a long time
this has been here for a while i'm
curious why you said no you isn't enough
[Music]
yeah now now you're pinned you're you're
night
[Laughter]
or or you should start developing your
pawn
no no no no no no no
still
i mean i mean i mean amelia senpai
wouldn't sacrifice her rook right off
the bat see one guess whoop because then
curious and play with just whoop
is it
why is she talking about horse breakers
uh oh
uh oh amelia's invites pushing amelia's
invites pushing me a senpai's
oh
no this is this is not a thank you
garrison pie
she is also aiming for
you get to have
you can get as many promotions two
promotions he can get like three queens
on the board if i remember correctly
right
you can get as many as promotions as
long as you have the pawns every pawn
can promote just get the queen why do
you no yeah you can you can choose one
you can you can choose one
and queen yeah you'd you'd want your
queen back wouldn't you you want you'd
want your yes the waifu
exactly why did you choose
did you miss collect did you did you
miss the
rook
is that it
is is that it she's she's going to she's
going to choose queen right there's no
way
there's no way she's not choosing queen
okay good
good
and then
swoop right
why would you go
after you got your queen
oh my god
oh
standby
senpai
like
again
attack
capture trenton
but if the tech isn't worth it you don't
go for it
she could have come here
and oh what the heck what the heck
that is an alarm
uh
oh gosh and amelia's and well have to
push her pawn for sure
she
to be honest i don't know
finally a queen thank you amelia said
oh man man
she's super close
she could maybe start going here
then
uh
kirsten pi will have to do a move
the garrison if i could go here
yeah um to be honest
you were doing really great i was i was
garrison but you were doing awesome but
i don't
i hope it doesn't end in salemate does
it end in stalemate i don't know
i don't know
yep and then she's checking out
oh she's
amelia's invites playing
amelia's invites playing with her food
mom
mom amelia's invites playing with her
food
no
why didn't she
why didn't she just why didn't she just
oh
amelia's invite that was so mean
that was so mean
okay this is kind of difficult right now
cause uh
this is very difficult
now now the knight is being pinned the
knight cannot go anywhere
and and this this knight cannot move
it's it's pinned you can you can only
you can only move your kit and carry
senpai
it's pinned
there's no no you can't
i believe
okay okay um
that that is that this is a very good
move because she's guarding
she's guarding
her horsey
uh um
[Music]
one thing i do is i can do uh is i do
this if i was emilia senpai
or or this this is also good
[Music]
now the king will have to go here or
here or go back
i think it'll better if the king goes
here because then the king will have
more room to escape there's a night
guarding it right
but but then she can do this oh but no
no no but if she does this then there's
this
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
she can't do this because there's this
so this is bad
top right right
she's not
give you up
senpai
the king can still go here
[Music]
yeah you only have here
here here like here here here
or or here but then again
oh this is this is
oh no no no no wait wait wait
no no no no no no no no no senpai no no
no no no no no no you don't oh oh here
here is good oh oh it's a mate it's a
mate it's a mate it's a mate it's
amazing it's a mate it's a mate it's
amazing it's amazing it's amazing mate
it's my destination this is mate it's
amazing come on in the mirror no no no
no no no it wasn't me it wasn't me
emily is invited we're so close no she's
going to start running no no you didn't
attack me
[Music]
right here right here see seated horsey
no no no you forgot about your horses
and by amelia senpai open your eyes
open your eyes
this horse is spinned
but then that means you'll have to run
away
no no no no no no no you can't move your
horse anywhere it's pinned it's pinned
remember senpai
sorry
so so you'll have to go here
or
here is one thing one thing for sure
this this this is a good move you'll
have to go here here's senpai
harrison
because if you go here you're not
mated yet
yet well i mean then she can still pull
nah i'm sorry senpai but uh
wait why did you go there
it's still inmate it's still mate it's
still a mate the syllabate is still a
mate it's still mate it's still a mate
it's still a mate is still a mate
wait what happened what happened oh
no no no come on stop playing with the
damn food
stop playing with the damn food
come on
here
no no no no no no no no no he this this
is the queen use the queen use the queen
please please use the queen of
everything i ask of you
oh
this is this is going to be a chase
isn't it anymore
[Laughter]
you went here no you can just you can
just get your queen here
you can get get your queen here
and it'll be over oh wait
shoot god dang it
god dang it
it was so close
well well
look
for the record um it it is hard to find
a mate when when you're still starting
off at chess i was there too
i was i i was there too i couldn't find
a mate too so i wouldn't blame amelia
senpai but
it was there
but it was it was there
yeah
no no no you can't go here because
there's there's a little horse
so you can't go here
you can't go here you can't go here
you're in a tiny box right here senpai
you're you're in a tiny box a very very
tiny boxing fight and there's nothing
that you can do about it
a very tiny box
a very very tiny box
like where else can he go because he
can't
oh yeah
you're just going to go in circles
aren't you
you're just
okay um
you can make the box smaller make the
box smaller no no no no senpai first of
all no no no no no
because if you do this then the king can
still run
stop it stop no no
just stop stop stop chasing
stop
senpai
this is this is just mean
this is this is
this is
this is a chase
senpai
come on
i mean listen right n now you're just
being mean
they're just being mean
see she she's in another box now she's
in another box you can't go here
can't go here
can't go here either
come on
you eat
carrots and buy no you get
it doesn't
amelia isn't
oh no
she's enjoying this she's she's
salvating this
and she's getting
what
did you get
why didn't you rock
my rocks
wait no curious in my way did you go
down
no no no what what pull
no you just no then it would be another
chase
it'd be
it you'd only have to go here
wait so so the king the king can only go
here
oh shoot
you know she might she might just get
the she might just get the the
the dang horse
she might just you know
she might
that was a lot of
what
but
i'm i'm sorry
yeah checkmate but no no no no no no
wait wait stand by don't don't
oh they're starting to roast each other
oh no
senpai amelia senpai this is this is
this is pretty bad for you
this is this is this is really bad for
you emilia senpai
see she can either take the horse or uh
i see
all right she can't all right
and i just saved
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
dude you're you're starting to make a
box
you can't you can't hear us in pi you
can't go there yeah you can't
you can't
she she certainly is
no no no no if you go here then harrison
van gaal can just escape to the to there
to the right
oh wait is she actually wait where is
she see is he
is he
okay so first of all you can go here
first of all you can plan it you can uh
you can uh
no no no no no
for now i'd want to i'd want to make the
yeah
exactly
so right now right now she's just
she's just
i'm um for uh
there is a stalemate
which is a draw
yeah yeah
uh uh-huh
yes
oh she can she can she can make she can
make the box a little bit smaller ah
she can
she could have she could have she could
have made it like a chopstick scenario
you know
is she gonna
no no no no no no she needs to use her
king yeah
okay now now now you gotta force the
king to go up good
you're you're close you're close to me
listen but you got this
you got this you're actually very close
you're very close you can you can you
can bring
you can bring your queen up come on
no no no
not like this and bye
bye now like this come on
listen right now like
you can
make the box smaller
no no move your king your king is
actually very useful and you don't know
you can go here or you could go here
actually yeah
no no not here
no no no no you gotta move your thing
closer okay this is good this is good no
no no no do this
do this do this
i mean
oh oh that's actually really good that's
actually really good yeah
check me
wait not yet
wait it's not it's not yet not yet
all right you can still go here i forgot
right i forgot i forgot i forgot so
close so close so close come on
it can only go here
not it's not a checkmate yet
okay okay you're forcing her you're
forcing a
okay
um
send by this
that's okay go here go here right yeah
no
here right
here
can go here first
right or or you can maybe start using
your
which is good you can't
yeah make make it smaller make her run
make her run
make it make her run
and then you can do this and then you
can start driving her to the corner
yeah
yeah no no no no no no no no no no no
not here not here not here not here not
here not yet not yet not yet not yet
here
i mean this is also good this is also
good okay it's looking good you'll have
to go back i have to go back senpai
soon the game is ending soon there's no
way that it's not ending there's no it's
not there's no way it's not ending okay
good
make the box smaller
let's go
let's go okay now now kerosene i can
only go there
and that will be the end
ah
oh
let me drink
that's it right there
huh
[Music]
it
it really ended uh
[Music]
the first part the first half
it wasn't that bad
the first half wasn't that bad
[Music]
like to start it was it was like
little you know
little beginner's mistake you know after
at the at the start
none of them did an e4
none of them did an e4 which uh which
would explain uh
well uh
they're starting chess you know
[Music]
like it was it was okay
like it's comprehensible
because they can actually make up for
their last moves but amelia
at the end game had so many missed ones
and uh
let me let me uh say this on her behalf
uh as someone
who
plays chess
it's very hard to look for a checkmate
checkmate
for beginners okay
uh
right now i'm already experienced so
looking for checkmates might be a little
bit easier
just a little bit
but
um
for this
uh
well i can see like like i bet amelia
senpai is kind of frustrated too because
the chat is coming constantly saying oh
my god me doing one made in one
checkmate made her checkmate here
but the thing is uh
it's because he doesn't know
how uh
the best way to check me
because you know someone who's not
accustomed
[Music]
which i understand her frustration
because i was like that thing i was like
sometimes sometimes when i play tests
everyone would be like oh my god ali
made in one but then i'd be like where
i wouldn't be able to see it because you
know analyzing
watching a test tournament while playing
chess alone that's like two different
things
playing chess like like if we watch a
stream about chess like we'd be like oh
my gosh you should go here like we'd
have this backseating power
behind us but since we're playing chess
[Music]
because usually when we play chess we'd
focus on one area
at least for beginners yeah i still do
the same thing i only focus on one area
and sometimes i blunder
and miss
miss something mm-hmm
salsa
yeah yeah yeah but but amelia's invited
very well she finally found the
checkmate
like it took a while it did take a while
but she finally found it
backseating vision plus one race
yeah exactly
caspy comes back a seat if your friend's
there
ellie
so so
never sharing the picture yeah that that
is that is one rule in chess
you should always look at the big board
don't always look at the little part of
it
so yeah that is all for today i'd say
both amelia senpai and harrison by day
they give their all
again
[Music]
had her ups but then
uh amelia sent by flipped the table and
actually won
[Music]
and and you know
i'd see that harrison fight is actually
a test player uh with her uh you know
when she blunders he immediately knows
you know i am
going to be listening
[Music]
to you
that's actually a very good thing
because
uh sometimes people would be like
sometimes people would blunder and they
wouldn't uh realize that's gonna
dangerous
hmm
she used to be in the chess club i know
there's some mistakes and there were
some good moments but all
it was all good game it was all a good
game it was entertaining to say the
least
so yes
yes realize your mistake is better right
it's better to realize your mistake
rather than not realizing it
and
uh amelia isn't bi again amelia's invite
she was doing a great job
like at first i thought that he was just
playing around with garrison
it turns out it's just uh because uh she
can't see the check
not not the check she couldn't see the
mate
and that's a common beginner's fault you
know
[Music]
entertaining oil nothing
are you gonna say people exaggerated the
pain
[Music]
okay you guys got a point about the the
end game okay the end game
it was a very long taste i would was it
wait was it like 18 minutes of a taste
it's just garrison pie skin
[Music]
is
thank you everyone
oh gosh
yeah
let's move our overlay shall we eat
[Music]
oh it was a good game okay
there was some good uh good moves and
some moves that are quite questionable
but uh foremost it was a very very good
game
yeah
thank you
yeah oh you look at it
[Music]
hi
thank you so much for coming everyone
okay
yeah so super chat super chat first of
all i'd like to say a very big thank you
to gosita
i still remember this chess match and i
can't wait to hear your thoughts on it
it was a good chess match
like uh considering that
uh it's been a while since garrison i
play chess and considering that uh
amelia senpai
only knew a few of the rules
it was it was a great test match
it's like it's like a
comedy
[Music]
as a rookie i'd say it was a great test
match and uh
i believe
if they do practice just a little bit
more
i bet they wrecked the heck out of me
because they have a lot of potential i
feel like
just with a little practice just with a
little reminder it's best if you do this
it's best if you do that because amina
senpai had the basic
idea of how tess goes it's just that
she just doesn't know how to me
check me at least
yeah by the way they did a rematch
uh me maybe we'll save that for another
day yeah
thank you and then next is from hire
some so so so thank you very much
and next is from uh jet lunar this chess
match brought you uh brought up some
good memories and analyzing it makes it
even more enjoyable thank you
they just knew the basics and they did
well exactly that uh well what i'm
trying to say
[Music]
amazing amazing
thank you and then next is from yakibuta
hi
arigato
and then from dude guy you've learned to
not bet good have this as a strange
uncle rewarding for learning why thank
you yeah i'm not i'm never doing any
more bets
i keep losing them and i keep regretting
so anyways thank you and then next is
from tk it won't be that painful a few
minutes later being intensifies
[Music]
oh it was just a little bit okay just a
little bit
um
thank you next is from uh patrick willow
oh hi i hope you have lots of fun with
today's review
i won't say anything about the match but
i'm just going to leave the money to
help you pay for the ptsd
treatment love you uh thank you patrick
and then from society boots this is a
blunder it would be a good title
it's not
[Music]
no no no i'm i'm actually glad
but you know seeing their level like
this
i really do feel like it's very possible
very very possible for a hollow test
like looking at their level like just a
little tips and tricks
and i bet they'd be flying with colors
is very very close
call a chess club they've gotten better
since that game they did
awesome
and it really is
possible
if they try hard i'll be scared
they'll be geniuses because i do
uh
out of all of my interactions with
garrison by nominating by they're very
responsible and hardworking
which is why i think if they practice
just just a little bit more just a
little bit more
did get it thank you
and then next is from uh the sinister
eyes kiara and chess club i don't know
about
jerry is in test club i don't know about
chess haha funny thank you
from black gamas i'm crazy ali and this
is my master class i'm i'm not a master
thank you i'm i'm still a rookie
basically
i'm still like a level 400 ello
thank you
ali next time you teach someone make
sure to show them how to make
yes thank you next is from
ghostikan remember when all you said it
can't be that bad
i mean it wasn't that bad it was it
wasn't that bad thank you next is from
new demon pain pickle thank you from
kent s i'm betting on ame amelia senpai
is definitely hmm
thank you
and the next is from uh female gossip
but thank you
yeah i'm i'm missing my paracetamol but
loves them thank you
and then next is from uh papering this
is a 2 300 ello play ollie you wouldn't
understand no i wouldn't i'm i'm just a
400 lo
chess player thank you and then next is
from super iron bob when there's a will
there's a way i know
i now must checkmate myself how do you
checkmate yourself
anyway thank you
and then next is from rastomer a ptsd
friend why thank you and the next is
from nick the struggle is real
thank you so much for the super chat and
then from annis uh ganbare always rain
don't give up don't give up yeah
which is what amelia senpai did she
didn't give up at all thank you
and then from out around the world
probably a good thing you're already a
zombie huh yeah thank you and then next
is from pinkbacon9 it's hard to watch
all you please teach this kids
should i
maybe maybe i should
what if what if like i did what if i
give a
lesson to kiara senpai and another
lesson for armenia senpai and have them
battle it out again like the third round
the third round of cara versus ami i
think it would be pretty intense
yeah
thank you
and then next is from
[Music]
hope like your pain feeling analysis
keep it up ollie thank you and then if
they're up for it if you're afraid yeah
if they want like a little
uh training session then i don't mind
only if they want to only if they hit me
up thank you and then next is from
uh sausage boots we simply cannot for
some the hundred thousand computations
going through the each of their minds
right now
it's probably
yeah
thank you and then from anthonyville
someone call an ambulance please i got a
heart attack while watching the stream
thank you
are
see a potential because well i mean
if you're ever
doing your best if you're ever trying
your best on something
then you can only go up from there is
what i believe
like maybe it's like a little progress
like
if we work hard we'll eventually get
there even though it's just like little
teeny tiny progress but progress is
still progress there's no way that we
can go down
it only goes up from here
so i do feel like there's a lot of
potential towards my senpai's
and then next is from
a lawrence freest
for the inevitably necessary therapy
thank you and then from stevie i didn't
realize i was supposed to have the other
video open i've been listening to all
your screaming pain for the last hour
there's a reason why i put a stopwatch
there but yeah thank you next is from
natsu89
ami is a time traveler that knew you
would suffer watching this so she made
this extra painful 4d chest
i i see thank you
and then next is from absolute link
uh profane funds for ali
thank you and then from sir robert baker
aka the muffin oh my god watching them
play
chess it's kind of painful ollie had
passed it wasn't it wasn't that painful
it was a little bit frustrating but
that's it not not really frustrating
frustrating isn't really the word i'm
looking for the the word that i'm
looking for is
but i don't know what it is in
english
yeah guys
so goombas is basically like you want to
just pinch their cheeks because you're
just
ah you know
[Music]
yeah i guess you could say that um
tickle it i like like i felt like
[Music]
i just can't hold it you know
i got it
so it's not really frustrated it's more
as a must i i don't know how to
okay
and then next is from uh
getherdin ali i think you need babathi
at this point boba tea
i got it right here
[Music]
ah ma mama boob
tastes kind of salty
[Music]
yes thank you
and then uh
next is from
from shinoda masaru alexa play good
steam what's a good steam but anyway
thank you and the next is from chris jbt
a 48 year old version would find them
made quicker than these two
uh just so you know again
i i want i want you guys to put in
consideration that uh mice and pisces
are still kind of
kind of new to chess
like
they do know the rules but but like not
the basic techniques so it only makes
sense they're they're not used to it yet
for example a vr player
let's say that someone new wants to play
vr vr isn't for everyone like someone
would get a hang of it quite quick but
some people will get really dizzy
because they're not used to it yet
if they play vr a little bit more then
maybe they'd get used to vr
right and well same goes yes they they
just weren't um
accustomed to the board hmm
yeah yeah yeah they're new
and it says so keep that in mind
it's not it's not that they're
it's not that they can't it's just that
they just didn't know how hmm
so yeren ami are great in other stuff
just not chess and that's okay exactly
everyone has their own
a weakness and strengths
for total newbies the game wasn't weird
exactly which is why uh
it's not like i said it was a little bit
exaggerated and then everyone says oh my
god it's so painful
[Music]
yeah
thank you
and then next is from
eggno dude we tried to warn you ollie
thank you from looking for the top this
is the consequences of your own actions
ollie i mean i learned a lot actually
from from this
from
[Music]
from their matim itself
i learned a lot because they were doing
they were doing open checks
like some of them were actually really
good moves you guys you guys got to
admit
thank you
and then uh next is from anthony phil
error404
brain's not found
thank you and then from flaming pants
are you having fun watching this chest
my charlie i was actually
i was having fun
like hearing my senpai's actually
uh trying their best
to
uh
to play
it was fun
like not
not at them suffering but just the fact
that they're trying their absolute best
you know
thank you
and then next is from orange cha bring
the rook to the end thank you and then
next is from extra ho nina's husband
number eight eight so ali what did we
learn today we learned that
um
you know garrison why had the advantage
at first
and uh amelia's invite was quite at
disadvantage
so what we can learn is that you should
never ever give up
you can always push through somehow if
you keep trying that is it's not always
wasteful
that's what we learned today
thank you and then next is from uh
i did x so have you seen izuru and
roberto's chess match
oh did they play chess too
[Music]
did they really
should i react to it
[Music]
i'll try asking them
uh
[Music]
i'm sure that a lot of hall members
elias played chess once
yes please they did not know how to play
chess and did not learn
well i mean
this um
considering my senpais i bet they know
how to they know how to play shogi so i
bet they uh somehow
did it i don't know though there's also
rainy versus fauna
oh i can ask them too hmm
often in that 50 games thing for the
switch yeah exactly
so
yeah review your own memes
no i don't want to cringe at myself i'm
going to cringe at myself at fourth of
december
yeah thank you
and then next is from uh luka umbrialdi
understand now only do you feel our
pains your anguish
i can see that you guys were also
goodness but i wouldn't say that you
guys were in pain but anyways thank you
and then next is from
kfb
gita
[Music]
thank you
and next is from zak skrug so this is
what it looks like when the dead when
the dead dies
i didn't die thank you and the next is
from jellomancy now that you've reviewed
the infamous amicura match how about the
roberto israeli chess match next
i said i should ask them first
i i wonder if i can actually do it
and i i i'll be a little bit nervous
because
[Music]
and then next is from akashiba thanks
for the same it was as exciting as
watching a movie thank you and you're
welcome and then from outer sky skyrise
thank you for the match analysis ali
you're very welcome
and then let me refresh
a little bit
next is from crazy shokai only if you
love chess watching
uh if you love chess watching then world
championships between two best players
now
ah we'll do that later because again
these things needs permission
thank you and the next is from borutano
ali please marry me
uh
i'll consider it
thank you next is from jensweiser thank
you for the same totemo
[Music]
and thenx is from
uh
[Music]
if you don't mind i hope you play go
game i think it's more difficult and
demand more time than chess or shogi but
it is simple if you want more house
point you win
you know actually
moon moon aroma the great moon aroma
he also asked me to play go
but the thing is i suck at go so much
and i don't have a goat teacher to teach
me you know
to teach me right but but for gil i'm
kind of scared
it was hello heart it certainly is
i need i need i need a professional
a go
player
if anyone knows a new london please tell
them to dm me because i would love to
have a teacher to teach me how to play
go
and uh
i'd like to get revenge on a certain red
haired senpai tail thank you
and then
no i i don't want to ask my senpai i
want i want to get revenge on that
senpai
hmm thank you next is from pinkbikini
it's like something you would hang on
the fridge because it's adorable how
hard they tried exactly
like either efforts an a for trying
thank you
and then next is from ultraman trigger
this is late for something nope you're
not late at all thank you so much and
then from looking for the top kfb here a
third match after a training arc would
be neat fun fact carol once made a
stream wanting her fans to teach her how
to play chess but it turns out we are
rookies too long it's endearing she
tried to get better for real though
then uh
man
if i i wonder if gara senpai is still
interested in in playing chess if she is
i would you know
only if she's still interested though
like like
only oh only if she's still
in interested iota
can always ask i don't know
i think it's a bit rude if i come to
kearsen by first so kanya
pangasi
because i just watched her stream and i
can't just be like yo do you need a
tutor
i mean only if he's into it
but but
well someone needs to initiate but i
mean i mean if he's not thinking about
it if he's not interested
then then uh then
you know
[Music]
but anyways that is all of the donations
for today thank you so much everyone
uh next is uh i have a little
announcement to make
[Music]
but i'm sure that
the management will do their best so
that we can put more merch on sale soon
but for now
yeah you guys can shop for acrylics for
for tapestries for t-shirts
[Music]
and
and then after this uh
after this if i remember correctly uh
anik is going to have an announcement
right
[Music]
like he just came back from his
chiatus
so we should definitely be there to
support him and listen to him
hmm
welcome to the zomlie it's been awhile
[Music]
oh and and don't speculate he he really
he really doesn't like it when people
speculate
[Music]
should be pretty obvious what it is
anyways it should be obvious because
it's obvious let's not point it out okay
let's not point
[Music]
speculation man exactly let's support
him all the way thank
[Music]
bye
do
[Music]
hi we're back here again
oh
[Music]
so
do
[Music]