[Music]
so
hello
[Music]
what a lovely sight you have some nice
bones
examine the skeleton
survived one day what a legend today
we're playing
don't slive together and if you guys
don't know the objective of the game you
should reread the title because it's in
the title
post cannot starve pretty much
supposed to see how long we can survive
for and that involves
foraging for stuff crafting not getting
lost
and working together as a team as you
can see we've already had some dust here
over on the right
all right you have a little well i like
it i'll try my best to guide them
but i don't know yeah you know the most
[Music]
it comes with my character wait really a
dog you're lucky
you're like a voicemail it's so cute a
girl scouts
i'm not bad so pretty much you just
spread out we'll find stuff you gotta
find carrots and mushrooms and
when it gets dark we can go back to the
spot now
i think it's getting darker now if you
look up at the top at the top
right corner you can see there's a
little red section that's just like the
twilight
that's like uh it's sunset it's not dark
dark yeah
okay it's not dark dark it's just uh
dark almost dark
yes it's dark it's not dark yeah
yes we can all go in the same direction
it looks like we're going north so
it you get really hungry you can collect
these seeds on the ground and you can
eat them
mushrooms you gotta cook before you eat
them uh or else you'll get sick
oh no and if you collect
oh it is sorry my bed
i like my character he looks like um
like a tim burton character like someone
that johnny depp would play
i can't yeah can i just pumpkins
huh
the pumpkins those are pretty useful so
like you can use them for
like uh torches no torches are really
important if you want to travel at night
what is this okay these guys are aggro
they're aggro
oh no i'm good so what happens
like around day 14 or so there will be
wolves that will try to come attack us
and we have to fight them so we have to
find wood we gotta find trees uh we
gotta find sticks we gotta find
rocks the basics okay okay
yeah it's like minecraft yeah uh you
guys find sharks and also [\h__\h]
yeah uh the poop you can use to make
farms with to fertilize your crops
oh of course it's innovative
oh my god someone's following us
i don't think there's anywhere to go up
here
okay we'll go back down we gotta go back
down anyways to get to the spawn
okay by the way
you can catch a bird and eat it but
sometimes it'll only give you feathers
instead of giving you meat ah
okay shadowy creature
what can
[Music]
oh we're pretty far from spawn so if you
walk on the path go faster
when the wolves attack we can hide there
and then they'll like attack them
and then they'll fight back sorry
my uh my johnny depp character is saying
i'm so hungry
uh okay i have berries for you if me
we'll we'll meet at the spawn
how can i recover my hearts though okay
skeleton is still just here
all right here's berries for whoever is
really gonna give you the valley
i think those
how do i eat them uh you can drag them
over yourself
[Music]
i thought it would be there again maybe
i shouldn't respond right now yeah we
both know
oh if you if you if you go to the spawn
beacon and you click on it
uh you can't we had six counties
yeah i did we're supposed to make a fire
uh yeah i got it i'll come i'm coming
away i think we're going to keep going
no no no it's okay we're okay i got fire
i didn't know we had six the next time
when you guys have sticks and flints you
just find it right away on the floor you
can make a torch
[Music]
that's a good thing oh and picking
flowers if you find any flowers that'll
help your brain juice
oh brain juice cool i need a bit of wait
we lose all our stuff yeah we got to
pick it up it's on the floor pick it up
oh minecraft hours
and if you pick up twelve flowers you
can make a flower hat
also cool i want a flower hat
uh
[Music]
just explore and then uh i'll make a
base for us so
we don't hide why's mine
hello no what the [\h__\h] oh
why is it so low
[Music]
i know
let's see weapons fight it's under fight
you can make a spear
so if you collect a grass but i need to
make i need to make a
a science machine hey okay i'm gonna go
back to this blind i've got
guys i might turn out to you now because
my audience said i'm too quiet but maybe
i'm too loud for you guys now you're
sounds good
twig if you find uh
like a twig bush it's like a little
thing sticking up on the ground
how do i kill a rabbit i want a flower
you have to catch it so if you make you
take grass
you can trap and then you can trap the
rabbit and you can kill it with your
bare hands
if i make grass
i have the grass okay i'm gonna make up
what we need now if any of you guys
have flint and sticks you can make an
axe and start collecting wood
and then with the wood i can make a
machine that can make us a bunch more
stuff
i don't i i have an empty elixir do you
need that
can i make a trap with fall fangs
fox fangs how did you pronounce that
full fangs yeah that sounds like a
halloween costume thing
no no
[Music]
are these pigs nice uh there are nice
pigs actually some some don't attack you
guys every year get satisfied
who is that i'm scared usually pigs are
like carnivorous
we gotta give them something okay hello
how do i breed some here i got berry
bushes
i should have collected more rocks i
need
all right i'm giving you guys a job
who's here all right
i'm here hello okay you you take that
you you guys collect wood yay
oh there's a turkey can i light the
turkey on fire
can i come in can i will they let me in
their house uh
no that you can't go in the house i'm
gonna drop torches at this spawn for you
guys okay or i'll drop
one torch uh you guys take care of it i
think i have
i think i have a light ah oh yeah if you
have a lighter you uh
might be able to use it okay i'll stick
with inna then oh
okay okay that's good and if you guys
have any quick then
you can make your own torch too what
does what does the flower do
when you pick up a flower it increases
your sanity
so it's good and you can also use it to
make a hat it helps your sanity
could be some floating wow just random
on the ground right
oh yeah yeah you can get it from rocks
too uh if you make a pickaxe hunky you
always get
okay i'm gonna i think i have enough to
um
i need two pieces of wood and six more
rocks to make what is that ghost
permanent fire
who is that ghost where's that ghost
your friend that's like your i think
it's supposed to be like your dead
sister or something
oh yeah wow did you see man
hey look there's something in the ground
oh there are many things oh there's
sticks
what is that what the hell race dirt oh
there's a dead body over there who is it
[Music]
i killed it i got me
my butterflies i can build a campfire so
i'm gonna go back to the base and
i'll build a campfire over there you
guys go back into the spawn yeah yeah
let's go back let's go back
okay faster
i see it now there's another moment
first style is very cute
i like these i'm most tasty
oh never mind okay maybe with some gravy
we could eat the most
it's okay i have i have six stones
oh oh you have friends can i eat this
mandrake
happy girl yeah your hand but it'll put
you to sleep
oh and not a hotel i think you have to
kill it nice
wait watch this you can turn that off uh
because
you'll run out of fuel and you're
lighter i think i don't know
also you can cook stuff here so if you
have like a mushroom or you can cook
seeds to give you more
yogurt i have carrots you want carrots
you can cook carrots
you just click it in your inventory and
then
click on the fire with it in your mouth
ricky
[Music]
the shadow scared me that the shadow of
the tree scared me
i have one here i'll just drop what i
have because i don't know what it does
here okay yeah we got a glove
there's a monkey paw what does that do
ah i think you can you can cook pretty
much everything
oh really i have butterfly wings
cooked carrots oh here we go thank you
for the butterfly wings
oh i was about to cook you're over there
you did it wrong
i'll give it back to you if you press q
and e oh somebody gave me carrots
yes i ate it
i thought i thought you dropped a bite
we survived good morning
good morning sunshine
uh you can make healing potion but uh
it's a bit difficult so like
if you find a spider web you wanna you
wanna collect
spider web from the spider nest and uh
it's kind of dangerous but once you
build
trouts out of grass you can catch the
spiders and they give you spider web and
you use that to make a fishing rod
and you catch fish and then the fish
make they make good heels
oh yeah
oh binoculars that sounds really good
beautiful i don't think that's
guys what should i draw yeah i don't
think we can use them
[Music]
i
uh so yeah you're probably in the swamp
areas in the swamp area if you walk
by too slow uh there are tentacles in
the ground look at your stuff
no hitting maybe not
you guys have any wood has anybody
collected some wood
yeah i have ten i have ten
oh okay i'll take some i'm gonna i'll go
back to this
tentacles here what is that what is this
i'm in what is a stage hand yeah
stage hand it's like a table with some
flowers around it
oh uh don't don't take the flower
but i did i did take a flower
i think you're sanity so if you check
your brand meter at the top
you should be able to see whether your
sanity is going down actively and if it
is it might be
the thing you picked up it's fine i
think
okay there's a frog on my tail
okay stomach okay brain
yes what is the other one
uh what stomach brain and health so much
for
no not november i can plant a tree i
found
nuts okay uh yeah
some some of the tree nuts you can eat
them but sometimes if you don't plant
it bad things will happen
some bad things yeah i have to pick them
up but i have a full inventory
yeah i got your lighter
that's the oh thing i could see from
there i'm coming back
all right i'm out i i brought you some
wood
oh thank you i got some um but i'll pick
it up if you just leave it there nothing
will do
minecraft
[Music]
how do i can i get the rocks with the
axe as well
no you got to make a pickaxe god damn it
top left
no it's pretty easy i bet you have
enough to make it leads to my new friend
what freeze gimme
no goddammit why did the rabbit sound
like
he died when he died
[Music]
now we're talking about i need one more
rock a turkey
i found a big turkey kill it i'm killing
it pretty hard to catch with the x
oh yeah i won't give up i'm used to
chasing things with sharp objects uh-oh
all right we have a fire at the base if
you guys get there and uh
there's no fire you just put grass or
wood or anything that you can burn in
in the fire and it'll you know like oh
oh my pig was just going home okay
i could really
are the pigs dangerous uh
the ones who try to attack you are
dangerous
there are some nice pigs okay
you'll know right away actually the pigs
if you give them like a
piece of meat to eat they'll be your
friend and they'll trap they'll chop
trees for you
oh have a sweet of them
let's see where the basil okay thanks if
you guys are standing near this science
machine i made here you see that new
tabs appear on the left side so now you
can make like
rope you can refine you can make rope
you can use that to make traps and you
can catch
bunnies and spiders and frogs
hey it's an episode of dr stone nice
going watson
you should probably go back literally
carrying
yes i was going to say thank you amelia
most helpful oh okay
oh should probably go home if anybody
wants some
trap you can use that and you just put
it down on the ground and
it'll like be automatic okay i'm gonna
go catch
some rabbits it's gonna get dark soon
just be careful
mm-hmm okay
here we go
i think jamaica to make farms well you
need the seeds that you get and then
stones and fertilizer but uh oh yeah
right here food you can just make one
here oh yeah we have enough that
our camp is just surrounded by
skrellingtons and fish
we can't destroy the skeleton so you can
it feels like home
really like decorative yeah they're a
reminder of our our
humble beginnings how about that whoa
how can i make a back pillow
oh a backpack you can make it uh uh you
gotta refine your rope and then i think
it's under survival you can make uh
uh okay it's under survival you can make
one ah
not the candy bag no it might be grayed
out because it might not have enough
sticks on fire i guess
i think there's a more advanced backpack
you can make with that can you make
things like
chess in this in this game
okay cool around babes are you even
awake
chad is so dead you're supposed to do
not starve jets
stay stay away from me get longer and
longer and so you just have to survive
you can kind of still explore at night
if you have like a torch or something
uh but it's better to just stay here and
cook or sleep you can make a sleeping
bag and sleeping at
in the night time it increases your
sanity levels if you're getting low
okay okay
i think my salary um are always low
yeah some characters it's hard
what was that what was that
if anybody ever wants to sleep there's a
sleeping bag here but it's better not to
do it now because it's going to turn day
time and you'll wake up immediately but
you can do it when it's in the red
the sunset time you can sleep then too
[Music]
wow
i'll work on on trying to heal if you
guys want to fight stuff if you find any
spiders
you can trap the spiders you can fight
them
and then we can use the spider web and
we'll go fishing okay
idea bye bye
[Applause]
all right we'll meet up again at night
okay sounds good
i'll go follow you i'll go do some
important things
do you have a trap i do
put it down anywhere around the pond and
then go near that frog and make it
aggressive
put it down okay and now go to the frog
and like tease him you want to taunt him
and then he'll follow you
and you lovely
[Laughter]
nice warts over the trap
past it tom looks funny my sanity what
do you know
i need some food where have i ended up
at
yeah we gotta make a chest and like
store food in there or something
oh god yeah seeds here eat seeds you're
a bird you can eat seeds
yummy but i prefer fried chicken you
know
i don't think there's any chicken in
this game but there are turkeys yeah i
did see one before we started streaming
i saw our turkey
you can't run i've cornered him i've
cornered him oh no
yeah turkey's scared no it's in the
water
snail skin no it's in the water
oh and no fish it's not for you pick up
soggy drumstick no it's not for you
i keep running towards the water and
it's not letting me pick up
oh uh yeah you can't go into the water
unless you have a boat
oh sorry kelly you're hardly boats
yeah you can make boats and we can like
sail the sea but it's pretty dangerous
so i don't think we're ready for that
yet
yeah as long as we have good eye the sea
is not dangerous for us
oh that's true right because like
somebody has to control the anchor and
somebody has to control like the
steering wheel
or like the sailors oh she can totally
do that she can she is made for that
oh yes all at the same time
many twigs yay i
desperately need food god damn it uh
okay i'll go back i'll have
have some food we should we should make
some
should make a crock pot we gotta burn
trees
a crock pot yeah
and you can you can put four ingredients
in there you can make all these like
different
recipes and stuff and then you can make
like cupcakes you can make cupcakes
sandwiches but can you make fried
chicken
fried turkey how about that fried turkey
you can make a turkey meal i don't i
think
you go you can make chicken nuggets
really
close yeah but you need honey from bees
oh i just literally ate my honey
oh it's really good for heels so chicken
nuggets they give you like a lot of
peach peas
i did it didn't though it did not yeah
no
not the honey by itself ah okay
oh well oh we're gonna build something
now
nice where's home
i don't see it's not home
where's home if you guys uh we want to
make a functioning base we got to have
like
a food source we got to have somewhere
to store the food
we got to have defense stuff so if you
guys want to like
recipes and stuff on the left side make
whatever you want
i am not lost i am not lost i got the
monster but are you lost
i am already back i think oh yeah you're
here you're here
that looked like crap but i'll eat it
thank you
maybe i have something useful for you uh
i have a bunch of rocks
and twigs that's pretty useful maybe i
should keep them oh dear
ah and you can use it to build stuff if
you want
huh cool are you okay good uh
oh we're back
okay we're good oh i got some meat
uh if anybody wants to sleep if you're
if your brain juice is low you can pick
up this sleeping bag here and you can
start sleeping now but it it'll take
your hunger so you got to make sure you
got like
a decent amount i think i'll wait with
that
and not do it right now yeah i'm really
hungry uh oh
i didn't notice how hungry i was i do
have one
uh chicken legs
oh we could have make chicken nuggets
i'm lighting up the place i think uh i
ate something
didn't know i had such something so
useful the whole time
i can make a compass is that you one of
the pickaxe fingers
i don't think so i mean we haven't we
have a map
i made a pickups i made a pickaxe
wow i made my pictures why are these
lanterns lit up are they always were
they always little no i put them there a
moment ago
[Music]
why is the game audio getting louder is
that is something
i hear something too
i don't know i only hear the flies from
the poop hey yeah
let's pick that up there we go
[Laughter]
i was like those flies are really loud i
need something really
oh callie do you have any wood i can't
make it you guys think i should sleep
away i have a ton but i'm also hungry
there you go thank you wow welcome
i did a lot of chopping today
okay we have enough thank you thank you
thank you super giant
thank you so far
pick up flowers where are flowers oh
uh there there are some flowers down
south
it's still not night right now right
it's still twilight uh it's about
to turn tonight oh god you guys ever
have any wood
you can add uh you can add uh
planks to it and it'll like make this
big fire like this
oh i have planks i can make a i can make
a chest does anybody do we need another
gonna die
[Music]
there's a table following me the table
where i took the flower from
a table
help i won't ever follow me all the way
up here
i'm back there you are uh did the table
follow me though
i don't think so i don't i don't see it
but it was there it was there i'm not
crazy oh it's there already oh yes
look at my table do you see my table as
well
actually if you make a hammer you might
be able to oh
yeah a desk could that's what the yellow
yeah i didn't know that uh getting nice
and warm really close to the fire would
do that
burn i get i have a job for you come
here okay
where's the flower that i picked i'm
really looking like johnny depp all
right take
this oh god don't equip it yet but take
it
let's miss me all right okay don't equip
me
yeah yeah and now i want you to come
over here equip it and set these
these scraggly trees on fire oh
but of course wait wait
i need the chocolate baby
is these trees are on fire
what a waste of wood yeah you're telling
me you can catch me
you know have you have you tried that
before i can show you how oh yes
i got a chop to help so if you find a
frog by a pond you just put the
trap down anywhere near the frog and
then you you bait the frog into
into walking into the trap oh i look
perfect now
i can't show you all my cat wow my ghost
is so smart they killed it killed my
my frogs for me oh yeah the ghost will
attack your stuff
like enemies i love my ghost my ghost is
amazing
flints nice i think that's
thank you i think so too looking good
where did i even get my ghost from i
don't why don't i
you don't have the ghost right it's like
a question kiara you don't you don't
have you play the same character but you
don't have the ghost right
oh yeah because uh if you there's like a
flower in my inventory and if i click on
it i can summon the ghost but i have i
just haven't done it yet i probably
should
hmm
oh wait hungry found a bunch of good
stuff
need one more flower to make a hat
yeah let's all get matching flower hats
i don't want to have a party
how's your sanity um
80 free but my hunger is still uh not
very
good looking yeah i'm making crock pots
now so
did you want me to show you how to catch
the froggies oh no i i
think i got it
i don't know why is all the audio
getting louder
okay uh where are you come come to me
i'll give you a present
it makes me sleep i found a man racket
oh yeah you can kill it right yeah it'll
make you sleep if you eat it
is that a good thing i mean i kind of do
need to sleep uh
here you go ah where are that
oh thank you
you're welcome it's dark i'm making food
we need to wake up
we need to kill rabbits we need to kill
frogs
and we need stuff to fill the crock-pot
with
make meatballs some weapons oh i have uh
i have some mushrooms yeah yeah yeah any
vegetables do you like carrots
i just need like a few more twigs and i
can make one i need three more times
does anybody have two
i have twigs i got
unless you're tweezers just in case if
you by the way if you guys
click or control click on something uh
you can have it
and then like oh okay cool
how big is this map like this yeah
yeah it's pretty big you gotta move your
dog oh
sorry like somebody pick up this what is
this on the ground
crystal ball thingy okay
[Music]
eat the bug which bite now if you feel
the crock pot
uh usually like it's uh as long as you
don't put anything in edible in there it
should
make something my seeds
[Music]
oh chester yeah i thought that yeah wait
who found chester
jessica that's not mine is that good
i don't know what's wrong with you pick
up a bone
hello i'm home okay i know
the following am i do you still need
some twigs
no i have a ton okay thank you um
what's this on the fire crock pot okay
there's no fire oh we can cook it there
now okay
yeah yeah so if you put a bunch if you
can put like different vegetables and
stuff together
there you go it's like different recipes
it doesn't tell you the recipes um
why are you dying i don't know
i'm gonna die
oh oh yeah all right i got i went to
sleep because i cooked the mandrake
or no i guess not no no it's just a
crawling horror okay
it's okay you can you can you'll go back
okay
wait why am i oh i'm hungry what should
we do i'm very hungry as well
me too wait do we have anything cooking
okay i'll make something with you
okay yes chef yummy why am i so hungry
i'm just gonna put
monster meat in there oh it's a monster
oh does anybody have what is it maybe
they can cook it huh
can i i'll just put i'll just make fun
of you
oh you guys can cook your seeds okay
give you a little bit more
if you cook yourself does that give you
back more
more hunger oh maybe not actually i
think it does
i think it does what i was looking at
was hp it's getting dark
how do you make uh weapons because i
feel like if i had a weapon
then i could kill a bunch of things and
get us a bunch of meat well actually
there's a spear right here on the floor
i don't know whose this is but
you see this spirit i'm standing next to
it you can pick it up and you can use
that you can equip it you can attack
stuff
cool okay let me see how i only try and
pick it up who's who's the hungriest
right now what do you what are you guys
hunger levels 55 goodnight
what's the one next to i think it's
stuck in the skeleton
what died
need rocks to make the hammer does
anybody have rocks
whoa i have some of this good stuff but
why is he i see the rock
i see i'm gonna take your rocks i'm
feeling refreshed
i stopped to like really well damn
and i have full hunger now there it is
okay nice
i can get oh okay let's go
sorry to have you make everything watson
oh it's okay
i promise i'll kill a bunch of things oh
chad
which direction should i go yeah it's
gone never mind
i think i think i can make you a spear
though where do i go
i just want me to go bottom left
i'm going for bottom left oh i'm super
hungry let's see uh
what can i eat we jumped over my trap
yeah cool
oh seeds noise noise hello piggies
oh nice thank you perfect i'll go kill
some things
here we go will they will they kill me
for doing that i wonder
um man no don't
no leave my ghost alone come with me
ghosty come with me
come with me don't kill no no no i can't
do that okay
um
wait so the stuff everything like
respawns every day
uh not every day there's like a cycle
some depending on what it is it might
take a few days to come back
yeah not every day oh what the hell
ah there you go since when are frogs so
dangerous
yeah they take items from you too when
they attack you oh you're
joking
i found the spider nest um ah
and the pig is so nice to try to kill
the spiders for me
uh he killed maybe one i got some silk
oh nice and yeah yeah we can use that to
make the
[Music]
stuff ooh
did that tree just move like stuff stuff
is good
i probably shouldn't try to kill the
spiders on my own right it's probably
gonna kill me
uh you don't have to kill them you can
you can make uh the flower traps
sorry i don't always have flour you can
make the grass traps and then you can
uh put them down on the ground and then
walk into the traps
i killed them all i killed all the
spiders
you killed oh with your ghost no with my
ghost and my pickaxe i got like a bunch
of meat and spider webs and silk
crap
you can put like one in each recipe in
the crock-pot otherwise it'll make you
sick
okay hey uh amelia how does one make a
trap
catch the rabbit uh you need uh
grass and twigs and then you gotta go
next to the science machine in the base
come with me got it okay i think that's
the next thing about it damn
my goal is to show you can you catch a
rabbit put the track down
yeah you gotta it's kind of hard to
catch one because like they're so
fast but what you can do is uh you want
to put the trap stand on the hole and
then put the trap like right on the hole
so then when they go back in and when
they come out
they trigger the trap and they're
running
damn he really wanted to fight big brain
it's in big trouble because i'm super
hungry right now i'm trying to catch
these rabbits but
uh i'm sucking watching rabbits is more
of like a long term thing like uh
you can't catch them right away you
probably have to come back and check on
the trap like
a day later i could like real trapped
guys i muted myself but do i need
these fangs are they useful for anything
i want to drop some stuff do i need to
binoculars other things to kill
probably not right i saw something
though and now i find um
spiders you can kill those you can kill
frogs the turkey
stuff moles don't go there abigail
[Music]
i have spider meat yeah oh
but we have to cook it with a recipe uh
yeah
okay i'm going back now and we can cook
some stuff so we can all
eat what's up my ghost keeps
like putting up a fight with these
spiders but it's like
killing everything legitimately wow holy
[\h__\h]
so strong i love my ghost
i'm bringing home all the meat oh nice
eating huh
no but didn't die
get in there i can't bubble shoot
hmm damn
okay uh i'll make food now
yeah thank you let's go home
i shouldn't eat that right now well the
mandrakes are really good they like give
you i didn't know they give you full hp
[Music]
okay callie when this thing comes out of
the of the crock pot you can eat it
thank you thanks watson okay i'll make
it up to you
i'll actually kill a bunch of things
you'll see okay
you'll see i will be useful
wait did my axe break a frog
thank you oh it's a teddy bear i was
wondering what that was that was nice
wow
where's michael so bright
you know my sanity is dropping it's not
too large
god damn it oh he's picking a fight
abigail
can we just can we just live in
happiness together with these creatures
why you always have to pick a photo it's
never an option
i wonder if there's a way to like
unsummon the ghost because i
i know you have to summon it i don't
know if it'll ever go away though there
must be a way
hmm
if you guys ever need more storage you
can pick up this bone and
this little chester guy this little
monster doggy
he'll follow you and if you click on him
he has a storage
oh yeah rock
oh nice i got tools now baby
progress baby all right so if
uh i can give you guys some tasks if
you're like what should i do
what should i do you know i'll give you
some tests uh
your task is to go collect a bunch of
rocks and there's a rock area
if you go to the east and then and you
go south
yeah there's a whole rock area i don't
know if you can see it on the map
but it's like a desert looking area you
can collect all those rocks oh
yeah yes yes okay uh
how do we boost our sanity again fish
right
uh boosting sanity you have to sleep but
if you
are hungry then uh you'll wake up
immediately or
you can collect flowers man picking
flowers really helps with your sanity if
you find any ah but there's a
there's a sleeping bag it'll be in the
chest oh i'm sleeping once
okay good well uh
is it when as soon as it reaches morning
you'll wake up so you just wanna
next time when you sleep you sleep in
the red time uh at the start to get as
much out of the sleeping bag as possible
we can make more those are really
um okay how about this
chat does it looks like it could be
something uh
delicious it's time to kill things uh
take out the butter if you guys collect
any vegetables or mushrooms or berries
those are things uh that you can put in
a crock pot
yeah you just make it'll make like
meatballs if you have two meats in there
and those are really
chilling look at this
nope wait how do you put it goddamn
i meant to put that in the crockpot not
my mouth oh
i think we might um be getting attacked
soon yes
[Music]
oh what is that what the what what the
hell was that
what oh what
uh does it happen to look like a giant
teddy bear
yes
did you make that i'm looking for
flowers to pick and i don't see it
run north follow the path north and go
into the beefalos and like stand
on them i need more berries
[Music]
little thing coming oh i don't have a
good feeling about it what can i make
with this stuff i hear the movies
yeah see you guys just come come up
north follow the path and
run into the beefalo you'll be safe okay
can we kill the wolves
yeah you can attack them quick
you can make armor or you can make grass
armor too
oh they're they're coming
it's armor huh okay oh i can make that
oh
god this is so bad
oh dear oh run go to hide
wait what is what is that noise
the wolves
i made i made two fishing rods if
someone wants to have one i'll put one
in
the store they're here
oh my god that's a wall what the hell
oh there's so many
[Music]
i did good ghost what a good ghost you
are thank you for protecting me
i had like two wolves running up to me
but my ghost protected me
and now i'll go fishing hey sorry kelly
i stole it
again
[Music]
are you still alive you know oh it's the
wolf
[Music]
should i can i fish anywhere or should i
go to fish somewhere where i see some
shadows
in the uh and you also want to fish in
the pond so we have upon
a pond a pond pretty close to spawn oh
yeah yeah you'll see how it works
fishing in any other game okay
i'm coming back from my shy loser are
you here you know
oh i'm very far i just can't remember
flimsy rod what
i thought that works
yeah that was interesting you got food
yeah so when you make the recipes in a
crock pot you can only put oh no
oh no i'm really not doing well huh oh
why is the earth shaking question
can i eat why isn't it meteorites
oh they're meteor
uh
[Music]
oh
only fish in ponds okay wasn't that a
pond ah you mean the really small ones
are really small okay okay one second i
gotta get the berries so i can make more
what was it crock pot oh yeah yeah yeah
in the crock pot
oh no there are wolves at the campsite
it's probably useless ah
watch out should i come to kill them yes
oh you also have a ghost now it's
killing chester
nice no where's the where's the spawn
all right now i get now i get the joke
behind chester finally
because he's a chest
i just got it now
that's like an enoch plan ina did you
suggest that name to the game
it must have been you your ghost looks
different oh they want to be friends
look so angry
oh wait there's free ghosts now what the
hell
oh no there's two okay oh that was kelly
oh
didn't recognize you as a ghost
let's make another question
can you cook never mind that's a stupid
question you can put
sticks in food but it'll it'll change
into something less
uh filling like only one stick you can
put
oh can someone light up the can someone
light up the the crock-pot
oh i think it just goes automatically
once you put enough stuff in it
ah there we go no oh who put in those
carrots
me i'm just gonna
is it cookies build a shovel
or a pitchfork no why did i eat it
uh i hate the monster meat oh no i'm
doing fine though idea
yeah you're fine
i can make so many things i can make a
pickaxe
i can make a shovel what should i make i
can make a pitchfork i can make a razor
oh why would i want to shave my face
my face is perfect that's a long shadow
i think you can shave your beard and
like put it up shave your
beard house right now
why do you keep on getting new skins i
need uh
uh i need some face i want skins too
also i still can't the server will drop
you like some
stuff you can put your clothes i'm
talking about armor you want armor
no i want the skins but also armor and i
still don't understand how i can make it
back what exactly do i need because it
doesn't lock up
[Music]
where is this game like what is the
story where's the lord
[Music]
there is no lord
need we can uh we need to build an
alchemy machine but to build an alchemy
machine
we need electric dudettes and you can
get those by like smashing
sometimes you might just find them but
you gotta like smash some stuff that you
find like that
there's like really weird gear stuff you
can you can make a refrigerator in this
game but
i don't remember how to get all the
materials
because your facts
it will go back
i will not let you get away
come on abigail faster
no stop running
stop running stop
stop let's go
stop
turkey
you ate the berries you stupid piece of
[\h__\h]
oh my berries i eat you with berries
that's how it's supposed to be
where is everyone i am in rockland
i'm in froglant okay
hydrated how do we stay hydrated in this
game i got it did you also just get a
super chat saying stay hydrated
yeah me too what the hell
at the same time they're telling us to
stay hydrated how sweet of them thank
you
hi thank you i need to drive the rabbits
away from where the holes are
my trap here
anyway yeah i shall stay hydrated
[Music]
what is
it's a massacre
so many frog legs oh my god
yummy frog i got a gold nugget
beer what is that
wet audrey rabbit into the water
i murdered it i have
so much food look at more that's a pond
wait
drop that how do i eat can i rock and
eat at the same time
no that was good
oh i'm fishing for the first time in my
life
go back got two rabbits why are you
doing all food
murder i'm good
favorite i have two gloves can i make it
[Music]
wayfinder marker all right
we're making rabbit tonight baby pekka
pickle rabbit pickles
[Music]
why can't i cook them i have this wait
uh cook what i'm trying to cook the
rabbits that i killed but i only have
two ah did you i have a
yeah i don't have anything to put in
there you need to fill the rest of the
slots it's gotta be four so if you have
like berries or carrots or mushrooms
one monster meat or one stick you can
put those in there
okay um see what i can do
what is that i have more
morsels oh wait do i have to
click something ah oh you can put it in
the crock pot if you want it'll make
um tasty meatballs
yeah i really want meatballs now hungry
hey i don't know how to
how how does it work the fishing yeah it
says hook and then i click on it one
time or
oh uh yeah yeah you uh
put it in the pond there we go like no
minecraft i got it
i never i never even fished in minecraft
but i got a i got a fresh water fish no
oh here i don't want to eat all these
meatballs myself
but i'm saving my meatballs for the
really tough time
oh good idea i'll save mine too
no you're so long what
it's okay living life on the edge okay
if we find any spider glands we can make
like this uh
potion as a healing potion we need
spider glands
allen do you need food my guy for now
i'm gonna wait till it gets real low and
then i'll eat my meatballs
yeah oh good idea i'm doing this
that was fun you think just like me
callie
i brought some ice what can we do
make some tasty drinks i think you can
make like a
you can use it in recipes i know you can
put it in the crock pot but
i don't know i think you might be able
to make uh ice cream or like some sort
of drink with it too
you gotta have like the different ice
cream
yeah you can make cupcakes in this game
you gotta like look up the restaurant we
have anything
[Music]
does that mean you can ride stuff you
can like uh
i don't know maybe murder i know now you
can ride a boat
yes it's [\h__\h]
yeah not with the saddle
yummy oh my god that was that was funny
looking
yeah what what what no you did like a
weird pose
oh i messed up
i'm just eating okay gotta stay in
character
i'm trying to not starve okay unlike you
understand hey there's nothing wrong
with starving we all have flower crowns
except for you guys
[Music]
i really want to grow the beard so i
really look like a real johnny depp
[Music]
you can also then you can shave the
beard and like turn it into a jacket or
something like confess
legendary all right so maybe
maybe we should build a boat if you guys
want to like work towards something we
can build the
idea yeah let's
i'm gonna go catch some more rabbits but
you guys talk about building the boat
while i go catch these rabbits
okay looking good
i just need a bunch of wood need planks
finally with two we need a bunch of wood
to make boats so
as much wood as you can collect you like
chopped a lot
finally i made a backpack finally
10 years later
congratulations just took me 5 million
years
trap who would ever make a bird trap
those poor birds
leave them alone oh you're asking how to
get a chicken that's how you get uh some
chicken you get a little uh
the chicken legs from them no no no no
no that's not how it breaks no
too much they're uh their area
move oh wait i love the i love the truck
down there i wonder if anything got
caught in it
i guess we can make that time
oh no
how much wood do we need all the wood
you can get
yeah okay
[Music]
now we probably need like uh probably
like 30 or 40.
oh my goodness
[Music]
um abigail come
come with me abigail won't be squishy
i should probably store some more things
i still got all my silk and spider
glands
oh i can heal myself with spider glands
is that for the heart or for the hunger
oh yeah yeah it's for uh healing it's
for we can make like a healing style for
anybody who's low hp
and you just it's really easy you just
need rocks and ash and i have some ash
so
oh and i got rocks i got rocks i just
need to ash them that takes a long time
i'm just supposed to wait for it yeah
you can get ash by burning down like
little bushes or grass
toys anything you put on the floor will
probably turn into ash
oh do i burn it down with my torch yeah
oh okay fire travels like between things
you got to make sure
like if you don't want to burn down the
forest or all of our stuff for example
you got to do it far away oh oh oh [\h__\h]
oh damn it
oh it's going to ask you there's a
certain way fire doesn't hurt me
no problem i just hold space you can
hold space and it doesn't go faster
oh you hold space what's that oh
i didn't know i kept clicking yeah
why does it take so long the fishing
stop the burning oh yeah it takes a
while
murder damn another two rabbits
i'm starting to get good at that
catching rabbits
oh you caught a few yep
nice
didn't work ah yeah you gotta you gotta
burn like little things like a like
a grass bush or if you have twigs you
can
you can drop individual twigs uh i think
with
um
i see okay i got the grass okay yeah i
don't remember where i put my rabbit
trap
oh no i think it you should you might be
able to see it on the map
maybe oh good good uh maybe i have it
i found your friend i'm like oh no let
me give it back to you
that's what i've been using this whole
time to catch rabbits
no it's totally fine
you can have the meatballs that we that
we make with the
rabbits fine
gosh i keep going the wrong way
i was just like man i really lose stuff
so easy
gosh here i'm dropping it on the ground
no no no no it's only got what do you
thought
if you want to catch more go for it i
don't know no
i don't even know how to use it really
i'm back
oh sorry oh you're good you're good do
your thing ina
do your thing i'm glad we have enough
stuff to put inside the pot
yeah just put a lot of berries and like
me i like hunting because it's simple
i can make a sleeping bag oh okay
[Music]
it's like at the top it's called healing
south
oh okay got it
whoa thanks
good night
wow i'm like a professional survivor
damn
almost done
wow ah i need your wood goodness can you
wake up
my what the wood other word i have no
one for you i'm doing so well
i'm amazed with myself um i think this
is because my mom was like a survivor
mom so
i think i learned it from him i have a
survival mom
really she taught me the ways yeah she
can do anything
with with no tools she survives in the
in the wilderness
is that cool yeah my mom is a survival
mom
oh do you hear that mom she's probably
watching right now they
don't you hear that mom they said you
were cool
get the camera mom look i have so many
friends with me
look at all my friends i used to be solo
link
okay go back through world take my one
oh no i
have my one good for all all my
[Music]
i don't know it's the third one four
three two one it's
oh it's hunger oh she dead
i thought you needed eggplant for that
ah
yeah oh there's more science
oh god what is this music make another
trap
is it the hands they're trying to steal
their fire you gotta step on them
i got
i'm gonna cut them up just like in the
german fairy tales
oh the dude with the scissors yeah i
remember when you showed me that and i
was absolutely terrified
uh deaf is terrified by german fairy
tales oh my god
look there i have limits okay listen
i want this prank oh wait it's
interesting that things spoil in this
game too
yeah i gotta cook my monster meat
goddammit i need some
some berries i have berries i'll put
through i'll put
three berries in there okay
thank
okay i'm gonna look for a suitable place
to put
our water stuff i think this is
no this is not the ocean what we might
make another base
by the water because that's we're gonna
put the boat
wait do you have my wood i took it
okay it's mine well will the food not
spoil if i leave it at the base
um
i put one uh one meat in the pot if
someone wants to add
uh berries you can make a crock pot uh
meatballs meatballs
[Music]
i just need some stone and then i can
move stuff over
my mouth i'm on my way to get some snow
now
oh stop but yes don't you know are you
collecting some stones
oh yeah i have seven rocks oh can i have
some
yes i'm on my way back okay
i need my potion again that's fine i'll
survive because i have my ghost
let's go that fella i'll leave them in
the chest
rocks i also have rocks if you want them
yes
oh yeah i have a [\h__\h] ton of frog legs i
got 16 frog legs
so if someone needs food i i got too
much oh you can make a sand you can make
frog like sandwiches
what sandwich oh hell no
have you guys ever had real frog like
before no
no from what i've heard that just tastes
like
i tried it once but it was at like a
really uh shady buffet and it tasted
really gross
thank god yeah i'm not surprised
have you guys said you sure it was
really frog like
snails it was a frog like it was a frog
like yeah
ew it was like frozen hmm i haven't i've
had snails before
is it what's gonna call it escargot oh
fairy fancier
i prefer fried chicken but okay you go
with what you like
right so what exactly do we need to make
a frog sandwich i got to the frog legs
if you just put one frog leg in there
already i put berries
[Music]
a little low though but it's fine i'll
probably should have cooked the monster
does someone want um some meat
like actual cooked meat
does someone need it i'm okay for now
but probably later
now melting ice oh no i'm back
[Music]
there you know go to my trap the
meatballs are in the chest if someone
needs them
oh darn it what is what is oh eyes never
mind i'm dumb
wait that didn't even make a sandwich
then made the same thing as before
the game oh
[Music]
no no darn it
it's expected give me my trap i'll
continue that
trap okay
thank you um so if i put four meats into
the pot will it still only make one
meatballs for everyone
uh yeah yeah so it's good to like uh
there's like a balance so if you put
like two meats and two vegetables it
should make meatballs but if you
put like too many vegetables and it'll
be like a vegetable based dish
you can use filler like uh monster meat
you can put one monster meat in but if
you put more than one it'll turn into
like monster lasagna and it'll take away
it's
monster lasagna that's so yummy yeah
put a stick in there it'll make a like a
kebab or something kebab
unless it's fish then it makes fish
sticks
oh yummy they all sound delicious i'm so
hungry i didn't eat breakfast yet
i'm starving in the irl but i want them
again
um i'm confused because i definitely
killed three things today and i only
have
one morsel in my pocket
okay that's what i need to do anyway
there are two things in the pot
should we kill them i was going to make
a boat but we're not really close to the
water so if we made a boat it'd be like
a long journey stop
away
i bet you know what i bet i was trying
to put them into the pot and i ate them
guys fight me
i don't see it i'm gonna go
oh here we go
yeah you can yeah wow put them in
oh yeah it's trying to make something oh
it's already cooking okay okay
yeah as long as you don't put anything
like weird in there it should make like
some sort of recipe
but yeah this is a lot today i don't
know why
[Music]
cute voices everywhere
okay
uh well we have like stored meatballs
here too in the chest
hold on someone is at my is up my abode
i will be back in just a moment
i'll keep going don't die it's getting
night now
okay i should go back oh my god oh [\h__\h]
is this all over tonight
i'd be okay oh no it's still bright oh
full moon is okay
yeah yeah oh your sanity might go down
but
it won't be too bad oh thank god i'm too
far away from our base anyway
ah there is an ocean it's to the north
we'd have to i'd have to make a new base
up there
oh
i hear some weird music how many more
stones is that all the sun
and lots more stone who needs ouch i'm
going to fight them
oh wow thank you go abigail
i choose you abigail your turn
um
[Music]
oh you can make it like leave my ghost
alone nina
what don't kill my ghost
what there's a tentacle oh yeah i killed
the tentacles sorry ina i killed the
ancient ones
that wasn't me it was the ancient ones
i know it kind of hungry
i have no responsibility for what they
do so
when you make the meatballs does it make
one for everyone or is it just one
meatball
yeah it's just it's just one set of
meatballs it's like one dish
that's terrible i'm too good at this
that makes me sad we should have enough
for everyone
well there's some extra meatballs in the
chest so if people get hungry they got
food there yeah
okay well i'm gonna go catch some more
things and kill some more
things i'm building another baby what
the hell is that
can i help i don't know what to do yeah
you can you can come with me get up
you help me make decisions about the
boat okay
where are you just
[Music]
uh i found the ancient ones um oh oh
dear bye bye abigail
you're not gonna survive that or maybe
you are well let's try
hello i love you staring
i picked a fight that was too dangerous
to me
[Music]
i got an interesting one i see you i
think what the hell was all that
that's not a black rabbit oh
yeah oh nightmare it turned in the
nightmare
do you have any wood uh i have twigs
oh yeah okay i go get wood
i only need two so you just want your
trees
oh man is there any way for me to get
abigail my best friend
back what happened to her oh yeah she
got killed by the ancient ones
she walked it on on her own
how do we make this my sanity higher
because i'm rabbits now
you gotta sleep uh you can make a
sleeping bag with grass
i think you just like yes okay cool i'll
do that
thunder survival at the bottom
grass and a rope which you see refined
at the science machine oh okay
sure i can make a rope already i think
well i could
if you made one once then you can just
make my sanity
solos uh oh
pick a rope with grass
oh god oh god do the rabbits look normal
to you gouda
they look brown and cozy to me flower
cream
when your saturday when your sanity gets
slow it starts to change how the
monsters look
yeah oh yeah
ah very low sanity food
gets restored by sleeping and picking
flowers
okay oh good idea i want to pick some
flowers my crown's
gone too how do i make a flower
i'm so hungry like uh outside of the
game like actually hungry i'm so hungry
[Music]
go get some chicken and yeah after after
the stream
[Music]
i should probably chop some
sure sleeping bag i can make you one oh
thank you please
i'll make one now
okay i'll leave it at the base thank you
here you go thank you
the flowers are gone good night
good night
i can't type that in the chat where's my
chat
you can't type in i think it's why
oh there's actually a chat oh
what the commands there's like hey
cute did you forward slash dance
i thought it would chop faster if i
helped but i guess not i don't know what
it does maybe it does kind of seem like
it did
oh
i could really use a healing potion i
got like one heart left
hmm ah uh yeah you could oh but i have
that you had a spider gland
yeah i still have two spider glasses
left yeah and just two rocks
did you get ash again okay yeah you want
to share
that sleeping bag with me oh i would
love to but it's gone
it's one use i assume so yes i'll make
you another one
i'm making another one really watson i'm
sorry i want to
oh that's okay i have a bunch of grass
actually i need two more grass i have
some here
hold on here we go
[Music]
whoever picked up the bone who was the
one who picked up the bone
you know i i
don't know oh it's healing he just
appeared here he's cute weird
yes i'm gonna you can take him
yeah i already have i already have lobby
yeah do you need cash
that would be dope
you should salute me
wait i need to pick more flowers it's
turning night again
i wonder why the table hasn't tried to
uh f word with us yet
i think i think you have to like maybe
it's because kiara took the flowers she
has to be near it
you guys step on the hands when you see
them
wait what the hell beautiful cali looks
yeah
thank you nice night night johnny depp's
midnight
i mean did you give me something
what's happening
[Music]
go away monsters i'm scared
i gotta protect cali from the monsters
thank you i do appreciate it i
appreciate your sleeping child
i know i'm real hungry that's not great
you're losing uh
something callie oh no no no no no no
those are the chest meatballs in the
chest
uh i ate one so there might not be
anything there cooking
the table's moving table's moving oh
no i think i think your boy might die
it's my baby
edward scissorhands is coming to you go
away
you always want to eat the seeds okay i
have the ash that you
that you're talking about ass
yeah real hungry while sleeping a good
morning
did please say like it's like a
trade-off you get more brain juice but
less
hunger
yeah you can put them in the crock pot
uh you can put one stick frog leg and
then fillers like berries or carrots
kelly kelly you need to draw some wood
here
a bunch of frog legs at once i'm getting
more wood what
i fed you in the middle i fed you my
wife
you have been fed thank you for the
assistance
important assistance you're welcome
i do appreciate it how do you make an
alchemy engine
oh yeah uh we need gold to make the
little i have enough to make it but i
was just waiting to make it
up at the base up top because uh
i'm making a new base up there i'm gonna
make one right now if you want to follow
me
i'm gonna make it right now uh where are
you
north i'm going north follow the path
yeah
planting trees we did by the way
reach one and a half hours oh
yeah yeah
it's been fun it has been fun we should
do it again sometimes yeah one
part two one part two is it if we leave
the server is it gonna stay like that
uh it pauses as news i shut it down so
as soon as i exit the game everything
will be
uh exactly as we left it so we can go
back to that stage that's awesome
yeah but i actually don't remember it
should be
fine maybe
she'll be fine i'd better stay like that
also i want my ghost back
today i'm not gonna attend go with this
frog today
dance with me frog legs save it for next
time
yeah all right sounds good good one
smells gross
i wonder what our death counter was at
oh boy
i survived 12 days i don't know man
i survived 12 days what about you girls
i think you're probably the same well
yeah i
oh 13. oh i died at the start we all
died to start
yeah yeah we all did huh another extra
time
well we really didn't do a bad job i
mean
i would think i would have thought i
would have done a much worse job but i
survived long enough
yeah oh and by the way uh if you guys
ever want to stream this game alone
there's like single player two
it's just called don't starve and
there's like a lot more content in it
and there's like a different island and
different biomes you can explore
cool very art style this game too in the
field
it's very nice i'll definitely do that
sounds good well thanks for tuning in
everyone thanks for coming to hang out
with us as we
tried not to starve together yeah thank
you for watching
thank you thank you everyone
everyone see you again
goodbye this weekend
[Music]
you