[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
I was looking for that
there we go
hi
I'm not sleepy
I mean I might get sleepy later but no
I went
outside
nice weather really good weather hi
papaya
I'm not tired you sound tired
the voice is in my head are you and I
hear you and you sound tired
I mean I didn't go outside for the
purpose of going outside but I
purposefully chose walking overtaking
public transport or a taxi
to get to
a place that sells
pet stuff
um
it was a long walk okay
scenic route it wasn't very scenic but
well it's nice weather it was nice I
mean yeah
in the end it wouldn't have made much
difference time wise
so I was like I guess I'll walk
um
and I realized I need to go to the pet
store more often to buy pet food
because people who go to the pet store
with their pets well mainly I mean
pretty much 100 dogs no one brings their
cats but people bring their dogs there
so that they choose oh which toy do you
want
yeah I should go there more often there
was like a little cute puppy and I I
didn't ask if I could pet but I I asked
about about the puppy I didn't feel like
annoying them about petting the puppy
yet
but in the future I could do that
cute puppy
yeah no katos unfortunately
um yeah I bought some I had to buy some
buy some Kibbles and then I bought some
wet food for smoothie
and I bought
some liquid
licky snacks
um because like Kibbles recently in the
supermarket doesn't sell the one I need
or want I mean I don't know I don't I
don't go for like one very specific one
but the ones they have at supermarkets
are often just uh you know those like
you I think you guys have it overseas
too the whiskers one for example and
like I've heard I don't really know but
I've heard that a lot of those that they
have at the supermarket they're kind of
like unhealthy for the cats
um
no they're not really fancy Virgo
yeah it's kind of I think a lot of them
have if I understand correctly wheat in
it and that is not good or green grain
free
grain of wheat or something like that
um yeah and I I heard before that it's
not healthy so a lot of those like
mainstream pet foods have it ironically
why do the mainstream ones have it the
thing that is not healthy for them
that's weird
hmm
the good stuff is insanely expensive it
is it for one two kilogram bag
of Kibbles
it was 25 bucks and then I bought like
what 15 little uh uh uh
uh 15 uh
around 15 I didn't count them
um of the wet food packages like normal
size
I think 85 gram per package
and one
small package of liquid snacks I came up
to a total of 50 Euro
50 Euro
for
the most of it was made up of the wet
food uh and the
and the cables
well
that's expensive
just because I've uh
just bought like a I mean it's not even
like a I don't know if it's a fancy
brand
but the cables um are some that uh like
the Vets always recommend the Royal
Canin I think they have it overseas too
Royal Canin cunning
oh I have super chats off oh it's fine
should I turn it on yeah you have it
overseas too yeah that one is uh often
uh recommended by that
um
and mine also recommended it
K9 K9 K9
no I haven't been super transfer the cat
food I'm just saying that it's like more
expensive but for the sake of the health
I guess like I I I can afford it so I'll
do it for my cats but if I didn't have
this job then it would be super
expensive to keep up a healthy lifestyle
for my cats man but even with the
healthy food stuff that I bought before
like it's from the same brand I've
noticed before that my cats you know
like before when I went to the vet uh
because I thought my cats were having
like an allergic reaction or something
like that
my vet made me buy their stock of K9
Royal Canin food
uh for like sensitive cats Etc
and I bought it from them and they said
you have to switch to this for now and I
uh gave it to them for a while but
didn't it didn't improve anything so
yeah even to this day I don't know
like what's the problem
but I still continue to try to give them
the
the cables for the sensitive tell me see
anyway so uh you see uh wait why is it
[Music]
I am wearing
of course
oh
[Music]
from Blue the accessories but I made
myself some fluffy shoulder pads
so I look even more like like a panette
um
I mean you know they look better when
they're like kind of cut off here
because otherwise you know they they go
into the booby
penetrification I wish I knew how to
make my eyes yellow and OBS but I feel
like if I make my eyes yellow then a lot
of my hair would also become yellow
because there's some purple in my hair
too
I don't know
so edgy though look at me being so edgy
waiting for the screenshot oh wait hi
wait
well that's not really in character it
should be more like this
there you go
okay so we're gonna play Fire Emblem
today
[Music]
it's been a while uh
but we have to get back into it and
oh wait oh no it's okay uh since uh last
time I played it on stream I got two
two more bracelets
um
so yeah I'm drinking a Coca-Cola
not sponsored
okay let me sorry I'm I'm chilling I'm
taking my time I know I'm sorry
it's been 20 minutes
I'm just taking my time taking it easy
Pepsi they really don't sell much Pepsi
here
okay let me
do come on what did I change
something with my game capture
please
please capture the game
what
um
[Music]
he's dead
why are you dead
wait let me restart the game capture
program
I don't trust it
it's not me it's you
microphone eh
microphone cracking
one second I don't have my headphones on
sounds normal what are you talking about
want it huh
huh
what
that's weird
it doesn't crackle now does the crackle
now test this
yeah if I guess the game capture card
because I sound absolutely normal
[Music]
static what the
what there is normal here
I wonder why
that's what this game capture card
got it
oh
oh it's back
what well now I don't
huh what did I change
ah
how about now
what
ah hello
sweet how about now
still cracking eyes gone oh
interesting I switched to a different
USB slot
for my capture card
Nani
oh
ah and now my capture card works
that was just around
oh
a space like must be killed on y'all
genius
no I don't think the USB port is bad is
that completely but I think it might
just have some issues
yeah
my turn no no I'm just I just always
leave the games open eh
no no no
we don't need to update
before update
greetings panetto hello it's panetti wow
yeah they don't take long but do you
hear
do you hear the people people
did you save in Metro I'm sure I did
you heard okay
ah
no don't get tired drink the Coca-Cola
music
Fire Emblem
and it was crackling for me but wait I
fixed it I probably fixed it I know how
to fix that I should
no
okay
doesn't even
the drift doll
[Laughter]
so you'll see now
um I have
tried my best off screen to make some
progress to save us some time
um
I mean progress well progress as in
I just oh this is where I stopped
and where am I ah
yeah I just I did some uh ring thingies
uh here look
I
or a day
I think she irika is new
and
no
wait here let's just look here
these are the ones I have now ah soaring
wait I did three I might I may have done
three
did I do free
did I not do irika on stream
I did Veronica Soren and irika
are you free
ah no I have guessed from the start okay
never mind then I did
um
Soren and Veronica Veronica was really
easy Soren was really difficult and
apparently I forgot to do a tweet
okay
gozaimasu
oh I want to keep that open
[Music]
we missed Veronica
I mean I don't think you really missed
much
no I'm not gonna do a parallelog today
we're gonna do story
we have to
started already
long time ago
you're late
besides off
more
[Music]
okay
save story till after final DLC
eh no
yeah
put her on the mage
okay I shall
gladly follow your advice
wait so who are my main just
for tencia
and Ivy ivy currently has laid for
whatever reason don't even ask me all
right I'll give her Veronica Veronica
I'll help
help
help so nice let her cook yeah she's
cooking
then you can have life leave it to me
live for Life yo
oh yeah
do I have one left over
I have sore and leftover do you want to
have Sauron
wait sorry isn't he kind of like magical
too he's also magical
gastonius thank you I was proud too of
you guys
so um
soaring on the Mage ivy on Sauron
can I also put
these together
[Music]
you can do this too right
sign on Celine is very fun too hmm
[Music]
yo
yo can have
hmm
[Music]
biles I guess also I've been trying to
get everyone Cantor
uh some of them have it so look look how
I was so
it ain't
all right I'll turn Super Chats on
because you guys want it I can't tell
but then
superchata
on
okay
yeah productive so uh kiwawa has cancer
Ivy has counterpanet has cancer uh
Celine has cancer hortensia's Canter
alker says Cantor Goldberg doesn't no no
she does yeah
doesn't have cancer yet
has cancer Chloe needs Canter
Tamara has cancer and forgot it doesn't
okay so we want counter for fogado Chloe
and kagetsu maybe
[Music]
but I basically I mean it's not like I
you know did some training with them
which I just did the the speed
the Speedy way of giving them cancer
just using my
using my SP I guess I mean the what what
[Music]
the arena
hmm
yes
so I think right now we can do it too
[Music]
uh emblem
it was so confusing though because
before one paralog I did all of these
that you just saw right I did all those
characters Facebook and then I went into
the paralog and I'm like yeah why why no
one can actually use it why is no one
cantering and then I was reminded
that you have to after getting an
encounter
go out of your way to uh yeah
set it as their skill that is so
annoying
you guys
it's so annoying so I did a whole
paralog without cancer even though I
just taught everyone Cantor
okay so I want to do Chloe for sure
anyway she already
they're already at five well then she
should be able to have cancer learn
cancer
okay
I'm Fogata psalm's very own Prince but
the last parallel that I did I had to do
with me
I have I have
um counter on everybody
um
I'm about to throw an epic Feast nothing
stuff he just said abs and good friends
you in cigarette thank you forgoto I
would be happy to attend I am eager to
socialize with my compatriots you sound
so eager
hmm
[Music]
momentum they learn momentum
he got I think he got blasted though
destroyed
okay who else
I know it I can see it say good five
five five
five one
we have plenty of bond fragments so
Bond fragments are not the problem
I am cigarette
what are the other points called
as pieces
it was fun was it not
incredible
[Music]
cigarette I trust you are well
it is important to me that all my
friends are healthy and happy I am quite
well but thank you for the concern
I intend to Hope fast until this war is
won
[Music]
I get to Boston
okay
and one more maybe
[Music]
huh
well I mean up until here everybody has
it and those are like the main units I
wait I mean
Jade I don't want to give up on you yet
so I shall teach you
meditation complete
I still I still love Jade you think to
do or me have you seen the DLC yet I
don't know
I played some on the DLC parallel
[Music]
I might have to write a book about this
that was riveting close close
the Miss was important from sigurd I
swear to approve my honor that you call
secret when you need an iron wall I will
be there thank you Jade let us join
together to protect our allies in the
fashion of true nights
it was nice comeback yeah she fought so
well
[Music]
damn
okay so then we inherit skills right
does not have
enough oh wait a second no no no no no
[Music]
okay but he still doesn't have enough
points
uh
uh uh Chloe also not enough points
that's why I didn't give her cancer yet
fogado does have enough points nice
oh yeah inherit and there's three steps
first you have to get to the level five
then you have to inherit it and then you
have to equip it are you freaking
kidding me
she's almost there
um
[Music]
and then equip the skill in the
inventory as always I just do not
understand
uh wait there wasn't was it no wait who
what
who
forgotten
[Music]
oh yeah
equipped equipped yeah
and clip the clip to grab the clip okay
okay okay so that's something I was
doing
stupid system
you can also cook skills from the
inherit screen oh
oh okay
hmm
thank you for the membership
[Music]
all right
let me make the music a little bit more
quiet in my ear
[Music]
oh wait it doesn't even change on your
side if you guys feel like it's too loud
or too quiet let me know
motion thank you oh
thank you soon guys
main story time that's right I feel like
I should just get straight into it but
let me check if I did stuff like the the
foof
oh they're okay
okay okay
nice
okay well we're happy
thank you for the membership
[Music]
okay and you cook for me
no okay let's see
um
[Music]
it doesn't matter let's just do them
that's all you're gonna put on the plate
foreign
the very top thing is the thing that
she's good at right to cook
I want the Dome bread
oh wait Tamara doesn't even like it
oh wait it's the other way that we're
around
is this what they both like no and what
they both like and what the cook is good
at maybe
all the sparkly ones is what the cook is
good at I assume
oh
let's make Berry sauce panna cotta
because this one gives free stats up
are there stats up for
only Tameron fogado or for everybody by
the way
[Music]
last time I cooked off screen
that she for the first time ever the
cook failed so badly that everybody got
minus stats like five or four minor
stats
I was like what the and I can't get
rid of this until like the next battle
what Tamara forgotten ah okay
so three of us had minus one stats on
almost everything
because
unbelievable
of course never cook again an honor to
make this whoever that was I forgot who
it was what is the dragon's favorite
food I'm dying to know probably the
leftover bent in my thoughts as I
prepared this Divine one yeah I could
get used to this flavor
she's so cute yeah I like it it's tasty
they're all so cute
oh nice so if male also gained deathless
too oh good that we haven't forgotten
dance of sweets
good B is rare I rarely get B why am I
saving
um
[Music]
you look kind of down yeah well
I think I owe you an apology what
happened
you're the one who stole my rib tips wow
I was saving those friends for late
night snap what I would never do that
ribs I know how much you love your
midnight wait a second what's this I
knew it business you don't trust your
own brother
[Laughter]
the laughing I get cranky when I wake up
on it Face animation is so deadly what
was that about an apology
I was thinking about what you said how I
wasn't around much in the castle I've
always felt that because our people are
free Spirits they deserve a
free-spirited Prince but now I realize
that it got in the way of our city time
doesn't tell the whole story you leave
the castle to get a lay of the land
make it easier to plan for a crisis
right so that if the worst happens
you'll be ready to advise me
of course you know well yeah we are
sibbies aren't we I know everything
that's going on in that cute little head
of yours I do appreciate all you do for
me as far as little brothers go have
boys I'd say I lucked out my family
we watch out for each other
[Music]
sometimes I don't want you to watch out
for me I just
like to hang out with me
you know
like right now
this is perfect
so territory oh my God
very sweet I like both of the voice
actors too alright so we did that
um
I don't know I feel like we could just
go
should I just go
probably have plenty Adams probably
let's check this one did I do this
allies to enjoy
should we get the subies up to a
[Music]
let's do it I'll wait if I do this
does it do all of them at the same time
because sometimes when I do like one and
then I switch the next one it says I
can't do it anymore I'm like what
what's going on
[Music]
it seems like it only did that one okay
to result
okay
and this one
there you go I did all three of them
[Music]
explain what kfp meant to my dad and I
made him even more confused than before
he asked what it was did I do good boss
well it is neat to know right
but
tried
let's get up to B
Pinette
please explain yourself
I promised we were going somewhere
special well here it is when I said that
I'd like for us to be friends
I did not realize that would entail
visits to ancient
decayed
ruins
precisely doesn't it make your heart
Quicken excessively so I'm afraid I feel
as if a vengeful ghost could steal upon
us at any moment
I know it is ever so Charming you find
it Charming wait I like this idea of
ghosts Charming why of course I simply
adore them I suppose I ought to thank
you this place is special to you
for that reason I appreciate your
sharing it with me unfortunately
people have a wide variety of tastes a
oh dear you are not by any chance afraid
of ghosts are you oh yeah I don't
believe in ghosts think of my composure
staying on the wall like a human
silhouette the hand prints on the
Windows oh the stale air well the
hamstrings that scary force of will that
I remain here are conscious
by one last thread of decorum The Pride
I take in my Royal office that threat is
about to snap yes it will snap any
moment now even a princess is only Human
After All ah so
with that I'm getting
it Princess Ivy slow down
that's all interaction I enjoyed for
once nice
foreign
like a lot of them are you know a little
bit
cringe may I say
um
but I like this one
good stuff
for once it was not about tea yeah
thank God
okay let me just collect those fruits
over there and then we'll go to main
story finally uh
I thought it was open
close that up
26 damn guys like the numbers on those
memberships are really going getting
crazy nowadays
those are like some big ass numbers
what you did
remember
[Music]
where is this thing oh yeah
29 oh my God
yo
oh 20 so many 29s
but damn anything above 20 is like it
sounds crazy so many months you guys
continue to support me thank you thank
you thank you
at 29 seems to be the absolute maximum
now
I joined pretty late what do you mean
pretty late
thank you ah thank you
your fault for keeping being good thank
you
[Music]
Sally my streak was broken and if you
like stop being a member for like a
month or two and you go back into it
does it start from one again
it doesn't right does it not just
continue but well then you don't
okay
keeps you strict but well then yeah you
just missed two months and you set back
I suppose at least yeah at least it um
keeps the progress that's nice
thank you thank you everybody thank you
okay
I want some main story please
[Music]
so let's depart
to world map
nice here thank you
where are we going next
to some ships what
is that the main story
[Music]
vote vote chapter
can we just skip that
since when do we have a boat whose boat
are we using
I'm gonna attack the
uh where where Vale and so are
and I will stand by the title
they'll basically propose to me because
she gave me one ring I didn't even
realize it last time I'm such a dense
protagonist
I'm so sorry bail I'm coming now to
accept your proposal let's go
I'm so sorry man
classic I'm always so dense you guys are
right I accept it now
the cold voyage
chapter 18.
fail gave the Ring of the Holy Night one
second Divine Dragon sombron looks like
I mean I haven't played much of those
games but it looks like he could show up
in one of those games like I don't know
Persona or something no maybe not
Persona I feel like that what's that one
game I played uh sponsored
that is similar to Persona in some way
yeah
yeah yeah
am I right with my feeling he seems like
it could be from that game
[Music]
I see it
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
thank you okay
apologies my Lord
ring of azure twins lost as well
twice my four hounds failed me you do
understand the gravity of all this
and fail
still in a deep Slumber no matter how
much I amplify her draconic impulses she
won't awaken she refuses her true nature
in that case take this honey
oh
what is it and an enchanted helmet
it will strengthen the spell you catch a
crown
to him my power with you you're gonna
brainwasher correct what is what is
wrong with failure
fails oh no
Thief use it when a time is right of
course as you will it
ah there is
that's really cruel I would like to
discuss
what
Pardon Me Lord Sombra but
lady Vale is your only child correct my
only living child yes that is correct
um
who's the mommy and when I'm like no in
terms of like do they conceive children
the same like make a birth the same way
these demons or do they just like plop
plop up by summoning a child or how does
it work
okay I wanna know
of course I was speaking from fear not
fact I'm curious why I ask such a thing
I want to understand
biology depicts is alive
I thought it best to raise with you
she spoke of an Unbroken drakkenstone
[Music]
but she must be mistaken
we both know the truth your children
were killed in the war a thousand years
ago all but Veil
a thousand years ago the one who stood
Above the Rest with hair and eyes like
fire what was the name again
something like
Sofia my Lord I do not remember all my
children's name
killed myself
yes what moments later I was imprisoned
collect the body
I
I did not no no
what I said
there is no and if you find that
offspring
bring me a corpse this time
yes Lord Sombra yummy as you wish
[Music]
thanks for arranging the ship for us
Alfred
laughs it's like my mother not me
when I said we were headed to illusia
she got one of the fleet's finest lined
up thank you Mommy sorry Mommy the
capital
well enough there haven't been any
attacks since we left for brodia
what a relief I told Mother what the
other side's been up to how they're
after Sovereign blood
she was shocked of course to hear about
King morion and King Hyacinth
understandably so that's for the
destruction of Flora Port the royal
family will spare no expense on aid
though it may be years before the
harbors returned to its original Beauty
we must feet the Federal
so that such Horrors never happen again
what's our plan
we head straight for illusia Castle
first we should
we should Rings or no rings if we don't
know what we're up against we could lose
everything besides
there's something I need to find out and
what's that weathervale is all right
from our Vantage the hounds certainly
didn't seem pleased they may attempt to
erase her personality
if anyone can do it that woman can how
do you know no Vale killed my mother
nothing we've learned changes that but I
can't help but worry about her
I hope she's not hurt yes I suppose
she's
my future wife to give us the ring or it
was all an act and she's just gaining
our trust established in the back again
that's worth considering
don't know enough to rule anything out
want to trust her Divine One excuse me
two ships flying illusion colors
approach from ahead
any sign of the hounds none however it
appears the enemy intends to attack us
and we've got no choice but to fight
them on the water
prepare for battle everyone she means
there's like
more important looking characters
battle is inevitable yeah okay so they
don't have them so only like normal NPCs
oh wait oh interesting map
[Music]
uh ships are connected
I like how the ships use
even though they're from different
countries
they've been made exactly the same way
they use the same planks
the same size of planks
same shape same pattern
this is just a popular at this time
even the the fencing and oh yeah it all
looks the same
so I'm just roasting them
efficient design
hey also why do these look bigger on the
side because ours look bigger on the map
only we're the small ones what the hell
bamboozle
okay
so what there must be at least one
special character here right no they got
a bump
Soldier but the rest is just normal NPCs
no double HP bars
no
top Riders the boss boss
oh
oh who are you
I guess okay one age people are like I
guess two
[Music]
how should we do this should we send
everyone on the on the left chip first I
guess so
no way but we have so many
[Music]
Oh chapter three plus so I don't even
remember
there's one more but you can recruit him
what
not like I want to
Elders illusion soldiers
old man and white
ah
Linden oh yeah he looks like a good guy
but also like
could also be very evil
sometimes the really good looking ones
are really evil
[Music]
um
well I don't really feel like I need
another unit obviously I already have an
Overlord load of units
unless he's like really really good at
something but
might just recruit but wait so if ivy
goes up to him
or Hortensia
do we not have to fight with him use it
to record and kill okay okay
but I feel like maybe first I'll send
everyone to the left because this is
weird to split
because then the left group will take so
long to catch up
is it weird if I send everyone to the
left first
[Music]
um
yeah do it
okay
not weird snowboard safe yeah
send the flying ones over there
oh we have a lot of units this time damn
nice too
I don't even know if I want to change
anything here
I might keep it this way
we're bringing everyone but fogado
oh man yeah that's fine though
Chloe needs some SP
a so that's good I think kagetsu needs
some SP too
okay SP do you get SP bunny just
participating in the battle or by
killing people by leveling well how do
you understand
there's Flyers maybe one no I do have
all Chris
by battling okay
but maybe I'll switch out to Rosado
that's fine
now
okay
through EXP
okay Coolio
well done
I'm happy with that oh bingo
although let me check the inventory if
everybody has what they need that's
vulnerable you know some sticks
um elixir
[Music]
to
a lot of bows I was switching around
some weapons too off screen
just so everybody has some variety
okay it looks fine I don't think
[Music]
other steps
I don't know if I have better stuff
[Music]
okay maybe we don't need a freeze
she has a physic okay
[Music]
my best rescue again
obstruct fracture
I don't know I don't really have
anything much better but I can give her
another visit or I'll give her
is this one at a distance or only for
next to you probably only for next year
maybe I'll give it a treat
and then
oh she got The Mending one
she got Mendes I mean that's fine
RNG one what
Franklin ah okay
I thought RNG when you guys wrote it
like that
does RNG always stand for range because
what about like the gacha RNG no no not
bad but like I hear RNG used in other
ways
has a different meaning then right
what's it stand for ah random number
generator there we go that makes more
sense
good news is the ship's got flame
cannons that'll set fires and slow down
the enemy oh wouldn't want our allies to
get caught in The Blaze
[Music]
you can just blame by placing a unit on
it and selecting fire any unit
you use the cannon once
flame cannons blast a wide area around
the impact Point instead of the terrain
of the fire
forever
be aware that the blast cannot reduce
the false HP below one it can hit your
allies too so be careful
maybe just in the beginning and then
when I go back my country has become
something unrecognizable Illusions Army
serve illusion no longer but the hounds
is this truly what I meant to do there
you see him
having a little bit of a conflict within
himself
familiar boys
um
all right I feel bad for him I feel like
he wants to be on our side so I will of
course
of course I will help him out with that
yes
[Music]
here of course where else
foreign
stay only for like one or one turn right
[Music]
and then you go here thank you Canter
thank you ready for me
fire in the hole
don't kill him let Ivy do the talk yeah
that's fine
all right
come at me
yes try me
[Music]
oh I can do a dragon yeah I got corn on
kakitzu right now
been using dragonvane a lot recently
um
but at one
I want to go here now and do a dragon
vein
[Music]
um everybody who comes into that area
afterwards will still be affected by
that uh terrain effect right
not just the ones that are already there
right
[Music]
it's okay
and I think I'll
um
ready for anything oh let me see I mean
I might just put them behind them
well that doesn't do
far
[Music]
all right
range sucks
[Music]
looks risky
yeah what do you mean nothing's risky
all is good
oh wait oh yeah right hers is a stone
pillar step plus free rest plus free
I forgot
boy or girl
[Music]
a guy okay
okay
[Music]
I can handle it
maybe not go here to Archer
foreign
[Music]
I don't care I'm bringing everyone over
there
I'll try
ready and able except for the flight
the Flies can chill
[Music]
well Rosalia Rosado is a little confused
of course
[Music]
no
no I really can't do much in this turn
huh say the word
oh
all right let's see what happens
here we go oh
that hurt
that also hurt
I know
oh
this
nice
I mean okay he got a 20 20 but 20 20 20
22 chance but he also got 90 chance to
hit what the
oh wait there they're coming from the
right side
[Music]
I'm just I'm just treasure and where the
are you gonna go with the treasure
you're on a boat oh you wanna have
gotten a small boat there hmm
I see okay okay you try go ahead and try
yes your tank stuff crit
so well I'm so proud
all right it's good that you stayed back
here
[Music]
boom
yeah you've got no chance buddy
absolutely no chance
before
[Music]
like I didn't because that looks so cool
yeah
larger incoming
yummy I should have left some people in
the middle boat
[Music]
well I mean
this will happen before they move it
will give them damage before they move
right
[Music]
oh yeah okay
let's see
I'm sweating
thank you for that info you're making
some of my viewers
nervous
by sharing that
[Music]
there's some Mages over there that's not
good for gold Mary is it
[Music]
might go back after
killing this or should I wait
I don't know I'll do it
[Music]
perfection
so by the way
I think I got some tangents
Georgie was so nice to write them down
for me
so let me share
[Music]
first of all I guess the easy one to
talk about did you guys watch the Holo
spy thing
did you watch it
I never actually ended up watching the
final product
yeah you did yeah it was cool really it
was fun really
yeah I think a lot of credit goes to the
editing probably I don't know didn't see
it but I would assume so because
recording that was bam
uh very tedious and uh we had to like
make Cuts so many times
because like I don't know it was kind of
like badly
organized no not really organized but
badly planned or badly I don't know
um
I think we all didn't know what was
going on
[Music]
well most of us didn't know what was
going on all the time so in between we
would like I have to stop and like try
to understand Victory this month what's
happening
and and yeah it was uh yeah also like
while we were doing it suddenly
yeah they would tell us sorry we're
completely cutting this out now
[Music]
to one of the free rounds we're cutting
completely because we're already in the
recording way way over time so this is
not working and yeah I think there was
this like one game
um
where they only ended up cutting it
cutting in one round but or or they cut
the game no they cut the game completely
I think even
which I found kind of sad because
um
the members were trying to guess some
things about me and it would have been
funny because nobody guessed anything
right at all
[Music]
uh no trust me you do not want to see
the full cut
hmm
[Music]
you do not want to see the full cut also
the thing is like I think the recording
for this was at like
[Music]
one or two am my time
and then somebody was late for an hour
so it started at 2 am my time
and then the whole recording because
everybody was confused took way longer
than it needed to be
so I ended at like four or five am
I think I like I even told you guys
about this like on Twitter or in a
pre-chat or someone's like it just ended
work now going to bed now
um
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah that it was quite a long
time ago yeah now you know what I'm
talking about
um
so exhausting and the harsh yeah
but as long as the end product doesn't
come across like that I'm happy
but because of these memories I I could
not get myself to watch the
um final version
I think all of us were suffering after
we were done recording I thought you
know I I had to share like some feedback
about what just happened and I wasn't
the only one a lot of members were like
yeah this didn't go so well
the end was muted what do you mean the
end was muted
the ending knew that
they left the end muted
what
up
[Music]
what
for how long
[Music]
completely muted or just like
voices muted but there was bgm or so 40
seconds to a minute that just didn't
have sound at the end was it an
important part
Connie was talking and there was no
sound
oh
completely silenced okay well that was
probably like accidental
hmm
[Music]
if it was just the ending then whatever
I guess
eh
well yeah anyway so that was a really
painful experience
[Laughter]
it was just uh it didn't go so well yeah
um but I don't know I I just wanted to
know if you guys enjoyed it
as long as you guys enjoyed it all is
good in the neighborhood
I had fun Parts but it was a mess oh oh
was that noticeable
it was fun it was fun really
like your reactions oh that was so funny
the hey I wonder how many rounds they
kept in because I think they were like
three or four rounds in total
that no wait no everybody had to
do I think every but every group had to
do two
lyric rounds
maybe they kept it all in because
otherwise it doesn't make any sense in
terms of points that was a really
difficult game damn but it's funny it's
a funny game I feel like
it could be reused the idea I like it
you guys had to guess song using lyrics
trans was it members I think it was wait
no no no no okay no that's what you mean
the other I thought I thought the the
game with the Emojis was fun too
it was stressful though because uh we
were typing in a Discord
and
you know there's a million emojis on
phone or Discord wherever you're looking
how to find the one you really want
really quickly man gotta type it in
I don't know how to do it
um
[Music]
should I stand here
it's got like a blaster if she stands
here isn't she
I don't know
maybe someone can go over there and use
it
there's a search for yeah yeah I was I
don't know I think I was maybe trying to
use it it was too late or so I don't
know yeah
[Music]
sorry I'm like so slow because of the
tangent but also I don't know what to do
don't fear for me
I would does he have a hand ax I wonder
wind
winds so strong
but still no kill
s
when did I record that was that like in
probably
[Music]
was it in the two-week break or I was
definitely in Austria so it was even two
weeks non-japan time or it was when
before
before I got sick in December
2019 on it
[Music]
like how you look like peanut thank you
probably before yeah it feels like it
was a really long time ago
is there a flying one coming from there
no not yet there's a flying one over
there but I don't think I can
free Channel
A Bad Case let me go here
just shoot you down and then go away
we met
forever ago
[Music]
where do we go with him
um stay here
and then healing
she has a physic let's heal
you're too kind
the Archer and the wyvern might kill
Chloe
ah
um
you're right
a bit
[Music]
that is not so good but we'll even
survive without her but let's see we
could can we maybe take someone down
here
not quite but wouldn't he die from the
fire before he gets to move
nah he won't because I live at One HP
never mind don't even don't you don't
even have to tap it in chat
but
hmm
I mean I might as well
[Music]
I will try to read that eventually
I can't go away that much
well then they'll have a choice
they'll have a choice to make which one
they want to try to take down
foreign
[Music]
eventually
five ounces of water
hold nothing back
[Music]
can't be very useful
Maybe
[Music]
what can corn do ah the flood
that's that goes in a line right
well it does like no damage
[Music]
so useless right now at least
an armor Slayer would be good
[Music]
it keeps them from moving
time
I guess
I don't know what else to do
[Music]
although might even be able to
get one of them
yeah I might really close
wait
we might we could kill him yeah yeah we
can we can
which means Maybe
really shouldn't have done what I just
did what about hand eggs
Revenge
or killer ax
Killer X even a higher crit we could get
a crit come on
[Music]
quickly now hi Obama
I'm sorry in the first hit
what am I doing
[Music]
I I could engage
and try to kill him but then damn that
would have been such a waste
oh no don't worry it doesn't kill at all
atrocity goes
quite hard
not
[Music]
maybe I'll do an atrocity
maybe I'll get a crick
[Music]
this came you always great on the second
hit when it doesn't matter
no when it does matter that's when you
get the crit on the second hit
yay
sorry so far I'm not playing very good
today
and I might rewind let's see yeah bye
yeah
speed wing
oh missed
yeah back in the day we couldn't pin
things I like that we can do that oh
[Music]
I expected that very good very good all
right I'm scared about this he only got
one XP no way
[Music]
oh man
that is such a stupid exchange no
let's put on it what does it do
goodbye
[Music]
I don't like that but
I think I'll keep it because I think
losing one unit is totally fine on this
map oh my god dude
nice nice the whole because she
used the the magic lens didn't she
[Music]
oh yeah no Veronica
no Linda's
gonna supportencia too right
[Music]
and whenever her character you guys said
okay Wawa Maybe
hmm
well then
[Music]
there's no more archers left
first of all
you little I swear
[Music]
it was so excited to see Veronica don't
worry
we have plenty of chances today and I
shall use Hortensia for healing again I
suppose
[Music]
music
or men someone
[Music]
was there something that increased her
range for mending like some skill or so
that she has
how come she can do that
if I was uh okay her presence
I don't know what to feel I want to heal
everybody
[Music]
then
we're taking so much collateral damage
emotional damage you know what I've been
really into these days and I didn't want
to say it
for some reason I felt like I don't know
I didn't want to sing it because bana is
into it too
but I've been watching so many
neurosama videos
I'm so
enticed Charmed Enchanted
yeah yeah and I'm getting so many
recommendations too it makes me so happy
I want to ask for a collab
yeah I don't know I know it makes no
sense lunchbox I know but I felt like I
don't know
who okay do some people really not know
it's so somebody made an AI YouTuber
who is like just so witty and funny it's
a cute little bird
[Music]
with an avatar that reminds me of some
anime uh up
I'm not sure was it or I'm not sure
where the art style is from
yeah and I also really like the
interactions between Beetle and
neurosama
no it's not lucky star no no no no no no
it's so funny
and then I saw you know I saw a lot of
their interactions one-on-one but I also
saw like a newer summer doing a collab
with like 10 different YouTubers who are
trying to impress numerousama and
neurosome was just so Savage
you can't win
if you managed to win over this AI
beetuber than them I know how the
you do it yeah the date show
[Music]
I kind of want to ask for collab
but I mean you know people always say
that I get along with everybody and
chihuahua in control and so on but this
is an AI a reckless Ai and literally I
can't
um
do much here I'm not I can't influence
it if it goes bad then it goes bad and
then I can't do anything about it
foreign
[Music]
the ultimate test
would be so funny she wants to collab
with fauna what do you mean the AI wants
to collab with fauna
[Music]
if I
if I'm worthy
[Music]
shall I go
it's just so witty
she mentioned she mentions fun all that
hey I please recognize me too
hey
[Music]
uh
suppose I did it right notice me a i
Senpai what do you mean Senpai that
sounds like I am AI too I'm not AI I'm
here I'm real but nowhere Sama is also
real
she's real in my heart
[Music]
yeah yeah if there's feminine chats then
the AI picks it up right yeah so that's
why some things she says are really
weird
some things are
really questionable too
and maybe
would not be accepted by a cover to be
on a Chihuahua stream
be careful
I think I should do another here but
damn I'm getting correct
she gets so unhinged
[Music]
now think about it I've just been so
much into these videos Man
it was so funny so entertaining
genius
like even if the if she says something
wrong you literally like you can't like
be mad or cancel her because I mean
it's not her fault
so she can never do wrong gets away with
everything
there's this uh veto what's her name
Annie
who seems to be drawing her new
uh design
I saw something like that yeah
looks good looks really cute so far I
started in like some YouTube short clip
I really like her art style too
he would
[Music]
yeah
cannot be blamed for any slip-ups
as we like to say
wait was there really no better than the
weapon for me right now did I even check
I'm so distracted
[Music]
foreign
like this thing doesn't even matter at
this point I'll just stand here so that
nobody else can take it
um
[Music]
you can pull Chloe back oh yeah I
probably will
but they might still follow me
let's have some fun nice quick where we
don't need it let's go
anyway I don't really
have a Twitch account I don't really go
on Twitch so I'm just relying on the
stuff that goes up on YouTube but it's
so fun it's so cute I like it
[Music]
I'm getting she could also kill this
dude though
possibly
not worth the risk Maybe
[Music]
I said
but then he'll go on the bomb
[Music]
I'll kill and then I'll try to run
and then I'll probably regretty
spaghetti
I know no I don't know if he wanted to
Twitch uh to stream on Twitch then yeah
you can make an account but I never want
to so I didn't get one
[Music]
oh wait not worth it
oh no no no no no no no
[Music]
right side looking bad
Oh I thought it's okay
[Music]
I don't have a
ornery but in that case I shall use my
staff to do something good
yeah what good fortune
oh a little attack from range
[Music]
heel or kill this dude I think we should
kill him
[Music]
need help
she got brain surgery and she can't say
anything nearby anymore really
oh no her charms well I mean not to what
extent
they must still keep her
[Music]
somewhat's original right
oh please no more dabs please
[Music]
okay okay we're good we're good our
um engagement made us take less damage I
think
huh
that was the Lance guy that was standing
in the front still right
[Music]
yeah
unacceptable
what happens if I take him down and then
run away
like I was considering to
not the sisters
maybe I'll
um
go until here when we think
[Music]
but I don't think tanette can take him
down okay oh she can
not that it's necessary though
unless I mean
[Music]
Chloe has cancer too right
bye now
is that yellow boot icon Canton
on the bottom
wait does she is she the only one who
doesn't have cancer
and then
[Music]
okay
then I think I'll kill him with panette
and then run away
and then
I could heal panette back up with Celine
or I could kill the other mob
thank you
[Music]
I have to because otherwise he'll attack
Hortensia and she'll die and we'll just
have the whole thing over again
over and over and over again
I'm sorry you had to see that
[Music]
fix up damage when she engages now we're
fine I think she'll be fine we'll see
will she be fine
ah
sword is uh effective but I mean I mean
she a physical man
okay
[Music]
I shall do this they'll figure out how
to deal with that
uh still alive
[Music]
I'll figure it out
and I guess we'll just stay here should
I
stand here
[Music]
is that dangerous
no
[Music]
four hounds are good and somebody hates
TV
what
that's what the DLC is about
the one I kept alive didn't do any
trouble
I'll see
I let my guard down
oh
I guess I can't fight anymore sorry
I've got a retreat
okay the right side seems fine
the way I did it now but
do I take another depth
[Music]
I don't know
oh yeah he'll join me yeah
[Music]
was it avoidable I mean somewhere or
another everything's avoidable
troublesome
[Music]
foreign
but like previously
that didn't happen did it in the first
time
but I just changed the things up here
[Music]
I didn't change anything down here
is not worth it
wow so sad you're lucky that she's dead
now and she can't hear that but it's
kind of disrespectful to the Dead
[Music]
yeah the Run prior oil was a normal hit
um
[Music]
we still have 10 units
and we're getting this one
I guess I'll just continue right away
unless we lose another unit
then for real for real we gotta rethink
everything
does that means we're just in some
really deep
okay
79 89 89 is fine
[Music]
that's how a lady does it
look and that's so strong
[Music]
I will stand right here
and we might want to get Hortensia
closer ASAP
all right oh what do we have left on
this side there's this dude who we want
to stop because I don't know what that
item is but it sounds important these
ones I guess we can ignore because they
don't seem to be interested in going up
Ryan
[Music]
he cannot reach
and that is good don't worry about you
lose their outfit which is a shame
[Music]
yeah if I got too close to them
and what if I don't go down and then
back up does that automatically bait
them
[Music]
did he just say onigiri
Kitty
really dramatic onigiri
[Music]
he did
is he fan of okay senpai
she's hungry what I thought I miss her
one
that's so funny
[Music]
big Kusa all right we'll do a Mantic
here
perfect this is a perfect turn
ikini
[Music]
25 hit chance from him to do 15 hours
even if he does it's not that Michael
it's
I had to stop you boy we got to kill him
before
okay
next
[Music]
the Archer is already
bothering me so I need to take that
Archer down but with whom
[Music]
do do
oh wait can I
can I
order ah use mounted weapon to attack
foe what mounted weapon
can only a mage use this one
[Music]
a healed cockatoo
Magic One
[Music]
oh
if I
was magic here no one
no one close but yeah Chloe isn't Magic
right no one
no one who's here right now
[Music]
um
I wanna one hit this bastard
better than ever
[Music]
my choice of magicians
is down to two
oh well
I will continue standing here though
just to block it from Intruders
and maybe next turn I can cut that Thief
off with gold Mary
[Music]
I mean he can do quite a lot of damage
too maybe I have to combine yes
but there's also one here
fine
[Music]
run through
maybe we get a crit 28 8
base damage is higher here
and we don't get any damage back
eight percent you know how it is
sometimes eight percent is like
100 percent
without a try
[Music]
yeah eight equals eighty percent
now okay I'll try with the model it's
better Chris come on
I would have probably quit with the
other one
[Music]
man
um
back at you
I shall wait here
this one's the last one here right
[Music]
but on it I might
let me test
[Music]
what about
a Christian
a Lord and Savior Jesus all Christ
[Music]
I'll make him wait here okay
yeah what the
just killed some flying thing
hey baby okay baby
nice crit yeah all crit
he's got many nicknames
[Music]
e
Chloe is serving us some nice crits as
well
you laugh
my little thief girl
you'll see some action soon
stand here
okay no more La says please I'm gonna go
crazy
does not frighten me
I know my wife
don't be like that come on
75 percent
oh oh well that no no no
I blew it
no it's okay I blew it
I can't believe I lost
[Music]
no
no no
that's too much
question is how far do we go back
I'm not accepting that
[Music]
yeah maybe
why don't you so early she was the first
thing I moved
[Music]
sorry you gotta do that all over again
I first attacked one of them and then I
moved over here didn't I
mean I couldn't move back even further
too
I don't know
well we engaged to take less damage
let's get from
I can literally do anything here
[Music]
I will not lose
foreign
[Music]
let's just stay here
um
then we may not even have had to
engage but you know
perfect
[Music]
okay okay okay so another thing I might
change is this
no way that wasn't what I was doing I
will change this but first wait wait
what did I do what are the things that I
did I healed someone with her right
uh who did I know
did I just heal Chloe
I feel like I also healed some of the
importance yeah probably healed um
the other one you're my hero
um
[Music]
gotta go to work have fun bye bye now
through
[Music]
seems like we all have a
a
ear warm from that
okay I'm still in it
oh didn't I heal you up
[Music]
originally with Celine
oh well
she has a potion and I think she didn't
even attack anyone
did she in the previous turn
um
okay wait first these
[Music]
huh I don't care I don't care what time
I don't know I wanted to ask you guys
some questions so number one for anyone
who has already like made it inside
um when you queue do you queue before
character creation or after
and like let's say you waited for three
hours and you made it in
but I don't wanna my plan my plan was to
stream two hours after I killed before
okay
[Music]
I want to do two hours after
so I'm inside can they like kick me out
for not being active for two hours
[Music]
not even that bad when I'm queuing in
Europe
I don't know yo it's way better today oh
okay
[Music]
for real such a big difference
usually less oh okay then I'm not so
worried okay
then time wise I don't know I just I
can't imagine how long I would play it
it's hard to say
[Music]
um
yeah tomorrow I'll do it instead
[Music]
trust the steel sword
foreign
[Music]
maybe I will I feel like I
uh the long streams this week have been
keeping me from doing stuff
I need to clean my apartment
and yeah
yeah maybe I'll start at 6 p.m my time
so that afterwards I can still cook
um or 5 P.M
[Music]
maybe 5 PM my time it's a weekend so for
an a it should be fine to wake up early
a little bit but not too early later
than today
and for Europe
7 P.M on the Sunday I mean come on
[Music]
uh what did I do next
I did not kill this one which one
it doesn't matter I can kill both I
guess
[Music]
yes I encourage a healthy and good sleep
schedule for you guys
[Music]
got a problem with it huh you don't like
it
[Music]
5 p.m 8 A.M for me and that's not too
bad is that PST are you PSTA gang
I appreciate you concerned thank you
that sounds so professional
oh wait I wanted to keep her like around
here
PSP damn I'm I can't believe I even have
PST live viewers because usually I know
I'm so shitty for PST
I know I know
simple enough going to dance well I
don't know have you tried
is your
um
do you think I will die
on tutorial is it difficult
is it very I mean you guys told me it's
pretty online but this is very different
from previous Diablo Diablo 2
[Music]
is that um right when I get to work so
it's perfect nice
perfect for you this is easy it's pretty
easy it's easier oh gameplay will feel
familiar well that's nice
easier than two harder than friends
I don't think I ever played three
I played two and I had troubles with it
but is the biggest question is the
inventory bigger or
is it gonna trigger me real hard again
[Music]
thank you
it's a nice Savage bigger no Tetris
more convenient not that much stuff
drops let me tell you bigger
[Music]
almost every item uses the same thoughts
I
I mean the old
triggering charm you know will be gone
because even though it was really
triggering I guess that was the whole
charm of it
ah
[Music]
have I cleaned up perfectly
did I forget something I hope not please
ah
okay
she survived
okay he came over but he didn't attack
me yet okay okay okay okay we're all
having a hangout on my ship beautiful I
didn't invite you guys but okay
okay so let's say tomorrow 5 P.M
foreign
[Music]
what a summertime oh yeah Sunday huh I
mean I don't care about the one hour
less
um
it shouldn't be a big issue 5 PM is no
problem for me to my slip
gets look bad right now guys
I slept way earlier last night than I
did the night before
even though that's the last night last
last night I just stayed up really long
because I had some work and then last
night I also stayed up a bit longer
because I again had some work okay
I'm good I'm good
for real for real
trust me bro
[Music]
man
here just take the stone
[Music]
quality time titty
[Applause]
okay I have to use my engagements what
you got otherwise I'm Gonna Get Wrecked
but look how much damage she can do with
that she
but I'll take another okay I'll engage
I'll engage
oh sexy
[Music]
this one
it breaks down but it doesn't kill him
[Music]
nah
I want to go for the kill
engage with life doesn't do much with a
thief
yeah well
a thousand gold on kilometers there you
go I mean I mean that's something
[Music]
whatever it takes um I don't know if
they're in range I hope they are
I'm not a child anymore
[Music]
otherwise we might have to kill him I
don't know
[Music]
okay I'm probably not in range yeah yep
I'm not in range
I might have to dance with my love oh
wait wait uh violet
oh this one
[Music]
he does a lot of damage so I don't want
to kind of
ensure that that doesn't happen
so I would just stand here
and get danced I think you can reach
from there
pretty sure
he's on a horse
[Music]
what did I just say
not going according to my kikaku
[Music]
I scared your dog
well
skill issue
[Music]
I should have put more people
around me
at least we have two people
[Music]
sub-optimal dance
it's a 50 50.
you you take what you get
[Music]
do you have time to talk about our Lord
and savior Chihuahua I should
I find myself reluctant to spill blood
broken knee
saying such a thing to my phone bill
blood but spill it on my team with my
teammates I'm the Divine Dragon my Army
is working to defeat the feldragon and
take back illusion the Divine Dragon I
know you're devoted to the feldragon but
much better if that helps Princess Ivy
is alive as far as I'm concerned I think
she's dead right now
[Laughter]
has always been to the Royal Family
itself please
of course
wait what if we're playing on classic
and she died at this point
[Music]
will he still say oh she's alive
or will that dialogue change
[Music]
is something I need to know this
she remains alive but kind of battle
what is that the case for every
character
never played classic so I don't really
know
so they're gonna be like in the somnia
but I just don't
battle
not all of them
only the main one oh
oh okay so she's just forever injured
cannot battle but can totally stand in
the thumbnail and participate in all the
MCs
yeah Royal plot armor I may be getting
[Music]
a road to the knee ah
Linda and George can I already move him
now
you need very interesting one dude oh
[Music]
okay
um another question that Georgie had was
did you get to check out the expo at all
before it opened after us no
that's why I was saying the other day
like
I wanna sing
it
I did not get to participate in that you
know things that every a lot of the
other members did on the day before
maybe next year then
I could not participate this time
sadly
maybe next time
I want to I will not let that chance be
taken away from me next time
[Music]
okay
sexy
all flowers eventually Wilt yeah and
girls I think it wasn't it only Iris and
Kelly who signed something
from the Ian girls
[Music]
ah yeah Iris and Cali from Ian
and only Muna from ID
um
and why is that guy so not dead
because I couldn't reach
all right come on
come on
you were beautiful while you lasted
no Ina didn't sign anything
what are you guys talking about
expand to Grand speed plus two to use it
permanently
[Music]
all right
all right how far does this go by the
way I just want to check oh I can't what
but she's
[Music]
but she's Magic
thank you for the membership booze
killing Edge
[Music]
and that one's for boyo says I thought
it was from Magic cases
[Music]
uh no enemies okay that's worse I
literally wanted to check the range okay
[Music]
okay I mean we lost units a little bit
unnecessarily above I think from now on
we'll be fine
by me
oh
hmm
[Music]
yeah
I'll take an Elixir because I think I
used everyone else so nobody can heal
go ahead you talk about this dirt Axel
is really hot with them you want to see
them alive
well
[Music]
you little spawning right in my
face
I sweat God I was about to leave
oh
I'm making holiday
[Music]
and
a steel sword come on come on come on
I said by now just really expect them
but I I just don't what why did what
oh man I don't I can't even
time to engage emblem and get
[Music]
that is very disappointing uh
so I am prepared
[Music]
if I'm engaged no there's no one
standing in the middle so I can't do the
running proofing of cigarette either
oh why so weak
wow yeah
[Music]
who to take down
I think I can only take down the the
upper one and then do some damage to the
lower one
's really strong yeah what the hell
I can break this one
[Music]
yeah but that doesn't really help me
either it doesn't let's just kill this
one
now it's my turn
why do we repeat our mistakes
wait
huh why did that say Chloe and Erica
[Music]
is that a what but it showed
a guy is that another thing show someone
else and cross attack oh okay
that is her twin
oh is it like with with the uh you know
the other thing where I was like why do
we not show the thing that I'm expecting
ah
okay should I still
engage though
because I even if I engage I can't kill
at all like it doesn't help no okay
can't break him at least that's good
Timothy
um
[Music]
and walk away a little bit
okay
they also Spawn from the bottom but not
from the top okay
where's our course true
Chris we gotta do something
nice
with the long ball
oh
[Music]
critical I'm still alive
that wasn't even necessary so yeah
damn son
I'm impressed
first fogado by the way
ah is it the this one
[Music]
oh
so weak
why is his Longbow so much weaker
what
[Music]
what the hell
it looks sad in comparison less strength
overall
he's a magical user
um
[Music]
I mean
at least you can't fight back
[Music]
I couldn't use the radiant bull right
because I was too far I think I think
Longbow was the only option sorry if I
messed up
it
yeah
I think oh the range wasn't
there
hmm
okay
um
can you do something
I could but nothing useful what about
here
not really sad
[Music]
um
am I still do it though
better than nothing because I don't see
how else I would use her here right now
[Music]
nine percent crit
go steal to ever go
you're dead
wait how much damage does that do I
didn't see that was plenty that was
plenty guys at all to believe in the
nine percent crit nine percent equals 90
crit
oh foreign
[Music]
who is left over there
only these three
[Music]
this one rest is baited but I wonder if
they'll spawn more on this side as well
[Music]
and wait we have four of these here one
of them can charge on the way back here
[Music]
right y'all we can charge a cocketsu
um
I'll engage emblem engage maybe it wins
but whatever
[Music]
I'm not alone anymore I'm not alone
oh man
imagine we could have seen her perform
that in fourth first
[Music]
I would have been so good
somehow
[Music]
universe is fun now
such a pretty song
I want to sing it again
[Music]
Astro girl also is from a taco
what but I'm happy for them it must feel
nice as a producer
to have your song perform like that
especially if you like a smaller
producer
you know makes me happy for them
[Music]
I saw that tweets too because now
Twitter literally shows me everything
laughs
whether I like it or not and is that
Canon dangerous for me
possibly
[Music]
hmm
the eye of Saucon
I mean I was already seeing a lot of
stuff before that just by my own skills
and intentions no but also because of
you guys and the ones that I do follow
like dakuma Elegance
and Christina yeah yeah
don't blame me
[Music]
a lot of that is not on me
138 damage
[Music]
oh the Archer
don't really want to bait the Archer
oh next turn
Who you gonna go for Connect
hmm
wow
she wasn't engaged that would have been
even more painful
yeah there should be
she didn't even kill
man
oh
go Chloe girl
she's trying
that's stupid
not rifle material at all
let's be careful
[Music]
a breaking good
I'll use the flame lands uh finish off
of the other one
[Music]
yeah
that's the way to go
rest in peace
[Music]
okay finally
we're gonna go catch up now sorry for
the weight of
[Music]
um
anything down here no
can we shoot someone
[Music]
how far
not
useful because it hurts me too
[Music]
yeah not not useful at all then
Maybe
how far with Lynn I'm sorry I wanna get
the one on the
oh oh
[Music]
that one look at this one bye
um
I want to change my mind but it's too
late now because the animals were close
enough to kill that one anyway I need to
get stronger until no one can beat me I
wanna undo already
[Music]
yeah I could have gone for the bus
because even they were in reach
should I rewind I mean by now I don't
think we need that many rewinds anymore
foreign
engaged
[Music]
so there's a soldier that I could kill
or I could get half of the
um boss's HP almost half
I think we'll just get started with a
bun
the range is incredible
it's not it's pretty strong but I mean I
guess it's a joke weapon but it's like
totally usable and pretty strong like it
has served us well a couple of times
it's like one of those items you get out
of that um magical
um well
um
who should I give them if I give someone
a uh the thingy it heals them all the
way up too right
I'm not all okay but plenty
[Music]
I'll give it to her
because I wanted to heal her anyway
I think this just makes sense
[Music]
we're gonna be done with this map soon
don't worry guys
but sorry for to wait
[Music]
retribution is due
retribution is you and I am true Nebo as
yo
yo like
absolutely what's the word
I'm sorry you had to see that
how would you describe her
I'm looking for one word not edgy
I'll pick this up no actually I don't
need to great Aether
[Music]
that's what I'm looking for thank you
thank you
he's cracked
she's the big Kraken from the sea
you know what I'll go down there for
some exp maybe but not before Tennessee
maybe someone else
[Music]
thanks for looking out
you're so cute
nice of luck but no magic magic Dooku
girl
[Music]
and
um
[Music]
am I like
um
very sensitive towards bow users I don't
know
I'll bring them both
ah
um
current now okay
step by step
oh
[Music]
I mean why not
I don't want to give him a kill though
because I'm not gonna use him
so he doesn't deserve the eggs
oh wait this is a nice dialogue
you fight for its decline
truly on the wrong side
so we get a betrayal dialogue
feeling big
old man got the moves yes he does oh now
these are finally coming everybody's
like all right
this is the last chance
I guess then you guys can get some exp
too
[Music]
by accident well
I want to check some more weapons okay
[Music]
oh
no that is not good uh
yeah I'll do it anyway
seven in exchange for 15. yeah but he's
only got 44 percent
I wanted the dragon vein but I'm one
step away from her
I like I mean like two because it was
only a dragon vein here and I don't
think I could go here
it's all right
it's a wad
I did not think I would be coming back
but
[Music]
um
even if I come back this is uh
oh God
I can't really help
I mean I can I will
I will
can't let back let's let these
allies behind
in such a dying situation
[Music]
and I think even with the engagement it
wouldn't have been so good
oh so
I'm not there I'm not there no no he
can't shoot again
I was like huh I'll shoot another time
that's not how it works
[Music]
oh
kind of useless right now
okay
take down
this little
insect
first
[Music]
momentum gives me more attack at three
months
[Music]
okay
wow
[Music]
I don't want to do all the dance with
him
what if I don't offer them an option
you know
okay here's some Thunder
[Music]
damn damn
more exp no wait I want to open the
there's a chance there
I can't can you read it if you can't
fogado
I thought I had to waste another turn to
get this
probably just money no a second sale
yeah
[Music]
served you right
okay
[Music]
party free twice
uh
I don't want to do this to him
that's so sad
but would he do that too which would she
do that to potencia too
wait orange is free can he do that from
here
incredible
you
no can I do something from here no why
does Tiki not give me anything long
range man
I could kill her right here
[Music]
I call some doubles
oh that sucks
well she goes for uh
good job potty potty
it turns only that felt like a million
years
damn
yay
safe progress
it felt so long
I wasn't even rewinding that much there
was just one rewind where I had to go
back a lot
but like
I didn't do it that often
is there any animals on here
that would be kind of weird
oh there's one I think
Ahoy cat Maybe
MVP I didn't really I didn't really see
[Music]
oh a seagull Pinette got MVP well
yeah that just makes a lot of sense
I don't know
any
I mean you know actually
only a cat on a ship doesn't make that
little sense because you can imagine
like maybe
when the ship goes to land and they
bring some food for long journey like
rice and stuff then probably mice come
with it and then you want the cats to
take care of the mice because you
if your rations are gone in the middle
of the ocean but it's a verb
it was sitting so cute
hmm
yeah okay yeah I feel like
maybe have like
witnessed that before totally in the
past when I was on a ship oh um on the
middle of the ocean yeah
yeah I remember I remember
she looks so cool
character design top notch
let's go
alucia is inside so
I've returned are you all right
whatever has become of Illusion
I'll still do what I must give report is
a little farther north I suggest sailing
there understood
near the castle under the cathedral so
we should be able to gather Intel there
I will inform the others of our
destination
[Music]
yeah I like the character designs
generally Mars
Makaya Roy
we returned without you but we'll get
you back this time
just hang on
don't be so dramatic
illusion maybe I got it from European
history solo emblems
if reunited we can at last Grant the
power we offer once every thousand years
we should discuss our other option
that is the far greater power Only We
Know About yes of course
Lumera what I don't like this idea
we shouldn't perform the miracle we have
to think of the future I agree the whole
future we can't favor anyone with it now
favor someone we're talking about numera
we can prevent a tragedy please those of
us who are scattered in other lands are
still learning all that's happened some
of us were at her castle
some were not
it's natural to see things differently
so we are not all in agreement at least
at present using our power every
thousand years is one thing
the miracle we've never used it before
is that like existence
the cost of doing so is not safe
they've never done it before you should
never ever use
of course we are not all here what might
the others think
but my day decide
is it like they make all evil go away
but it also means that they go away
[Music]
probably
I mean
they can't be ghosts like this forever
right
we're back in the somnia looking as
beautiful as ever
let me collect some stuff
is it true that I have not told you
clearly about my throat expectation
story experience guys is that really so
foreign
such a beautiful uterus I have not
damn I guess huh
I didn't go into details all right let
me try to remember
it was requested
yeah the one with the picture that I
uploaded before my 3D showcase on
Twitter I uploaded a picture of my
throat and everybody was like what the
and that's exactly what I wanted
yeah I still have that picture
uh sorry I was getting uh sick like two
or three days before
my 3D showcase and it was getting worse
day by day so I was like panicking
[Music]
but I didn't want to cancel it because I
knew
I would have to go on a weekday
otherwise and also just in general like
people announced it at that time and
people expected at that time so
I wanted to avoid that what are we
getting a squirrel cake a lollipop
and yeah we've seen the drama storm
before some books though I will not
throw these away don't worry
um
for some stuff in there the other day
yeah and then you know I willed my
health into existence not really just
momentarily
oh okay I'll start chilling here
um and
through
because of that I said well on the night
before I said I think I'm fine or on the
actually
[Music]
on the night before before
two days before I think and then they
were like well
that's good but the studio wants the
studio team
wants you to go to a hospital
to get like a doctor's approval
[Music]
um
otherwise you know they won't let me do
it I was like okay
I guess
sounds like kind of
um
like an overreaction almost but okay
okay
I'll go I'll go I mean I'm also kind of
worried maybe there's something really
wrong with my throat right now
it'll be good to know
so
now I guess this is different depending
on the country but I do wonder if
there's any other countries
that do it like Japan
but I think I've told you guys before
that in Japan the way it works is
there's like you go for everything you
go to a hospital a big ass Hospital
that's why it feels like so
hey they're exaggerated to me
but even for like having a little a
little cough or a little sneeze you go
to the hospital because every all the
doctors are at the hospital there's like
no small offices
um
I mean maybe there's some small
hospitals but
it's all hospitals here in Austria
there's like a general doctor's office
there's like millions of them so you go
to your most local closest one and then
they will send you to other small
offices with like experts on whatever
you have
you know that's how it goes
[Music]
um
kind of like that in yours you mean like
with smaller general doctors
I think Americans would try to avoid
going to the uh
[Music]
going to the
who should I go with going to the
hospital
by any
uh what's the word it's like so
expensive right
send
[Music]
ivy
doesn't matter
by any means necessary yeah
so
feel Pros that's good
um what was I saying oh yeah so they
wanted me to go to hospital
and they said they'll they'll pay for it
I was like okay well if you want to pay
for it because I don't have a travel
insurance or anything I never get that
kind of stuff
Maybe by now I've had so many cases you
know like in Greece where I
broke my neck
that by now I should uh maybe
indeed get insurance for traveling as
well but something I mean I've been fine
and if I do something while in Europe I
guess I'm I'm probably still fine pretty
sure I just made it in your world even
without traveling
health insurance I think I'm totally
fine in terms of cost
girl if so make who's a soulmik are they
soulmik eating outside is
I hope at least one of them was soulmake
[Music]
none of them are are they because it's
the the desert
um
only the ones that ate get it right
uh okay so yeah they said they'll take
care of it so
my my manager team then uh tried to find
a fitting Hospital maybe possibly with
like English speaking staff or so like
Foreigner friendly
um
and they found something that's
fortified
is that AOE healing
I thank you I buy you thank you I buy
you
[Music]
I already have one oh well I mean a
second one will not hurt
do come again
yeah I also I don't know wouldn't I
think it wouldn't have been unnecessary
but oh well they did that
and
um so let's now
then in order to actually be allowed to
the hospital
over the phone they were asking for me
to do like a temperature test
even though at the hospital at the
entrance they also do a temperature test
but just to get an appointment I guess
they also wanted a temperature test so
one of the managers like scrambled to
quickly get me
um a
what's it called a you know the thing
the thing you know what I mean
[Music]
and then we did that and it was fine so
yeah then we hopped into
a taxi really fancy taxi and then we got
to the hospital
and it was a huge Hospital
it was like around the day and around
the end of its like business
so when we went there and they were
expecting us they were like hurry hurry
please fill this out like really fast
and I couldn't even finish filling it
out even though I was trying my best to
be really fast with it
couldn't even finish it let's see no
what the hell where is the thing that I
want
and they were like please calm down
please please come we don't have time
we're about to close where is it
[Music]
am I blind
wait is it four to five why can't she
not use it
why can't she not use it
she's not a magic rank huh she's B
ayou
wait
she's at okay
[Music]
okay
uh
and then and then and then yeah
they let me when the lady was really
nice the lady that was leading me she
was like oh you're you're only hunger is
so Joseph like for real for real though
wow
she was really nice and she was also
speaking actually pretty good English so
they did have some
English-speaking staff which is
incredible I have to say for Japanese
standards
and then I went into this like small
room
where a doctor
and his assistant where yeah
or like nurse I guess I'll just tell the
story now because I can't
concentrate
and then
yeah okay so I sit down and um like I
like tell them my symptoms I tell them
how's it been going how it has been
going and blue
I just told them that basically I
started just getting a little horsey
um
and yeah that it was getting better and
that I have basically my management also
told me to tell them that I have like
some important
TV program or so coming up where I have
to talk
in his life and it can't really ideally
it can't be canceled
um and so I explained that to them my
management was like there after they
went into my throat
first I was alone
um
so yeah
I explain it and they're like Okay Okay
so
it immediately they're like okay we're
gonna put a camera down your throat
I was like
immediately I knew that this wasn't
gonna go well because I'm just not good
with a lot of those things it makes me
feel really blood sick
um
so I even warned them I said I don't
think this will go well
[Music]
but
I immediately however also thought this
would be an interesting story to tell on
stream so I guess I will lose
go through with it it didn't really seem
like I could say no anyway
yeah they said no no better than your
nose well they are gonna go through my
nose they told me for the nose then for
the fruit
yeah
com combined
and I I was like I told them that like
even those covet tests that go for the
nose
I really can't handle well and the
assistant told me oh
it's not as bad as that actually the
cover test they heard more in her
opinion I'm like a little bit relieved
after she said that
and then so they put like some kind of I
guess numbing or like pain relieving or
so uh spray in my nose
public
as if that would help
I know man because like it's not just
going for the nose it's going for my
nose deep deep deep down to my throat
yeah a local anesthesia I guess
I don't know if that really did anything
it did feel weird too even the spray
felt weird so
blah
it definitely helps you wouldn't want it
without the spray really
[Music]
yeah so okay so they
they start
putting this camera through my nose and
first it was like
the first moment it felt
manageable
but
yeah the deeper it went the less I could
bear it it took a lot of time it felt
like an eternity and at the same time
this is the problem the assistant the
nurse she was like pointing at the
camera
um and and she was like you have to look
at this look at this look at this look
at this so this is you know where we are
right now I'm like I don't want to look
but she like kind of forces me to look
so that's what what is making it worse
and then uh
for real man
real man and then they both like kind of
ask me a question and before before they
put it in I asked them if you would want
to talk could you talk while it's in
there and they said oh if you wanted to
you probably could
but they say it as if it's like not that
easy though but it's possible so they're
aware okay and then they ask me a
question while this is like deep
down there in front of my vocal cords
and
I literally can't speak and because I
know it it feels weird like
I was already getting sicker and sicker
and my stomach was turning around and
I'm like
can we not and yeah after it went down
my nose I was like
you know feeling really sick so I was I
was like petting but the nurse's arm
and kind of strangling her arm too but
more often I would
put
trying to signal to her that I can't
take this please take it out now
and and the more time would go by the
more aggressively and panicly I would do
it and I was like oh I was like you know
going like like
I couldn't speak but I was making these
noises like
this is
and they ignore me can you
believe it what's the matter
with them maybe they're just so so
what's the word that I learned the other
day desensitized
dead
the the tortured voices of their
patients is just like they think it's
all fine
[Music]
well it took so much longer than I
thought it would
I'm tapping out the bad chance not the
bench
[Music]
they wouldn't stop they won't stop and I
really felt so sick
and they like the doctor was trying to
explain to me so these are your vocal
cords and please try to swallow now so
that we see if they close properly and I
tried but
and it seemed like it was fine but like
what what the man
eventually
um
I I was starting to faint I felt my
whole body
was like feeling
I don't know
like I don't know how to describe it
[Music]
it was definitely losing all its power
and I was feeling like jelly
um
yeah
and I was leaving my body my soul I was
literally dying
[Applause]
and I was losing it and
finally while that was happening and I
was just like oh
dramatically dying
I stopped patting I guess that was the
sign for the nurse
because I stopped doing this
I just went like
and she says oh Dr Sun we should maybe
y'all
oh I think we should I think she's
fainting we should probably take it take
that thing out now
so I heard that and I was I was kind of
unconscious but at the same time I was
just I don't know
my body left my soul no my soul left my
body
they separated temporarily uh
I did hear what they were saying though
I was okay
not really but I was okay but not really
though
yeah
um man that felt terrible so they take
it out and it feels like I hate it
never want to do that again they've
never done something like that I don't
know I don't know anyone in in Austria
who's ever experienced something like
that but in Japan you say I'm proud and
immediately they stick that
camera down your throat
so unnecessary I think it's uh oh yeah
the interesting thing was the bill
afterwards because the the thing that
took up the most money was like the one
milliliter of local anesthesia
took up like
um I mean compared to America I guess
it's still cheap but for I don't know
European
anesthetic it I think it costs like
like 100 bucks
for that one milliliter of spray
um
it's always the understanding yeah yeah
okay
[Applause]
camera wasn't even that expensive but in
order to use the camera they combine it
with the anesthetic so you know I think
they just want to make money that's why
they immediately go for that
but then turns out so you know they they
take the camera out and they're like
really worried about me so they lay down
the chair completely flat uh trying to
get me back to life
um
and I was so mad that they didn't end it
earlier that they let me get to this
point in the first place I was legit
like pissed off
um I was like really sweaty too from
that experience like it felt so weak
[Music]
um
and they were like for a while they were
just trying to you know
waiting for me to come back
because I was feeling really dizzy and
sick
so after like five minutes
uh they they beam me back up
and the doctor explains to me in a
million difficult Japanese words
like medical terms this and that this
and that blue but in short
you're fine
like there was some inflammation
uh I think at the nose like close to the
nose because of all the blowing my nose
but throat wise you said you're fine I
mean some of the liquid from your nose
is like dripping down there that's why I
had to flag them I guess I don't know
but well you said fine you're fine
and then my managers came in and I said
please tell the same thing to them
because I don't really know if I
understand right now
if there's something I need to
understand
um
so he explained it again
and
at least I got my picture
we check you live great thank you that
was so worth it
my nose felt kinda
or the whole tracked from nose down to
throat felt kind of violated for the
next
half an hour
I had this weird feeling in there that
something
was there that shouldn't be in there
yeah I tried to like get that feeling
away with drinking some tea but it
didn't go away it took a while I think
that was also partially the anesthetic
making me feel weird
[Music]
yeah so unpleasant I hate it
make me feel so sick but I also felt so
stupid because
um where did that happen to me ah
I had something
uh some doctor experience before where I
was told from the doctor
that none of his patients ever reacted
to this
like that ever before so sensitively and
it made me feel kind of like
ashamed like what the why
made me feel ridiculous for reacting
like that but what can I do if my body
reacts like this like I fainted
basically partially again at that time
no it wasn't the hair thing
was something else but
um yeah
apparently others don't react so badly
and I did
um
so that wasn't nice
[Music]
it was so so so
unpleasant that experience too and it
made me feel sick and I also had to lay
me down flat and it took a while yeah
so I guess I just generally there's just
certain types of procedures that I just
my body can't take it it will make me
feel really nauseous and and make me
faint
yeah but because I had that and now it
happened with the camera thing again I
felt like
kind of ashamed that something like that
can so easily
take me out you know
put it on Twitter some people answered
to me and told me that they've had it
done before and they they know it's like
really unpleasant and they also really
don't like it and hurts and they don't
like it yeah
so then I felt a bit better hearing it
from others
[Music]
emotional damage
and other people told me that
uh they've had it done without a local
anesthetic
and it was really bad and I think some
people even told me their front camera
went for their fruit
and am I going crazy but I feel like
somebody told me
somebody had a fruit camera
go through their butt
does that make sense
is that really a thing
[Music]
what
or maybe not uh
maybe not all the way to the front but
um I don't remember anymore at that
point
hahaha
[Music]
I don't remember anymore
that's the colonoscopy
yeah I've heard of that
[Music]
I don't remember anymore people told me
that that's more painful or less painful
in any case it all sucks you should not
have a camera inside your body
it's just not supposed to be there
otherwise we would have borne would have
been born with a camera in our body if
it was supposed to be there we would
have been born like that we weren't so
it's not supposed to be there
yeah it's not natural that
but yeah the doctor told us that we um
I'm fine
only prescribed me some throat uh candy
type of but more medical looking type of
fruit thingy the keeping me and
some painkillers
and
something
to
help with the painkillers or like I
think the pinkles were also a little bit
for inflammation at all I don't know but
generally what I was prescribed
felt like stuff I could just get even
without prescription in the pharmacy and
I ended up like
only
using the Los Angeles a little bit
and maybe one painkiller but
yeah
yeah after all that right what the
it was like such basic
I guess it just really meant that I was
fine which
um I didn't really feel fine because
after that I got even sicker after the
3D showcase
yeah
um
[Music]
well I don't know it didn't feel like it
was that worth it the whole Shenanigans
didn't feel like it was worth it but the
studio wanted a confirmation that I
would be fine so
but on the 3D stream day
I was really trying my best to get to
like a state where I could talk normally
but damn I I was drinking that magical
paper KOA stuff and tea with honey and
Los Angeles and everything Los Angeles
uh
all at once
making my tummy upset again
but yeah
in the end it didn't go that well on
stream it sounded fine but I was really
suffering
it was so painful
that whole experience man I don't want
to get sick anymore
[Music]
I believe Los Angeles didn't help
La isn't the Dream City that your father
was
okay
that was that
thanks for suffering fruit yeah I kind
of had to
[Music]
um
but it shows me that miracles happen
even when you're like really really sick
you can force your mind
to get better
it's literally a skill issue
okay who do we oh panette almost level
up
I am panette
the termination exactly
I really thought I had you oh my God I'm
sorry are you injured go ahead Danika
not fair
but okay I'll take it oh conversation
you guys want to talk about that you
want to talk it out
I don't know if I recommend that oh
everybody else is like far from a level
up
[Music]
um
kiwawa is max level is she just gonna
forever stay on level 20 how does that
work
okay
[Music]
alrighty
will do will do
is she just turn level 20
[Music]
right here the Crown Princess of soul
Victory so
[Music]
oh
so wait wait no not like that uh change
class
[Music]
so just Dragon no Advanced uh Divine
Dragon again right
I want to see the outfit
yeah okay
just Divine Dragon what about hero
[Music]
it's hero
it's fancy I am the hero
why isn't it wolf not gives your
ponytail
I wanna see a preview
[Music]
polio
vinyl premiums that sucks
oh now stay here so we go back to level
one
what a weird system
okay at that point let me just go
what
what is the reason behind this system is
there any logical explanation why it
won't just at this point if there's
nothing else I can become
just let me go up higher to 30 40 50.
[Music]
it makes no sense
that makes no sense
no no no just makes no sense
it just makes no sense can I level up
anyone else
um
[Music]
foreign
no
[Music]
I think not
judging by my knowledge which is endless
[Music]
because there is none
it's to inconvenience the player
game would be too easy other words
[Applause]
it goes back to Awakening and Faith of
reclassing where you kept your skills
but had to reset your level
doesn't make as much sense when you
don't get the skills
yeah all new characters already advanced
that's boring I want to see some changes
[Music]
make sure you have good weapons and
weapons
I don't understand all of that like
what's a prioritize
um
you have to use money on seals to keep
getting stronger well that's so stupid
that's so stupid
ah good night
[Music]
they have some cool new stuff
thank you
the next chapter is so rough although
people have told me that before and it
really wasn't
a deal
get something fresh huh maybe gold Mary
we have something
maybe an armor Slayer
killing Edge
inflicting deadly wounds
[Music]
should I give her a Netherlands
thank you
great weapons are best so killing Edge
[Music]
I keep I keep killing it
here you go op
P okay
[Music]
everyone to cockatoo
well who's
who is in need of new weapons of my
basic team that I always use
oh she's only using a non-upgraded
silver lens that's kind of sad
I guess it's fine
thank you
an Armor's Lando
[Music]
maybe instead of the silver sword I took
that from someone
[Music]
do I have like one lying around
take care
if foreign
[Music]
oh does someone have an armor Slayer
oh me and there's a warm Slayer
fight dragons
[Music]
barely even uses the armor Slayer though
I feel like I almost always use
liberation
[Music]
killer weapons Bates Engraving
I'm so indecisive when it comes to stuff
like this
Mages just nuke armor so I never
bothered my armor Slayer yeah I mean
that's what I try to do as well the
moment where I see like a strong heavy
armor dude
and just go at it with my majors and I
always bring plenty of them so
more fun time is not an issue
[Music]
foreign
she never uses her slim sword does she
why does she have a slim sword
[Music]
um
okay
assistant cockatoo is fine I'm eating
chocolate
and um somebody should get
the foreign
[Music]
it was hard for her to hit
yeah
I relax foreign as fire right so instead
of L fire
oh no wait isn't that
[Music]
Wonder
ful
a truly Mighty Thunder tome
cannot follow up oh sick the Thunder can
fall up right oh no can also not follow
up
um okay
I don't want the fracture
take a
maybe amend
[Music]
or take the treat again
I wonder if like a obstruct or something
like that would be useful in the next
map
warp would be nice to teleport
um
which one rewarp or warp or rescue
[Music]
all my my ceiling stapes this stuff is
only really needed on maddening
deals with a far away Ally to the
hundreds yeah I think I'll take a rescue
for like situations where someone's just
from separating so far away or like Jade
for example
[Music]
I don't know what to do about these
weapons
it's been
[Music]
so as this country makes uh
advice
um
[Music]
foreign
there it is
oh good night oh
triangle strategy
oton my sweet sweet summer child
I wish I could
[Music]
don't you know that
if I could I would
that's another
Square Enix game is it not
you know how it is all those beautiful
beautiful Square Enix games
I am forever cursed to not play them
it's killing me and that's why we're
upgrading the killing Edge
[Music]
I'll go plus two for now
forever it seems like they're forever
Out Of Reach yeah at least Cali got to
uh
a point where she can now play Resident
Evil 4 good for her
different company but also apparently
problematic to or difficult to get you
know I should upgrade the 11th sword yo
I love the leaven sword
so good
I currently don't have interest in
resident four but
what was that other game that people
told me you can do multiplayer I I was
considering to play that with someone
um
yeah it's like the difference between
English and Japanese
location
[Music]
Resident Evil 5.
oh yeah
I I guess we said yeah to play that with
Cali
anyway
um
could upgrade the flame lands
but upgrade this one
[Music]
it's fancy
I love that design
is it worth it
do I even use that one
[Music]
Kelly had problems starting the game up
really
[Music]
lollipop lollipop lollipop and next with
the sweet set the surprise when consumed
as an item but recovers uses HP I wonder
if it's as useful as like the croissal
bow
[Music]
it no longer needs games or Windows to
function
ah oh one thing I'm trying to get to
work uh soon when my brother comes over
he's gonna help me because I don't want
to use my brain
um
and you know I'm probably gonna do this
after I'm done with like Fire Emblem
and Metroid Prime
but
Sims one
is finally gonna happen you know I
bought all the games like a long time
ago already
uh but I heard that it's kind of
difficult to
get them to run on current PCS
yeah but I really want to play I want to
play this one
challenging too
so I'm looking forward to it
mm-hmm
[Music]
just as difficult as getting the average
one the other one well possibly
I don't know but yeah I'm gonna make my
brother do that for me I mean I have the
games like physically and I bought uh
another because I can't find my other
one I bought another external drive
and find the other one is
the sound it was difficult and I love
all the expansion packs they had back
then ah they made some similar ones for
you know Sims 2 and Sims 3 and so on
um or some of them are even like
supposedly the exact same theme
but I don't know there was something
about Sims one that was just so magical
and so much fun
ah hello Raiders
right from home
and in graphic card errors yeah
something like that is what I worry
about but I watched like I skipped
through a tutorial
before tutorial
about how to install Sims 1 on current
PCS so
it seems totally doable you just have to
go for some annoying steps this and that
but it's possible so that will be a
thing I'll be playing soon
did I upgrade anything else guys
um
it's so hard to see like who these
people are maybe the steel sword
sword
all right I don't I'm pretty fond of
using her at the moment
[Music]
a nice membership could say they've
reached the right people that's
beautiful
killing Edge yeah and I did plus two on
that one
daggers for my fifth oh
my one feet
that's worth
it where's the daggers this one
oh I already have a bunch of her things
upgraded but I guess I'll give her
I'm gonna run out of iron
should I upgrade the silver dagger or
the steel dagger
a bit more
I don't remember which one I used the
most
but maybe all of them are worth it
[Music]
of course are not worth it still and
silver okay thank you
I'll do plus two hmm
can I do this one too no okay okay this
is it that's all I can do
[Music]
unless I exchange
I think we're good good to go did I
forget something I mean I could play so
many ah actually I I one of the things I
did on the plane was play that flying
mini game The shooty One
I got uh I unlocked I think another
level on it
it's been fun
I feel like we could go now
[Music]
that game is fun I like the mini games
flying while flying on a plane exactly
shut up hey
ask parents yeah yeah uh I I don't know
yet but there's many things I want to
play with I remember remembered the
other day actually just yesterday that I
wanted to play uh Luigi's Mansion 4 with
Goodall she was into the idea too
I'm gonna go now guys
I feel like uh
there's nothing really important that we
need to do I mean we could do some more
things but I don't really care wait
actually no one more thing
I heard there's some support stuff we
should do that
yeah
I cannot wonder about your past I
understand wanting to preserve some
secrecy but please tell me a little
about Don't force her to dogs herself
okay my parents abandoned me when I was
small after that growing up was anything
but easy I don't like thinking about it
and I like talking about it even less I
am so sorry I know well the pain of
being elected by one's parents you too
when they say I'm gonna go now I mean
we're gonna go to the next story it was
a hopeless drunk my mother was always
out partying who knew that we hailed
from such similar backgrounds I wouldn't
have guessed but it's reassuring in a
way
maybe I feel a little less alone
Bandits incoming on our position let me
count nine no ten where I don't forget
to jump on a say we'll show them listen
up Pinhead there why was you I think
they're in your head twice about messing
with me and her one more step and we'll
turn your intestines into outtestines
and we'll see a single one we're not
here to kill anyone
if you're here to be killed well
my hands girls are tied girls enough
acting
interesting
okay it's here
hey Pinette how's it going
quite well thank you you appear to be in
good health yourself Eddie
yep good eye huh
[Music]
is something the matter oh sorry I'm
being rude
panette your stylish fashion sense and
refined speech are Peerless why thank
you
they're reading the line so flat oh
fashion sense is amazing do you mean I
assure you I am not what do you carry
yourself like a noble woman but you are
not one I smell a fake oh that is
ludicrous called out Landorus even so
you won't admit it fine if being blunt
won't work I'll have to get sneaky see
you around Pinette
Good Question
come from
you're looking real healthy girl well I
don't know that's not even that bad
because so many times people told me
back in school and at work and so on
that oh you look are you are you have
you slept are you tired oh are you okay
are you healthy are you good are you
sick are you good Chihuahua
skin is so
so white
are you okay
you look really exhausted
stressed
that's a wonderful day for laundry
thank you for worry but don't go about
it like that and Grace
is that even allowed
I should hope so I love laundry care to
join me me she loves laundry are you
sure you might discover that washing
clothes on a sunny day is refreshing and
restorative keeping neat and clean won't
exactly lose you any friends either
yeah I don't care
or maybe you've got something hidden
among your unmentionables and don't want
me to see
laundry hand comes to him when I suppose
I'll take your word for it
I will not wash my clothes by hand I
will not go back to Medieval Times like
that sorry just for the sake of a stream
it just is I would rather not get into
why maybe I should actually I better go
as she's cute
I wonder what that was about
let's
[Music]
I did really consider building some
furniture
um that I just ordered on stream though
but then I figured the furniture is
actually pretty big so in order to
capture that without like showing my
legs and so on I feel like it would be
pretty difficult so I decided to just
not do it but if I get some like smaller
Furniture certainly princess Tamara
maybe I'll do it what do you need
I hear that you're from a mining town so
you know a lot about minerals and stuff
that's right my father was a gemologist
so I picked up a fair bit of knowledge
how Hunter
yeah
I'm on the hunt for a big fabulous Jules
have a place in mind but I'm not sure
how to go about finding a gem there ah I
understand why you came to me oh I
wouldn't mind joining he was such a dim
if you're interested in Jewels why not
visit a jeweler after all I'm sure
they'd sell you as many rare stones as
you want yeah but that's no fun I'd much
rather find one for myself
weasel that's a rare perspective well if
that's the plan I'll be happy to guide
you I feel like we'll take a few notes
along the way ideally we should ideas
for my next novel perfect but I get a
dazzling jewelry what could work it's
like um like a big flowy
long skirt because that doesn't show the
shape
of the legs I guess so that would maybe
hide it well you know what I mean big
flow is good
but ideally
foreign
not really I think at that point it's
just uh the principle of not showing
anything even if you showed it and let's
say it's exactly the same shape and
color as it should be
even then it's just the principle at
that point
wait up it says Tamira need something
[Music]
strong word I just figured you were
headed off to eat a snack nope I was
about to start I still have another
philistream then why did you have
because I want a big grin on your face
in Japan but I ended up not doing it
huh
I guess that tracks it's the one I had
it all backwards with the childhood I
was about to ask if I could friendship
books sorry to burst your bubble
then again training with you sounds
pretty fun maybe I'll tag remember I
think I talked about it oh you're gonna
work out with me they're so cringing so
funny why not if you exist then we can
have a nice yummy meal together your
treat
ah I see what you're doing fine by me
I'm not gonna pass up a chance to pick
the brain of the future queen of Psalm
nothing too heavy all right well we're
just gonna go for the pages
[Music]
but uh on pictures that I already took
and censored everything that's you know
that shouldn't be there
now that sounds like content honestly
it's just so hilarious
I do want to do it
sorry I'm skipping that because I
genuinely I'm sorry but I don't care
I don't care about these two lines they
exchange with each other
[Music]
them all up again eventually anyway
um
[Music]
I think ready for another story
are you ready
I'm gonna throw something into the world
before I go to get some more funny joke
weapons
give me something new
I wonder if I could get up to five
Rarity but uh I really have to throw in
something good
so I want to
sacrifice
[Music]
already brings us to two
what could throw in the brim Slayer
nobody's using it anyway
[Music]
I feel pretty good though with two stars
how about this
[Music]
uh-huh
we do have this Killer X plus one that
he's not really using because we're not
using him but I don't know I feel bad
about throwing away a killer weapon
um
ah can get rid of this L fire
maybe this one too now we're at three
stars
hmm
I wonder if this tiramis storm is any
good
and I wonder if it makes a difference if
you're throwing a physic with one charge
or with 10 charge
you can't really see the difference here
fortify oh no no no I'm not throwing
away at fortified we're gonna rescue
[Music]
I want something good
fracture no
oh
charges don't matter
L fire oh if I throw in an L Fire or the
chances really high to get a tiramy
storm
is that how it works
[Music]
but I don't want I already saw them I
want like a joke sword weapon I think we
haven't seen that before
no
um or a joke dagger
[Music]
oh I know I know the value determines it
but I don't even know what's good and
what's bad to throw in there and I don't
want to throw in the really good stuff I
need the really good stuff but
still
[Music]
a fire is a really good tone
oh yeah
um but you know I'm past that now I
don't need so many
[Music]
dude we have like a joke uh ax
I'm gonna throw in this iron great ax
plus one
[Music]
oh no the lollipop is a joke weapon
how about this one and
um
oh wait you got the spare plus one we
should switch that out
[Music]
I can't do that
can I
[Music]
I guess that makes sense with the
chopping
I thought it was like a stapler so
[Music]
I only have one more slot I want to get
up to four at least
not right as vain
[Music]
but the worms layer
we can still come so bad right like the
shop is selling wormsler if I really
need one we can buy one back but I don't
really think we need them
I'm doing it
do it I want to see and I want to see
the funny stuff
kind of stinky that was fun okay okay
good people really don't seem to be too
enthusiastic about the worm Slayer nice
okay
I will be surprised hopefully next time
bye bye wormsleya bye-bye
what's next we're going to land again
and people said next one is really tough
it's not that far
give her a port
the vine dragons Army arrives at a
lively illusion Port after fending off
attackers at sea
sounds like nothing's gonna happen
[Music]
click
making good use of everything
[Music]
any rings that I should switch any rings
that make no sense to you guys
I feel like
uh I don't like using the great Aether
I'm sorry
I kind of want to switch pennant but but
the weapons kind of make sense on her
the urban and the hammer
Ray give Yuna called Korean
okay
Corin I believe in you
[Music]
um
for Vantage give Leaf to pennant
who I compare it for Wrath
[Music]
I come back so good without grade over
huh okay what does rap do again
Lucina
Lucina sure why not
[Music]
if either Ike or life to planet
what what for Selena we have life empty
right now but uh
foreign
is better off on a mystical unit
yeah hmm
[Music]
so they can set fire to stop enemy
approaches and debuff enemy stats with
one to three range foreign
[Music]
I know I've been using her like that
anyway but
um
[Music]
which still sea level was the hardest uh
so far
I remember struggling a lot with the
soaring one I don't remember the ones I
did on stream anymore if I struggled
with them
because MC already strong
it's true Tiki leave it to me I think
that actually matches well
they they match well in terms of skills
and so on and then Celine is already in
charge of healing a lot and then she can
give people second age people
hmm
sticky acute
so then for wobble I guess we could give
one more life Leaf left
should we
[Music]
current on them seem really strong spawn
stage hazards
life is useless don't say that poor life
no
um
[Music]
we can take a bile off again
although nah I think I prefer having
Bala from someone else
so that someone else can call this dance
me possibly that I'm seeing
but if we just took away a really good
emblem from kiwawa because koala is
already so strong then why are we also
against giving her a less good emblem
maybe it's fine to give her a less good
emblem
because she is already so good
[Music]
it'll guard are we going back to
edelkard I did that before I had a
little guard on me the whole time
[Music]
okay fatal guard Count On Me
I am ready now she's cursed with leaf
I don't even know why you guys say she's
bad I don't know is she really
what does Hector do again Storm's eye
wasn't that pretty good
I could give her Storm's eye because I
don't know I I don't think I'm bringing
um
that dude
with me
Hector makes
a lot better oh okay
okay yeah the game has a lot of goodies
I'm just gonna do it like this yeah
return the battle guide with Kiwa
oh
there oh whoa
I have returned story yes held the
report to Lord sambron go
bet he was mad we lost the Rings huh
very
knew it so he's gonna punish us he must
have think yes let's go it was a
scolding nothing more
he impressed upon me the gravity of our
role that's all
he must really love us feels good to be
appreciated as lady Vale woken up yet
this is getting Reckless we should
dispense with the magic for now allow
her to return to normal
lord sombron gave me an enchantment a
decent person
for her to wear
a helmet imbued with his power that will
amplify the spell I cast on her finally
I can erase the defect from existence
I intend to use it shortly
I would like to have some good news from
my next meeting with Lord sombron
speaking of news our warships ran into
the Divine dragon's forces no luck
stopping him
sounds like they're sailing to illusion
as we speak huh moving faster than I
expected yeah
[Music]
what he even looks like a good character
of course they're so good of YouTube
maybe he's the next one to join us can't
have you going all alone
you'll accompany her won't you
very well
no you need to be babysitted little
child of course but you'd achieve even
greater things I think it's very likely
to well out of these four all the more
praise for me then right
one thing
try not to be unpredictable challenge
then we depart
will be back before you know it
okay
they're coming towards us
ah Mafia he's way too attached to that
other Veil yeah that makes it doesn't
matter he's gonna defects and won't as
long as he stays in his place the four
hounds are my family
love Mafia oh you play too many You can
predict everything yep yep but I mean
this game in particular
what lady Vale said about having a
sibling is just very predictable
that Dragonstone of her something about
it being even for someone broken as
dense as me yes exactly we need to look
into that
the situation bears
examination and I did predict that mommy
would be evil but
um turns out I was asking too much from
the game
too much like
intricateness
it was way more simple than that they
just kill her off immediately
here we are I didn't like the free
hassle story more yeah even now I say I
wanted it to be better defended in the
beginning we just sailed right in I was
already saying that in the beginning and
then people were like
[Music]
it was a chance I gave it a chance and I
still say free houses the better
what's wrong this is a port town it's
typically bustling with people
why is it so quiet
I see someone over there
maybe they can tell us Divine One wait
that's
using magic That's Heavy on what is the
corrupted easy peasy yes
and surely not the only one here you're
right you're you they must have spread
through the whole town which means I
also want my friend mile Mark which he
came One Day dragon mean to destroy
illusia too
that makes no sense all I know is we
can't turn a blind eye we've got to get
rid of them this map was toxic wink we
move on poison what and abandon the
people here
precious Ivy tell us what you want to do
we leave this place
but there are people in danger we have a
responsibility to help them that's what
we did at Flora isn't it
we got there right after the attack
there were people to save look around
we're too late
far too late
there aren't any survivors
I would have wished nothing more than to
help the people here
but with every passing moment more lives
may be lost elsewhere
we cannot waste our time on the debt
we must protect the living this is
terrible I don't think I could abandon a
town like this but
it's not my decision
that's the choice Princess Ivy would
make Divine One
impressive he knows that was thank you
for your support Divine One
now
to the castle oh you're gonna cut it on
just like that who's there I guess so
makes sense oh hello okay
that's me your old pal Marnie
oh and Mario's here too we meet again I
really wish you decided to stay and
fight the corrupted would have been so
much easier but the Divine chicken's
afraid of them
what isn't that right
[Music]
what did you just say you little
the Divine Dragon was thinking only of
what's best for everyone
again I'm a Divine Phoenix not you too
please not YouTube oh yeah yeah whatever
will ya you're annoying me excuse me you
little I will show you a long time
ago and I won't let you just walk away
wait how's this for a deal drop your
emblem rings and you can go
I don't think so we figured for the shot
though right well time to fight then and
don't worry we brought lots and lots of
the corrupted just for you tell me one
thing first please I need to know what
bill is she all right lady Vale she
[Music]
our lips are sealed
tell you what when this is over I'll
whisper it into your dead little ears
how's that we'd hope to learn whatever
we could from the people of this town
but with no one left alive we're glad to
get the truth out of you one way or
another
she has challenged me
I will teach her a lesson I will spank
her with the chakra
what's it called
and then she will go Ami Mia
mavier take oh zephia permitted us to
use
[Music]
yeah you did what Marnie when this is
discovered oh that's why it means toxic
scolded punished please for Lord
sombron's favorite besides if I capture
even one more ring imagine the praise
I'll get I'll be a hero
case he will not forgive you
the lecture okay just put it on if you
ruin my chance to shine I won't forgive
you
oh okay
that is a lot of poison but in theory
the map looks easy
[Music]
um
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten and twelve okay I have 12 units
oh I'm coming straight from my ship
kind of annoying because
apparently I have to go around here
unless I can fly
okay so in the middle I think I'll just
put
flying units
I really care about the bomb or should I
use it maybe I should at least once one
person
maybe a flying unit wait the bomb can be
used by anyone right
nothing
um
if you did call me Divine yeah
time to show that pipsqueak was busted
he was still being too nice
one tail chocolate
huh
I mean like this one
[Music]
doesn't matter if we just go down the
middle no
what is this one
oh we can save another house
okay I actually two
um
what do we have what are these wolves
move night
heavy armor
worm and I just uh I don't I don't think
I brought a worms layer
oh wait I could still bring it
[Music]
I didn't get rid of the wormslayer right
did it wait was that the thing I got rid
of where we said oh we don't need it
oh yeah oh well nice thanks for not
warning me
it does not work I am
wrapping yeah yeah ironically the worms
layer doesn't work with the worm
which is what the
explain that to me
aren't they all Heavy Armor
foreign
[Music]
oh they look so heavy
I just went by Design
there's a recordable unit
could it possibly be more the air
I have a feeling
I've Got a Feeling
and I'm gonna recruit movie yeah it's
not him
it must be someone with a name
oh wait this isn't you
his friend already
this one is already friend
[Music]
o
she's gonna be rightful of
perfect waifu material for uh what's his
name the guy from the beginning
[Music]
okay well we'll just talk with emcee
um wait oh she's stuck here interesting
no no I'm not bringing Linden what the
I'm sorry but no
I will bring Michael
and besides that
um I might just keep the same team again
sorry I kind of like just feel fine with
this team
uh Chris can too okay
um
[Music]
so I said flying unit should be it
down here
and do I have another one
yeah
perfect so everybody but Alia who I
can't switch anyway
can just fly up straight up top and
I might want what do I even need two
um archers there's not a single flying
unit
I might leave fogado behind what do you
think
Warren would help
I could prank someone else
[Music]
um
dancer
shade
sit down okay I almost don't like that
sure see that logic
fire fire fire
see those should always be on the field
every month
there's a little leggings that possibly
uh
okay we can bring Cedar sure
see I'm bringing him from believable uh
what ring for seedel what do we have we
have life
or what if we just kick out fogado's
ring is by left
oh
[Music]
life
bye love welcome goodbye love to someone
else though
I don't know man
that's what I was thinking
let's keep life please sorry
and then buy left to someone else who
would appreciate it
maybe it's the
old memory I think I want to give it to
her
she deserves a good
emblem and I didn't really appreciate
having secret before
no need
um there silence I'm ready
[Music]
what do you think about this
you'll see that last portable hit also
breaks oh
I want to save
you scare me with that statement
[Music]
yeah it'll be fine it doesn't all have
to be absolutely perfect internet
wait but we the Flies are still in the
middle
oh wait oopsie one more thing
I don't think we should have the dancer
here we should have panette in the front
like this
and
yep
[Music]
it's not the problem experience if you
don't spend 30 minutes preparing I feel
so bad though like because it's on
stream and I know it's kind of boring
sometimes if I do this too long
okay one more time
I hope we're good
I hope I have everything
that I need
yeah
Divine One the flame cannons with those
you can burn right through that miasma
yeah but how fast
the place is infested because I've got
no choice but to cut my way through
these moldering bastards hey I'll help
you let's go I shall help you
I really can't go that far that's really
stupid
[Music]
if it takes longer you will have to redo
it or just having time I guess you could
say it like that a hit
so all right so where do we start
there's uh like only a couple enemies
here but I'm guessing that
if I if I am here in the middle won't
they come up to me anyway
if they really wanna
I don't know if it's worth it to split
like that
[Music]
also it's not poison it's just the
asthma
mavia warps enemies
should I oh well I mean there's a house
here so we should take care of the house
[Music]
and I can only almost reach
maybe I'll just send like the bottom
team down to the bottom but not no one
to the top because there's not enough at
the top
and for rescuing the
[Music]
um
the villagers what do you get again just
exp or an item or what was that
or just honor
no houses
an item
[Music]
am I okay uh this one this piece is free
okay
I
hmm I shall wait
I'll go I'll go downwards I don't care
I'm sending some people down after all
I guess
[Music]
I'll send her to
is it bad what did you guys do did you
send them all for the middle
does she know I guess I don't know
hey what should I know
of course I don't know remember what Ivy
said what did Ivy say
that is that they're all dead
and it doesn't matter
yeah but I thought that since there's
houses to rescue apparently there are
or is it gonna be like a thing where I
go up to the house and just says they're
dead
hey I thought this was like a surprise
like exception like hey there are still
some after all
yes
okay but even ignoring the house I was
still thinking like
maybe one group can be down here for
killing these mobs
reward ain't worth it maybe I'll just
get their Corpses
let me cook I guess
we'll see how it goes
[Music]
shall we dance shall we dance oh wait
there's another Cannon here
useless
should I dance
[Music]
she could reach the house
huh
Sherry dance
[Music]
so
what's gonna happen
[Music]
uh
uh I could just undo this
[Music]
I think I will will I really need all 10
charges
one of the enemies has an item which one
what item
it's just a
a healing item
are you not that strong yeah but I
already moved everyone
I'll have to take all the damage
first
[Music]
don't like that
I don't know if I'll even dance because
[Music]
um
could just love the safe oh
what we never needed all 10
uh thingies so
[Music]
okay
no we need all rewinds
nah come on just one
did you just say it
no no he didn't
I don't know about open the other one
opening the other one maybe that one has
a better item but
I will go here
[Music]
yeah yeah you said come and face me
yeah okay next As You Wish I'm gonna not
there will I regret you spaghetti
whatever you need
you guys didn't tell me so I'm just
gonna do it ciao
wait that again is actually useless
[Music]
oh wait I can't talk from here right
are those boxes gonna be in the way
[Music]
oh I have to go this way I think
I will obey
sweet
thank you
at least one person who listens to me
[Music]
my hotels are so weak
that's what I'm talking about
[Music]
should I
equip her El fire instead
because she's gonna attack back with the
thunder right when people attack her
but most of the time I know it has
rained but most of the time it's kind of
unnecessary
don't think that really
yeah more damage better
[Music]
on that case
Thunder does like nothing
[Music]
wait how much does foreign do on him
oh and almost killed and I only take
seven
holy wait can foreign work from uh
one more step back I think so
yeah
oh
okay now
I'll finish them off there
uh
better to do oh this one
Ivy is busted
oh yeah and there was another tangent
that I also realized I forgot to tell
you guys about but I feel like I want to
show you
with video footage
it's about the choreography parts
I wanted to tell you what parts I came
up with oh
oh they're healing each other again what
parts I came up with from from the 3D
horrible
he warped someone but we're too
[Music]
damn it
whoa hey please don't kill her so soon
connect please
[Music]
right in front of stuff here oh okay
all right all right
they're all coming towards me anyway so
I guess I don't have to rush towards the
middle thank God
first just bait them all
um I'll bring her
to the middle
oh wait I can even attack there's
someone right there
hmm
[Music]
sleep now
yeah girl let's go I have to stop you
not find cannons
[Music]
um yeah I guess not I don't know
not for now I mean I could again wait
[Music]
could oh I could get three of them
the crits feel so good
so sad that fire can't kill though
[Music]
um kind of unfortunate
what about engage
[Music]
thank you
what's efficient
effective I mean
great night well that's heavy armor what
the hell
[Music]
at least I mean that breaks
is pretty good
the sword breaks but I can just use both
on the laughing
if I may
yeah
holy Maui that is a cute meatballs too
even
[Music]
oh wait I should dance
let's do that again
[Music]
we can't but we can finish with panette
I guess
if you could talk about your notes
taking journaling somewhere and try and
struggle myself
I don't do it during conversation I know
it's after
[Music]
like during like vacations and trips and
so on I just like
after
um eventful day I just check out my
phone and then write everything down in
short words but honestly it's really not
pretty like I I really like how some
people keep up really pretty journals
are you for real
[Music]
you feel real quick
yeah I'm keeping I guess I'm keeping
some sort of a diary but only on days
where something interesting happens
[Music]
sucks wait ah she has icons
but I'm not standing in the miasma here
but he's standing
full death rest Plus 20.
but
but if a crit on zero happens
doesn't it just stay zero I don't know I
feel like then it would be better to go
for the Revenge it also has a high crit
ER where's gold Mary
she's down there I didn't see her
um she can't do it but she can
[Music]
break
no no she can't okay
I thought the sign says it can break but
the
it
the tax below doesn't show that it
breaks
[Music]
oh I need to do at least one two
um
wait then if I take a step back and I go
spare it still does a chain attack right
yeah and I don't get damaged back think
genius absolute genius
allow me
and then finish with connect
[Music]
anyway so yeah I saw like YouTube videos
and stuff of people keeping really cute
girly journals and I have like all kinds
of like cute stickers
and stuff that would work for that
but
please work right yeah okay but I'm
never using the presses I have so many
cute stickers that I just taught
whenever I saw them somewhere
[Music]
but I never use them
but yeah so
I don't even want to see my journalism
it's just like
really rough notes of
uh
yeah whatever happened
it's not too interesting
[Music]
you could rewrite your notes in general
well it's not even like worth it once I
tell them on stream they're useless to
me
[Music]
I really don't need them after that
I wait
[Music]
I want a dragon vein but I wonder if I
should do it in the middle of the fire
but afterwards no but nah wait doesn't
make sense the fire will go away
afterwards anyway if anything I should
Dragon vein in here
[Music]
they exist solely for the content you
but I don't has anyone ever mentioned
any other whole life en members that
they do that
I feel like I'm the only one doing that
like so
what's the word
regularly writing down everything you
have good memory if you can recall those
changes from really rough notes no no no
no no no no no no
of course I can remember if I write down
like some notes easy easy
[Music]
I think one big reason is just because I
do really long streams
and some of the streams have a lot of
like downtime too
so I just want to make sure that I have
something to talk about to make it more
interesting but it's a bit more boring
and also
generally I always say people thanking
me for telling them stories
about what we do and I I totally can see
why you guys are interested in that kind
of stuff so I wanna
make sure that the fun things we do
offstream are also shared if you guys
I think that's important oh
what a waste
and she's like I think I mopped by
everyone
unless she moves back after
also she can get hit back
I'll just move back after
I might have to stand in the fire drill
yeah the notepad is merge when
none of my priority list
[Music]
yeah yeah I reckon you guys like hearing
those
stories so I will continue
doing the thing
[Music]
thank you yeah
engine pad good merch ideas
hence the main attraction the games are
just a bonus apparently yeah
so she doesn't take damage from the fire
yet
I could have if I kept yunaka around I
could have changed this
area
oh well
um
why doesn't that do any damage because
he's in the miasma
okay I want to say
what the Sauron do
[Music]
attacks area with fire wind and thunder
Magic
[Music]
sorry do nothing my God
should bait them out of there I have to
[Music]
do it
I can't say I can't awake don't say that
[Music]
corn I want to use do you knock on this
turn
cuteness triumphs
so indeed
[Music]
uh
I was about to ask like who else comes
talk to her
Prince volquest am I glad to see you hey
I got Princeton's letter about heading
to illusia figured you could use an
extra Soldier I appreciate your coming
here I'm sure diamont and the Divine
Dragon will as well how are you on the
other Royal
stats eh the Castle's plenty safe I've
even been doing something for a long
time waiting for our King I apologize
that we weren't able to return his body
to the castle
will not bring further grief to Proteus
people
I will see that my brother returns alive
know that I've got your back I won't let
one more drop of proud brodian blood be
spilled
[Music]
I'm over level for this it should be
fine but
yeah I would be confused like for people
who don't have the DLC
you know they would have to do
skirmishes and stuff in exchange I do
The Parallax so
no
[Music]
I wanna reach that dude
all right I can bring it on
oh nice
nice warped a little fire damage I would
say
[Music]
uh confused because of the request
really
anyway
[Music]
yeah I think
if this isn't sufficient then honestly I
don't know
it would be I would have to like really
grind squirmations but if the game wants
to wants me to do that then honestly
it I'll have time
it was pain in the yes that
yeah I'm not really level one
[Music]
that game doesn't encourage branding
skirmishes well thank God
[Music]
anymore what you gonna do hmm
so convenient they don't even have to
move even though they're on a horse
they could totally reach me without
being warped dude waiting
that one was right in front of him
oh oh crit ah
good job though oh no oh okay okay
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm not gonna set everything on fire
again
I think I won't
[Music]
yeah I've been as op
P absolutely op but we need uh somebody
to heal her
what stuff do you have mending
that is perfect
rough spot for Ivy unknown I'll protect
her just wait
um
just you wait
tomahawk refax it looks like a Beyblade
they both look like a Beyblade
engagement ah okay remind you I want to
I will
I think it's time for
for an engagement to see how much damage
it does on the bus or we should do
doubles we got the double too
no no no no no no oh no
no no no
thank you the one I wanna see comes last
but okay this one has zero anyway hmm
[Music]
it really doesn't do much damage and
most of the enemies
[Music]
can I not just
you literally can't move your cursor
freely you have to go for all this
laughs
clones might be better for now
[Music]
okay let me check for all the weapons
once I get back there we go
no change
[Music]
should I use doubles oh no
oops
I love calling bubbles uh doubles
yeah well I mean I feel like we're all
just like waiting here
here I guess we can wait here until he
warped every one he could
hmm it's kind of boring
uh give me something to do
work more than one please challenge me
[Music]
um
huh
person I like Blossom better
I don't even know
I don't I wasn't I mean I watched it
sometimes but I wasn't like the biggest
fan of it back in the day
[Music]
I watched it when I could
but you know
[Music]
I could
attack from here but not worth it cause
what the smart
[Music]
basically just bait everyone to where I
want them to
and like
[Music]
if I go here
no not with her at least
grant me yours
I Cannon can erase some milk yeah but
only want to do really close ones stupid
if someone can reach it now
be nice
can't can't
only if dance
[Music]
okay that's it
and
I should go as far as possible yeah but
um
they'll get damaged now too
[Music]
we're back yeah
right a clear yeah
okay I'll use it um
a little bit further ahead
[Music]
oh it still hits both
sacrifices have to be made
the oriented looks closely enough ah
I See Fire
inside the mountain
[Music]
this just seems like a waiting turn to
me
[Music]
they'll go for the
decoys anyway
maybe I'll send someone else here as
well for help
[Music]
okay
oh
I thought he was just gonna work
although you know Noble NPCs
no he warps
it's fine with me
time
okay
damn
[Music]
normally my doubles are pretty you know
um
you can make a lot of damage usually oh
I mean when I say take a lot of damage I
know they have one HP but I mean they
often uh Dodge
foreign
that she just did
[Music]
oh my God they're lining up stickers
would have been perfect
turns 40 of lost ice cream to damage oh
oh that's sick
nice
[Music]
did I bring no healer down here that's
really unfortunate
[Music]
my resolve is unchanged
fine by me
[Music]
you
silver x o p Ah 67 72 67 62 67
ah
great day for
should I stand right here for it
[Music]
why should I um
here Mandy
maybe here
but
yeah yeah maybe here
she will die from chain
not next to measma
[Music]
here
she she has a second HP bar guys
[Music]
she'll be fine
but I'm not sure where exactly to do it
they will let me I made here they will
come over to me so
what wait does it happen
after they all come over to me or before
I forgot
I'm gonna do this at the end for rewind
okay
[Music]
they got to move first
um
[Music]
that's also rough
I know it's risky
[Music]
I know
ah
[Music]
I wanna go back as much as possible but
that first minus 20.
it's my ah
[Music]
even if I go here she's in range anyway
use your Alice to block her off yeah
yeah I will look I can do it
Shield Gambit no just no or maybe even
engage wait
Dimitri Dimitri
just normal attack
don't worry I will protect you Celine
with my life
I won't forget you
she's so dead don't say that she'll be
fine she'll be fine
can they go around me
look they can't come here can they
they can't go
I don't think so and I'll just have to
protect her on the other side too
like down here
it'll be fine
pythagore units can shoot
five
maybe they won't even go over
[Music]
let me cope
I really should have brought a Healer
down here
[Music]
so what if I
put her here I feel like the algorithm
would prioritize the two front people
and Pinette
[Music]
oh yeah Celine is the Healer
are we winning
or definition of winning
[Music]
leave space for grade eight I was gonna
move her like here maybe for the great
answer
[Music]
I mean panette would go here
or you can dance with Philip oh
[Music]
the hammer or Raven
Reuben gives me Restless brain but the
hammer
is good against armored
and I might have some armored people
around me
[Music]
even cooler
yeah yeah I think um hammer yeah
we're having splits opinions again
Hammer they don't have magic
okay have it it's habit time
I might have to undo all of that but
you I will never give up
so
[Music]
what are we gonna do here
um
many things can be done there's four
units right in front of me
[Music]
wait where is money ah she's here she's
she's still kind of far
foreign
[Music]
effect redo last 20 minutes
no also that felt longer than 20 minutes
yo there's been so much cool Metroid fan
art Metroid fan art
it's so cool Chihuahua cosplaying
Metroid
not Metroid Samus
[Music]
It just fits so well I love it it was
like so many good ones
yeah make me so happy I will definitely
have to use it for film now I think I
also changed the the second streams font
nail
um I just left that one the same because
I was like yeah I don't want to make it
from them now
[Music]
such a perfect match
oh German match wouldn't be wouldn't it
be actually so cool if
Metroid became my thing and then I get a
Metroid ambassadorship and then just
like you know Corona got like a Sanic uh
recolor maybe they can give me an
official Metroid outfit next
that's too much like a life today
full-on outfit not three color is
I don't think that Woods
uh ever happen that's like a lot of
money to spend for a company I think
but maybe I don't know like
collaboration merch or I don't know
something like that would be so cool
no harm in dreaming
um
I don't know how about the Metroid Prime
[Music]
Publishers I guess it's the Publishers
who would decide that how are they with
like
sponsorships today like to collaborate
with creators
do they do that is that something they
like to do
[Music]
it's Nintendo doesn't it I guess
Nintendo doesn't give a about
collabing with me
do they
probably don't
okay I will immediately seize all my
dreams
[Music]
that's right I gotta be um Chris Pratt
yeah yeah true sorry for assuming
[Music]
that I was worth anything
and
emotional damage
thick flameless oh but one HP really you
gotta do me like that
I'll do it anyway
lame Lance does this have some crit
three percent come on come on
[Applause]
yeah okay
[Music]
all right she's the only one who doesn't
have cancer
oh
[Music]
that might end badly too
I wish I could move the doubles
[Music]
good to go difficult positions here
she's gonna die Sophia might die
hi
I'm not playing very careful today at
all I'm just so aggressive today not
healing much
I don't wanna heal
Ivy I think
so
I mean she she really cultures from
um oh wow that damage look at that
[Music]
good wind
I'm overthinking things is that even
possible in Fire Emblem you have to
overthink things that's how you play the
game that was my impression until now
[Music]
okay waiting room
and then
I will do the death
I will just read three oh wait so first
completely unnecessary
Overkill
well done
did you guys see that corn Pizza by the
way what is that place
now with all the corn some American
place I think it was
[Music]
still stuck here
Little Caesars is a joke
it's a joke
why
I thought that was serious
[Music]
it should be real
I would genuinely get it although I
don't think I could get it alone because
I don't think I could finish ever ever
all those corn cups damn
up
no what I oh you know what I shall make
it myself in a cooking stream
they don't really want to do it right
Little Caesar's response to me
to actually make that pizza in a cooking
stream
yeah
and even if they don't sponsor me but
what
I'm trying to most of you hey hey we
don't want to lose our sponsorship
I guess she's staying there
fine I'll do it myself yeah for real
though like what
it would be so nice
[Music]
wait I'll stand in front of her
yeah
that was totally realistic I mean it was
a little bit like
it was definitely
funny but in a good way
unbelievables with me I believed them
[Music]
what is the best corn to put on the
pizza
for me I never noticed there's different
coins
what do you mean best corn
[Music]
I would have bought it yeah me too but
like in a group
with some corn lovers who which should
be like literally everyone because how
can you not love corn
there's yellow and white
[Music]
oh interesting I think I've heard of
that before we only have yellow corn
here
I mean maybe if you would look for it
there might be white corn
but I don't ever see it anywhere
[Music]
white one is sweet
I feel like a
yellow one is also pretty sweet
okay
sit down KFC this might be a oh this
waste no time
can you attack another time
yes you can
oh shoot
I'm sorry Divine One
well at least I moved Ivy pretty much at
the end so I could still easily change
that up what's gonna happen here oh no
why he goes for gold Mary who is Full
House
only free damage okay easy peasy okay
okay okay
[Music]
I still gonna redo it in a way that all
the enemies there die though but a lot
of them just had like one nice piece I
think it's somehow manageable
but we gotta bring Ivy to the back
nice Chloe
music got serious too yeah
yeah so stop the underground EDM club
music oh that hurts though
okay another one for gold Mary
I love gold memory man I didn't expect
that I would use her so much
oh ah that's fine that's fine fun she
has dhp bar and it's barely the damage
anyway everybody's getting in the
perfect
perfect go ahead please you will be
served by Prince tonight she's your
server please tip her well
see no one went for who was it Celine
look look
oh look at this beauty
maybe not that yeah one HP and dead
it was
a wise decision from Pro Gamer
takamasikiwawa
but
um well we'll go back a little bit
because I don't want Ivy dead
I mean even without
we could manage
but let me just redo that okay
yes I see 500 steps ahead I I had a
feeling that it was gonna be fine and
sometimes you just have to listen to
Wawa a draco shield in the top house
I'll think about it
is that really so good
I feel like I already have one and I'm
not using it
um so ivy
how far back should I go
thing
I think really until Ivy Maybe
wait if I go to this point
uh I can is this before she attacked or
after she attacked
I'm confused
I'll crest
okay
hopefully this will be fine
uh
we have two moms that'll be fine
I promise even if she attacks here she
can't go back that much
bring her back let her heal herself
for vulneri
and then
put someone beefy there
yeah
and then uh heal this one from a
distance with 40.
[Music]
should be fine
look up glass gem corn oh is it
invisible corn
a transparent corn or so is it like
really Seafood corn
[Music]
but you know I just really love corn
with butter lots of butter and some salt
yeah
makes me turn into gremlin
I shouldn't have done that
I feel like I thought that she I would
attack first
[Music]
but I
um I won't rewind I'm believing that we
will survive
actually
[Music]
um
zero times two
oh tomorrow
[Music]
why why
okay but I think I would be
less mad about kagetsu dying
then about ivy
thanks
feel that horrible to have on counter
attack all right I'll change that too
late now but yeah
okay
oh
let us waste no time
he goes for
example he got baited
foreign
[Music]
yeah like how this played out
all right
here we go let's look at this marvelous
scene once again
just feels good that's like one of the
most satisfying
animations and after effects of uh and
engage still
a second time so yeah I hope you like
your corn Pizza
it was a thing
Bam Bam Bam Bam
you're done for
you see you handled it
I did not summon with uh Veronica yet no
[Music]
mum
I will not be cut down
yeah you should be healing yourself
that's uh one thing
what
um
again
then the question is what are we gonna
do with these people down here are we
able to do some decent damage
yes
I think panette is gonna like completely
be in charge of this worm I have a
feeling the others don't really do much
and she has two HP bars so
it's the hand ax
she's doing this much damage with the
hand X and even gets a chance for 17
crit
ICS
does that mean I could attack from here
to the snow okay
damn all right all right 17 percent
I'm gonna
create a fan club a Pinette fan club
with a website and everything we need a
fan club
I am officially a fan I mean I'm I'm you
know this whole makeup I have on for a
while now
in my recent phylum streams
because I found such a big liking in her
right away no that was just kind of I
guess because blue thoughts it would
look funny on me
but I think it's Destiny
switching ships no I wouldn't marry her
though but I'm just like I want to
support her she's my Oshi
crit net
change into Warrior I think she's fine
the laziest but surely as a warrior
should also be rocking everything
wow
maybe the makeup infiltrated my brain my
pores from my pores into my brain and
influenced me to
like love her so much but then
what a queen
like that
that sounds completely plausible
Chloe's still the powers in my Game Plus
I can I shall if I can I try I think I
want her to load up here
but I know it doesn't happen until next
turn
I'll just use another Wolverine
okay so what's up here
um
[Music]
honestly now there's too many units down
here
but they're gonna reunite soon
just stay strong up there stay strong
[Music]
that wasn't illusion
who can we
kill easily
I guess
should I even focus on the boss
immediately I have to take down at least
some of his
Little Friends
do some
some cleaning up
yunaka for poison food
oh
sure that's a good idea
you might be a genius
foreign
next turn he will hit strong
no no there's two bosses so even if I
kill him in one round which is not gonna
happen
you ought to what
[Music]
wait yeah
I feel like I want to hit him in his
face directly
yeah but then I mean no okay well you
stop here to do someone else
ah
Safi doesn't have cancer so
it's not much but
if it's a tomahawk anyway then we're
gonna move
step away
be healing not doing
um possibly yeah
um
oh wait I can't even hit him in the
space anyway
that one space
[Music]
I guess I'll do it
nonetheless
okay how much
free
whoa
he's so strong would that be dead if I
wasn't that scoring
no
I can't think I took up one step too far
nice all right it's all right it's all
right
[Music]
um
I'll do this
and then I'll just move back
unless you got poisoned
ow
what is that book He said
just wrap already
so that one double though
so I feel like if anything he would go
for a double again rather than at least
is it go time
it's go time baby
you know what they're engaged
to be healed so she does a lot of damage
here the flame lands
huh
he can't move is he Frozen now what
don't forget you have fortified oh oh
yeah
it's just like
oh beautiful
didn't that leave him with one HP before
and now it doesn't
can't do this
[Music]
I still have a lot to learn
[Applause]
um I think
Hortensia has the AOE Hill right
yeah
but if I do that I have to stand here
but she can counter away she can cancel
away
five radios what if I do it here
yeah yeah yeah you're perfect perfect
ideal
it doesn't heal much but
a little bit to everyone
yo
oh pee
as I am
but I'm not doing much damage here
cool will I use to attack him who will I
use to attack him
still have my Oscars to learn
the I still have my Astros going
[Music]
it really doesn't do much though
if I shoot with Astro storm then I might
stay back here
okay
[Music]
I
I'm just going to yeah no crits
how
Castle
now let's use the killer Bowl
comes out as the same
now I guess I'll use it on this small
we're just really not doing much with
the bus right now unfortunately
[Music]
okay
finish him
how
that is not enough
it's hectored wait Storm's eyes
[Music]
uh I still don't really understand
Storm's eye
does that work
because I don't actually do this damage
right now right that's what I remember
but
it's American Tank
uh
I've been up close
use it if you want her to tank I might
want to tank in this situation yeah
it will be nice to see that in action I
don't think I've ever actually used it
ready and deep but that'll be good
even finish up this NPC or do some
damage here oh let me see what let me
see what uh is that it
so
[Music]
that's so stuck
sorry I'm so indecisive right now I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry
ah
okay
thank you
I'm just gonna kill him this is more
important because even you know
the more in this case
quantity over quality don't want all
these idiots around here
steel sword
yeah don't worry
fortunate
okay okay
and now
um
I'll cancel away after that or should I
use Veronica now
let me see
someone here some is a random unit
that was an ally it's an African ah wait
she also has a damn fool
okay but back up
it spawns right in front of me probably
a random unit like an NPC style unit or
and can I use them or
no Moodle
you can't move after her dance moves
let's find out
just an extra unit
the extra unit that has fun do I get to
use them right away
three or four or five star units
yes
a sword Lance ax or
something that doesn't do any of those
like maybe a magic unit or so
well YouTube
[Music]
or I go blind
I could be both of green X and strong
green I agree okay I agreeing I agree
yeah she was doing that when I was doing
her pillow it looked really easy
who's it gonna be
oh God
how could you be there twice
I already have a little garden
[Applause]
that's so cool
jackpot baby okay hey I'm scared to lose
her
and
she gets attacked
oh I feel like if she does that she's
already gonna die next turn
because she gets so much damage
don't send her to the boss well where
else
here I don't do any damage on them
either so I do the most damage on the
boss actually
yeah let's do it
use me don't fear okay
she'll disappear after and get over oh
okay I'm sure disappears anyway then
what the hell
yeah a crate would have been nice though
a little guard
would have been nice
was he gonna go for oh Halo card and I
still have a double out there
do me a favor and die quick money this
one you cannot turn into a ring are you
sure you want to do this oh what worms
player I'm not a worm though
oh
ow okay
I was really lucky though enemies nice
oh it's going too well guys it's going
too well
that was fun
I feel like in terms of damage
that was worth it I would say
uh I was acting as a decoy as well
buy a horse what the hell what the hell
maybe need another
uh AOE heel eventually but
only these two are really feeling right
now
all right if both bosses are right in my
face though that kind of sucks
it's kind of rough
cookies however
nobody except this one is standing in
miasma right now that's pretty good
[Music]
oh about the flame gamut yeah I'm not so
like
my brain does normally not understand
and I can just use that in combination
it assumes that I can only set things on
fire and then that's it
it turns out I can do more I drag me
where is she
here give me an order
but at the end I would say
Dragon win first
but then my attacks are also gonna be
winning a few people
but the whole field
oh
I'll have issues with attacking too
no no no
Dragon Blast Dragon Blast
but who does dragonflies
it's just some of both applies to when
you attack too
they're not in sport they're gonna be in
the Square
you're not connected to money
here
I don't really I don't really agree with
this
do you guys mean torrential Roar
okay okay well I can't go there though
the chat is confusing me actually we
have learned already the way I do the
things often is also fun
well I'll just do her own thing now
[Music]
I do want to get rid of the fire at the
end though with dragon bling before
yeah
what the is Dragon Blast
you mean
what torrential Roar thingy
but doesn't it do one more time damage
on me before it goes away if not then
okay then I I'm okay I was just keeping
it
do you wanna do you do you do you
Chihuahua way
just like the Almond way
okay okay
uh man that's man I have so many units
down here
[Music]
I'll just start with the lowest side
then we don't have to think so hard
right now
waiting good
and then I'm gonna do like a really
smart thing how are Blues look
she recharges I dance for her
now she can move
oh wow okay wow
[Music]
who can you attack
them up here
oh you're right I left that one
all flowers eventually will
yum
[Music]
here's the other idle guard on her way
to kill anyone stab them in their back
for calling me the Divine chicken when
I'm really the Divine Phoenix
[Music]
I guess I'll just wait here no action
just just talk for now
the gang's coming
reinforcements are coming is there like
wait this is so easy there's barely any
illness left I'm about totally go up
here if I wanted to
but I don't really wanna
I don't care about the shield
no I didn't I didn't get under my skin
at all
because it has no meaning to me at all
so I don't care about things that don't
apply to me yeah please see
even though there's so little enemies
left I still have to think so hard
artist is nice
is just the ideal thing right now but
let me see how much damage
oh
okay
[Music]
I've been engaged with Veronica looks
might be fine oh I didn't even check
until now yeah
I'll put it like Green version that she
had with someone
cleaning up
I could use some tea after that
[Music]
hmm
yeah
she looks like a completely different
person though
pretty well
[Music]
ah zero
stay late
[Music]
I challenged my face
level eight
and forgive me handsome I know this
imposes a burden upon you
what are you gonna do
okay
[Music]
she's still in this defensive sense is
she or was it only for that one turn
me not understandable
no
I feel like it didn't help at all
because no one went for her
the day no one attacked tomorrow
wow
29 what no
I think I'll just do this
that's okay then feels like that's the
most
difficult to engage skill to use at
least for me personally
uh okay
I understood what you meant eventually
I'm just confused
[Music]
maybe he'll miss
that's cool
why are we through good
works well with someone decoy ability
[Music]
hi Charles
then
wherever
[Music]
cooking
18.
I don't know I don't know I don't know
oh yeah she's also there
I'm trying
to strike not that strongly wait
because we're just staying in this one
area that I cleared up
not worth it magic for the sofa but at
least I'm not getting any damage from it
I feel like
okay it's not
the best
wow whatever if this is
I feel like
I already need that heel again
all the other charging plates are so far
I think I'm fortified but I'm so sad I
can't do anything without Chris
do I got exp for doing zero damage
let's see
I do okay
foreign
Apple into their mouths
I'm loving the Spotify
go here and last but not least I have a
little dragon vein this area
so what I was thinking of doing if I
could have reached that point for the
torrential Roar that would have been a
good option too but I couldn't reach
anyway so you know
Brad what's left oh my God
all right
uh you know what I'll take it I'll take
that damage it
what else can you do nothing so my turn
here we go there we go yeah
God
no I don't think they'll they'll make
money take much Adventure look look look
was smart
what's up here
oh cool yeah
[Music]
oh sacrifices have to be made the fight
I love you though sillies don't take me
wrong don't take it the wrong way
I love you though but oh no wait I just
charged her though that's kind of sad
oh wow
that'll be fine
look
very open
Boss bosses have missed and wasted their
turns
isn't the RNG too good on me another man
yourself
nice nice
walk over
[Music]
oh
something why is it true that you always
so overpowered
wait 56
[Music]
what about
um
[Music]
is it better if I do it from here
oh yeah it's it it is it is but she
doesn't um
fully die from it
kind of regretful why does she keep one
HP from this position
right
[Music]
it wasn't the same over here
because who in the beginning said I need
10 rewinds I can totally test this out
and then waste the rewind on it oh she's
even here oh wait it still keeps her
with one HP I thought that I saw Zero
when I was there but I guess it's Roy
doing that trickery
all right
I'll go here anyway
[Music]
that person was actually saying I didn't
need them
yeah really but people always also said
though that this map is really difficult
I am the Divine dragon
even the crib you Roy for holding
me back
Aya she did miss the counter of course
she did
I would have wanted a refund otherwise
[Music]
maybe killer ax
um Chris
yeah
hell yeah
um
all is going well
so
are you capable of this no really
maybe with the killing it
can I get two crits in a row
so yeah
I could use a hot spring yes I can
tell
I shouldn't even be able to Crick my
dances
if I if that was possible
I would make it happen
get two extra moves
um
even with a low chance I would
alright
again
we could either heal again or go full
damage this turn and possibly I don't
think I could really end it and maybe
me no
no
[Music]
I mean let's just see what happened I'll
go with the others first
dude
this one
five times two plus nine wow okay
he will attack back
oh wait this one what am I doing
and this one kills
[Music]
an epic battle all around oh I win this
one
this feels really good
service
all right Tamara
um
ah
I think I'll use tomorrow again
[Music]
I will die
really
that's mean
not nice
how about
[Music]
40 damage
save the Mages for money oh my God
all right
if
he
does some decent damage too but
let me check something
that is pretty decent I think I'll do
that
might end in this turn anyway
maybe we'll even get a
oh wait I didn't use the killer book oh
well strike
it's our okay I feel like we can
do it in this turn
for a fight that looks like one HP left
ah who wouldn't do much damage anyway
because I want to use that person to
just get rid of that one HP
who would do the waste that like that
that looks like
that looks good that looks good
oh wow yeah
fail
you have a best tactician I agree
breaklands
oh interesting
land spill for expert Willows if user
initiative combat attack twice
maybe switch with uh uh I don't know
Revenant is awesome
okay
foreign
okay we can think about it another time
but for now for now
um
hello we all right you will not cough
so concerning that who does the least
damage so I can just get rid of the one
HP
a little bit a little damage
oh
I guess she'll just be Dragon veining
again or or you know what just get some
get some exp down here
I
thought you could kill him
oh man
but it's just this way
and it does no damage
if we get the boss down then this
wouldn't matter at all anyway
in that case
[Music]
and this is so stupid
believe in the six percent crit
watch
and learn
come on okay
okay okay
good tribe
okay now
we just have to take this
down
[Music]
I think the one hungry we have filled
both Mages here and the ax lady
so either Chloe or the ass lady for the
one HP
I know who
who is more capable who is least capable
thanks lady
she does have a tomahawk
here
all right I'm using Chloe for it
we gotta do like one more turn and
repeat our mistakes
we'll be fine
I'll show you we mean
wait does Roy again give her one HP
at the end
um
[Music]
elfire is the only useful thing
but she'll kill me 45 percent
45 percent
that's pretty high
how long have you been doing this fight
yeah not that long
I be first
and she doesn't even take that much
damage
thank you
wait but she's gonna sit
one HP right
even if
I get her down on her knees
oh and then my remaining actually does
zero damage
Maybe
if it takes us another turn anyway then
I prefer to take this
exp and let's change below a threshold
but it seems like she's getting that one
[Music]
I'll take the EXP
in this case
[Music]
does this do anything no
not worth it
going back
drinking elixir
block of oh oh
well it's fine this is the last round
last turn what's that ow I won't be much
use in this sorry Chloe
some people had to die
attacking from there
did they get stronger
these mobs
come on look at all my units here
Okay who wants to do the thing hmm
the kiwama do it
wow we'll do it but wait first we kill
that other mob too
yes that she will pay
I will teach her a lesson with my holy
chancla
personal
it is personal
taking you personal
say the word
can you do at least this
wow I'm so proud oh for so soon
any other exp to gain no I mean I know
I'm missing that item but whatever
oh wait yeah this one this one this one
this one I'll be okay
can you do
Kevin
think whatever you like I see you
my spy with my little eye
[Music]
a chicken that's going to the usual room
and the final plastic
[Applause]
[Music]
hopefully you will learn a lesson you
little
hmm
was that goddess icon
explained
finally
um
[Music]
only eight turns again lucky eight might
be my lucky number
and panette again MVP in
jury
I'm just a big finger rings they took
the Rings Connie we must Retreat now
he's like a bed to her right now
yeah and after all your nonsense about
being exempt from scolding
now let's hurry to Lady Vale wait tell
me is Veil all right we're just having a
nice talk there a new kind of magic to
use on lady Veil if she does the true
lady Veil will never awake what do you
mean the true lady Bale the others think
this is a happy outcome
but I
I have always worried for her safety the
sound really didn't want to protect her
don't you
I have said too much
Marty I am returning now with or without
you
not only by me we took back the Rings
besides I have a feeling that Vale is
going to need him right at her side oh
emblemakaya emblem Roy oh
never lost faith that we would return to
you
[Music]
in this Kingdom
Sovereign blood is no longer enough for
him he's abducting the people the
feeling when Sombra drains them they
turn into the corrupted close
[Music]
song brodia firenay
they'll all suffering oh yeah now I must
act now if any of my people still remain
I must do all I can to save them those
two came all the way here to stop us
from reaching illusion Castle the four
hounds must be desperate to keep us at
Bay
let's find out why
ah
it's already 9 30.
62 hours now up to 64.
six more chapters left oh maybe finish
next week
although six
I would have to do some longest dreams
maybe three chapters per stream
seven more not six
three streams at least I can
I go finishing I can schedule it three
times next week with my most
oh
[Music]
um I'm taking Monday off
so I could
because my brother is coming over for
some job interviews
and
forever take that day off then because
he's also helping me build some
furniture
you know
he has like four job interviews on
Monday and Tuesday
he told me
yeah I hope I hope one of them will take
him come on please
please
so
um okay so I'll be reading super chats
after this
maybe on Monday I can do some
hi owl
cute Monday maybe I can play another
parallelog but
[Music]
um
I don't know if I can really do all of
them until the end
but in terms of like bracelets and rings
I don't feel like I need them all
would you say guys
[Music]
I have plenty now like
so many to choose from
one more could be nice too but
[Music]
um I don't need them all okay
but I don't think I really have the time
to do a parallelog on stream
I'm glad if I can
testing already 64 hours in this if I
can uh finish it soon that would be
noise
yeah ring wise I feel like I'm plenty
um served also so many tattoos
come on
[Music]
and after you're done with the story you
could still do Parallax right so just if
I want to play some Farmland privately
afterwards
go through some more I'm assuming I can
do that yeah okay
how long to beat says it's 40 hours 40
hours from here
[Applause]
[Music]
the more
um
you plan on doing DLC Corner that's
coming next week
probably not
[Music]
um
did I just do chapter 19.
I don't know I haven't been really
paying attention to the numbers
on standard difficulty
yeah okay then probably really at least
free streams
unless sent to an endurance which I
think is too exhausting
we won't do that
[Music]
but the end is near
a long long Fire Emblem Journey
[Music]
but it feels like it's been going on
forever but in terms of like Stream
parts this is only the eighth one not
even that much
many long long screams
gonna be a bit sad
to finish
uh
this already
but it'll be good to move on to other
games
[Music]
again
just because I just they're throwing
jrpgs at me left and right
it hurts
I'm getting migraines
I hope that by the end of the year we're
not like running out of games to play
but I feel like
[Music]
oh yeah
okay let's see what the well gacha will
bring us I want something new
not the horse poop
chocolate it's a chocolate bar and they
literally gave me a silver sword I feel
like I put some sort in there
yummy looks good
I've been eating a little bit too much
chocolate these days I need to stop
also my usual breakfast is back which is
you know pancakes with the
chocolate spread and now I am I am
stopping with the strawberries for now
I'm just having bananas instead so
chocolate banana crepes for breakfast
basically
daily
see nothing wrong with it
it makes me happy
I need so much kind of chocolate today
me too
[Music]
maybe be support oh I'm not sure if I
did
I like peanut butter and honey crabs for
lunch
I don't think I'm a big fan of peanut
butter but I haven't really
tried it much in my life I mean the last
time I tried it was a long time ago
maybe my taste buds changed and now
maybe I would like it who knows
there's like one
thing is it on the top or in the bottom
I think it's up here oh yeah ready
I'll do the support some bonds
um after or before the next stream
so let me save
I guess that's it for today we only did
two but lots of story progress
it's all right it doesn't really get
much faster than this
foreign
[Music]
nice engaging thank you sorry I didn't
have too many
engines
[Music]
I mean I kind of did but
the six hour stream already
[Music]
those Dodges and crits were incredible
today I feel like I was luckier than
usual
even with my slightly Reckless
strategies but
it's not Reckless when you know it's
gonna go well
you believe
what's this
oh
[Music]
more like confidence
we played like that because of
confidence not because of brain horde
amazing RNG is truly blessed today hell
yeah anyways got lots of Courts today
too yeah that's true
it was all right
you have good builds the stuff you
cooked off stream what you want us to
hey
sad if we missed the good support
reactions well are you playing the game
yourself at all
if you're like really curious I guess
you could look up a video that has all
the support conversations
[Music]
here's some support conversations
so maternal sophistication is all about
gently embracing everyone
drawing them to you
I get how it works but actually pulling
it off is something else entirely I just
gotta keep observing you I'll learn all
your tricks eventually whatever I can do
to help I hope it works oh but wait
before we get started let me wipe your
face
did I have something on me the heart did
but I took care of it now
thanks Chloe wait that was it
that was it just now I just naturally
trusted you and let you know my voice
without even thinking about it having
you dote on me felt I don't know
peaceful oh did it that's so sweet
unbelievable I can't let my guard down
around you at all anyway let's get
moving I need to see more of this and
can I marry her first huh why on a warm
day like today it's important to drink
when you can oh sure
[Music]
anyone what the hell when is it gonna
like be available
we gotta be a support as opposed but
[Music]
Princess Ivy I was raised in pale Sans
okay I get a ring soon
you said you dislike unknown quantities
the worst idea I'll Grant you once you
come to know how to choose this time no
longer be princess and retainer but
friends and friend it is worth trying at
least
my father has great swordsmanship I like
them
[Music]
have I done something wrong how foolish
of me I should not have presumed you
would wish to hear my unicorns up there
too but forgive me Princess Ivy
I should have noticed sooner it was not
what she wanted no that's not it
on the contrary I am actually
brother please
with me was so important to you
I'm flattered
thank you oh
I don't dislike you cagets I do dislike
unknowns
they make me wary
but that doesn't mean I dislike you as a
person and after today
I think it's safe to say my impression
of you wonderful so we may become
friends soon not the worst idea
okay for me I would say my top five is
hotensia one
Celine
[Music]
Celine tool you're not Capri
Chloe
four
okay it's nice total
but like in terms of everything like
um how to use them in battle how the
designs are how their percent
personalities are like everything
combined
[Music]
um
I think I would put
I don't
I love using planet battle but her
design and her
uh personality are not my favorite at
all
I mean she's interesting but um
it's a bit funky
well Tamara is nice too though
design and personality wines I love
Tamara
but in battle she hasn't impressed me
that much
[Music]
okay so I would say Hortensia won
Ivy is amazing in battle
but it's not my time
cool though
I can't see a one
Celine too
um
foreign
how about
Chloe
Chloe and you're not got free
to remember four
[Music]
iv5
that's my tier list
or who to marry list
connect and gold Mary
something like that oh yeah well trained
hmm
you know Jade
I like her
so cool
something
maybe because she's so slow I just
always like
always lie behind
hmm yeah I do prefer quesada like if we
had to choose between the two for me
like kisawa would be like on the top
level of marriage
priorities
[Music]
turning down Veil well Veil isn't even
near an option so so
you know
[Music]
because Sarah had a lot more story too
yeah
okay Sarah you know like how can you not
love kusara right
she's just
oh I can't even
she's her design is amazing her
personality is amazing her story is
great
she is a great to have in your team too
[Music]
I only have six cards in the game yeah
and like half of them are guys
[Music]
definitely
my waifu
[Music]
okay
so let's move to my office Halloween
dude
I'm
[Music]
hmm I used the fancy dress outfit today
because I figured actually like style
wise
since the colors are a bit darker
and you know panette wears like this
Gothic Lolita style dress
I figured it was kind of closer
where the frick is the chat there
and with this one I can tank off my
feathers
which normally I don't like to do but in
this case it gets me one step closer to
panette
what happened to your mouth people keep
on
hey
I want to look like panette
oh
working one more go okay while we're
here you notice now what the hell
guess chihuahua has been gone the whole
stream today
only
yeah I fooled you guys I guess just
cosplaying
look at the eye color
it's me don't you recognize me by my
eyes if not then does that mean you
haven't been looking at my eyes at all
maybe you should be looking at my eyes
some more
so that wherever you go whatever
I look like you recognize me by the one
thing I can't change my eyes
wouldn't that be romantic eh
when did you get here huh
yeah skeletonized I think Cali would
recognize them anywhere
no matter what haircut I had no matter
what makeup I had on my face
kind of disappointed not gonna lie
oh sure
oh thank you
goodbye for the marry so many good
choices yeah
even though like we're the ones
the ones I don't know actually there's
not so many weird ones but everybody has
grown on me even panette who was the
weird one but she grew on me because
she's amazing she's rocking every
freaking stage
here's another Celtic one guys
oh man
wow
I feel like these nostalgic museums if
you don't use them for a while and then
you do Nostalgia effect is even higher
and therefore
feels like it's healing you
[Music]
like ah it's home after all we're home
this is our home
one year
take me back to debut no please no
please don't take me back to debut
I mean then maybe I could change some
things but
though please don't
no not the microphone
no
[Music]
um
maybe I should just write a comment
with timestamps
uh
of the 3D collab stream to tell you
which part I did myself
come on do it now because I should break
so much
ads first anyway
yeah I could I could avoid so many
problems but I mean even if I was to say
I could
that's not quite true because back then
you know I asked for example well I have
no money to get my own really good
microphone
[Music]
so that wasn't really an option
and then staff wouldn't lend me when
they said there's nothing available for
me to borrow for my streams in the
beginning
yeah what I could have done maybe is
like
um
is that really possible
[Music]
yeah I was kind of on my own for a lot
of things
I still won't get this yeah I mean they
have microphones in the studio but they
just I guess don't lend them don't
borrow them
and back then I didn't even know that
the
Studio they had there was a thing
what if I would go back in time with all
that knowledge then that could have been
an option
um and I guess
um
if I went back with the knowledge that
the microphone wouldn't be good then I
could maybe borrow money to buy a proper
one from the start
hmm
but you know I I was like using it and
then we did the test stream and you know
everybody nobody said anything
like oh maybe you should get a better
one this is kind of bad
nobody said anything
I mean I was audible at least
I figured as long as it's Audible
well what are you gonna do
it's all right I didn't mind your own
bike it sounded fine to me well thank
you
I mean it sounded okay it's to me in the
beginning too
but
oh no
I mean the bigger problem I would say is
like
um
PC
most of the PC problems weren't they
only when I was streaming at manager's
place
was my PC back then in the beginning
also
I was able to play it some games wasn't
it
okay you just reminded me of my Yakuza
what was that before I got the new pc
must have been before
I used that PC for a while didn't I that
first one
even ah because I I didn't get the the
new pc until I moved into that new place
the house I think
that's when I got the new pc
that means I was using it for a while
[Music]
for like almost a year that's impossible
because I was in Japan only for half a
year
and I got the PC before I mean I was in
Japan I was in Holland in Japan only for
half a year and I got the PC before
I left Japan so that's impossible
your memory is betraying you
[Music]
stuff like that I felt so pressured and
stressed out about because I'm like
doing a sponsored stream
an important one from a big company at
that and then
I'm like representing the game in a
really bad way
[Music]
felt so bad about that but like that's
not something I can fix at the spot
in that moment
yeah I thought so too I thought oh
that's the end of me people will never
sponsor me again and now you know people
continue to sponsor me and now like I'm
like one of the go-to
sponsorship people
anyway
so
I think in the end
even when some things were scuffed
sometimes in the beginning I think after
that I always put a lot of effort into
doing my best to represent the games
giving them a good image
being enthusiastic about them
and that showed
[Music]
well Manuel well give me an example of
when my PC didn't have enough horsepower
recently
most of the games I play are console
games anyway
[Music]
so it doesn't matter that's more of a
game capture card problem when it
sometimes acts up
life was fine
I don't care a whole cure acts up on
many pieces though no
it didn't really affect me
yeah I'm not curious like not the PC
fault I would say
yeah it likes for many people Diablo 4
will be a stress test all right well I
wouldn't say that it's like
I mean I'm totally open to improving my
PC it's just like I'm kind of like
helpless when it comes to that but I
have said many times already
in the past months that I would consider
or want to
get a different graphic card Etc I even
talked to my like a friend of mine about
it like I just go
promise number one I'm kind of like
helpless about it I don't know what is
good what works with what Etc
and the other thing is it just didn't
really seem that urgent
and it really isn't that urgent
but it's not like I'm rejecting
upgrading my pc at all
they were also yeah really
unre reasonably expensive graphic cards
for a long time now it's okay so that
one literally like considering it
no I asked my more um it
very friends
friend
like RBF
I'm about it
huh
I'll probably upgrade like a before or
around summer
well Manuel
that is
for just holding on to something that's
two years ago and since then I have
changed my ways I'm using free monitors
I even bring an extra monitor when I
travel now
I even bought a monitor for traveling
and I have a gaming laptop too
um
only free what free is plenty please I
don't I would maybe even add more if I
had more space on this table the problem
is I just can't find bigger tables
[Music]
you guys are just keen on roasting me
I'm using six screens what for real
I don't need more you can start stacking
just like ah I didn't like her setup
though
I feel like her settled I just I
streamed of it like twice at least maybe
three times even I don't know but it was
very uncomfortable for me I don't like
looking up and down up and down so much
sideways is better
maybe the one thing I would maybe add is
a monitor above my middle monitor
this is fine
it's just Overkill then
that would just be Overkill
I don't want another one this is fine
like nobody can tell me that I need more
monitors there's still whole Live
members
who was it some en members told me one
at least and they only have two
so honestly
oh oh yeah and I think some I've seen
at least one Japanese member's place
that only had two monitors too
I don't know who it was but
[Music]
it was fine free is ideal for the kind
of streaming that we do I would say
to not have
to have a little bit more vote clean
environment in terms of windows
four is overkill and I would not change
my opinion on this you got me from one
monitor to three monitors and this is
enough nobody can convince me that I
need more
[Music]
yeah I think two is the best of the day
though I need three at work but I don't
like it
I really I think it really depends on
the positioning of them
no
fourth line she shall not cross
I mean if you think about it I have a
like a phone right in front of me that's
also a monitor
so in some way I do have four monitors
and the phone is necessary there right
there it's necessary I do like you know
I use it for doing stuff like
this this
yeah
so I think it counts
[Music]
you know what I recently uh found New
Zealand Taskmaster
so grateful because Taskmaster
the channel I don't know what their
issue is
but they still don't have like the most
recent two seasons up on their Channel
or so two or I don't know one maybe
why
they're just uploading like little clips
of the seasons they don't even show yet
um
New Testaments are in the UK now
can plant it they have to put it up on
your top
for real they're releasing season 13
right now on YouTube
because I literally just gotta recommend
it on YouTube that's why
for eight eight days six days eight days
ago
Series 13 wait this one I've seen
but well you know not only
but they finally released
oh yeah yeah they've been working on
releasing protein
okay okay I've already seen it
and apparently they're already
at soup soap where is my other two
seasons eh
so now I started watching New Zealand
task monster but on the New Zealand
taskmas Channel I don't know is New
Zealand task monster new because their
channel has only like six clips or so
full episodes while the UK Taskmaster
uploads generally full episodes
generally and a lot of Clips but the New
Zealand talks about the what the hell
why why why only six clips or so I want
to see more
I just recently discovered
New Zealand they have very funny English
but it sounds nice
they have some funny pronunciations
British baking show
baking
maybe it's still going
probably
please
the irony of her saying that is golden
New Zealand accent is funnier than my
accent
in a good way
[Music]
you oh
oh
you want to recommend something again
[Music]
all right I know what all right bring it
on baby bring it on
if you do it now then I might write it
I know you love cats maybe I'm not sure
maybe maybe
but this is not important
it's gonna happen
oh Super Chat
chatting starting from
I suppose
part two out of 400 okay yep
I figured
we love cat do you want to play with a
cat do you want to take your cat to the
last together see them play with other
cats and also you can play with all of
your friends lucky you
oh I love cats but
cat related game
The Strain was nice but you know the
things I love about cats don't really
come across well uh in games because if
I cannot really physically touch them
[Music]
satisfy my cat love
really
isn't that the dragons
where are the cats
what a stretch
hahaha
huh
Ark what survival evolved
cats
I Googled it
[Music]
oh apparently there is
Is that real
I don't think you can actually there's
like some
really rough looking cats
and some like big wild cats
oh yeah that was a big arc Arc Arch I
feel like rust yeah I know I know I'm
aware of that I know but whole life
members were playing it back in the day
before rust
I mean but honestly you've made like
you know stuff like dead space and so on
those kind of
those kind of recommendations Al are
less likely for me to play than Arc at
least so you're getting closer
I I played rust so Arc is like not that
off
but this kind of cat
it's not really what would get me to
play
[Music]
you're continuing ow don't pay us put us
on the menu brainwashers we are proud to
be KFC we don't know why but you deserve
better more scary more Thriller
games I will find for you no no thank
you that's so nice of you but no no no
no no need to find more scary more
thrilling games
no
don't worry that is not what I'm looking
for
ow
trying to help but just helping in the
wrong way
man is on the sacred crusade to make you
play a horn game but art was in the
horror game maybe I should just accept
it and play Arc once and then he'll be
happy
let him cook
[Music]
hmm
he deserves it I would listen and I will
continue
to look at his cooking
what isn't that just like torturing him
making him suffer more and more
you don't have to disgrace for it anyway
oh yeah somebody told me oh yeah yeah
yeah apparently in Diablo 4 takes up a
ton of this space
you have to Dean sell something
Fatal Frame
but he didn't even recommend Fatal Frame
will that really make him happy
he wants to purposefully make me play
things that I wouldn't normally play
that's his kink
[Music]
so
I don't know if we'll ever meet
each other on a neutral ground
Fighter for l
continue doing your thing I will let you
cook
you waited so long or you could have
said it earlier but thank you Al good
night
sorry for not being excited about Arc
but you knew that was gonna happen
didn't ya
I think deep in your heart you knew it
good night
Red Dead Redemption has cats oh
it's the cowboy one right
Wait no that's not
which one is the cowboy GTA
oh it is okay
you found in that one
all maps enabled Arc is over 400
gigabyte big holy
carry all that weight induction
oh wait I should put up the thumbnail
s
here we go
[Music]
no I'm not doing 4K super chats I'm
doing the Super Chat of the 3D
the Showcase super chats reading Super
Chat
uh recent
[Music]
sorry it's late
that's not even that late just 12 days
on the 12th day after your birthday I
wish you a happy birthday
slightly shorter but fun
no I did not get the Wii games yet
remind me on one day before
it is one day it's two days before now
yeah remind me tomorrow
pinky well if you read this in time
before the three years we
each shop closest maybe you could make a
stream out of it like Windows shopping
with chat recommendations did you also
send the superchar to KOMU because she
did exactly that
what are the odds
um
who knows chat may help fund some
choices too hmm
no I mean in the end I could always just
buy like some leftover physical copies
right even after
I mean
maybe that super challenge no this cat
it's a tragedy
a lot of digital only names yeah but do
I want them okay tomorrow tomorrow just
remind me again tomorrow
after Diablo
yeah tomorrow
[Music]
yeah
I don't I mean I think I peeked at a
list of Virtual Console games and I mean
they didn't really feel to me like I
really needed them and wanted to stream
them eventually
[Music]
so okay
was amazing I've been waiting since you
debited for you too dorks the same
together and it was even better than I
thought it would be hope you can collab
with her uh again one day Chihuahua
cover song or something
you
already
got something you normally would have
never imagined
and already
for more
greedy greedy little one one chicken
to my brain don't worry it's there but
not priority at the moment
you know who I need to do a song combo
with first
you know
Sarah Gutenberg
I'm glad I could make you happy
for once
because you always like
sometimes
you're also soon
[Music]
I hope you enjoyed the yunaka vision bye
you're not caught in my brain Unika
Vision project
laughs
I was imagine imagine being on a Unica
Vision screen saying hiya papaya
I would have been so funny
I also have yunaka vision
ah also thanks for your daughter Kobo I
know trip was extra difficult but you
know what trip was worth even with
running around rain and wind
um
oh yeah I think I heard about your trip
you went with someone else right
yeah oopsie but immersion
that's unfortunate though because
enoshima Academy really really beautiful
when the weather is nice
oh but even a cloudy view up there
it still look decent it's so pretty
sometimes like a I don't know a cloudy
dark weather on an ocean is so
hmm
atmospheric too
yeah Stormy can be nice
day one of Expo was also rainiest heck
the line sucks oh you guys have to stand
outside on a rainy line
did you bring umbrella
I think I remember like many years ago
when I went to
makuhari for I think it was for Tokyo
game show
I also had to wait outside for a long
time and it was also raining
so once again
you're just like sharing the same
experience as me
oh and I think
was that to me was that me or did it
happen to a person next to me but I
remember
somebody either me or someone next to me
had like a paper bag
and then for the rain
it just ripped and fell apart
in the line
oh wait I think it was me
because I think somebody then gave me a
new bag like a
like a plastic Birch bag or so
I feel like that happened to me but it's
been like so long so many years since I
don't remember
that was
same thing happened to you
no yeah the back was out of paper first
and then it broke fell apart
from the rain maybe if I'm like resting
it on the ground
and then it's soaking up the rain from
the ground
okay is that really the lyrics it sounds
like it though do you ever feel like a
plastic bag
what why does it sound so accurate
those are the lyrics
drifting through the winds
good as Baxter
how does
[Music]
no I never feel like a plastic bag
drifting through the wind that is not
relatable does anyone relate to that
I mean she was probably trying to say
maybe like do you ever feel like weak
that like everyone's pushing you around
I don't know that's what she's trying to
say
following the crowd AKA I'm back in the
wind
nah that is a terrible mess metaphor I
feel like that doesn't work
going with the flow
do you ever feel like a fish in the sea
following the other fish
that are in the sea
Katie what a stretch I mean she probably
didn't write it herself
okay anyway uh glad you enjoyed it
nonetheless maybe another day you can go
one day when it's sunny
chat
goddess it was my birthday a few days
ago I want to be congratulated by all
the kfb and the goddesses
happy belated birthday
thank you
[Music]
right now I can read your name too
there's a Korean party Minion
over the table
um
I never know that one no
I'll figure that out later
maybe a bowl for now
I never read the Korean part of your
name before
but yeah
once more that's like an in-between
they say the g really harsh most of the
time
I got it right
and always fine but my teacher always
says no when I say o for that one
hmm
I guess it's probably more of an uh than
an o
that's what she's trying to say
I know I already said happy birthday to
rinse Rebels
gosh I'm getting hungry again
anyway
thanks for the rest of my dad and I hope
your birthday was wonderful
thank you for supporting me and drawing
me so beautifully all the time please
draw more I'm waiting
thank you soon and a kiss for you
what are you cooking today I still have
the fish from yesterday but
um I kind of need to make a new sauce
because the stuff they gave me to make
the sauce for the it's supposed to be
two servings but it kind of was so
little that I own I used it all up for
the first serving
now I have to make something
I don't know I hope I have something
fitting
at home to make a sauce
I can have something
but besides that I have leftovers from
yesterday
yeah the fish was so easy to make and
like I didn't even season it much but it
tasted so good fish is easy I only did a
salt pepper
and the lemon and then you know some
some parsley and turbo scrambled all
over
it was so easy the fish is so easy man
fish already has like such a good
taste from the get-go I mean it's like
kind of on the simple side
it's not like overwhelming taste but
yeah
[Music]
I shall make it more often the lemon
does like everything you needed to do
and pre-scale yeah pre-scaled there was
no weird bones in it either
it's a hick by the way from Austria
because we have no ocean but we get some
good fish from our lakes and rivers
so it's not like we have a
big problem in getting fish it's just
like the more oceany
Seafood that we can't really get here
but we have a lot of good fish from
lakes and yeah Rivers yeah yeah
freshwater fish eat
um
oh
I mean more fish
I think I also ordered already something
a fish recipe for next week too I think
I did like three weeks recipe deciding
in a row already in advance so I don't
forget and miss it again
playing Magic oh have fun
those are more healthy than ocean fish
with that clean water really are they
are they
everything
catfish also good I don't think I ever
had catfish they freak me out
just as they should
anyway dominate
I feel like I already saw this maybe
when it came in but whole life is the
best and you are the best wife of a kfb
I love you thank you I wanna see honey
I'm a cosplay quinoa again
very good
but
I feel like her I think she did a crony
cosplay right that was really like wow
and oh can we cosplay
but I also want to see more Chihuahua
goes like
spicy
very good
we'll have a field day
with whole life summer this year
oh
you guys saw right there's like gonna be
a new swimsuit it was announced right
we thought about it before
I feel like they even showed it didn't
they
yeah they showed the winner I think
it was a teaser it's just a concept I
think they showed
just being very careful here
the teaser and not the the video teaser
and they showed like art winners
pink I don't know
they showed the winning swimsuit yeah I
think so I don't want to say anything
wrong but I'm pretty sure they showed it
because I feel like I saw that then them
showing it and people reacting to it
no no no I didn't leak no no no no
yeah they did beer they showed up here
because I guess a lot of you guys missed
it
swimsuit concept yep and the painting on
eel
in case you guys gonna look it up
and got it
need to see this what the heck yes you
have to
you missed it
um
no one tweet from Whole Life Twitter I
don't know
I don't know where it is we're tweeted I
don't know where it is
I really don't know
where do we look it up good question
there's like one person in the chat who
knows about it so help help
official YouTube is full of this
I mean
it's out there just find it
should be on the Ford Fest website maybe
yeah go digging there maybe
possibly there through like oh sorry
from dakoma she linked it huh
right like right now or a while ago
you'll find it guys
I can't spoon bait you no spoon fit
yourself
I'm Gonna Keep I'm a spoon to myself I
only spoon feed myself with the Almond
spoon feeder
thank you
student metal mental Jetty oh
geez
did I just read that name perfectly
oh my God I read it
oh it's the one that says he
um went back to school because of me
um
congratulations to you and to me for me
being able to read your name now and you
for going to school
powerful
ow thank you for the pinky
oh boss I'm sorry I can't go to your
concerts I can't buy tickets because of
the country
what the please kfp enjoyed this
concert instead of me I'll sit outside
and cheer what what about online what
about online oh you're still in the chat
right for Boss because I can't see a
thing
oh
what about streaming could you not
stream it either
hmm
there were like two Services where you
could
stream it from apparently spawn and the
other one
I thought streaming was for every
country
the e-plus was originally blocked but
spawn work right
I hope Al got to watch his first spawn
Maybe
you just meant like IRL tickets
e-plus was even more expensive
um
I only saw problems from equals and
Alice not to let maybe try from Spawn if
you only tried e plus try spawn
spwn
maybe don't give up
it's working
still have time it's gonna be up for a
month
I love you Mamacita see you next time oh
Nelson Ami Mio
Jeff star navigation for the pinky hey
thank you how are you meeting and any of
oh I already I think
I reacted to this already or you asked
it twice
any of senpai's for first time on day
one a whole 27.
no
not really
and I think I met basically Aqua symbol
for the first time
thank you
for real concert
stay true
Mamacita cute
so maybe I didn't
did I
did I maybe I didn't I already met so
many
[Music]
as well thank you thank you
thank you for supporting the
classification
of kfp
a
Canada new nickname
[Music]
wait wait are you saying goodbye right
now
no you're saying you're back
[Music]
wait the pinky sound
ing goodbye because you little
[Music]
oh
give me a heart attack
okay well you said you know don't need
to read a lot I'll I'll look at it
closer next time but damn
almost dropped this egg
I can't even read the whole thing
because it's not the whole thing yet
reply to chat's reaction to the G word
yeah
yeah but you guys are just being over
dramatic and I'm like
um really concerned
no no no no no no no it's different
thank you
[Music]
you guys are just exaggerated
okay let me read that super chats
um what was I Ghostly
um
this was when I was constantly saying
although super chatso too
again
[Music]
from France
ah you're the one who made it all the
video
thank you
[Music]
foreign
one so you moved from Korea to Europe
oh three years already did you learn the
language of the country you moved to
hopefully you picked something up three
years
and fairy I mean I know there's people
who after three years are fluent in the
language and then there's people who
after three years of living in that
country
maybe picked up five words
so I wonder which type you are
thank you very much for celebrating with
it
and yeah I hope you feel happy
and well in Europe I wish you all the
best
thank you for
watching me think European Time Zone
perfect to watch qawwa
so hopefully that continues and you
don't leave anytime soon
I really admire you for keeping trying
it's something I more often than I'd
like to admit fall short in what was
this about
what was this about
trying what
does someone remember
all right I'm not a good example it took
me only like a month
to be able to speak
like daily conversations
I was a little bit of a miracle
the problem with quitting once I start
anything
that's rough Sam
a feather on my face that's not a
feather
I'm getting Kane
look I haven't heard that one in a while
[Music]
flexing
um
very fast learning yes
anyway
I don't know what this was about but in
any case thank you for your sweet words
angel thank you
and well
Maybe when you when there's something
where you feel like
Wanna Give Up
think of kiwawa
and try a little bit more you don't have
to like
try endlessly like me
but just maybe
endure
a little bit more
one more day two more days
depending on the situation give it one
more chance
one more chance than you would normally
do
believe in yourself
um
for the pinky weird I know I love quinoa
but every time you say croissant my
memory gets fuzzy and my hands slower
moves to the answer button
socially work her way into my mind what
do my oceans mean
are you unhappy with that
do not unsup in any case do not unfab I
warn you
don't you there
unsubbing
knife emoji
this is a threat I will shove 50
consoles into your mouth if you dare to
answer
sorry if it was annoying but I just it
was a face okay it was a face bomb it
was indeed a face okay
you have to give me like one quarter
face
forgive me
if you cannot forgive one Castle face
then
maybe we're not meant to be
no it's not ongoing I'm just saying it
because I'm reading all these croissant
chats
ah thank you
silent Nerf thank you for the pinky from
Australia hello fellow Australian as an
employee who has been almost exclusively
uh walking since you left Japan you know
makes sense being able to catch you live
again these weeks passwords has been
amazing just like the early days love
utensil oh
that's so sad
we have a long distance relationship
I'm guessing you are not here now
man
I'm sorry it's time to say goodbye hi
vodking hello silent Nerf from the
future this is kiwawa from the past
I remember when Kathy had a ton of
Awesome kfp
was it ever a ton
I don't think it was ever a ton
but yeah that's unfortunate
but I'm glad you didn't give up on me
yet just because you couldn't watch me
live anymore thank you that means a lot
to me
silentner
thanks mate please continue holding on
strong
maybe one wanna hook and like
lend you a hand to hold on
don't know how he does it
is
Junkie
chunky go
um
yeah
correct
checking
oh
yeah
[Music]
an electric cat apparently don't touch
no touch
I got it wrong again more or less
yay okay
[Music]
thank you
I would see
would see
what is he now muffin eight thank you
for the pinky the last one SWAT said had
two different signed cards and there was
also the starter decks of their own
possible sign cards I was lucky enough
to pull amen's first best card and Anime
NYC but of course I also have yours too
oh thank you
lucky very lucky
thank you for getting the cards do you
also play with them or do you just have
them for the sake of having them
taxi thank you for one two three four
five
orange super chatos
I'm a little late in the sentence but I
was a little taken away during your free
showcase that I didn't know what to say
I was lost for words
your showcase was perfect it was
uniquely you cute funny wholesome
uh
see
and your performances were breathtaking
be proud of yourself like we are of you
it was a long wait but seeing you in
glorious 3D was well worth it seeing the
myth 3D showcase was wonderful
culmination of all the hard Rocky ladies
have put in since debut and seeing you
connect with so many people during your
time in Japan has been a true blessing
now I'm currently packing before I leave
for Japan in the morning making the
great cave pilgrimage I saw to cheer for
you my Oshi I didn't manage to get any
fast tickets but I will still be
cheering you on
thank you man
I just can't wait to see on your iron
outfit I already know your performance
will be amazing if we will be watching
and sharing but more all over the world
so sing your heart out
beat much love
thank you yeah I love my idol outfit
I hope you enjoyed Japan
even when you couldn't
get into the Fest but
I saw even the ones in Japan who didn't
get into it
still had a lot of fun so that makes me
really happy I was worried that you guys
maybe feel like
you wasted your money if you bought a
ticket for the flight before getting a
ticket for the Fest
he was the one who organized the first
watch along in Japan that's sweet
it's nice
he organized the kfb Oscar in Japan
thought that was a combination
nice
and that's what I actually thought
this
is
[Music]
nice
thank you for doing that for the
community very sweet of you thank you
soon I hope you enjoyed it
hopefully next time you can get a ticket
let's try our best
I will push so that they give more
um like make more tickets available for
overseas
um people who come from overseas for a
real live ticket
to increase the number
hopefully also they'll get a bigger
venue
urea of the house right thank you and
teach Elite
that was that
[Music]
any ideally I should read another one
but the new hair one is so many oh at
the alpha talk of day one is also so
many and the Metroid Prime first one was
also quite a lot
[Music]
Let Me Maybe read
um the second Metroid Prime stream super
jump
only those
right now
the Korean one I already read
in the last one last dream
nothing is
this Wednesday is my birthday oh
for my birthday gift I want to get the
honor of sending
thank you for your hard work in this
Ford Fest I'm always cheering you on
from behind
happy birthday
thank you for choosing me over yourself
to spoil
spoiling yourself on your birthday
I hope you left some for yourself
better
my cats are wishing you a happy birthday
too
thank you for supporting kiwawa
please continue now that I'm learning
Korean for real
maybe eventually you can send a Korean
Super Chat and I'll read it
and partially understand hopefully
thank you for the support
um
[Music]
if you opening card packs as for Prime
today just explore check them out for
rooms you haven't been I haven't already
read that I think but in terms of
ayonaki
foreign
in terms of card packs
I think I just saw
uh staff telling like all of us
if we want booster packs and stuff
they
oh the the new ones
they can send them to us
start in the announcements
like everyone not only uh the
not only
the
um ambassador
so I guess I'll get some
and then I can play with my friends I'll
get my own car too
I should have told me this earlier
because they already released them
yesterday didn't they
apparently no packs released yesterday
and well
I'll try to get some but it might take a
long time to arrive
well another thing we could do which I
think I saw some whole life member doing
it this way
um I could have a staff member
open up the packs for me on camera
streaming it to me but it will be my
cards
that way we could do it
pretty fast immediately
and then after it's opened they can send
it to me after that
somebody did that was it forecast Empire
have you seen how much you're selling it
for no
not really
is it selling well
yeah it's not quite the same but in the
end I mean
what am I gonna do that's so much
different
I can I can like tell them you know
don't don't turn it around yet don't
turn it down and then bam
yeah and then that can make staff do
funny things with their hands and force
them torture them
actually that might be funny if you
think about it
the difference from usual might make it
funny like how I tortured the staff
member
in the forecast of announcement stream
I'll ask for it
um
get some good cards
all right all right
um
thank you thank you thank you soon
you may have figured it out by now but
Metroid Prime is more scanning and map
checking and shooting
yeah
maybe that's how it should be but I'm
doing the opposite
yeah yeah I'm gonna read the one from
the first Metroid Supreme stream stream
another time because this one has less
super chance and I just want to get
something done without cutting it off in
the middle of
uh the reading
[Music]
completion's sake
what does that mean but don't worry it's
okay I know it's confusing because the
thumbnails are the same
um
yeah sorry Daisy I hope that's not like
triggering or so
I'll try to check them out more and scan
more but I think
I'm getting there I'm getting there
slowly but surely
it is something
oh you got
to end the city thank you Delta thank
you soon
what's the story behind you and massages
just trying to survive somehow
there's no story
ah
copyright me credit me SATA when you use
squat me up to your Star Trek friend
bloody Olive bloody Olive thank you soon
again thanks for the pinky
ah
yeah I think I read it in my brain when
I saw it I'm sorry attention did you say
more Metroid because match Super Metroid
free the absolute goat is on the SNES VC
also match for Fusion 4 is on the
Gameboy Advance VC and thread 5 is a
switch game
their side front games though Santa
played dread it was great
oh maybe dreads
instead of dread five
[Music]
let's just dread and you're giving them
numbers because of the chronological
release
well for story order
oh well
we'll have to mess that up
and Christopher
you need to chat thank you
we grab the Duncan mental Jelly Time
Kevin Dunkin became a great thank you
ah this was when I was getting really
tilted every donut called thank you for
the pinky love you my queen please be
happy
I'm so salty about that moment I do not
want to think about it
that was one of the worst moments in my
career
in terms of
not because of me
hey
that's terrible what did you super chat
you were
um
yeah trying to cheer me up because of
the shittiness
of the situation
hmm
[Music]
I will not have you guys
fault me again now nope
nope
foreign
oh man
you know what how it how it feels Miku
mp153 garlics thank you for the pinky if
you want to start playing feel free to
do so I think most of us would rather
see you happy regardless of what you're
playing you needn't force yourself with
that said that we are having fun
watching regardless of your setbacks or
progress thank you oh my biggest
motivation to not stop was because the
short was to stream
nice one Chihuahua
nice
nice one what's going on am I having
like
Strokes recently
[Music]
I am just reshaping the English language
from scratch
I'm tired
recently maybe it's my turret instead
makes this kind of stuff happen
hmm
I'm tired
[Music]
he's got me up Mimi that's right
eventually someone will have to make a
compilation when we get more of these
moments
I'm counting on you cow carrot for the
backtracking somebody will have to make
a compilation
all of this
every time I
mix things up
yes
Brandon thank you soon
[Music]
I'm not sure if that would help
Mikko 101 actions
croissant
Dominic thank you for the pinky a small
thank you for motivating kfp to meet up
all around the world my first Japan
experience
it was your first time it's truly
amazing I hope kfp can meet up in the
future too
wow
nice damn but it was pretty short wasn't
it
I hope another time you can go longer
but I hope you made the most of it and
we're satisfied but for the first Japan
trip one week damn that's rough because
there's just so much to do
and I guess you spend a lot of the time
just like
doing
like fan meet up things and stuff
he's still there is he no that's good
then now maybe if you're still there you
can focus on
finding all the famous landmarks and
stuff
yeah damn there's so much to see
back in Europe iirc
he just came back up here now there you
go I thought so
wow
well well
you must go there again
eventually
so next year
perfect Fest
if there will be 50
seconds The Chronic section leave David
alone thank you McCree Duncan shouldn't
Miss ah
foreign
[Music]
but my boyfriend once so I can't be too
mad can you guys not like switch
Mimi
like I don't know
make your boyfriend wear a big coat and
then hide inside
maybe there's a way where there's a will
there's a way
yeah chicken stick undercoat yeah
strategy
oh I have the boyfriend video call you
that's also an idea
I mean if your boyfriend did win the
meet and greet for me as well
then yeah you could just have him open
a a zoom or just a voice call
on this phone
I mean
that's bending the rules but I don't
think anyone can say anything about that
if that's what they want to do with
their time then do it
I allow
I hope the audio will go well though
I will allow it
loophole
[Music]
May believe
you know that I actually don't even
end the word when I beep it
I don't actually say it behind the beep
so that I don't accidentally miss the
timing of the beep
and then I you know you hear the whole
thing
I had my subscription
Donnie
well
um
more complaints I see you guys are not
even like affected by it
when I feel weak and hungry I need to go
I want a camera YouTube frozen pizza
but I don't have frozen pizza
I'm in a big frozen pizza mood
tomorrow Sunday I can't even buy frozen
pizza
I'll fall asleep now
really
[Music]
it was behind me
ah
bye bye light
laughs
don't you tease me about my hands now I
am supposed to be threatening worth it
okay
thanks for the fusion what's that
um oh another game
able card that was good
I want to try this again and see what I
get because if you guys said three four
five stars it doesn't mean like
all the ones that actually are like the
fancy engage rings are the five star
ones and then three and four stars are
those like just little you know boom
ones you get from the ring that job
the randoms or are they also
engagement rings
people
generic okay
[Music]
so for example they're like those like
shitty Rings you know that I give to the
shitty units that I don't use
common enemy units
[Music]
what do you mean with generic oh
generic
yo I was so lucky
[Applause]
sick that's incredible
meanwhile I'll go make sauce and then
make food
already make I'm just making sauce and
then eat food and then maybe eat dessert
I have salty salted caramel uh
cheesecake
dessert in my fridge
cool do you want one
oh oh making myself even more hungry
um
okay uh tomorrow uh change of plans 5 PM
stream starts and Diablo 4.
and
um I will make reservation when wakey
wakey
because now
no
has a Minecraft Terminator
what
up
she's gonna do doesn't say what she's
gonna do
I mean it's probably at 2 p.m at 2 am my
time so
not like I will take part in that but
she said Minecraft hello wow I wonder
what her plan is
maybe finishing Atlantis
um
that's a surprise
cheese no she can't beat that whatever
before me because she's in my Weaver
beating group I think
it has to be a group thing
we have a Monster yeah she's in my
wither beating group
oh yeah check out the new server aha
yeah you know I wanna I wanna play
Minecraft again too but I just don't
really
nothing interesting present weather I
can't doing the weather
I should poke them again because only
mummy replied
okay
Pokemon go
all right go down
hi I'm papaya
this reference they will not understand
sorry for a poke
wanna do
reader
I mean it's just a random greeting
okay
I love you guys bye-bye and Germany
Fire Emblem
what's fun
more next week
foreign
[Music]
good
morning
[Music]
foreign