[Music]
oh no what a terrible fate to not be
with any allies or friends to start this
day with no one by my side
ah I've spawned in directly on top of
someone actually oh good thing I did not
share my screen why did it show the IP
of
[Laughter]
that oh what a terrible
day so much is going
on so much wrong is
happening I just Lo it inside of someone
and then it took me out of the world
outside of that person and showed the IP
Flash the IP on the screen and put me
into another loading
screen how terrible when is it going to
put me in this game I'm ready to
spawn hello I am no longer inside of
anyone what a Terri what wait who is
this person you see my screen now who is
this oh I think that's staff I'm turning
around I'm getting away from them do you
do not see yet I I'm making sure
um nothing is wrong before I show you
guys everything that is
wrong goodbye staff I'm out of here
is that a
dog think staff's being chased by a
dog where is
it you see
that got killed by a do
[Laughter]
Wait no that's
K is
that taka nasty Kiara who died right in
front of me that's Kiara actually I was
like who is this no that's k
[Laughter]
one second I'm getting party
invites I'm also trying to
send Ally invit
look oh this is with shiori
sorry this work hello
hello oh hey I can hear you I hear
you where are you what's up girl how are
you doing I don't know I pressed random
buttons and now I have you as a friend I
just watch Kiara die right in front of
me I don't know where she is now that's
hot I'm sorry for her though but that's
hot do you think she come back for her
stuff I want
to I don't know
no I don't know if I should take her
stuff oh she's right here I don't think
we have much oh never
mind
stu oh darn she's naked we're so naked I
cannot be seen next to all these naked
people
it's okay we can cuddle up for warmth
around the naked bodies of course this
is the perfect way if we stay naked
we'll never be
cold yeah exactly maybe the zombies will
even think we're one of
them ooh but what do they want to join
our cuddle
pile I don't know but I found a house oh
there's dead people
people I am not I am just in a okay
so hello
everyone
I I want what my goal is
today I have pushed to chat talk so
don't worry I'm not just yapping into
hii's ear right now what what my goal is
is I really really really really really
would like a
car by the
end of this week long series I want a
car I don't know if it'll be possible
because I have no game knowledge
especially on 1.0 but I want a
car
okay might be hard
yep everyone try to come to you guys try
hard never mind I guess I'm going to be
okay we're all heading towards
be oh go to
them is that a
chicken I need to craft um
clothes what is it Stone ax I need this
for sure I need clothes cloth fragment
potentially what is the clothes called
all these Noob clothes oh I'm am
broke give me
this I'll make my way towards bioo and
Fu
moo worry
not if I was a beaver I'd be eating so
good right
now okay and then let's just make the
rest of this what do I have
gloves okay gloves this scary looking
Hood outfit not two outfits not so many
of these outfits shoes
equip equip equip bed roll Craft um what
else do I need a club club torch torch
torch
Club torch oh we need cloth fragments
and animal F welcome to the party YOLO
oh Welcome to our home our party
home it was lonely hi we're so lonely
without you welcome I don't know what's
happening I think we're heading towards
we're making our way to beibs
yeah okay you're actually around where I
am fa like near a
lake is there a lake oh there's a river
I yeah there's there's water oh my God
everyone is so far away oh my God why am
I over
here they head towards
them yeah there's like a cabin near a
lake a multiple of them
actually oh a
resort we should make home in a resort I
know it looks like some typical horror
area she
fancy yeah car really useful right now
oh you can also press M to find where
beibs
is it's going to run towards some um I
think what I want to do
personally is I need the
loot so I'm just going to have to GA run
over there open challenge windows with Y
redeem these um redeem redeem redeem
redeem redeem redeem redeem what bow and
arrow
bow craft
[Music]
Arrow like three of
these redeem redeem redeem now what okay
craft a land claim
BL good job Survivor
oh so the traitor's over here
too do you guys remember the Sham
wow yes
sham wow wait the guy that's like dead
dead I didn't mean to make it morid yeah
he sham de I didn't know he was dead
either I think I know either I just know
it's the Sham wow I seen on TV yeah what
about
it I need to add for oh I found a sham
sandwich oh is it edible or is it
moldy you should try eating it B can it
be moldy yeah eat it yeah eat it eat it
eat
it CH Wild guy is not dead older later
if you don't eat it soon oh he that's
true actually that's a good point it's
not getting any younger oh no it was
made with the
heel the heel of you know like the the
butt of the bread shoe heel it's like a
isn't it called the heel
of heal bread oh hey you're
new oh like the butt it's desperate
desperation yeah the but the desperation
sandwich f is that you me neither I ate
you're naked sort of wait I think I oh
my gosh I think I'm having a bowel
movement don't look at
me no no no it's beautiful 30%
how don't appreciate each is bowel
movement this is what happens when you
eat a sham wow I'm shy I can't go if
somebody's
watching there's there's got to be a
toilet in
here wrong this a zombie I think it's
okay it's okay it's okay they don't like
outside they're like us
introverts hold up I'm putting clothes
on you have clothes I haven't is it
reflected on me
sandwich yeah there's there's a person
there he coming he's out there for your
bowel movement are we going to kill is
this the
traitor you already have a spear oh his
thing is so different I'm
primitive ow and
hurt I can lie wow if there's a traitor
in their oh she is still alive their
area or they'll be coming over here can
they not loot their bodies anymore
how the hell do I get inside I don't
know the hell is that when we did the
the practice I made a bone knife but
they didn't give me anything peace out
wow that was a really loud squish sound
okay well we can look for a toilet here
if you
want okay has to be
one I'm sure there is and then you can
take it I found the toilet oh go there's
a
zombie hold on I have to go I
accidentally broke out the door so don't
look where in the to
it's okay it's okay I I'll distract a
zombie you better not [\h__\h] come here or
I'll you actually had to poop in this
game is that even possible I think so
it's this I'm
26% of the way
to to
BM are you actually going to go in the
forest right in front of everyone has a
lot of Health I don't no I found a
toilet but the whole world is our toil
toilet how are you going to play the
forest if you can't even [\h__\h] in it I
should go here should finish this Quest
I don't know I can't seem to figure out
was I'll meet up with them soon I think
if you just stand in there you'll
Release Yourself you know you relieve
yourself in the toil yeah just stand
find your inner peace okay
okay is it always down here oh man she
is so much health she dead now all right
you
may remove your sandwich in peace now I
gu know how I don't know how possible I
don't think you I don't think you can
actually poop in this game there there's
an icon which very clearly
means come eventually on its own without
interruption
do you need clothes am I wearing clothes
actually you are you are wearing
[Music]
clothes I guess my percentage is slowly
going down but the implications of that
are so much worse than if you
just go to the all right I'll try making
your clothes oh thank
you get it out of
here all right closer being what happens
when you eat we have not progressed far
toward be huh oh but we're getting so
much stuff it's good right
CH okay I'm about to drop the clothes
here thank
you you just couldn't bear to look at my
my clothes oh I can hear your B
movements or is that a zombie huh no
that's not me
maybe you sure are you sure I think I
heard it made a little grumbly sound
grumbly grumbly and your tummy I'm so
embarrassed I never should have aten no
no it's okay it's okay it's special it's
special oh what's this we're
zombies let's screw up well don't just
stand there with thumb up ass is doing
these things still the best way to get
exp
oh no where is this oh my God so far oh
wow oh jeez I guess I'll make my way
towards the best
way all right did you want to keep
exploring you want to
heads maybe with something else I feel
like this will give us good stuff we'll
head towards them I think we
can I think you need a wrench if you
want to salvage
cars
oh can I make
stuff here make spear too oh thank you I
made an
axe here's your spear the ax to to
harest items it'll give you more
compared to
punching I'm not messing with
that head on over
[Music]
lots of
stuff I have points available of course
we need this
okay what else we need this else need
this more
find we need more
strength more
strength get another one of these
yeah yeah let's go find her I
guess okay I am far going
north wait gig is not that far from us
now no I'm on my way
for we go find her go together oh R's
also uh nearby she's right there
oh I sent her a party invite since like
she's
yeah getting a chased
by who's that go
away nice job leave me alone I very busy
right now I got places to be
spendly thank
you places to be things to see vehicle
Adventures I'm going to make my
car do that voice chat only works like
party wise
yeah and it's not proximity right this
yeah I can hear you
guys yeah yeah even though I'm so far
away raor
this maybe should thought we were evil
of our outfits well I mean we looked
apart but that doesn't mean we are the
part get away from
me let's just follow her she knows to go
okay and
then what is going to die
okay oh what's this I don't
know you need to looks important though
wrong with him goodbye or an ax I think
the axe works yeah yeah it's working
another dead person I don't care
important all right I harvested some
I'll let you have the
rest it's just small
stones grab all this
stuff
oo Stone tool quality get away from me
ow she hit me leave me
alone just continue my way over
hopefully I'm getting closer to
them I am going across the gigantic Lake
good yes in quests she does want me
quite badly oh did we lose ra it's okay
she's like headed towards one area
anyway she
gone should we should we find GG uh
isn't she on the way I am walking
quickly with
V she's uh near the lake area and
everyone's gaed
up hell overturn trailer food food pick
you up though if you want
G it it's okay I'm on my
way all right well we can stay
quick I'll be right there in a moment oh
God
nice hey sh that she did not know she
could crawl not know she can
crawl have one of
these and then crap out of
these their
backpack yeah they small Stone thank you
for telling me about my Quest Craft land
claim
block take one day to get to the rest of
the group I'm I'm running I'm running
towards
them yes
okay we should all right we're heading
towards you Skyrim style Skyrim
style yeah following the the thing at
the top
oh I'm also following it but getting
distracted yeah me too Arrow
Arrow more Arrow maybe we should go loot
more houses too it's going to be a while
before we reunite with
everyone did they make it I put my bed
here though oh you have a bed oh it's a
I think it's a spawning Point yeah it's
my cheat oh is that you guys make a
bunch of
beds huh sauce hi oh hey what's up hello
hey you got clothes too I have cloth I'm
clothed I like that we all have very
scary hats yeah we do look pretty scary
oh hey there's someone over
there now we look pretty wait do you
mean that a
shotgun zombie look at the shotgun I
have
running you have a shot nice oh oh how
did you get a gun I did a
quest oh my God I just one tapped him
that's crazy hello who who are you too
bad I can't hear you I know oh we should
add her let me add
okay I send a party
invite I
be yink
yink if I was a beaver I'd be eating so
good right now
so yummy what a yummy yummy
tree holy [\h__\h] my bad I thought was
going
to
forgot oh no I'm out of
stone I'm out of stone
me asking the real questions I need to
speedrun my car one second goodbye to
your
head I guess it's this way are you
shooting gig yeah I just shot him in the
face
oh do you have ammo gave me 12 you take
your bullet back from his brain I wish
give me more ammo give it to
me just put it back in the chamber it'll
be fine she towards it's fine and let me
go
right
okay I like how we have this ADHD oh
crap what's that kill exp exp I have a
gun don't
worry I missed a waste of ammo
this let us primitive folks handle
it okay okay I'm clubbing I'm clubbing
her I'm clubbing her yeah we clubbing we
partying all night I'm out of stamina I
can't my girl rest up eat an egg I need
another sandwich what is this building
over here I'm going
inside you guys already loot this or is
there a dead person here cell tower oh
well R went through here and maybe the
others oh
oh well they left Behind These
electrical parts though they left behind
an office chair they don't want to take
the office
chair There's a
Zombie die
scum you will not touch these beautiful
women well thank you my my
night jiggling and
blushing XD
Roar gloms
you oh wow I can't climb this see what's
up here anything else here I'm climbing
the cell tower so hopefully I can get
some signal on our cell
phones i d I'm dying I lived I lived oh
my oh good job I'm hungry I'm I guess
I'll never find out what's in C
tower all right I I should probably eat
this egg raw you should eat a sham
sandwich so you can also have tummy
problems like
fa I recommend it do you do you have a
spare um I have an
egg wait what is this what oh my God
what God I
lost I I I I lost I spawned with it
actually focus it all tabbed off of my I
SP a death threat or
something
oh all right they should be at this
house I
think okay they're all just inside of a
house together doing
what playing family uh sorority is that
how I say oh sorority fan
fiction oh Pon is at the
traitor strange
we look like a cult the paaw residence
paa res
do kind of look like a
cult all right is it time to wait
everyone I guess we join the Discord
call now I suppose so now we can okay
all right I'll I'll stay here though
I'll see you in a bit okay me
too make sure I have my this
fo a see
we we had
80hd took
using we we have someone
[Music]
evil I have control I don't have no
control of my chos
[Music]
hello you look beautiful this is this is
my PC set do you like it oh
nice garbage oh I can sleep on top of it
actually okay maybe I
cannot I got this place it's pretty cool
should I sleep I'm going to find a you
like it very I mean yeah yeah it's co
what happens if we the apart
yeah I like it I have some privacy too
sure I don't think we need getting
anything from me I got to place this
does anyone want to come I want to go
try going to a farm to a
farm also please let me know how the
volume is everyone let me know how it is
in chat
Co come with us me my bed roll okay
okay let's wait a second is there a
Trader near here or you guys Trader
lless what you say is there a Traer near
this
house we haven't found one yet we
haven't done
anything I like that even in the
apocalypse trenda thing and we all
wearing the same style I accidentally
clicked on something
Friends by the way if you guys open the
map you can set a marker for where home
is open right
click you can set a marker that's
[Music]
nice this is I'm sorry every time I all
tap back in I punch
someone that's what happened I don't
mean stay away from me okay truth truth
please don't touch me yes don't you
don't touch me
Tru
Tru careful don't each
other kill each
other
probably disappeared we're crazy okay
this way I think was the farm Yep this
way wait wait who am I following
everyone looks the same a
little follow
everybody follow this
the oh goodn okay but I'm going to have
ADH on the way that's okay you have ADH
at any point you
want oh
there oh I got the
farm up The Corn can we make stuff out
of this can we cook cuz I got some meat
and potatoes like dead and green corn I
think get the green corn get
[Music]
the I feel like we should probably be oh
they're dead let's go yeah there is real
corn there get can we get some to weant
them stole that from you we have potato
SE those are still growing got to be a
good farmer I'm hitting a tree in this
apocalypse with corn that's all I need
I'll survive
the cor are dead
though they just can't eat the the
people
what I mean they're just zombies they're
not
people okay this this area has three
three skulls on it I don't know if we're
ready for that oh does that mean like
danger we're going to die yeah I look at
the green ones Lo's probably really good
but I just don't think we're ready
surpris like skull images so I noticed
that the green corns actually contain
seeds too probably oh they do we could
set's a ear corn they have something
different we could set up a little farm
by our
home it feels like that's a seed we get
rid of the Dead Corin what happened
there's a house here here yeah I see you
got this is be careful this is the three
skull area yeah it's a pretty you all
have each other though it's okay there's
zombies everywhere run run
run you got to run what are they going
to do it's
okay what are they going to do
[Laughter]
huhn all right I hope the corn re like
resupplies maybe a farmer shows up and
take care of hopefully it's going to be
where
the the so much I'm going back
home yeah I don't think it gives you
anything can I eat okay we can eat wait
don't leave
me so we just need the big
ones or the green we found
[Music]
some who wants to focus on getting food
maybe we should split into like yeah
good idea food gatherers this is just
like Hunter Gathering and then the
people that stay at home
time let's go organiz do I found a land
claim block destroyed this oh I think
someone put I just put that there for
the quest worry
not I don't know
my so if you put a land claim box down
apparently um it applies a hardness
modifier to blocks so it protects it
protects damage I'm something
apparently so like you're safe in the
zone I guess or something like that or
the player who put it down is safe in
the zone it's like your land now my the
house yeah we have one of those I put
one in the living room
oh oh we're in the same uh Ally group
too so we should be good to
go it won't be harder for us to destroy
each other's things if we need to
exactly are we all in the same party
have a question um um no party is
six how do you level
up oh level I think he got to kill exper
oh killing zombies okay if we find the
Traer he gives Quest and he gives a lot
of exp from the quest want to go with me
on an adventure to see if we can find
the trador I know where he is he's
really
far yeah I have one on my map too oh
okay is it the White River
yeah yeah if I can share this way point
if he wants to trade he should come to
us that's right he's not going to do
that I
think be face by the way or he's hello
oh
[Music]
hello oh I found
people
people welcome
welcome wait you guys are all wearing
something
why aren you wear where's your hat a
there's a hat yes put your hat
on what you should probably it there a
there kill
it your I will craft you a hat oh oh
wait no I see a hat oh thank you yes put
it
on Oh
yay
civilized let me
he's down down I he's
[Music]
not um he's far I don't know how to
share the way Mark with you guys what
what if you send like a screen oh I I a
screenshot gloves I'm missing gloves oh
there it
is can we eat the craft anything just
yet
there's l claim
box S I can make a Char
meat meat meat meat is this our base
this is our base
yeah we should probably
do what is this land claim
block our home Bas now basically zombies
SP around you see it I put it in the
channel the map thank you what if we all
put our land claim blocks like around
each other so they won't spawn within a
let's protect the house we
get where can't do anything right how to
make land claim block this oh I have a
land claim block um I don't know where
to put it though uh it won't let me put
it
anywhere they already claimed this land
claimed yeah is there a maximum to can
only one person claim a land cilia Sor I
don't know how are you cooking oh this
is Mor I'm meat oh here maybe here right
there TR to figure out where to put this
oh yeah I can't put the l clim oh yeah
it's a pretty it's a pretty put it here
I am dying of
hunger want to eat we need to
un take a claimed this
land put it by the river let's see if we
can cook some more for
everybody maybe here oh we need cooking
items oh we need cooking oh I like the
their placement of this
fire anywhere these days you just put in
the fireplace can't believe
it we should probably try to find um
like a cooking pot and a frying pan so
we okay
yeah I found a I found a cooking a grill
outside the house I don't
know some water we have some water in
inventory here near trees is there a
town
near H there's a town very far
[Music]
away that's water some food oh that the
hell I'm going to eat scary food
oh by the way night time soon everyone
um oh you guys have a nice out here
wonderful the idea that I have is that
vc1 is for the home and then all the
other ones are for like going out on
different excursions together that's a
idea nice idea I don't think we're
eating that would be great
sorry I want
I'm
here cover the river she's here I don't
know what to do it's about to
be I'm focus on
finding okay I'm going CHS too if anyone
wants to go on an
EXC stroll I'm going to collect items
I'm going to gather stuff so I'll stick
around the house okay okay okay I will
debate on what to do I will go
solo de how how does iig
how is it here skill tree I'm pretty
sure cornmeal oh can I eat
this oh you need water to
cook yeah realistic it sucks H finding
water would be a good idea for us I oh I
can more Stones how do we like purified
water you have to burn it
made how
evil oh dear what a terrible
person I think you need a pot how do we
get a pot a
bedroom arrows have to find a
pot I can craft
cornmeal yeah me
too I don't know how hungry I
Amad bed where did I put violence
between our allies is consider con
erning very concerning yeah let's not do
how I know when I'm not hungry how much
do I have to eat I have harvested what
the heck okay I think I'm scary sound
did you hear that sorry it was my
stomach it's night your stomach sounds
like a
zombie I'm sorry I don't mean
it what I don't know what no stomach
really sounds like a zombie I don't need
it I don't need it oh are they trying to
get in stop saying that about stom it it
really sounds like a it's zombies I'm
going to try to like build walls or
something yeah it might be a good idea
to stay
inside oh we're not supposed to sleep
outside but it's so beautiful the Stars
like beautiful they're coming in they're
coming in stop talking about my stomach
that way how' you repair those
doorsa
w i me to be fair we don't have closed
doors nor windows
oh oh that's not
good oh my
God who did this to
me what the anyway I think I build a
building block I hope this item
is how do I change to something
else how do you what the heck I can't
man building is hard
if I just destroyed us at this point how
bad is 12%
dentary 12% bad compared to doesn't seem
that bad
double my first I need an item that
place build maybe I can snipe
too I'm hoping to just put a block here
so we don't have Windows that people can
see us through
good idea yeah these zombies can't watch
us yeah and think about us and think
we what kind of weird thoughts you know
weird thoughts can you name one weird
thoughts or weird
thoughts
girl I swear okay that's a building
block okay can I open the door or
no help there's a weird
zombie mom there's a weird zombie
outside on scaring
crony have a candle what's this to put
this dang no fear huh ladies I know who
to
Woo you're not afraid of
anything there you go I hope she do we
need any more doors
anywhere I think we're good I think
they're they all look pretty
healed how'd you board them up
Kiara H I just want to place a door
somewhere
um this is
Minecraft
yeah camping songs the acoustic guitar
how do I I have a
kazoo ohy there's AER here we can eat
unless it's a zombie deer come here deer
don't eat don't eat the deer did we just
naap it ran away you cannot sleep like
Minecraft
sadly you cannot sleep oh no it's evil
Minecraft if
only just need one more Stone nice I
just need more wood the trader
Quest do I heal if I sleep at least
no what's the point of having a
bed spawn point I think can fortify
things I'm low and stamina and I'm
thirsty how do you use so much is wrong
with you this this you guys experience
thirst and hunger turn it
on God at the right you see a bunch of
wood make sure it has fuel and then you
just turn it on like
this
oh does this building block even do
anything we have curtain that should be
good put some corn in there BL and wood
block how do you tell what you need to
cook something I have to join a party a
recipe I think how do I join a party
Jo part oh
yay uh allies wait no party just like a
variant invite
me can invite everyone
right wait I received a party invite oh
sick oh
I'm currently not in the party I can't
aim this bow and
arrow
yeah thank you and then yeah you press
just press
[Music]
buttons you need a party or you good oh
do I need a party I I think I'm in a
party
with CC and
crony
yippe y
probably stick around and harvest things
around here but if people want to go
expl thirsty my character is like never
satisfied wait how do you experience
hunger oh okay you have a hunger bar too
cron it's just very hard to see it's a
green bar beneath your inventory so
privileged yeah my
invent oh now I'm Hung
okay Welcome to The
Gang This is good for harvesting bodies
if you use the bone knife you can
Harvest bodies like in
Rust is it safe to go outside yeah it's
safe yeah you can go out okay yay it's
not too bad right now yeah because it's
day
one need to build Tom we die though
there's a dog with glowing eyes you
think that's I'm exced I think
sooko
bow say a good
sound shift uh click or shift
click shift
click
oh flamed area unless they allow it you
have a
curtain to oh can you not build in the
house
area my chat just yeah we can't place
anything in a claim area but I don't
know they can allow it I place
stuff I place like random blocks oh hold
R okay let's try about this one no it
just
rotates oh if you like do
this hey that's my stuff wait I I
thought it turns into a wooden block I
I'll just pick it up oh I got to repair
it I'm sorry animal
stuff I thought it turns into one
BL I'm just cover up our
uh oh
yeah if you want animal Fatar kill an
animal and then if you right click with
an axe I don't see any animals oh I
probably need to UPG go hunting wait
really find that bunny I think so I
can't you just need a stone
axe mind oh don't you need to like
upgrade with
stone really I have the axe
yeah tra
quest Quest
oh oh you need more wood I don't have
enough wood I guess I uh I have
oh so thirsty anyone got a
pot no we don't do pot around here pot
here I'm out of here not in this
household you will all starve without
that
pot should do
something I can't I need more
Stone how do I pick this
up I can't pick this up what are you
trying to pick up get stone a block this
block that I placed down punch it punch
no I have no here you are this try try
using an
axe God damn it I have to break it why
is everyone dying it's dangerous out
there than you so much night
time maybe there's a to farm I'm
thinking that too maybe we should go get
a
pot yeah yeah we should you ladies want
to put together wants it I want a
PO let's go to The Farmhouse and see if
we can get a pot that's
die well risk we're will oh God the
zombies can crawl on all
fours okay I'm leaving it to you see
guys well I mean I think that she
already knows this very well get down
God I don't have stamina oh are you
down no no I'm just really tired she's
just a little eepy oh there's my base
I'm eepy weepy eepy weepy everyone's
dying yeah
I think just having
my just want to fix my stupid Stone
egg why don't I just make a new one so
much easier it's just gone that's why I
need
Stone
ah I'll get some scrap
metal is that you hitting the car oh
yeah you know it girl you and your
vandalism oh yeah this car is in my way
I'm going to destroy it man what if it's
like from Pixar though you're going to
get us in trouble oh oh his name I
forget they so nak I don't know I never
watched it actually F you black sedan
why I I got a magazine for like making
cars from a zombie nice oh nice good job
you can store that in a crate maybe oh I
already learned I'm hungry again oh my
God right you're the car person now
that's your job I am the car person now
let's
go that is your job now your endless
supp that's not a good sign
scary too all right I'm at the farm in
case anyone also wants to play Harvest
Moon Harvest
Moon okay is there a monster there yeah
it's really scary probably oh it's
breaking it down oh that's a big
one trying to get in the house maybe
defend the home that's a big end it's a
big one hey crony can you defend the
whole base yeah I'm trying I can now
make a stone axe oh God I mean I could
have fixed one probably um I think it's
over what's wrong what happened there's
a big guy I he can have it he can keep
it
not our house I'm shooting him I'm
shooting him get
him
ooh oh he's dead oh no he's not dead
okay he just faked it how many arrows
can this guy take ow ow all right I'm
heading back there oh God okay I didn't
want to use this but I suppose I
will oh I'm I have the corn okay hope I
don't miss
this what the whoa I didn't want to use
it but he had gun I got it from the tra
other Arrow I stole all the
arrow oh sounds like a
clicker all right I'm heading back is it
a lot of zom zoms no we got rid of him
he's gone now oh good job a
b what what are these noises I'm
so oh yeah that's the dud that was
chasing
me click I'll crap I'm out of
stamina it's a little hard to
see oh no here you get him the front I
get his back I'm infected jeez what
you're infected we have to kill you now
you got to die sorry
I with ligma what's ligma
ohma I want one of
them oh man here eat some corn maybe
I'll heal you hello think you will I
doubted no but it tast we can e some
popcorn some corn corn or some popcorn
corn M yummy sounds really good all of
that I broke into a house you guys but I
want to wait till it's daytime before
going in there
even though you're infected oh thank you
I think in the end we'll all be infected
eventually that's
sweet that's good to know she's giving
us her
Lima yay you don't want it oh I if it's
from you I guess you already have it I
mean you already have it gigy no it's
not yet I haven't been corrupted
yet all right then it's about time stay
away from
I won't get L much
today coffee seeds oh that's
bad better way you seem very
knowledgeable can I borrow you for one
second in the voice chat okay I am
moving to three
okay hello hello hello I I I'm like
super
overwhelmed with the skills oh God wait
I shouldn't have joined this battle uh
with the skills I don't know what to put
skill points into and what oh God what's
important and what
[Music]
um can you assist me you or don't you
know like much as as much as I thought
you thank you for I do not know as much
as you know but minor 69er and
motherload are very good ones to have
cuz they give you more resource es yeah
in the strength skill tree and then
there's Scavenging things that you get
more loot are usually good ones to get
so if you like looting which we need a
lot of material and resources so maybe
the Scavenging perks and then you might
want some maybe some health stuff oh
wait that's someone oh s Cil oh my God
wait wait wait wait I thought that was
from the second scary
monster why is it so scary
oh
God he can't get me if I
leave literally doesn't know where I
am challenge each charge meet complete
that was a
challenge there's a beautiful baby dough
over there that I'm going to kill if I
can just get a clean shot at this with
without it looking at me oh it's so fast
okay I have no idea where these shots
are going when you're 500 miles
away okay this one will this one is sure
to connect sorry sorry gigy I had to uh
apologize to oh it's
okay okay oh my God there's a a lot
going on um okay you said what perks the
motherload and and minor 69er are good
ones if you're hitting rocks all the
time and you get exp from hitting rocks
and and then the Scavenging ones like um
69 it's under the strength one in a
perception you go Scavenging perk so
maybe lucky looter Treasure
Hunter and then you should probably go
into the one that you
want your main weapon to be in and maybe
some recovery
perks what I don't see any minor succe
ner in the Scavenging per oh oh it's in
strength so at the very top under skills
there's like the eyeball and then
there's the muscle and then the plus
sign uhuh you can swap through the and
strength yeah who is chasing me get away
from
me inreasing tool damage to bring on
rocks and trees faster
okay and uh Modo is where it's under
perception so the
eyeball
mhm and then you can get I think
generally the ones that are good to get
are tailored to your play style and if
you're scared of dying probably some
health perks but resources are always
very important in survival craft game so
I always think resource collections good
to get
okay okay well I I'll take a look at all
of this yeah
there's a brawler skill you should get
that I'm going to go fisting again I'm
going to fist these
zombies you'll put so many skill points
into Brawlers so that you can be Auto
fisting they come close to me I start
fisting right off the bat I don't even
ask who they are I just I just
start oh I have yet to be fisted by
you oh wait I have to I have to oh thank
God I didn't use them can give them back
okay okay oh get hammered big hitters
okay uh if you want if you want we can
go back up or uh you know okay want go
back to the chaos we can go back to the
chaos we can stay I'm going to go
explore over here too I I want to join
you but let me just ask cilia one
one I'm it turns hav read your magazines
oh really
okay you can have them here I put them
in this crate
here something that
anybody did they disappear after the
yeah they disappear
after thank
[Music]
you oh [\h__\h] wait one sec whoops I didn't
mean to say
that I mean oh shoot oh no sorry
oh oh gosh Dar you give it backl this
this your uh golly your reward
you thank
you smart together
y together the club is better
now skill okay I'll go with kie if
anyone wants to go call and I are going
to the
farm I'm not going to survive with
oh my
goodness can you guys bring like food
and water I'm
dying let's make the stone ax and then
things will go faster oh food cornmeal
you can make
cornmeal what is
this and then
you I have a feeling we're going to lose
all of the resources around the house
how do
I how does one eat
eat it's like you're learning how to be
human
again how does one get hungry where do I
put the
food I'm
learning that looks
important how does just let me know if
you want to go somewhere okay if you see
on the map I'm at a gas I'm at a stiff
tool
station wow we should go to the trader
and do quest to though the trader gives
a lot of stuff oh you went okay I Haven
yeah I went to the trader before and he
gave me a gun a really far one yeah it
was on the way on the way I spawned
quite South and then that was the trader
it sent me
to oh you think it's safe to go alone to
the Traer uh at daytime it is after I
explore this stiff tool area I'll come
to okay yeah I'll
join okay do we all tra in the same
location though I think so they're
pretty
St okay oh there's a snowy
area I want want my snowy area to be
there's a scary dog in there with bright
red alpha
eyes no it's the
dog all right I'm making sure our home
is up to base or up to code or whatever
[Music]
thank there's a castle up there we have
to have enough wood
though do we have enough d
you can never have enough doors
honestly I actually used doors to slow
them
down pretty pretty
good there's a
[Music]
castle Yeah in the snowy area oh my God
make a that would be good for later see
down down what do we need for the torch
man my character is so thirsty I am also
very hungry right now yeah I'm
surving sick of it I just don't know how
not to be we're sorry we are commoners
we
peasants how does one become hungry oh
okay now I'm very hungry I
guess you have learned the ways of the
the common folk ah yeah so this is how
hunger
is unfortunately
don't
shovel
oh I'm
hungry I am searching toilets don't
worry I'll find
food can you find water in there oh I
found some water in the
toilets oh good oh no anything is
helpful can
I you okay yeah we're trying to get
resources yeah we're trying to help
you resources you can leave them the
crates since we'll all be sharing them
okay if we get the cotton plants then we
can make them into bandages and
heal here food oh this is not
good how do you ever heal from an
infection I think
you yeah you die just accepted do not
get
infected INF you're dead now good to
know maybe you just have to have really
good hygiene and it goes away eventually
I don't
know except this way
live I why there so many dead corn get I
don't know what they can be used for but
I have a feeling that they're all good
or maybe I can make more doors what
up antibiotics and honey honey honey
eggs are expensive
do we have to kill them kill the bees
yes Kill the Zombies yeah do we have to
what are you a zombie
[Music]
apologist I don't know I feel like you
know they might not be that bad they're
trying to kill you them the only answer
is
kill okay I'm going back home kill where
is home where is home uh home is on the
map PR
than
you no
problem the
pi let's back I'm just killing one it
looks like the weather is turning oh oh
very yeah oh why so
FY 7 a.m. or is it 7 7 p.m. in the game
I think 7 a.m.
okay I think it 24hour clock okay
good scary B yeah I know many of you
guys are scared of
this yeah they killed my family how how
can we make a farm that's so
unfortunate
for
hello what are you searching for in this
area
area I was reading books oh you're
reading what's your favorite magazine
Vogue I really like wiring
101 it's a good
magazine yeah it was so good I read it
twice two wiring 101 I just missed two
point blank arrow shots on this
thing well if I find point blank arrow
shots 101 I'll give it to you oh thank
you I need to learn how to
aim ooh
exp I'm trying to explore this stiff
tool shop they have a lot of stiff tools
it looks like oh
yeah it said it was like very dangerous
so I left it's not dangerous with the
both of us here we already killed two
zombies that's true I am I'm incumber
and I picked up too many potted plants
but what are you going to use the plants
for
decoration yeah I thought people would
be so happy when I brought home they
were love they're going to love your
plants I think so I can't tell if that's
a town across the bridge I want to
go I found a a burnt Forest down the
other way that's scary down this way
yeah I'm going to go across the bridge
okay good luck on your quest thank you
good luck on yours thank
you you can go scavaging for
it this way it's
top zombies I think there's a town over
here I can't tell this is a town like a
chest before destroying them we need
clay soil and R the flesh is
from dead bodies not zombes oh human
the
head I need to find de
carasses should make able door in the is
that our bag that must be our bag that's
our bag from before Oh it makes did I
get my bag
0.1% what if there zomes let's just grab
it and go
great or is it slow ah it's going down
I'm healing myself with honey
oh how big is this honey works why is it
so big if you guys get lion just look
for um tree Stomps and
uh get rid of the tree stop get the
honey and then drink the honey
[Music]
okay what's that block is that a I don't
know why is this door so weird it's like
it's FLH anywhere no honey oh P push no
get it get it this this is a useless
door gosh are usually not so I think
we I find this to be a useless door I
don't know I don't know oh it's probably
cuz it's this thing I
see oh that's this is not the way to
home there's the ho
really weird okay I'm just going to
focus
on thought that was funny
yeah I need water I just drank my last
of water
it's a beautiful day yay kind of weak I
guess I need to find I don't know find a
deer
carass Let's Travel towards the Traer
and then we might to find a deer on the
way someone wants to come with me to the
trader oh go oh I'm going there right
now you I'm at the home okay home and we
good together okay let's put some stuff
on
I'm coming home I was a little far away
I found a town thank you than to me can
I just make a maze put it all away and
then we'll take what we want yeah I
don't know what to do
here that the flesh need to cook the
water Bamboozled they'll be like why is
there so many I have to find some iron
if someone needs by the way there you
go everyone will be
I'll leave here for now what's up with
the doors what do we need it for again
for I don't think
so stress crafting crafting Under
Pressure oh god oh we can plant
trees first was for
planting okay
okay this is going to go without so
close yeah I'm so close to home I'm
coming okay let's just find some
resources for now we all right I see
everyone split up oh there's a building
block
okay
okay so what are all these storage
crates are they all just like stuff that
we can call
her from other people probably yeah I
think everybody has their own little
storage for now okay I just put the I
put food in one storage crate since
we'll all be like hungry so hungry we
are
[Music]
starving
God so
long seems like I can name it we have a
lot of rock
can if you guys go near the farm please
collect more corn did you find a pot
okay a pot
yeah a
pot how are you cooking without a
pot we can lab the
C let us know down when you're good to
do you want to go
to V tree okay let's do it okay let's do
it okay this and I don't even know put
that candle there I am so hungry and so
thirsty and there are so
many
people my
GG I mean this in the nicest way
possible but everybody's starving GG
you're not the only one here am the only
one Starving in here and I need you to
give me your
food I'm not feeling so well
either guys ta stand by tax I am I am
starving personally I'm about to go
forage for stuff cuz all I have is corn
and I'm sick of it
sick of corn be sick of corn yeah
although if you go to the farm please
collect more I'm going to go to the town
hope the hopes please get me more corn
where do we get
water you have to find a river and then
I think you still might need pot or a
water bottle to collect water from it
what about can you turn snow into
water maybe you can drink from
it gets
heavy all right I'm about to wander off
see you guys goodbye goodby goodbye have
a great
one I craft a tin land mine no that's
not what I
want corn
Pizza what are we having for din about
corn Pizza
[Music]
corn corn is a luxury you should be so
glad you even have
CS is it safe if zombies ever
[Music]
come is anything safe in this world no
oh
see I found a
hospital a hospital a hospital who wants
to go to the hospital hosit hospital I
want to go to the hospital we can cure
your ligma here
y they got the supplies oh okay
cool hosital hit oh wow you were really
far oh am I damn yeah I found a town I
was trying to find a grocery store but
there's not one in here oh there's a
grocery store I love shopping I love sh
we can shop at the hospital it has five
death
skulls oh wow
wow I love that let's
go bye friendly
zombies I love
that I'm sure there's food in this
Hospital of five
friends I am going your way
yippe
[Music]
yippe so gigy did you already do the
like digging Quest from the trader yeah
I did the digging one you're wait how
did you get to the trader you went
walked yeah W both of you oh on the way
to you guys I went there how did you
you're damn girl okay maybe I will walk
to the Traer he gives you a
gun so friendly yeah that's where I got
my shotgun from the gun that's nice
maybe we should get guns before we go
into the five friend hospital or we
should just go in you're on your way
I'll
wait well well then let's get
digging rather than a gun I'd prefer
some water and food but okay maybe maybe
at the hospital they'll have water and
food
o they might yeah you're in
deeral you would expect Hospital people
at the hospital
that would be a welcome sight preferred
more dead than the zombiie yeah compared
to the zombie oh no have Undead people
that would be
terrible ooh
purse oh what oh wait oh that looked
like I don't know that looked like
Chanel
maybe what are you going do Rob the
zombies of their purse no there was a
there was a purse lying around oh
got me some Louis Vuittons
[Music]
maybe got them
Gucci who died and left his Prada bag
here for
me oh that's
crazy at this day and age in the
apocalypse I'm very hungry your maximum
stamina is reduced how do I know
that oh I love the Chikorita res
it like the bananas the
bananas no that's the
Pokemon
yeah I learned about that one today what
why did I pick up an office Chita or or
Chita ban Chikorita Chikorita
bananas I'm eating a raw egg
M what what's the goal in this Quest so
yummy me H do I just deep dig deeper and
deeper until I find something yeah you
basically just dig down and around in
that Circle until something pops up for
you sometimes it's pretty far
down damn I'm hungry and
thirsty
is I mean this in the nicest
way I
know we're all suffering here
I'm
not what since when maybe we should just
convert to zombies since now I decided
to stop suffering oh oh that's a spirit
like a Buddhist approach yeah yeah yeah
I'm out of stamina this zombie is going
to take me out of my misery
die maybe Life as a zombie is easier
maybe maybe they don't need like water
and stuff so I'm not
dying
closer somebody's
boat I can probably drink
glue
probably did you do that when you were a
child wa I'm thinking myself a grave I
realize go I do have Louis
Vuittons in the apocalypse
had seven bucks is the trader evil and
they just like trap you into building
your own grave and once you're deep too
deep they will like cover it up like you
you covered up in never mind I think
there is treasure maybe they weren't
lying they were not lying why would they
lie to you in the apocalypse I don't
know maybe you're in in with them and
and you were just trying to kill
everybody I would
never you could s
oh my God there's a dead body here
that's awesome I think that the front
door is 3,000 HP
strong oh don't worry I'll break it
open are you sure yeah by the time you
get here it'll be
open okay let me try right
now I go back tra
f are you on your way to the
trader yes vaguely
oo sorry that wasn't even on
purpose it's a reflex it's only
natural ouch I'm sometimes you just oo
it's
true ow garbage okay the vulture is
attacking me I didn't even know that can
Happ happened do I look like I'm dead or
what sorry I I'm working on
it I thought you said it was done I'm I
don't turn
away she'll be done
soon just just get so tired yeah hitting
this
door me me
too
hi just it's just so hard oh oh what
open oh I think I'm dying to what oh
goodbye what are you dying to to
her ooh okay oh he gives you a for a gun
what did you take uh gy did you take a
pistol or I took a
shotgun oh oh she lived from a
shotgun oh that's a lot um this is not
good a zombie just fell from the
ceiling wa that's crazy I'm getting out
of
here five friends it's five
friends uh your friends are a little
aggressive don't worry I have something
to put them out of their misery I missed
run it's okay I don't have any EXP
expectations you should have
expectations I could do better I can do
better I will do better I'm sure you can
okay okay maybe just not
today why do they run faster in the rain
ow oh I had shotgun cells oh
oopsy how come I can't drink the rain
water
shotgun why am I so
how are you so picky in the
apocalypse
just they made
it tell you would you can even get more
oh wait I can drink water what water
just just look up at the sky and it's
slowly plish your
um does really yeah no really try it no
no
no person is busy okay I'll try
it no it doesn't
work why would you lie to us what is
wrong with you you sick freak is us
being in the apocalypse not enough for
you you have to play with us too what
are we like little animals to you
I'm just getting wet I just cannot
believe you would do such a terrible
thing to us you
hear disgusting
freak we're already tortured
enough you think being thirsty is a
joke did you do any other quests like or
the zombie okay I should though I'll
stop here you
should you know what faa's on her way
here so I'll wait for fauna to
dig and
[Music]
then maybe we can all we can do yeah
questy another one yay if only it was a
shortcut to get to the trainer maybe we
should build our house next to the
trader yeah yeah yeah right just move in
some else we're not that attached to the
current house are we no I hope not
no oh oh my God what the
heck what M if you're in the same party
you can share Quest
mhm close it close it close close
it I'm hungry again what is this this
human bodily functions can I buy a bread
or something from you sir please
[Music]
I have 39 Casino
tokens nice what are you going to do
with that I want
food but it's
expensive you scared the [\h__\h] out of me
like what is
that so scary looking
my
bad first you lie to us then you s up on
me you get off on scaring people lying
to
people oh no oh a sham sandwich I hope I
don't get diarrhea with this m you
probably will oh search fany I live
another what does sham what does sham
mean I've been eating those for a while
now um it means you will if you are not
lucky you will poop your
pants oh
oh I only know sham marriages I only
know sham wow sham wow sham
marriages oh my God there's a
person you mean a dead person oh my God
there's a dead person I see dead
people can
soups and this is so expensive like in
apocalypse can you not have some
mercy why are they burping oh ew they're
like I don't know yeah why was there no
grocery store in this town how did they
get their
food I guess I'll look for my own food
if this guy sells for so
expensive hi guys
hi how is how do you say it again like
I'm home I'm home
[Music]
no that's
[Laughter]
[Music]
still okay we got some stuff you have
food yeah we found food 30 meat we we
Hunters we have yeah as as
the I I will say you are the the leader
of this group am I um wouldn't you say
it would be very much smarter to like
move to a house that is closer to the
Traer yeah I think that's a good idea I
think for now this is an okay first base
bro you guys are blocking my
way you're
welcome oh no sorry yeah maybe too comfy
here because we have a crate that's full
of food for example we going to need to
move
hard maybe we can make a
second yeah second everything yeah yeah
I'm going to keep these shotgun
yeah any goodies that you find just dump
them and I think everyone should get um
a bone knife at a certain point cuz
they're really
[Music]
useful and then I'm going to make a
magazine crate and please only take the
ones that that you think you want to
kind of minmax yourself on I personally
am doing like a fortitude strength thing
but for example there's like a medical
journal for nerds okay if you're a
freaking nerd what do you guys have you
have you found any other journals so far
an academic
one she she's a what does it called
she's a
scholar freaking po Dexter all
righty Winer she's the winner of the
spelling be so of course that is true
does anyone want to try going to the
trader so we can do some Trader quests
because I feel like that's where the
food and stuff will be easiest to get
and water
water would be very nice I definitely
need water but first can we get a snack
can get a little snack first I'm very
hungry oh can you guys who you're at the
house when you go to the trailer can you
bring some food with you to share the
only one that can cook from us is Bib
and I don't know where she is right now
so yes we need more chef and I'm so
thirsty oh I'm so thirsty I have one
water I'm so thirsty so bad but I am
about to die take it thank you take it
okay so we let's wait wait let me ask
what people's doing one sec I'll be
right back oh thank God what is this I
feel so much better
desolation have food please you know I
could probably cook some eggs though yes
eggs are easy to
cook how do you like your
eggs I need water dang it uh Benedict
bened cumber batch
oh nice
there I love my eggs like that also
ladies I a farmer so if you find any
Farm relating things let me know cuz I'd
like to start a farming a little farming
plot okay okay but probably won't plot
until we're actually at the trader area
you mean farming magazines or something
like that no uh farming yeah farming
magazines yes you're right that's
correct thank you I do have one
blueberry seed by the way yeah seeds
collect as many seeds as we can we're
going to need
I have a
potato you have a potato you have a
potato all this time talk about hunger
and you have a potato I have one potato
yeah we can share this
potato got to split the potato like what
we all take a bite yeah it's dire times
please potato
F okay I have beg the cook is on her way
and she will make us all food yeah and
then we can go on an adventure to the
trader and see if we can oh I found
coffee disgusting
coffee why
me 30 and meat or who was that was it
you 30 me I have 30 meat
the you it's uned uncooked this reaction
is genuine
the other ones they were fake this one
this one's genuine this
genuine wait so how do you get water
from a river do you just like how do you
drink it I'm punching it but I don't get
any
water you punch water to drink yeah to
get water through your skin it's when
it's raining look up and then you start
drinking we' been this
[Laughter]
that's a
spirit yes ladies yes you were even
there when we've been through this and
you judged crony for it
what these other people in this call
don't know that yeah I don't know what
you're talking about what do you mean
you talking about yeah no you're just
telling
lies what what did I say actually happen
or are you guys messing what I have
diarrhea no like it did happen
you have a lot going on with you yeah
this a didn't know you were going
to I was just reading out I what it said
does somebody have Golden Rod flowers
yeah actually there is a golden rod FL
space
everyone talk about there oh my God
there's a diarrhea icon on the screen
well I don't want to see what that looks
like
jeez oh I want to see that yeah try
eating some more shams
sandwiches oh you'll get
there I'm back sorry about that sorry
for wait but just the flower is not
enough right you have to you have to
boil it oh also I'm infected uh I need
to take any that's okay we'll cool you
when the time comes don't worry no for
infection I've just been uh eating honey
tree stumps it's really efficient good
idea I'll go oh I see the diarrhea
symbol now you diarrhea let's go
diarrhea girl
yeah let's go diarrhea
maxing yeah let's share a toilet
together I feel all been like isolated
as survivalists for such a long time
that it's hard to gauge is that is that
romantic are they flirting I'm not sure
I think it's bonding for sure yeah it's
dire times get it I don't think I
understand silly welcome home
I I brought um ever evering pot I have I
dropped like 30 meat on you I can make
bacon and eggs and I can make boiled
meat so I'm going to God bless in the
heavens yes
please I will B
t let me cook we're so lucky that we
have B to make bacon and eggs for us
yay can you make tea too
bio um let's see with the Golden Flower
for oh oh I found a golden Ron flow oh I
cured myself thank you for the tip oh
you can make can purify water as well oh
please yeah we need that
yeah if you have murky water I can
purify it I have that too it's we have
some wow oh that's cool I
found bacon and egg we two murky water
I'll drop it for you here you go yay
yay look how cute our house natural
merky for the murkiest
reasons M yummy a nice first house but
we close to the Traer yeah actually it's
okay since we're near a river with our
empty bottles we could theoretically go
near it GA water and just like boil that
endlessly I hope wa you guys have
bottles I don't have bottles the Bott
disappeared infinite water trick where'
you guys get bottles mouth just open
your mouth look up you can't why would
they do
that what about glass jar I split a
stack I'm blind I think
right I'm just going to do a quest now
then okay
okay oh I figured out okay thanks have
you seen the Traer yet Kiara if anybody
has any more cooking books uh please
give them to me so give them to you I do
see I don't actually know if it's like
super important to be honest I don't
want to I don't want to Railroad and be
like oh we have to be super careful when
I have when I don't know but this is
just like my inclination but maybe I'm
wrong so just be you
yes I am at the I have some Golden Rod
flowers can you boil them so that I can
drink them okay so that we can drink him
okay thank you how do I give it to you
I'll just drop it okay and I'll also
craft armor so I'll read
this I'll go for medic if you want to
give me the medic thingy it's too
expensive oh the medical journals I put
in the journal crate which is over here
Journal crate it's right here next to I
need I need one more level in cooking if
anybody has
any cooking magazine I can't make somewh
else
okay the trader sells the tea that
you're making for 144 coins I don't even
know where to get coins damn we get
coins that's crazy that great my
diarrhea is going away on thank you sir
anyway did I take the CL I'm happy for
of meat right now I found some acid if
you think that could help your stomach
problems it would help with the liquids
I guess don't really oh be do you want
to put the the cooked food in this one
the storage crate which one the right
one and we should try to figure out how
to make a farm the one that the one that
you're looking at y this are where I
need to go for my fetch Quest when did
you take this Quest oh I think you're
sharing cuz they're in the same
party I'll complete it for you don't
worry how are you already there oh I was
just walking wait I don't think I can do
it for you doesn't let me okay I'll wait
here so you coincidentally there the
moment I took it oh you can label the
boxes good time my
way what you cooking we can make we can
make glue I can eat
glue not bad idea I'm just gr meat at
the
moment okay awesome it's like a big
sleepover surv yeah I love it you look
like the how do I how do I take only one
item instead of all the items guys I
don't I know do not
know oh control right water yeah control
sorry I got to drink some that's okay
I've been dehydrated
water control
right I like not as dehydrated okay I
heck yeah why can my skin not absorb the
water from from the skin why not cuz
you're dehydrated glass STS just
disappear that's
stupid
e why why would the glass STS disappear
after using them am I just going to crap
out glass like charts now you
eat you ate the glass
raining too bad we can't drink it open
your mouth can I open my mouth open your
mouth yeah
yeah yeah you just have to look up at
the sky oh my God I already drank all
the
water in a the quest oh yeah I think you
are please here I'm so thirsty and so
unwet we do be Dr
I can't tell if they were kiding maybe
no we're not you just you have to wait
it's very
incremental I've already Dr oh spooky
storm too is there anything we can do at
night oh probably around the area oh
cry crying you have to find supplies in
here I hope the mushrooms grow ins
inside there
Golden Rod SE we're
seeing what
zombies okay where is he
stuck no I think she's doing a
quest
you oh you're on your way I'm on my way
it's really scary it's it's dark all
this very scary
oh maybe I can't Farm
here I probably
Farm a rotting
flash yeah we need a farm plot if we
want to
farm this might be all the man I can't
make my hops does any want to go to the
trainer for a quest if not it's totally
fine I didn't want to I didn't run to
rush I just thought if you going to do
something else not us I I got to go
there anyway um the is going to take a
couple minutes to cook but I played I
played might be one
upstairs it keeps saying charge meat
people
no Char meat is the food it is the food
oh really Char meat wow meat
is good at cooking look at
my that's the
option that's all I can make right now I
need one more
to I don't want to take both it's okay
it's okay
put one back challenge
eat yum you're going to eat my Char and
you're going to egg O it's so nice and
dry okay I'll cook some eggs too I'm
dying I'm dying you have water wait why
are you dying should I not be here no no
you should be here you should be here
what's happening don't worry washing the
taste off the mouth wait should we go
into a VC the yes okay yeah which one
four oh
two one to
four I
I this isn't four sorry sorry my no wait
wait what what are you guys doing are
you going to the Traer oh we're doing
ki's Quest right now we at the quest but
I started the quest before fauna and Sh
were there and it said if you're not in
the radiers you will automatically fail
the quest so all I'm going you guys love
you I'm going to make food while we're
here
campfire oh o I
have I have a lot of stuff if
anybody car want to
stuff what kind of stuff I don't even
know mechanical Parts iron pipe lead
duct tape polymer Casino coins like food
I've got food you need food and I
actually I guess I'm somewhat fine with
food but water would be really nice but
I guess you don't have water I don't
have water but I have an old sham
sandwich that caused my diarrhea it's
now slowly going away so I'd rather not
eat another I can I can relate that I
understand but so with the fire you can
cook yeah
yeah how you need a pot
though I knew need a
pot I don't have a pot damn
it wait I don't understand how do I get
this skill why is it locked I can you
might have to level up your the main
stat so if it's blocked from getting you
might have to level up strength or
fortitude the big
attribute strength or fortitude like
monster Chef or something yeah
yeah uh okay I'm dying of dehydration oh
God no is there no water water
outside
oh I'm scared where are they why is the
music so scary you're surely still uh
healthy in terms of um HP take him take
him where are
they upstairs upstairs yeah now he's
here he came down I'll look for water
why is he chasing me there's two
zombies oh oh oh oh no oh I've got no
stamina cuz I'm over encom howly do you
die after it there another one there's
another one there's another
one here we shouldn't be in here I have
I guess I'll die either
way go we left alone taking I
di my they're eating me they're eating
me not you respawn respawn I'm
respawning I'm running
[Music]
backwards spawn near my backpack let me
he how close am
I somehow there's more zombies then
there I thought there would be guys I'm
not hungry anymore I went into the
garage come into the I seem to it seems
like I'm going to die because yeah not
even my stamina up when I'm this first I
guess dying is theit better option at
this point maybe oh they're fast now cuz
it's night
time is there any downside in dying
besides that you have to run to your
inventory um it changes the difficulty
level of the game
oh to being easier yeah and then it like
changes the loot tables and stuff but
doesn't really matter we're just having
fun okay so I wouldn't mind being easier
oh my God there's like 20 zombies okay
very EX in the garage it's safer God
should I just let her kill me then my
diarrhea will be gone too I running to
the garage I'm running to the
garage he's still just on Dat
yeah just
uh this is really bad big guy I'm
opening the garage I'm opening the
garage open
it byy I have an
tion I'm going to
die wor die all for the quest decided to
die but but the stuff
we can do it if we keep respawning we'll
get it okay I mean it'll be daytime
eventually yeah yeah
yeah I very close stuff I failed the
quest do I have to accept it again oh
they're all around
my they're all jumping around my
backpack
uhoh ow oh they're all eating my while
I'm maybe we should leave because our
Quest is over
yeah no let me just take my backpack how
do I take my whole backpack there's a
button in the top right of the Box yeah
it has up arrows on it uh it says take
all uhhuh okay top left top top right of
the box top right of the so not of your
screen but of the Box what if you die
without picking up your thing oh I don't
actually know right I am also not sure
okay let's run away I'm out of here we
should find the house next to the trader
I think that's a good idea okay I think
I'm in trouble cuz I have no
speed is it because you're thirsty I see
it's cuz I'm it's cuz I have too much
stuff oh oh yeah I also there's so many
zombies but I have so much good stuff
just it's okay you keep dying you get
get your stuff and you'll go a little
farther than last time each time black
St super there a lot of zombies
though oh
no I found a a mining magazine but if
you learn it you learn how to make
coffee
ow this is I don't know it says super
strong longl lasting coffee that kept
you warmer than a well Digger ass can
craft black strap a super strong coffee
a good Miner needs to know coffee
there's way too many zombies near my
backpack and I'm freezing is your
backpack still in the in the quest
Place yeah oh no no no no no give me my
backpack I see you I see oh no did you
die again oh no you got your okay you
shouldn't come over
here you di
again I think I'm in trouble I just
don't want all my stuff to die cuz I had
so much good stuff I think the house
you're next to we can make home there
that's Oh no I got a skill on
accident die die die
die this looks like it was a child he's
wearing like teenager clothes I feel bad
okay I saw someone wearing a t-shirt
that said RZ
RZ I
is it that zombie farmer oh my God he's
got a good
Farm a nice house oh I I found a house
we can make it's really close
to the traitor okay I'm almost there
I'll start putting stuff
down I'm leaning a
mil we'll kill them at our new house F
it's not that house I don't think so
that's a DB house which house is it
wait distract the zombies I'll find the
right direction um I can't distract
them okay okay I'm running towards the
house that we're apparently okay okay
okay I'm going to put a chest down there
are zombies in here but we can turn this
into our new house um what more zombies
could you find an empty house once I
kill them it will be
empty die spawn there die no they don't
respawn okay they just spawn around you
the Clement
residence oh I leveled up oh yeah yeah
I'm in here okay it looks
peaceful what is the um I might be
leading a million zombies to our
new once I kill them they won't be here
anymore it's very wishful thinking I I
like
it wait did I lose
them hopefully okay I'm just going to
offload everything there zombies in here
I didn't lose them I didn't lose them oh
don't worry I have a gun with four
bullets
you let's barricade
away oh oh you shooting them with the
shotgun I have shotgun I have no more
arrows okay okay okay
reloading reload storage CR yeah yeah I
put that down
die I'm behind you behind you sorry it
takes me really long time to reload okay
okay okay okay okay C living room
die b
roll why can I not use the Band-Aid at
this time when I'm
hurt um I think one of the band is only
if you're
bleeding oh I
think all right well we have a house
so yes is this really where we want to
stay until we find a better place it's
good enough
okay maybe there's a pot in here it's
pretty close to the trader
too oh I still need to go see the trader
we can go pick up quests
together understand this I don't
understand this I don't oh there's half
a zombie on the
[Music]
stove what's for dinner half a
zombie how do you how do you make a
barricade um you can make spikes and you
usually plant a bunch of spikes outside
your
home how do you how do you like
barricade the window oh do you want this
Tactical Warfare book what do you learn
from that
oops oh it's assault
rifles I don't need to learn how to make
an assault rifle I don't either I'm
going I'm going unarmed fist going to do
should we make a bed roll and then place
it here or yeah I put one in here just
randomly in this
house what and what happens to the other
bed roll that we placed elsewhere
I think as long as you use this one this
is your new spawn
point
okay when I place it it is automatically
my spawn point or yeah it say it's owned
by you okay
um wait a sec I need to heal myself
somehow if you die you'll be full health
again that's been my strategy so far
oh okay I also make a wooden crate and
place it somewhere we can place it on
the wall oh
nice okay
finally
this oh I
see I got my fists
out H oh my God there's a zombie
upstairs upstairs let me punch him oh
okay I'll let you punch him you haven't
propably properly cleaned this place yet
punch his face
danger he's killing me he's killing me
you guys need help I'm I'm cling him I'm
clubbing him I'm clubing
him ow don't F
[Laughter]
me I forgot there was friendly fire
are missing
me door is Li she's in
here is this smigle in here sounds like
smigle that's my stomach we
have and this door is locked but there's
like look look do you want to spend time
together hitting this gun box oh wait
zombie I'm punching him I'm punching him
okay okay getting my club getting my CL
you guys might need help huh where
me we're danging up on the zombie I'm
going to die oh he's hurting me he's
hurting me ow okay I did the finishing
blob with my sledgehammer nice oo
cardboard bom do you want to do you want
to hit this with me hit what this gun
chest SC oh that will take a while yeah
but what if there's something really
cool in
here I believe it's
has so much HP something must be really
cool in here I think there's a zombie
downstairs is this house cursed will
there always be like zombies on
Gathering here no I unless they smell us
I'm scared oh I think they smelled
me I'm hiding in the
bathroom we have reached Day threee by
the way oh yay day
three but we're not playing today until
the seventh day ride that would
we're only playing until day four end of
day four or one more hour
yeah or two two yeah two more
hour I'm still relatively awake even
though it's 5:00 a.m. so strong I heard
you were adjusting your sleep schedule
for this oh yeah I I kind of like messed
it up cuz like my 3D live it was like at
2:00 a.m. my time because I was trying
to be more na friendly for for it and
then after that was my music video
reveal so I was just so excited so I I
stayed up long and then I was like well
seven days to die is in the middle of
the night for me so might as well not
fix my sleep
candle yeah now we're we put on land
claim block land CL
[Music]
block f are you what are you doing don't
die I'm hiding in the bathroom I hear
the zombie aggressively shall we save
the m in in the SP how do you say it I
shall thing's almost
openid 17 I have 17 HP I can't go down
there fauna I'm
sorry I wanted to place my bed roll but
there's no room in the bathroom live in
theath there's no room with the
bathroom okay don't worry this a almost
open okay is it the safe or yeah once I
break this open I'll come kill that guy
or you'll kill me
one or the other I feel so safe around
gigy she's like hardcore yeah I have to
open
this 1000 I have a machine gun now oh
yeah machine gun distress yeah yeah did
he give me ammo too I he gave me a few
shotgun shells he might be in there with
you
somewhere what if there's shotgun ammo
in this chest that would be so cool I
still got to give you I still got to
give you my shotgun ammo okay you can
also put it in the crate okay okay I got
15 machine gun rounds so I'm got to be
very careful with
my I'll go
like one shot at a
time which is not one I usually would do
with a machine gun but okay it's open
what was in it did we get anything did
we get anything GGY I didn't get
anything it was a waste of time giggy
okay um bad news f there's nothing in
the chest good news be careful it sounds
really scary down here we're on our way
to help
[Music]
you I'll clean up the
attic you're hiding here and the zombies
not even
outside but it's so
loud he is not inside the
house don't worry I will I'll kill
him don't go out there
dangerous was the zombie just a mirage
perhaps that he's here he's just he's
just
Outdoors
oh he's
chilling oh
S I want to sneak up on him he'll never
imagine someone coming from behind to
hit him on the head if I can even find a
way out of here yeah yeah yeah
what I have found a
cing magazine for people and cornmeal
and chicken he knew I was here I let him
in I opened the door like a vampire I
welcomed to our house he's going to suck
our blood the light in my eyes is f oh
no I killed
you stop this
meop she came the best
me I love S I love feeling
safe oh don't worry I spawned on my
bed oh where is he now I killed him
oh why why are you naked KY sorry I
didn't mean
to that was very made me very
uncomfortable I know I'm just like a
really buff man he's over here should I
let him inside like the last one
welcome in come in
help I'll use my
sledgehammer on her
butt don't worry I'll hit her on the
head while she distracted by eating
you let let me hit let me okay okay okay
okay 7 HP you go gy okay okay okay CH
some hey guys her don't worry I got
her good very good good progress good
progress put down the the block the
block oh the land claim block I can try
crafting one let
land I don't want to do the bed CU I'm
oh wait this is somebody's backpack is
Ski's back
probably where's the I I purposefully
spawned elsewhere now because I was
scared that if I oh other way turn
around wait did you guys already choose
spawn on your bed and you were spawned
in the house yes you're going the wrong
way right now if you turn around you're
going the wrong way saying that's me oh
you're so sweet thank
you thank you you're taking you're
having an eye of where
going me
that easy she Dr
she dropped rifle world do you want to
learn how to she dropped two rifle
worlds I need I used rifles do you want
steroids uh do I want steroids okay take
it take the steroids off of her
body this will make my better
probably this green thing
oh only 12
minutes 12 minutes of AR steroids I
never use
items don't you use machine oh I use a
machine gun oh I oh see I don't I don't
know cooking uh shooting is different
difficult I don't know anything
about guns even after all this
time H oh we have the land clim block
nice keep it's daytime if 4:00 a.m. is
daytime we so
vied
E I don't know what I expected to happen
I punched some guts until they
exploded Yik it was it was very
gross is that a zombie or a we survived
the night we did it is that you where in
the distance yeah I'm looking at a car
I'm opening this car are you looking
into buying a car in this economy I want
a car so bad we should get a helicopter
aim big or a little toig
helicopter yeah you can have helicopter
in the end game oh that dream is too
large For
Me Maybe too large for seven days I want
a bike I want a
bike oh yeah there was a bike part in
the you found right yeah handle bars for
my new
bike
a let's go get a quest
oh Nest I'm crafting lots of
arrows o nice arrows are always good I
should probably craft some more
too generally I haven't crafted in a
while try need again for arrows
feathers wood and
stone what wood and stone and Feathers m
pretty sure
yeah okay I've neglected the
feathers
e keeps punching e they keep exploding
all grossly
eoss but I got 80 XP for
that we're going to be so we have to be
the richest people in the
apocalypse I have seven bucks
yeah oh seven books or dollars books
dollars I wish I had seven books wait
can you spend money here yeah at the
trader but he's so overpriced does he
take cash no you have to uh sell the
cash you have into like your dollars are
worthless
oh there's actual bors in and corns
there is
just eat buried
supplies am scared to go in should I go
in oh that
sound hello I'll sell you Goods but if
you cross me you'll meet I got a quest
to go dig stuff up oh is it the ah it's
the first Traer Quest I guess yeah okay
good yeah start there and then we can
try the the fetch Quest again at some
point
okay oh I have iron arrow heads do you
want that GG okay [\h__\h] if you don't
like my food you
can brass brass it looks like
gold
ooh brass yeah we can maybe make a a TR
with the brass
yeah from bone
champ I have a quest 500 million miles
away
oh what quest is that um I don't know if
you see it on your map but it's called
tier one
clear no I don't think I see yours okay
I'm going to run over and kill them oh
maybe hey wait no don't go with
me oh I hope fauna was
digging okay and then we can go the
other one dig
mhm another
sandwich no don't eat that fun dis Terry
sandwi I'm getting used to it though
really can we build tolerance towards
there's a perk you can buy oh but I
didn't buy
it one
point H Chad tell me what to where to
put my point if I want to be able to
make healing
items ooh we need Aloe
Vera or correct but can you cannot make
that by default I think there's a book
for it
[Music]
cuz this is just boosting your natural
healing rate am I just supposed to
dig magazine only oh really okay did you
start the
quest yes oh no oh should I have waited
no you can start
it
okay I let my device die
uhoh not your
device not my device like I'm digging my
own grave you are I will be burying you
here where's my shovel this my shovel oh
oh you found it food here I will dig
your way out there's a zombie I will
kill you this zombie instead while you
dig your way out I'm
stuck I'm stuck don't be stuck I'm
killing him he has a very cool shirt
very not a mustache where are
you
what oh you're the you
did
whoa how can he
jump how do you get two places so fast
it's almost like you're cheating I run
really
quickly I'm getting him I'm getting him
oh no I don't want to be in this hole
ah
him oh sweet sweet
exp okay we can go turn in we're going
to the trader again so we can turn in
the quest okay okay and once you accept
the new Quest I'll go towards wherever
that starts and then we can start it
together ugy
I have an aloe vera
seed that'll be great for making an aloe
vera Farm maybe I think you need those
for healing right yep
yeah ah okay I put the shotgun shells
into my wood crate you can take it when
ever you want thank
you wait am I going the wrong way wait
is this way
right yeah that
way okay I'm out of
stamina and we just automatically be in
the same place where we were before is
it like randomized they're random quests
you can pick which one you want to take
and then I took one that's really far
west why would you do that can we get
the that's in head I know you can share
them yeah cuz that's what was happening
when I started the quest and you were
there then we were sharing it actively
but the people who weren't close to it
were not sharing it I see so we should
start it when everybody's there at the
objective
so I'll go towards the trader for now
cuz you girls are dare
ug Che what you need to craft better
gear like wouldn't I need a new magazine
for that you
might and this menu is just so much I
feel like rest was easier uh heavy armor
like that one maybe he has books he has
books yeah but don't he so expensive I
know what a
scam yeah
yeah I need an armor magazine oh I'll
return back to the house real quick cuz
I have 5 million items again oh okay me
too actually oh you
okay I'm here I see
youi
salvation no no my my took it from the
bird I am the bird mother of all ready
away with feathers in my
mouth you have eaten my children
feathers M yummy oh my God yummy
feathers the most terrifying of them all
you so happy about
it I'm so sorry I can't believe she did
that do we have to just pretend like
everything's fine because otherwise she
will go against us she keeps defending
us from zombies so I think we have to
this world in is kill or be killed it's
like we're befriending
Sauron isn't that bad it's not that bad
is it no no a bit dramatic we're just
befriending
other oopsie sorry F you like Lord of
the Rings right yes you did you try
watching rings of power no I have I have
not is there a reason for it should I
well I people [\h__\h] on it so much but the
second season that just aired it was
pretty good so scared to say it I think
I could like it cuz I really like I
really like fantasy and I really like
word of the ring setting so yeah yeah
yeah yeah people will probably like
every time I bring up Lings of power my
chat go like shut up I don't want to
hear what you're saying but but the
second season was pretty pretty good
so if you just want something more like
you know like fantasy just see it as a
separate fantasy show you know
it doesn't need to be good for you to
like
it yeah what does that mean wait say
that again it doesn't mean to be good to
be good yeah yeah interesting Teen Wolf
is my favorite show ever you think
that's a good show wait giggy giggy
giggy wait don't run out come back did
you see the ammo in in my crate up here
here here here top left why is it up
here oh thank you y it's not in the way
okay well then shall we uh did you guys
already accept the quest from the trader
or did you just I have one Quest I have
not
accepted okay well we can go to the
really far one we'll get it once we're
there for giggy okay okay we can see
there's anything fun on the way too okay
any books to read you're so lit oh yeah
that was laggy let me make sure that I
have
have why isn't it isn't on my compass oh
I see it it's 1.6 km West o o all right
but let's not get into too much trouble
until then because otherwise we might
just arrive there
dead no no it's fine keep respawning
infinitely fauna you know what somebody
says what fauna likes Twilight cuz it's
bad it's not true I like it I like it
cuz it's
[Laughter]
good you haters in the chat you
haters I mean I've never watched
Twilight you've never watched
Twilight I purposely stayed away from it
and perhaps it was the right choice
but I I don't know but you know I don't
know vampires are like a little bit too
tacky for me what about were might too
you might hate it
then but if you love anything
vampire you will probably like
it even in Sims I didn't like the
vampires the Sim vampires a little
strange vampires yeah those aren't real
vampires yeah no they seem pretty
realistic to me
have you seen a real vampire before they
act like The
Sims I I assume that Sims is a life
simulation so everything that is in
there must exist in real life yeah I she
they teleport into your house and then
they play on your computer until you
asked her to
leave have I been deceived is it wrong
have I been
B real vampires smell you from a mile
away and then smell your
fair oh no oh they got a good good
nose yeah then you just smell so yummy
to them gy are you also a Twilight fan
then no I'm a werewolf fan but I like
vampires too but werewolves are in
Twilight no but if you're a werewolf fan
Twilight is not going to be a good time
you it's a mushroom Mining Company
mushroom mining oh fun there's an RV in
here here do you think there's
stuff wait fun
wait are are you should we go in there
without gigy I'm not sure I left looks
interesting you guys should
go I'm be liing for the quest okay okay
okay oh yeah wait where where is she oh
that way that way this cool thing got
you oh the
RV yep like Breaking Bad sh I am
Breaking
Bad oo I think Breaking Bad ruined RVs
for me cuz it's all I think of now I
didn't watch Breaking Bad either wait
you should watch Breaking Bad I should I
watched it recently it's good and better
call Sal too is
good yes there's a pile of books there a
a harvesting tool crafting skill book
and a workstation crafting skill
[Music]
that's a
lot I'll just take the books for now but
I won't use them so we can share a
picture of one of the game developers
dogs every time I see like a regular
photo of an animal in a video game I
just assume that it's one of the
developers pets treasured animal is this
pict does this mean that the picture of
this bird here is also from the
developer of the game no this is like a
photo did you see this
one is the developer this bird looks so
human like oh yeah this is a dog on on
someone's lawn and then this is an eagle
at the why would why would the developer
not have an eagle he could own one I can
imagine him owning an eagle if he wanted
yeah is that legal probably not but who
are we going to tellal Eagle it's IL
legal
eagle have you guys seen the name of the
developers of this game no idea like
when you copy
paste to do that their name is on that
on that copy paste
thing their name is on there yeah yeah
you should look it up oh I forgot to put
it in my description cuz very last
minute us fire
post wait she's running oh wait what G
just like runs away and loses
got to be fast in the wilter track
her licks the ground she went this
way she's on a mission I use my vampire
senses can you smell me
m oh my
God I found Oh I thought this was a
church but it's
not that is not a cross that is I don't
even know what that
is W those are
lights oh it does look like like a the
vultures
get Zombie f the vultures please oh we
got it oh I was so mad cuz I thought it
was like a regular
vulture it's just a killer vulture no
it's a zombie vulture and you can't eat
it I feel like vult are just always
zombies yeah kind of
D be
like all
right get down get
down I can't doing so good
Arrow did I get it we're doing good
indeed Oh I thought you were a
zombie here in this world it's killer be
killed doggy dog world I want to get in
and F him him
[Music]
what's inside this guy's kind of strong
he's slapping me uhoh he has stronger
fist than
you are you okay being infected by the
zombie oh that's Theo oh it's a
lumberjack he's strong he's very
tanky ah he can
jump the oh no he's eating I'll avenge
you I'll avenge you oh
no he's eating he's eating I'll stop him
don't you dare oh he he's dead he's
dead the is such
AE I want the dress give me the dress
lady there's a
dress really nice dress Dr yeah
oh wait did I lose my experience do you
actually I thought you didn't lose
experience when you die I don't think
you do wait what's purple the purple bar
oh yeah it
is is it
lower it is I think unless I leveled up
I level up
I think I leveled up actually you're no
longer infected so we won't have to put
you
down you would do that you would put me
down I might have to Old yell you I
don't want to do it think of the rabbits
[Music]
Lenny the rabbits are so beautiful going
to have a nice rabbit farm just look at
the water and don't worry
I zoned out for a minute what are you
talking about I don't think that's old
yell well do you want to be a dog or a
human we're talking about um putting F
down she has gone through too much
already she has to go through a little
more why no what are these trials you're
putting her through should we go across
the water or should we go around the
water is it smart to travel through the
water are there sharks in the big Waters
no but you will get wet hat
on is is this guy did he used to be in a
biker gang yeah right he looks like the
bikers in
GTA except for the helmet they were
hiding
damn he's B he is really B
is to go for a Canon event oh hold on
guys I want to kill this rabbit what no
I want to F no don't hurt the rabbit I'm
sorry but I need the fat this is about B
how we eat no why the bunny it became a
fish oh we killed it it became a fish
did it Fly Away it no it dived away way
in the water yeah I just went like onto
the ground in the water and like really
far really didn't want to be eaten by
you has some crazy survival skills
bunnies on the water I guess we can go
around cuz there's so many houses
nearby yeah do you want to look into all
of them yeah who am I to turned down a
cool house a
boat we have
that that would be nice it's kind of a
weird boat though
private
yacht yeah me when I'm inviting women
over yeah I have a
yacht gives me impression that this is a
shop because there's a new sign that
says
open but I don't believe it oh hi zombie
hello
zombies
ow oh my gosh they have ceiling zombies
in here what ceiling zombies
terrifying like a ceiling maybe it's
hanging from a ceiling fan maybe ceiling
fan was the curse the the cause of
death ceiling fans nowadays guys some of
these zombies are so
tanky yeah it on day three now they
don't get strong that
fast
dead sorry I might have punched you no
no
yeah but if we go to so many places I I
feel like we might be very hurt by the
time we get to the destination just
we'll just respawn you know about that
right you know about of money from the
from the cash register we can share our
findings want oh two magazines a wood
splitter Electric crafting skill and
workstation crafting skill do any of you
use 9
MMO I use 7.62 very specific and I have
found a pipe
rifle a fully built pipe rifle acquired
do you want one FAA because do you have
a gun yet no I don't use guns has my
fist it weren't guns the the uh reward
for the digging I got a I got a a pipe
weapon oh okay a pipe weapon a
book that's a great
reward it's the only one that came with
a book it's the only one that improves
your
skills I'm E I think it is the best
one Pur uses the same oh nice then I'll
continue using cuz I have that
ammo okay
well this was I'm running out of space
yeah I'm full up on garbage again yeah
that's also why we shouldn't have you
know there's just so much fun stuffit we
can
consolidate Gigi do you want my feathers
okay I'll just learn wa did you run away
again no
[Laughter]
no I'm here I'm here will we ever run
into mountain lions I have a magazine
that teach that that gives us 10% more
damage against mountain lions mountain
lions do you want 10% it's not that much
rotting flat okay do you want
gas what okay what about iron you're
just giving her your trash we're
consolidating yeah it's you want clay
soil uh no not you want a
splint maybe do you want um cloth
fragments
and plant fibers and forum and maybe
cotton oh
no how about a sewing kit shotgun shells
I'll take those oh yeah nitrate powder I
have nitrate
powder how do I one of these I'll take
that do you want a
mushroom just a singular mushroom yeah
do you want singular
cornmeal okay I'll take the cornmeal oh
my gosh girls do you know how I separate
one item from another um right click
potentially right click okay does
somebody want this magazine it's a good
one for oh I read a few of these oh you
read if you give fun then okay or you
could get even
stronger where you oh I read a few of
these too both get stronger you want a
seed wait maybe I'll take it back cuz I
se
okay oh the seeds I'm leaving
what we're following we're following I
guess we can go across the water I
suppose Quest I'm on my
way oh there's a car in here
who
drowned guys I can't breathe here the
car drowned what kind of question is
that it's telling me that no way you
can't breathe here why not I don't know
why can't I
breathe that's weird Okay this game's
broken can I pumpk my stamina okay this
is why maybe you shouldn't swim across
big Waters because my stamina is am I
going to die scared too try breathing
I'm I'm I'm guys guys just make it AC
cross just make it my stamina loaded
back up okay while I was how am I
thirsty when I was literally in the
water this question will never leave us
I suppose yeah wait this water looks
clean maybe we should drink it it's very
green I mean blue
[Laughter]
oh nice
shot die oh oh whoa I think oh there's
another one I would really like to find
a cooking
pot I know right they seem rare for like
how much you need them yeah where's our
cooking poie he's dead don't worry we're
only 400 m away from my
quest it feels like a much longer have
than that we got so many goodies on the
way it's
true
oh this is true I have terrible news
everyone you say more water no but I I
can't breathe all of a
sudden drowning okay I'm back just keep
keep your keep your head
up I'm drowning and I'm back it's a fish
a zombie on the shore over
here Dodge him Dodge him and I'm back
and I'm drowning and and now and now
we're back we're swimming no I'm
drowning too don't worry were you had
full stamina when you left
no no oh oh I should be sprinting huh I
didn't know I was sprinting in the water
I didn't know you could it's very fine
when you're not sprinting I'm
drowning stop sprinting is fine when
you're not sprinting There's a Zombie
over here don't look at him don't make
eye contact I've already made eye
contact she's walking in the water maybe
she will turn into a drowned in the
water how can she do
that maybe she will did she change no
maybe she'll have a trident when she
turns into a drown that'd be
sick I realize now you're talking about
Minecraft why you were talking about The
Witcher for some
reason oh did you watch The Witcher
no I
didn't but I did
beat I right you were playing it you
beat it you beat it well just the just
the base game I still have the DLCs to
play I'm going to play it at some point
too should it's really
fun it's good right now I'm playing
Zelda and then also now I will start
playing Diablo again because
[Music]
Diablo
yeah g you
did you play the you did you did you
play the main start or are you going to
start from the beginning I'll start from
the beginning okay okay and we can get
together for the DLC yeah oh do you like
RPGs
fa what is a um wait did we talk about
this what does a stand for augment
reality it's like the top down style of
game
RPG yeah kind
of like Diablo yeah yeah Diablo
4 what about I played torch light too
what is that a long time ago I think
like
Diablo gy gy stop fun it's really far
behind wait I'm I'm coming don't worry
[Music]
okay gy gy so fast I'm sprinting once I
get here
yeah I'm going the wrong way actually
halfway through the main story so like
I'm pretty close apparently to the main
story ending and then I'll wait for
youy yeah I need to maybe that'll be
better than playing a World of Warcraft
together I don't know we can do both we
can do both you guys going to play wow
you want to play WoW I'll play WoW with
you really let's go kind
I only tried to play WoW once and my
experience is it took a million years to
level and then I got tired of it so I
used like the level boost that you get
when you buy it but then I switched my
class and then I had no idea what my
class did because I was suddenly like a
Max Level different class H well the
thing is I already told gigy we're not
taking any kind of level boost no level
boost yeah cuz I feel like the it's for
the Nostalgia you gotta grind through
the quests and everything go for all the
beginning like areas that you that you
experienced in the past I think when I
played it was like when was it it was
like in
2020 or something no maybe it was
earlier 2018 oh and I think they like
paired down the leveling a little bit
since then cuz it was very long at that
point
maybe there's exp like
experience I just don't I mean like the
the something that boosts the rate of
how you get
exp I want to boost the level is this
the quest spot or yeah it's a quest spot
hey did you start it yeah I started it I
think I was no am I I did do I have it I
think I oh I think I have it too
yay drop loot
a I hope they he's got shotgun shells
yay more
shotgun oh jeez they're here I thought
they were dead I don't fit through the
door how did you make it through the
door I haven't been
eating lost some weight okay I got rid
of the
door get him get him get him get him oh
there's so many of them oh this is such
a cute like American
Diner oh love not sure about the
customers
though maybe we should call the manager
like yeah guys not how you should do a
business here oh I missed my shot I am
not throwing away my shot you haven't
missed your shot with me
yet pointing my fingers can we get
married on wow is that a thing what yes
we have to have a wedding on Wow we can
invite everyone to our wow wedding yeah
oh God we got to go to the to the to the
in yeah what is it the
server spicy time and spicy time in the
in take off your armor we to consummate
our
marage and just sit down on a on a bed
and where the walk oh L we stream it
everyone has to see our marriage and
everything after too yeah otherwise it
won't be believed that you yeah that we
got married back in the day Ro where's
on the roof I think there might be
zombies up there kill them we haven't
cleared the area yet in medieval times
for royalty you know there was always
people they watching to make sure that
the the air has been placed and the lady
you know
I don't want to die I don't want to die
there's Louis Vuitton up here yeah this
I'm also oh my God don't worry don't
worry I'm taking the shot I'm taking the
shot
okay I'm sorry I'm just really into
medieval
stuff like wow
isit I'm
dying I was an
arrow who hit you with the
arrow I don't know that zombies can do
that it's crazy
I the zombies knew how to do
that that's what I
get anyone still alive we did it we
cleared the quest we did
it shotgun shipping crate why is it
always shotgun Grave Digger
mod more
Dam hurt hurt the hurt the dirt hurt the
dirt do you not want the shotgun shells
oh where are they in the crate ah and
there's 9 mm ammo which I don't think I
use do I does somebody need need the 9
mm ammo I have some in my inventory I'll
just hoard them do you need
7.62
ammo uh I need yes I need indeed I drop
here even though I have yet to use my
gun I'm scared to use it there's another
photo of a dog and I'm telling you it's
one of the developer
dogs look at this
dog it's very
[Laughter]
cute he's just wearing an outfit on a
couch this is so cute this is totally
one of the dev's pets that is someone's
dog for sure yeah they should have name
plates too yeah I don't like the dog I
don't like this dog that's the kind of
dog I don't like I'm sorry where's the
cats we need more cat where are the
cats actually one of them is lying next
to me on the bed a I can't believe she's
still here normally she normally she
goes away when I'm talking she know I
stream like talking no no no no she
likes me talking but she knows when I
stream cuz whenever I talk to the
computer she gets it and then when I'm
done talking she immediately re-enters
the room yes oh give me your
privacy our cats are so smart I thought
it was only I thought it was only my cat
didn't like and leaves a but when she's
like really really needy then she will
stay in the room like now she really
want to be next to
me yeah it's because like I interrupted
our nap that we were having and now
she's like what the hell where's my nap
I was supposed to have a nap with you so
now she's here cute it's her bedtime
it's kind of late for her it's always
her
bedtime how much HP do you girls have
83 83 I have a bow and
arrow we can try to go straight back to
the trader Traer you know yeah and drop
off all item okay oh is she dead he dead
oh damn it okay next time we're in
danger I'll test my
gun don't worry guys we're only one
point 2 kilm away from
home we get closer sound like much oh oh
I just realize that by the time we get
there he might be
closed wait he closes he closes at night
he hates us oh well we can sleep over it
should we go to jimbos wait that store
looks really cool I want to go to
jimbos 800 worms for you yeah also here
is a
zombie oh there's a lot of zombies at
jimbos wait where did you go yeah let's
let's save my ammo for the Jimbo uh
zombies the jimbos jimbos we are on our
way is this a good idea yes it's always
a good idea what's wrong with dying and
coming back to life you know workbench
it's a destroyed workbench
oh mailboxes
steal their
mail yeah mail boxes are funing we them
I can learn how to make a
coffin that will be
useful wait what do you do have a coffin
I don't know sleeping
them like a vampire a
vampire oh wrenches one wrench oh those
are useful I think you can use them on
the car in the car do items have
levels they do or do I have three
wrenches maybe both or it might be a I
think it's a level three
wrench inside here oh the door is locked
I want to be inside
jimbos I lost an HP on the fence
oh you break this oh I'm I'm dismantling
it all right oh you're crazy you're
crazy oh there we
go uh it's very loud in there and
there's a zombie behind you okay how do
we use this oh jbo is that
you taste mine she's shooting Ault okay
left my cat has decided this is enough
screaming ow ow the vult Jimbo watch out
I have a shotgun with your name on it
okay oh he has
mood well it seems the gun was very
efficient do you want some 6 7.62 mm
ammo oh
yeah I hope Jimbo has it
h i know how none of
these I can
eat is that what it is
yeah I have found so much water in
here it water a lot of water like water
we can't drink because we don't have a
cooking pot I might drink it
anyway you want to drink it for you
kiaha what water ammo oh ammo okay
that's nice thank you I found some water
I found some pure or mineral
water can I please you can drink it off
of me after I kill this person belly
butt yeah you can sip it right out oh my
goodness that's the best way to drink
water it gives it a little bit of a
taste you know a nice
taste get him get him I don't want to R
my Amo okay you can have my pure mineral
water let's go
what's in here thank you oh there's
ceiling Zombies watch out ceiling
zombies not the ceiling
zombies yum yum I'm punching his
head oh
no oh yeah oh yeah oh wow that looks
like fireworks oh my
no you
good oh
no I'll be okay where are you I jumped
down from that
room oh wow oh where did she there's
quite a bit don't kill me
I I have one HP one HP I missed my
shot sorry sorry I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry for fre don't worry I won't miss
this shot
after I drank water
man don't worry I won't miss the next
shot
ah so I will spawn near my backpack
now oh oh no okay they're gone we are
safe that was
scary I'm coming to get my backpack
oh there's somebody here still oh okay
die
waa oh God I F you with zombie my
bad Jima where are the cooking pots I
like how
unlike was it like that with Minecraft
or so when you pick up all of your stuff
it goes back into exactly same slots
where you originally had it yeah
right why super
I'm checking his
boats boats boats boats nice
boat he's got these homemade boats
too everyone in this world could only
make
boat can we get it started I
wish but there's helicopters in the game
I wonder if there's also like anyway we
can have our own boat I know then we
have to swim
anymore it would probably wouldn't even
be worth it right cuz are there any like
real big like oceans on this map
probably
not that must be good loot oh it's not
really oh should we be swimming back to
the
trader oh is it going to get dark soon
yes I'm swiming we try to make a way
back
wait do we have a fire can we make a
fire I can make a
fire or should we go back we could go
back okay I'm going
back okay am I cucumber no I'm cucumber
I'm so
cucumber damn that's why we should go
back
ladies I want to grill some
corn me too but I don't know if I can
actually I have the recipe but I don't
know if you need a pot or grill
everything in this game needs a pot we
don't have it I know it's like the
apocalypse can't you like improvise a
little bit guess
I'm just throw the corn right on the
fire be
fine eles let's make eles you would
think there'd be more abandoned pops out
here too yeah
right maybe the Traer has all of them
all right Trader we're coming back them
them when does he
close I think too early 8 or already
closed now yeah cuz it's like 10: p.m.
now uh he opens really early in the
morning but like
6 okay I'm we'll get there we we we'll
still need some time to get home anyway
wait where's I'm following fauna fauna
are you following gigy no I'm swimming
she's swimming she's still in there ah
my leg is broken and I'm over anding
wait do you need a splint oh yes I need
one of the splints
I no don't worry I'm almost there are we
going to have to take you out back and
shoot you no I'm not ready I'm not I
have so much to live
for the splint here you go
thank you what is this Flint does it fix
legs yeah it's going to fix my leg also
it's actually broken okay it's not it's
not my legs fault I just have a fracture
so oh it's not going to help me I'm
going to eat this egg
instead oh I can hold the Flint though
since you're over
encumbered okay a raw egg good no no
does not taste good at all do you want a
lamb
[Music]
fashion I'm disappointed in you girls
that you're not ready to eat a raw egg
especially youy do you want of corn I'm
eating the eggs you can have this
corn me f i don't need it you don't want
corn you I I'll take it but I have like
I have chicken rations
and but just one each okay I well we
should get running if we in one spot for
too long they'll
smell just like a vampire will imagine
the
smell of us
combined oh there's the smell like what
do we smell she's so fat I missed she's
too fast she smelled us she's killing me
I don't want to die she's a
Zoomer I hit her oh you got
her oh she's still alive
okay I think she's dead good job I mean
we could just run away from her
but we got exp right yeah we get exp
yeah okay all right you ready to swim
across the ocean ah my leg is broken oh
no good thing we have another
splint wait the zombies are coming wait
I should can I swim with a broken leg
yes if you want to survive you will
wow oh hey heals in two hours oh wait
that's pretty good speed can heal your
leg like that speed oh zombies Sprint at
night that's why they're so fast makes
sense so fast like
[Laughter]
vampires I am definitely swimming slowly
what are your thoughts on zomb iie
vampires I mean vampires are kind of
zombies right they're Undead so do you
think zombies are
hot
no there's only one hot zombie one hot
zombie yeah there's
one like the ones in this game not
really the ones in the dress still have
kind of banging bodies though yeah I did
notice the one of the red dress
I they model them like
that she was a she was a model in her
past
life um when I get out of this water can
I have a splint or whatever it is yes of
course thank
you I'm almost out of the water too the
one person without a broken
leg so
fast what fun also broken leg no wait I
thought I thought your leg got healed
immediately by the spint I think mine's
a fracture I have to look at my debuff
oh it's a sprained
leg jumping or sprinting will delay
healing or even hurt you what the
zombies will catch me this finally made
my dream come true I always wanted to
break a
leg you did wait really yeah I never had
an experience like breaking something I
mean I I have't either but I don't
really want
you you never dream of having a cast and
having your friends okay kind of kind
of and then like I don't know your
friends always carry your backpack for
you like to your next CL maybe they
would would
they you want to break your legs so
necessary have
friends I you thank you all right how
does one use this where did it go oh oh
it's it's like a ah I see use does it go
away right away it does go away but I
have like 39 M of a leg I don't
understand what that means 39 M of a
leg
l oh I think it's something like a cap
in how much I could run or no I don't
know is it
minutes a minutes
oh okay that's confusing because I could
also stand for meters
so I see I can't run or my leg hurts
more damn this Affliction my stupid buck
of
[Music]
life okay okay are we there yet are we
there soon 6 90 M don't worry we're
really
close oh okay well then this place looks
familiar oh we're in America wait this
is the place this is the place that
where we were chilling and hanging out
when or is it when we were um testing it
out a couple days ago
oh at least at least the group that I
was with when we were testing the game I
think we were just in a field yeah and
then
stabbed me while we were talking staff
was talking to us I just got stabbed
stabbed you because you punched me you
didn't even notice you punched me you
should take this to court hey I you have
no proof this you have
no does it feel faster if I use another
splint I don't know you should
try kind of want to
try see if it stacks
oh you cannot use that at this time okay
but I think if I Sprint uh the time
increases for how long it takes to heal
doesn't like a sprinting I hear a zombie
I'm scared no sprinting with the
splint her eyes are glowing red uh B
strong together we have two guns we
could take a reded
one we have six Fists
we can't use them like fauna does though
she she kind of she's kind of the
Fist more than you how disappointing I
know all I am was a shotgun and a bow
and arrow maybe you should give your
fist like is it like a a weapon fist
weapon you should give it like I mean
the not in game I mean your actual fist
there's a there's a dangerous zombie oh
God oh God I can't run okay I'm going to
try
oh stand still I'm out of
shots ouch ouch it hurts me I'm going to
die stand still let I can't it's going
to kill
me that hit she oh oh no she's still
alive still still alive still alive oh
oh oh oh reload
faster I'm out of I'm also out of ammo
I'm out of am out of ammo oh she's dead
she's dead she's dead she's dead it's
cool it's cool it's cool we're chill oh
level up level
four oh we're at the Shady Slaughter RV
that's the RV with the
dog it's just a picture don't worry it's
a real dog I started sprinting on
accident my
ankles if you die do you lose the quest
I don't think so only if you're in the
process of doing
it aren't we in the process of doing it
now it's done return to Trader there's
no way that we can fail it now knocking
on
wood I hope he happens soon how do how
how do I repair my mealing weapons and
tools um if you press tab there should
if you click over it it should say
repair underneath it wait really down
the icon you just need the m it's gray
out cuz I don't have the materials but
it doesn't show me what materials I need
otherwise I'm blind I don't know I'm not
sure where did you go what it
needs maybe there's a popup that tells
you when you try it or you might need
the book for it if it's high level why
do we need books for everything and this
economy I was able to rep repair my
sledgehammer though I guess the
materials are just whatever you would
originally need to build the gun for
example but I didn't build it
so there are repair kits also I found
one
[Music]
once we're so close I can smell her just
like how the zombies can smell all of us
combined is your leg well enough to be
running no I forgot I forgot
this is so
sad the uh zombie but this one's eyes
aren't glowing so it's okay don't worry
I'll try not to hit you with my bow and
arrow
oh oh he's
dead he's indeed dead you're you're you
have feathers in your mouth once again
there so
good I just love feathers feathers too I
eat the feathers know how long I can
tolerate
this more
feathers not
[Music]
again you know it's crazy how many birds
there are cuz they're laying eggs
still and and yet I haven't seen a
single bird I only seen vultures you
think they're the one laying the egg
well yeah that's what I was going to say
what does this tell us of about if egg
or bird came first when there's only
eggs
around I think the egg came first yeah
but then why is the egg not making the
birds if
there I guess maybe we should stop
otherwise we're we're destroying the the
bird line watch me put this egg in my
mouth
no give it to me I'll sit on it and I'll
hatch it I'll
no ow she's stabbing me why you killing
our future well don't worry I ate all
the eggs in my inventory Al I didn't
stab you I sledg hammered you he sledg
hammered
me I'm 14 seconds away from being cured
for my my bad leg wait are you infected
14 oh I guess you just had a fractured
leg just my poor sprained leg can you
two girls give a kiss on my leg maybe
that will make it go away um one oh your
toes are I'm out of
here thank you wow I feel like that gave
me a big healing
BM I'm healing the world is healing
really
honestly yeah you've already forgotten
about Gigi eating all of the eggs why
would you remind
her
I Orange lady why h no I would never eat
the eggs on the ground that I found
never you are lucky that I am reliant on
you are we there yet we're so close to
our house I know right are we going home
yeah the tra's not open right now oh
yeah there's a zom she's going to bite
also I think our session is basically
end is it ending at the at like when are
we ending it no Day end of day four or
what I think that's the end of day
four cuz I feel like wasn't there like
there was kind of a plan so that we can
time when the when the invasions
are
yes Trader opens Trader opens at 4:00
a.m. 10 minutes wow why is so Random
that's so early uhoh
he's on all
fours barel just like a
werewolf that's the sound that that
thing makes sounds what
apparently I make sometimes
what we have an example no wait what's
that called again I might die I'm going
to die
goodbye he can jump he has the jumps he
can
jump he can jump he can jump a stop
revenge he's juming Revenge oh he he
died he died he died a raptor oh yeah
people said I sound like a raptor
sometimes I think when I laugh or no was
it when I laugh or when I I don't know
but sometimes apparently I sound like a
raptor and that sounds like a raptor to
me does sound like a
raptor right I need to hear example yeah
I need to hear you do that I honestly
don't know when do I do that Chad when
when I laugh really that's so wrong
I don't laugh like that I laugh like a
lady I'm going to kill this deer so I
can feed my dependent wives like that
you found a deer if I can kill this then
my wives will depend on me more and they
can't leave me cuz I Stockholm syndrome
them in the apocalypse are we the wies
I've missed every single one of these
arrows she's a little bit
delusional don't worry I kills it we
have meat for dinner I do appreciate
that but I learn how to cook it though
I'm going to learn how to cook it for
you wait I want to I want to punch it to
I want to get animal fed give me give me
I I think did I no I Arrow we're home I
didn't get any animal fat but I got some
steaks
okay so uh I wonder if we if it would be
worth it to not just rely on bibo
cooking for everybody especially esally
when our teams are often separate maybe
we should also learn how to cook we can
learn how to cook I think it's good that
multiple people know how to cook
corn does meat go bad like raw meat does
it go bad no it's I need a grill I don't
have a cooking grill it's over it's over
how do we make a workbench oh we need
workstation level
10 D this is so different diffult I know
much oh I have a like a fire buff wow
wholesome is there an auto
deposit um no move items to fill up oh
there is oh there is on the
bar on your inventory
[Music]
what is this ergonomic G ah will it be
easier to use the
gun I feel like we're going to die of
carbon monoxide
poisoning no we have an alarm
it'll house is filling with smoke right
now
is here it's
fine oh my God it is very it's we have
open walls do you see the window out
front we're missing the
window yeah it'll be okay we'll be fine
in
here um
question although you oh wait
recipes chat is this also from a
magazine
this
also
skill stone tools should I put a
what need what
oopsies not mean to stab things who
Digest
[Music]
do we have any more magazines lying
around that nobody has read yet that
could be useful I put I don't think so
these two cooking in here if you want to
learn how to cook Jesse we have to
cook oh yeah the cooking
magazine who of us should be the cook
who who should be the chef I think I
might have one point in it already oh
then go for it wait do I
where's
cooking there's a lot of cool stuff in
here the
potato why you keeping the rotting flash
will that ever be
useful we just never maybe it will be
H could be I need one more duct tape and
20 scrap polymers and I can make a de
collector a hole oh I do have one level
okay I'll read some I could make
cornbread but but but I we don't have
any cooking
items cooking items as in like a
store yeah there isn't like a pot or
grill literally have
nothing do you think the trader will be
open
now did they sell like a pod I think he
has some I I know we have enough money
for
it I can make grilled
meat wait can I no I
can't I can make something
though cornbread chat what should I
learn what should I you can maybe buy a
pot or Grilla at the trader yeah we
could put our money together I think
after this trip we have quite a bit I so
drunk right now I'm
fast as and Furious what are you
drinking I drank some beer and now I'm
seeing double where where are you just
started
sprinting to get so much done while I'm
drunk
this so can I not put a skill into this
chat is this magazine only I still don't
understand this whole
menu I know it's a lot
right what weapons do you like so far I
don't really care I mean I think it's
good to have one like weapon like a
hammer or so besides the
gun just in case I run out of ammo so
for now I'm doing slash Hammer the
Traders open everyone these are the
books the Traer open okay
you guys already so far SM off the face
doing one job doesn't make ladies got it
we don't have to turn it in at the same
time right it will feel it will feel
more wholesome I turned it
in I so
fast what a Zoomer you think he'll be
mad if I dismantle his truck yeah he
makes a noise and everything he's
like yeah try
Ste his stuff why didn't you just carry
me with my broken
legens he has a cooking pop for 600 and
a cooking grill for
600 wait I don't wait how do how much
money is that I have 400 on me oh I knew
you were Casino token in your inventory
I have I have almost 200 Casino tokens
oh oh wait that's what it wait there's
some in the um there's some in the chest
too oh we can get a
pot is is there no way to find a pot out
in the open world I guess there is we
just have to find
it it's probably very rare jackass you
sell
stuff it's only worth nine the cash you
must be yeah the cash you should sell
and you get the coins that he hased is
it worth it good luck kid
uh I would yeah yeah yeah I don't think
you can use the real money for anything
else the the the cash the US dollars or
whatever that is I got quest to go to
the mushroom Mining Company oh we've
passed her that was the Minecraft thing
that you ran away from and me and FAA
looked into it for a moment oh now we
can kill it for
real wait
he how do I give back the
quest how did you give back the quest oh
I just spoke to him and then he's like
here's what I have for you cuz you
completed my
quest oh oh I'm so dumb this menu is so
overwhelming chat I'm sorry tactical
Warfare proofs assault rifle crafting
skill crafting skill a bundle of free
random oh I think I'll go for the what
did youth girls choose I took the
club I took the book what you got the
club from oh the club book randomiz oh
okay oh oh he gives you 400 Casino
tokens too that's
crazy oh he's so mean
though can treat us like this just cuz
he's richer than us in the apocalypse
he'll be hearing from M can that's the
worst part once we get our cell phones
working again we can tear down his small
business and leave bad reviews on yel
yeah yeah are you already going to the
next oh no I'm going home first okay
okay you got to wait for us wives should
we yeah wait for your wives my wives
that I'm making dependent on
[Music]
money cooking pot Andor gr we should get
the pot 700 coins
now you take the one from the
house yeah
yeah yeah we can we should we should you
know invest in if we get the pot we can
boil our water so it's no longer dirty
and disgusting oh yeah wait I have a
water purifier but I don't know how to
use it oh
interesting where is it I don't even see
the
pot oh I took the ones inside pot the
chest we have 500 or I pulled it
together I have
521 oo so maybe we can get both the
grill and the pot yeah we can make clean
water oh okay wait this water purifier
goes in your hat that doesn't make any
sense oh maybe you can drink dirty water
and it's like a straw you have a br
attached to your
face I purchased the pot so do you buy
Grill they're trolling me it
doesn't oh why would they lie to you
okay that's
and how much Italian did you learn with
her
um I I feel like I already had a good
amount of knowledge cuz I learned it in
school a little bit
so it was like kind just remembering
what I learned there like what she was
teaching me was like stuff I already
learned in school but I had to remember
some of it she reminded you about
Italians I am pretty decent why did you
take your hat off seeing your does go in
your hat bright Joker green hair is just
so
shocking all the Stu was there no better
green than that no
is
the once or twice that green should fade
into a more nicer F green yeah why you
say it's di it's
natural I'm sorry girl that doesn't look
natural to
me even though you're
nature not very natural do you have 100
coins I can have yes why are
you with you you be barefoot don't judge
her she's Barefoot by default sorry
mean no s I respect this girl got a
cooking girl I'm going to go back home
okay okay she what happened she's so
intimidated let's go I got the pot you
got the grill and we got the girl also F
and the girl okay
trying to put my shoes back on yes
yes were you modding your shoes too yeah
I was Mo
modding yes modded shoes well you modded
your shoes huh got a cool flame on it
now what no
way it's like when you put charms on
your Crocs you are Barefoot still so I
haven't put them back on
yet I should just AFK for 24 minutes cuz
my my Fe are still
broken I'll eat some
pears oh I Love Pears but I feel like
they're often a Miss like they're either
hit or miss that's very true
pears Grill depends on the type of pair
yeah you can make us grilled meat now
fauna I can I think I'll put the meat in
here so you can cook
it does it really get more if I run
let's
see wait should I cook our stuff does it
go bad no it doesn't go bad it's fine it
doesn't go bad does not so I can just
cook it all
yep let's go I'm making grilled corn it
went
up it did go up up a
minute grilled corn he
L
wow I I'll drop free steaks can you take
the RW oh
God you're cooking them too I didn't I
didn't want to drop in over there thank
God they're not catching
fire oh wait I can't make good meat yet
that's okay I can only make charred meat
should we wait our house cing I guess we
could wait a bit open this she's getting
better at cooking don't bully her oh
gotcha magazine gotcha I got Rob
robotics crafting skill two of them and
armor crafting skills two of them and
spare crafting skill two of them oh
wow I'll definitely learn the armor
crafting skill
I'll learn this
too I don't know what kind of Robotics
you can make in this game but sounds fun
can you put the pot in oh yeah uh
how I can make cornbread I think yeah
you put it in the thingy oh oh okay yay
our
cooking fancy I have to learn how
to girl sometimes watch like those
videos on YouTube where like pretty
ladies will like Vlog themselves going
camping and like really professionally
like they're absolute pros at camping
and sometimes they bring their dog or
all or there's like at these camping ons
sometimes they have cats apparently and
then the cats will go to their camp and
hang out with them through the night
which is so cozy I want what they have
seen those I want to learn all those
camping skills man should we go camp
thing IRL yes yeah IRL I would love to
but does any of you have experience C no
okay should we go
glamping
glamping maybe like honestly I feel like
glamping is a little bit too much maybe
like an in between between camping and
glamping yeah we don't have any running
water but we have an
RV what IRL or name I'm not sure what
IRL we have to get the IRL
RV you have an RV no we could rent one
inv we're investing in an RV I will say
that I have camped in the very very
wilder
wilderness be like last year and made a
video about it and have uh provided
myself with eggs from wild
chickens wild chick I remember that
video could you watch
this I wasn't okay for what did you like
the scene where I I like cut from like a
baby chicken
to it's cinematic I will definitely say
Ju Just so I mean I think you understood
what happened there but no chickens were
harmed in the making of that
video yeah that was the real wilderness
you can be our camping Pro you can teach
us how to
Camp okay I don't really know how it
works but I have a
tent and a a nice sleeping
bag can we all is your tent big enough
for all of us I think we could fit cozy
no we would
snuggle I'm down oh sorry I took all of
your water out it's taking 30 minutes to
cook what's wrong with my 30 minute
water it wasn't it wasn't outputting one
at a time it was just going to wait 30
minutes to cook all the whole
stack I want to make
cornbread I've never had cornbread
before we need more cooking magazine you
never had corn we should get cornbread
IRL right yeah I do I do need more
cooking magazines oh I don't think I
think I have one we can run towards
doing the mushroom Quest while our stuff
is cooking and then maybe go to houses
on the way and we can find some more
magazine I have a magazine that teaches
you how to make super strong coffee I
think we need
coffee I thought it was a mining
magazine but it seems like it teaches
you coffee I don't
know well if you're in the need for that
it's in my
crate you can learn become powerful of
coffee there's a lot of H life members
that you could bait with the coffee you
can wo with coffee yeah yeah rule the
world coffee rules the world if you like
corn cornbread is excellent but
cornbread is something like cake right
and for me cake shouldn't taste like
corn it's not really cake I mean it's
sweet but you eat it with Savory Foods
usually I feel like the texture is un
like a cake
too
yeah huh all right it's kind of uncommon
here in Austra I
think
yeah what's it called anyway mice C mice
P German what is
it mice mice
M I'll look it up mice Port mice port
cuz corn is mice and bread is B
chat why are you not telling me normally
you tell me everything I guess the
German speakers are sleeping right now
it's. I guess they are I'm my
really well well well oh wait oh no
never
mind I thought we didn't go to the Traer
yet but we did wait KY where are you why
are you 200 M away already running no
I'm hit I'm hitting rocks and trees go
to the mushroom place we can go to
mushroom Place yeah we should go to
mushroom Place let's go as long as one
of us has the quest we're good right
yeah yeah yeah I think so okay wait I'll
drop two more things off how's your leg
is your
leg it still needs 17 minutes and if I
rush it will be longer oh no
Timber Timber are you yelling timber I
was going down I'm yelling timber
timber
yippe
yipp
yipp yipp huzzah
huzzah well everyone should come to my
house irel and then I'll drive you to
both Costco and to get
cornbread and you can be my passenger
princess and you can sit on each other's
laps and we can get pulled
over what what no I'm fine
sitting what the I'm going to I can't
just have only one of you be my
passenger princess it's either are you
not the passenger princess if you're in
the back no you'd be it's like then it's
an Uber it's like hello you're uber is
to Pi you up pretty good too right where
was the I don't want to run all the way
to the trader if the quest thing is in
the other direction oh no it's this way
yeah okay okay okay where we need a car
I know we need a car so bad do you see
where all of them are inside that's
where our Quest is the rest of them
where all oh are
they oh they're
there
ah okay oh there's a bunch of people
there ah the last H cuz some people
already ended their Stream So the
remaining girls uh came together it
seems see
M we're the last one standing for today
huh yeah yeah well do they have a
cooking grill and a pot we should ask
them we should flex but they'll probably
yeah should cuz wasn't bio already
cooking with her bare hands
potentially I see that is not quite the
same make a splint no I I can't use
another splint cuz I already have one on
but 15
minutes 15 minutes unless I run too much
then it's more again uh this sucks I
regret this already I why did I wish a
broken
leg how did you break it in the first
place cuz I fell from a high oh like
Mountain this game is too real yeah so
scary the diarrhea and the broken leg
then the Vampire Zombies and then the
really sexy zombies too so realistic
that's so
realistic and then me objectifying the
really sexy zombies it's like can I not
catch a
break I play video games for
escapism watch horror movies no scary
sometimes sometimes I'm sure there's
sexy dmes in in there too right should
we find
one I hate horror movies yeah they're so
scary it is spooky mon yeah October I'll
watch a scary movie if it has a sexy
zombie in
it we should just watch scary
movie The First Watch Scary Movie you
know do you know scary movie
yeah we can watch scary movie The unary
seen it isn't Dumb which is that the one
with Jason no that's Friday the 13th I
think the first one is the one with the
exorcism on the lady where wait a supply
drop I'm running for it yeah see those
suckers not if I hit those first wait I
can't run so fast we'll get it for you
oh they're the supply drops are really
far okay um I don't even see oh see they
far it is so far are they good I'm not
they might be good if we get them before
they do even though we're working
together yeah don't forget that
we're not enemies we're not Rivals like
in Rost or Soul maybe we should be we
might die though cuz it's noon right
now it's okay what's a little death in
the grand scheme of things wait why
would we die oh you're already going for
it she's coming see
you I need drink I'm out of here how
much longer do you do you girls
personally want to play today um until
stopping at the 4our Mark right so is
that in in you mean in 10 20
minutes so is it worth running there for
you
two yeah it's only 400 me away right
yeah well then don't get distracted like
a Zoomer all the time and run into other
places while you're going there oh don't
worry I already
did F stop her I can't I really want to
see what's in this
you'll never make it in 20 minutes I'll
make it we're so close it's actually not
that far yes actually not that far we
ran further for the quest but does that
mean we're not going to the mushroom we
can still go we'll make it I don't think
we'll make it running we're so fast
there might be a mountain in the way oh
no a No Mountain High Enough girl a no
mountain low
enough just get me to that supply drop
right now there's a there's a mountain
okay but what how do we get around this
mountain there has to be a way around
it get yourself a
horse and then oh no just go straight
up I need a goat hey I haven't seen
horses in this game yet I guess there
are no horses if there was a horse I'd
eat it already
what well the hor is defeated it so
much you are such a
werling what is this
scarecrow this Farm is using a naked man
as a scarecrow I have arrived at the
mushroom Mining Company I will just wait
here until you girls come because my leg
is healing slowly we're trying to find
out how to scale this mountain oh I just
went right up it oh you can go right up
yeah okay okay I need
food just like a goat hope I have enough
room oh wait I have all oh no egg egg
egg egg please please please egg please
egg yes
egg uhoh there's a Hopping zombie over
here fun are you carrying food with you
yeah okay when you come here I need like
at least a piece of something okay thank
you
there's some good stuff in
here was worth
it girls look at the
time plenty of time plenty of time I'm
almost at the other supply
drop
okay let me look where you
are oh oh you already collected one of
those supply drops what was
inside um a blueberry pie oh armor plate
Rod Golden Rod
tea craf skill magazine bundle a
blueberry pie and a claw hammer well you
said blueberry pie twice we are two wait
did I oh there just
one one I really like are you hungry for
like am hungry
[Music]
IR the talk about cornbread made me
really want cornbread gigy what's in the
second one six books and a Blaster cast
for your broken foot oh oh a shame that
you're healing in 10 minutes
yeah too
late well for next
time I also got two fisting books for
FAA wait I want that I want the fisting
books nice
okay we're heading to the
mines
okay come over
here yes
yes
Moria I want to watch the
H which one the new ones the new ones
there's a new one they're not really
that new yeah there's like an old
animated movie of the hobit not that one
um no no no
no no I just want to watch the CL so to
say I guess you can't call them classic
but the one that you know that I mean
the free Hobbit Mar Freeman yeah yeah I
do like him as
bbo yeah bbo Bing you know for my last
for
my up until now all like my birthdays
and anniversaries I have collected
several greetings from Lord of the Rings
actors have you yeah I did get uh Sam I
think right oh and I do have uh an
autograph of Sam I think oh yeah and I
got Bill ball and I got fro too right I
have uh like video messages of threee of
all those three that's aesome there so
many of them yeah
you're almost done to my
mom what almost done you're collecting
all of them right you're going to get
one from every single actor well I I
don't know I would like gimly I would
like to get one from gimy if he does
that stuff but I I'm guessing he doesn't
cuz otherwise I probably would have
already got the
video no you have collected them all I
know I got Pippen I got
Pippen s and Pippin that was it right
right I didn't get
Billo Pippin was so fun
is like so funny
literally do you guys know watch did you
ever watch gimo
girls no no I remember you talk about it
though why does nobody relate to me with
g girls I have yet to find somebody who
likes the show as much as
me I like the
meme the M the meme go piss girl
is that from Gilmore Girls is it
not why man that's go of girl there just
so many
girls oh
God or is it from Golden Girls because
they're golden I don't know I don't
think the Golden Girls are telling each
other go
P oh my god when I when I Gil girls to
cie she thought I was talking about
Golden Girls and that was a pretty funny
misunderstanding cuz I was just yapping
about Gil girls this whole time in her
head I'm talking about old
ladies hello come made it back you made
it would you like this blueberry pie oh
please thank
you take the F
thingss yes thank you
eat these magazines the blueberry pie I
think gave me a running
buff I got more fisting magazines so
many oh a bow magazine two bow magazines
and two explosive
magazines
wow nice what do the explosive magazines
do let me
check explosive crafting wow okay does
anybody already have anything on
that not sure I don't think I don't
think I
do do you want spear
[Music]
hunting is that the CRA for crafting
Spears yeah oh bleeding damage Spears
have a 25% chance to cause bleeding
damage well that's kind of
cool uh interesting I don't use Spears
right
now someone should take wait is she
stealing our stuff no no I took it I
took it paranoid too I mean I guess
we're friends I guess we're all friends
need
REM
holy oh I have another cooking book for
you maybe you can make us meet I can I
can make you meet now there's a person
inside the quest so I can't start it yet
oh I oh I don't know why but but aren't
they just leaving right now cuz you
already came out of here why can't I
start it free ah bi bi also
left so I I think they're done with that
Quest now let me in let me in the quest
one of you should take the banded armor
modbe I have to dig and put it on your
shirt can you just do that oh yipp yes
oh so remove your armor and then there's
like a modify slot and you put it in
there oh wait wait don't run so fast let
me try that remove the armor modify slot
is giggy already running in there don't
worry I'll clear it out I'll clear it
out for you so you don't have to worry
about a single thing oh that's so cool
ah maybe that works the same way with
the shovel then yeah yeah
ah F how did you figure this out I think
my chat told me
wow wait how do I wear it now
uh uh okay I got it oh it doesn't really
reflect in the visuals but okay I'm sure
you're stronger now I'm sure I am
mushrooms oh can we eat them yeah I
think we can at least pick them up for
now and then cook them for
XP for forood
oh well I have no ammo at all it seems
so we have to go me
melee ow ow ow oh jeez this bone knife
is not so efficient I don't think it is
do you need a better weapon C was saying
oh you got to get the bone knife it's so
good like bones it's for the hunting
animals so you can take their skin and
wear
it really no it's just for you get more
um items when you kill an animal if you
use the knife oh let's go deeper Gigi is
like probably really deep in it yeah
yeah I
am what did you go I guess we only have
we have like nine minutes 10 minutes oh
yeah yeah we got to rush Speed
Run
ouch oh no
yeah get
him
ow
just swinging at
him dead he's dead he's dead he dead
take my arrows from
him do we go up here yep I can see
inside of
you so so
empty empty
there nothing in
[Music]
there I am full of joy and happiness as
long as I with you girls oh I saw that
so what you're seeing I think is just a
mirage stream Mirage stream
Mirage every time I see you shake your
hips I'm obsessed with the the sequins
they like sparkles on the shorts thank
you thank you so good I'm glad you like
it Tak new song hey wait I'm too scared
to make that jump with my broken leg
Yeah you could always wait over there
there's knuckle wraps in
here level two oh and ammo and a muffled
connectors mod I don't know what that's
for oh that's my ammo let's go muffled
connector
make it more
silent like why do I need to make
stealth kill these zombies yeah I don't
know cuz if they can't hear you then
maybe you can't alert other nearby
zombies or so I don't know think is
there anything up there no it's just a
shortcut oh you can go back around or
you can make the shortcut to the
entrance oh I'm scared to make me too me
too I'm going to break my leg again
wait I'm scared to use the ladder we
already cleared it yeah it's baby Zone
what was there to clear so easy I think
Gigi just did everything this is just
like parkour civilization right now you
guys are jumping for the chicken Beach
no it's
Minecraft you should watch it I watched
the entire thing at two times speed
yesterday which is like wait 4 hours of
Minecraft yeah Minecraft Parkour
civilization I'm lost perhaps possibly
no never mind I'm fine also I can't
believe I will give you credit because
we still have 10 minutes or 9 yeah yeah
the tra and this okay I think we're
winning not that it's a competition but
if it was I don't know maybe the the
others aren't doing so bad either does
TR show up and they have like a
helicopter already yeah no no I think
we're winning we should get to cocky
also I'm thirsty do we have water at
home maybe we have so much water cooking
right now okay I'm going to drink out of
a pond cuz I have the mod that lets me
drink out of a pond want to
wear helmet lets me drink out of the
pond I think how you just your head
in um I think wait how do I
drink uh open your
mouth Gul gulp gulp gulp gulp gulp oh
you need your
hands wait I'm I'm 130 M away from you I
want to try to wait don't you shouldn't
drink it unless you wear the helmet I
can give you the helmet yeah yeah I'm
almost there I'm just trying to not run
too fast cuz I have 1 minute left on my
foot the walking Bri
filter
[Music]
mhm 55 54 53
52 oh I found you girls hello hello
Governor blue is f fun oh okay let me
experiment and fill my tummy with
water wow
primitive Hood where is
it ah there it
is wow so how do I drink the water in
here uh have an empty hand and then you
can push e at the Ed
what but I'm just punching it again
girl what come over here H I thought you
were just messing with me again no
traumatized from
crony can't believe this
works
oh is there any indicator to see like
how I think you're not supposed to drink
too much right or you'll get sick
oh press yeah but I would like to see
like good look cuz we have a bar for
like stamina and a bar for health do we
not have anything like that for drinking
there's on the on the bottom right side
you see it underneath your ah the blue
one super hiden wait is that oh and
green is
hunger is it purple is exp maybe yeah
purple's exp and then left side is
hunger and then right side is water oh
wait I shouldn't be drinking this
without the
helmet just slurping it up here it is
here it is it's okay in the water it
didn't seem too bad it seemed fine okay
A little bit of fine little bit what are
you doing with the gun oh that's
bi why is she threatening us I don't
know we better go turn our quest in yeah
we should go and then end it maybe she's
telling us like girl you have to end the
stream today get off of the server get
off the
server soon soon
just getting back the
quest people scares me I know why she
just walking menacing around cuz we got
the supply crates is that why well
they're ours she
mad she mad well she got to stay
mad oh I think our last name is the
Clement yeah our resident that's our
house yeah that's our house name
everybody wants to talk to this guy why
can't he talk to mon one person I don't
know you can talk to him you have to
angle yourself a little differently from
them oh I guess so yeah what do we have
this
time I'm getting the medical journal
yeah I'm getting the magazines again too
what do you mean you're getting the med
does he only offer one to you I get he
only offered one I get bundles all the
time
what maybe maybe this one medical uh
Journal is better than all these that
I'm getting
maybe let's open gotcha time I have
received explosives crafting times two
Sledgehammer crafting uh two of them
okay and spare crafting ah lame no wait
that's the old one armor craft is that
is that from before I got I think armor
crafting is new I learned
the can you
upgrade your weapons to the next
level me I don't know anybody is it
possible I don't even know how how I
would go about doing oh you can't you
have to recraft it I think yeah I got to
get the skills going
H wait did they
leave one of them left
left oh CR time it's
time yeah it's time it seems to
be oh they also left the voice
chat oh are they they ended
already I want to say I had a blast with
you girls I'm glad we got
[Music]
I mean I I feel like it's probably like
lame if we always stay in the same
groups but if we end up I don't know
somehow up together tomorrow again I
wouldn't mind I wouldn't
mind
together this is our Clement
house you found the house
already I'm running okay I can run now
my my leg is
healed it was fun
it was fun yeah we did so
much yeah
yippe we can end once kiawa gets back
home I'm running I'm running I'll go hit
some
trees let out your
aggressions why you hitting them why
don't you get an axe yeah you use the
stone
axe so you are using it right oh yeah I
am okay but if you really want to let
out aggressions you should use your
fists that's fa's job to fist the trees
she's the master Fister
here right you lost your job I lost my
job in seven days to die she became the
fter I saw the tree fall
Timber okay I'm home welcome it doy
M no no no no but I mean that food would
probably be also nice to be
greeted by when I come home my I'm hry
I'm not that hungry it's fine I have
some pears no it's fine I'm not actually
hungry okay okay is our water done yeah
a lot of our water is
done
cornbread hey is the water in in the
yeah it's inside it how inside where's
the corn meal oh I took put okay now I
can put it in the top
chest I can't find anything wow where's
the
cornmeal I've got some cornmeal too I
think in my chest yeah I got two
cornmeal we had
more I did not take it maybe we have
been no I'm might wait it's literally in
my
inventory I'll put the cornmeal into
this seemingly food focused chest I'm
making a bunch of cornbread okay okay
okay shallel be time out it's time to go
let's get out of here
goodbye my sweet
princess
farewell farewell thank you for
playing thank you I guess tomorrow is
same time mhm is it an hour earlier hour
God yeah an hour I have a collab but if
I can make it I will see you guys okay
you going to join Midway through or I
might join Midway through if I can oh
okay okay goodbye keep the house warm
for you I'm going to come back you're
going to be so much more well fisted no
going to
cook
that I I don't know what other words
Master Fister uh puncher
p knuckle knuckle girl Knuckles and
Sonic and
Knuckles
yeah all right all right then good night
I guess bye bye good night bye bye take
care see you
later
by okay I left thank you all for joining
today I made sure to hide the screen
just in case I don't flash the I don't
know IP or something thanks for watching
I hope you enjoy I had lots of fun
playing with them tomorrow I will be
playing Planet crafter with noesa but I
will be back on the server the next day
and I'll hop on at any time that I
possibly can if I see someone online I
might hop on no POV okay good night
everyone I am now we're going to find
food find something good good day good
grind today where is my ending sh
goodbye farewell
[Music]