n
[Music]
oh
n
[Music]
K KY
King ah
hello hello hello hello oh
CH what I prepared you where did you
go oh K hello
hell smoothie what are you looking at me
for hm baby I had a nap
today I slept a lot in
total I was just very uh much in a
cuddly mood and my cats were too we were
cuddling our hearts out
and honestly when I wake up and it's
already dark outside it just doesn't
feel right so I think my brain wants to
just be in bed even more than
usual but um it's okay I had breakfast I
had a little bit of pizza before the
stream and I have left over pizza for
after the
stream um yeah welcome to the graveyard
shift yeah oh my God it
is weird it just feels wrong by the way
I went back to my archive to check
something the exact time when I left the
server and I was the last one to leave
the server was like around uh day 19
6:40 a.m. the reason I noted this down
is because I read a comment that there's
a common very common bug I don't know if
it always appears but um there's a
common bug that like just by being like
you know when you in the game and then
you leave the game and then uh yesterday
I was like staying on that home screen
for a while just by being in the home
screen
apparently the time might still
pass
um if that's the case then the time
should be uh quite a bit past 6 40 not
only because of me staying in the home
screen
um
yeah but also I I did see I DM last
night after I ended like maybe 20 30
minutes after my stream I I was just
like looking at my Discord and I saw
Ra's Discord profile still said playing
seven days to die so I wrote to her I
was
like and she's like uh don't don't worry
I I'm uh I'm just uh uh on the home
screen and I'm like okay okay should be
fine yeah but then I read this comment
like afterwards and I'm like hm could
this be
bad we'll see we'll see I mean in any
case it surely wouldn't be like because
after I told her that she she completely
closed the game but after I uh what was
I saying oh yeah uh even if then it
shouldn't at least be 7 Days Later it
should just be
maybe a few hours later in the game but
yeah we'll see and
um you sure I'm starting again a little
bit early just like you know I want to
Yap a little bit before we go because
stress stress the moment we get into the
game stress stress stress
uh there is a
RAID zombie raid maybe in 3
hours
uh zombie night baby oh smoothie
smoothie laid down even though I'm
[Music]
yapping I apparently fauna's cat does
the same thing that I keep on mentioning
like when they're sleeping when my cats
are sleeping in here and like the moment
I start my stream I start yapping and
they understand and then they they leave
they leave the moment I start yapping
and apparently fauna's cat does the same
but fauna's cat like is on her
lap lap cat and then she starts yapping
and then snail leaves yeah uh and I I
heard about that and I wrote to her
F that is so
relatable my cats also usually leave
when I start talking but recently it
seems like smoothie is sometimes a bit
more uh clingy than usual and doesn't
mind me so much anymore yapping so
sometimes she stays in the room
H yeah ah yeah Ollie Ollie's birthday is
today so I guess the zombies are
throwing a birthday party in
game today to I don't know what exact
day now it's 13th October for me
already so I don't
know uh let me try a little
bit I wonder who's going to show up
today I didn't look who has their
reservations
up so I don't know I just know
that uh today foku will join but not
that
long seems like they are just going to
be there for a short
session
um I wonder if crony shows
up well geky will the the usual gang
will seemingly be
there yeah
yeah what she's drunk she's too drunk
what do you mean she's too drunk what
why is she
drunk she's too
drunk
what she had a drinking game
stream oh okay
drinking every time she
died okay can't relate honestly can't
relate to be too drunk to do something I
don't even know what that means oh
Callie joined my
VC rather than oh rather than B's VC
what does this mean guys what does this
mean she wants to be with
me she wants to be with me
you are welcome to be with me
Celly I I'm really bothered by a second
me being there all the time but oh well
I want to see what time it is it is time
to see the
time let's see the
time okay no it's fine shouldn't oh
immediately at the same time people
joined and you know what we're going to
do first things first I looked at some
skill like recommendation videos but I
don't I don't know like there's probably
better ways to do it there were just
like the typical things like oh you got
to get lucky uh was it lucky
looter no not that one other other
things like uh oh you got to get minor
69er oh you got to get
um uh I don't know uh here healing
factor I want to put one more into
healing factor I think you seem one one
Health every 25 seconds with natural
healing critical injuries okay I'll take
one of these um yeah game is actually
too quiet I think
um let me change that a little
bit
okay
um I mean probably still a little bit
quiet uh give it you guys were
complaining last time I'll I'll bring it
up a little bit more
did I miss anything YouTube only just
said not really I was just uh I I just
entered the game and uh
oh where my girls at where my girls at
uh I think I I might want to put more
into parkour and I should put something
into machine how the [\h__\h] did I not put
anything ah I didn't put anything into
machine gun yet because this was saying
assault rifle and the whole time I'm
looking for like hm is there anything
for machine guns but okay but this is
machine gun but then here says assault
rifles I was just confused you know uh
but never mind maybe I just should have
read this part cuz here it says machine
guns it's just overall confusing cuz the
magazines also say the magazines
specifically just say assault rifle they
don't say anything about machine guns oh
bioo came
down oh everybody's training
me all right we'll put uh grunt gorilla
what was this so this one did uh 10%
more damage faster fire R faster reload
and more ammo oh see that's the whole
time why I wasn't finding 7.62 ammo much
by
myself should we get the second one too
I have two more points you are no
commando but you do what it takes to get
a job done machine guns deal 20% more
damage 10% faster why are the enemies
gone by the way I guess they just
despawned when I'm
offline find more machine guns
Parts um I don't know if I immediately
want to put another one into that uh but
let me see I was also writing
down to perhaps put one into physician
why can I
not intellect level three ah up
here ahuh you AR the brightest color in
the box but you occasionally hit the
nail and do head shot damage okay
200%
okay and
220% yeah I guess we'll spend all of
that so next skill point I can put
something into physician what does that
do again more
effectively it's not that important is
it oh but no it's more about like this
stuff oh party invites are coming in uh
uh some of the girls are unmuting but
I'm not ready
yet
[Music]
um you get exp to you by using bandages
first a bandag what I didn't know you
get exp from that let me move my
microphone you get exp from that but
probably not
much yeah the The Cure yeah that's
something that I was hope it for that's
the reason why I'm looking at that yeah
um and then later I'm thinking about
where are those
skills uh yeah um I might you know I I
actually will put maybe one point into
this
now uh reduce costs and stuff yeah okay
and then eventually I might put stuff
into Grease Monkey too yeah and then I I
also wrote down generally besides you
know I'm I'm mixing and matching right
now but the girls the other girls should
probably just go for one full armor set
and I wrote down so Raider set for fauna
would be good uh assassin just for
anybody who wants to be sneaky but I
don't think generally that's anybody's
play style um biker set is like one of
the best and preacher set is one of the
best that I can recommend yeah but I
think they even they can look at my
workstation and look at the armor that
is craftable right or even they don't do
they have to go to the workstation ah I
think so right cuz otherwise you just
see this this
stuff um they can go to the workstation
and check out the effects themselves
right
and figure out what they want I
assume you can make the iron
Sledgehammer
oh I
shall iron Sledgehammer at at the
workstation I guess
right ah [\h__\h] duct tape and [\h__\h] but
besides that I can make
it
okay uh I have to know how much
materials what does it does it
[Music]
say ah you can take dyes off the clothes
in the clothing store what for
free mixing gears the besta you think so
but it's too
complicated oh well hello I muted well
hello have a nice day everybody w wow
the Wawa armor Shop is open for business
yay we need armor kits right yeah armor
kits that those can be crafted too you
can check out like uh what do you need
for it okay it's crafting armor kit uh
yeah armor crafting kit needs okay my
cat knocked over something uh armor
parts sealing kit and duct tape yeah I
have this stuff awesome okay I'll go get
it and I'll have you make me a nerd hat
yeah okay let me see what level I can
make today's
uh Quest currently the nerd hat that I
can make is at level three so it won't
give you the best exp buff yet but like
pretty good enough it's a good any exp
buff is a
good agreed oh yeah my command do you
see the quest that I just took on your
screen by chance yes it's highlighted
there okay anyone who wants to join me
on the quest that's in my party Gigi
you're in my party oh I forgot I have a
quest near there too oh wait let me join
your party get my party I sent you an
invite there you go yeah not sure where
you are but I'm going to see if we can
go do the quest y are you guys in the
desert clear the right yeah clear that's
a clear Quest
okay I'm here I'm pretty far it might
take me a while to join you guys can
maybe do one Quest without me first oh
that's okay I'm just like looting the
area and killing baddies okay how's that
going for oh my Lord yeah I have so much
wood I'll come a little bit later I'm a
beaver oh just kidding it's you G I
thought uhoh
[Music]
okie
dokie turns out I do need the Tactical
Warfare magazines that say improves
assault rifle crafting skill because
that apparently also includes machine
guns many I put so many in the in the
magazine chest so you should check
either old house or new house I put like
seven of them in there ooh thank you
awesome nice hey Gigi and and uh bio if
you want to if you want to do a quest
with me I'm right in between you guys
okay
hi yeah just meet almost there mid I
here nice nice welcome bab I saw over
there she
was welcome welcome I have lots of
magazines any shotgun mags I have a
rifle world is that different I think
Kara needs that one maybe I have a
batter batter
up one I have handy
Land O an explosive magazine if you want
do Quest we're starting and you're right
next to us wait yes where are
you yeah we're in the town that we were
at last
time good luck
I'm going to do some other stuff right
now in the beginning sure do your thing
yua I'm on my way later thank you for
your
services
yeah very excited well you're really
looting and shooting everything
huh do you want some
wood yeah I'll take your wood okay come
here and take my wood de right here for
you swear to God
3,000 that was half my wood I want to
make a one I'll get some more don't
worry she's full of wood I have so much
wood
cool cool it is kind of cool thank you
Grandpa's awesome sauce what okay I'm
here yo they got Grandpa's awesome sauce
oh my Lord that's awesome sauuce yeah
all right ladies let's go go wait wait
wait take this
book oh is the baseball one yes G schol
books which books
andyland
um yeah this
one oh and it's a lumberjack one too
I've been reading these ones and then
the ones that improve the club or axe
biu aren't you reading harvesting rifle
world oh no I'm a handgun
oh read rifle World I'll hold on to it
it seems like you really want to give it
to me and I appreciate present what does
rifle world
do
oh I don't know what does it do I don't
know cting um I'll just hold on to a fre
sniper rifles no no I don't need sniper
rifles that's fine just the assault
rifle
magazines cuz those are for machine guns
too apparently yeah get them ladies yeah
good
idea bikes here I'm going to destroy
them why did I take I hear in the closet
oh he's got yellow eyes oh he does a
tough one
Gary we sure hey when can this these
spikes go away okay cool I didn't stab
you did I no I don't think so
okay oh
hello maybe going up this way is better
you sure hello the spikes are popping
off hello remember killing me Pik
house got rid of all of
us oh who thata to your
head nice good job ladies what are you
doing zombie
was awesome oh I had something for you
to read right here that was stupid
strong thank you there is stupid
strong kind of awesome this bat's broken
I agree my sledgehammer is broken too so
nice feel like we're experiencing the
same things even though we were in
different
places
crazy there's a lot of medical stuff in
here someone should take one of these
medkits
oh oh the barb wire oh yeah good idea I
wonder who would be a good
choice who okay I muted myself because
uh so I can Yap with you I'm looking I
guess for machine gun parts I think I
have one in my chest uh cuz this icon
looks familiar to me maybe they have
some lying around here randomly uh then
I could craft this and I'm assuming this
is better than my current one by far I
haven't had a new gun for a long time oh
what the what the [\h__\h] is this pipe
shotgun ah
huh the same thing I have but like not
broken and nobody's using machine guns
besides me let me take
this I can disassemble this one wait do
I get machine gun parts if I dis if I
scrap it no but can I make machine gun
parts no right
okay but okay machine Let's track this
machine gun parts the rest is okay like
manageable
um yeah um uh she said wait was it B who
said she has all these magazines
probably not in here right in does she
have machine gun
parts no I don't see machine gun parts
um
materials Machine Gun
Parts Spring I don't know we probably
have Springs at home but let me take a
couple in the magazine CR okay I'll
check that out but I'm also looking for
machine gun parts machine gun parts tell
me if I'm missing them if if I am
looking at a chest and I don't realize
where is the magazine
chest in this house I already checked
ours and got four magazines out of that
one is it maybe downstairs magazine box
am I
blind magazine ah
uh yes I am uh that was one assault
rifle that was only one but that's my
ammo um that was one here and one at
home H for at home I mean at our
home
uh
yeah is there any more elsewhere wait
did she have any in her no right
no
well that's fine there are handle backs
bars in a box for bike I already have a
bike uh I guess I read several yesterday
yeah that's probably it but I don't see
any machine gun parts and you can't make
those yourself
H
[Music]
um ah hey ammo oops stack and more
orange dye let's go I'll take
it
um is this all the all the boxes they
have maybe I mean for like Community
chests
oh Alo Vera um um um um want to take the
armor PS too um I'm personally done with
crafting my own armor for now uh so the
other girls they should have access to
that when they feel like when they feel
like they know what armor they
want who's is this
who's is this they have a tire remember
that tire guys it might become
important later
on CeCe okay good that's two tires so
far maybe there's some more elsewhere I
think that's all I can make use of here
although wait maybe some
glue duct tape how much duct tape do I
have I have some
glue was there duct tape in the
materialist
chest I do not see but
honestly H cie also needs duct
tape so I don't want to take like
everything that's in
[Music]
here Cece's chest had machine gun
parts
H well they're machine gun parts so she
wouldn't need them right ah wait Cece's
just was upstairs right it literally was
just there somebody needs
to make this L this ladder more
efficient
okay machine gun parts
really
sick actually
amazing then I should be good to go to
craft one at home I do think I have at
least one machine gun part I think
so all
right let's
go back
to uh wa Clementine's home maybe this
time I'll take a different is there a
better road to
take h
are we oh
what are we back cuz I'm losing
frames oh no no it's going down the
frames are not dropping
anymore uh yeah my internet was
gone double
WWA okay well it kicked me out of the
game and my internet was gone let me get
back in actually I guess it's good that
I wasn't with the group
group yeah yeah
yeah let me go back in
[Music]
again we'll take a while to load
in oopsie well let's unmute a little bit
tells it how it is it's okay I needed to
be punished for all the times I've
killed everyone anyway so this is just
my own retribution you have killed a lot
of people maybe we have them to turn off
friendly fire from here on
now we we could oh we know a little hard
we you don't think so because sometimes
people want to be killed like when FAA
killed Cecilia because Cecilia wanted it
that's true oh there are there are
flaming men upstairs be careful flaming
men
Hallelujah there's flaming man I'm glad
I wasn't with you girls cuz my internet
just died and kicked me out you can no
you know evil is FAA behind me right now
no oh no don't wor I make sure to not
hit you you see how strong that bat is
one hit one hit dead if you hit them in
the
head fire is part of the experience more
upstairs yeah it is part of the
experience did you girls hear why CeCe
can't join us today because he's drunk
he's too drunk that's so funny no oh
yeah she was playing she took 100 sips
more than 100 I heard
133 130 130 sips of
what cocktail we need to hang out a
little
more incredible Jin
Jin sips of isn't Jin really strong not
not I wouldn't really I think that
whiskey would be a little more oh yeah
whiskey would probably be a little more
intense but I have
a with the poopies cuz I ate a sandwich
oh no I don't have you need tea I don't
have te need tea do I have anything that
helps here you go that'll help you oh
thank you eat some more sandwiches first
okay okay let
me sandwiches and then take
it you have to Mid Max your hunger
yeah yeah all right time to take my tea
shells yummy is anybody working on
Salvage tools I um let me
check Salvage tools I have 12 on Salvage
tools oh okay I'll give it to you um you
use heavy
armor oh I use heavy armor or she will
she will here you go I have heavy armor
for you oh which one is it a helmet
helmet oh oh I think I already have
helmet that one
yeah it's you can hold on to
it
helmet take shells I probably should oh
thank you I probably should PR your hat
not going to
lie but it's so dang
cool no I kind of can't like an old rock
star
I did you girls already finish that
first Quest yes
yeah we can probably we we have more
there's a there's a GG clear nearby oh
yeah we could do that I'm just going to
quickly build myself a new machine gun I
think and then I'll come over
[Music]
okay going be
bodybuilder you think we can start your
quest now or do we have to wait we can
start it
I should be there
now oh she's
Speedy what you can't pick up a bike if
it has stuff in the storage
yeah what's the point it's okay you can
just ride it ride it and park it um no
one's gonna pick it up if someone does
steal it I'll take it don't
worry I'll make you a new one if someone
takes it I'll give
oh we can we can share a b the wives can
share a
bicycle mock your bicycle you can you
can lock your bicycle and enter a code
for it and I don't think people can
steal your B lock your bike yeah there's
a locking function that's amazing tell
me your bite code now no it's one one
one what a good bite code the typical
whole life password you can get into all
of our social media accounts if you just
type in 1111 one one one it's very
secure mhm oh yeah come on give it a try
hack
us one1 is the
password they're going to get us locked
out of our iPads for a
year oh no not the iPads no my iPad code
is different though it's very funny that
you guys think we're joking stiny man oh
my
God he's going to vomit my friends in
the head with my bat
oh have I already finished my Quests for
today how can that be can I give you my
um a bandage if I hit you in the head
please maybe as an ingame today so then
maybe yeah cuz it was 6:00 a.m. when we
ended last
night oh God there's a lot of big popos
here are you kidding
me there's no way that I one shot him oh
my gosh you're a
menace what it had to be be a critical
hit wait isn't there someone in The
Walking Dead with like a terrifying
baseball bat like that there is like a
villain who was it oh yeah Negan yeah
and he kills a bunch of characters that
I love Yeah Yeah spoilers just kidding
well you don't know what characters I
love B silly oh okay what character I'm
call This Bat Lucille in negan's
honor yeah bat name
gy yeah the trees you planted in front
of our house conceal our house so much
it's it's hard to find the house now and
it's hard to find an exit and an
entrance
it's don't worry I'll chop them down
once I come back please
do let you take care of it I don't want
to kill
you I also don't want to stab you to
death you will you found a fake wall oh
yeah
nice smart fa's got better eyes tummy a
I hear it you hear
my I didn't hear anything do it again I
hear them do it again this might be a
wall too actually hold
up please this could be a fake wall need
that Golden Rod tea I'm okay oh hello
hello oh this isn't a fake is it oh ow
the spikes still hurt
no huh what's that noise oh oh someone's
using the
defibrator yeah after the spikes I
really
hurt do you need a bandage fauna oh I
had a a kit okay so you're good I'm good
for
now I can craft one I'm level 14 well
well
so let's
see we did it now I can get body so no
machine gun parts anywhere I swear I had
some but I guess it was just the handgun
Parts um but what I need Sledgehammer
Parts
too ah these ones steel what I had
something like that well that's cool I
guess at least
something uh okay let's look at
the steel sledgehammer
wait but I can't make it yet what do you
mean I'm not strong enough when it comes
to sledgehammers yet I I have like
plenty don't I 12 well how much more do
you
want
eh what why does it bring me to
harvesting tools I don't even
understand wait are we F oh oh
oh
oh wait I have two free steel and I'm
supposed to be making iron sled
parts do they look very
different robotics steel steel tool
Parts steel spare steel and even more
steel sledg parts really I need the
other one or I guess we're skipping that
sledgehammer and just waiting for the
steel one cuz I don't see any what am I
what which which one was it
again you don't need parts oh I don't
okay thank god well that's
something um what was the iron
Sledgehammer okay needs let's track this
one wood leather duct tape forged iron I
don't think I have any more duct tape I
might just
take forged
iron forged
iron forged iron and wood do I have
wood wood
has I might just take duct tape from
the she's not here today this is the tax
for not being here
today and are there I should make a
chest for like right
here
um wooden crate just for like related
things that belong
here I don't know how to write anything
on there but okay armor
parts for now I don't
know uh
oh the iron in here here is all
gone I'm
thirsty do we have water uh yes probably
need two
honestly if I'm that thirsty can you
make more iron I need to check if you
have Forge iron in your pack you can
upgrade the storage capacity of those
boxes
oh
H wait I'm looking
for iron well there's so much money in
here
need to convert that iron iron iron iron
iron
iron iron iron iron iron iron no iron
iron how where did all the iron
go that's
steel iron iron iron iron iron okay what
about uh iron Parts iron things
there
H I run
what is this lead iron iron iron iron
iron who four
[Music]
wheels Club
Parts what engine B need to have an
overview of what we have okay let's make
more iron I guess because I don't know
where the hell my iron
went I guess it ran away
but amazing
I see like Bigger Pockets mod and stuff
is better I
think wait am I not done with quests I
think I
am I don't know if there's anything I
can really give
her not really farming these days so I
don't need these oh beo I have ammo for
you
there's really no reason to even sell
her thing did I make iron out of
iron no I don't
understand about my
wife smelter give me a
sec I got to make some of those armor
kits now soon for guua would you like a
mod had for mil weapons that lower
degradation by
25% I'm okay I'm not too worried about
degradation thank you very much though I
appreciate it I'll put it on my axe or
something then yeah yeah go for it you
can definitely make good use of it and
this I'm going to put maybe on my
current shotgun even though it kind of
sucks I am sorry you right in front of
me I tabed back in are you drinking
again
I'm sorry dear I didn't mean to punch
you don't tell anyone okay okay I won't
want to ride home together okay are you
coming home we are coming home yes yippe
what are you coming home for I to
offload stuff and cook I guess okay so
many things I will do Quest I need to go
home too though cuz I have too much
stuff yeah what is the best way to get
home a quick trip home might be a good
idea
um where even is
home so North well there's this main
road we could
take well we could take the main road
and then go west and then go
north okay where'd you go I went into
the okay let's go this way aren't you so
curious what's in here yeah I guess so
I'm working our working our
[Music]
legs getting swoll ever skipping leg day
want to follow you oh
gosh well when you girls come home and
offload and you're done with everything
then I'm ready to do quests anytime
okay don't which is this way probably up
oh maybe this way if the bike can even
go
up quick
question
uh what weapon do you put this
on can I put this on a machine
gun oh it seems like
yes wait my other didn't my the broken
machine gun that I scrapped also have a
mod on it what happened with that maybe
it didn't have a mod on
it so wait what did that just do the bar
looks what did that do CHR when F from
the so you mean when I'm not right
clicking I do that I used to do that a
lot but I don't do that so much anymore
H what does the metal change on clubs
oh I don't know what to imagine you
[Music]
please bruh
bro why is my internet so [\h__\h]
today
why why is it so
[\h__\h] I don't understand it's not fair
let me in let me in
game what why not
working yeah I guess like I don't know
if it's maintenance but like I guess
when if they were to do maintenance it
would be in the middle of the night huh
not during the day it would be when
whenever whenever people are supposed to
be sleeping
BR please I am I I'm in the dire
situation in a d zombie apocalypse you
can't you
can't like [\h__\h] over my internet now
somehow I can't get into the server
right
now this is
important
man I can still I can still see the
water is still warm I don't know why
it's
warm oh
delicious yummy my
IP hint of hint of G this is
G it's like water it's like flavored
water where it's like you run a run a
fruit over a faucet and then that's what
it tastes like that's that's it ran over
yes a fruit in a faucet
I'm eating blueberries here you go thank
you thank
you oh an A B potato yum yum don't tell
them I'm in their fridge in their fridge
eating things right
now yo can we get some Cooks maybe
cooking some more of this meat cuz we
have a ton of raw meat we have 52 raw
meat I will cook some more Cooks in the
kitchen great I'm going to do we have do
we have eggs cuz oh there's a bird what
the heck I'm out of
there oh my God there's a lot of
birds out of here is it really
Birds nice I hear I hear more there's
more oh my go shooting them out of the
sky get them Ratt okay they're going to
give me a bad
[Music]
reputation we need better representation
of birds in this game
what was I you okay yeah I'm just taking
out my
anger wait I your party invite mailbox
oh thank you you're welcome I got kicked
out twice already out of this game and
out of the
internet wait do you read Magnum
enforcer I do here you go thank you
what was I making I love how you ask as
though it's like we're subscribed to
certain magaz like that
are no have a
few zombie Birds let's get out of here
more birds show I'm stuck on the
mailbox and I can't pick my bike up
cuz oh no who built this
Forest yeah who build okay maybe maybe
we can we can we can smack the mailbox
to death yes okay let's smack the
mailbox wait I got it I got it okay oh
yeah mailbox magin huh oh hold on hold
on I'll send I think I'm free I'm free
okay okay thank
you oh
no oh shoot I am I don't have time
Adventures Water I'm
fine just open your mouth collect the
water yourself with your mouth why is
that not possible I'm very mad about
that I know you're right I wish we could
turn snowballs into
water is that worth it lowering the
level on it and making it on level
two is that worth it cuz machine gun
parts don't seem to come very often to
my
hands wait I have free Parts I don't I
don't no no no
My Stream buffered again the parts will
be get more com ah yeah I guess you find
the things that you're Skilling into
more
[Music]
right close and personal with some of
the zombies yeah get some
XP yeah we should try to craft as many
nerd hats as we can yeah
definitely I was
don't don't Tex and ride everybody I was
watching you and then I also hit the
car so far this
traitor I have one armor parts I think
that you just need
one uh full what for the nerd hat yeah
and let's see we need for the nerd hat
in order for me to make it on level
three it's free crafting kits if you
just want it on level one I can make it
for you for one crafting kit like
apparently it really
correlates yeah I think it would be
better to make it on a higher level if
you can get more armor crafting kits
okay I could have sworn we had
more you can make them with pretty
simple ingredients but we're currently
always lacking duct tape why are the
birds still foll
you why I'm still duct tape and I'm
putting it back later I see you biking
with two birds overhead another
one sound yesh we just brought the
desert back with
us they're knocking oh wait is this the
house really loudly oh yeah that's our
house yeah get rid of those
trees for God's sake duct tape from the
old
house I don't want to see these trees
anymore o it is night time can you still
make glue from Bones and duct tape
actually we'll make her some new ones
right
now
better just kidding
could have swor I had
glue my iron Sledge was canc
why what I'll take you with
me all right time for a very frightening
bike ride back to the new
house what is that does anyone have
eggs yeah that's what I was seeing we
can make bacon and eggs with all of them
I think we have a lot of eggs at the old
house
m spikes did not really affect him huh
where all the egg I will look for
eggs ah shiny eyed
zombie fin the moat with spikes came in
handy I will if I can find the entrance
to our house I will direct him to
it SC ladies uhoh I fell in some spikes
I
think he's here he's here oh God he's
fast he's coming into our house he's
chasing me he's chasing
me easy I feel like I'm breaking our
house there we go so scary nothing to be
scared
about this all get rid of the
trees my character's so hungry I hope
you guys are grilling some meat
um well I have some for you hey
chefs we need eggs where are you looking
I'm on the way to the new house I guess
we can make regular grilled meat but is
it worth it I don't think it's worth it
we have so many eggs at the old house
that bacon and eggs would be so much
better can we get an an egg delivery oh
God all right I'm turning
around thank you
I'm turning
around what happened to my armor it says
crit does that mean it's critically
damaged we have some baked potatoes and
grilled corn in here that's good I might
eat some of that tied you
over
yeah well we're waiting for the good
stuff right
[Music]
yeah hey Chef all right I'll be
waiting we have one bacon and
eggs yum
yum I guess I shouldn't have been just
fisting those eggs in my mouth I guess
you eating raw
eggs I I was doing it to prove a
point
to I asked her if she wanted to see me
eat these six raw eggs I don't
understand why this happen happened I
don't know why I didn't realize I when I
click on it can I mean ex but I don't
know why I just wanted to see like the
details or something why does it take so
long no touching no touching forgive you
stop eating those eggs ra see how you
have a problem I can't help so much
protein you've made your point don't
worry gig okay I'll stop eating the raw
eggs please no more this isn't Japan you
can't just do that I have a tummy egg
I'm not surprised 13 13 eggs here we got
13 I'm going to go put some of stuff you
can you should check the cooking pot uh
at the house or the one of the cooking
pots cuz I think I was cooking a bunch
of bacon and eggs before oh yeah so you
might want to check oh you were there's
five and there's yeah there you go you
can go ahead and take it and bring it
over you okay I'm going to eat one of
these bacon and eggs okay there for any
myself alive
okay and then I'll bring the rest of
everything over to put how many armor
parts do I need for the Hat Kaa uh if
you want it on level three then free
sadly I have three oh
nice what else do you need uh the rest I
can take care of myself I think okay
I'll give it to you don't go get I'm I'm
in the house in the
kitchen in the real kitchen where
there's no cooking to be done hey go
okay no cooking is happening whatsoever
yeah okay and then I'll take
my forged iron and the leather nerd hat
is wait did I pick it up you gave me
free armor kits I
did where did they
go or was it oh maybe I gave you armor
parts oops oh yeah I guess
so I think you can have them back
okay let's see how you make armored kits
you need sewing and duct tape I actually
have some duct tape for you bio I just
need to get some glue oh no I have I I
have the other things too I'll make them
quickly okay okay okay wow wow armor
shop well I stole your duct tape in the
old house just so you know so I owe you
three duct tape we need duct tape more
duct tape oh I can craft duct tape I
have a bunch of cloth and we just need
glue I do need oh wait I can just make
up too I
think yeah it's simple
ingredients can never have
enough true
enough I like how this game brings you
to like even later in the game you keep
on needing simple ingredients that you
get early in the game yeah even the
simplest things like claw fragments and
stuff like that it all has a purpose
yeah which is nice I prefer that to
always learning about new items and
never needing the old ones
yeah for
sure okay I'm almost there I've got a
delivery of eggs and I'm I have the kits
for you okay I'll go back to the kitchen
I'm here I'm here here you go to make my
nerd hat too kiaha okay we'll all be
nerd n be so cute why did I go to oh no
I made a mistake put away my
M where did my leather
go quick there it is okay there are
zombies
here
crafting and finish you going to look so
cute
yay where are you rid of my preacher hat
put this
on oops that's fine oh getting some air
do I cute oh wow I didn't know you had
such a beard you do I look cute very
cute oh my gosh you guys mad look at you
look at you am I am I cute do you think
cute very cute those
glasses
perfect hey they're having a fashion
show without
me we're matching we mtic I want to show
you guys my mustache wait I have cool
facial hair too please well I already
know your mustache it's very siick it's
very cool you know it well don't you
it's so in style yes it's very scratchy
for smooches you're such a fashionist
smoing all the ladies I want the person
who dug this hole in front of the
traitor
dead no it's
funny I I want to meet them I would love
to meet them and shake their hand and
give them a smile and tell them how good
it is
the hole Yeah the hole ah yes it's a
good hole it is the best hole what you H
are nice you can hide in them what are
you doing now giggy oh I'm hitting trees
enjoying
life the
beaver can never have I'm looking for a
nest oh somebody's screaming oh yeah
there's a screamer I heard that too
actually
oh whoopsies that's me ow here they come
oh oh yeah there's a couple coming
towards our
house I will help defend
the help where are they help I'm out
outside I'm out of stamina I can't hit
them thank you oh my God that's
SP need more
stamina oh there's a lot jeez let's go
oh there really are aren't they oh my
God oh my
God
ow ouch
o I'm infected too a little
bit a little bit just a little bit yeah
0.4% not that bad it's not
bad nothing a little honey cow face wa
see we're great team I like this action
I wanted some exp bring me more oh
there's more I hear more you asked for
more you shall receive Kiara where is it
coming from there's still someone
alive sounds so
close he's on the ground he's over here
I'm just having aack really quick so
hard to
see yeah he's chilling the didn't see
you down there hey gaha I have the
materials for the nerd hat you do nerd
Hat's so popular all right
yay yeah your special Kiara brand nerd
hat I will get to it right away thank
you so that you can show off your
nerdiness proudly so excited I've been
preaching for too
long let's see I also have the eggs I
don't know if we have
ingredients that's okay I got your egg I
will just zombie it up don't don't
become a zombie no had finished but then
no your your current hat what's going to
happen to that it's almost broken so
it's fine
okay well well this will be hopefully of
good use to you ooh and I can put my mod
my intelligence mod on it to make it
extra nerdy ooh intelligence mod what
does that do
SM I don't really know what it does I
don't really know if it's even helpful
but I'll take
[Music]
it byebye preacher hat let's see why am
I fatiguing maybe I will make this por
steel this is so silly
[Music]
oil hey guys why am I
fatigued are you tired you swung too
hard now you need a little nap the
bullet is eepy I guess vitamins maybe
maybe vitamins will
help oh yeah we have some I'll eat a
couple
oh
uh I have this for you parts for later
since I think you're using hammers oh
thank you thank you are there steel
steel
steel I get so many Steels let's my
parts I eat this if anybody finds
machine gun parts please let me know I
just need one more I'll let you know
okay I wonder if there are any at the
old house I'm pretty sure I them Che I
checked no there was
um uh not enough not enough dang it
that's rough dang it yeah some glue
um is coffee
good um it gives you a buff I forget
what buff it gives you but it gives you
something coffee yeah coffee gives you
stamina regen
20% oh that's good stamina regen is good
does it fill your water or does it make
you dehydrated no it makes you it fills
your thirst it does
and pipe shotgun is not even maybe maybe
we should be making drinks with the with
the empty water then just drinking
straight water I feel like we need glue
maybe yeah glue is what cuz I have a ton
of cloth there's like 91 cloth I have
more glue I have a couple more
glues oh nice cuz that can make duct
tape and we really need duct tap GL
water too while everything needs water
yeah oh
see I might make some
glue
yeah
oh good idea I have fdy glue oh you can
get all the skills one level earlier
with the intelligence mod so it's very
nice mod o
cool I'm going to make my sledgehammer
cause some sick Burns today cuz it's
going to light zombies on fire yeah I
want to see it in action I want to see
it too I can actually show it off
earlier probably I'm making it right now
oh I'm going to take some bandages whoa
it's conly on
fire ammo thank
[Music]
you look look f look my sledgehammer
it's on
fire oh it is you put it in the fire
yeah I I honestly don't know why it's
how it does that but it's fun hey kiaha
you're making armor right I don't really
know if this will be useful to you but I
feel like you should you should take
it schematic oh yeah I mean anybody can
put that on their armor to make their
armor stronger I think yeah oh
yeah well you can have oh oh but ah this
is the schematic too I see never mind
I'll I'll learn that yeah yeah I shall
learn be
helpful
okay I want to do
Quest okay I'll do a quest with you I'm
ready I'm ready for quest really yipp
yeah I just I don't I'm going to come
home and drop stuff off and um we can go
to the new Trader okay yeah I don't have
any uh quests personally but I'll just
do whatever you girls have I think there
is a active Quest but I don't know who
activated it it's 88 me away I have I
have a tier 2 infestation and then Gigi
also has a tier 2 infestation up oh nice
well let's go do those perfect 4:00 a.m.
okay does anybody use
clubs yes here I think I have a mod that
you could use o oh I dropped it in the
right here thank you metal chain ooh the
chains yeah people have been wanting me
to use the chains so thank you I brought
home a eggs I have five five eggs and 20
meat good job oh than bread winner
providing for the family that's why I
accidentally put who he is everything
into my inventory on
accident
wel I woke up on a bunk bed
we're going to help but
we doesn't look like anybody our house
oh we have a
new right now I figured maybe uh do you
want me to come pick you
up it's night time no it's 4:00 a.m.
you're
fine yeah and you guys can be on our
team and get the EXP if you want we're
going to go and find you I should if you
if you look at the map and zoom out like
really far you can see a bunch of our
names on the map and that's that's new
house
location okay we'll go on a
quest you
good that's not that what you trying to
do I'm going to go towards the the tier
2 quests
the
to is anyone learning how to lockpick no
oh I think I would like to okay here you
go thank you but lockpick when we can
just Brute Force open everything bying
apparently there are safes that that
won't work with I had to lock food oh
wow so it might be nice to have we're
going to go on our journey and once we
everybody oh is it okay I see at the old
home here there's a bunch of magazines
and animal and stuff yeah you can use
whatever are they can I take everything
at Old home or is it still um we're
going to we're going to go back there
for the raid um so maybe leave some
resources but whatever you need you can
take okay yeah just stuff that you
need we'll go on our journey then and
then have a
question sure make sure to take lots of
quests at the trader if you want to get
a bicycle
okay okay we
[Music]
will do we have a any honey Now by any
chance no I'm still infected
too you can buy it from the trader
actually he just charges too much thank
you the lady she charges less I think oh
really
MH she's so
nice yeah she's a nice lady she wants us
I could get used to her she wants us so
bad yeah I'll just get some tree
stumps on the way to the desert or
whatever that place is yeah I'm sure
you'll find some honey have better RNG
luck than me have you been looking for
it
too for the honey no I'm good now but
whenever I do need it it just doesn't
pop out of the stumps M yeah it's a
little bit
rare
yeah okay so I'm going to go there
whenever you girls are ready we're going
to do quests there right about
ready yeah I'm on the way some food and
water
yes yes yes so we can stay strong for as
long as possible yes and some Band-Aids
are there tree stumps in the burnt area
as well or should I check in the I think
I did see
some but I'm not exactly sure but
there's a lot of
trees maybe like generally surrounding
the area if I see any I'll try and break
them
okay I wonder how much percentage until
you die from from
the from
the sickness illness 100 oh god well
then I got a lot of time there's a I I
found a couple stumps I'll crack them
open for you okay appreciate it find any
honey is that where honey is in stumps
yeah yes I need a stronger
axe wait I'm still on quality one we're
heading for the invation quest I have
quality five
a quality five wow man you're a beaver
huh I am a beaver I can make iron tools
now too but I haven't touched the bench
you're the tool Master yeah for my
Beaver activities now you need to like
truly RP and bite them with your teeth
and that's how you yeah yeah yeah just
like that ah
infection is everyone
infected I'm not you mean you're going
to get infected yeah once I bite
them I'm sorry Kiara my luck is just so
bad I opened up the stumps but there was
nothing it's
okay I'll probably die anyway I think
after a certain percentage uh honey
doesn't work anymore and then you need
antibiotics okay oh can we craft that
well maybe
someday Maybe somay
feel like
we so after
5% honey doesn't work anymore what oh oh
well then I kind of want to find honey
right now oh tree
stump I think I would like to find some
honey
too I found one a tree stump
please oh no my character's hungry and I
didn't bring any meat dang it oh I've
got food oh really oh chef yes really
thank
you oh no it does work it just removes
5% time Ione okay I see y good job gu
also I have two Hammer magazines for you
crafting Yi you can take them thank you
did you put it in like a box or so no
I'm just waiting for you at the location
oh I'm coming now Quest now that I have
my honey I will hurry
decided to get rid of these magazines oh
my gosh us trading magazines is so fun
yeah it's nice everybody has like a
different specialty yeah that's why I
kind of appreciate that we're not like
20 people or so in this collab because
then I feel like I would lose oversight
of who needs what and now we have such
clear roles and it's really
comfy yeah I like
this me too me too yeah usually usually
I don't play like a killer in games like
the the really physically strong ones so
this is new for me but I'm having fun
what do you normally do food cooking or
something like that yes thank you how
about some bacon and eggs Rand stuff oh
my gosh my chef a blueberry
pie yes chef thank you Che that sounds
so good you have a Band-Aid here have a
Band-Aid just in case I'm visualizing it
right now in my brain I'll take your
Band-Aids phone
I'll take your Band-Aids off your hand
snake a snake there's a snake snake I
think it's just an angry zombiie I'm
going to punch it I'm very stay oh it is
a snake also somehow St a
snake what is that chat why why am I
laughing at my
ligma oh ligma yeah like my I have an
icon that's laughing at
the
radiation I guess because I'm laughing
because it's going
way yeah of course that's definitely the
only reason that it's it's Ling okay got
is a little
weird okay I'm kind of in the area
now what's
Lima what is Lima stop you it's a very
serious
illness that cannot be cured
normally how do you cure
Lima yeah how do you Lima you know it gy
I don't think I do I've never heard of
it before
jobs who's that oh oh wait how do we get
huh Zoomers these days don't even
know Lima balls okay I said it someone
had to say it Lima balls lima lima
balls a this time it's you sacrificing
yourself B thank you you're welcome de
do you have any
Band-Aids I do okay there's a bird watch
out so right click works for the SL
too who is that over on the roof I'm
getting chased by a
hog help
meat don't miss
Wonder wait stop running
ah I don't want it to bite me it's dead
one hit you guys are on the road huh
yay Yum Yum Yum wait are you guys going
to infestation or bi boo infestation
getting Chas by P any any of them we are
at bio infest wait that's your arrow
there's an infestation of bi Boos yeah
yeah many of her get
infested real quick and then we'll do
GG's okay and then I want to I really
want to go check on the Twins and make
sure that they're ready for the the
apocalypse so I'm going to go talk to
them after this okay okay we can we can
also start preparing the old house for
yes we need to prepu as well cuz
tomorrow is the chosen day wa The Chosen
day the dawn of the final day so
strong I'm looting a pig real quick okay
you're looting a pig yeah so much
meat okay you don't like that I'm
looting this pig please don't leave the
Pig please don't I'll do my
best just get the meat just get the
meat I'll keep my thoughts to myself
what are you thinking about the pig no
no no they're funny share
them thought thought you didn't want me
to I only pretend like I don't want you
to it's it's really I speak in opposite
speak which is really annoying okay so
you want me to lose the pain I love it
yeah I'll get your bone and meat you
guys got some water all right yes yeah I
have some water and some tea sorry I'm
going the wrong way just water will do
from the tap is fine I don't want to pay
extra for water just give me tap
water thank you what does this look like
oh it's
chained all right you guys ready so
ready are you done looting the pig yeah
yeah but now I'm lost I'm almost there
okay I think I'm almost there you're
here I'm here let's get start yippee
finally Quest yipp
time yippee kill them all yipp oh you
could break it or you find an open door
different
door ah dang
it they really tried to board up this
house huh a why do they need us to clear
out these infestations because like no
one's there anymore what's the point the
houses don't have a point we want to
make it liveable
again
mayal ow did I oh guess we're breaking
down door want to break down a door oh I
would love to break down the door open
we're so in oh they're in the way cash
there's actually they're alive they're
here oh they're very much
alive and on
fire my hammer takes so much to
swing keep up the good work
everyone help okay almost died are you
are you okay oh no I'm not okay you have
a Band-Aid Ure them
outside I'll need a Band-Aid later
here's the bandaid oh thank
you a best best girl see where you work
done bi Boo looks so funny with the hat
and the
[Music]
beard zombies fear me I'll oh there's an
AK machine
gun I pick it up and give it to someone
else it's bleeding for the
ceiling I just opened the door and you
stabbed me I didn't know I'm bleeding
out it's it's you need okay need band
Instinct take this forgive her I have
thank you I will use this bandage
too here and also yeah your health is
low so use a regular bandage too hold
up let me see I'm sorry blood from my
friend thank you no problem heal
yourself is someone up there oh bio okay
me and find are up here I don't know if
there's any more bad guys maybe here the
closed door is always a bad still some
more I have ammo for you oh wow okay
thank you I'll get shooting
then no
mercy there's an
upstairs cat picture new cat I'm not
sure if we've seen this they love the
cat
pictures I've seen that one orange cat
behavior oh maybe we did see it it's a
good cat
yes every cat is good cat there are no
such things as demon
cats I
agree they're all perfect angels yes
you're the ones that are not worthy of
the cats there's a hole hello where the
last
zombie probably down the hole come on
jumie who's a good jombie who you jumpy
yes you
are oh maybe it's down no h do you guys
see an orange dot I do see an orange dot
that might be it's upstairs somewhere
cuz it's pointing up second floor
zombie oh no it's second floor second is
this second floor what I don't is the do
really going to a zombie it seems like
Po
outside yeah that's a little strange
maybe the zombie is outside oh I think
it's a bird outside oh yeah yeah on top
of the other I did see a bird's nest oh
there's a bird out
there yay we're done okay this Quest is
complete complete nice job
[Music]
ladies a bit thirsty okay are we're
going to go straight to the next Quest
yeah uh yeah it's right below us okay
below follow you also is it possible for
uh Kiara to repair my bat at a workbench
possibly uh I think with a repair kit I
think you just need your repair kit M oh
okay just do and you can do it yourself
here let me let me give it give you one
you have a repair kit bi boo thank you
yeah appreciate that so
prepared okay and I use it at a
workbench right no no you just
unequipped your weapon and should be an
option to repair I see thank you B
you're Lifesaver yeah thank you so
much nice that's huge uh which Quest are
we going to H tier 2 infestation gigy
yeah yeah it's just down the
road on my
way I'm almost there too I'm getting
wood oh no she loves in case we need it
you have a wood Addiction in case you
know serious wood addiction a this bat's
so
cool I'm I'm I'm there oh they have a
tree house how
sweet not when I'm done with
it she's going to think of the
children you're going to watch me do
this are you going to dismantle it
you're going to watch me do this
I like this tree
[Music]
house the tree house you actually hurt
me this is why we can't have nice things
oh we it
back you're going try again God is
gracious should I do it again do it
again do it again are you kidding me how
many times do you need to fa The
Treehouse to be satisfied Gigi they
cannot have a tree house not when I'm
around
no that's to I can't believe you're
doing this in front of f that's messed
up it gets so messy around she can of my
7,000 words like there's a lot coming
there's a lot coming lot are they
mad shooting me stop shooting me I'm
sorry I was I wanted to help oh
no melee is
suffering it is feel that
I've got nine HP no
no I can I I can blow on it kiss I have
I have two thank
you oh my god blowing on
it does that help it should it should
thank you I hear it helps helps meal
what kind of house is this what were
they doing here
kissing what have I done they are super
lost
myself not the same person anymore this
zombies stuff is getting to
me I'm becoming one of them it's okay I
beat b earlier too why would you beat
your wife I didn't mean to I just lost
myself I found a
couple puning bag take the shotgun ammo
there's there's a ton of bi boo ammo and
Kiara ammo in this Ed cat it's yellow up
here thank you sh Messiah oh oh God he's
big why did I miss so hard there also a
really good machine gun shotgun shells
I'll take them Dr some behind you GG do
you also use a shotgun oh my God I have
some though okay it's so
noisy it is
okay I'll make sure they get
it
oh what a big
family a pipe machine
gun yes where's bio there's there's a
ton of 9mm ammo in this yellow crate up
here I'm upstairs I'll come down after
you know I'll grab it for you cfee no
there's a lot of there's a lot of things
in the house right now I'm kind of
occupi the house I I the door these
houses are getting more
intricate oh yeah what is this for are
they protecting themselves from US ah
couldn't be the floor is turned into
zombies oh wow
heck is going I want to get rid of this
oh oh oh are you guys destroying more
floors no no I'm not trying to it's
doing it on its own really is there an
upstairs
okay I was thinking is there an upstairs
it must be your house we're not done yet
does anybody have any dirty water I can
drink I I have
water I'll drink the dirty water I
checked toilet
over oh no okay I'm outside the
house here some dirty water upstairs do
thank you leg H you have to be able to
get upstairs maybe yeah where's the last
zombie bird again if I want to get
somewhere I'm going to get there so I'm
going to make a little makeshift
stairwell mhm outside sounds good
did you grab all the ammo where was the
ammo did you
say I am holding on to it now okay good
okay I don't see an orange dot
anywhere where at the zombie
behind actually why am I picking up so
many
things let's eat this okay I am on the
second
floor if you want to join me I made a
little stairwell out oh here here you
are sir oh I see I
see oh wow he's quick and he's on
fire that zombies on
fire oh is this zomes on
[Applause]
fire I can't jump that high I'll let you
girls check it out we can stay down are
a lot of dudes like a whole lot of dudes
and they're very strong oh really so
many yeah send them down push him down
okay all that was it huh good job team
yay more more more more more Quest more
quests here are you guys' ammo by the
way bio and Kiara you guys want a ton of
ammo a butt ton I got a butt ton this is
for bioo okay and this is for Kiara
where is she where is this beautiful
pink-haired woman Oh you mean pink hair
pink mustache
L are you on the still Oh no you're
there yeah oh
oh oh are you down there Kiara yeah all
right I'll bring it to you if you're
down okay if you're on the bottom floor
I'm down for it okay yeah so I guess the
only way to get up here is by making a
stairwell outside now leave it to
me yay all right let's
see where was are you destroying the car
yeah what for do we get parts first job
yeah here you go the cocky
Chum it's for you thank you so a lot of
bulls I'm swimming in
ammo all right I need to make a new axe
new stone
axe
wow anything it's just satisfying oh we
don't get to pick it up a no I have an
armor book for
you I take I take
I have a cooking book for you nice
exchange thank you thank
you pumpkin
cheesecake have a cake the world is
saved let's go I'm so happy cheesecake
will be our savior anybody find any
baseball magazines I do
love I have seed and medical
okay well if you find a baseball one you
know who to
call who
Ghostbusters you
no
hey raid in the cafe I think somebody's
been
here it does
seem well let's see what time is it
broken we can go back to the Traders and
then yeah we got to turn in this Quest
after all start preparing for the thing
there's a safe in here already oh I have
lockpicks maybe we can get another Quest
when we turn it in yes more quests more
quests okay oh I'm in the wrong house
okay I'm coming come to me there's a
safe I'll head back to I do
feel what do you mean ask for the AK-47
does somebody have an AK-47 what I do
yeah I was going to give it as a present
here
whoa here's a it's a AK47 where did you
get that found it in box
oo thank you enjoy cuz mine was just
about to break my my shitty machine gun
oh enjoy yippee brother you in the
middle of day 20 is it upstairs or
downstairs it's down
okay I just want is
going to turn in a quest where I'm in
the basement I thought you went
downstairs basement but no no it's wrong
house you're the wrong
house come to
me I'm coming I'm just a little
silly make sure they got their weapons
and
such are you two just raiding houses
over there still there's a safe I did
ask them what they want to okay um they
said shotguns but everybody wants to use
shotguns I wonder why wrong house are
you doing this on
purpose look at your map I like to have
my
map okay I'm here a little embarrassed
but I'm here be right back you guys I
got run I got to run real quick I'll
be
okay ready to
go
um Barrel extender
mod
ni okay it is unlocked you can take a
look here's your pay for a it's a wooden
bow a singular wooden bow so worth it
what is this reward well it's not a
primitive bow at least I have a lot of
books for you
kiawa cool thank
you I will take a look at
it what why I these rewards I don't need
any of
[Music]
this are you serious
now are you
serious I'll just take the ammo for
other
people okay
um oh I was hoping you could run over
zombies yeah I think you can but only
with cars not with bicycles were you
trying it with bicycles yeah yeah yeah
that that won't work unless you have
spikes on your bicycle or so now that's
an idea
maybe I should have Tak oh yeah can we
like tie a spear to the bicycle so it's
like
pointed very
creative hey there are you looking for
medical supplies or just here to g g yes
I have something for you I don't know if
it's good for you or
not I am waiting with anticipation
here a beautiful
bow medical supplies beautiful maybe you
would like this because you are obsessed
with trees as
well oh wow look at that southern
farming
difference earn some Dukes what a
beautiful thank you for the seed
magazine and the bow you're welcome
you're welcome please please read it
somewhere
private I will read it in front of you
fun are you still Village Place oh
you're coming here I have
magazine thank you I took a
notification she's playing Seven Days to
Die oh she said she was
too did she sober
up just for the zombie horde I
guess maybe she can have the real
Drunken Fish yeah ah there you are yeah
they didn't have any good requ reward so
I just took a magazine for you thank
you also who uses 9mm again I do oh I
have I took a lot of 9mm ammo to give to
others as
well where is
bioo I'm by the booby lady the booby
lady
okay that could be any of us almost the
quest booby lady here I dropped 9 mm
ammo on the floor
oh thank you
yeah rare zombies like polic oh damn I
should have chosen that Quest
huh when is the we still have time until
the r yeah let's do the quest we should
do Quest I also here's assault rifle
crafting oh thank
you you the
best F the rest
use use yay oh you have unlocked machine
guns AK-47 machine gun Quality 4
yo if only I had machine gun parts
what's a nail gun do we need a nail gun
for
things I don't know wait B have you read
nightstalker volume
3 um I've been reading Night Stalker
different volumes have you read three
already which one
three uh bladed weapons do 10% more
damage at night I think I have
[Music]
okay reloading is so slow I'm going to
take that
skill my leg Yeah my leg why is it
broken again or still what happened oh
do you need a splint uh I mean it's just
2 minutes I I I'll just wait
people you should get the nail gun it's
the best building upgrade tool oh I did
I did get a nail gun jump okay Ladi I am
going to go help out the twins but feel
free to continue your
journey okay all right I'll see you
later okay see see bye we do more level
two quests right over here we do yeah
I'm here one okay let's um K do you like
all of
these oh yeah yeah I'm reading for
you did you get the you doing medicine
too I
am oh thank
you that's a lot I'm going to get really
smart yeah become the smartest there
ever was how full is your inventory F
it's pretty full
okay all right I'm ready to move okay
are we going to the the the bunch
there's a bunch actually F A giggy is
already at one right I think yeah okay
go can I ride a bicycle is that okay
when I'm have I have a broken
leg is that
acceptable I hope so where are we
going just don't Sprint okay if you
don't use shift okay I'll be careful
blint no it's 37 seconds oh okay soon I
will be healed which
way over there wait where are we going
uh back to where we came from I guess
giggy is already there no I am hungry
and thirsty let me bring you stuff
yay
okay n 8 7 6 5 what are we counting down
for
three 1 happy New Year happy
year happy happy
2025 indeed happy birthday happy New
Year happy Christmas Happy Everything
no my my leg a photo of a family do you
think this is a de family or a stock
photo
family stock photo I thought you said
dead
family dead
family it could be both it could be dead
and a stock family stock photo family
that's true if it's taken long
ago that would be sad it would be
sad but in a way they will live on in
photo time someone makes an
advertisement and purchases the rights
to use their photo yeah wa I'm here
which Quest are we doing first the gigy
one uh okay I don't know I'm at the
house okay let's family with me all of
these quests okay I'm coming you know
that's a that's a great idea when I move
I'm going to just put a bunch of stock
photo family pictures
my place so that way when some robs me
they think there's more people living in
the house than just me they perfect I
don't know if that works because if
nobody's
home somebody's got to be home for that
thank you have to go after the after the
eggs and bacon yeah does someone have me
um
food are we running out oh you still got
we're running low m
it's not the best food but oh no corn is
the best
me oh I can cook it up sometime
okay did you know corn is so
nutritiously bad that the corn we use
today is chemically altered and
processed to make it nutritional before
we eat
it
yummer what what I love
superfood oh we have
begun okay okay I'm here let's go with
new gun I'll open it gun oh oh amazing
do you see the family right here oh
that's not that family not that
one something on me oh there is
something on
you don't jump on me don't jump on
me
no ah a
concussion have you guys ever had a
concussion that's kind of crazy feels
weird
conc makes your screen kind of blurry
for a moment
oh but I'm good you see the family wait
get 1 hour 40
un
bro I almost punched B
boo it's okay I probably deserve it
no here's armor crafting
thanks I'll just photo frame while you
guys are fighting Pho photo frame
pretty which family do you think that is
a typical
American oh
family with money you think it's a stock
photo
yes I think it's one of the devs
no hopefully
not hopefully
not
[Music]
oh what is this zombie
doing yeah I saw the C message do we
need armor parts I mean generally um
eventually uh hello oh ah we
have oh people no people you're going to
get hit from the side careful uhoh my
hero oh did I hit you with the
shot no I'm good
okay
meow meow
[Applause]
meow so many yes toilet
water and with your hat you can drink
that too or yeah I
can what do we have wiring ah somebody
wanted electrical crafting
right somebody I saw it like in the
Discord it was
[Music]
cie oh Cron's online oh and's online oh
everyone's ready for the hoorde now
where's the last zombie why are they
always hiding I think outside because I
saw someone crawling
there I saw crawling zombie
like upstairs upstairs okay another
upstairs there's a there's there's
there's a there's a rope oh God rope a
rope how to get up are you fine are you
okay I think I'm okay is no I'm not okay
actually I'm
run run oh I see the Rob okay I see I
see I see I see
there's yellow eyes aim do what's that
growling noise is that your
gun
ow
okay it's really scary oh oh the dog the
dog do the
dog it's F okay we're fine fun it's been
cleared it's been clear that was
crazy damn they hid the dog in the Attic
huh place for pet wasn't there a dog
house outside that would have been a
nicer place the foreshadowing mhm yeah I
guess so I think every house that has a
dog house might have a dog Enemy Inside
wow take care take
caution ooh
shipping
crate Thomas
Harris William
Dillinger John Smith AKA to
Fresh there's some wanted people with
some realistic
looking pictures as if they took them
from Facebook
yeah right Facebook did they take them
from their own
Facebook those really look like they
could be from
devs yeah are you looked at them too mhm
it's the working
Theory well if I was developing a game I
would want to be included somewhere too
yeah right I have bullets for
you MOS di yes you di m
[Music]
hey thank you does anybody here
read
books I love reading no I'm aill
literate wait I need to look uh do I use
this maybe I do I'm at the next
Quest this anybody have food outside of
stinky sandwiches no maybe we should go
home we're
all I'll this potato wait wait wait eat
this potato it's only one but yay it's
better than the stinky sandwiches have
to get out of
[Music]
here without hurting
myself oh
there yeah I'm so full I'm so
cucumber yeah
and hungry and thirsty oh very oh my God
I'm so thirsty uhoh maybe I should drink
my Yuka juice okay I'm going to see if I
can make it to the Traer in time before
she closes okay oh yeah okay let's do
that when did she close though
nine in an hour I'll make
it let's go zoom zoom zoom let's go and
then we are speed I don't know should we
still do more quests after that or
H could um I guess it's not tonight the
zombie R
right the can do them and turn them in
in the morning and then get ready for
the is good
ho um do you need a Band-Aid your health
is
low I but let let's go to the Traer
first so we can get before it closes
okay I'll survive for do we want to go
home once to unload or do we just want
to keep on going I don't know maybe we
should try to do more quests if we if we
can cuz we're going to have to go home
for the raid yeah okay we can find some
food okay live I still also have one
more quest in that
area let's clear it
ooh wait where am I going is this the
right
place oh
yeah oh yeah I have a oh yeah we have a
few uh quests still okay me too me
too man stamina why always so low I knew
you had it in you good work
[Music]
ammo pipe bomb also sounds fun infected
no
problem hey that stuff a little
fix she doesn't really have any
food up on
wait she doesn't want to show me her
yeah she doesn't want to show me her
stuff either sorry it's cuz
I'm oh is it like one at a time
can do one at a time I thought it wasn't
Oh I thought it
wasn't I feel I've us it
before look supp okay lady you can try
now it's just realistic I
guess hey there it works now for medical
supplies or just here to check out my
otheres her other wees
I don't know what do I even
want does she
[Music]
have does she sell I leveled up
again well I'll sell some
stuff what can I
sell
uh egg
it sucks that certain things you can
only sell in a specific amount of
stacks so if you don't have the exact
amount of that stack you you can't get
rid of it oh that is that is
weird the traps electrical traps you
need a lot to build
anything I just knew you fighting
something you like electrical traps you
want to make electrical traps
yeah I don't think anyone else was
reading it or collecting it so I started
reading some but but you need
25 to build
anything oh yeah you're the one who
wanted wiring electrical oh yeah I got
one for you is this cuz no one else was
reading it but I guess I can start
specking into it well CU I don't think
anyone else is here take it take
it thank
you are you moving
no okay I thought my game was like dying
okay thank
you oh wait I have ammo for you of
course you do you always have ammo for
me how much do you have in harvesting
tools I think Gigi is learning that oh
yeah I have harving tools how much do
you have um I have let me see
where did I put it where is it I have 18
into harvesting tools I'll give you one
then when I see you are you already
heading back here's your dirty water I
know how much you love area I love my
dirty water I'm going to drink this
right now
yeah take a peek at my
selection might eat this old
sandwich I'm going to eat the old
sandwich please don't hurt me will be
few minutes oh scared me you know we
don't have
CLS if you're still inside while she
closes does it kick you out yeah you out
oh
okay where's my bike oh what do you mean
I'm first I just drank threee cups of
water this house do you guys want to see
pictures come here there's so many cute
pictures oh inside is she going to close
there's like there's dog she has dog
pictures and bird pictures what she's
selling machine wait are you still in
there can you buy machine gun parts
before she closes is she Clos ah I'll
try she you biking I don't know if I'm
going to
make closed early how dare she she
closed 10 minutes early what the heck
where myice why would she do that wait I
can't find my bicycle has anyone seen a
bicycle lying around
there's a there's a bicycle icon if you
look around oh yeah should lead you to
your bicycle oh found it okay okay I'm
going to for a bad review
for okay but good to know she has
machine gun parts I'll go get them later
um so let's go back and make some quests
even though we're all kind of thirsty
and hungry and cucumber we'll be fine
we'll right we have do we not not have
any more food at all on any of us I have
one sandwich some raw corn and potato M
raw corn surely in the house there'll be
food maybe we'll get lucky and find
something she restarts tonight so they
might not be there s
no but it's okay for right now I I have
a a better gun than before uh like 5
minutes ago
so so it's not too bad we already got an
upgrade maybe for the next hor
night look at him next time I'm not
coping it's it's the
reality yeah Calli gave me the
AK 47 or
whatever we're doing this one
AK47 the bioo one
[Music]
coming oh w a tree has been found who
did that by who I wonder I just don't
know okay one we doing I guess we'll do
this one this
one this is fetch
clear okay so we need stuff this is an
oat Farm there should be food um
magazine here
yummy okay let's find you have to clear
and find supplies I see no problem we're
multitaskers easy oh found a sham
sandwich please don't give me diarrhea
please don't give me
diarrhea it didn't give me
diarrhea the diarrhea
[Applause]
gotcha all right still standing
I thought they were dead this guy's
strong
oh oh they were hiding medical supplies
here
what found a medical journal who learns
it again I learn it good
okay lots of medical journals and I
found food already like a sham sandwich
and peers per
[Music]
wonderful I feel like they hide the
career Satchel so well I got to look
everywhere oh yeah I
forgot find
that mine was hidden inside a watch
where am I are you girls upstairs ow oh
yeah I'm on fire fire oh
no that's not good run really fast run
really really fast and then make it go
out like that I brought more
owie I want I once uh uh made a kitchen
go out in my a fire go out in my kitchen
by just blowing really strong believe me
did you I totally
did I remember a fire in your kitchen
was it the same one yeah yeah I think
pretty sure now I'm on fire run run run
run run
run it works oh I'm so
hot has anybody found their supplies yet
I found mine
oh still looking for mine if there's a
down arrow does that mean
down oh I should should look at that too
yeah or does it just always have a down
arrow I don't trust it oh I think it
does have a down arrow armor crafting in
here please pick it up I'm somewhere
else I think or wait I'm here where you
are now medical crafting in here ooh
where
upstair it's a scary zombie he's
spinning
oh he kind of hurts I'm I'm
scared help help huh help
help oh help I'm coming my sweet are you
coming it's just standing there I'm
standing here but I'll be
there why you looking at that leev trunk
so long
Run keep running keep running keep
running I have so much random garbage in
my inventory are you putting it in thank
you I'm dropping them maybe I should
drop my 2,000
wood I dropped 2,000 wood if anyone
would like 2,000
wood where's you had a
book medic there's a medical book up
there I'm not sure if someone I I I
picked it up for you I have two now okay
no I still need to find mine my Satchel
me too it's really
R what is
it
oh that's the normal way to get
there
uh uh I don't like being
[Music]
hiding oh oh the
fire
dodged where are these
satches they might be in the
walls um no way use your radar okay I
found mine in a
wall okay I mean that's kind of
sus I got it do you want a dirty water
fa yeah I do dirty water thank
[Music]
you may downstairs yummy here wait is
there a medical book somewhere did say I
got two I got
too oh I found my Satchel
yippe
yippe did everyone find their
thingy yes okay
yeah shall we go to the next Quest yeah
yeah I am here oh do we have the same
Quest over there there's two people who
have a quest there I
think is it the
same oh the day reset I had the quest
limit but now it's yeah day 21 we're
being so
efficient wait I'm almost there almost
there and let me give you the medical
journal so I have it off of my hands
T thank
you let's
go got to get my gun out what is this
clearing okay fist
Out
ooh zombies where are you where is
everybody oh there's one watch out for
the fire mhm oh they're on fire it's
biging a
hole
die he's back
up get down he so
strong it
hurts okay ow ow oh no I forgot my bike
oh I'll pick it up when we're done with
this Quest run run run if you're burning
just run I walked right into it my depth
perception can we walk under it no we
can't oh my
go I'm going Dance I'm going to bur
Dan eliminated
her oh no don't play with fire girls
when you're low on HP fire fire fire ow
cannot blow on it to a oh my god wow
what a I will break this
wall okay I'm really
dehydrated we could go to a
pond what
what why how
I know
why huh oh there's a button go around it
there's
a why do this thing is on
fire I don't want to touch it anymore oh
hey it open
fall I'll go around there ah help help
zombies where
be out
[Music]
outside why they break watch
out they're still
alive gy you use arrows right I have
some arrows yeah you arrows I'll give
you in a moment oh in the window oh my
God oh my God there's so many
ow I don't know
doesn't matter what kind of arrows you
use any I use them all
okay oh I feel like I shouldn't be here
I feel like I shouldn't be here by
myself upstairs where did you go oh
upstairs okay let's go careful there's
zombies coming
down oh almost shot
again ah teamwork so titty oh I
leveled oh there more zombies H there's
definitely more up here I believe
oh oh yeah
[Music]
hello oh he's so
green is this the infected
Quest is there
green wow he's glowing yeah he's
glowing oh
this is
new
oops o what's going on
[Music]
here
what where where where to do some you
have to do some Parkour but there's a
there's some around you can there's
another floor upstairs
uhhuh
oh what is this
chamber
what secret
tank this is all a little scary yeah
watch your
step ow zombie bird
but I do see a zombie there he wants to
be uh
released can I shoot
first
oh I think we have to do something about
him oh there's
a another
level there's one like behind a locked
door in the middle
level I don't want
to oh
my
scary
y
okay the roof zombies are dead oh not
quite the roof roof but there's like
several
roofs there's another level up words
this place is gigantic yeah oh there's a
roof roof I'll try to get up there hello
there okay I'll try to do something
about the door
but it's still there can you not just
open the door from there zombie why do I
have to do
it I wonder if there's a key for this
place loud scary oh my gosh all
oh help help help
help oh okay well this
works are you up there yeah they're on
the roof roof there's a I'm
coming I've got no
stamina so many of them
uhoh yeah after this Quest maybe I'm
done for we're done yay we're done but I
wait I want door over there and still
need to open one more door to some use
tactical Warfare uh yeah I think I do I
do is that the assault rifle
one I don't know yes it is okay that's
mine I have one it shall be mine wait
I'm I need to break this door otherwise
I'm not
satisfied
ooh anyone's hungry I got C
can I use your hat FAA to drink water
yes is there a water source out there I
found murky water oh and here you
go f I have another quest in the exact
same location but we don't have to do it
now as this one yeah the same house I
think there's a cool down yeah oh
okay also water
bicycle where's your I don't
know where are you anyone super starving
uh getting there and I have an old
sandwich I'm not I have a Mery water you
could drink the the water in combination
of the Hat might work yeah
yeah I just I can't find you
girls there's uh there's some stairs but
you have to park
for it and they're all the way up there
oh
okay we got to check these there's books
in here where newspaper dispensers four
of them there's books in every single
one of
them except that
one oh I found like six books got to
take a look at them but where where is
everybody I have cat
food actually I might need to eat the
cat food I'm going to eat the
sandwich you'd rather eat the sandwich
that gives
you I have I have good stomach strong
stomach are you in the
house or I'm trying to leave H okay I'll
look for my
bicycle bicycle
and let's
see
um I went in a
tank 4:00 a.m. Traer open
yay can give back Quest
now first find bicycle oh I think I
think I found your bicycle do coyotes
attack
people um yes yes
yes but it looks so
nice it was so cute and pretty
oh I'm
bleeding Dam
hit you right in the eye huh my
eye sorry people I'll be your eyes you
have any of those
bandies I don't have any I have a
regular bandage it'll stop your bleeding
indeed my bleeding stopped I'm just
dying oh
no maybe Trader Jen can help you
are you still lost in the building I
finally made it
out okay I'm going to the trader giving
back my quest and
okay I got a couple of books but they're
I don't know if anybody wants these I'll
put them in the book chest at home
later
[Music]
okay see if she has gun parts yes very
important of utmost
importance then I can already make a
level four gun
right come
on I feel like I'm not learning these
roads at all I'm still we're still new
here it's okay it's okay map Reading is
an important skill
I wish I could drink this rain I was
just thinking the same thing literally
op my mouth and looked up the moment you
said
that why can't we put like buckets down
and stuff I know we have a du collector
that's like bucket we we should just be
able to you know have buckets or like
use our hats
true I learned the crazy trick if you're
ever um on a d dted Island uh what you
can do um to filter water uh you you
take some you you try to find some
container maybe nowadays you know with
how dirty the ocean is you can probably
find a plastic bottle somewhere up the
shore take the plastic bottle cut it in
half H take some um uh water ocean water
place it in the sand and then the second
half of the cut plastic bottle you fold
it uh on the bottom it will make some
kind of like catchy container and then
you put it on top of it's hard to
explain but but but but over time this
will filter the the sea uh water the the
salt out of it and then you get clean
water only a few drops per day but if
you get a lot of these you can have a
lot of water
eventually survival skills baby good job
I knew you could do it filtration
camping I want to drink that water I
hope we don't need to use this when
we're camping I I will if if if we get
to zero one day we'll remember this just
for
[Music]
fun yeah I'll take this P oh did you
guys get the next Trader Trader
Bob I don't know oh yes I did get Trader
Bob wait does that mean she didn't give
us anything special she didn't give us a
motorcyle she gave a nail gun right oh
yeah she gave me mini bark mini bar Park
mini bike
parts oh that's a motorcycle bike no
looking for some healing yes I think so
kahua I have stuff for
you thank you thank you thank you I
wonder if anybody is investing into
explosives crafting does anybody know I
kind of want to I like
explosives I have I have some Molotov
and bom
okay I'll start I'll start learning
explosives yeah let's go
yeah mining tools is anybody fighting
with mining
tools I have the art of mining Volume
7 don't know who to give this
[Music]
to well I'll just put these into the
chest I can't think right now baby G
which one mining art Min I'm mining
okay um what was I looking for machine
gun parts
yes bye bye all of
them okay what magazines they have
explosive s and farming I
see feel like I've never seen you with
your hat off
I have cool glasses now yeah you
do I don't know it's kind of giving
scary Vibes though the you don't like
how I
look what's wrong with my glasses I
don't know I'm just getting scary
Vibes what kind of Vibes maybe it's the
angle what about this from the profile
view in the
profile thank you so much maybe hey come
again
from the the mustache and the bald head
and the
[Music]
glasses well my bartering is plus 2%
with these so maybe it's threatening oh
2% that's going to do a big
difference we should all start
small we got to start somewhere yes got
to start from the
bottom from the bottom now we here are
we going back or like home
yeah it's it's the
21st got to prepare it's almost time we
must probably go home bike bike wait did
I ever find my bike where's my bike
ah all right then it was uh a fine time
questing with you ladies it seems I'm
not ready for tier three yet though so
maybe soon but
H I do have one more Quest over there
maybe after the
raid
oh all of the girls are currently at our
new home are there by any chance trying
to fortify our new home I wonder oh
let's go find out let's go
yeah she had automatic magazines
what I didn't see them I'm blind
I'll check it out before I
go just me the open road and 10,000
zombies this is just like Mad Max what a
lie witness
me I
watch mean for the first time and I
didn't think I would be into it because
like like I don't know I don't usually
watch stuff like that but it was so good
yeah it's just like seven days to die I
I started watching I fell asleep you
asleep I fell asleep so much is
happening yeah it's like the most
action-packed movie like everything is
happening every second I was really
tired that day
I maybe why am I going the wrong way
how much does she pay for that
8 it seems like my type of movie though
so maybe I'll give it a second
chance it's it's fun it's a fun movie it
is
fun the world is
cool and
bald yeah bald cool and bald
she sells it's so much more expensive I
sell her something and she she puts oh
you can't even eat the raw
corn wait is it just cuz I'm on the bike
yeah I think so you can normally eat it
I'm pretty sure I have to eat the raw
corn cuz I'm starving any more of those
thanks
anyway no fa it doesn't have any
nutritional value super corn I have no
choice I can't guys I can't buy it knew
you find something you like wait is this
a shortcut this
road curving
Road let's find out I think it is goes
right
home I want to have food at
home could we have a Lakeside date so I
can drink your water yes I could also
use
water wait I want to go where girls
are I I would like a sip sip too just in
case so we don't waste
resources you're so
far just catch up to us whenever you
whenever you're ready I'll try I'm going
to the lake to the north I feel like
that's the best water source for good
sip
sip I also have tons of meat and five
eggs for you to cook oh
good me too I got some meat as well meat
too meat meet too meet
too nice to meet you nice to meet you
too thank
you we are all made of meat and Flesh
and Bones so maybe nice to meet you
isn't so far
off we don't have to resort to to
cannibalism just yet I know we're all
starving but but you look so yummy fa no
you're
[Music]
F people always tell me I look tasty
they say I look like fried chicken to
them in their
eyes they're just
projecting mhm yes they are they're the
tasty ones mm you hear that kfp
okay here you go
she's running into the Blake
wait did you get like being used I got
it okay I got so
[Laughter]
scared it's the most PR precious hat of
all time I'm trying to find oh here we
go yeah your hat has been passed around
so much at this point everybody's
wearing it you're probably getting
lice no none of us have lice I have no
hair on my head there I will Jud Jud
anyone for having
life I have PTSD from lies so no
judgment I
have yes drink a gallon of Lake water I
am ready to stop drinking ooh tummy egg
thank
you maybe by the time you're all done
drinking I'll be there almost there yeah
yeah yeah go go go go
[Music]
my I mean sip sip sip
sip W I'm really
chilling you are really drinking
all oh so
tasty almost there almost there almost
there o day 21 it says it in red now
okay I think I drank to
get and this is only our second okay I
don't want to roll down the hill okay oh
I'm I'm I'm I'm almost there I'm almost
there I'm literally there I see you I
see
you fauna awaiting me I'm
waiting it's like you have to babysit
people for drinking like it's a
dangerous thing or something it's very
dangerous don't over drink
water ah there it is B thank
[Music]
you I wonder if we can make more of the
water purifier P where did you get it
did you find it I just found it I don't
even remember where I found it maybe
maybe they'll sell the mod for it cuz
like the the Traders rotate their mods
and stuff so maybe we got to learn the
schematic for it
yeah okay do you think that's enough
I think if it's at 90 it's enough
90 oh
okay there you go thank you so much
let's go home I miss home I hope I hope
it doesn't look too
different never know what to expect
after a long
outing I know suddenly there might be
five rows of spikes in front of our home
more trees more trees yeah but the trees
would be probably there for a different
reason for giggy's addiction oh gosh
what did you just I have to plant more
trees trees are a natural defense right
yeah a little bit but we also won't be
able to see clearly anymore okay I only
see spes good good question mark is it
good
it's been a long
time we're finally home AO
[Music]
Queen wait alloy cream is already the H
finished
thing potato seeds oh I hear I hear
something
they inside I think they're in on the
back of our house or so oh knocking on
our door what would you want we don't
buy anything we don't want to buy
anything please go
away okay all right all right they're
getting a little bit too
rowdy oh yeah they're knocking on our
back door I didn't know we had a back
door W she dropped some
loot what did they
drop oh night vision mod see in the dark
with this Hightech night vision head
armor mod oh oh and oh weighted head mod
schematic interesting knives and
machetes
is it for I can use that I have knives
and
machetes uh wait what does this say
knives and machetes do not have a head
that can be weighted oh I don't think
you can use this yeah never mind uh but
it's for all melee weapons except knives
and
machetes well I'll put
it maybe in
here should I make my new gun now
[Music]
chat or now is the time right yeah but I
just got the
AK-47 if you've got the
materials I don't want to replace it
already
but maybe maybe I should I think we
might have to just make grilled meat
fine yeah that's okay CU if we don't
have enough eggs carnivore diet I guess
yeah it
[Music]
is things just disappear when I click
that
button I wonder where they
go ooh vehicle
crafting I think I've been do I have to
keep the crafting window open to
craft no I don't think so it goes
passively oh okay
cool I think I'm learning that um
potassium nitrate where to put
that making gun
powder
spicy ah do they H nerd head nerd head
uh okay okay okay okay did they were
they going to give me anything uh like
armor kits for
it wait let me go down to n
SE hello hello want to get you some it's
fine it's fine don't worry nerd hats
have been requested I
hear yes we just finished a quest we're
not too far from the new house but we
probably need to start working on
getting ready for the raid
anyway so we're going to go turn in a
quest and then yeah we have some hungry
folks here I can now make them on level
four already but I will need four armor
crafting kits unless you want it on a
lower level oh the nerd hats yeah yeah
um they have they do have some armor
parts um I might actually if if Lok
wants to make a level one or so a nerd
hat I'll take it and I can give them
mine because they need exp more than I
do what we'll see we'll see how many
armor parts we have cuz I think I think
that there was a bunch in the crate
at the
house parts
we have here and
there I think bioo had like four in her
personal chest at the old house so I was
going to ask her about those if she'd
like to make a
donation I know I I got a couple too I
just I don't know if I can make a level
four nerd hat maybe three is fine
yeah yeah
how do we make the level one
hat uh with one yeah I mean there's some
extra stuff but the most important thing
is the armor crafting kit um I'll make
you actually you know what I'll give you
my level two I think nerd
hat uh or wait wait wait wait wait
wait let's
see yeah donate to the animal shelter
their new armor and I'll try and craft I
think I have enough cloth to craft you
guys some better primitive armor it's
like a higher level I also have a ton of
magazin oh yeah you too no
problem I actually have a ton of
magazines to give Kiara
yeah I need more duct
tape do I have any duct I have two duct
tape okay that'll be enough I'll see if
he has any stuff I can use to make duct
tape we're still using the old uh base
right today for the attack yes okay hey
Chad does this
increase the this doesn't increase
magazine for shotgun does it glue glue
we should ask for glue
right glue yes we need glue as much glue
as possible it's not shotgun I figured
as much just get the magazines oh that's
a food bundle
workbench oh wow another
workbench that's a big reward oh they're
giving you a
workbench yeah yeah it's a reward for a
quest nice then we could have two next
to each other because again we can't use
it at the same time it seems right okay
I grabbed it nice no more jobs let's see
the
inventory don't can you make a bicycle
oh you you should be able to but it's
just it's a matter of we don't have the
parts yeah I would need the parts but if
you do enough quests you get a bicycle
Quest okay okay let's
leave uh let's
go should we all go should should we go
to the old house now or the new one
or maybe zombie coming up behind yeah
okay okay let's go to the old house and
make just check the spikes we don't have
to make more but maybe we can like fix
the ones that need
fixing or should we stop by the trader
first since the trader nearby one more
armor okay okay okay okay and then we
can get some stuff there oh there's some
air
drops those air drops that's the S yeah
uh
this
[Music]
where
okay
um our inventory is full again so we
should go do something about
it okay I now have an old level two nerd
hat that somebody can have and one new
level four nerd hat that I'll give to
[Music]
Fu how about how's crony doing crony uh
crony CCE you guys probably need some
exp
right um yeah yeah I can live without
too you know I could make chest
somewhere I can even more crafting kits
then I can make more nerd hats
okay okay I I'll see if I have some and
I'll I'll I'll I'll but right now I'm
too I'm a bit far away okay put it into
a chest somewhere uh I'll put the nerd
hats that are like free to take into the
armor chest in the new house okay yay ni
thank you yeah I mean if there were
spares would love it but otherwise you
know it's okay well there's still enough
time I can probably still make more I
just need more duct tape and stuff I
wonder if someone get the supply drops
Gigi's kind of close I wonder if she's
going to get
them it's fine we need to focus on
getting
ready yeah we want to focus on getting
ready but I'm not sure what getting
ready is so
fortify materals upgrade your armor I'll
make you some armor I said I was going
to do it so let me I'm going to make a
bunch of armor with cloth thank you we
have cloth I think if you can give me
some cloth that will help me if we do
have cloth oh we have fragment oh I see
I wonder if you can make a full cloth
with the fragments you can craft it I
think thank you I think cloth fragments
are fine I'll take them
okay this house is so
cramped we need a bigger one number
three thank you oh perfect this is
actually yeah this will be great okay I
can use that okay we can make more so
we'll make more
yeah okay and I'll see this oh oh oh oh
uh Cory you should buy lucky loot sorry
guys you should buy lucky
looter lucky looter it's like a I heard
on a guide you really shouldn't do that
one reason why why not it doesn't make
much of a
difference but if you want it go for it
go for it don't no no no no no okay okay
I just read it and I was like this would
be good but if if the gu says no then
don't do it okay never mind all right
let's go back no more curtains we can't
have curs we're not going to survive
night don't say that I think we'll be
fine we'll be okay dying is normal we
will be the one who
dies that's heroic but you know we won't
die just stay in the back a little
bit stay in the back naturally because
we're scared but
magazine old house which is this follow
me
okay I I
follow I follow you something something
baby that song is that does it go that
way I follow you you into the deep sea
baby I know mean someone back me
up help
you
know come here come here full m into
this room I'm not
insane they're all kind of different
levels but it's better than what you
have right now so thank
you I made another nerd goggle level
four so um one nerd
hat okay let's put this stuff on if
you're going to give if you're going to
wear the nerd hat though maybe else okay
yeah wa wait but I think hi is here so
we can take oh wait are you who's who's
we're in the in the new house we're in
front of you yeah uh oh yeah one of you
Cecilia crony fight for life for this
level four yep
okay you want it you want it but there's
a wait take take the level two one of
you can take the level two one in the
chest no actually I think I think you'll
benefit more from having this here take
it I'll take the other
one wait I can can probably SM like
another one if I get more duct tape and
stuff no no no thank you thank you no
no huh I have the the fragrance here so
fun behind
you
welcome y thank you very
much thank you 8%
Hood then yeah it's a level five
primitive Hood who wants the Primitive
Hood maybe give it to um I think CeCe
needed it oh no I I have the I have the
the I have the head K now okay I'll hold
it for now may CR I'm level four she has
level two I'm making you some better
stuff
curtain oh some stuff more plant
fiber oh we have a lot of plant fiber oh
okay nice that's that's big that's big
news yes we
do is almost time make the gun okay okay
okay no more we should put away the r
ner hats unless they give me
ingredients yes you got
to um okay crony come over here I got
some better armor for it's just higher
level armor yippe here you go uh
yippe the Hat I think somebody else has
the very strong face mask who's not
using the very strong face mask face we
have the that one the strong the
Primitive Hood yeah if you could give
that to crony that would be
awesome it is yippe yipp now you're
fortified where that go
yay look at how strong we
are ah
grony you want a baseball bat there's a
baseball bat in here oh I have a forge
ahead if someone needs that oh yes yes
please please yeah here I'll give it to
you I see you I put it on my feet okay
in my on my
bottom oh have two
even
wonderful
Bellows what is that aim for the head by
the way aim for the aim for the head
sorry no problem it's so cramped in here
I can't help it definitely also get a
little bit of a little bit more medical
stuff so like maybe everybody take like
a couple medical things like a or
something which one am I making chat I
don't have any I'll Take One medkit For
Me Maybe everybody just you take some
painkillers or
something we should probably boil all
the murky water so I'll do that yes I
also have some as well oh we have
some okay can you can you like just put
it
all hold crony hold on a sec let me give
you do we have a magazine box in this
space as well God yeah the books yeah
yeah books are here right in front of
the fire oh okay thanks crony use this
use use the hold on oh oh thanksuse pain
the [\h__\h] CH oh thank
you you didn't have to it's okay I have
magazines for you a than you where's
where is do you have any more claw
fragments by chance yeah they're in the
I have
10 oh really
yeah oh okay wait wait on the ground oh
thank you and this behind you y yo thank
you yo oh so many
gifts you got to make the armor for us
you got to make the armor okay
okay placs
here the armor part yeah oh yeah armor
parts will also be useful for a lot of
things okay we only had that one so I
maybe we have some oh maybe you should
use this Celly oh yeah I have I have a
since you do shotgun I have a thing
improves weapon handling while moving or
firing from the hip because the weapon
becomes more manageable in close
quarters oh really interesting let me
see me grab that from you yeah I put I
have my little little hands on it let me
see cuz I don't use a gun you can thank
you where is this here and I think we
can put the mods in the magazine section
too because um they're like all
learnable yeah that's a good idea Close
Quarters I don't really know if you can
shot I think bi might use this cuz she
uses a pistol oh okay okay I'll give it
to her when I see oh she's here cilia we
found some ala seeds I don't know that
helps at all but um I would need like
actual aloe vera but it's still nice for
the future when we start don't know how
the farming works we do have a farm
here no we took down a can I scrap can I
scrap all the level one primitive
outfits cuz it's taking up space in the
armor section I think so I think you can
that yeah probably scrap
it scrap it pretty sure we have these
things ion in my crafting
boxing is always a good
idea unless it's something important and
it's not I have another workbench I'll
put the workbench down somewhere
else let's see
so
blind yeah I am pretty blind there it is
what if I put the what's a pipe rifle is
that good is it
bad uh do you guys have murky water yeah
yeah you guys put it all there okay I'll
boil all of them then that'll be good ni
there's a person standing there Callie
is a pipe pipe pipe pipe pipe rifle good
can I use dad uh the only good pipe
weapon apparently is Machine
Gun okay but uh let's see I wonder if I
can make another Shotgun If I find
Springs uh Springs Springs I need seven
springs for my new shot uh machine gun
oh dang it you're not using the AK um I
was using it it was so good but I can
already make something better now at
level four why don't you give it to
somebody else maybe if you're going to
make another gun oh does somebody else
use machine guns now I wonder I don't
have any guns yet have you skilled into
anything no no you haven't skilled into
any
weapons no cuz I can't
piek you can't piek oh yeah it is choice
I was waiting for well I we didn't need
it for the first round and I didn't know
so I'll do it now okay I'll go into I
don't want to do anything
like maybe
I'll shotgun
Master uh I'll be right
back yes hello hello I'll make it for
you but I need to wait for a little bit
more iron um oh do you need more iron
yeah I'm foring it right now I'm also
needing a lot of iron for myself too uh
I need one I need like five I need seven
more iron for myself as well oh okay a
lot of iron the work bench can you make
is it expensive to make another one uh
I'll check but the the iron is being
made in the Forge that's separate
oh um but wait
I I need for your nerd head wait how
many armor kits did you give me three
okay I can I already actually make a
level four nerd hat for that I need four
but I have an extra one that I can give
you and then for free yeah for free a
discount for my for how do you call
someone who's only related to you by
being someone else's wife who's who
you're also their wife I don't know
sister
wife I guess something like that but
we're also wives so we're not really
Sister Wives
wait now I ran out of lever no wait I
have a bit more lever oh yeah okay okay
okay okay okay done with the
forge does anybody have some more like
iron for me to like smelt there's
there's 100 already in the yeah that's
not enough we need more more more oh
that's not enough okay I'll look I'll go
out and look for more I'll also look for
iron M please please me too
also maybe if I Springs I need Springs I
thought I had Springs I I have Springs
in my inventory have I have one spring
I'll take that one spring no I have nine
Springs I'll take Seven
Springs here just take take all of my
Springs
amazing thank you are we are we
fortifying this
house no no okay okay Callie is going to
the the main
house oh it's time soon soon wait did I
give you your hat oh wait F fun I have
your hat oh my hat
yay level four nerd
hat now I can match everyone else yay we
look so cute gosh I look
crazy wow it suits wait you know wait do
with the green hair and now even more so
with the hat and the go why do you have
alien glasses you look like the lady you
know from that photo from that chocolate
FB um Charlie and the Chocolate thing
yeah WKA not Charlie you look like a
lady from the picture yeah sad oompa
oompa she was just trying her some
Springs I'm going to drop it oh I'm
actually I I have enough now oh okay
I'll put them into this yeah
[Music]
um okay OA
Loa
cute what am I
[Music]
doing I need so much
iron so much iron I'm looking for more
thank you that's so sweet but oh wait
with this 10 + 4 oh yeah
um more I'll probably get there do we
need to head over yeah might soon
soon the sooner the better probably get
mentally
prepared
okay what the blast furnace speed up
foring yeah but I don't have time to
make that right
now I'm going to make it after the
hoorde I'm so busy now I found a little
iron deposit o oh
nice are you right you are our
uh what are you again minor yeah minor
69er Beaver
yeah scary okay do I have one
more it's getting
scary why is the thund don't worry come
into my arms and my iron
hole you'll be safe down I'm ironing
straight
down I now have 1,000 iron oh my
gosh so efficient you can just thr it
into the
forge
okay okay I made my machine
gun there's a lot of hammer books Hammer
books I use Hammer books Sledgehammer
books the in the book one
okay I wanted to keep digging but it
looks like time will be soon I'll I'm
hungry can I eat this pie I'm going to
go down yes
okay cilia
imig hey that's me have you decided on
your choice of
weapon um I want I think I'm going to go
stick stick
stick no no club club club oh really you
just want to focus on one I feel like I
don't know if anybody else does this but
I chose like one melee and PE PE Pew
yeah I think it's do you like the
assault rifle do is it fun it's fun for
me it's like I don't know much about
guns
and okay then I'll go with that one okay
uh I I can give you I can hand you down
my old uh the one that Cali gave me what
I will say though is that if if you are
using clubs and you want to level both
your your shotgun and Club strength at
the same time like they shotguns and
clubs use the same strength metric so if
you wanted to use shotgun might be a
good idea cuz you could minmax it a
little better but I'll I'll I I think
I'll do one skill in into because I
don't want to go since the weapon is
already Meely then I want one that is a
little bit further so I'm going to go
with assault rifle for now but I can do
I can change my mind with time I think
one point is not going to I would like
to hand me down please are you in front
of me
no I am at the old house right in the
I'm coming there soon Maks okay so the
hord is starting in 3 hours is should we
all go to the vc1 then yes I think
that'll be a good
idea jump over
there you see one me see
one hello uh brain slow do I have any
other modifiers here slow too
seriously I can use my blocks in some
kind of fancy
way where my spikes do you think maybe
we should move like most of the
materials to the new home then or do we
just have this place as a backup I think
it's nice to have a backup but we can
slowly try to move things
[Music]
over
mhm what okay so the back door is
closed um let's
see this
[Music]
Oney okay and the
front I'm going to show up last minute
again
uhoh
the let go oh let's put
magazine there some shotgun shells in
the magazine and ammo s
spot
okay and
then oh
nice this is nice no
okay all right does someone have a
higher quality shot shotgun Maybe
um um oh are you using a pipe Shotgun by
chance uh yeah so I already gave uh the
double barrel shotgun that I had to F
but I wonder if I can make a shot a
shotgun double barrel quality one let me
let me look it
up
than I have shotgun parts I just need
five forged iron duct tape and spring
I'll see if I can if I can make
something for you oh thank you better
quality does anyone have
wood have wood the beaver has
wood look at this can you can you can
give me some of it I'll just make some
more spikes
uh sure just a
moment I'll give you I'll also like help
repair the spike yeah okay so you kept
some wood because you'll need that in if
you want I some
I'm so
hungry need to go back starving I'm
going I'm just going
to and then I'll bring you your your
rifle nice thank you okay I'm going to
reput the spikes outside be careful when
coming in and out of the
house
okay was there any fortification added
again or is it same as last time same as
last time I don't think I think it's
going to be
fine I don't know if I can go in time oh
gosh uh run run bicycle
bicycle
a it's so nice take me a while to two
minutes
tops ow I think I'm going to die
actually you know what I can do I think
I can make you a pipe shotgun that's
higher quality it it won't be double
barrel but it'll be a higher quality
pipe shotgun oh thank you you I just
have a level one is the thing so okay I
can
get level three dang it hold on a second
oh no you don't you don't have to like
straighten yourself cuz I already have
the club that you gave me so oh yeah it
is a pretty it is a good club um okay
let's see pipe I just need glue might
not why not six glue
really does anybody have a ton of glue
let me see glue are you in the old house
or new house uh either one oh iar
there's some yeah in new in the new
house yeah but depends on where you are
it might take you a
while anyone new
house any there I I just left a while
ago I'm on the way to the old we need
you don't go too
far but wait are you making it for for
Who ah what about
that maybe we should we can check the
the box is here there's a bunch of maybe
we can find maybe if bi has glue I'll
just pay her back for it later oh yeah
bio's got five glue never mind all right
B I owe you five glue we might be
overpreparing
again we might be fine I mean
overpreparing is better than under
preparing
right
pipes only three pipes I wonder if we
have more pipes pipes in the new house
there's definitely some pipes
man okay
I might have
some oh
no she's going to die I just need pipes
you're sending her she's going to die
pipes what do you mean what are
pipes why is she so
confused pipes okay
okay okay okay okay somebody has
[Music]
um I need them for a pipe shotgun I'm
making for crony actually I'm stealing
them from VI
sorry no you don't owe me anything just
take it it's fine get to the base hurry
I'm trying but I went the wrong way dve
Foster use your bik go through the river
you don't have to go through the path go
through the river I'm trying I'm
drowning try harder don't shoot me when
I get there please I'll try really hard
not to I might enter with the zombies oh
oh then we might have to Don't Shoot Me
don't shoot me I'm almost
there food we have 60 bullets let's make
them count put
okay yeah you guys will be fine I'm
going to show a little perch that you
guys can if you want that with an
Italian
cilia and ammo oh my God this shooting
platform is so good thank you you're
welcome you're welcome
shoot you made it yay I going to shoot
you no shoot her shoot her no it's not
too
late it's dangerous this place is
dangerous does anybody else have any
pipes any amount of pipes at all not
right now have any pip
sorry okay I can make you a level three
I can make you a level three
shotgun the zombies are here I recommend
the club they'll be here in 20 seconds
oh so beautiful you want to see it's
going to be
fun you 65 ammo as well to help you out
crony all right oh thank you where are
you I am
outside oh I see you waiting for death I
think everybody faing
see okay here you go here is your gun
and here is your ammo my God you didn't
have to what the heck that's a lot oh my
God use them well but remember it only
it only shoots one at a time yeah yeah
so just be ready for that I'll make them
count oh boy here we go oh God here we
go uh-oh good luck everyone oh gosh
we got this it's easy easy
easy kinky can you put one more block
here for me wait a minute okay I I can't
jump so high
yet oh
party they're
coming shot are not the best to have at
this let me make it for you real
quick thank you oh oh God there's really
a lot of us yeah thank
you oh
God okay no one's out no one's out on
the field right I'm going to throw mol
not go on the okay what be careful
okay oh old spit all the vomit now oh
they're spitting ew it goes pretty
far okay seems like no one's attacking
the house from the other side it's only
the side okay okay nice
they're getting in them okay all right
all right this might be pretty by this
time I forgot to put my bed roll in here
oh my God it's vomiting like crazy oh
I'm
scared oh
wa it's a bit laggy too wa that's
vom uhoh are you
okay I need to get
bed you ow don't hurt me
uh-oh uhoh they're going to break for
the spikes soon the first band inside in
the food chest and also food anyone
needs a break no they're going to break
for the spike soon over here oh are they
okay
can can somebody build more spikes I I
don't have materials for it I'll build
more spikes I have some
spes is uh on the left side of the house
okay I'm building spikes right now all
right all
right I don't know I'll cut this tree
down too while we're at it more
wood but what about the natural uh uh
you know oh ow ow zomes on the hill on
the hill uhoh zombies on the hill sh
from the brid sho from the bridge
zombies on the
hill they're they're coming from the
front of the house now again from the
Hill from the
hillair how do you coming from the
hill C CC right click to activate it and
then throw it with left click
okay oh go behind cring Dodge Dodge
backwards okay
okay I thought the bomb would kit
you oh there was a bomb I didn't even
know
that yeah but it was very very little
Hammer Time
baby a bird oh the birds are unfair the
spikes the birds don't care for the
spikes bir those are birds are not that
strong it's okay yeah the birds are like
spikes down okay I'm putting spikes on
the front
calm over here
thankfully watch out for the dogs a oh
it's okay I'm running oh wow am I
taking okay dog is dead it's that's a
big
dog oh dear the dog
hurts am I helping
keep shooting am I
helping someone's naked out there can't
reach you can't reach it's
[Music]
me Miss
spr okay I'm going to try putting down
more spikes God
scar I'm crating more spikes too I
killed the bird with my
fist he's in he's in wait is that a
where did they get in there is okay
maybe we can filter them in in a certain
way like choke them through let's try to
refor toate when there's
time fortify it okay there's a little
bit of chill time right now down time
healing and food inside in the food
chest yeah time so oh they're coming
they're coming from the left side left
side
oh I'm going to throw a Molotov so don't
go in the field on the left side yet
okay should have brought my Molotov
cocktails this is definitely different
from the first
nights yeah yeah oh nice
fire god so many them are broken
it'sing save going to throw pipe bombs
also on the left side so don't don't go
out oh watch out watch out watch out
watch
out make it go boom I saw it right in
front of me there's a lot going on on
the left
side yeah there is a
lot
W make him go boom yeah make him go
boom
I wo don't worry don't worry we'll be
fine okay they starting to come a little
bit from the left be behind a bit
okay there a lot on the left
back don't mind me
I'm my God he's having a contion over
there reloading reloading get him get
him get him all right I going to set the
field on fire
again nice people
nice I hope he doesn't set the spikes on
fire by himself
burning oh nice get hopefully not I
think we got him
uhoh much better
shotgun I'm out of ammo soon there there
he is where are the repair kits do we
have any here inside I'm pretty
sure they're coming from the Southwest
Southwest there's the big one the big
let
out throw
it I'm helping get him get him get
him
yeah nice job
team
yeah oh no don't break it through is
Faun out there using her Fists she
always
does she has no fears the F I'm jealous
yeah I'm getting I'm getting bonuses oh
my gosh I'm super jealous of f right now
I'm going to go and
fight she's so
brave I'm brave too I'm too scared to go
out there yet but I'm out of ammo soon
so I'll probably go out and die oh watch
out same okay do not shoot shoot okay no
Ty watch out behind you there's a big
guy yeah that's what I thought
officer oh oh oh back back there is he h
the TR I don't we hit him there are a
lot of GRE stuff so
weird do we need to be I don't know
maybe I should go outside and it's so
laggy I can't
hit it's pretty
laggy tried to hit them like face
through me oh my God
reloading oh wow terrible swings for
me we go
backwards
oh goodness okay get get him they
trying oh that one's really strong
down the orange ey ones are very strong
I need to get out of
[Music]
here I'm going to start throwing pipe
bombs watch out people on the
field I'm out of
ammo I think we're almost out of ammo
too I'm
scared who's who's outside right now
besides fauna oh fond just went in I'm
in I'm coming back
okay I see I'm so scar
okay so that I can go back out and fight
again damage to me I don't know why it's
almost over
no we got this bad not too bad it's not
bad I'll make some more
spikes be com there go back go back go
back
big one oh there's there's a there's a
lot from Southwest
Southwest uh-oh oh it's laggy out here
there a
zombie yeah hit him with the
fire
okay
stamina
stamina oh no I'm going to die a
concussion
they are
camping oh love love dying oh joy day to
die yeah Seven Days Seven Days to
Die oh crazy exploding head
emoji shocked face oh
boy
nice do
it go get all this
they break the house the doors are
open
two so close not
[Music]
D just one it's fine it's
fine get off my Bo are they is it
done in
there calm suddenly didn't it until 3 I
F I fought 4 a.m. it seems quiet now
it's they're preparing for the next
quiet recoup everybody okay
recoup hey did I die last second oh it's
over for real oh man why did I die last
second oh it's over it's quiet too quiet
it's too quiet too quiet I don't think
it's over ladies to a happy song or
something I thought we were leaving Ladi
many do we have left if we don't have
any 79 is it over there's the music's
gone no there's no way it's over I don't
know it feels over I don't feels over
what the but the the the the the the the
the the sky is still
red and the Happy song isn't playing
what
little touch this okay you got it I got
it okay I'm going to put stuff in the in
the storage
[Music]
oh well too wonderful we've done we've
done it once again but I think next time
maybe one more row of spikes because
they do seem to be breaking through now
yeah just one small row that yeah what
hell I wor if we're going to I I wonder
if we're going to have more like flying
type enemies as well if that's a thing
oh
yeah there was only a few birds and more
ammo also there's iron Spike that you
can build now apparently uh uh better
spikes uh it's not over not over not
over where are they it's not oh
that's you me yeah did I scare you guys
a little bit it's just
me you're such a
troll a little silly sometimes she's so
silly I think it's not
over it's
over it was a light
yeah it's over apparently you can you
can uh get through them all before 4:00
a.m. we were just
fast okay free waves that makes sense
okay yay we did it that was
fun it felt more intense than the first
time yeah yeah the first time was
[Music]
an we just got so much
stronger stronger together everyone we
didn't die help good job helping you did
you did you did
it you guys are doing great how do I fix
the Spike oh God not with our body not
with our
body I'm stuck on a Spike oh no am can
we heal now we're going to di we Qui
down let's maybe maybe fix
oh let's heal let's
let's that's kind of a weird noise mm I
hope it's over cuz I already left and
went far
away yeah yeah it's over it's over yeah
it should be done I think speaking of uh
how long may we be online today 4 hours
total again or um I would I would be
very happy if if we could if people
could not play past uh 45 minutes from
now okay sounds good okay course we'll
play again tomorrow of
course you know just to make sure that
everybody's got enough time to level up
and such and do a bunch of quests
together and such yeah yeah there's
shotgun ammo and uh 762 ammo in the old
house so take that before you leave the
old in the ammo box I think oh yeah we
need to end here for today but if
anybody wants our our our what's it
equipment we have
the right oh yeah you can borrow to
someone else I
guess yeah I'll drop it for now
okay thanks ah I I I was going to drop
the other ammo in the new
house let's check the current stage the
game stage oh uh Faun is the one that's
furthest in game stage
50 what did I do how did I get F this
what's a game stage you're just fting so
good punching things punching game stage
not been leveling very much I wonder if
I have the EXP debuff or something maybe
I'm just not doing enough Quest I got to
do more quests H want to Dr the goles
again oh yeah I'll bring it into the new
house okay okay I hope it gave you some
levels yes
[Music]
nice everybody looks so dirty look at
them
nerd should we put our levels into
strength again what weapon are you
enjoying using the shotgun or what are
you using strength is probably best for
that okay strength for shotguns and
clubs I want to take some of these
materials like iron stuff from the old
house to the new house since we have a
forge over there good
idea yeah a good idea we'll see you
everybody bye byebye see you later thank
you byebye bye bye will also head out
for now I have a different stream I'm
doing um but I will see you guys
tomorrow don't overdo it
cie bye all righty bye bye I'll see you
guys later bye bye take care see you
tomorrow
O2 O2
O2 uh yeah let's do quests I need to get
rid of my exp debbed
okay Ying yuming yuming we love yumping
here y y yumping we're yuming yuming
yuming we Ying Ying we yumping we oing
we yapping we Ying it takes so much
stamina stamina contest let's start
already Zer I'm
[Laughter]
out I love yuming what you yuming about
cool I think I'm like I have like a
radioactive sign are you sober now yeah
I tell you sound
disappointed sad about it
no I'm happy cuz I was then I could join
I didn't want to be the weird drunk
uncle at the party no I think I would
prefer great you would have been the
life of the party
yeah um wait where is where did Cory go
where did you go me yes where are you oh
there do you want to do you want to do
quests
too uh sure I'll do one yeah can we guys
join you even though we don't have
bicycles
yeah bicyc L pointing and laughing no
imagine not having a b bu of try
hard yeah we don't need we like being
healthy and moving our legs properly and
walking are you je of the of the ding
ding huh watch is ding
dinging is low impact exerc col I'm
going to the house back first to a new
house I need to drop stuff off that
house okay let's oh you can repair the
bike too yeah you can repair with repair
kit so it's actually pretty nice also
you can dye it whatever color you want
yeah I was going to say what a
coincidence you all have your colors but
then I realized
well I wish take you guys with me but it
doesn't unless you like move with
me it's kind of works it's a little a
little bit it's kind of working kind
of as so if you girls join us should we
still be doing tier 2
quests yeah we did that with CIA too
yeah I think they they get
regardless KY earlier
CIA that's a good
password better than one11 at least
one11
do1 has a password right guys no ever
nope a we're totally joking by the way
for legal reasons that we never use
one11 of course not yeah no
way I feel like we slow it this way
people then if we just
walk wow bals really are pretty fast
yeah thank
bicyc but don't tell them that 10 quests
or so we don't need bicycles cardio is
good for
you what do you think Bing is it's also
cardio but it's less it's less cardio
you it's not less cardio it's like
longer cardio cuz you can bike for
longer and you can run yeah but we're
going the same way wait where did you go
I lost her it's over I lost her it's
okay you know I I went acoss the river
you can cross the river with a bike over
here hello what I always get off of it
you can go straight through what yeah if
you have Salina you can just n through
it huh that's crazy that's strong do you
go underwater like on the ground
basically yeah yeah oh I guess my common
S 5 Seconds my common says has prevented
me from greatness it
seems but now you can aeve achieve
greatness yeah but I'm always low in
stamina guess I can't do it
then wait just get more stamina where
going oh I oh okay it's this way I was
waiting for
crony oh I'm I'm ahead of you it's
okay we're going this way are we going
that way okay yes we I'm just going to
where Kiara is oh I'm towards the house
but I'm taking weird paths I
think oh okay and Mining a little bit in
the in
between I'm not getting what I want in
here
that's
h no
that's where's the iron I can't find
iron oh I
have uh I am
bringing 1,300
13 what 1300 not
13,000 still that's a
lot yeah that's a lot that looks like
iron oh you call it iron too I'm so
happy you do what what wait who who
what who did you say that you call iron
do you wait you call it
iron yeah you call it
iron yeah but your first language is
English
oh you're getting
owned no I love it though I was trying
to relate to
you are you kidding me right
now I thought that wasn't normal I
thought
only people like me would say it
wrongish iron iron iron iron
iron
iron IR oh I feel so seen I kind of
like it's like the character from Avatar
iroll Uncle iroll you don't call iron I
literally can't find my house most of
the
time look for the trees look for the
trees no but like get rid of them I'm
sick of them they concealed it's like
it's just like Twilight but I should
still be finding my
house it's not normal vampires live in
this house yeah vampires live in this
house the Clementine
family I thought they were called the
cins that's we can't yeah it's a reboot
we can't take it for copyright reasons
it's a spinoff
okay okay I put Aon in the iron in the
for uh check the book chest where are
they going electric and fooding oh thank
you I love reading we made it
yay
[Music]
yay eat do eat
doas
what I can make a robotic
Sledge oh I don't know what that is wait
Raider Sledge like a the trees are going
into the house hey chill fauna fauna
likes it what are you wearing on your
top
oh what what is it
called what are you wearing right
now
Commando oh I think I have something of
interest for a set
bonus oh Raider top
perhaps for your Raider hat although you
are wearing a nerd hat
nowon uh I think it does oh this the
more you wear wait this is a good outfit
yeah
thank you I found it somewhere
SC my
hat you look
hardcore this is WTF what the FAA oh
what the
fauna I was thinking of something else
but I guess that's what it's supposed to
mean in reality
yeah and I got some Rog boots l i
l but I I'll put some Rogue boots into
the uh armor chest whoever wants this
wants it can take it thank
you thank
you oh I have fist stuff on here
for I'm sorry I don't know what came
over me ex I don't mean to hit my wife
so often what what was that you're a
wife Feer E I can't help
it can't help
don't cry my
sweet don't let them know you have to
change can't keep going on I I stopped
drinking is that not enough isn't the
gambling
then it is the gambling I dream of it
yeah take
this oh thank you I think you might like
it do I put this on my weapon yeah
Oo we have like electrical parts and
mechanical parts that kind of stuff
somewhere somewhere I think we should in
the uh the miscellaneous
crates we have a lot of parts parts in
these two chests uh might be able to
find it there oh yeah there's robotic
Parts in these wood stor these unlabeled
wooden storage crates right here next to
fa there's some in there nice thank
thank you
oo
okay I got so much stuff oh my God
careful it's very cramped as you may
have
noticed yeah it's
careful is there any leather
oh I have 12 how much do you need I
need um I need 12 oh okay here's 12 oh
thank
you okay
um
seeds H oh I'm hungry
are
you yeah oh tummy rumbles oo I have a
banana bread I love banana bread they
have banana bread no sry pumpin bread I
was disappointed pumpkin bread is nice
too I like banana bread
better it's behind you on the floor I
just put it on the floor thank you I'm
going to eat it
[Music]
it's not it was nice and moist thank you
I almost punched you in your face were
you scared did I frighten you a little
bit what's wrong maybe I'll do it anyway
ah just because I'm wearing glasses the
way you don't like it it wasn't your
glasses it was what was it it was your
the the the worm under your nose oh is
little hairy worm come closer and get a
better look son a worm I'm doing some
renovation you're scared of me I see I
have good reason to be
scared don't be scared wait you look
like Eggman from from Sonic oh thank you
that's a compliment
better I want to move this too
ideally oh that looks pretty it's pretty
was in the
way okay I five for steel I'm burning
again there's some oh forch
steel why do you love burning yourself
man
I do you need for steel I have some I
have 15 yeah I need oh nice I just need
four okay and then I can make my item
thingy that I've been wanting I'm at the
forge Workshop thingy H here you
go I dropped thank you so
much okay the windows are patched up
which is
good nice nice oh you're fixing our
Windows oh yeah the exterior oh giggy
she's the F yes do you have something a
mod on your head
item um
um no do you want
this where did it go oh thank you my
sunglasses are just going to have light
shining out of it I don't think it would
be
visually visible but uh damn I wish it
was that would be
amazing okay we only have like 30
minutes left until Cali kicks us off so
maybe questing
soon oh I can make dynamite now
oo yeah I'm done to do Quest I'm ready
yeah I'm
ready where should I there's a chicken
give me your
eggs oh does anyone have food I have
aren't you the
sh aren't you the one that cooks there's
bacon and eggs in the out
Cooks I guess I guess I'll just use a
little bit of meat without the egg just
cook the meat yeah oh I have three eggs
wait oh okay here I put it thank you
Eggman does anyone happen to have Aon a
bon a Buton I bon
bon um yeah there's some in the weapons
chest nice thank
you
[Music]
um
uh what was I going to
do ow oh
no everyone on fire it's so crap we need
to renovate the house make it more
Spacey I think what we should do is we
should have a third house near the next
Trader because we're we're on like the
third Trader now or some of us are so
we're all going to be over there later
so maybe we should have a house
there so I will make the house more
spacious breaking some blocks I'm
renovating oh no are you on fire because
it's so cred wall right there here we go
I got rid of the load bearing wall take
take these arrows please off of my hand
thank it's just a few oh so much more
spacious yeah it's getting somewhere why
is this trash can here in the middle
I'll get rid of the wall to the bathroom
too you don't need privacy you don't
need privacy we do not need privacy in
this household oh we don't need wash
yeah we're family no you can still use
it just in front of
us I love that agreed the wide open
Toilet
yeah Smash It smash
it yeah we smashing together giggy look
at this wow perfect I would love to see
someone use the toilet with the Cece's
box over it
be it's okay we're Idols we don't use
toilets yeah it was useless from the
start the sh
[Music]
sand we just have so many meetings oh
just there's a wild boar over here let's
kill it let's take his eggs kill it
maybe it's eggs oh I him in one punch
she's one punch girl punch
can you guys your party CR and
I oh I think I think I'm G to head out
so okay okay
okay take care good night night thanks
for fixing byebye
[Music]
byebye how much time do kids oh 20
minutes uh 2 four let's go make a quest
yes Quest quest Quest run run run run
run shall we go to the tier
two place oh yeah cilia needs an invite
though I think
yeah
bicycle bicycle
there I so quiet hello hello hello hello
hello
[Music]
hello we need eggs is there can you make
a chicken farm
I think we might be able to but I don't
know how got to do some
research uh okay I'll make my way to I
have a quest over there so I'll make my
way there to oh I see your quest okay
I'll head over there to all right can
you I haven't I haven't gotten the wait
who's the party
leader you
me is it you is it me k k I think I
don't think so I think it's is it me oh
it was me yeah it was me all along
chicken chicken be nice to
it oh uh
H I was very nice to it really thank did
you treat it to to some food did you
give it some
corn uh they like corn
oh they do can you put the chicken that
is with you on the phone so I can hear
it
[Laughter]
has a lot to
say oh it seems like the chicken is fine
yeah okay I'm relieved to hear
that I I let I let the chicken go on its
merry way it went across the road oh
that chicken crossed the road huh oop no
I'm glad I did I'm eating raw potatoes
what is going on here I can make meat
stew meat
stew
yummy mhm and vegetable
stew meat stew is probably better
right
uh I'm just it's funny to hear that from
you fauna yeah I
know between meat stew and vegetable
stew m
honestly like IRL though there's so many
times where I just prefer having
something without meat just because it's
just so filling and sometimes I just
want like a bowl full of vegetables yeah
yeah often when I get like a curry or so
I'll just order a vegetable curry
because they put so much meat in there I
don't even need that much meat oh some
days I just eat a bowl of boiled
broccoli and that's it bowl of broccoli
but it season I season it good so it's
tast
yeah is it grilled or cooked or
raw it's like steamed broccoli oh
steamed Steam and and then you put like
seasoning like sesame oil and like
peppers in it and stuff M okay hope I
don't get lost to you guys oh you have
someone on foot like a noob we can eat
the SN hey now I'm I'm alone now you
can't do
that it's do what you can't you can't
you can't say that hey can't call you a
noob oh because I'm T hanging up on
you level up I don't believe you would
do that where was my exp
de I don't think you have exp de what um
yeah you don't I don't there there is no
consequence to dying well then
awesome cool uh yeah I've been I've been
past level 65 for a while and I have not
gotten any exp de from dying so I don't
think it exists m
server anyway I am fine with
that where did the playing on easy mode
baby server baby baby serveron seven
days to
[Music]
die I can finally jump two blocks hi
this zombies on
fire wow he had a lot of loot what's
with him why is he carrying so much
stuff for what what are you
hiding wooo
snack snake are we ready to Quest I'm
ready but I don't think everybody's here
we are here I am wait you're there yeah
we're fall you're so far us no us two
are here yeah me you've been waiting
we've been waiting this entire time just
a little bit we weren't here that long I
I was at the house and I was like I I
kept I was like oh are we going and then
I looked at the map and suddenly I see
you
guys like
no you keep us waiting the Serv
Clos we're chilling okay we're
chilling we're just looking around yeah
I'm just killing
things all the things you do yeah you
know yeah just ending some people's
lives some zombes
suffering releasing them from their
suffering just some casual violence you
know as one does during a zombie
apocalypse yeah
relatable is it
cathartic yes that's nice I like the
sounds when my knif pierces their flesh
oh like the yeah I actually don't like
it Prett good it's
disgusting
yeah are you okay I was peacefully
hitting a tree and there's a
dog and a bunch of other
zombies we do be like that sometimes
where is this thing yes I'm
I'm pedaling as fast as I can oh
biker oh you're over there okay wait I
think this is a real life dog no live
it's getting killed by the
zombies friendly dog it's a friendly
dog oh you guys are here I'm I'm trying
to save the dog hop on the back don't
hurt the dog save the dog I'll save you
save the dog save the dog okay
oh oh cut okay okay don't hurt me don't
hurt me don't hurt me
please I have a bone do you want a
bone meat meat
meat need meat to eat but he's so
cute it hurts me too you know you while
you're cutting it apart me meat
belt
off oh man yeah he's going to Doggy
Heaven okay it's a nice place I'm in
heaven now I'm ready everybody here so
sorry I died I now don't worry so sorry
I died
begin let's let the chaos
begin oh gigy you're in already what are
you hitting why are you hitting that
log she's she's she's she's hung up
about the dog ow why why do you keep
stop running in front of me I'm hitting
log stop hitting us I'm hitting the
L is there a way up a it's the fireplace
again watch out for fire oh
god I think I'm just going to leech XP
off of you guys okay yeah
I'm wearing you're wearing a nerd hat
right yeah yeah okay good the good one
even I'm going to cheer you on go go woo
oh oh I'm bleeding oh God I'm going to
die the hammer is so fun don't die I
have one
bandage are you dead ow have a
bful wait that's not you where is be
I'm behind you I'll get the zombie
first where is okay hello ah I'm sorry
regular bandaid a delay fire is off
friend has been
found oh but be careful with the coal on
the ground doesn't that make you go on
fire too no
oh
zombies we like to this a really
confusing Place yeah this is the parkour
this is hardcour civilization this
hardore civilization yeah watch out for
the
be I'm
dying
fun I like when you turn them on fire no
that's not how you burn them on you and
my my sledgehammer has fire on it ooh
it's really cool that is very cool
that's I have
another wonder how that would probably
be a really
effective uh type of weapon in like
apocalyps burn them oh makes sense yeah
burn the stinky
corpses oh that must smell B actually
e e
f are you up there no no I'm
down
people I'm up here the door is
locked hold on I'll just smack the door
yeah Blue Force
wo I'd help but then yeah I'll get hit
probably I have a better oh the window
might be
easier there's no ledge at the window no
there's no death oh maybe that one
I have brought a bird maybe it coming a
bird oh I guess it's outside still I'm
contributing me too me
too what's HP
at
660 f i I have the
stone you stop hting people trying
not I try to get the perfect
angle bro BR 40 HP you owe me a
bandage once I find one I'll bandage you
up almost there almost there almost
there why is it so slow the bird that's
making the noise crazy yeah what uh oh
we can still we can still get
him yeah window
oh h oh help help I am powerful yeah
take your time takas take your
[Music]
time
falling bird W he went all the way
down no he got back up what who where
what wh's all the way down oh I can kill
him from here
sniper machine gun
sniper oh was that a lady in the
dress I think there was a man really I
saw a red clo thing it reminded me of
the beautiful
dress
water no it's empty was it murky I took
one water yeah it has murky water this
BR is a chill
where is the bird I don't know why is so
loud where should I
go there like a bunch of
stuff oh oh there you are
okay are you going are you
up where are they there's some there
there's one in the door in the door yeah
but it's locked too I
think I don't even know if I can make
the
jump on the roof sled I'm is it
faster
man oh no wait where did they go
damn it I will avenge you B boo thank
you what happened were you
overwhelmed I I was at like 5
HP oh there's a bird he already opened
it up was a really loud Bird Okay the
bird is dead oh thank
God been screaming this entire
time oh
what who is that right behind that
monster how did you make it how did you
make it
there I went down the elevator I believe
genius where's still not finished yeah
where's the last
monster been here
forever one might have fallen all the
way down yeah I'm not sure the music
stopped they were like oh you girls are
taking too long
we didn't pay for such a long music
track I hear it I I hear something yeah
I can't tell where it is
though I hear
a
hello sounds like
crying I found it
oh you're
downstairs all right we did it did it
finish
[Applause]
yay okay uh if we have one more nearby
already we could go otherwise does
anybody have no mine's kind of far let's
see H we could go to T Jen and see if we
can accept the quest that's close by um
mine's kind of close to her but not
really I think it's over the mountain we
could go straight there finish it off
shall we go to gig's Quest okay and then
to Trader and then
ended okay oh wait bicycle
do
bicycle oh I'm so hungry though I'm so
thirsty especially
hungry oh
sham sandwich I have some raw steaks and
a sham
sandwich that's at least something you
you can't get sick eating raw meat right
m not an
apocalypse maybe I'll eat the raw egg
tartar steak tartar M with a little raw
egg on top of
[Music]
it well I hope we make it like after
this gey Quest I hope we make it in time
for the traiter before she closes closes
yeah hopefully we're going to have to
speedrun RTA style
yeah are we going the right way yes I
feel like it might take that long just
to drive there
yeah should I drink the Yuka
Juice drink it
once I yeah drink it yeah after the
bicycle
right almost almost there what is it is
a fetch Quest G Fetch and clear I think
I'm not going to make it in time because
I'm running I'm going to go to the I'm
going to go to the train okay okay keep
her open keep her
occupied I I'll try stalling as much as
I can tell her not to close or else an
angry mob is going to show up we take a
can we take a quick want some water yeah
okay I
also me too if only we had more
hats I know wait actually I don't know
where your Trader is yet so Traer do you
see
like yeah go straight go straight
basically I know in which what direction
you're looking at it's the Green Field I
guess you don't see the map yet but if
you go straight over the mountain thank
you try to keep on going
south okay okay okay South
okay and it's like a I'll talk to her we
the people that come into the store 2
minutes before closing and then we like
take a long time no but she'll kick us
out are you looking do you think you
have a size in the
back sorry oh you know the people who
come in at like 9 9:00 p.m. be like do
you have the size in the
back oh
theore the oh do you have this in a
different size oh yeah it's always it's
always I I worked in retail a lot and
then it was always like please look
chick in the back and then you just go
into the back and come back and you're
like there's no we don't have that does
anyone have antibiotics or honey no no
no uh but Trader Trader dad J Jo George
Sells it it's fine does anyone have any
emergency food no I have Rock meat oh
yeah raw meat or raws maybe I'll eat
this raw corn meal
H don't CH hello Trader
Jen I met her I met her she's a here is
your cute is she a doctor why does she
have I'm wearing it really quickly oh
okay take this
G ooh the art of mining
or your
iron
my uh yeah she Hasam maybe I don't know
in four minutes we should I mean it's
not that exact I would
think
but minutes 4 minutes and and plus like
5 Seconds it'll be okay
right yeah yeah yeah she's not that
strict a little grinding off stream just
a little just a tiny
bit it's fine it'll be fine she'll
forgive
us okay uh we can begin I'm
here
okay okay what is this
person
okay I met the Traer I'm happy um I'm
going to go see you guys
tomorrow you good night
byebye byebye or good
[Music]
morning
true why are we doing this to a
graveyard oh no I sprained my knee again
you sprained it not
meee what this
guy I'm leaving no back into the grave
of you you dead oh
god oh now my knee is
FL oh no are we looking for he's getting
back up he's getting back up
stel yeah I think we're looking for the
satels dead now no he's dead okay now
he's
dead I already looked in that casket
there's nothing in there I thought this
was a barbecue grill like who's grilling
out of a grave yard oh right in here
maybe oh yeah oh oh there's a whole
dungeon down here
probably be careful found mine oh yeah I
found a lot of scary things down here
W watch out for the spikes there are
spikes spikes oh there okay
wow this is co wol this is different
mhm maybe we got to get rid of these
things here and there to see what we
need
no
oh I'm
starving
that oh watch out behind
you what was that
oh I found mine it seems good maybe it's
the same for someone else I don't know
watch out watch out oh he's glowing oh
he's green so easy to see
ouch oh
scary oh oh oh ah that's
me you you're both green different green
get out of my
swamp it's her
swamp get out of her swamp
swamp I have 30
HP oh there's a oh there's like a hidden
thing over here oh a car Satchel who's
oh
nice a book crate I love
books
books there's honey here you still need
honey oh I need honey me
too you can yeah you can eat it oh
Dan I'll buy mine from
Jane Senai Tex is strong as
ever it works it just
works books have been we spanning four
generations here oh we are
a good mix M uh has everybody with the
graveyard who's missing their
Satchel or do we all have it I have mine
I have mine I have mine okay done we're
done zo run where is
Exit please don't close
please where is the exit it's here is
here R don't close
was it 900 p.m. then she when she
closes I think 950 yes 9 okay we'll be
fine
maybe how do you get there
though there's a there's a windy path
there's a windy path behind the house if
you see the map I see it I'll follow for
now yeah she closed early on us last
time like 10 minutes
but I think we're
fine
9:45 we're fine fine we're to minutes
over we're going to get banned oh no
we're going to get reported don't report
us
[Music]
please
come I'm stuck me
too I looked away for a
moment are we going up a mountain is
that the right way I yeah go up the
mountain and then slide down the cliff
you won't take fall damage if you just
slide down whoa I changed the controls
or something something's
weird oh I don't like it there's birds
up here I really want to check the nest
but I'm
not I see
it I'm going to slide down with my oh my
gosh it's a little steep
ah thank you Mouse
button is it really okay it's so
steep wait did you go left
or I think I went right I'm going to
slide down on my
butt maybe oh yeah this this little work
especially now with my parkour skill I I
already have this
do I
yes run run
run another successful day in seven days
to
die
yeah slowly I walk into the
church oh hi oh that's a lot of ammo it
in one place but if you that I don't use
maybe
this maybe oh tier three stuff now yeah
I still don't have
it oh there's a night only
[Music]
Quest asking
again yeah still no sugar
butts whose Sugar Butt are you talking
about could be anyone's could be yours
that could be a nickname hey Sugar Butt
what's up hey sugar take a at my she
gave me mats to craft a mini bike
o
shotgun oh there's battle up
magazines but I don't
should I should I buy this for Cali Cali
wanted uh batter up right yeah she was
she's BL weapon baseball bat yes yes
yes uh with the volume does it matter
like if she already read volume three
can she read it again I don't know what
volume she's on I think can't read it
again ah cuz it's a book I'll keep it in
there maybe she read it
already oh okay farewell I am so hungry
me
too goodbye see you
tomorrow
bye sleep for business stay safe out
there going to eat this St Quest failed
oh that always shocks me I know
right sell it sell what hey there cutie
pie need a little healing
[Music]
touch I'm getting so
the one boxer
now oh I got you still have that per for
drunken fist we need to get you lots of
beer I don't does it do anything does it
help me I don't know we got to find out
books books books books books wait come
outside in case she closes okay I'm
afraid the stuff is going to get and
we'll forever separated I have armor for
you armor sorry for you a here's book
for you as well so sweet such sweet
exchanges who here uses
shotgun uh Callie does okay I'll keep it
for now I forgot to sell
the woman let me sell my money for more
money you have 20
seconds
easy than
feel Callie watching did you just call
her JMA
yeah jenma I imagine her to be jenma in
a different timeline in a different
Universe yeah oh W oh that scares me
every time
purch well I'll think about that skill
point next time all right I'll I'll I
guess I'll end it here me too
by a good had a good time by bye bye
[Music]
bye oh
mhm this time I'm not like the last one
standing until much
later I ended
properly yeah that was another 4 hours
of 7 Days to Die 6: a.m. yippe yippe I
guessing next one is probably next time
uh the same time again probably um but
you know what I'll
do I'll read a little bit of super
chats uh an extra seat schematic oh not
so important oh hello wa hi wa how you
doing wa thanks I'm doing good wa how
are you doing wait maybe I can talk to
myself differently
wait hi
will
wait
uh hi wa you're a little bit taller than
me how come I thought we're the same H
oh this is
confusing do you want to kiss
yeah but I'm a bit shy oh me too oh you
too no need to be shy about it right
maybe we can start with like a nose
kiss come here come
here you guys know nose kisses they're
really sweet now do should we do like a
butterfly kiss you know how to do it wa
yes I know how to do do you know how to
yeah of course I know how to do it h
okay you just blink really fast on
someone else's skin
a tickles a
tickles okay after all these weird
kisses are you ready for the real kiss
do you feel more ready for it now a yes
I do thank you for considering my
feelings okay here I
go oh my God my first kiss
with
myself I could practice kissing with
myself no what am I doing I want to die
oh well W you can't you're Phoenix oh
right I
forgot how romantic it's romantic isn't
it almost as romantic
as our kiss that we shared true
true it's 6 a.m. yeah so
what I'm going to read some super chats
we're both going to read some super
chats maybe we'll read it faster when we
combine our powers what do you think wa
could work could work
indeed one can only
try Oh wrong direction here
okay little bit of
distance let's play some music I'll just
stay in this black
void today's hoorde was quite exciting
wasn't it I was a bit scared that they
would break through the only reason they
came through there at the end was
because I had a hard time getting back
in without letting the zombies in as
well and then I died but is there really
no XP depth
I wonder how you can tell cuz I didn't
pay attention if I lost any XP or so but
then I did some Quest and I immediately
leveled up so or I killed a monster and
immediately leveled
up I've been loving everyone interacting
in this me too me
too yeah we have like a little bit of a
level Gap now it seems with some girls
maybe we
can uh
catch up or they can catch up hopefully
but they don't have to in the end it
scales like with the quests too as far
as I know the EXP they get scales and
the difficulty of the hordes everything
scales
although that hord was pretty difficult
so I
think uh it cares more about the US like
there's more high level players than
lowlevel
maybe yeah but CC got a a pretty decent
machine gun I uh like right off the bat
today I had to work with a shitty
machine gun for days now so having that
good one right off the bat must I think
I think that was uh helpful very
helpful and now I got my level four
machine
gun but now I have to share ammo it's
going to be
rough well as long as I am still around
these girls you know where the ammo is
going toward
we got to learn how to make I think oh
no bio has bio been making ammo I've
seen uh ammo in the output here and
there sometimes yeah we we'll need a lot
more ammo I didn't have that much this
time because I gave like a half of it or
a third of it to
CC um and then I when I ran out or when
I was about to run out I became a lot
more careful with what I'm shooting the
hammer is really fun but I feel like I
die so fast I don't know what to do I
want to go in there with the horde more
but I die fast and then it's hard to get
back into
safety it takes so much stamina to
swing need more perks for into the
hammer watch's your stamina yeah I need
more stamina I need to put all my skill
points into stamina
honestly what's how do I put what what
was stamina how do I get more stamina
what skill is it hey shut up why are you
doing these noises
microphone fixed it
audio St let's get audio stock
going do we have anything interesting
among these unnamed audio stock
files I like this
one I like this one
too like this one
too
jungle well you barely hear it do you I
like this one too
a this one's cute
[Music]
too isn't this one nice it's
cute have you guys heard the uh the Mage
remixes people have been putting out
remixes I retweeted like two of them
today somebody said you have a grip you
can use to make your Hammer let take I
do oh oh I think I know what you're
talking about I think I
[Music]
remember I'll check my inventory it's so
confusing everything's so messy and I
can't there's no there is no search menu
right in the chest I wish there was I
wish there
was you have to level up you have to
level up the Mee weapon perk that you
want to
use to reduce the amount of ah uhhuh
which one was the was there a
sledgehammer M weapon
perk was there which one have I put
anything in there skull crusher okay let
me put that in my
list skull crusher so no particular
stamina perk I should put it into I
should just put it into skull
crusher W kiss we already kissed we can
do it again I can do it
[Music]
again want to do it again
yeah nice good
[Music]
kiss can't look at her she's so
pretty
help okay okay okay uh
[Music]
if we were to read a little bit of super
chats now which ones were would I be
reading does anybody
know ah
G just mention to Luigi this the last
Luigi Luigi just mention to Luigi luig
was it the last L
stream this this is the one found it uh
this one has a good amount of super
chats let's tackle them shall
[Music]
we by the way I still have a video that
I should put up for members but I keep
on
forgetting the there's not really like
much uh in it it's not that much but
it's a little bit of an outtake uh video
but really it's not that much there it
wasn't much much recorded
seems so yeah okay let's let's quickly
read this one I'll finish
[Music]
it K thank you cute yeah had so much fun
performing chiku Midnight Rider dun CNG
y dun R free
d
r t than for the pinky let's go W back
my birthday best gift ever I hope you
had fun in Italy with Nissa we did we
did thank you so much happy belated
birthday from the both of
us
wa am I a twin or am I just a clone what
am
i h you know what red super chats get
kisses right but what if I don't kiss
you but I kiss myself instead justce
once
mirror it's a mirage it's a mirage
stream
Mirage anyway anyway happy beled
birthday Tassimo thank you so much for
your support sorry to keep you waiting
but I hope you had a lovely
[Music]
birthday I hope that this following year
for you will be an amazing one and
[Music]
D Midnight Rider d
Sky should I put
[Music]
oh
sky pbn
thanks for the finally I and celebrate
this even if I can't come see you often
because of hard working I'll always
support you oh thank you so much I
appreciate it yeah I don't see you that
much anymore but as long as you're still
around I'm very
happy are you ready for a
kiss too bad you're not getting one this
time just
me hello
[Music]
smie has arrived she's like hello
where's my breakfast I'm confused
because now I'm getting dinner for
breakfast and breakfast for dinner this
is very confusing but I guess it
balances and cancels out I'm I'm hearing
this too by the way it's not just you
guys the voices in my hand no it's the
voices next to
me red d d d for the p
somehow without YouTube unsubscribing
problems for the P shut up I can't I
don't it's hard to think without problem
I'm now what are you saying I'm not sure
what you're saying what is she
saying
wow uh yeah double I don't know maybe it
was really a double
um I'm guessing you mean that YouTube
didn't unsubscribe oh yeah right this
was when I was testing you guys you
weren't able to uh write in the chat
right yeah yeah
yeah so
uh uh uh uh uh uh I said it first I said
I
[Music]
said I hate her her I hate I hate you I
hate you more I shut stoping without
shut up my God
this maybe we should should
juste yeah
[Music]
we're fine we're
fine why the [\h__\h] are you
subscribed why are you not subscribed
what do you mean of course you subscribe
you can't be a member and not subscribe
right oh
[Music]
gamer cre d
l char
[Laughter]
[Music]
girl make the
red we missed the anniversary of me
finding you during your can you be quiet
just I need to read this and understand
what they're
[Music]
saying be a little bit
quiet we missed the anniversary of me
finding you during your first K with
your first microng I missed you my first
YouTuber I love you boss September 15
2020 thank you for 4
years thank you girl for this lovely
speci special message you get a special
kid
or we get
speci so you can watch
[Music]
watch thank
you for supporting me so
long it's been a long time that's a
special stream to find me right my first
that was I was very nervous nous and
everything was so sced sced right but
you chose me and I chose
you why is there two because you're not
streaming Mirage often enough so you
cannot tell apart a mirage and dismantle
it properly this is what happens you
need to stream Mirage my new song e on
Spotify Apple music
whatsoever or on YouTube the music
video yeah it's as easy as that you've
been
slacking
roll happy
birthday even I'm late I'm sorry chunky
chunks thanks for I'm still young for
years 11 days by now
maybe maybe already 4
years chunky chunk chunk but you get a I
get a
kiss Thank you la no thank you thank
you shut
up thank you so much CH hope you will
continue to support me and her
Bob
James
window
un this seems to work like I feel like
I'm breing this faster than
usual feel like it's working Studio Ro
pinky
it I very much enjoyed the ton reflect
on the fourth anniversary it was was the
of the death versus the Phoenix lore I
was so happy so dramatic thank you I'm
glad we were able to perform that I
don't even
know if there was another option or if
we were just assigned that I think we
were just assigned like he was suggested
and I was like yeah this sounds like a
good
idea maybe next time I'll perform it
with myself
now that I'm two people I can do that
with
[Music]
you you duplicated the you have made my
last how's that
work how does that work how many times
did you duplicate
it he moving I wish I could duplicate
her baby
[Music]
g d k space waterful thanks for Pinky I
waso before debut I always said I was
your fan since Twitter days thank you
wow you you found your path to
Enlightenment so early but only got my
membership on my kfp account 2 years
after because I couldn't afford it
earlier
in this economy I get it I remember the
early days you were so cute and it was
so chaotic
maning yeah the early days I don't I
wish I wish I could have done things
better and more successful from the getg
go but we learn and now I'm here doing
things more smoothly like
smoothy oh she's taking a sit
not [\h__\h] just a Sit she's sitting down
on the bed on the spot that chunky wony
likes
actually why are you stealing her
spot it's actually just my moap shirt
that I threw onto the
bed and so now they like to just sit on
the
shirt
specifically it doesn't even really
smell like anything I think like it's
not sweaty right
now yeah she's loafing she is indeed
loafing oh a
coincidence yeah I've been doing some Mo
so it's really messy in this uh actually
the bed is messy I just threw everything
on the
bed anyway thank you so much space
waterfall moving on y d pathetic
engineer d
roond if I speak faster
maybe maybe she can't keep up you think
she can keep up
[Music]
it hurts my
brain it hurts me
[Music]
can you guys even hear what name I'm
saying wait you yeah yeah you yeah
you yeah you can't kind of
barely loud and clear
okay yeah it's getting
mushy we're done soon don't worry let's
get through this we can't just end it
half yes I'm committed are you committed
M oh I'm committed I'm committed to
you me
too where
was UN Rick
Rick
golden n diesel d
[Music]
how does she know when I speed up and
when I speed
down she can read my
[Music]
mind chocolate d red d
s
o s a
o I have one brain
[Music]
c g what's
up thank you
you're worth it what a deal it's so
funny your Super Chat makes even more
sense now you got two cases for one red
super chat from two
Bas what a
[Music]
de as if you knew
it you planed it ahead you knew this was
coming maybe you're the one who created
my clone which is you no you no you're
the Clone no you're the Clone
[Music]
no I
hate TV t
waterful D Yoshi putting d game 8910
D almost
there almost
there which one you like left more what
the
[\h__\h] what about
[Music]
me he for
Pinky thank you for appearing in my live
during one of the worst times I had a
store classified as an essential
business during that period and people
weren't nice to me oh I wonder what you
literally help me keep my sanity well
[\h__\h] them [\h__\h]
them
and just ignore their [\h__\h] if you
can I'm here for you w are here for you
we are right M we're here for you
please
anytime come to
us
[Music]
mare naan thanks for the
pink can we artificially fill your
sanity meter to
tal I think I'm Al
I mean look at us there is no
sanity to be filled up
up there's nothing there do you any
there's not no not even a fragment of
sanity left here in this
void all you can do is stream Mirage to
help me help me
[Music]
please otherwise I won't get rid of her
ever I'm going
[Applause]
[Music]
insane luig
clone pink we love you boss and we love
you dog Hood we
we what a
coincidence 0193 thanks for the pinky
here's a Super Chat to heal your sanity
K how
F all of us kfp are on your side we
share with you smk tkj is already ready
to clip
this hi there
[Music]
are you recording you're so welcome to
C I noticed
[Music]
you I don't know I don't know there's
nothing interesting going on here please
move move along move
along it's all normal it's normal
nothing weird in kfp ever
all of us are on your side we share you
with you the pain that you feel that we
feel right everyone of us support you
with everything we can you're strong
girl you know it we know it you can do
itential maybe this is a late after
effect from Luigi's
Mansion
Insanity no no it's from Mirage
not being streamed often enough help
me but thank you mobus my sanity will be
healed soon I feel it it's getting
better it's getting
better take Luigi
clone Luigi got Clon
too maybe if I find a solution and get
rid of my clone I can teach Luigi
how to get rid of his clone ghost with
weapons taunt when you discover them
with dark light giving you a free flash
I'm sure hope you read this on
time I don't know if I ever used that I
possibly didn't read it on
[Music]
time m to late but
thanks I appreciate it thanks for
trying TI 72
Swan blood
CL wonderful
and simply
than I feel as
[Music]
if my
sanity is just for
[Music]
now becoming
better I can tell the difference now I
can tell the difference this is a good
start
[Music]
didn't get worse
no no no no right
right I should probably
[Music]
sleep we should
sleep in German we say
Al see
[Music]
n