[Music]
um
yes
what is your what is your goal for today
or your
motivational speech
trust no one and survive
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
hey
a number one detective today i will
perform
my duty as a law abiding
justice seeking detective hi
uh are you guys
hey
[Music]
is
hello my name is
i will do my best not to load
[Music]
today
hello
[Music]
hello everyone my name is
and i'm going to kill lots of people
today yay
yes i kill you i'll kill you
why did they hear me what do you mean
you can't hear me
[Music]
yes i know i'm still in standby guys
because you can't see the code
go go in a second oh yeah code new code
please
go to the hotel
[Music]
can everyone put on the image from the
rules
[Music]
yes
that's why we're ending it in this uh
quick explanation
we try the first round
okay maybe
okay
no no okay
oh
oh my god
foreign
[Music]
why can't i see discord
okay we are playing the first game only
with eight people
so let's just go okay
because uh has some problems
no problem just make sure everybody's
code is
hidden nobody okay
all good
[Music]
um
they're gone it's just you guys and me
now
um huh
i mean it would be cool um it would be
cool if i could figure out how to
show discord on the screen but i don't
know
oh well anyway i'm not looking at chad
anymore um
[Music]
because you guys will tell me who it is
uh so
so we're not gonna do that i don't know
how to play this game
oh what's this
can i do something fun here oh cool
oh it's a game here let's play the game
all right sick
ah what can we do here use it
oh wow that was it it was that easy
i mean i'll take it but
ah i knew it oh i saw that coming
oh man uh senpai wait come back that's
my body senpai
except my health
let's go listen to what they're saying
of course of course
[Laughter]
what are they saying who do
[Music]
i was just running around figuring out
the audio i need some water
i'm gonna go get some water issues for
some reason
from one ear but okay anyway i am not
suspicious
[Music]
oh by the way sorry guys it's been a bit
of a long day if i sound tired excuse me
i'm moving so there's a lot going on but
we'll still have fun have fun
i'm calming down so it's cool
[Music]
well let's do some tasks i guess
let's see you're dead finish your tasks
to win well what can we do i wonder
let's see i want to help yay here
download five days come on man
it's like old pc kuna wait a minute
we're playing an old pc
[\h__\h] lol smiley face this is what i get
just have fun thanks i will i'm having a
good time just a little tired that's all
let's see what else can we do to help i
can move so fast i can move through
everything look at me go
i'm going to be speeding around howdy
oh oh oh this time oh no
senpai hello hello hello hello hello
hello lambie
what a shame
i was in storage with ina and botan
but lamy was with polka myself okay
i saw botan i think i was around botan
and
electrical and then she left while i was
doing the
thing the
[Music]
oh
i'm
[Music]
you always suspect
foreign
okay sorry guys i just realized that my
stream was set to normal latency
i don't understand why that is because
um i have it auto set to
ultra low latency so alrighty
it's fun
oh they need my help hang on
okay senpai's got it okay there's
something here
i love how the ghosts are the ones that
are on all the tasks hang on
yes insert the card uh here
here it is okay i gotta swipe it there
we go
i did it i did i was useful
how do we hang on
i'm here to help all right let's see
what's going on here
i think i think the thing at the top
isn't there like a percentage
is
oh
[Music]
people
yes
okay
[Music]
uh i will figure out the discord thing
uh soon
yes it's not showing up for you guys huh
it's cool
uh we'll figure it out um once i get
killed which i will
i will die um all right matt hold on you
know looking sus over here why are you
following me
watson watson
you know
let's see what's going on here
okay what have you got here hold on
i don't like how many people there are
around me here let's see
ah sick that was easy i don't like oh
i don't like when people get close to me
what are you doing here you know
let's take a look look at the cameras
what's going on here it was looking
suspicious
ina looking real sus to me
no how could you
try i can still look at the cameras
let's get out of here
i should probably help um i'll figure
out the discord thing when everyone's
chatting but uh for now let me see what
i can do
to help out
here we go what does this do oh that's
easy
some of the tasks seems very very easy
to do hope someone finds my body soon
okay where's your next
iso huh what is this
how do you gather the leaves and like
throw them into it hang on
hang on get them in there get them in
get them all in
test complete it
you and me what the heck
uh both both on senpai
oh my god look at this
report the body enough report the body
oh here we go
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
ah
i should be able to add it now i think i
know
i was doing the last emergency test yeah
and i saw i was on
i saw a minute wait you know did you say
you were doing oxygen task
no i was i just got to it when the body
was reported
because i saw a minute
oh i add a browser source
[Music]
just the moment everyone
i'm a little worried i don't know if
something's gonna um oh
shoot i'm supposed to mute i'm muted
okay we're fine
uh hold on let me just keep playing the
game for now
no we can't do anything about that huh
only the normal tasks
let's see let's look at the map ah okay
ah am i supposed to
ah i mean that's
that's fine too i guess i saw i saw it
no it was fun
[Music]
[Laughter]
guys
okay i feel much better now
oh
foreign
[Music]
wait there's wait there's an echo
what huh
god i hate the i hate the um the normal
latency thing
i hate it so much probably makes the
viewing experience um a bit different as
well
with us being rather behind
let's see what's going on here okay
again with this in the storage okay
that's fine
we can do that
let's see is this not wait where the
heck am i
oh tab opens the map it doesn't
okay hold on okay okay okay i see where
we are
i see where we are
do your tasks what the heck
hi oh man this is nuts
oh
[Music]
um
wait i saw i saw
polka with ina the last time i saw
[Music]
no just know
[Laughter]
i don't know
huh
[Applause]
oh
good detective
foreign
why is there still people joining that
don't belong in here
why do people find it
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
all right let's see what happens we're
gonna go now
bye bye
ah crewmates again really looking
forward to being a killer at some point
see
uh hold on i kinda wanna this is like in
the way
put it there okay that was bothering me
all right what can we do no come on
please
i'm watching all of you it's one of you
two isn't it
all right let's see what we can do hold
on let me look at the hang on i'm
looking at the
let me let me actually look at the tasks
because that's something that i always
forget to do look at the tasks
all right swipe card fixed wiring uh
start the reactor
okay um
well the wire
all right hold on
hang on let me look at the map
huh
hey hey
hold on let me get out in the open real
quick all right we're in the cafeteria
let's see okay so here are the things
that we have to do they're marked on the
map okay i see them
we're learning how to play the game uh
and we've played two rounds okay so here
we go we'll go down
and go down
what was it in storage that we had to
fix hold on
show me okay nothing is in storage to
fix okay well there's a shh
stuff up here hang on
oh there's a lot of stuff to do
i guess if i was a killer i'd probably
come up behind someone uh that was
fixing this right here huh
that seems like the smart thing to do
right
huh
on
what
what what the heck yeah
i can't [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] this what
hold on nope something something else
let's do something else i'll figure that
out later
[Music]
can't look at the chat for tips because
someone's going to tell me who it is so
senpai senpai there's a dead body there
someone's dead i'm probably next
but i gotta fix this i gotta fix this ah
okay i thought i was dead for sure
foreign
[Music]
oh
um
oxygen otherwise the game just ends
up
[Music]
bye oh
interesting um it didn't say though if
senpai was an imposter or not oh
hold on hold on we gotta do some things
nope can't go this way really don't know
the layout of my own ship
nice going all right
[Music]
all right gouda i hope that you're doing
tasks hold on
um senpai's gabra
i really don't feel good guys
okay watson
watson are you waiting in the shadows
watson watson suss
listen
watson hella sus one's waiting for me
i'm telling you that watson is waiting
for me
i'm gonna regret this i'm gonna regret
this
okay we're fine i gotta take care of
this other stuff oh man we're in trouble
let's go let's go let's go i don't wanna
die
okay senpai's there
all right oh god i bet it's focused
senpai
oh man oh go go go go go
it was good
oh
[Music]
got it
bye
foreign
[Laughter]
yes
it says math maker is full
do you try the new code
[Music]
okay
foreign
um
suspecting that uh some might not
understand
how the oxygen thing works uh there's
like two spots where you have to
uh correct it or fix it
you you girls all understand does
everybody know how to bring up their map
yes yes okay
we also know uh-huh yes how the oxygen
works
no no
[Laughter]
it's like tasks right they are marked as
yellow
yes yes i know about those i don't know
how to do those emergencies when it goes
like thumb
yeah yeah yeah then then you should
ignore the tasks and go straight for the
red
yeah i do those they're also okay but
there's like two
there's two okay and it seems like like
uh they think that maybe we don't uh
understand
how the oxygen thing works oh i mean i
don't i think i think i get it i mean
i i do it
at the reactor where you have to do it
with two people
oh no yeah you have to wait for someone
to come i guess
if you are
[Music]
foreign
so
five
ah cremate again that's cool
we'll get him we'll get him
we'll do exactly what we're supposed to
do
hold on hold on let me see if i can bait
senpai up
i'm not suspicious watson
uh oh okay hold on can't go that way
okay here we go here we go
run quick oh someone else got him
okey-dokey oh wow you guys are quick
all right well let's see what we can do
next hold on
i'm kind of trying to bait people right
into seeing me alone
and then they'll be like hmm kelly's
alone
all right hold on let's see what we got
here so we have some
like oh
i saw that coming i saw it coming oh hey
hey let me step by
hey at least we can do some tests right
hang on i can't help them
it's cool simple i got this leave the
wiring to me i'm real quick
leave the card swiping to me
yeah i gotta i gotta admit i'm pretty
handy on the
on the card swipe oh no hold on hold on
that's not it this one
here we go my spirit lives on and is
helping you all
it's kind of nice whoa can i go into
space sick
i guess that's about as far as i can go
that's fun
oh man let's see
what do we got here okay oh
there we go someone found my dead body
once again
always first to die hey you know the
drill
electric room
[Music]
and
i think lemmy is somewhere else
[Music]
with me i was with nelly for a very long
time
i was in
huh i'm storage i'm good at getting
killed
it's kind of ironic i like it
pretty good getting killed in games
[Music]
yes
well let's go do what we can um
oh hold on check the map okay cool
i can go through walls it's very helpful
okay um some of these tasks i like what
i didn't even do anything
all right i like the wider ones they're
very easy
cool i got on here
oh we know that poco senpai is one for
sure
huh what's up what
haunting your corpse senpai
what can i like do something with this
here oh communications communicate with
the
calm sabotaged oh no everyone's
gathering
everyone's like what
oh man sabotaged
download data i can't it's been
sabotaged you guys got to do something
about it
you can't do that one yeah i thought so
well let's see what else is popping off
yeah we can't do the communications oh
here we go wait
i don't think i wonder i don't think
that we can we can't do the emergency
ones
oh here's the oxygen right this the one
that we apparently can't figure out
what
i was standing over the body and uh
polka was just standing there so she
didn't
oh [\h__\h]