foreign
[Music]
ready to rumble
hello
[Music]
it's pretty wild
um
I think I'm on wait let me tell me um
some of us introduce themselves and the
audience yeah
ABC
yeah okay okay what who goes first in
the alphabet Oh me hello everybody
um Amelia Watson hello live and number
one detective At Your Service uh uh
yeah
you don't use that so often do you yeah
I thought is that a new thing I liked it
I thought it was new yeah I thought you
had it into the um
[Music]
from Whole Life English what's up
all that good hi nice to see you
guys welcome yeah I am recovering I was
I was a bit uh under the berry under the
weather yesterday I'm doing a bit better
today though and very excited to play
with you ladies yay anticipating
[Music]
I draw with a mouse
but you could live your mouse drawing so
I don't know
it actually dropped worse with a tablet
believe it or not I find that hard to
believe I know I really understand I I
really don't know
we all have our tools of choices you
know
[Music]
where did you get them from
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's Iris I am
[Applause]
uh somewhat new
um
project Hub V singer David uh last month
yeah for those who don't know me Pirates
uh I'm very excited this is my first
time collabing with all my YouTube eyes
stop laughing
I'm sorry
sorry
that doesn't work sorry
apologize
how confident are you in your drawing
skills
[Music]
ah yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm just as good
as you seem to be a mystery uh-huh yeah
I haven't I haven't drawn yet actually
but I've I've been telling people my
streams that yeah I'm I'm Godly at
drawing but no that's just that's just
me
um you know put giving putting a really
um strong face in front of them I want
to tell you guys the truth now oh I I
draw with Mouse I mean I do have a
tablet too but like girls fii I can't I
can't draw with the tablet
[Music]
but since it's like the first uh whole
full hallway and collabs since Iris
joined I think for the sake of having
conversation we should not mute oh as
long as we don't like give away what
we're writing
all right introduction
hello my Indonesia from Whole Life
English
um
yeah
[Music]
I I like to draw I'm looking forward to
trying a lot today
okay
yes yes yeah yes that's it
and meals uh hello
Phoenix this I've played this game a lot
now today even today I've played it in a
separate stream and I'm playing it three
times this week so I would like to say I
am the master of garlic phone
um let's freaking go let's go
indisputable Undisputed and with this
dream I think we would all like to give
a big big warm welcome to Iris welcome
to home
I'm still I'm pretty nervous but yeah
no no need to worry
a little bit I think we should start it
off with normal and if we if we want all
we can cause which is six people so the
rounds should probably be pretty short
we can try some other things too but
normal I think is the bestest
um
[Music]
look better yeah oh I okay let's go okay
okay three two one
okay
interesting an idea
[Music]
see I'm really on the spot now okay I
already thought of this one since I was
a girl
uh I have mine already
a hint bottle I feel like I feel like
like very wide broad suggestions make
for funnier outcomes
when they are open to interpretation
but mine definitely is not
wrong
okay look at that
okay wait did I just give it away
you didn't I don't think you gave
anything away wait we got it we got we
gotta drop faster
sorry I don't know what I'm doing I
didn't do anything I didn't say anything
what we heard nothing Coulda you didn't
do right well I heard nothing I really
heard nothing
um yeah I was too distracted by my lack
of time
I think I left my Roomba going in the uh
the kitchen
right
[Music]
you're using a Roomba I have a Roomba I
like to sit on it
oh dear I don't know what I'm doing
[Music]
I got I can't know at that time is how
much time is it we don't have enough
time
almost half time
oh
[Music]
um this is the warm-up round right yes
we have so much time to draw so many
different things don't worry about it
right okay
[Music]
I gotta warm up my
my drawings what the hell is this what
the hell is this I love my drawing brain
somewhere I can't find it
[Music]
I don't know
this is a hard one
um
I feel so awkward drawing this okay
yeah yeah
um
if you add a little bit of color it will
make it so much easier to recognize who
you're drawing oh I hope this is enough
also don't don't write anything to your
drawings
okay okay
shape
why is there so many of them
all right
okay now I know the rules okay this is
easy this is
[Music]
um what is this
oh this is adorable
foreign
this is what I get from death
oh you guys you guys did get to see what
I wrote one sec
I'm just kidding I'm excited
[Laughter]
[Music]
I see I see
oh I don't know how to draw this without
because
yes uh
[Music]
oh
on the right side you have some tools
you can erase and you can also go steps
back
oh steps back okay oh you have a you
have a custom HTML picker as well that's
nice I'm gonna use this
[Music]
never mind oh yeah it does work I'm just
dumb
[Music]
yeah
by the way today I'm playing Christmas
music on my screen
no I was gonna put music on oh no
so nice the bells and everything
make me feel so nostalgic because it's
music that I went that I was using uh
during the Christmas time
nostalgic
you feel oh God I don't have time
yeah not a lot of time here huh
[Music]
not a lot of time can you zoom in music
makes me sleepy
foreign
[Music]
it would look like okay so there would
be fingers okay
um
wow this is rough this is rough you guys
[Music]
oh yes
I mean uh I forgot what what uh
nice weather today isn't it
yeah
it's very dark outside I can barely tell
oh wait wait wait wait this this here we
go now everybody will know who it is
right
we're just kidding
oh my God this is
I mean I like it you're not a problem
with it
um
you guys can't oh I haven't really
blocked oops
but I want to make louder
oh you can't see the game start again
thank you
[Music]
I always thought this way is there like
points you can get like are we supposed
to be guessing when people are another
one no in this mode there's no points no
no
oh all right I don't know what this is
but okay
[Music]
man
I am confused
no Iris how does it feel after warm up
in her life English oh yeah yeah tell us
everything I'm feeling getting used to
everything yeah yeah but everything
still doesn't feel that real
yeah yeah it is actually not real it is
all a dream I miss oh wow this is one
long of a dream
the dream is so nice I also don't want
to wake up I've decided to never wake up
yeah yeah
I can't wake up yeah
save me
uh
maintenance new hair battling oh my hair
yeah it takes a good two two to three
hours styling it ready
yep I woke up super early for this
[Music]
the sun's wrath I thought that was like
so set in place you don't need to like
you wake up like this I wake up like
this oh it's even it's worse when I wake
up
oh God it's all over my place
yeah my hair brush my hair brush it gets
a lot yeah a lot of hair just gets
wanked off when I'm brushing it yep have
you seen those videos where people clean
their hair brushes out after like two
months or so and the water is like brown
yeah
after two months
two weeks
oh my God
I don't know but I think I'm done I
don't know no one will understand you
yeah oh we're done oh my goodness and I
think
um
actually we should do auto so we all see
it at the same time normally I do manual
but I guess Auto display
then three two one
a present to others ice
[Music]
Merry Christmas Iris
dentist scared of Hope
you're still alive
get it now but I understand this game
now
stick figures are Godly wow this is
beautiful this is really good I like
them
you guys can um save save the album if
you click on the button to say that so I
wanna be on Save Duty or I I will do it
okay okay okay okay shall we go to the
next album
Santa missing suspect descendant another
Santa Fe
oh my god
oh I'm searched Thomas and Santa
couldn't
[Laughter]
I'm wearing the leotard
it's very cute if that was even still
about
um Iris but I didn't put her in there so
I guess that was right by putting her in
there
in there because she loves Christmas so
much
I don't like it much more once you get
to know these five sentence
us here yeah become Santa
[Music]
oh no
you face your face
you understand it oh no oh
cute
[Music]
okay
I see I see
that is so cute yeah Kelly really
enjoyed that beauty
um
I liked the plot and it was very
dramatic I enjoyed it
yes the writing
came up with that idea
[Laughter]
[Music]
escalated a little bit let's go let's go
oh
I recently not found out yes
[Laughter]
we're gonna finish mine
beautiful there's a dolphin there what
is that
okay surrealism
[Music]
not bad
oh my God good ads you wanted the chaos
I got that one yeah
what does blessing mean
s
it's beautiful
that was really good it was a nice first
round ladies nice yeah
we're fast we shall do more
should we do another normal one
I don't know what do you suggest how are
the other moons well the others are
partially pretty difficult
um for example
um I think maybe sandwich could be
interesting people have been suggesting
should just suggestion sandwich a lot
tasty want to do that one we can try it
keep drawing Until the End finally
describe the last drawing we will
understand when it happens I suppose oh
is it gonna like layer all of our
drawings
I think so yeah sandwich oh I see I get
it oh stop I guess
okay okay
um
[Music]
I think that's good that's a good one I
think it's good I can't think of
anything yeah that's the problem
I'm excited for your prompt everyone
yeah
let's go something simple
screw it let's do something fun let's go
a little while great doesn't have to be
crazy
oh God the time the time is ticking so
quickly oh God okay
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
shut up Kelly shut up
don't shut it off Kelly
talk I can't like I can't let you know
what I'm drawing
oh uh I just feel like making it cursed
cars to spawn do cursed okay you betcha
girl you betcha
[Music]
also how's it different from the other
one yeah I'm not sure what we'll see
starting from the next round oh
[Music]
um
are you fit everyone
uh
oh yeah art skills coming at you
yeah oh I'm so oh yeah
you're gone
[Music]
why does it not let you save your color
you should have like a custom color Bank
you can say oh yeah
unfortunately oh no I'm not gonna make
it I don't know uh don't worry other
people will finish your drawing maybe
oh oh that's a good idea so maybe we
should leave room for others oh probably
yeah I'm not sure
uh
usual okay
[Music]
oh my God
wait no
uh oh uh
okay okay at least it's recognizable I
think all right this is not recognizable
mm-hmm
yeah yeah okay okay let's see what
happens
what's next
oh
memorize it recreated
oh God everything is awesome
uh this is really cute this is adorable
thank you thank you
wait what
all right I got it we're going point for
Point here
[Music]
oh okay
I forgot the whole job okay okay I think
I remember
[Music]
oh my God I don't remember I already
forgot
break also I don't even know what was
going on there
oh
oh yeah
[Music]
oh no oh God
um I'm so sorry
[Music]
I keep wanting to control Z you can you
can't you can't drive
oh my god I've been doing it
okay I think I thought you can't pick a
custom color
you can
oh you have to click the big big Swatch
I see it yeah
[Music]
you learned something new every day yeah
there were some something like that in
between wait one two three four
we have space
hey this is not bad I think I'm
improving I think we've seen
improvements
ringing uh oh
believed now you wait for me game you
wait for me or I'll be angry
I'll be angry and you don't want to know
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh what's happening
yeah that'll have to do
oh
my God what is this what is this
foreign
oh my God what is this wait does this
time count as well oh my God
what
okay okay okay what all right this is a
no-brainer
what
okay I didn't notice there was a a
bucket oh wait no it didn't work lucky
bucket
um
but something like that
this is really difficult
I like this game
I don't remember it I also enjoyed this
game this is pretty good the Simplicity
Simplicity is the way to go
[Music]
um
also there's like someone missing you
oh man
uh now I actually still have time damn
it
wasn't this like as accurate as we can I
think so yeah
yeah
much as we can remember right
and your artistic interpretations of
what you saw God
[Music]
um
I captured the essence of it
I don't know about this one
I actually have it in early because
there was no no more to say I guess the
reference was just so simple
[Music]
[Laughter]
today's piece of art is oh my gosh no
it seems like is it oh maybe I don't
know I'm pretty sure is it sandwich I
think sandwich is like that yeah all
right we're we're going in we're doing
the best we can with the tools
okay okay all right it's not even be
able to talk about it because I just
want to make jokes about what I'm seeing
I think you can make graph jokes about
it also as for the ones we see it anyway
so
all right down remember
oh
[Music]
yeah looking good ladies looking good
beautiful and then there was a
oh my brain power
who is ASMR right now
we can all do it if you want if you
desire that nothing maybe later
hahaha
was it like this
I don't know what happened here
uh oh yeah
can we get like a purple
a different color
nice
oh nice oh cute wait wait wait wait wait
wait oh yeah I have enough time
oh I don't know what I'm doing drawing
skills are evolving through every single
round yeah
[Music]
I'm gonna be able to remember this game
that I was before
I don't know who this is
you you the time traveler out of all
people don't doesn't have enough time I
can't stop time
[Music]
just go back in time and answer
that's cheating
[Music]
okay wow you're fair you're Fair player
huh nice
she doesn't use her skills like that I
respect that
is
[Music]
beautiful it was a good one another one
good one oh
[Music]
I expect them which is pretty accurate
No but I don't know what happened
there's one more one more thing to do by
the way five out of the six so oh and
then okay then we'll see other things
I hope you know that
I love it what
oh
God oh did you hear that no that was my
hip bone
[Music]
um
have the same issues though I really
want that brace that we were talking
about I want a brace for my full body
yeah the shoulder braids to make sure
you don't punch over like the hunchback
yeah that's smart nice that's a good
purchase you can get one of those game
around
because it's been so fast actually wanna
go for it slower let's do display mode
manually okay then you can open it up on
your own timing
okay starter okay
I see right here
I was detangling her hair but getting
stuck okay okay
I think I did a pretty good job
that's so cute wow that's pretty cute
yeah she has a lot of things
a lot of mascots stuck in there
so do we all get the same
and
then like draw it
yeah yeah
oh oh let's let's check out gudas
[Music]
yeah
did you know good at what was going on
when you saw that image did you have an
idea no I just thought it was Iris oh
singing
look
[Music]
all right let's see Watson's
no I'm just thinking okay okay you're
all going for the
singer's getting like like music notes
made it looks like that yeah yeah all
right and Iris straws herself beautiful
well my conclusion what Cali
[Music]
okay okay
yeah
well for each other uh each person who
led the album says next next and we
follow that person uh you know what I
mean yeah okay
did I write comments is
tomorrow
didn't it just start today again
you know what happens when Taco Time
ends what why oh I Wanna Know
yeah
sorry okay I'll open there we go
nice interpretation
happier and happier
to happy I think how I know I know how
this one ends
thank you
I say you run out of time there oh yeah
the Paint Bucket continued to betray me
over and over again we have an opening I
can see them
[Music]
anymore if it was alive or not so I
ended up drawing it dead
oh no well that makes sense according to
the first one
oh no
[Music]
is this what happens when Taco Time ends
I guess so
okay okay next would you like to read
your prompt
underneath
who's under there
I know it's underneath the detective
desk
[Music]
thank you
oh
no
okay I gotta I gotta blame eyes for this
one I got I got a flame yeah I'm very
confident I did it perfectly oh I'm sure
you did
[Applause]
I almost died
and what I thought when I saw that was
[Laughter]
beautiful it's like Rugrats
very good I love it all right
what's up please read Grandma's missile
being launched ready for takeoff
um
[Laughter]
thanks perfect it's my girl missile oh
oh okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
disappeared from the drawings
one by one
they're gone
well I kept it very simple
having more in person oh wait
the whole rocket thing just disappeared
from among us to Pac-Man an autistic
edition of Pac-Man
including the British but
there wasn't enough letters
okay I love the face on on all of them
oh my God especially the animals yeah
next one
yeah Cali
Ian pillow fight show it to me show me
what you got like I don't remember
drawing this pillow fight
hello
[Music]
your hair your hair grew out look how
long it is
long hair I think my chest detached from
my head
obviously some pillows yes
all right
Florida
[Music]
well it fits again I've been trampled
it's fine
it's okay I think I think I saved you I
think I saved you kind of thank you apex
predator
Apex trampled
[Laughter]
how am I supposed to follow up with this
themselves
hi
[Music]
I mean technically that could be correct
yes yes
oh no it's amazing bad yeah okay no good
good
in battle
in Bat what what battle all kinds of
battle all kinds of that yeah yeah I
have I have magic powers
until now I have no I'm hope I don't
kill people
don't let me catch you killing folks I
will have to get you through that you
guys are the monster because you're the
ones who killed I don't know okay all
righty next up Iris please read your
prompt you're a suspect I'm an
investigation
okay
okay okay oh
um I missed the Trident I think
I forgot about you I recognize yourself
okay yeah okay
that's cute
oh no oh
[Laughter]
oh yeah
all right
[Laughter]
[Applause]
nuggets might come back
my stomach hurts
is that your power you got so close I
wouldn't I thought somebody would
interpret it afterwards so I just
because I don't know yeah
I will send them to you all after lunch
was
we have ten
um a bit more I think we can squeeze in
another normal yeah let's do it okay the
first one was not only 15 minutes yeah
okay all right okay let's do it
okay
um
think Kiara thing
[Music]
chat got any ideas
you're right
okay
suggestions submissions
what the hell I hope so someone really
good gets that prompt
s chat
okay all hydrated
[Music]
party time
oh
oh uh alrighty I'm on it
leave it to me
okay not great I ran out of time my
prompt is possibly interesting
no problem that's just that just makes
it better you know yeah maybe I left it
really vague so we have to see what
others come up with
um
oh boy what does this look like
so we have this picture
um oh gosh
uh and then this one I had to write a
letter in this
since this is a topic right wait this
this is pretty much true though
[Music]
beautiful I feel I feel I feel it I feel
it I just feel it it's beautiful
[Music]
um
dead ly
[Laughter]
I did not think of the composition of
this picture very well before I started
drawing oh my goodness I like to see
everyone screams after this
oh
[Music]
maybe a chance the more color to this oh
dear nose
[Music]
oh
okay
okay I'm done
[Laughter]
oh I see yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah well I mean
okay this is pretty easy
I wonder who got mine
this might sound better does this sound
better this sounds better oh that sounds
better
[Laughter]
um
okay beautiful all right
[Music]
what's that mean
oh easy oh it just described myself
oh geez oh
I need to Google someone real quick
what's up
um
no no no I'm Googling no no I'm Googling
this one tell me what is that what is
that I don't
language of memes
[Music]
thank you it's happening okay
um
okay I think I know who this is Maybe
ah man if I could draw this could be
really cute
what's the turn huh
oh
[Music]
um
uh
I need to try
okay okay
uh uh uh
[Music]
I'm crying I don't even know how to
interpret this
are you okay
[Music]
are you good you're good
Cara's not good
he's gone she's gone he's gone she's
disappeared forever
oh no
are you okay are you good
we need to call an ambulance
[Laughter]
Phoenix is dying
Cali do something
[Music]
oh no
I don't recognize who this is what
uh
and my cards real straight okay I'll
just play in my cards real straight chat
who's this who's this this is okay okay
okay
I got this
[Music]
is that a sword
oh disease
my eyes are no I didn't have enough time
what does this mean
oh my God Don't Make Me Try So Many
people again
I don't know what this means oh but yes
I do
foreign
[Music]
okay we can do this we can do this we
can do this
[Music]
nope I'm right
okay okay
um
[Music]
go uh yeah
I want to Google this
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay uh
um what
do I have to do this
hopefully this is yeah
[Music]
um
I have given up completely
uh never give up never surrender
this is what this animal looks like I I
don't I lost hope even though hope is
right next
you right next to your girl
just look to yourself
yeah cool wow wow I don't know that's
kind of charming
why is that so Charming I don't know
oh I got this oh
oh no
oh
[Music]
everybody's gonna know what this is
right yeah yeah
oh no
come on
lots of time lots of times
[Music]
oh my god well we started out with
fingers
oh greatness from this
oh that was good that's good that's good
wait I feel like I know
to turn
sleeves
oh I think I know where this leaves
you'll love to see it all unravel
wow good and I'm always dead in these
things
oh realistic
there
[Laughter]
do we have a Jose please
oh my God oh my gosh
oh you can say I could hear this
image and it sounds exactly like that
it's kind of perfect
mommy oh man okay okay Taco Time yeah
those steps in a Lego Lego
no I really just couldn't yeah
it looks like a Sesame Street character
Muppet
gone wrong
I guess because it's the only male three
person that we would draw
position of the Lego was a little weird
to me
this was the the one where I started
dying by crying oh no oh
that's what happened
[Music]
[Applause]
when I was crying
wow that's yeah that's very yeah okay
[Laughter]
I thought you meant banking like you
Bank a turn
of money
it's okay
okay
[Music]
I didn't finish my prompt okay we're
talking about yes I my brain
um okay I'll leave it up to your
interpretation
much room for interpretation yeah
I mean that's pretty cut and dry oh my
God
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is good okay okay
in her natural habitat
yeah I mean everything looks normal to
me
good stuff
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I'm sorry
what if there's opacity
[Music]
I don't get this oh
well you know it went it became so hot
that they melted into one body
monster
every day
so don't make sense
[Music]
um yeah just so we don't get in trouble
the right person got that one now
let's go
so good
smash smash
nothing beats one
yeah
this is good this is a good one that's
good okay
Inna puns is trying to well okay
my brain I didn't know how to oh I
didn't finish okay right
I mean
[Music]
oh that's a good one
you understand each other this is the
the telepathy that we have after almost
a year
so I don't know that there was an inner
pot in there I just guess oh wow
my intuition trained
domination with Halloween
so many people again
hey nice job everyone
that was a lot of time all right good
job I had a blast wow I will send them
to you afterwards everyone can pick one
to upload on Twitter or five or two two
how many ever you want okay I have a lot
of a lot of gifts gifs about okay by the
way how do you guys say
if
is it not
hello
I usually say GIF when I speak German I
think and when I speak English I tend to
say gif
yeah yeah it was it was the pineapple on
pizza before pineapple um pizza was a
thing
[Music]
let's count down
three yes three
oh no I covered everyone's face okay
[Music]
[Applause]
might as well be one year
it's finally ready
tomorrow it looks like a later today I
think huh yeah nothing like uh very soon
like what's 15 minus nine
[Music]
thank you
sorry guys taking over
in plastic
the hoof and Jack Pages going up in
approximately five minutes
tweets on hololive English Twitter is
coming out in I think 20 minutes if they
don't decide to put it out earlier now
but it should be coming out in 20
minutes right yeah soon
these Plushies are uh Point big
your words
35 centimeters that's big you guys 35
centimeters is Big yeah totally huggable
I heard they're really really soft
[Music]
some people don't think in centimeters
we have a picture
whole life's number one model
you know what these look like they would
fit perfectly in a T-shirt cannon they'd
be really good yeah
with these plushies oh
throw them around the Battle of the Gods
no it does not come with Yago
unfortunately we're sorry but Yaga could
honestly like just quit his CEO job and
become a model at this point
is calling
thank you I think it's that I'm not
really sure
let's keep you dude I thought it's like
a like a magazine on your models I was
thinking
DQ like Jake
okay
um
yeah that's a good point when uh when we
all eventually meet we need to have a
big pillow fight with these yes
[Music]
but then they'd be questioning you
know you're gonna look inside they're
gonna open them up
[Music]
to cut them open
I cannot risk that dissection
oh no please no
I will not know if he's cotton in there
though is there anything else besides
cotton in there I'll find it out I guess
cotton
are there beans in there well I think
it's more like the soft like plushie
yeah they're really soft I've touched
them
I have I have held them and I have
touched them I want to squish the face
and distort it make fun yeah I've
touched those as well they're very soft
yeah all right well Iris how how did you
like your first collab with the whole
life English it was a lot of fun like
everyone's art art levels are just out
of the world
[Applause]
um
actually and that's not me being ironic
or sarcastic they actually you did a
very good job thank you we are so glad
to have him on this collaboration yeah
thank you I would like to collab with
all of you guys again yeah of course
yeah let's keep doing it yeah yeah I
mean some of us just like me have not
done a one-on-one collab with you yet
yeah yeah yeah yeah today was the first
time for me to collab with you
half of you guys oh wait yeah yeah yeah
let's do it soon Minecraft
give you an official tour of the en
server so you don't get it yeah
we'd have to show you around yeah yeah
let me show you Phoenix then I think
it's actually already stumbled into
Phoenix
isn't it like the restaurant the
restaurant no no that's kfp but I
probably stumbled into a big Village
yeah oh by the way Iris the hole that
you fell into because now that we're all
here and I fell into that hole a few
months ago several times and lost a lot
of things and I was always wondering who
made that dug the hole yes
what wasn't me
wow my view is that no one has any
record of anyone ever digging that hold
on on stream but I kept it open because
I was like well well I was the person
who dug it to fall into it
[Music]
what is this
or something like that it would like
react to something suspicious
oh God you made an investigation
[Music]
who was it I wonder that whole of death
where was it I don't even know what it
is like if you go through kfp back to
like spawn
yeah
I mean I'm responsible for the the
stairs uh in kfp I will own up to that
oh not that in a different hole than I
don't know different different hole
that's like one block wide but uh five
million breakdown yeah yeah go straight
down it's out in the middle of nowhere
and when yeah you just like it's really
hard to put in there yep
and they were trying to maybe just uh
make a landmark or something or no it's
like really close to my house so what if
you did it Kiara yeah
oh I'm blaming the others
[Music]
from Spirit this conspiracy theory
I guess this will continue to be able to
number one
does anybody are we gonna cover that
hole are we just gonna leave it there
please just the warning sign that's it
that's fine there yeah it's a memorial
it's an important part of Holo en
history
yeah yeah Emma what were you saying um
does anybody have any like individual
announcements like maybe a stream you're
gonna do or something like that
oh yeah uh so tomorrow
um I have a karaoke stream with a
special guest a guest who is not in hold
alive
check it out we're doing uh archived and
also unarchived streams so please
thank you that's all I have anyone else
um I'm gonna play
uh
uh the police officer officer
yeah and then we're gonna continue Devil
May Cry finally so that's all
yes
all right
um all right then I'll say it next week
I'm playing Minecraft with my real
mother uh on my channel
it will actually be amazing because for
the people who don't know my my mother
is better at Minecraft than all of us
here she's really good and she will
teach me um some stuff and we will go
get never right together
how the farm never rides it'll be fun so
let me know we'll be on our server for
one day
thank you
oh my God I want to say hello I didn't
say you guys would want to do that oh I
didn't think so okay
like all of you she uh checked all of
your streams out trying to think of some
embarrassing stuff to tell me yeah
[Laughter]
you
okay anyone else with announcements
uh
I'll be streaming subnautica later on
today
[Music]
finally got myself
anyone else
I have a morning show that I'm gonna be
doing hopefully week weekly but uh
Sunday but I'll be gone for two weeks
after that and then another one
okay okay
[Music]
that's cute too what's it called well
I'm at in the a.m
um
yeah yeah my title oh thank you I will
be watching it it might be archived but
I will be watching it yeah
definitely check it out yeah
Orlando this weekend yeah heading out to
Megacon in Orlando Florida in the US of
a uh you can meet or talk to us or uh
show up on our panel I believe
um mine is tomorrow and Kiara's is the
day after yeah I'm on Saturday on Friday
and uh oh yeah if you if you can't
attend it in person if you have a ticket
then you can actually watch a stream of
it so you don't have to be there in
person but you still need ticket there
is a stream
[Music]
we're looking forward to seeing you that
is the first one that kicks off the
Halloween in America conventions America
and Canada conventions tour Legends yeah
so cool
okay so okay so snowy say goodbye yeah I
think I think the uh Booth should be up
by now question mark sure
[Music]
thanks guys
[Applause]
[Music]
what okay
goodbye
foreign