[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
kick anything
hello
oh
hello hello hello I made myself even
bigger what what's that
obs
okay I notice I'm too big for you to see
now but it's okay
hello
are you send it but now I descended
are you ready for some rings of Power
are you ready
so who here is watching with me but has
not watched the other episodes
I hope there's not too many of you
because that's stupid
bye
that's way too many here
that's you oh
um
with some episodes but I got to just
okay
uh okay ref
tldr from me truly
I will try uh okay so
the show starts out
um focusing on several groups of people
okay
um
number one we have galat Riel
kind of the most important character in
the show
Galadriel you may still remember
from Lord of the Rings and so on
yeah yeah so she they show her uh when
she's like pretty young out on the trip
it's a trip
desperately trying to find evil and then
kill it because she's very certain that
it's still out there
but they just can't find it she has like
some other else with her and they're
like [\h__\h] you Galadriel we're so sick of
this [\h__\h] and they eventually
abandoned her because the trip is
suffering uh maybe the real suffering
was the trip we made along the way you
know because yeah they couldn't find any
evil
but she was like I'm sure [\h__\h] this so
she comes back and then they send her
out uh the the the most you know
cool coolest elf in the neighborhood
he's like Galadriel you are you have
done so much good for us so we thank you
by basically killing you so
they sent her as they apparently
traditionally do on a boat trip
you know where people go when they're in
the midlife crisis and they don't know
what to do with their money
um on a yacht you know with other older
people you know pool music
that kind of stuff live music yeah uh
wasn't quite like that yeah yeah valinor
that's the place yeah so she and many
other elves were as as a as a thank you
sent to valinor where there's like this
scene where she goes she's about to go
through this big
cloudy whatever which apparently is deaf
but happy death yeah because these elves
they live for [\h__\h] ever so it's I
guess good for them but then I think a
storm was coming up maybe maybe no the
storm was maybe after I don't know but
yeah she's like [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] and she
said like I don't want to die yet I
still need to find evil and then maybe
die for the evil that's better so she
jumps off the ship and she's on her own
in the middle of the wide [\h__\h] ocean
when she gets am I gonna
you know as as detailed as I'm
explaining this it sounds like I'm gonna
explain the whole show
she gets picked up by some dude
um who's not an elf and he's like only
on a little piece of tiny wood and they
go for storms and [\h__\h] and get attacked
and [\h__\h] and but they bond and they
eventually end up in uh online they get
they get picked up I think by a big boat
and then they get brought to their place
and they're like hey yo where the [\h__\h]
are we and turns out they are in what's
that place called a numenor yeah
which is
kind of like really
um
isolated
they don't have much to do with the
other continent
and therefore they feel Superior unhappy
but numenor was originally like created
and gifted to by the elves
yeah
something was there you know there was a
connection and The King The King back in
the day he was like really chill with
the elves
um
but eventually they thought like [\h__\h]
you else
um and yeah now now they're like really
really like racist towards them
so when they see Galadriel walking in
they're like ew stinky disgusting ew
by the Valar not the elves okay well I
don't know whatever my storyline is
better my my explanation is better
so yeah yeah yeah they're like you so
she has to do this whole thing where she
gets them on her side and eventually you
know after a couple episodes she finally
does after being partially held captive
and also it turns out that the dude that
was with her is supposed to be the king
of the list
I suppose yeah even though he's like
oh I don't wanna but then after a while
he's like I guess I'll do it South not
the West okay me honestly for Russian
south ah the cell phone okay yeah yeah
the South
yeah help brand help brand
okay I swear to God if you [\h__\h] piece
of [\h__\h] in the chat we're right with
what you just wrote there and you're
spoiling me on purpose
then
I'm gonna block you right now
if any [\h__\h] bastard wants to [\h__\h]
spoiler me before I watch the last
episode to ruin this [\h__\h] for me for me
I'm going to kill you
so
um
anyway
meanwhile meanwhile you know she's she's
a galactualist trying since she has no
one [\h__\h] else she's trying to gather
an army by the way to fight the evil
that she has yet to find it's so funny
actually
so stupid actually
collateral
slight really paranoid but okay so she
tries to get the people that hate her
the most
the minorians
to join her on their trip to kill some
evil in the Southlands and then you know
you know that happens eventually they
finally get over it after after having a
vision oh yeah yeah then the queen not
really the Queen but the emperor
whatever of the that place I'm actually
enjoying telling you guys this whole
story
she's she's like
[Music]
um
like she has a vision where the leaves
of a pink tree start falling here we
just called that Japan in Spring but
you know you know she's like oh my [\h__\h]
that's a bad Omen
um
[Laughter]
okay yeah
eventually she even she joins them
oh I just realized because I got rid of
the the front part of this
there's something weird
there's something weird oh the chickens
shiny or so I guess we'll never ignore
that okay
um okay so that's that's the that's the
collateral set and while all of this is
happening let's let's talk a little bit
about the the humans I don't I'm not so
the humans for me they don't really do
it for me but basically what they do
like they focus on this like family of a
mother and her son
um in a little village who are the first
to witness the evil that is coming back
basically her son finds a random uh
object that is actually like a really
really important key to the story key
uh and it's evil and it's like it's kind
of like the ring you know with with
Frodo putting it on and like feeling the
power and all that and becoming
corrupted but hopefully not
um yeah but uh like more in a fancy
version it's not just a ring it's like
it looks like a sword at first he thinks
it's a sword but it's not really a sword
so yeah he finds it but he doesn't tell
his mommy he's like keeping it to
himself and but the problem is while
he's using it the evil kind of I guess
senses it and goes towards it and finds
eventually the family destroys the
village and they're [\h__\h] and he still
doesn't realize it's because of this
thing and he still hides it on the same
uh in the same in the same kind of you
know
um scenery there's like a guardian elf
you know he's he's an he's a guard elf
but he actually has a big crash on the
human lady so he does everything in his
power to protect this family
yeah uh uh and he's like really op like
if they have to fight a [\h__\h] Army
and he's the only one on his side that
can
lift a finger in war then due to plot
armor he's still gonna be alive at the
end and [\h__\h] blast everyone away yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
uh a little bit ridiculous but you know
they they have some like confrontations
with this dude who's leading the evil
they're building like a tunnel to go
below because the uh as we've learned
these Orcs they are like the type of orc
that does not like the sunshine kind of
depressive and and emotional edgy too
nibial babies
um yeah so they don't they have to go
through the Earth so they while they're
digging and digging and digging they're
going towards you know the humans
knowledge so the elf eventually finds
them and then he sees oh the leader of
them is not like an orca World whatever
no it's
and a corrupted evil elf which that dude
I have to say he looks
like perfect for his role I think he has
that evil elf face it's perfect
yeah they burn in the sun yeah yeah yeah
but then actually turns out that some
humans uh on this in this world they
still support and want Sal run and the
evilness to take over again uh you know
you know so uh some some humans like oh
yeah where's Sarah and this evil elf
dude is like [\h__\h] you Sauron
I don't know he's like in in early early
retirement [\h__\h] him
I'm sorry I'm kind of not really and
this is not really how I went down but
it's something like that
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah and through all of
these episodes until now we're still
like who is Sauron but there's one more
mystery one more mystery the hobbits uh
which are not the hobbits you look at
them you think oh is that the Romans but
no it's not the habits for [\h__\h] sake
they're hard foots unfortunately
um and these are basically Hobbits that
um travel at all times they're always
traveling uh yeah they're always always
traveling and they have like these big
carts yeah and they push them and they
pull them and every once in a while they
stop and then they keep on going that's
them
so there's like two children in this not
Hobbit family that they focus on
uh to Children two girls and one of the
girls uh she gets really attached to
something she finds which is a huge
huge human a giant almost uh
which is like who is who is found in the
middle of a big like field that looks
like a meteorite hit it almost as if
this very human this giant was the
meteorite that struck the ground and you
know is now lying there like a little uh
naked baby yeah Meteor Man basically so
she finds that dude and and he's like
naked in a big hole and everything's
like burning and hot and attitude
and she's like Ayo and he's like yo I
don't understand your weird words and he
really acts like a baby but he also
seems to have some weird power and but
now she's also stupid like that other
human child and tries to take him with
her while also hiding him even
huge how can you hide him so she tries
to try something because she thinks it's
some kind of like uh of miracle and and
Destiny kind of thing yeah but every now
and then yeah he does some stupid [\h__\h]
where she gets like freaked out and
she's like whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa stop dude that's that's
freaking me out
um
yeah but she feels destined to help him
and and she wants she wants to help him
also because he seems to look for
something he feels like he's looking for
something in the Stars yeah but he's
also not sure what and but he seems to
be really [\h__\h] powerful
he does not however look like Sauron at
all so he doesn't look like sound he
doesn't look like Gandalf so I'm like
who the [\h__\h] is this
um
you like what do you guys like my
summarization so far we're almost done
okay so these are the groups uh but yeah
okay so eventually they all come almost
together when
um oh no wait I forgot the dwarfs but I
forgot them because they don't really
play a big role they're just they're all
almost the only really perfect thing
about this show but
they don't really so far play any like
important role so there's some dwarfs
okay during the world famous durian he
is the son of the current King in this
age and he has a a really
um
funny witty wife as well they have
children that their children one of them
is the father of the future Gimli
so that's cool to see some connections
you know but they live in in the
mountain and
um they still seem to be connected with
some Elves and then there's this elf
called alvarons that we also kind of
know and he's you know chit chatting
with durian Dorian eventually finds a
really important material called mithril
at the same time as uh elaborand uh is
being told by his leaders that like she
swear like dying man like holy [\h__\h] my
hair is falling out my lashes beautiful
hair and ah we're all gonna die the
light is fading the light of our
beautiful tree is fading look and yeah
this is like really dramatic so
um alaran visits durian and sees the
midrand and then realize at some point
oh [\h__\h] this my friend is the key to
keeping us alive so they're like you
know trying to trying to get the dwarves
to really [\h__\h] stuff up and stop it
as dwarves that I love
um to share some of that [\h__\h] my
friend especially after they see a whole
[\h__\h] vein in the mountain that's that
could provide more than enough mid frail
for the next 500 000 years but no no
Daddy's the king is like
doing that for you I want to see all my
friends die and I want to be all alone
and have no friends
this is better I want to be alone in my
mountain and have us all die from
starvation and unhappiness and
loneliness yeah hmm
yeah so that's kind of how the last
episode ended
um like oh sorry [\h__\h] you not giving any
of you if any of you any of that even
though we just saw the proof
that the Midfield could save them
um it's [\h__\h] sad
um but this is why I'm saying they don't
really play a big role so far they don't
do they don't add anything to what's
going on on the other side so that those
are the four or five parties kind of and
then finally collateral with all her big
army and suddenly all want to support
her they arrive in the Southlands they
meet the humans right at the perfect
timing right when the Orcs are attacking
the humans Last Resort Village where
they build some really drum in a really
dramatic way build a defense with a big
strategy that where they thought they
won but no actually they didn't win they
just sent out you know decoys and and
then the real Orcs come and they're like
[\h__\h] and you're like you're like as a
viewer you're like [\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
idiots of course that was not it that
would have been way too smooth like
[\h__\h] butter better uh and then at the
same time you see a scene you know
cutting back and forth to the Galadriel
Army like Galloping on their horses from
how far away and how far away is that
for some reason
they go so fast as if they knew the
exact the exact GPS location Google
Google GPS is telling them turn right
turn left go straight
be fast because you have about five
minutes and 32 seconds until they all
die
I I am I am not [\h__\h] on this show
like many other people are but this this
kind of is ridiculous but you know magic
uh and they arrive at the perfect moment
and they save the humans kind of they
still have many casualties
um and then oh [\h__\h] this is okay you
know they thought they thought they
finally
um are done with the Orcs okay
and they got the leader as a as a as a
prisoner amazing amazing you think how
could you possibly [\h__\h] this up
Galadriel is like interviewing them like
I interview my guests in in the whole
talk and she's like how did you get into
Laws of Power what's power of rings
and he's like [\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
and and yeah they they have him hostage
but they look away for one [\h__\h]
second
and the volcano oh that's quite far away
explodes turns all the beautiful grassy
Southlands into mortar that's a big
exciting reveal you know
um and then in that moment this [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] escapes
like oh my God you had one job like one
[\h__\h] job one job but that's like
really dramatic when the volcano
explodes this goes like boom and and and
and and and
um
you see at the end of that one episode
you see Galadriel standing there like
facing the explosion of the volcano it
doesn't look really realistic that she
would survive it but of course she does
we all know because she's in the later
movies uh but
um yeah then the next episode starts
when when with like all the old
casualties of the [\h__\h] Mountain
explosion and that's the first episode
no no no no
that's one of the most recent [\h__\h] it
was um ending yeah
yeah some people survived it um the
queen from numenor She's blind now [\h__\h]
she doesn't want to tell people though
because
for whatever [\h__\h] reason
um I guess Pride or whatever but then
yeah they want to go back the numenor
people the ones that remained or
survived they want to go back because
they're like
and let's let's we we have tiny
peepees
um we are now gonna
put them between our butt cheeks and go
back to numer and let you guys deal with
this [\h__\h] uh but then suddenly they're
like no wait wait wait we're staying
after all
[Laughter]
um to face it together
oh the dwarves are nowhere to be seen at
this point and the humans uh the the the
hobbits the fake Hobbits are still
somewhere doing their thing uh
oh but then yeah last episode they still
had this one more important Revelation I
guess which wasn't really a revelation
but they were you know
um actually integrating the big dude
into their Caravan he was helping them
push it because they're about to be
kicked out and they didn't get help
anymore but they got him to help them so
they were able to catch up but
but um
uh
then of course he causes trouble again
and everyone's once again is like what
the [\h__\h] and then he helps and he makes
uh the tree go whoa beautiful but no one
really you know appreciates it so then
in the night time uh
uh
uh these these people one more one more
groups of people that you see every once
in a while in the show the weird people
that where one looks like Eminem's
people made up made a whole meme about
it I think uh they look like some kind
of like mix between Sauron people
and magical Heaven people that are
really evil that you have not seen a lot
of the Rings or so before honestly I
don't know what to do with these people
but yeah they this is a group of like
free people and white white
um garments and they look evil but they
think there's something better and
they're Wonder wandering around in the
world looking for something and it seems
very obvious that they're looking for
the giant
um because they keep on checking out the
spots where the traces for the giant are
and then and then and then and then
they kind of more or less
find him in the last episode uh um but
not really they're like I guess I forgot
they were like on the way to finding him
like really close to finding him I think
uh yeah yeah and she oh yeah they they
were like really evil and they
um they completely destroyed and and and
burnt all of the Caravan down so the
harford's had like nothing left yeah
and then they oh oh he was already gone
oh yeah yeah but yeah they they they the
hartford's carried the aftermath of that
um
okay so that's it that's it
I did all of that in half an hour for
you
isn't always here uh
I don't know [\h__\h] you don't ask me these
questions I'm confused
don't ask me I
am perfect PowerPoint presentation you
can't ask me anymore this was a perfect
explanation if you have any questions
then you weren't listening
no no no questions
[Laughter]
why am I not moving hello
okay I'm I'm so basically what we're
waiting for in this episode is uh the
answer to who is the Giant and
um also who is Sauron I guess yeah so
let's let's watch this [\h__\h] it's on
Amazon Prime I have it open I hope you
guys have it ready too
I'm not high on low side I'm judge is
really uh actually got pretty excited
hyped up with explaining all of that
um
one one thing I want to say I I I I I
understand that you know a lot of people
don't like to show and criticize it
um and you you have you're totally valid
in your opinions and you're welcome to
have them I just don't really have such
high standards I guess but
um not saying you don't you're not
allowed to have an opinion but please
don't try to ruin the mood here and sour
my mood and my enjoyment of the show
uh now in the chat okay that's
unnecessary I I want to enjoy it so
please don't take that away from me okay
I I also think some things in the show
are definitely not perfect but I'm
enjoying it nonetheless so yeah please
please don't ruin it for me okay we
don't have to make fun of it I mean you
know I like making fun of things I
consume every now and then but please
don't go overboard let's enjoy together
okay foreign
open we're gonna start from uh zero
I suppose
uh I have the sound muted I think oh
yeah
oh wait there's like um uh there's a
there's an advertisement first that's
like 15 seconds
let's let's skip that why is there an
advertisement in Amazon Prime oh well at
least it's not like in real TV
okay zero okay there we go uh it's one
hour 12 minutes 27 seconds
uh and let me see audio I do English
subtitles with English audio
okay
skipping intro now we're gonna go from
zero zero zero zero zero
send them
okay Amazon watch party feature oh I
don't know how that works that's I guess
on on Twitch I don't know why that [\h__\h]
works I'm sorry
I don't know but I have a timer here and
I'll start it I'll start with we count
down from three to one zero on zero we
press play and on 0.5 I press start over
here because I can't do it at once okay
free
three two
one
zero
yay let's go let's go let's go
I would have preferred to watch this oh
there's a there's a recap let's not skip
it this is good for you guys listen
we prefer to watch it on my TV but oh
well
this is that's the evil guy the evil guy
the evil he killed wait I forgot that of
course he didn't kill Sauron
oh yeah and then here he [\h__\h] up once
again that's giant that those the hard
foots
those desire the elves of the Dwarfs
no don't wanna
so you see magical cherry blossoms
falling
oh and then magical fire falling
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
he did maybe
oh yeah yeah I think they went back to
bring more people right that's why she
was just on the boat
oh yeah galadril is often heal a dude
yeah yeah I forgot about that detail
she's going to the elves probably also
bringing reinforcements maybe who knows
here we go
hellburn yeah
oh is that the giant I think it's Giant
Aaron gallon the Greenwood
he's like Gandalf's ice I would say
which is why I was like could this be
gando but none away like nah
unfortunately
I wonder though Wizards like Gandalf how
long is their lifespan in the Tolkien
universe
he's probably evil though
okay then in theory I guess it kind of
could be him
when we think about timelines
but nah
see the thing is I don't know if it ever
was told in the books how Gandalf like
came to where he ended up at
like how he was as a Babu Babu
it was okay
she's spooky oh my God
oh no
real slime machine please stand now
please stand up
okay I'm gonna take this serious though
hope you know that guys
oh
I have a
Apple
oh
ah okay so that was not a spoiler in the
chat before thank God
he's so wrong I but someone is a wizard
too so but I guess ah this is reborn and
it makes sense though that he's that
that could be him because wizards live
so long right
[Music]
hey we should be happy that they reveal
it now because I feel like some things
they're gonna not reveal at all in this
season two seasons
and then not show it until next
season I
I I I think this opening is beautiful
but also boring
I always always skip it
but
what
if so someone someone didn't he also
because they have like history of
Gandalf didn't he also have like
wasn't he also just a normal wizard at
some point
no way I'm thinking about saddle man oh
wait I'm mixing them up because they
have similar names I'm totally mixing
two things up I'm sorry
I'm thinking of Saruman
Sauron was also an angel though what
does that mean he was an angel are those
people Angels considered angels
oh I'm confused I'm confused who are
those people
why why why uh question mark
that's the right sound
[Music]
oh collateral girl
oh they have construction up there on
the left side cool
oh
make it into sand I don't know
whistles are angels in the talking
Universe what
cool okay
we need to nerd out a bit more and talk
about all of this at some point
maybe at the end of the episode
wait where's your surprise that she's
still alive
in the ocean destiny
oh
mm-hmm
I like her
she's so cute yeah
foreign
hell friend
that's how the elves became Zoras
oh
I feel like I could receive a quest here
give me a quest
right in here
it's like in World of Warcraft man
our final fantasy
looks like plastic
oh yeah
oh
or
now you're talking
but with this tiny itsy bitsy tiny bit
smart boy
but why would he be sour and we already
know who's sour and Reginald
sorry
pretty decent
she she has one of those faces that I
was talking about when I said I don't
think that they fit into oh
what
let's go I was saying uh
I feel like some of these faces don't
fit into the universe like hers
because she looks too perfect
she doesn't look like for
like Frosty world
but no one understands what I'm trying
to say
she fits for nominal hmm
oh man
my guess maybe
I wish it does
but the main human lady I I really feel
like she could be in a [\h__\h] Disney
movie
but not here
oh yeah yeah it is one of the balls
there was like a couple of them
apparently I didn't even know that
until this show
there's a couple of these seeing balls
just like the Rings
they honestly could like at least give
them a couple more of those man
a crown
huh
what
a little piece of [\h__\h]
oh oh what what
she wants she wants him
that was us I need someone to look at me
with those eyes
oh man why are all the the leaders such
idiots
[Laughter]
okay he just really reminded me of
biblong
foreign
qualities
can we overthrow this dude
hmm
you're writing that down
of proverb rock paper scissors
[Music]
I want to marry her she's pretty
she she's
She's a Beauty
wait why is she is she sussing him now
what
I was out of nowhere is it because of
that
what she said what he said what the [\h__\h]
why
so I am bend
um
you're late I was I was tangenting for
the first half hour and you're late
but there's DVR you can go back in time
and still watch now
me no understand though
foreign
whoa
oh
they fixed his back he can finally stand
straight
that was pretty epic though
this is pretty cool because you know
I've I would have never known about
these people by only watching The Hobbit
and
Lord of the Rings
oh there's a hard foot there oh [\h__\h] oh
they're not in the books
yeah I want to learn more about it
though
hoot
that was a hurtful wasn't it
that's not a real verb
I knew it
good try though
um
is this also like the the rise and
creation of Sauron is is that any of
that in the books
what
wait what there's two what
all of the stars in the books okay okay
oh
oh you look so gucky you shouldn't have
been here
oh
killer
oh that's him that's him
and he's gonna
he's gonna save her because even though
he's evil he really bonded with the girl
don't you hate it when someone says calm
yourself it just makes you even more
less calm
to be honest I I when when the Salomon
and gandal played that Showdown on the
on the big tower
these kind of movements they look so
ridiculous to me
it's like oh I'm turning you 60 degrees
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
foreign
so much going on
this is probably what
never mind I'm getting confused again
I thought it was Saruman
them up because they have such similar
names
[\h__\h] our foots
oh my God
oh
[Music]
Henry I'm spitting [\h__\h] you
I caught us earlier
you guys are idiots
look
the best advice given in this show
give up already on him
oh my God
no he's really not
how are all of them still alive
as if it was this difficult to kill a
fake Hobbit
oh
okay
Sauron Redemption Arc let's go
Redemption before even becoming
something that you have to redeem
wow Sarah my ocean
wait he's not someone
oh man I don't know
like
hey
told you you shouldn't have been telling
me anything
oh
oh but why didn't they think like they
were so certain like and now they're
wrong where did they get their certain
list from them to begin with
um
I mean he could still be Sauron
you know a cute child can always make
you think you're good
eventually maybe he's still like
turning bad
I don't know
moths are gandal for later
all right we're still got a lot of show
left that's true maybe a second season
even with all the criticism they can't
just end it there after one season after
all this big commitments they took upon
themselves
oh
no this is not Netflix we're talking
about Amazon here
Netflix may be doing [\h__\h] like that but
you know
I don't see Amazon doing that
they're stubborn
ah see Five Seasons locked in there we
go
I'm excited about that as I said before
I'm happy about any kind of
Tolkien related content being turned
into a movie whether or not it's
good or bad well
it's not the worst thing okay
anything is better than nothing to me
[Music]
oh wait
um why do I keep on
crashing today
by the way the snack I have for today
I was inspired to buy it by the French
snack box
the prince cookies with the chocolate
inside but I have a special version
it's more hazelnut apparently
really like those as a kid
oh yeah that's really naughty
foreign
Mr chant I only have eight episodes
I want more
hmm
foreign
next season Maybe
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] deserving dead
hmm
what
what are we seeing Oh different flags oh
did they change
the ownership
oh no they're morning
that's what the flags are for
oopsie
oh I mean that was to be expected
people die when they die
oh
wise
hmm
no
tttors
yeah it has to happen naturally
I just wanted to be asked out
since
he wants to be romanced properly hmm
oh
hmm
a ring
a ring is round like a crown
[\h__\h]
well collateral you kind of forced it on
to him
that is true
okay I'm gonna be real mad at the person
in the chat
in the beginning
oh [\h__\h]
hmm
it was really good faking to be good
oh
mm-hmm
I'm sorry
I'm very picky with faces okay for the
particular roles
what
thank you
yes totally
trust me bro
look that's creepy so creepy so creepy
so creepy so creepy
[Music]
sunrise
why is he even trying to convince her
if he's so powerful
no need for that
what is this [\h__\h] romance worth
what
okay honestly it would be kind of a cool
second timeline
and evil queen galatriel
hot
oh [\h__\h] she's she's been successfully
gasoline
it's kind of weirding me out because
Sovereign for me is just this thing in
the
glass ball
but now it's like
he's a human with feelings
so weird yeah to me it was always just
an eye
oh [\h__\h]
yeah oh my God
yeah I mean it's probably an act too
yeah but even then you know it's
weirding me out right now
it doesn't fit him but look it's
probably not really like his real
identity
oh man
yeah I understand he had a
human form
that's okay that's all right
oh
not a whole chat
where the [\h__\h] did the other dude go
what do you see
oh wait now it makes so much sense that
they're making the ring but didn't they
make several Rings not only two they
made like what six
afraid for the elves uh they made their
own couple ones and then the others made
their own
12.
gone with the Rings
[Laughter]
okay have fun at work
one made by Sauron
foreign
[Music]
oh I I got some Shivers now
the free onion rings
don't ruin it
oh it's exciting
Gandalf is this you
I thought they couldn't have Gandalf in
in the show
face down
is that is
big riddles we're probably not gonna
who is that I'm not even gonna know
the season
it could also be the
the forest one
I guess
that sounds very kind of like doll
that sounds like something he would say
it sounds so cute
[Music]
oh
he does look kind of like summer mom
maybe but I mean that could be a
coincident I don't know
yes Iron Man was good before I guess
yeah
they can't have Gandalf in the show
maybe they can have Saruman and this is
Cyberman when he was so good
and within those five seasons we will
see how he
how he
turns into an evil one
[Music]
maybe they call him
foreign
easy work around
Saruman didn't like Hobbits much so I
think it's kind of
these aren't Harvard still
kidding to me they're Hobbits
foreign
[Music]
because I think if I remember correctly
my mom told me that you can only use
whatever what's in the footnotes and
Gandalf was never in the footnotes I
think
supposedly
was never mentioned into footnotes
but I might be wrong maybe he was
mentioned at some point
oh
no no no
Hobbits are always so wholesome man
oh
exciting for excited for her Adventure
in the future
oh this could just be like
foreshadowing thoughts
she's like a female Frodo
Maybe
and this is the female soundwise
[Music]
is she joining yeah you tell me she's
joining
I'm gonna cry
please join
this is such a frodo-some interaction
oh
Joy no
no this is farewell
no ah
[Music]
two Hobbits
oh
this is so sweet he's so sweet I thought
he was evil
iron she I feel like she said Iron
oh
all right
what
what they're so sweet
they're so cute
is that something kind of said
is that something he's
[Music]
making
he's the he's the one who shall not be
named but he's there nonetheless because
how can you do a show
without Gandalf flag nag sorry flag nag
I was gonna say it sounds like something
he would say I forgot he said it
oh man
see see this is not so bad right this
show ain't so bad maybe it had a rough
start but it ain't so bad
you just have to open your heart
right
I'm enjoying it
mm-hmm
[Music]
that looks like lasaga fresh out of the
oven
hot hot
it's it's things like these though my
fingers makes it worth watching like you
see the creation of the Rings
you see the creation of Mordor
stuff like that
the the first time they find this or
stuff like that yeah
or just read the books well I don't
wanna oh my God
that looks like
ironically
funny
yeah she didn't tell them the gym
ironic
all right all right all right all right
what what
that's not a ring
I'm shaping it now
oh
mama
whoa whoa what what
ah
why did he come here anyway
why was he so troubled
oh
drama llama
ah the plastic worries um
well
she looks
a bit evil
oh pretty
what
oh is she not Galadriel
is she shape-shifting is he
shape-shifting
and she secretly made a her own one he
secretly made his own one
in this process but then why would he be
so kind to help them make
the free ones for them
I guess to keep up the
the facade
nah
oh
there you go okay okay hmm
it doesn't look like
he would be Sauron
[Music]
oh
listen listen
who was that
Sauron
and we're going to find them
oh
I felt really proud you know like in
school when you know the answer and you
shout it out before anyone else does
ah season two preview please
season to approvia please please
please I beg you no
no
no no no
it sends me to a show called the
peripheral [\h__\h] you
hey
oh they have like
wow I didn't see this before because I I
always watched it on the TV and I didn't
see that they had like if you scroll
down if you're on the PC
they have
what 23 weeks of file why because they
mentioned the ring 23 times
you got real time or you should watch it
I I know that one is also you know known
for being not as good as the books but
you know
well if you scroll down you see you see
some info about the characters and the
places
oh the second age the second age began
after the downfall of morgov the
original Dark Lord oh this is
interesting the early part of the second
age is a time of relative peace
allowing kingdoms of elves dwarves and
men to grow and flourish as the wars of
the first age become a distant memory
wow
oh elves the firstborn of All Peoples
Peoples English Toko
all elves are Immortal and do not
anxious humans do though in times of War
they may still be killed
oh yeah many of the High Elves the elves
who lived in valinor in the first age
long to return to the home they left
behind but feel it is their duty to
remain in Middle Earth to protect its
Realms on people's peoples
uh-huh
oh
I want more
I want more oh oh oh oh some info Okay
galadra Legendary Alpha Warrior the
command of the northern Army is far from
the wise a thorough Lady of Lori and she
will one day become spoiler this much
younger Galadriel is a headstrong and
Relentless and obsessed with hunting an
elusive evil
lumenorians queen regent Muriel oh
there's like info about all of them
I want to read this one her aging father
still officially holds the scepter of
the island realm numenor but queen
regent Marielle is its acting rule by
the way stop
though the kingdom is at the height of
his wealth and power Muriel Bears the
burden of a terrible secret that looms
over her entire people
ah
guys uh so
so
let me make a poll
did you enjoy this episode don't be
don't be a sooner a piece of [\h__\h] you
know I think some people just they're so
set in their mind that they don't want
to like something that they will not
accept something is okay
yes no
[Music]
um
here I make a poll for you
not enough yeah what the [\h__\h]
not enough dwarfs at all but I'm I'm
sure they will play a bigger role in the
coming seasons
um
tell me what you think
oh
okay
oh come on Mama
I'm asking for this episode in
particular okay not like the entire
season I think this episode was really
good
I mean you have to make the last episode
you have to
I only listen to a lot of options
could use more drugs
okay so have good moments um I'm like I
think it made me really hype about
more
and did a great job at that
and holy [\h__\h] thank God I did not have
to see that human lady again she wasn't
in this episode at all and I said I
don't really like her
I mean she's nice and all but yeah don't
like her
she's boring
her Romans with the elf don't give a
[\h__\h] about it
she's she's too pretty
pretty
um
and her plot armor is too strong she
should be dead by now
oh
needs more giant eagles
oh I have to oh no I have to restart
once again
oh
Mary Sue oh that's an interesting way to
put it
yeah a lot of death fake outs yeah yeah
yeah that's true needs more dragons oh
wait yeah at the end of the last episode
remember where they they showed a really
short like one or two second scene with
was that a dialogue
wasn't there some I'm trying to remember
something like Gandalf saying that he
fought a dialogue
now that makes even more sense if that
was the case if I'm not mixing up things
right
didn't kind of fight one
yeah yeah
so that might be oh there might be a
thing they're going for like in the
later seasons
oh
read the books for the love of God stop
being such a [\h__\h] to people who don't
read books but you know what you know
what the other day the other day because
my mom gave me the first book I was like
I held the book in my hands and I took
it
with me with the plan to read it
to us I was going to a specific Place
otherwise why what's with the connection
today oh
and then and then I I
didn't read it but I was about to read
this okay I was so close
and now I would prefer to just listen to
an audiobook To be honest I might do
that I'm like really hyped up now
I'm so hyped up
I'm so hyped the problem is like you
know I think I think I think audiobooks
would be better for me in this case
especially because I know that a lot of
the Rings books are really difficult in
terms of language
um and and I already have problems with
like focusing on books when I when I
read lines that sometimes I have to read
the same line like five times until
like my my brain registers what I just
saw
no they're not difficult yes they are I
don't know what the hell you're trying
to tell me but at least in German they
are and in English they would be even
more difficult for me since it's not my
my first language
fantasy speak is always difficult
um
no the ones you gave me is the German
one I think is it well I didn't pay I
didn't look so closely
no it's German it's German it's a German
one yeah yeah pretty sure
um
yeah yeah Hobbit I know Hobbit is easy I
know I know
Lord of the Rings is a different story
I wonder if my mom watched this last
episode already
she's she doesn't like the show but you
know I feel like she's also sundara and
can't help herself
yeah yeah yeah yeah
that is true golden Umi
that is true typhen thank you
you guys are based
all right let me um turn on some bgm uh
stop moving again what's going on today
is it because I played around yesterday
with my
things
to set up froggy Wawa
you guys are gonna love frank Yara so
much by the way
um
you cannot love
[Music]
I love her I want to be froggy wama
forever
oh wait
oopsie thank God you didn't hear that
um oh wait I need to why am I looking in
here audio stock
[Music]
at this one maybe this one
all right all right
all right
[Music]
so I I will give this episode a 10 out
of 10. uh or 9.5 out of ten and I will
give the show in general because I'm a
kind-hearted spirit and merciful and the
best I'll give the the whole show
um
as a whole
I'm giving you an 8 out of ten and I
know you guys are gonna be like oh well
what has no taste
she's stupid I don't give a [\h__\h]
I'm gonna give a [\h__\h]
I'm happy with it
most of you saying seven out of ten
that's nice
I'm surprised
three out of 10.
open your heart
this is so mean through the tennis mean
you just wanna be grumpy
[Music]
you guys gotta give it a chance maybe
we'll take the criticism too hard and
make next season better for you
complain
Club playing beetles I don't know what
to say
that retrospca
oh come on
[Music]
hey if you're so mean I'm not gonna
write super chats hmm yeah
it's you know
[Music]
it doesn't mean
yeah
I think so too velocity Pablo it's
tough out there man and Lord of the
Rings has so many fans that are really
really really critical
[Music]
since he's in the movies huh
well maybe maybe he's really not dead
he'll just come back you know I've seen
it done in shows many times before
someone is fought to be dead but comes
back after like 20 episodes or so and
like bamboozle I'm alive
because the books were already great so
why we rant tons of plot elements that
clash with one another because
because more from the books that they
would have gotten the rights of books
I mean you're you're just like asking
for something that was impossible to
them anyway
of course it would have been great if
they followed more you know accordingly
to the books I guess but then like
I don't know we I guess we can fight
about this endlessly but I don't wanna I
don't want this as I said to be ruined
for me
I want to enjoy it
um
well sometimes about money Daisy
sometimes
because you just don't want to sell
something and that's okay
I'm sure they they already paid a [\h__\h]
ton of money for the footnotes so they
probably offered a [\h__\h] ton of money for
the books too
[Music]
um
yeah it's pointless it really is
pointless
don't ruin it with me you can you can be
mad at the show okay but don't ruin it
for me
oh
[Music]
okay
my room is absolutely Darkness
just like
sauron's heart so let me turn on
the light real quick
maybe the best thing about
today's stream for all the the rings of
power haters was my
my my my 30 minutes of
chit chat in the beginning
[Laughter]
with this chonkers rated chunkers didn't
watch
the chunkers writes everything 10 out of
10 because she's cute and she's happy
and she's um
she's a little little cutie patootie
bucket
you guys are so
vehicle some of you
ah
gosh
can't take it I'm gonna rinse up a
chance I'm gonna ignore all the cynical
statements
ignore it
I know
Daddy
okay uh I read this whole talks of
Bachata thing so I gotta read what the
golf
what what the golf
[Music]
that was fun that was a fun stream
uh so let's get rid of this we're just
gonna stay in here
reading
[Music]
at a time
ignorance is bliss yeah
and
not being cynical as Bliss
oh wait what am I putting this up
[Music]
foreign
if you're saying you didn't have fun
watching that with me
I said this on Twitter but one reason
why I wanted to watch it together is
because
we
we have a special history watching
Lord of the Rings and to have it
together
with the members and it's let you know
you guys always say oh that was so good
that was so good once you know the Rings
together
and then there's something new like that
and I'm like okay let's watch it
together and y'all are like me
I liked you geeking out thank you I want
to talk more about it I I there's
there's so many question marks in my
head but maybe
the more I ask the more question marks I
get
[Music]
um
questions over questions
yeah not all of you
some of you are good chickens
it's hard to live up to that it's true
yeah that is true very true
have you seen Twitter a few hours ago no
I mean yeah but like what exactly are
you uh
hoping for me to see
[Music]
I was dragging so much better
hmm
I can
maybe agree with it being better but to
be honest like
uh
I I
um
this is difficult for me because
I what I like more about rings of power
one thing is
um there's not like it's more
bright in terms of you know not so much
like
intercourse
[Laughter]
and you know I don't know like it has
more wholesome moments and all that and
uh
I enjoyed that and then one more thing
is I guess
it's just so high but the house of the
Dragon kind of has this too I guess but
it's hype to see uh
characters that you know from like the
prequel sequel or whatever
sequel um
[Music]
so when you know that the base of what
you're watching is your favorite movie
Lord of the Rings
then
it just adds so many extra points
to the product
um
I feel like Lord of the Rings and Hobbit
and rings of power
are more
the style of story
and the style of Storytelling
that I like
but I also really love Game of Thrones
and House of dragon
but House of dragons so far
wow I really enjoy it okay I'm gonna get
like
Stones thrown at me probably and
tomatoes and [\h__\h] but honestly I might
I might have to say I enjoyed doing some
power
why
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh
[\h__\h] but do you understand where I'm
coming from
Percy oh oh hot day oh yeah unpopular
opinion oh [\h__\h]
like even if we talk about it
objectively the house of the Dragon was
maybe
better objectively in terms of I don't
know following its origin story also I
don't know
in terms of like story
I I I still I don't know and Vibes
there were also many things I didn't
agree with and rings of power but you
know
oh I'm glad there's at least three
people in the chat who kind of agree
with me holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
um yeah I like high fantasy stuff but
House of the Dragon is kind of high
fantasy too no
more of my type of fantasy no I guess
you guys do see a difference there
that's nice
chilled for the tomatoes thank you
dark friend ah
with this Dark Fantasy and high fantasy
I've never heard of those terms before
[Music]
oh I was trying to focus more on
pullings and stuff happening while rings
of power had like a little mystery um
and still as I said I think the chime
one big charm is um
you know the the fact that you know now
Gandalf isn't there like holy [\h__\h]
Gandalf is in there guys kind of isn't
there are you listening God that isn't
there
oh and it works I love the dwarves
I noticed something we're gone sorry
flat nug flat nuggets in there
um
hmm
yeah how to train us not have Flags
[Laughter]
oh
no but I I like both very very much both
shows are
they made
this season for me very enjoyable every
week I was looking forward to those
episodes
so excitedly
um
House of the Dragon Mall wings of power
more
seconds
but now he's now he would be great or
maybe he's not he's not even he's
probably transparent right now
at the moment he might be transparent
oh I guess he's brown now okay never
mind
no no no and the last episode he passed
that he passed the hobo stage
kind of the unwashed is that a title he
actually had
what do you feel about the new Pokemon
tradition I like it I mean because it's
a frog
simply because it's a frog I like it
no
[Music]
fluke
well it's not the grimy
very simple design simple yeah guys
compared to some over-designed Pokemons
in the past
um games I guess so yeah
yeah it's funny how he has four eyes
froggy Wawa also has four eyes if you
think about it two fake ones and two
real ones whoa
kind of The Hobbit
the whole boat
[Music]
huh
I mean I
changed some things yesterday but I also
changed them back to its already origin
I thought well
I have to keep on restarting the thing
oh wow
a snail snatcher what
what
guys I'm so excited to show you froggy
Wawa I'm so excited I'm
I'm sad oh yeah wait if I forget I
wanted to ask one thing
[Music]
ah
okay
I'm excited for frog quick ah I really
have to hold back to show you too much
yesterday but I showed you the teaser
did you guys watch your little teaser on
Twitter
foreign
[Music]
she's so smart that wasn't even her most
smug face
I haven't even smugged her face for her
that was basically just her Santa face
she can get smarter than that
yeah yeah
although her whole existence is smug on
its own
she's like
solidified smugness
[Music]
yes smack is off the charts
yeah she frogging oh loud she frogging
originally that was when I wrote in my
tweet oh loved she frogging
but then I I wondered if people are
gonna get the reference so then I
changed into onyo she's frogging like oh
no she's morbing
but originally it was like oh Lord keep
coming kind of kind of phrase but both
works really wonderful
well the end you sentences with Kenna
maybe not as much as peculus Senpai
answer was sentences ends her sentences
with pickle but I might
I might be quacking
here and there yes
Maybe
maybe I'll take the opportunity
clock
kettle
oh that would make it easier do you see
good idea
but I want that um probably the flow the
flow wouldn't be so natural though
if I always had to push a button
um
I'm probably about to say it myself
hmm
I think in German a frog
when you write down the sound he makes
I think we also say quack though
quack for
for
both duck and frog
yeah I think so in German we
what what am I wait
and they're masked clock
for smart
clock
[Music]
oh yeah
yeah
did you ever watch Game of Thrones of
course I did
[Music]
grab
oh my God I can say that now holy [\h__\h]
[Applause]
ah all right all right let's learn some
super chants
for the pinky your whole talk is awesome
I'm very proud of you I think you're
doing a wonderful job by being the
bridge between fandoms you also not just
host but also camera woman
live translator and script rata you're
very professional and awesome
yeah this time I didn't prepare a
close-up
um it was too much to set up but I had a
I had a
I had a far up
not not a close-up but a far up
the next time I might add a close-up as
well so we have several different
views and I know people liked the
close-up previously I think I think
people liked it a white shot yeah
the whole studio yeah I showed it in the
beginning and then I forgot I thought it
wasn't good to show it most of the time
so at the end I showed it again and
people who came into the stream
somewhere in the middle they were like
mind blown like hey yo what what just
happened why did what what's this what
I like the brain explosion I that gave
that that that gave to people
yeah it's cool to see everything
together
and if you liked the chicken pattern
seafoam boy uploaded the chicken pattern
on Twitter separately
if you want to look at it it's so
artistic
and uh a video that goes through the
whole studio kind of
mm-hmm
Patsy Duncan so around our donation for
the pinky
uh starting in January if all goes well
I'll be attending a local Culinary
Academy oh to become a professional chef
oh
my passion for food was always there but
it took you to reignite it after so many
years what really
I'm glad you always had a passion for it
so thanks for being my inspiration Kiara
I hope someday I can truly impress you
and others with my skills food brings
together people just like you brought
kfb together in the end that's what I
want to do make people happy oh
I don't know what you've been doing
until now but I'm happy you found
something that you feel passionate about
now that's really important and I think
that will drive you
to be
very successful with it
um I'm very happy with it
that's really nice
yeah good luck good fun
enjoy do your best
and send me some food
[Music]
what are you doing here from
bro why why why thank you I'm sending
you this now because starting next year
I'm 80 sure I'll be working from the
office again
oh that's next here why would you tell
me such sad news now
you're saying goodbye to me
profile
pray for you little [\h__\h] you're not
leaving me right
[Music]
but no not even not now I mean like next
year you're gonna still watch me
right
[Music]
what do you mean you'll try of course
you will
from what happens maybe you can't watch
everything but you definitely still can
watch me a little bit
hmm
I experienced huh wait thank you for
wait wait wait where was I oh yeah thank
you for creating such a wonderful
community and thank you for helping me
get out myself more I experienced in
almost two years more than I could have
ever imagined
following you and supporting such an
outstanding Phoenix made me really proud
and more than happy I remember when I
clicked the comment member button you
were playing Mario Kart in your cursed
in German that was the moment I thought
to myself oh my gosh she's the one
I then started to watch Vlogs and fell
deeper and deeper into the hole because
you had captivated me with your funny
but also very honest way you can still
give you you gave and still give me a
reason every day to look forward to the
day after the hard work that you are
there to cheer me up again I hope so
much that we also enrich you days like
you do for us there's nothing
um we want more than for you to stay
healthy and happy we love you my one and
only Oshi thank you for everything
that's a bit or like to send you this
rainbow but I'm not sure if I'll be able
to send it later
me
no what the hell
bathroom
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
profile
you still have to watch me after you get
that job
it's not like you can't watch me at all
anymore
you so no need to say it like this
I'm gonna be
very sad and cry
[Music]
hmm
find a way to stream right straight into
her brain
[Music]
fro fro you made me stop moving
why
[Music]
yeah weekend we can you have time on the
weekend
or do you have to work seven days a week
bro
no no no
no no no no
no no why you why you no watch YouTuber
V2 but why
[Music]
why YouTuber
right
[Music]
oh why
I have no one's reachable or 24 7.
wow why no why not watch during work
why work why work at all
watch watch vegetable
s
you know this is not a request it's a
threat you know that right
awesome thank you for the pinkies it's
Thanksgiving in Canada and I'm thankful
for chihuahua and kfp for making this
year so great
thank you Jackson I hope your
Thanksgiving was lovely I've never
celebrated Thanksgiving before but it
sure sounds nice
[Music]
hope you had a good time thank you for
sharing your happiness with me
a loving Fred yeah
I use many words when few do so true so
true
I need money to survive
no you need kiwawa to survive
um
is it not true
do you
thank you I'll give us home food and
water well that's literally kfp for you
ah
MK 203 thank you for the pinky so now
that you have broadened Your Horizon and
tested out a variety of different games
what would you say is your stands on a
game like undertale it actually fits
really well into the spooktober oh the
game has skeletons
on the channel uh I don't know no
particular stance
it's not not that I ruled it out for
um it to be streamed on my channel
completely
um
but I wasn't into the mood of playing it
or inspired to play it
recently or anytime soon
at some point perhaps maybe
a little overrated good but overrated I
can imagine that
[Music]
um
I don't know
um well next week will be frog week and
then the week after
I I will try to get some
on theme streams but
I don't want to force myself to play
really really really terrifying horror
games so it will be mostly like Luigi's
Mansion and a little nightmares too I
think because we still have little
nightmares too
to be played
and I don't know what else to be honest
[Music]
ah
I have one collab with Dana planned
and also
um tomorrow
you know tomorrow I'm playing uh the the
cooking game
um but
ume was like Hey does anyone know anyone
want to play OverWatch 2 and uh I was
like
yeah if if you play it during a time
that's okay for me then I wouldn't I
wouldn't I kind of want to join maybe I
got into it because of
um I I would suck and I would drag you
down but if that's okay then I'll I'll
join and she was like yeah okay well I
can play early
um tell us the time mume hasn't yet oh I
think we're starting at 10 p.m my time
so we have cooking game in the early day
and then shooting game in the later day
are you streaming your POV oh that's a
good question
will I stream my POV
maybe not
I might not
but you'll hear me on moment's Channel
and maybe you'll even
um see me moving on women's Channel
yeah actually so I guess a little bit
less pressure Maybe
oh I can if I'm not streaming I can
focus a bit more on learning the game
and also I think I'm not the only one
participating I think one or two other
girls might be joining Maybe
so
then I don't have to talk so much and I
can try try to instead of entertaining
try killing
[Music]
um
or the other two I'm not sure because
maybe maybe so I'm not gonna say
anything
[Music]
foreign
but I'm happy I'm happy then
um
you know
they're they're doing it in my time zone
kind of like you know often I I don't
want to you know I understand they want
to stream during prime time so you know
often when the girls are like hey I want
to play this and that
um that I don't even say anything
because I know who they want to play in
their time zone and I'm just gonna
ruin it the yeah
um like gonna make everything
complicated you know
especially
like for example gouda has a set
time slot
like for two years now she always
streams at the same time right mostly
so
[Music]
yeah I don't think she wants to really
change that up to stream like four or
five hours earlier if if it's something
that she's planning if she if she joins
a a project that someone else initiated
okay but if she initiates it then I
understand that she wants to stream
during her usual time slot it's just you
know tradition
um
yeah sometimes sometimes she makes
exceptions but you know I don't you know
you know it just makes things
complicated so
yeah yeah yeah but this time this time
you know I was the first to answer mume
so I I got
um I took the opportunity to ask for an
early time slot and honestly it's a
weekend so what the hell 2 pm EST you
guys said is not not bad I would say on
the weekend
foreign
[Music]
yeah she really seems to want to play
but I haven't tried OverWatch 2 yet
is it like really different from
OverWatch one will I be okay I mean I
wasn't really okay in OverWatch one
but
it's exactly the same okay cool
same damn game okay
okay is it the same characters do they
still have the cute Dorito girl
same but less players oh like a smaller
team
five from six
yes the real girl is still in there
honestly why did they make a new game
same characters and just a team that's
one member smaller what
what
there's a new cute healer girl I may
like oh
everyone's asking
[Music]
but at least surely all all maps are new
right they have to keep the same
characters I understand that because you
know how can you kick out Diva she's so
popular
without her it's not OverWatch
some new maps old and new
both maps are the same
[Music]
what I mean okay I really don't have
much to do with OverWatch I played once
so I'm I really
I I have I don't care I'm not
complaining really but if I imagine
people who played a lot and are
OverWatch fans and I really wonder how
mad these people are
and how confused
but now it's free right isn't it on it
wasn't OverWatch one
uh
not free and then this one is free
I guess that's at least a big good thing
actually for newcomers I still had to
pay though
terrible timing
should have started my OverWatch Arc now
not back then
if you own 123 oh
oh if you just now join it's still not
free really oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh
[Music]
I have all the characters
huh
oh the characters from OverWatch one
join
The Roaster in OverWatch 2. if you had
OverWatch one
never had OverWatch one
then you don't have diva
[Music]
oh
oh I stopped in a in a perfect face
expression
[Music]
interesting well I don't really care you
know I'm not
deep into the OverWatch
fandom so whatever
ah where was I here
in transport a type thank you Cyrus
Duncan poison fangs monkey thank you for
listening to do you thank you
Super Snake Mario thank you for the red
super chat hi Canada today is my
birthday and I can't think of a better
way to celebrate than spending some time
with my dear ushi I'm glad to be here
with you today oh this was my first time
off really calling you my ownership oh
now I feel a little embarrassed and look
at me I'm shy oh no are you here in the
chat
Super Snake Mario you here
happy belated birthday
happy belated birthday to you happy
belated birthday to you happy belated
birthday Super Snake Mario happy belated
birthday to you
it would probably be even more belated
because you don't seem to be here so the
time you listen to this if you listen to
this it'll be even later
but congratulations
yeah I hope you enjoyed your birthday
and thank you for calling me your Aussie
I like hearing that thank you so much I
wish you all the best
and don't be shy don't be embarrassed be
proud be a proud kfp the p and kfp
stands for proud
and Phoenix
and so many other things
yeah
thank you for being here thank you soon
proud Nicks
proud Phoenix yes yes that's me
it's me that's me doesn't mean that's me
so a case for you super snake Mario
oh all right
um
gonna end the pole because I feel like
13 percent
a 16 is not fair I feel like you guys
are [\h__\h] with me the 16 I understand
maybe five or ten percent or sixteen
percent these people
episode was not so bad
anyway
whatever
kfp visuals
to the usual room
yeah this episode was good yeah people
who didn't watch probably voted too
salty people
I'm watching you you know that
[Music]
wasn't working I couldn't watch it
okay okay well that you got me there oh
that makes a lot of sense that's why you
didn't enjoy it because you didn't watch
it at all
okay that makes sense
of that one ship is still sailing
it was never a ship to begin with was
just
one piece of wood in the middle of the
ocean
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] they
ah
if I ever re-watch this show now with
the knowledge that that's Sauron
I will be looking at it so differently
holy [\h__\h]
damn
[Music]
to a room you can't vote if you didn't
watch it
you probably just wanted the pole to go
away right so that it's not a bother in
the chat huh
yeah oh and you want to see the results
yeah yeah even if you didn't watch it
you still want to see the results
absolutely this is just proof this is
literally proof that the pole was rigged
cannot believe anything
never believe
[Music]
in Game of Thrones fans
ah
recount
[Laughter]
no no recap burn it all burn it all
there's no such things as votes and
poles
no
I'm currently happens
thank you soon Happy Thanksgiving to you
too
not a portable donkey Channel thank you
soon
come on
oh man
remember in this stream when I talked
about that German TV host who made up
all these fun TV shows with celebrities
one more thing they did was
um what do you call that sport in
English
um you know the the one where like can
can be alone but also can be with four
four people or so I think
um
wait
uh what what oh walk racing okay
large metal pan
IC
get like a frozen bobsleigh
track
and and on top of that you slide
and really fast speed
wait I'm so confused
originally
I'm so confused did he make up a sport
what
[Music]
they're they're doing it
live
with literal frying pans
okay okay you know those those two half
tube looking things with uh frozen ice
you know yeah yeah yeah and then you do
you know you know where that famous
video was filmed where where the Lady or
the dude was it a dude he squats and his
pants rip apart
so that sport but with like kind of
frying pans and celebrities that's
another one another show that this dude
came up with and was the host of
[Music]
it's called
VM W okay w m w o k w m VOC VM VM is
foreign
world world championship
hmm
yes yes yes
he's like he's like the Elia Watson of
German TV
or he used to be
yeah that's such a good example oh my
God I'm a genius
Nene diesel dancing for the rest of a
chat hi little devil kiwab on today's my
birthday in my time zone it's my second
birthday to spend time with you and kfb
always fun to be here and thank you for
being my sunshine for these two years
foreign
[Music]
microphone but she's requesting ASMR
you're good
yes yes
hi
there you go
and happy belated birthday to you too
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday to you yeah yeah
you're welcome yeah
you can balance work with kiwawa
yes
please continue supporting kiwawa don't
leave me otherwise I'll cry
please continue thank you love you
excuse me
correcting thank you for Pinky really
love the ending part of the karaoke
oh oh well I love the whole thing really
looking forward to the next ketoka
already oh thank you that's so sweet
I'm glad you enjoyed it I have a good
time too I sang my heart out for you
guys so
yeah you better you better be enjoying
it
oh
interesting uh thank you so much Carlos
hopefully the next yeah okay won't be
too far apart
uh
someone got
um
this guy asked a question in Japanese in
a super chat but I don't know if he's
here
probably won't hear the answer
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
way too long like there was so much Chit
Chat blue so much conversation
uh that I was like guys how are you
gonna cut this that's right don't cut it
give us more than usual normally I think
it's like half an hour
they should make it a full hour
and then they were like we'll take it uh
to consideration
hopefully they're not only considering
because I feel like honestly otherwise
they really would have problems cutting
this thing I I don't see how you could
cut it down to half an hour
it's not realistic
can't upload it on my channel no no no
no no no no no no
no no
I didn't record it either
[Music]
I guess honestly that would be a fun
idea though to upload the uncut thing
I guess but nah
no no I would lose
its specialness
[Music]
yeah I'm the host I was nervous about it
but I think it went quite well I I
I was honored to be the host
um but I felt more pressured than usual
I feel I think until now all of these
official programs that I've been part of
it was always someone else being the
host so this was the first time that I
was the host for something
in an official program
hmm
I was quite
pressuring but it was an honor hmm
wouldn't mind doing more like that or
just generally be more in those programs
it's always a pleasure always a pleasure
I always have fun doing it and I always
like seeing the results they have like
really good editing stuff and really
good thumbnail making stuff their
thumbnails are so good man
yeah I like like the things they kind of
came up with for udobasho specifically
like even for each Corner they made a
specific logo for each Corner they put
so much work into it
the logo they made for it all the kfp
corner I like that one and the one they
made for Dana's corner I really like
that one too
and and then they you know they make all
the graphics for the games and all that
damn
they put so much work into it oh
not only for this program but generally
for all all of the official program
shows yeah there's a lot of
passion in there
um
yeah it's definitely Japanese style of
editing
but I like that that's what I really
like
about it
um
[Music]
apparently I'm the only whole life that
we're streaming right now it's not
really so
probably and members starting like a
couple hours one or two free normally
normally Inna would start streaming now
but in a chandoko
I'm Ahmed deprived Yama has been busy
I've been having trouble getting a hold
of Amit too
me too man but it's okay she's busy I'm
not mad or anything
oh it's temples
streaming on Twitch I see it right now
on the
whole life schedule website
oh wait maybe they're done already it's
only like two hours this is the span of
two hours oh they still are
but besides that I guess on YouTube I'm
the only one
that's on YouTube
[Music]
me
I'm dominating YouTube
what
wait no I mean I mean if you're talking
about the whole life uh girls only but
apparently Estelle from Hollow starts
also still streaming also doing a really
long stream apparently apparently
foreign
you took dominance I am dominating on
YouTube
you have all streams open right now and
now it's not a challenge
I'm watching all whole live girls at the
same time right now it's not much of a
flex at this time
[Music]
weird flex but okay
this was random cool fans you know what
I've noticed couple fans I love Google's
fans are like the people who always uh
ask about come to Brazil
just randomly come in here and they're
like come to Brazil but no they're like
collab of Cobble and Cobble this and
Cobble dad
I'm not mad or so it's funny to me
it's just so Random so out of nowhere
like no one no one was talking about
Kobo
but okay okay chillax okay I'm gonna I'm
gonna ask who for collab okay collab
with Brazil clap of Brazil live in
Cobalt what no we're gonna happen
[Laughter]
let's let's bring Coco to Brazil
uh
[Laughter]
yeah I don't know
um now I want to do a cover with Kobo
but uh
you know I told her that I'm I have to
work on an album so I won't be able to
really
[Applause]
take the lead on this one maybe because
now I'm working on a cover and then I
want to really focus on the album so I
told her that I told her if she she
really wants to she says she wants to
and I told her then she might have to
take the lead on that one
um but yeah so far I haven't heard
anything so probably I I have to take
the lead
yeah
nice so nicer
oh
I'm getting something special for froggy
Wawa made right now
froggy Wawa keeps on getting better and
better
I'm unleashing her true and full
potential at the moment
fans
no it's I know she got deceiving now but
this is we're talking about you know
like two months ago or so
started talking about this like one or
two months ago way before she got this
evening
it's okay though I don't think she's
um
worked on a collab
song cover before has she
so
if it's her first one I understand that
it's hard to take responsibility
[Music]
why is frogada so smart because she
knows she's better than you
oh my God the Frog inside of me is
speaking
she's speaking I can't hold her back
anymore I'm becoming a smoker and
smugger and Frogger and Frogger oh no oh
god oh
the transition is starting it's happened
ah
is she better than biyama well she can
eat her so yes
but not really
in reality she's deeply in love with
biamin
there's things that froggy Wawa can do
that even I can't do many things
actually
many things she's already Superior to me
in so many ways
[Music]
it's almost sad
it's gonna throw you out of the push-ups
now
I mean
she doesn't have to frog squats that's
their natural life stance
um Slavic fellow
duncastron 5000.
foreign
[Music]
noises I think we would have gotten
there eventually
um
I don't think so
I don't think I could have hidden that
forever
[Music]
thank you for the clap clap thank you
I'm gonna read the wrongs from
uh the snack box
there you go all right I'm gonna read um
everything in French now
you think I'm joking
um
[Music]
I
understood everything
perfectly
cool
[Music]
ing what
wait wait wait wait wait
looking for the top Mercy bookoo
[Music]
for the pink Super Chat
Mercy look who's not German what the
[\h__\h] oh oh you're jokingly like hinting
to Kobo aren't ya Orange
stop confusing me
salute I'm super hyped for this French
snack box here's my predictions oh this
person seems to be French karambara
Pepito curly and maybe something from
Berlin
I don't think we had any of that did we
have any
of would be funny if they put a tattoo
what's that also can I have a happy
birthday it wasn't December happy
[Music]
birthday
happy birthday it's kind of late it's
quite late it's hot and not an hour a
week late but Happy Birthday uh
on every anniversary yeah
although you're not here I think but
happy birthday hope you had a lovely
birthday
and I don't know if you have any of
these snacks but I I hope that this
snacks we had were not too disappointing
for you
um I think this the snack box was okay
she was decent I would say yeah thanks
for watching
thank you also for the pinky I hope you
enjoy snack from France thank you thank
you
are you from France too
because you say it as if you're from
France it sounds like you're from France
are you here right Ghana
oh no we're kind of always surprises me
by being here
shouldn't be surprised anymore
oh my God
oh we're gonna not here
okay we're gonna
oh
[Music]
here no go go show me
must be on the toilet or so
[Music]
oregano is rygona
raigana is Right goner
no
thank you though
oh I see you in the chat oh there's a
whole lot of French Discord what
I didn't know you had your own Discord
oh hello to the French people bonjour
I hope it was fun for you guys yeah
hope you like my French France inspired
outfit too that was so cute oh my God
Brandon Duncan Valley and dankishun
ah you managed to be there nice too
thank you for the red super chat bonjour
bonjour bonjour
thank you for coming and my French tank
person
yeah
yeah thank you soon for being here
[Music]
I looked I looked so cute and looked so
flawless I was in love with myself I was
looking at my cute self for hours after
that stream you may have noticed I even
changed my Twitter profile picture to
the French version of me
I look too so cute
yeah
right oh my God
I probably will change it to froggy Wawa
for frog week and then I'll change it
back to something normal probably after
that
yeah
yeah yeah
and Brandon Duncan oh wait I read that
one cut down hey thank you for the rest
of the chat oh wait I forgot the case
for volley and Valiant come here
come here
and then thank you thank you very much
[Music]
thank you thank you
thank you wow
[Music]
kitchen
oh Orangina is from France oh I didn't
know they should have put an Orangina
and Georgie Jones
[Music]
and out of time it's not 29 thank you
for the Reds but chat I had my doubt
about the red the pink and but that's
about I had my doubts but three weeks
the usual room has taught me the arrows
of my ways I promise I will be a good
whole chicken for now from now
wow it worked I know
I always knew it would work
yeah
oh Orangina is now owned by Japan oh
I see it so much in Japan that makes
sense not all though
that's what you guys always show up
together because you share a Discord
interesting now everything makes so much
sense
Florentina is my favorite blonde girl do
you mean me
because I said I was a blonde girl
I said that at some point I think
oh well anyway thank you welcome back
from the usual room Channel
thank you
happy birthday also kind of late but uh
oh dear how do I say this
[Music]
foreign
no one noticed okay happy birthday
here we talk
what
Rachel for Millions
thank you
oh yeah you were the one who messed with
Lang hope Marshall
you're welcome
[Music]
did you eat some yummy cake
what's your favorite
why is it chicken cake
foreign
feel free but you know this year
the the convention who shall not be
named
did not seem open for cooperation in
some sense
can't get into detail but
I know
I don't think there's better chances
next year but yeah
what
disgusting I love nijiu but which member
do I have to shun from now on
this one
is
Michael
okay that's fine she wasn't my Washi
anyway
okay what the hell
need to use an idol group and um
uh
Apparently one of them had a chicken
cake for her birthday
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
no idea but Yoma can't hurt anything so
I doubt it but there's um
something else where I previously said
something
where maybe things have changed maybe no
no
[\h__\h] I can't say it I'm not allowed
Chris Duncan this is
Carefree Thailand Branch or do you sleep
thank you
I did Carefree talent I love you too
it would be better if luina told you
Thai language oh
oh yeah right she speaks a bit of that
doesn't she
a bit or much I don't know
have you ever eaten during no I have not
and I don't plan on eating such a thing
just to hurt myself
what's on the whole live Reddit
I'm going through it now why would I
check who I've read it
Brendan
what's there
huh
well what about that
[Music]
ah
yeah I'm
I don't know what to say because I'm
just so ridden with jealousy and anger
and sadness that
I cannot find the words to describe
anything with words
[Music]
[Laughter]
hahaha shut up shut up
shut up
I'm so hungry I'm so angry
I'm so angry
always other branches being treated
differently
I'm so angry
look at my angry face
I haven't been the same since three
hours ago what was I angry about three
hours ago
whoa what
[Music]
I'm never angry no no except for now now
I'm so angry
I'm frogging I've got a frog
mean people in a chat okay yeah
I may have been angry about that
what are you talking about
what do you mean
but I don't want to play that stupid
dating game before blah blah on Twitter
she was like let's play this together
I'm like what it's not even multiplayer
what the hell are you talking about
oh I'll gladly collaborate for you ollie
foreign
but not a game like that
what the [\h__\h]
if it was cute girls but then still
it's not a multiplayer game
[Music]
oh gladly you play a multiplayer game
with her
yeah
but I know was brutal
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah it's periodic table that's like
what the [\h__\h] a dating game she was
looking on Twitter she was looking for a
dating game that she remembers where you
date a periodic table and in my mind I'm
just like
girl what the [\h__\h] and I answered her I
want
just holding back in my answer I was I I
wrote
um
I think you dreamed that or so but I
originally wanted to write because
periodic table I wanted to write
you dreamed that nerd
but I couldn't bring myself to add the
nerd to it
because I don't I love Ollie and even
though she would probably get the joke
and I I couldn't get myself to say
something like that to her
foreign
it gives me flashbacks to
School even though I don't think I was
ever called a nerd but you know bullying
by calling someone the nerd no
no no
pain even though the word nerd I think
fits her if you think about her whole
math Arc
a horse with a boy's face
oh God Japan why
[Music]
oh my God
I like the hatofuru boyfriend game
though
that wasn't that one is legit
[Music]
calling all your nerd would probably
encourage her yeah I think she wouldn't
have had a problem with it but
since it's written
message and you can't hear my voice I
wasn't sure how it would come across so
I I kept it
harmless as harmless as possible
but babe was playing it oh my God
KFC Dating Game perms when never
never
[Music]
I'm done with that you know I wanted to
play that as my first game after debut
and honestly
probably absolutely no problem with
playing it but for some reason
just never getting an answer so I'm like
whatever at this point whatever whatever
I'm gonna make my own Dating Game
was disappointed how can you be
disappointed how can you expect anything
from that in the first place
[Music]
like honestly I I I I would never go
into that with any expectations
uh blue thank you for the pinky you are
well you're well qualified as an idol
thank you
I'm sorry sweet of you blue
I think I could be
an idol but I don't see myself as an
adult in the in the sense of what I
think for me is an idol
we had the discussion already and you go
you can see it differently I might be an
idol that someone looks up to that's
okay
thank you
[Music]
couple Indonesia Duncan
all YouTubers are men that use voice
changer in doing their job why don't
they use their natural voice instead of
voice changer because all men who are
being YouTuber don't have job and need
to donate from Weeps
[Music]
okay
is this so serious Super Chat
well you said a troll I don't I feel
like it could be both
sure
why why you use voice changer
why you deceive me why why you lie to me
why
is the is it a joke or who knows we can
only know if that person shows up in a
chat and says it's a jerk they're not
serious about it
hahaha
all right all right okay I get it I'll
turn I'll turn off my voice change
[Music]
but I did I did like see it
uh Richard was using voice changers
before it's very obvious you hear it
you hear it
it's not something you can hide very
well to be honest
I think
it's quite easy to hear the difference
so
um
you've heard it in your nightmares
I'm sorry
yeah yeah it will always have a slight
robotic sound to it
um
even the best ones
best voice changers I think I have yet
to hear one that really at least one
that you can use live
in real time I've yet to hear one that's
really convincing me
did I miss my Super Chat yes you did but
here's a kiss
oh I did I did not know about 40 Sensei
though
I did not know about that at all because
I did not listen to her at that time
uh the game of Queen donation astral
film reduction building Channel Duncan
spicy chicken
unit 723
thank you
[Music]
Green Olive Tree in English
I love you so much thank you
I don't know why you wrote that what
were we talking about
oh my guess about
whole Idol group thing I think because
the one before talks about
no wait I'm not sure what it was but you
always always lovely the pizza oh my God
I thought it was something more serious
you know what I am gonna eat that pizza
today
because I I don't want to cook I'll cook
tomorrow
but that's fine because I cooked the
previous days
[Music]
oh
will have to thank you
Sharon how you doing
how is
the start of your weekend huh
how's it going I'm gonna get the pizza
yeah I'm gonna eat pineapple pizza
and you cannot stop me
ice
[Music]
this name looks like it was if I say it
out loud it's it would suddenly mean
something else
why am I stuttering so much today what
the [\h__\h]
eyes
[Laughter]
it just exactly looks like something
that's trying to get you to say
something that you don't think you're
saying
voice changer glitching
well I'll say it
my
elf
at least this one's harmless
[Music]
right I am
isn't that so rude right you can't
relate at all you would never do that to
me would you right
[Music]
all right
I am done with this
I think I'm gonna leave it at that
[Music]
it's getting late yeah
at least we got two streams well we're
chilling we're chilling we're not like
fall behind or so we're good we're good
[Music]
whatever
um
[Music]
yeah we have a
probably more or less short GTA stream
but yeah but I've heard that there are
several endings and uh
I have been
unfortunately kind of spoiled
and in at least one thing
I know there's going to be a choice
which is unfortunate but at least it's
gonna give me some time to think about
it but
um
what I what I can do however is now I
can plan
um to do several endings if it's
possible
since there are several endings
um maybe if it's if it doesn't take up
too much time I can try to do
more I know there's free endings
apparently
I'm logged in
[Music]
it might be awkward why
I'm not
okay you're safe for your choice okay
you guys just have to help me to avoid
doing any mistake you know
avoid having me lock myself in okay
please thank you
because then I wouldn't mind trying we
probably have the time for it so
[Music]
um
there's an end you need to press F while
speeding in a vehicle yeah
oh and these will take up more than one
hour
well all in total
lit or one each
is a super obvious choice we still have
a choice but one what does that mean
extra saves I'll keep that in mind next
time we play
you're fine for my job oh no
the new one and you probably will enjoy
it even more don't worry about it oh yes
me
what does it mean
s
[Music]
once the final mission starts is when
you're given the choice uh-huh okay
just replay that mission right
I'm okay
all right okay we might do that
I'm gonna try
[Music]
good night at 6 30.
first time I'll see the different
endings oh cooking simulator yeah I have
to make a thumbnail now
all right I stopped moving again so say
and in Germany
[Music]
good night guys thank you for watching
the finale together
I know I had to force some of you guys
to do it but I'm glad you guys did it
and I think you guys are glad too even
if you don't admit it
is
[Music]
good night everybody
yay
that was comfy
coffee quack quack quack quack oh no
she's frogging oh
[Music]
ah this
would you say it on Twitter I had to
laugh so hard about that
someone made a a cow carrot made a video
where you know he estimated what sounds
these piano
things would make and it sounds so
awkward
it's ruined forever
[Music]
forever
I love that because it reminded me
um of some YouTube videos back in the
day where people
um made like voiceovers and sound overs
really awkward ones of like music videos
I think
you guys remember those
like they obviously made fun of
those videos like on purpose
but you know like like farting noises
and whatever
and squeaky noises and whatever
ah so they they don't have it only for
music video but like for sports and
other stuff too I guess yeah
[Music]
it's a rabbit hole
Avatar have fun with that
[Music]
someone should wait make one for do you
oh that would be
so [\h__\h] hilarious
yeah I want that
I need that foreign
[Music]
do you want that yes I do
all right bye
[Music]