[Music]
do
[Applause]
[Music]
do
hello welcome
everyone
[Music]
there you go okay now it's there should
be only the game bgm
hello i
have been so lucky to
spontaneously receive access
to the technical offer it's a currently
uh alpha test
state estate game is too loud okay oh
yeah i turned it up really loud oopsie
how about how about
how about how about this much
how about this much i turned it down a
lot
[Music]
maybe we will have to change it a bit
more once we're in game i don't know
uh so yeah uh yesterday just yesterday
we had a little minecraft stream
where i uh just found out
that the the uh
resurrected like remastered is coming oh
like it's not coming out yet
but there's a an alpha test and i i was
like
wait oh my god i i was like starting to
get like really
um nostalgic because
i used to play this
uh a long long time ago i
i i might have been in my
well i accidentally asked my mom because
my mom played it as well my sister
played as well my brother my whole
family played uh diablo
we are all big fans of diablo and all
kinds of other
games in that area and anyway i asked
and she said i was
somewhere between my sixth and my
seventh
life as a phoenix if you know what i
mean that
is a very young age to play
diablo therefore i was also very very
scared back then of
even just like the tiniest things
but i don't know the game just had
something
that was really fascinating to me anyway
so i wanted to play it anyway so i would
either like continuously uh
start the game over and over and over
again and never go past
the point of killing and dario never
never did that or i would play a little
bit on my mama's account who was already
very very very far
and and just have fun on her account i
did that too
well today i am a full-fledged warrior
so i think i can manage
i can manage but i am so excited because
uh
i yesterday i was like i i found
out about it and i quickly um
like messaged uh manager
management if i can uh
you know somehow still gain access
although it would have been already
pretty late so uh
since i thought it would be too late
anyway i just signed up by myself
for the alpha test but obviously i have
not received no no email
um so that didn't work out but once i
woke up this morning
i saw that well
some strings have been pulled i have
been invited
last minute to the technical alpha as
the second member of her life
uh actually bulldogs and i played it
yesterday slash today as well and
she um played a little bit of diablo 2
resurrected
um as well today and so
yeah now i am the other the other whole
life member who's gonna go
get into it and i'm really excited
because this is gonna be so
nostalgic and i'm i see that you guys
are also very very excited about this so
let's get
into it
[Music]
okay let's create a character at the
moment you can use uh three classes
and two girls which i'm very thankful
for
and this boy the barbarian so you can
play the sorceries
very popular choice but i've been told
by my mama
and by you guys that she's very
difficult
then barbarian easy to play i guess
a very buff um can do a whirlwind later
on that's fun
uh and then there's the amazon who uh
is i guess balanced uh
when you compare it to those two and
i personally want to go with the amazon
yay
she can use the spare and the bow
uh so we'll have fun with that she looks
sexy too so hooray
big plus i i feel like maybe
we could depending on how long i play
this game today and how long i would
need to play
act one because there's acts one act one
and act two that you can play in this
technical alpha
and not more um than that but that's
already a lot i think
so um if we have time we could also like
peek into the other two classes but
i think also a lot of you already know
diablo 2 and played it
and so do we really need to do that i
don't know i just want to see how far we
can get today
and i will name my character kiana or
should i name her
kiara kiana
as google translate likes to translate
my name
uh to always when i write my name in
japanese
um what sounds more
diabloish
kiana with ch okay hotlinks
keanu c8 i feel like it it does give its
what the hell what is my a not working
it does give it some cool vibes
let's go over some italian vibes shall
we let's create her
and i don't know if normally
you get like i don't remember i really
don't remember
uh good day good day wait
am i lagging is my avatar thingy uh my
my camera lag oh no it's
it's it's okay that was just for a
moment um
uh i don't know if normally where before
you show up here maybe you get an
opening sequence or something like that
uh but maybe they uh i don't know i
don't i really don't know i don't
remember anything besides you know
rough things uh
this is still lagging oh yeah
is it wait am i lagging or is the stream
lagging we need to make a big difference
there
[Music]
it's right now okay okay okay i think i
think just for a moment uh
uh i i was lagging but okay whatever
let's hope for the best
and so there's one cool feature
for for the people who don't know diablo
2 but also for the people who do know
diablo 2 when you look at this now
i i gotta be honest at first i was like
what changed cause this is exactly how i
remember it from three million years ago
this is exactly what it looked like to
me
i i don't see a difference but then you
press
g and you see how it really looked like
this is so weird this is such a weird
phenomenon i think that you get with old
games
you see an updated version of the
graphics and
you're like this is exactly how it
looked like to me back then
it looked so high definition oh i
remember her butt oh yes i remember her
butt like that
yeah her butt looks like yeah i remember
those legs oh
maybe that's why i like legs so much in
thighs well
it's all covered up in it no
they covered up her butt oh what
do you say this enhance i wish i could
enhance right now
okay well that's shocking but other than
that uh you see there is a big upgrade
in the graphics
um even though like at first i was like
what but then i saw this and i was like
right oh my god it's really a huge
upgrade
it is a huge upgrade but i don't know do
you guys get that too
where you look at like i don't know
where you think back on older games and
to you it felt feels like back then
it was just like so beautiful and so
high
quality i get that definitely that's
awesome
i'm not surprised to see your kind here
many adventurers have traveled this way
since the recent troubles began
oh but none like me heard about the
tragedy that befell the town of tristram
some say the diablo the lord of terror
walks the world
again i don't know if i believe that
but a dog wanderer did travel this route
a few weeks ago
he was headed east of the mountain pass
guarded by the rogue monastery
maybe it's nothing but evil seems to
have trailed in his wake
you see shortly after the wanderer went
through the monastery's gates to the
pass were closed
and strange creatures began ravaging the
countryside
until it's safer outside the camp and
the gates are reopened
i'll remain here with my caravan i hope
to leave for luke lane before the shadow
that fell over tristram
consumes us all ah if you're still alive
then
i'll take you along oh cool you should
talk to akara too
she seems to be the leader of this camp
maybe she can tell you more
okie dokie this is actually
i'm not sure was i able to read back
then when i first played this
i definitely didn't really understand
what was going on in the game right i
love this this glove
thingy as the mouse curse is so
nostalgic like the whole
interface is so freaking nostalgic help
help please help
okay hold ctrl to run ah okay
hold shift to use a skill while standing
still
okay okay hold out the highlight items
on the ground
okay okay okay i will probably not
remember these things you guys remember
these things
and press escape to bring up the game
menu tab to bring up the autumn mob
enter enter enter to go into chat mode
is that even does that even make sense
with uh
solo player mode by the way there is
currently
in the technical alpha there is no
online mode
um but who knows maybe in the future and
there will be another technical alpha
the online mode who knows
uh to toggle between legacy and
resurrect one yeah i've showed you guys
that
uh after zoom the game camera
look now i can enhance i hate the box
ah why is it gone here oh but wait
that's so
oh that's so right that's so pretty now
you can see the beautiful graphics way
better
oh the graphics are really so good now
but where's the butt
where's the butt i am upset
wait wait wait give me the help back is
it age okay
uh uh bring up the mercenary screen
what's the mercenary screen
oh i can't i can't open it right now yet
okay
shift one two three four to give a belt
potion to your mercenary
uh-huh uh while changing a skill press
f1 to f8 while mousing over
it okay i hope i will i'll just uh
remember that on our own
eventually okay
oh you can see your durability here ah
interesting okay okay okay uh and now we
have our inventory
which is to me so freaking nostalgic
i love this i love like like moving this
around in the inventory and you always
struggled with the inventory space i
remember that
oh look i can i love i love this so much
they love this inventory i love it you
don't understand
okay you don't understand unless you
play diablo before then probably you do
understand
but ah and i love these little these big
big balls like the red one and the mana
one that was always
empty was always empty oh
that's so freaking nostalgic okay where
is this where is this woman that what
was her name akala
what is this you uh
oh you're not voiced more okay i welcome
you traveler to our camp but i am afraid
i can offer you but poor shelter within
this rookie two walls
you see you see our ancient sisterhood
has fallen under a strange curse
the mighty citadel from which we have
guarded the gates to the east for
generations
has been corrupted by the evil demonness
[Music]
i still can't believe it but she turned
many of our sister
rogues against us and drove us from
dance our ancestral home
now the last defenders of the sisterhood
i even dead or scattered throughout the
wilderness
i implore you stranger please help us
find a way to live this terrible cause
and we will pledge our loyalty to you
for all time
let's do it okay um
have informed me that a cave nearby is
filled with
shadowy creatures and horrors from
beyond the grave
i fear that these creatures are massing
for an attack against
our encampment if you are sincere about
healthiness
find the dark labyrinth and destroy the
foul
beasts
made a great eye watch over you
oh my god it is cute it is cool uh look
for the den in the wilderness outside
the rose camp
you're not gonna give me like any
directions like north or
or wait uh no it's on it and
where's the um
the map is nostalgic everything is
nostalgic
oh my god my mom and my mom is watching
this stream right now because she's
jealous
[Music]
and my my sister was also very jealous
when she heard
um that i am chicken and my brother was
also jealous they all want to play
uh the technical i know blizzard if
you're watching this but
i kind of got this through a japanese
blizzard i guess so
uh
just kind of need to tell them if you
have some clothes left over
my mom really wants a cold and my sister
and my brother but okay
i'm just joking no pressure no pressure
uh okay okay okay so uh
this was a rope in camp and waypoint
interesting i don't know if i understand
that
so we're just supposed to the only it
looks like the only way to go out of
this camp is down anyways i'm hoping
that we just have to go down
should we just already go outside trying
to go fight let's go entering the blood
more
we're out guys let's go who is guilty
purge this land of the shadow
i shall purchase land of the shadow
yes i will i will oh oh my god there's a
oh my there's a lot okay
okay so this is how you fight you
basically just click i'm just clicking
there's a
uh you gotta click accept uh oh
i got some armor you gotta kill very
except on the characters
on the on the mom's uh minor man up
nice oh it's a it's an ollie
hello that doesn't hurt you does it
oh did i feel like how can you kill a
zombie did that did i really do that
so inventory actually automatically
equipped it because i wasn't wearing
anything yet uh cool cool
good job i'm not going the right way i
wonder
what is that crap sash
she also automatically equipped that
very smart
very smart kind of need to sneeze
and now look again uh look at that
oh my god the graphic uh difference i
love it
wow it's so beautiful
it is so beautiful
oh my god this is so weird like
this is how it looked like to me when i
was younger so
weird this is not the first time i've
had this before game laughing
with the nostalgia
sorry always maybe i should just follow
this path i wonder if i'll reach the
right uh
place if i follow this up are we going
straight to ontario i hope not i'm still
kind of scared like
and dario is like my childhood trauma
i was as i said i was never able to uh
yeah auto collect gold yes
i was never able to um beat her
because i was so scared of it so i was
just running around and poking these
these enemies and having fun rip only
there's a lot of ollies and a lot of uh
demons oh i level up besides
okay wait wait wait let's go to safe
spot
oh i remember this interface
okay okay okay okay
so we got we got five stack ones now
you're not gonna attack me are you okay
oh is he
ah well i am on amazon
what's dexterity
vitality is i guess like health i guess
that belongs to that okay attack
a chance to hit
[Music]
what should i go for i wonder maybe like
dexterity and strength
energy is for i guess i don't really
didn't amazon need mana i can't remember
i'm not doubting it that's okay i
thought so
everything though well you know what we
don't have to think too deep about it
it's only act one act two and it's just
in
a technical alpha so not too much
thinking but i'll put it all into decks
for now
full decks uh stats yes yes yes okay
and then here i guess can i one skill
choices remaining
i guess i'll just oh wait
i i am bone crossbow javelin spirit okay
well let's go for that i guess we
did already i can't even undo that
oh okay gotta be more careful though
next time i do that but now i think it
was okay
full backs let's go let's kill some more
demons and zombies
flowey someone on the map is called
flowey
oh hello turn back wait wait wait
wait okay that was important okay what
is it
turn back i can tell that you need more
experience to fight safely
did i go wrong you should complete
akara's quest before venturing further
search for the den in the wilderness
closer to camp
ah closer to camp there's a den in the
wilderness
we okay a short bow another chest with
some money
what was that can i pick it up
there's so many enemies i want to eat
i just heard it bonk against my shield
because it actually worked do i not have
to
i love moving those stones i love moving
those stones oh my god
okay shut up guys uh i need to
uh find first of all
okay we can already clip this second set
see how that works is there a shortcut
to switch it without opening the
the inventory
[Music]
i'm scared to push any buttons one two
three four should be the
should just be the um
oh you guys know everything do you guys
remember that from like millions of
years ago
are you also playing the technical offer
where do we need to go did i go around
closer to the camera maybe to the right
side what's that
oh yeah the music too wait that's not
where i need to go
but is this what they what you meant to
dead then
the chest oh a short sword
and gold oh no oh no kill them
kill them all ah wait no yeah i'm using
i forgot i'm using the bow okay that's
that's no problem uh
well it's getting dark wait is it is
there a date night system in this game i
don't remember
don't call the audience old farts okay
because then
you're calling me old fart
we don't want to roast anyone
i didn't
[Music]
am i going the right way okay i would i
i wouldn't mind
getting uh back seated on weapon that
i'm going the right way
should i just follow uh wait what the
[\h__\h] i mean
i followed that path first but
what does that well do follow road
okay i'll just go down
i'll go down here that way hoping that
that is the right way though
oh [\h__\h] it was something like that
wasn't it
that you get a different map
[Music]
oh my god it's so nostalgic
dead bodies are you gay oh you got me
got myself oh yeah
let me check my inventory how full is it
oh damn uh
14 24
uh we also don't need that i want to
keep some things to sell later
hopefully i can sell a oh my lot of
do revive oh yeah oh my god yes that was
a thing oh no
oh no
it's okay you are full-fledged part-time
where we are now
no need to be scared can i run out of
errands
oh you guys waiting there can you go up
are you too lame to get up
oh i can't kill them from here oh
he's reviving them
oh so many so many so honey
keep keep distance first
and then close combat
[Music]
stop it
let me try that gold
[Music]
huh
shift attack and stand still
ah then i don't have to click onto them
exactly
you leveled up wait i still
automatically go to them with the mouse
[Music]
[Laughter]
and one of those okay magical arrow
bye everyone
why not why not
always go with fire wait did i actually
use that up yeah
i stopped kill all the mods all of them
okay that's an easy quest no
[Music]
wait kill him first tell him first kill
himself
just get rid of it there we go
it is a useful to press shift
can't care anymore wait so i didn't
wonder do they
quantity oh 173 that's quite a lot
should i change out for a new one wait
these look maybe i don't know if they're
strong
wait a second wait a second uh
oh full inventory already
[Music]
how ah but they don't have any strength
and this is not much more what do you
have
nothing okay both are
ah balls oh yeah that's something
else okay okay i thought you could use
that as well
uh trying to get used to using uh [\h__\h]
oh okay okay does it just try to
oh my god this
[Music]
he looks fluffy too looks like a good uh
plushie for
um with your beds
what was that thing ah
kill him big boy he's fluffy
look at wait wait i wanna see um
he's so shiny now he's got such a shiny
bird did he wash his fur over
gravy perhaps in this version
wait kill him
okay what about you you want to die too
i wonder if you're the boss monster girl
the goal is just to kill everyone but
does that mean
that there is a boss in here also we
gotta be clear we don't wanna we don't
wanna be uh looking for someone
we missed later on it's gonna be
annoying if i miss someone
equip skill
[Music]
skills
wait i don't remember that oh
scrobo oh record a bug
skipper
ah you get only two skills
arrow as well should i do both um normal
we want normal attack
wait so it's uh oh right ah right click
left click
right click screen oh that's easy okay
okay
now
i think we got this area so let's go
down here
oh no nothing was there
does it automatically recover was there
an automatic recover function
if not then yeah bye
gotta get used to just clicking uh
um controls why is he not hitting
quick everest
you recover health and mana okay it
seems very pretty slow though
stop stop stop
oh we got all kinds of fancy things
let's kill them first
stabbing
[Music]
oh it tells you oh that's nice of them
okay
so we could use a minor
monopoly why not then let's oh i filled
it all up nice
what ah because i have it open it does
that
okay they had some accepted but we don't
we don't use it but we want to sell it
don't we
so maybe i get rid of that and i get the
sept
oh
an ambulance don't you want to wear that
i'll identify i can't
i probably can't wear it yet because
it's unidentified what else will charlie
nothing okay what about here scroll of
identity i
identify i remember that
out please what else
[Music]
okay but no i think we got everything
cool okay five months is remaining
five monsters
i'm so excited and i just can't hide no
no
the way my mana is getting used up here
oh no
okay okay magical
did you see a magic belt or do i have
one
no magical perhaps now the sisters will
trust
oh wait did i i did it
[Music]
magic portal shrine
oh ouch ah sure
[Music]
i can't use this yet can't use it
hold on here we go nice
okay is that it when you run over there
see we missed something
i mean we missed no enemies but maybe
some items i don't know
oh i think we did it well
enough is that a teleport to go back
home
oh just fine oh hey
i did the first little cave
what did i forget to identify amoled
you want me to identify it
there we go
is there like some
oh i was trying to find a
i can oh one that's nice that's exactly
what i wanted
okay i've come back wait to the doctor
[Music]
one takes that's exactly what i want i
can read my mind cleanse the den of evil
you've earned my trust and may yet
restore my faith in your mind no you
[Music]
oh interesting
gossip what's the glass that's only been
our guest for a short time
i sense that war eve has faced many
harrowing trials though he knows as i do
that a terrible evil has blanketed the
land his only real concern
is to reach the eastern trading ports
with this caravan
it's fast in phoenix yes you can trust
the phoenix's introduction we probably
already heard before train what the
street
oh she got those books ah
total of identify where's the difference
between uh tome and uh
one of those scrolls this is just
because it says i don't know
can you use it more often well like
forever
if i carry it with me totally okay you
got a bunch of
fun things not holding there oh weapons
oh all of that yeah oh this is so
this is so nostalgic twenty scrolls
oh ho ho ho ho nice that's pretty good
but look at this oh my
[Music]
you can play something in there you see
that circle
you see it i'm gonna cry
[Music]
oh my god
wait wait we got another point oh my god
why not what is it
baby nostalgia right now to see an
amazon in these lands
you're very brave to have come here many
of my fellow sisters have fallen under
some dark spell
and if you're not careful you may fall
prey to it as well
don't worry i'm strong i can't fall in
the dark spelling mistakes i've just
reported an abomination in the monastery
graveyard
apparently and dario is not content to
take only
blood raven one of our finest captains
in the battle against diablo and tristan
who's also one of the first to be
corrupted by andario
now you'll find her in the monastery
graveyard raising our dead
well it's already time to fight on dario
not abide this defilement
if you are truly our ally you will help
us destroy
her is it already done that was too
quick i'm not ready
i'm not ready
oh no a blood raven
okay okay okay okay okay wait what's
your name
let's talk to the other people
try hi there i'm charcy the blacksmith
here in camp
it's good to see some strong adventurers
around here
many of our sisters fought bravely
against diablo when he first attacked
the town of tristra
they came back to his true veterans
bearing some really powerful items
seems like their victory was short-lived
though most of them are now corrupted by
daario what is
why why do they get corrupted by her ah
well you can
get repair here ah oh
she's got some nice bows but we got a
nice one too
one two two one two five
one two four two to six that one is
nice one but
wait how much we don't have that much
but oh we should sell our [\h__\h] here
uh wait wait do we want that um
quantity six oh
okay
[Music]
okay we don't need that what is that by
the way strangling gas
potion i uh is that something i throw
and then have fun with it i don't really
want it i think i don't know how much
does it sell for
240 i don't need it
i don't need i'll give me some armor
give me some but i will probably find a
lot we'll probably find a lot
right we don't really need to buy
anything here it's happening
oh wait now i could actually afford the
this ball
[Music]
oh maybe i should get it
very fast attack speed faster
i want to get it now
yes no regrets
take that one awesome okay
it generates mana too
plus one to mana after each kill oh
all right let's go to the next
[Music]
ah oh that's the act one oh we're
already at the second one cool cool cool
and look for the black raven on the
burial grounds next to the cold plains
and the border the grounds next to the
cold planes
i hope i can find it okay
[Music]
what should i buy one of those tomes
you'll think i should buy one
you're still i i know i'm an act one but
i mean if i
ha uh if i finish all these quests
six quests is that one act one is over
buy the books
you like the thumbnail guys
oh my god this is your dad wait let me i
guess
wait do i even have enough money right
now yes
yes uh
360. i can do it 360.
[Music]
okay then in theory i don't even need
the small ones but whatever let's go
[Music]
i was a nasty crack oh yeah the
thumbnail
i feel like it stands out so much uh now
um like like generally my
something's all very bright and mostly
orange because of well
me stamina shrine does that fill up my
health then i don't want to use it up
right now
[Music]
yeah you're running away huh you're
scared huh
where should we go why can't we go left
now or should we go down
put the scrolls into the book i thought
it comes with all the scrolls
[Music]
huh
if you don't follow the path isn't that
nice well there was nothing inside there
right now but still
still it's perfect there's no path going
down here
but i guess we're going to go left to
where the the woman stopped me before
wow wow
see this one this is what happens when
you go off the path
dagger cat
already pretty full mem uh inventory
should we go back and sell this
[\h__\h] but hey we can
[Music]
we can do that we can wear that wait
that's better right
oh no it actually it's not bad
oh damn it okay
[Music]
should we do it on that one
okay energy why not
low explosion
you know what i hope i want a quick
little kind i want to go back
it's close it's close i'll go quick i'll
do it fast
i'll do it fast i just need to sell what
i just received
the skeet guy we didn't talk to him yet
can you also sell and trade
with me what day do you park
and i can already tell that i'll be your
best friend
in this fight are you sure about that i
spare weapons some gold
a small gem is all i want in exchange
for the equipment
oh sorry that was uh by accident
[Music]
we need to focus focus focus guys no
gambling
also i wanna i wanna apologize for
changing my schedule up
completely um the schedule for the rest
of the weekend
will change depending on first of all
how long the
technical alpha goes and how fast i
finish it
and but yeah
tomorrow the kanoke is still happening
the member stream
will happen one week after uh the
original
date it will stay at the same time
however as an excuse there will be
um two member streams next week so thank
you for your understanding but i
need to play a diablo right now it's
very important very important for me
what kelly is here kelly you would like
this kind of game i think did you ever
play it
this is from my childhood
what did kelly say wait maybe if i
scroll quick maybe i find it
quick no it's gone
it's gone what did you write
okay i'm going i'm going off off the
path again shouldn't do that
there's no multiplayer right now so no
there cannot be any multiplayer uh
at the moment
yes ah she wrote yes kill them all whoa
let's go we got improvement from
death itself that's herself
thank you for the membership welcome oh
i'm slow
gotta wait for my energy to come back oh
oh what the hell
the way they die is like really dramatic
and fancy
my death is a bit cooler joe i go up in
flames and ashes
what's what's up why are they walking
away like that
i leveled up again
[Music]
rejuvenation potion
you might want to use one of those and
uh
see how everyone turned off like nice
okay what's that small
charm she can even try to gain more but
i have to
identify it right seven maximum stamina
wow
okay just keep it in the inner die okay
to the waypoint what waypoint
this thing here
oh i activated it what does that do is
that uh
is that a portal now
[Music]
can i teleport to the camp now with that
fast travel okay sasuka we don't need to
go into the cave right
we can stay outside i think
right
[Music]
oh my god
oh i've got no mana that doesn't
surprise me
lots of does it please make it uh go
into my inventory automatically
into the book automatically thank you
[Music]
this game is hitting my boomer nostalgia
with samia my friend
i am glad i can make everyone happy with
some nostalgia
the moment i i got so excited hearing
that this was coming out and then i got
even more excited hearing that i can
play it
so i wouldn't really want to say thank
you to
uh both management and
the uh blizzard and activision people
for making this possible letting me in
last
last minute superior throwing knife
noise
okay just follow the path kiara
[Music]
here right now i don't have one oh wait
oh
one summon attack what
jam oh i do have a scale ah
i did get one i forgot about that
did that even hit right now i can't
carry anymore
why not
[Music]
uh
why is that why is the opacity of that
solo
because it's [\h__\h] or because it cannot
be repaired
how about that one see that's
it's a thorough ah
okay i don't want any of that let's keep
the space for something
bigger and more important left or right
left all right
ah i feel like uh the spare
with shift on doesn't work so well
because she doesn't automatically run
there i wish it would automatically run
to the
closest ending
the bow is pretty nice though
[Music]
oh i should should i use maybe i should
put a minor one
here
yeah for now i think um only miners
would
do the trick
[Music]
okay
okay oh oh god am i going right here
[Music]
where's your leader huh where's the guy
who revives you oh
oh
[Music]
i see what you're doing there
okay okay nice one nice kiana
cool skill shrine
diet they don't deserve to live so they
don't deserve to revive only i
deserve to be arrived and resurrected
because i'm phoenix
[Music]
god we gotta look at all those items
that are dropping here
oh my god okay uh
no oh my god another one another one
and they don't stop coming and they
don't stop coming and they don't stop
coming and they don't
stop coming uh let's take a
stumbling opposition i guess
oh oh my god so many items
chip root ruby rubbing ribbon you will
be
both she'll break us won't you
do i have to identify them do i still
have one
i don't appreciate i already have boots
oh
it's so exciting hey
i got some new shoes on large charms
do i need more arrows 239
[\h__\h] moles
oh yeah anything else that looks special
strangling guys but you know
superior buckler ah chest oops
nothing let me something
i threw those away i think that's it
okay wait oh we can stack on rails
let's try
huh
what ah did it fill it up to maximum is
that what it just did
[Music]
gas pushing good money wait what what
just happened yeah i feel more skillful
why why why why oh does that give me
like a short time upgrade
oh damn i took it i took it accidentally
okay
[Music]
temporary buff oh no
oh so many of them
pick up a sash okay what's that
oh oh you're one of those [\h__\h] again
[Music]
okay there we the moment what was go
what was that what was that ah so
periphery now
you might throw it away eventually but
oh
that's huge wait should we identify it
damn this one is locked
okay wait did i need to go down here oh
there's another chest that i didn't open
i know i've been holding out every now
and then don't worry
that's the place where we need to go
seems to be pretty far away
i gotta look for that chest up there
is a chest
items are money okay then let me try to
get uh
this one and this one
fits in nicely
there we go whoa
[Music]
um this is not blue but
it is green so i suppose it's also good
oh
[Music]
i can't take that one yet should i maybe
ah yellow blue white that was it was
yellow
that's even better nice okay
i think i'll take another one of those
fire ones and
one well maybe ah [\h__\h] maybe not
strength
no it does ah strength goes into fire
ever imagine a damage oh
maybe one here too and then the rest
there okay
i'm gonna i'm gonna balance it a tiny
bit you know
oh my inventory is full should i go back
home once
and sell stuff i could go back home with
a portal oh yummy
okay i can't oh i chipped
uh
[Music]
sounds like a plan mm-hmm but i wanted
to help us
is the topaz worth a lot we will throw
away
what's that chipped around you just
throw away one of the mana potions
and take it down
equip sash
also an idea
oh it's way better
okay oh okay
so scroll up town photo there we go
going back once
and then hopefully after that we'll find
oh
where we needed to go uh
was that close i wonder anyone is fine
everyone here
is fine i think no not you
[Music]
ah the chest in the camp this chest oh
my private stash oh what do i want to
put in there
maybe some potions
because i don't need all of them
not sure what i need the stamina potion
for
you have some of those
[Music]
maybe this one too and then we'll go
sell some things
the gems i don't want to sell the gems
is there like a shortcut to throw it
over to that like some button
uh key combination that makes it go over
to the stash
and right now i remember those
should i identify the things i'm selling
as well
right click hold ctrl
[Music]
do i get more money if i identify at
first
[Music]
question
okay i hope i have enough
[Music]
oh i ran out already
but this one is all oh why is it red
ah not high enough to actually use it oh
i thought i was already
actively using it i see hi dude
not here good day you're my best friend
right so give me some good
prices here uh have this
and this and this and this and
this one this one
this one this one keys i
keep what should i have not thrown away
all right i forgot i do wear shield oh
can i have it back please
[Music]
another one are they the first girls
okay
[Music]
acara hello
it's your favorite phoenix back in town
good day oh you healed me did you just
heal me
kill me that is very nice of you i need
a
yes yes yes
yes okay bye bye
yeah it was yellow that's pretty good
isn't it
are youtube struggling is it lagging
we okay i think we're okay wait let me
check again
where are the grounds next to the coal
plate i feel like i went like the wrong
place maybe because i went so far maybe
or is that really so far away
ah wait i can use the same portal
oh i thought that would be uh
only like one way ticket where is it
[Music]
oh
oh yeah that's cool look at all these
dead bodies huh oh wait
ah you can use it once to go and come
back ah
oh no
hold up okay that probably takes up two
wait actually wait i use a javelin
wait is that better than mine
[Music]
oh wait um six to fourteen oh it is a
bit better
yup okay changing maybe throwing that
one away
okay this is the right way i don't know
my follow path hello
okay i accidentally further away good
that i noticed early enough
entering estonia field
that's we need to go to the
cold plants though am i wrong
there wasn't oh wait entering ah here's
a and entering the cold plains
so right next to the cold planes should
be
the burial grounds that's what i'm
looking for so maybe it is
the other path there was like two paths
i guess i took the wrong one
[Music]
wait nope
yeah it must be that one bird brain why
oh i remember
okay now we should be on the right track
[Music]
wait you don't want that one that's
probably also [\h__\h]
[Music]
wait i wanna see that's but mine is
filled up anyway right now
we'll find more
they're demons were those women were
demons
ah they're too pretty to be demons trust
them
you're saying you don't want to go on a
date with them you don't trust them
enough to go on the table
okay go back change
oh wait no
[Music]
kill him first yep again
all right get that money get that cash
bolts yeah okay it is time
uh i think for javelin upgrading um
[Music]
can i get a different one what do i have
to i think i have to
work on that one that's okay next
[Music]
one more vitality and more decks
lots and lots of decks
no i'm scared i'm scared i don't think i
even was ever able to kill the blood
raven even that was probably impossible
for me
i i remember though asking my brother oh
my mom
great sorrow and misery oh no uh to just
kill the boss for me
and then i was able to uh
continue uh playing
they killed it for me and then i
continued playing on my right i was
never able to kill the
the boss oh is he in here
is it in the mausoleum
hungry then is it is
[Music]
is it outside i wonder is it they didn't
say anything about the mouth of william
okay i think i gotta go in here i don't
wanna
i don't wanna ah what's wrong
[Music]
uh do an uh a thing of a thing
i did no problem in phoenix i will
revive
i will revive oh my god do i have my
stuff
can i is this like minecraft when you go
there and you pick up your stuff again
or is it gone
will it be there
i have to get my body need to pick it up
okay
but it's like right where that dude is
oh yeah
i thought i had a i know i don't
i don't i have to run all the way there
will i be fine with
no no things
just need to grab it and run yeah i
can't pick up things that quickly
i can pick up my whole corpse i hope it
will pick up everything quickly
it was way point that thing not the
portal ah
[Music]
okay okay i got it
i'm on it okay there it is
walking slowly inserting dominance
where is it what's somewhere where
oh there it is
where are we going cool place there we
go i'm
[Music]
maybe i should have stayed in the
bathroom
[Music]
oh okay they're pretty slow whatever
um stop following me
stop stop stop stop
[Music]
oh my god it's fans fans of mine
here's it can i use that
oh wait what why did i change
respect my privacy that's so hot so much
to ask for
so wait
where does my oh why do i have my things
not all of it huh
oh
open the portal before fighting a bus
okay
that was not my body but where did i get
the equipment is at the corpse where did
i get all those uh
porsche potions wait did i have them all
along do you not lose your potions do
you only lose
your your equipment
oh god well i know exactly where my body
is
i know exactly i'm scared to go there
hold on
[Music]
oh
first of all that
okay okay that's that's a good one okay
okay
where's my good job did i didn't i have
a better javelin than that
oh well also i don't have a
i don't have an anti-thingy potion no
well
anti-poison potion okay okay
i cannot heal it i guess so i just gotta
uh continuously
use the potions huh okay no problem uh
[Music]
do i have to does it do i have to do
that
[Music]
did i miss anything important
wait i forgot something it seems
[Music]
and
okay
me you're sure about that
wait he's not poisoning me right now oh
he's almost dead oh whatever
are you done
wait wait it's not moving them over here
where is he
ugh
what's killing everyone around us
rest in peace sister no no no don't rest
in peace
rest in hell
[Music]
oh it's a big one identify that
it's a too good for me at the moment but
we will probably be able to use it at
some point
why not
[Music]
yeah i'm the real gamer
oh i'm i'm i'm facing my old traumas and
and demons that have followed me all my
life
is that all you didn't drop me anything
besides that oh come on there must be
something here
more items come on there must be
something in here
wait did i skip a lot of enemies was
there a lot of enemies and i just went
straight to the boss and
i could have killed a lot of enemies
here
i shouldn't should i go inside check the
crypt there's a crypt yeah bye
ah oh
is there enemies in here what
what kind of rachel was that
oh what the hell is going on in here
what oh he dropped some nice stuff
what's going on in here though this is
kind of scary i don't i'm not gonna lie
why are they not dying here
[Music]
wow by the way uh just so you can see
the
it again look at that difference
[Music]
look at that graphic improvement
i want you to appreciate it get that
capped
i want it down
i need more wait superior javelin
oh there we go is that my old one
it's amazing yeah
unidentified let's hope it's a good one
this has six
uh to twelve okay yep that's better bye
bye
oh i'll take that one too oh no wait let
me sell that one
that's probably a good idea like mana
minor healing yes
and the gold how deep are these
do you really know that deep
good memories of this game the originals
you have to play these days
i'll probably buy the remastered version
sounds good to me
wow you might have to be a little bit uh
patient still
but i'm sure it will be worth it there's
lots of lots of characters here
whoa
is that the usual room it does have
barrel
turtles it's not like the barrels and
after your riser
sadly a bit different yeah the usual
room
has some similarities here oh come on
i pressed the brown button
we're gonna love those barrels i'm a big
fan of barrels
[Music]
ah we should go home i guess because we
got pretty much a full inventory this
looks pretty big
i don't know should we go for all this
damaged club oh hello
sorry to wake you up buddy
a rose key
[Music]
take the key leave the arrows
i can go up here use port as well should
i i opened one
uh outside actually
i have one ready barrel barrel
[Music]
yes i know i'm aware of that
oh but we want that one and the chip
sapphire
[Music]
we need to do something about stuff
yeah let's do that nice okay let's take
the staff and
go back
[Music]
okay okay okay i gotta go back
oh can i even find out of you i think i
came from here
and i went there and
down here and then left
i like the ritual that they're doing
there uh
could take some inspiration from that
some embarrassed explode oh thank you
for
telling me that should i maybe not be
opening so many barrels
i didn't know
no i have a portal here don't worry
okay what is it lagging
[Music]
okay oh i came here to sell some things
and maybe what's with my quest i have to
come to you
not to cut out here oh well you can you
can trade with me right
this is my old one no that's my new one
i cannot
wear it yet but soon what that's so
cheap
ah identify first oh 808
wow bye-bye
i'll keep that and this one is um
oh a defense four
this one to energy defense free
foster hate recovery i guess the one i
have now is maybe better
wow caleb thank you so much
thank you for the huge support and
donations it's getting really dark in my
room let me turn on the light
caleb thank you i appreciate that
are you are you singing to me are you
singing hello
it's me caleb i've been wondering if
after all these years you'd like to meet
to go
over
[Music]
whoa
okay okay i'll go okay and i turned on
the light
i can see clear everything is beautiful
okay we want to talk to kasia i did your
quest what's next kasia
beautiful hardly believe that you've
defeated bloodraven
though she was once my closest friend i
pray that her tortured
spirit remains banished forever oh
you have earned my respect stranger
thank you and the allegiance of the
rogues
i have placed several of my best
warriors at your disposal
oh i like getting a friend
oh higher oh
is there is there uh somewhere no
well then they all suck just kidding um
[Music]
do i i'm wrong right with the assumption
that you
uh cannot teleport with them
they will will they follow me oh wait
they go
get me one for free oh this one
will she follow me through the teleport
thingy
also what's my next question ah there we
go
wanna give me a new quest kasia the
sisterhood
[Music]
quest please they found me everywhere
she fall to the death wow okay that is
that is a lot of
uh gotta say
passion and i forgot the other word
should i stay a while and listen
maybe uh yeah maybe akara
knows what to do
it is clear that we are facing an evil
difficult to comprehend
let alone come back there is only one
horadrim sage
schooled in the most arcane history and
lore who could advise us
his name is deckard kane you must go to
tristram
and find him my friend i pray that he
still lives
tristram is that like a the next camp
you want me to go there
question go for the underground passage
to the dark wood search for the tree of
initials and recover the scroll
that sounds very complicated put
underground passage to the dark wood
where the hell is that
where is that it's the camp from the old
diablo one
[Music]
porch light games never heard of those
thank you for the red super chat
thank you for your recommendation i
might look it up
do i just go in the same direction i
wonder ah
maybe maybe the other wait i have a
portal though but i don't really need it
right now i think we're going somewhere
else now
[Music]
yes should i oh wait maybe maybe at
least go to the waypoint
from the cold planes yeah and then and
then use the other path which might lead
to where i need to go
oh i cannot run anymore
[Music]
oh you guys seem to know torch
torchlight i've never heard of it do
do i need to put something in here maybe
this one because
i guess i'm a little five right now
where do i see my level
[Music]
um oh and this one oh beautiful stones
also i would like uh one of those
healing potions and change it
for that thank you
ah no there was the only language
that is available for the alpha is
english right now which is
thankfully fine for me um i love
five well one should we i guess we
should bring you along though
because i feel like we'll level up
pretty soon
and
[Music]
okay we don't need that many let's go
oh wait that's her she's level two oh
wait is that her i can give her
equipment too
nah not right now i hope you're not
attacking the chickens saying seem kind
of panicked around you
you could fill up your belt
[Music]
what do you mean with my belt fill up
no it's here cold planes
[Music]
you can give your stuff oh well we'll
see we'll see what we find on the way
so i guess uh we went
where is that where's that path that
turned into two paths
[Applause]
[Music]
there
do you want some boots can you wear
boots it was all right
you can't wear boots unfortunately why
not
huh come on got dexterity
oh what did you oh they're all dropping
their diamonds
oh my god i'm a fist i'm not
is that how you pronounce it
you got a leader where is he you want to
bring me to you later
ah there he is
scroll over identity oh there's a dagger
a blue dagger
okay
what is that i went to before didn't i
killed everyone
already oh i could get skill
noise thank you i am most skillful now
[Music]
are you guys ready the stony field is
that where i need to go
this is your underground pizza passage
to the dark woods search for this tree
of in
nephes is that the right way
to
what's that so well what does it do it
fills up my health
thank you
[Music]
this is on the way okay good
don't get too close to my friend
whatever her name is what's your name
[Music]
no there's another one
okay okay we're doing fun
okay what did i drop a lot of stuff
oh but nothing nothing too fancy let's
get one of those potions
in one of those potions we can sell our
little boss
[Music]
papaya her name is not papaya you can
give her potions oh
wait i i need to heal myself or i just
drink from the well again i think that's
a good idea
death takes its toll upon cali
give me my money back
why was he so strong oh no should i give
me another one of those
chicks
thank you but why does kelly need money
for me
um that's kind of sad wait wait where's
kasha right kasha gives me
the ladies
oh i don't have the money right now oh
[\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] okay
[Music]
i didn't know kelly takes money from
dead people
[Music]
the reaper creeps the money not only
sells
business is business well i guess it's a
it is a job isn't it
it is a job we gotta make some money
somehow
there's all kinds of ways to make money
nowadays
okay let's wait for a moment i i need to
be able to run again why am i wearing my
running shoes
but i do have shoes though but that's
not the right ones i want my own ones
oh you're still there what the hell
where's my body
there it is oh okay
they didn't we don't demand clean crips
everything okay now
oh now i can kill them easily okay
okay they kind of scare me they kind of
scare me now
not gonna lie oh wait my skills are
there okay
okay should i go get my
friend back she probably would be very
helpful
watch out for his electricity yeah that
was pretty bad what
what what the hell those do not look
like crowds i've seen some crowds out
there yes i should
okay wait oh my god
let me use oh i only have one
but the waypoint is close okay
oh well
she isn't my friend don't say that
greetings
uh welcome back don't die so quickly
maybe we should give her
some weapons but i can i still cannot
wear that but
um
can i buy something for her
i'm only gonna find something won't we
[Music]
well i do have some stuff to store
this this i can sell that
so that's oh okay
gave stuff to the pool girl
[Music]
i should also buy some should i buy the
whole book
i guess so it takes out a lot of space
though
i want a book to put all my potions in
that would be nice
by the way by the way
can i no
is there a way to quickly put them in
these empty slots
[Music]
food life is not a lot well it is if
you're dealing with so little slots
okay not in town not until you are in
town
no ctrl doesn't work oh well whatever
and uh i guess yeah we're gonna buy the
blue book thank you
okay okay
[Music]
wait did i just buy it no
oh my god
by the way why is it quantity free
why is it quantity free how does that
work
is there a limit to how often i can use
it
oh gosh
i can combine them oh okay at least some
ah some more squirrels i don't need that
many teleporter smells
i don't need that many oh well
okay you can have that and have that
have that take some of these things
so that i have more money thank you
okay now
i forgot to put one more uh pretty stone
into my private stash there you go
okay and now we go back
okay store my money ah ah i guess you
could have done that too huh
okay let's go
[Music]
i'm scared
what what did i hear did you attack
someone yes you did
stand behind me okay we don't want you
to die
just nothing inside how useless
of course i grab whatever's shiny i like
tiny things
[Music]
another chest oh that's nice i need some
healing torches thank you actually i
should have bought some maybe
lots of enemies right now where are they
all coming from
she can wear that she could wear that
to good use put that to good use yes
i agree couldn't agree more
okay i'm going off path again what is
that over there
gym shrine
what does a gem trying to do
what is that culminating potion
what does that do oh it gives you a
diamond
oh thank you okay going back on my path
three gems oh nice
okay okay okay however that was not
where we were supposed to go
what my house i missed that house
we could get some nice loot here hello
oh hello that looks like a horse cow
how in horses the head looks like a come
on let's look at it
in old quality oh cute
oh my god these graphics
oh wow that's so nostalgic guys
the quality i guess for like standards
from back then
was really good back then already i
think right wasn't it
what is that that's it we found it
let's go here
oh what are those monsters happen
that that sounds funny like it was like
a like a joke on english language
it was yes yes it was indeed
i've heard about the count leveling i
think i remember something from my
childhood with a cow level
can i make her use that
oh ah miss chapin oh
now this happened
which means wait i can use this one now
and give her
the old one
[Music]
but don't die yet don't die uh
you can use it but you don't you're not
allowed to die yet okay
okay we still need some gloves
here we go should we up
i'll take all the first to stay behind
me i feel much stronger now oh wait i
should actually
you leveled up too cool
oh power strike that's lightning oh yeah
yes i want that lightning wait it's uh
this one oh that sounds
good to me that sounds pretty good to me
the enemy's uh lightning was also pretty
damn strong
you know what you stay behind of your
arrows and your ball and i'll i'll be
the
front rail warrior i'll protect you why
is someone here it's kind of suss
thanks to the level up i guess
[Music]
nice
good job wow
follow me follow me
thank you guys for the super chats
favorite games all the time diablo 2 is
definitely one of the favorite games
from
a lot of people as i've heard you guys
also seemed
so excited when i said i would play it
so i'm really glad we can play something
like this
on my channel because normally i guess i
play a lot of games that you guys
don't know or don't like that that much
i mean
some of you you guys all are so kind to
watch the streams anyway
but i'm just a big fan of jrpgs in
general
but that doesn't mean that i cannot
appreciate a great classic like diablo
2.
i do appreciate this game a lot
[Music]
it got so much chump
definitely does that electricity
electric boogaloo jrpg is still fun to
watch
yeah for me personally for jam for jeans
it's like i like the cute aesthetics
so diablo 2 is definitely
not what you would expect from my
channel i think you can't really see
that just from
from how much the thumbnail stands out
today
but it's nice to have like a little bit
of variety too and uh
a little bit of a different kind of vibe
and atmosphere
and when i was younger and playing this
just for fun
i really didn't
get much anything from the story into my
brain
and although i've heard that diablo 2 is
like
not that i've heard opinions that the
apple 2 is not that much
about the story it's more oh that would
reveal right
what's more about
just i don't know killing people
i do expect to see some nice story in
here as well
so let's see what we'll get oh
there's a lot of people in here
i shouldn't go oh no no no no
kill him first
i'm enough to do that
but i also don't want to do that even if
i could
does that waste my phoenix
[Music]
oh no oh no oh no
i ran into a huge camp here it seems
there's another revival up there
okay you know what
i'm gonna use the monopoles oh they
dropped a lot of points nice
there you go there's still so many
[Music]
nice oh we're gonna pick up a lot of
items oh
oh that loots
well abaya is dead but
it's okay oh i smell shield
i can't that's okay this one i'm not
throwing away
i am a shield user i forgot that the
first time gotta be honest
that's why i threw it away i i sold it
you wanna
[Music]
heart level
uh defense 2021 but hours got like
extras to ours is still better unless we
saw put some stuff in the sockets right
and what about this one i need undefined
uh there we go
oh ten percent fat to hit recovery fifty
percent faster block rate ten percent
increased chance of locking eighteen
percent enhanced defense
truth life lightning resist plus nine oh
[Music]
that is a great shield
now i don't need a buy anymore because i
got the shield
what's that health shrine
i should probably stay on my path what's
that
my arm recharge no thank you not right
now
okay well uh sorry for um
destroying your party you had there but
honestly during these times you
shouldn't have
such huge parties anyway so that's that
it's not my phone where are we where are
we going exactly though
oh i don't use swords but we got a
yellow sword
don't run away
but when in doubt kill them with an
arrow
can't run away from that oh that one
went up in flames
i'm the fan police yes fun is over
where you can move stones i love that
[Music]
looking for a tree
looking for a tree okay maybe maybe it
is over there who knows
let's find out
[Music]
chest okay oh nice i need those potions
thank you
[Music]
thank you for the super chat
for me need arrows
oh you see that there ah afraid
yeah did anyone drop arrows
superior preserved head what
a head
that's for necromancers uh it's not
i don't need it right now i think i
need some arrows
no one dropped arrows you for real
and do we need to go home
that's okay maybe go home sell that
thing it's quite expensive okay
where did i drop it there we go should
we go home once
i mean i got a [\h__\h] ton of portals
well let me pick up what what i can
there anything else like in
buckler no that doesn't fit into my
inventory
i am over burdened
[Music]
why did you have to die
this one also i can't carry anymore
come on
what's underneath nothing
okay okay okay i'm going
oh sh okay i'll make my portal here
[Music]
hello
papa i did miss some golden earth oh
well
okay i use you uh please revive
uh oh it's getting more expensive
actually wait couldn't we
put something in in into this one ah
i wonder but this one is uh just great
should we use it with the software
let me just keep it in depth wait we can
give it to amaya
well you can get some oil oh
that's right
[Music]
when she dies though does it just land
on the ground or does she keep it
until i revive her
[Music]
not here greetings
identify sword before thank you for
reminding me
this one yeah okay we're selling that
holy whoa mommy mommy
okay she keeps it okay
should i buy something else
[Music]
we need some more identity identity
identify scrolls not here akara
thanks for hearing me uh
this one yes yes
yes
[Music]
oh my god
i didn't think i would run out of arrows
but you don't have that word
no
you got some arrows yes
[Music]
no oh yeah
should i repair two
in the mist
okay oh they're cheap
goes away put that there
and by the way dad i will sell that one
too
and no i want to take your picture
okay ready to go guys let's do
what we need to do finish another quest
find that
camp i guess oh i'm gonna read though
again go for it
yes search for the tree tree
okay i don't know
there's a lot of enemies here i'm in
danger again maybe we don't really need
to clear this
we forgot to store your gold again hi
cooking i will not die
this will not be uh age well i guess but
superior
who are you fighting with again huh
get that get that chuckles i'm in danger
that's a flag
okay i'll stay on the path i guess
generally the idea is to stay on the
path
we can do that why did i give her a
question did she have spots for potions
no
[Music]
is it are those better
her picture oh okay i will do that next
time she is about to
die i shall not let her go ever again
and the key shift number to give potion
to the nurse
oh i got some emeralds thank you because
i've used them earlier but that's okay
too
are you guys excited to play diablo 2
resurrected whenever it comes out
damaged hunter's bow
are you guys waiting for it did you guys
sign up did anyone get like a key
because you could sign up anyone was
able to sign up from what i've seen
yes yes it's excited excited okay okay i
asked so many questions it seems
cool actually is playing it now
or like has access i suppose not many
i want to play a java in amazon they're
nice yeah
i don't like alphas waiting for the game
release oh yeah
why not why not i mean you can also
still play in the old diablo i guess if
you really want to
play the full game right now you have
done your job well yay well where's my
job this stream is not sponsored by the
way this is just me
um sudden like seeing botan senpai uh
got invited to the to the alpha and me
being like please
i wanna play it too wait black marsh
who are you
this is not where i need to go
there was a waypoint ah really let me
use that real quick
damn it that that uses up so much is
that gonna stay there
i got a lot of potions too now
[Music]
all right let me put some in my let
me put some i am overburdened
[Music]
oh let me find that thing teleport back
sell stuff come back
i guess that one got the golden one no
that's not it
i hear this one there we go
whoa that wait what about stonyfield i
feel like i missed something
did i just not activate it what i was
there wasn't that
oh well
as far as i know there is no release
date someone in the comments
asked this is just the alpha but i think
there's no
no release date yet i could be wrong
though so
i can't guarantee anything um
i didn't find it but i was there wasn't
that damn it
do i need so many potions
i'm leaving some stuff here yeah it's
still alpha so i
i reckon it will take a while
oh anything else i wanted to get no i
wanted to sell this though i guess i'll
identify it
okay that's some money at least
[Music]
only four of each what you've seen
before how many i needed the [\h__\h]
okay now put one more in
okay not here going back to
the dark wood
[Music]
a tree guys have you seen a train
somewhere
should we ask some of the tourists oops
what did i just do
[Music]
should i have some of the tourists out
here
oh another chest
tree of influence yeah that's what i'm
looking for
[Music]
i have a skill point oh
multiple shots cold arrow
cold damage and the snowing effect ah
that sounds actually
actually quite nice might want to switch
over to that for a little while
focus on one element god damn it okay
wow that's okay it's just the alpha no
need to take it too serious right
maybe a bit more tell me
what do you think about my build is it
okay
you actually some people go full decks i
wonder
large axe noise noise
it's okay to try different stuff yeah i
guess so black marsh
do i really need to go here am i wrong
besties you're welcome to answer me
do i need to go through here i can't
carry anything you already can't care
anymore that was quick but who did who
revived you
what is writing you you [\h__\h]
no not yet oh god damn it okay i'm wrong
well well well i can't carry anymore
well i guess whatever it's there bye bye
[Music]
i could go to the final boss if i wanted
to
let's see maybe maybe i don't have to
follow the path maybe it's up here
have you seen a tree
surprise
i shouldn't get so close
what's what's happening what else she
doing
[Music]
i'll repeat myself no problem there's a
lot of people who didn't hear the story
yesterday
and when i was like i need months
uh in my sixth or seventh phoenix life
i um oh my god my mom
and my sister and my brother they all
played
they all played the apple too and
uh i kind of i guess i liked the look of
it i was scared of it loki but i still
wanted to play it so
my mom let me play it thank you mom
and that's maybe what started also
my interest in like other games because
afterwards a few years later
we started all playing world of warcraft
as a family
i was probably like in my eleventh or
twelfth year
or thirty thirteen fourteenth
uh life life things life
when i was playing that i was playing uh
world of warcraft yeah
and after motherfuckoff i was going
independent i was playing all kinds of
like anime mmorpgs
uh am i still going to wrong path
yeah game of family
it's quite nice because i got like a a
gaming piece like not a gaming pc but
like a decent normal pc quite early on
and my mom and my brother and everyone
was
always i think they knew what they were
doing
like they know their uh i'm gonna go
yeah but as i said i was really scared
of diablo so i never really got far so
all this
is uh still somehow like very nostalgic
to me but also very new to me
at the same time don't just
nothing
[Music]
full inventory again by the way should
we go
for the portal again it's right over
there
you've got a great family well thank you
[Music]
hmm
i guess we'll go again we'll go sell
again
i'm bringing them a lot of business
by the way the buff that i have right
now does it give me extra
exp is that what it is
tree is visible in the map you saw it
[Music]
i didn't see it was that close
i want to get blue or higher items yep
okay
yes yes what do you think yes to exp or
yes to
the tree
[Music]
identified
thanks guys how many do i have for
[Music]
and do you guys think i should keep all
these
charms well should i put them away
because they take up a lot of space but
i feel like they're pretty good
like this one gives me 12 maximum
stamina and extra gold
this gives me maximum stamina too
sure they're pretty good yeah but i do
have too many parts that is true
i actually i'm going to take more of the
smaller ones
wait do they stack
wow so many potions
i shouldn't be so scared to use them all
up huh
let's put one more here
okay why are these uh stacking and this
one isn't stacking
what it i don't know why doesn't
oh wait it's not like it's just one two
three four because okay
no problem i understand okay well then
get that that
is the hot piece yeah
and oops this goes here
okay sorry for the weight guys we are
back on an adventure
it seems we have uh too much potions yep
it seems we have found the tree
i didn't see it how did you guys see it
you saw i said it was in the mouth
[Music]
at the bottom there
is
oh my god
okay that was kind of lame i mean
i was lame uh should we go back into my
five
i'm sorry
i kind of want to go back and revive
that was so fast
ah reviver okay
maybe well while we're at it um take
some stuff with us we just cleaned
cleaned it all up but why not take some
stuff
damaged buckler
[Music]
get the tree click the tree first does
it give me
something oh maybe the question
haha they're running away power
it's all of you cowards thank you
what a strange looking tree oh i got
this growl i don't have to bring that
back
yes to akara now okay if we have to go
back anywhere and let me check out this
house
i can't carry anything can't carry shut
up
no can't be for real where can you apple
carry
do we ever get an uh an inventory
upgrade please say yes
i need mana yeah yeah
low quality light crossbow
but this is huge
[Music]
what is strange talking bath
never what like you can you never get it
oh my god they really want to trigger
you hot don't they i can't was it just
i wonder if that's what if that was just
something that was not possible like in
a technical way back then
because it's a really old game i could
actually believe that
maybe back then it was just not not
possible to
program that
[Music]
wait i'm sorting some things here
let me take that axle and where that
cell doesn't fit okay
what about that though i am over
breathing
there we go okay
going back pick up your potions
put the plushies in the bathroom i am i
know they're all filled up right now
cordon but there's one right here a free
one
right over there
okay that's quick we got time guys
uh rogue encampment
[Music]
oh i am back akara wait
let me store some things
[Music]
[Applause]
oh again good i have translated the
runes on this scroll
you must find the can stones and touch
them
in the order that i have written oh
okay thank you uh
how about
we identify them things and sell them
maybe
haunted spell of wolf
this one has more damage
but we got fancier like extra traits
59 to attack ratings 7 poison damage
yeah
oh i got that poison damage on the
enemies because of that ball oh
i was wondering
i would say get rid of that get rid of
that
get rid of wait can i can abbaya carry
the crossbar
crossbow class
also someone she could have that buckler
i guess when did i give her a shield
[Music]
she cannot use it all right whatever
i did give her a shield but i don't know
if it's better
probably not okay like you always say
drop your gold okay okay i'll go go go
[Music]
is more expensive all the time should i
just get someone else
the search for kind what is a sadquest
deckard kane has crucial knowledge about
the evils we face
you must find him
[Music]
no but what about uh other mercenaries
that's from mine i would have to play i
would wait um
she leveled up right wait what level is
abaya right now
should i keep avaya
prices increases per level ah
[Music]
well then i guess i just keep obayah
right she's back
otherwise say welcome back to abaya
thank her for all the troubles she's
been going through with me what do i
need to do
both of the karen's current stones in
the stony field touched the stones in
the order found on the scroll of
universe
do i have to still carry it oh my god
okay
oh oh
oh abaya thanks you all for welcoming
her back
where are those stones let's go find
them
[Music]
on my way
what what are you guys all saying
hakanisho is that the next boss
back on issue time who is that
i don't remember such a person or that
monster or demon
[Music]
i saw the stones already oh that's nice
okay wait am i summoning an enemy with
that i don't want to do that why is she
telling me to do that
yeah i saw the stones
what oh wait i'm back here
go to the cold paints ah
i have to go back where i came from
originally wrong area
back to the last zone yeah but wasn't
that did i didn't i not
come from here
stony field yeah that's where i did not
was just flashing oh
but i did not uh take a and activate a
portal there didn't i
oh like that i came from a tunnel ah
wait how did i get there use the way you
pour into the cold cold plains
okay where was it again
my point is all the way up here
cold planes stony field but i don't have
that activated yet
right sorry i'm going a bit
round about
could have also taken a a
scroll i guess shannon do you know what
time it is now well yeah it's half past
eight here
why are you trying to tell me that it's
really late at your place
well i'm sorry but trust me diablo is
worth it
[Music]
give items to mercenary ah maybe this
cap
where was she able to wear that she got
a normal
oh look at whoa look at that that's for
babari oh
too bad i can't really give it but you
know what i can give her 27 hours
what you can't use it oh i was going to
be nice to you but
i guess you don't need it
sell that cat should i take it with me
why did i not open a chest
okay well if we're going back to sell
something then
i'm once again taking as much as
possible with me
but we're just constantly selling things
now we're getting rich in diablo
it seems it seems actually rather easy
okay wait no not coal plants uh first it
seems rather easy to
get pretty rich in this game
and who do we want to sell to chelsea
oh oh okay
[Music]
oh okay okay bye-bye
that's all i needed you don't sleep if
you play diablo
i see a lot of people were very addicted
to
diablo perhaps so good wait where
up i guess
hopefully
[Music]
and then hopefully we activate the the
checkpoint
[Music]
what am i out there now
is it this is the right one
[Music]
i feel more skillful i feel it
hello
sorry anything any treasures in here no
lame lame thanks
you are an egg now you're part of kfp
now hope you're happy
so many well you kind of want to kill
them all night
i feel much stronger did you level up
again nice
and we're going we're getting off of
unmapped
all right wait wait wait wait wait
did you see it i see the stones oh but i
still don't have the portal the
checkpoint
but those are the stones aren't they
amit
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait wait i want to
look at it okay let's just kill him
first i guess
oh there they are okay are you know
their enemies want to disturb me
i'm gonna touch some stones okay this
has absolutely no
weird meaning so just leave me leaving
me
what is that extra stone doing there
okay what you're not gonna show me again
wait but i think i remember uh it was uh
i didn't you're not gonna show me again
but okay it's written there now
okay uh this one first
and this one yeah i remember that
should i be scared
oh it's a portal
what awaits us here
oh that could be uh good for her
no oh actually no
you know what put that there
okay let's go find waypoint oh [\h__\h]
i still didn't find it it's as if the
great war were fought here
blank like better oh i don't know why it
dropped oh no
is there still one
just okay go back find it okay
where is that why can i not find it
what shouldn't it be around you
maybe somewhere here
well don't bother with that there's just
some
idiots what is that dream
[Music]
okay let's kill them
oh did i oh
look for tower and black marsh oh that's
enough the next quest i already got that
one from here interesting
question
interesting short ball maybe something
for her
uh no
kill that freaking tree
oh it's already dead oh my god it looks
horrible
what did we do no that tree doesn't
deserve that kind of treatment
oh is the baby here again
[Music]
wait where is it oh and here is the cold
plants we don't have
no we do have the cold planes
teleportation thing right we need the
one that comes after cold planes
stony field it should be here read the
book okay one second one second one
second let me try to find this
stamina shrine oh wait that's what
stamina is before running isn't it
making me notice that that tree didn't
deserve that treatment
okay okay
okay that's fun thank you for that
[Music]
is it i have a feeling it's over there
come on come on
oh my god chill guys don't yell at me
what book
[Music]
did i leave an item there uh
i mean a quest book
what it was at the start ah that one did
i click the wing right away
uh uh oh okay chill
i need to go there in a moment
should we go to the city ones
we got a sword to sell
that was far away
go to stream might as well go to suit
yeah i might as well
okay one second we'll make it quick
i'm gonna earn some cash again i back
the twist and the phone well it's right
there so why not
not in town
[Music]
i'll leave some arrows in my because i
don't want to throw them away
not in town
okay not that much money but okay oh
wait actually why am i carrying uh
[Music]
i'm not carrying that with me
is that kelly in front on the front
cover of this game
nope that is not cali
but it's i guess it's one of her friends
actually it looks kind of like death
sensei in some way i guess
she's she probably knows him very well
i do wonder if she played diablo though
like she didn't answer it anymore did
she she only wrote one comment
abaya follow me
there we go you're weak
ghost rider oh yeah it also looks a
little bit like that
oh thank you i actually needed that
[Music]
oh i like string city i don't like it
look at
those drops again
okay actually i gotta level up too ah
because it's a scale okay
[Music]
what oh i want to sell those
or yellow
[Music]
man the inventory fills up so quick but
you know what we probably got enough
money anyway we don't really need to get
that
rich at least not like in the
alpha because we're only playing act one
and two
right so i could i might as well just
drop wait use the arm oh yeah wait
we'll use it myself what the hell what
nice i forgot i could use that i thought
that was maybe for another class
what happened to the cow oh
wait is that the camp is it dead
oh no oh wait i
switch oh my god what happened here
body oh i burnt it well i guess that's a
good thing
but we maybe we didn't need to pick that
one up the car was just sleeping
oh i hope so oh that's a lot of money oh
oh there's really a lot of money i feel
bad picking that
up oh maybe take some misters
[Music]
ellie
oh my god they barely take damage maybe
because of their shields
okay that was a welcome party that i've
never seen ever before something like
that
a very weird awkward welcome party oh we
got a blue
jawbone cap we can't carry it
oh come on we don't need that small
shield
ours is better
um we still got no gloves i would
appreciate some gloves
that beats welcome buddy get me listen
up
why don't you want me coming in tonight
for y'all
that used to be a pretty fountain not
anymore
[Music]
yeah oh my god still burning that wasn't
me i promise
i'm a phoenix and i like fire but
i don't want everyone to die
i'm a good thing i mean that happens
there have been evil phoenixes in other
worlds
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
wait can i even kill them
[Music]
there you go what was with him
a club i am overburdened okay
careful yep he was a bit strong
[Music]
chocolates
wait i'm doing something right now
[Music]
like famous like character or what
i'm sorry i just said i just felt like i
was in danger
[Applause]
the yellow one on the top right
help wait for me i rescue
you oh no that's our portal ah
where
[Music]
every now and then but i don't have
space right now anyway so
but i should maybe throw these away
i don't know i need to stand in the
potions at all
[Music]
oh wait we could get back to her
is that better than what she has yes it
is
[Music]
okay good luck with that oh i'm counting
on you don't die on me
we need you here hey guys
where is you so dark here
stupid skeletons
where is he where is he
the card i came to wait
no he's not in thank here
came to the center of town was he right
there and i didn't see him
that explains why i heard his voice ah
oh
i heard him it's so dark ah that's cool
sorry what's the daddy didn't hear you
deckard kane i mean i didn't hear you
but i didn't see you without delay
[Music]
oh you made a portal us
visit
oh that's rude okay if we have to go
then let me uh
take some stuff
okay okay okay
he ditched me why do i have to use my
own portal
tonight i'll just use the uh
there you go
i saved him yeah and he leaves him what
is his problem
[Music]
hello heal me oh i'm full healthy rest
your life to rescue you that was no big
deal actually that was really easy thank
you
you must seek his counsel immediately
does he know something
[Music]
i wonder i can
he will identify stuff for free for me
that's a token of my gratitude
i will identify items for you at no
charge
but only when i'm here okay that's why i
still need the book i guess
i don't want to identify things
otherwise prevent the disaster which
devastated tristram useless that our
greatest
fears have come to pass diablo
the lord of terror has once again been
set
loose upon the world as you know
some time ago diablo was slain beneath
tristram
and when our hero emerged triumphant
we held a grand celebration that lasted
several days yet as the weeks passed
our hero became increasingly aloof
he kept his distance from the rest of
the townsfolk
and seemed to lapse into a dark brooding
depression
i thought that perhaps his ordeal had
been so disturbing
that he simply could not put it out of
his mind
the hero seemed more tormented every
passing day
i remember he awoke many times screaming
in the night
always something about the east
one day he simply left and shortly
thereafter
tristram was attacked by legions of foul
demons many were slain and the demons
left me to die
in that cursed cage i believe
now that tristram's hero was that dark
wanderer who passed this way before the
monastery fell
i fear even worse my friend i fear that
diablo has taken possession of the hero
who sought to slay him
if true diablo will become more powerful
than ever before
must stop him or all will be lost
he took took control over some kind of
hero
i'm sorry i moved the microphone
diablo why
el diablo oh dear okay
oh well let's sell some things
talk to decor again okay not here
i went for items oh he just
automatically did that okay search for
candy forgotten
quickly in and quickly out is all the
advice i can give you
about is that about them
oh wait that's completed oh here we go
look for the tower and the black wash
beyond the dark wood okay that's our
next quest oh so we did free quest
in three hours should we
stop it around here
[Music]
wait no i can still ask him about that
even though i already
know what's up read the book i forgot
the book now
damn it greetings when i fled the
monastery i left behind the horizon keep
going
keep going enchanted smithing hammer if
you can retrieve it for me
i'll use its magic to strengthen your
maybe one more quest
that this one
okay i feel like for one i'm taking one
uh 40-50 minutes
for one quest it seems okay let's see
is there any anything that's better than
my shield no
defense eight minus 12. this is all [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
we don't need that we don't need this
either
we got a nice ring wait oh ring of light
15 attack rating light radius what is
that light radius
make me sparkly please
all right sounds oops sounds good to me
yeah i mean today was supposed to be my
birthday
and i i do plan to play i don't
oh wait we got this one too ah i do plan
to play
and okay let me tell you my plan because
everything's changing so my crew plan
although i'm not gonna say this is 100
fixed but my current plan is tomorrow
we have i think at 3 pm or something
like that we have um
uh the karaoke which i still have to
prepare for
it's a 900k you marry phone kinda okay i
hope we can
reach it during this stream a bit scared
to be honest
uh what did that
birthday that i said it's my birthday
what
[Music]
did they say it's my
i birthday order ramen today oh
what why a birthday
did i say it's my birthday is my brain
that broken
see my mind is somewhere else
so confused i mean today was supposed to
be my only break day of the week but i
got so excited and the thing is i don't
know when when the alpha is ending
so tomorrow uh after the karaoke
after we're done with that i want to
uh stream diablo again however i don't
know how long the karaoke takes
so we'll probably start around
[Music]
one hour after today maybe something
like that
happy birthday thank you i wish i could
do a breakdance for this birthday
to celebrate this big day we gotta do
breakdance but i can't
i'll try to learn it okay
i think yeah we should we should end it
here then tomorrow we continue and maybe
get a little taste of act free as well
i hope you will all join me tomorrow so
um and then on sunday so well tomorrow
the member stream will be
replaced by the uh by this diablo 2
resurrected
[Music]
and it will hopefully get even further
and then sunday
instead of neo tomata we'll be doing a
super long super chat reading
super chat reading uh where we hopefully
um
you know i wanted today i wanted to do a
spontaneous super chat reading because i
do have a lot to catch up on
uh which is a bit yeah bye but
yeah diablo happened
that's a priority i'm so sorry guys i
know that
some of you maybe want their super chats
read as quickly as possible
uh and not like five days later why not
do the super chat reading now because i
have to order food now
and uh today is my birthday
i don't want to stream too long on my
only birthday and it might take hours
and hours
let's just have a really long really
long super chat reading on sunday
yeah i hope that's okay for you guys
unless well let me see how much this
stream got maybe we can read the ones
that only came in in this stream
uh oh yeah i feel like i can do that
until my food but yeah i have to order
my food first
and then we'll read the super chat
where's my phone
and if my food comes before which could
quite possibly be if my food comes
before the super chats
reading is done then i might just stop
in between
i think that sounds like a plan so we'll
read the the diablo super chat now
because it's not that much
the others we will read on sunday
my voice hurts
[Music]
okay then for today that's it uh i'll
i'll take
two or three minute break uh into the
super jet intermission and then i'll see
you in the main
screen to do a little reading okay
thank you guys so much for joining this
is a lot of fun please join again
tomorrow
for some more
let's play as long as either the
technical alpha goes
or as long as um
act two is done because you got act one
and that too
let's see how far we go anyway a little
intermission guys
see you in a moment thank you all for
joining if you want to stay for the
super chat reading you're welcome to
stay
okay see you in three minutes
oh my god
guys oh no
oh no i closed it i didn't save
i closed it i didn't save this doesn't
have auto save does it
[Music]
[\h__\h] my god i hurt myself so much
no it's free oh i'm so focused i'm gonna
cry
[Applause]
it's three hours of progress it's
honestly i'm gonna let me check oh no
i don't think so cause it says like
leave and save
when you leave like i saw that when i
tested it out
but i have to also order food at the
same time no
no it saves really
8 amazon
[Music]
okay okay okay see you later
in five minutes
oh my god oh my god okay
okay my god i was about to cry
okay please tell me this ramen
oh my god
[Music]
um
okay oh my god thank god there's auto
safe i didn't even know
when does it save the whole time how
does it do that i didn't see any
like saving a function
was there anything like thank god
did the original game also have auto
save
it deletes your maps what do you mean
with that
uh when you finish quiet ah after it's
oh that was when we stopped at a good
point i guess yes it had okay okay
okay
[Music]
ah you mean reset resets maps as in the
enemy spawn again that i killed and all
that
kind of stuff
originally online
[Music]
so glad you didn't lose progress me too
oh my god
so i think i'm ready
i i will only read uh
oh hello no chat i will only read the
super chats from
uh this stream and the rest will be red
on sunday
and so hopefully
since my ramen is coming soon i wanna
read through them quick
i wanna once again say thank you so much
to um
whoever was in charge of giving me the
permission uh so quickly
to my own management and to you know
activision thank you
i'm so excited to play this game you
have no idea
when i when i when i opened the game up
i was already like
so nostalgic so
this is absolutely beautiful and i'm
also so excited that you guys are so
excited about it like the
hype was shared and makes me happy i
hope we can uh
tomorrow continue it with everyone it's
great that it's weekend right now so
i think it should be easy for most of
you to come to see the continuation
tomorrow let's try to
try to uh get act 2
finished maybe as well but it really
depends on how long
the testing phase goes honestly i have
no idea
i'll be practicing songs
before the stream and today i'm actually
trying to sleep early because i did get
up super early today
and uh didn't sleep that much i did
drink um
i don't do drink but i feel like i can
sleep i'll try my best
i'll actually try to sleep early today
yeah
i'll try my best
because i need some hours to uh to
practice it ends on the 12th what
oh there's info out there when it
actually ends oh i didn't know
because i i don't this was also
spontaneous that i don't have
all of the information i guess on the 12
hold on we have enough time
oh that's nice how was the doctor's
appointment it was really
um comfortable well
thank god because like i used to have
like a normal insurance uh like the
general insurance that you get
like anyone gets when you work at a job
in australia you get a free insurance
health insurance
and uh with the free health insurance
comes
all kinds of doctors where you don't
have to pay for anything at all which is
great but
those doctors are usually all overfilled
and they don't take much time for their
patients
and they're just often also not very
nice and i had that experience
uh with some doctors and
it was just like i had i had to deal
with it because i had that free health
insurance and that's what you get for
that
but this time since i don't have any
insurance at all right now i had to go
to a private doctor anyway
and she was really really sweet and
really kind it was not about my
shoulders or anything but we'll get to
that after i get my insurance which
should which
should be next week anyway we don't have
time to talk that much about that but
maybe we can talk some more about it
tomorrow or on sunday let me start
reading quickly
[Music]
okay let's go
i just want to express the deepest
amount of gratitude for blizzard giving
our sexy birth mother permission
to play this game same here oh my god
and thank you mama for playing this game
i am even more in love with you than
ever before and i didn't even think this
was possible
why because i'm playing diablo that
makes you like me so much
thank you thank you thank you i'm glad
to hear that
did you see the gay or european video
about you yes i saw it was hilarious
um oh yeah i also want to say once again
thanks to blizzard
or i i don't know who exactly was in
charge i feel like it was like the
japanese blizzard team
um because they also retweeted my my
tweets
on their uh diablo japanese diablo
account
[Music]
i don't know if they're still listening
but just wanted in case they're
listening just wanna say
thank you to japanese blizzard or like
japanese diablo
social media team or whoever is watching
so thank you have one more as well and
i'm glad you enjoyed it let's let's
uh play it until the end of act two
let's get as far as possible
hope you'll enjoy the whole journey
how long you learned japanese i got
fluent after like half a year and after
that i just
perfected it but i've been speaking
japanese for years and years and years
now but
in theory it only got uh it only took me
oh god
there's so many things i want to talk
about and you guys ask questions like
yes i got interviewed
the thing i posted on twitter but i
gotta uh quickly read the super chat
because my raven is on its way
but yes i don't know if you guys saw on
twitter but i got interviewed in
japanese it's in the japanese
magazine so mostly i guess this is
interesting for the japanese fans
interviewing
yes my childhood nightmare oh we didn't
see her yet i wonder when we will see
on ontario uh
she'll probably look as beautiful as
ever daisy thank you for read super chat
last stay awhile and listen you know uh
i like how you guys uh have the only
like nostalgic phrases that you hear a
million times in diablo
i like that we're all like bathing in
this nostalgia thank you daisy
thank you i hope you enjoyed today's
stream and i hope you're gonna enjoy it
tomorrow as well because we're
continuing this is gonna be
diablo 2 all weekend yes and thank you
thank you thank you thank you
thank you very much
i think he's not here right now he said
he wrote that he's gonna watch the
archive
but okay happy birthday
christophe sanchez and mrs duncan i
never could have imagined that you'd get
permission to play the album so quickly
after a discussion
yeah honestly i was just like after i
found out that
you know this is happening right now i
just kind of like
loki asked if this would in any way
anyway anyway be possible
and i honestly didn't think it would
actually be possible i was just
not believing much in it but it happened
it happened it was really sweet it was
not even 24 hours
at the start of this stream it was not
even 24 hours ago
that i found out about this in the first
place
so that is uh speed yes felix thank you
thank you for the rants
okay i have no idea is that a dialog
reference again we witnessed the
resurrection of the warrior once again
yes it's more games where i can fight
i'm excited
by the way diable was one of the first
pc games i played and it was the
beginning of a lot of my
kinks i guess well it's good to see you
playing
the games you love thank you wait what
kind of kings
why maybe the bot from the amazon i can
imagine you
must have been the reason why i like
butts so much too
cause looking at that amazon's butts
damn
oh my god look at that butt
look at that butt
that's that's a nice book yeah is that
is that the king that you have uh
developed felix is that it tell me about
it
it's a we don't we don't shame on any
kings especially not the butt kings we
like the butts
thank you please continue watching the
diablo streams we'll
we'll go as far as possible thank you
thank you i'm glad you're enjoying it
it's very nostalgic for me
and must have been also one of the first
pc games for me as well
i don't remember playing anything before
that i probably
played if anything maybe sims won maybe
but i'm not sure i guess that's
afterwards
a lot of stuff happens we'll do a diablo
free stream in the future i don't know
um i i don't know
we will see uh stimuli
spare the chickens it didn't seem like i
could kill any chickens anyway
jenkins monkey duncan the able to
basically define my gaming childhood so
happy to see you play the game even if
it's
still only just an alpha yes thank you
i'm also very excited thank you
right next to sanchez
you get scared of ruins well that's not
because of
him being in girls but just because of
his placement suddenly him showing up
like that that scared me
no i'm not scared of ghosts or anything
else it was just you know
yeah brian for no issues
it's really cute how excited you're a
boss thank you i don't know it's
i just it's you get when you play such
old games you get excited over the
most ridiculous things like the sockets
in in the items i don't know it's like
crazy like seeing the interface
seeing that the the the health and the
mana um
circle thingies everything is so
exciting seeing that
it's the simplest simple things the
simple things in life
changes review of the other two good
graphics but no booty yeah
it's it's lacking lacking the booty but
maybe
maybe there'll be more sexy outfits
eventually who knows
uh delbert kanye kid kiteside
of course the [\h__\h] is down here oh
happy to see your name your character
kiada of ch punk my can't be friends
because they keep pronouncing it wrong
they pronounce kiala with ch wrong did
they say chiara
ah stupid stupid stupid
nah that's not how you say it
uh suvitori takashin nck zero zero six p
and d donkey optimus prime thank you for
the pinky wow diablo 2 is also so
nostalgic for me remember the secret cow
level
i know there was something i never
played on my own i think but i i've
heard of it many times and i feel like i
probably saw it
uh like when my mom was playing but i
don't remember it
but eight bucks and streams oh suddenly
german
uh
food and the best games ever
technical
on
um
[Music]
and fun see you can hurt the chickens in
town oh
you can hurt them heard h-e-r-d
interesting we gotta check it out next
time
thank you and yes yes i hope no one is
mad at me for changing up the schedule
like this especially the members i'm so
sorry but
uh we'll do two member streams next week
i'm really sorry for changing it all
up
what why did that
h-e-r-d i'm not gonna hurt the employees
i would never do such a thing
mutes downgrading
goddammit kiana this game is hitting my
boomerang i already read that one
nostalgia but i'm so freaking happy
you're playing this hammered in for life
wait what's hammerton
is that some another npc
[Music]
yesterday nothing happened yesterday
shut up
you know not the way you wrote that
super i should help it but read it
read some things wrong i don't know
i don't want to say it out loud maybe
someone can't relate
because when i read this game is hitting
my boomer nostalgia bone
my my i'm adding some letters there and
it's very disturbing but thank you
thank you for i think that was a red
super chat thank you very much
it's okay i don't know you probably
didn't but
this makes me feel a bit uh weird
thank you
jesus morales irving thank you for
reading
hey kid are currently watching your
stream while getting over being sick oh
i was wondering if uh one when you once
you finished the stream you would
consider react
i already watched it yeah the game or
your friend why you guys asking me now
about it i already watched it
uh or the cost of concordia by internet
historian
and i would not react to the second
thing but i already wrecked the first
one um like
privately i think if you haven't seen it
look up
chiara gay or european on youtube it's a
great video
i don't know the original joke but it
was still funny to me
thank you donald
thank you very much i'm glad you uh
are feeling hopefully better
already or if not then hopefully you'll
feel better soon
just keep on watching kiara i will give
you life
and energy i'll give you a good kick
ricky let's go
there the minimum age to play diablo 2
uh 16 or something like that but it's
okay
i i had my parents parental uh
how to call it my my mom was
was protecting me oh she was always
there when i was playing the game until
the week
so that's that's something else right
then it's okay right
oh i supervision yeah i had prior to
supervision
it does does that still matter whatever
it's all good but
i was shocked to hear how young i was
back then oh my god
that's crazy that's so surreal
dice bar dan question mysteries thank
you one of the best streams you've ever
done
what oh missus at what point did you
write that wasn't that quite early
seeing you enjoy yourself and reveal
reveling in nostalgia as a treasure
can't wait for more diablo too thank you
i'm glad i'm i'm gonna be honest i was a
bit nervous because um
so many people watching i wanted to do
progress but
i'm gonna do it on my own pace uh
and uh i mean i got i got a little bit a
little bit
lost but not exactly i think we're doing
we were doing quite well were we
i think we're making progress well
enough right
hopefully you did great
you did good thank you you did just fine
okay
and uh i'm getting used to the fighting
system too sometimes i forget which
buttons uh like shift and out i
sometimes um uh forget
like like my hand is not quite used to
the controls yet
but we'll get there and i'm glad it's
not as
not as difficult as i thought it would
be i died a few times but it was okay
at least dying uh and picking up my body
is not
as stressful as it is in near automata
somehow in new york tomato it stresses
me out way more
okay
dynamic infrared
[Music]
2 stream kiana i'm looking at my diablo
2 cd-roms
and thinking of reinstalling that do it
do it does
does it even run on like new pcs now
because i've heard that like older games
sometimes don't even run
on the new pcs nowadays
is that a thing i feel like sims 1 for
example i heard something like that if
you would try to play sims 1 on a new pc
right now you might have issues
but anyway if you if you can't do it and
you feel nostalgic go a little
go on a little nostalgia trip with a bit
of tinkering it runs it had a patch
oh nice
okay okay by the way everyone talks
about diablo 2 in diablo 3. but what
about diablo one
is that good too i never heard of i
never hear anyone speaking all about
diablo one
is that good too clever
once again thank you for the huge i
don't know if you're still here but
thank you for the huge red super chat
500.
hello back to you thank you for the
genuine
huge support thank you so much the other
one is great too
diablo is great it was good
[Music]
did dad ever get a remaster
well why is diablo 1 ditched and they
just went straight for diablo 2.
[Music]
did that ever get a remaster
no and probably won't well that's a bit
sad
[Music]
okay well once again thank you caleb
hope you're enjoying the streams
and uh thank you thank you for the
bottom of my heart it's really not
necessary to throw
out such huge huge donation
but i'm i'm glad that you're spending
your time with my streams thank you
yeah thank you
hey if you ever have the diablo itch can
i recommend the torchlight game to you
oh i lose it was there a second person
[Music]
who suggested torture is that the person
where i was that that i
read already before torchlight
um i am curious but
oh at the moment i have absolutely no
idea what that is
never heard of it and we probably don't
have permission for it
hmm well thank you thank you dolce v
that was him oh okay okay
pk scratch duncan
[Music]
lots of ways to make money all right are
you trying to
are you trying to uh
uh what's the word ah
but i hate it when i can't think of the
words that i want to say
i hate it
i can't think of it
are you now not implying are you make
like making up
making up for uh that's not the word
what i mean but maybe a similar word are
you
what was i no i forgot what i was
generally trying to say
i am like trying to talk something
better
no [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] i don't i don't even know i was i
don't know i don't know
justify justify i guess yeah maybe
that's the word i was looking for thank
you
are you trying to justify the way that
cali is charging money uh from me every
time i die is that it
i think that's what i was trying to i
think that was what
i was trying to say thank you
thank you daisy thank you
honda morrison
remastered version isn't good well you
have to judge by yourself
by watching my stream and then later
playing it yourself
i hope you like it cyrux thank you soon
thank you it's monkey donkey soon have a
lori thank you soon
i'll try to remember that redundant the
nostalgia is overwhelming yes it is oh
my god
some of my best gaming memories is
playing this with friends you see
since i was super young i i didn't i
didn't even know this game had an online
function i guess maybe my mom probably
uh played it online but i never played
it online i just played around
on my own a little bit and killed a few
zombies and that's it
but i never played it online maybe if
the remaster comes out
maybe some of the other girls uh want to
play it with me
and then wait how many players can you
play with is it four again don't tell me
it's the four
again it's always four it's always long
how many can you play it with
up to eight oh that's good okay okay
cause i feel like callie would
definitely like it
girl would probably like it you would
probably like it too
i'm i would probably i think everyone
would like it honestly
maybe they already like it maybe they
liked and played it before as well who
knows
possible full collab yeah but who knows
when that ever comes out
might still take a long time
don't don't get too hyped up yet
don't get too hyped up is callie a
dungeon coil type of player
i'm not shooting actually what she
played like
oh didn't she already play something
like that is that is that called
dungeon crawler but she played like a 2d
uh dungeon but i feel like just the
whole atmosphere of diablo is totally
her thing
anyway continue continue no time no time
[Music]
where was i jacob brown
thank you and it's so cool to see one of
my favorite videos playing one of my
favorite games of all time thank you
i went hard thank you did you get your
ramen it's all the way
thank you doctor have fun with your
pizza
set dec
[Music]
first approach i swear by god said my
first super chat will go to the one
halloweens
playing rapper e or eva starcraft or
diablo so i think i'll become a member
now as well
sorry if my english is bad it's not
better though thank you oh my god
you you were you had this uh
determination
that whoever plays starcraft or diablo
first will get you first super shot
that's funny
well thank you thank you very much
i hope you're enjoying it you must be a
huge fan of starcraft and diablo
i hope i can play diablo
so well that it's up to your
expectations and
that it doesn't make you mad
[Music]
black happened when you started the game
and then when creator ported to tristram
at that moment game was written
generally oh you're telling it to me
so detailed thank you yeah whenever it
was like loading the game or something
like that it did lag a little bit i
guess but that's okay
yeah used all your pc resources
generated as fast as possible but it was
no upc phone yeah i think it was okay
after everything was loaded it went
smooth right i'm gonna check the
archive though to see uh how it went
gonna check it out ex legendary hero
danke
uh uh snake logan
tong paw foo donkey sharon bones balloon
thank you for the pinky
me and the other skellies all always get
bullied
oh i still appreciate the attention
balls
you're welcome i'm just playing around
with you guys y'all are
made out of bones so it it doesn't hurt
too much does it and you can just all
assemble
yourselves back together right did you
try capping the fps
on me yes i did try but it didn't change
anything at all
i think like me being myself whenever i
lag or don't i haven't been 60 fps for a
long time i think i think that's really
just the internet
um can't do much about that
i skipped your question again if kenny
looks like gooda would you love her to
say more or less
well the same i guess although
kelly i i don't want kelly to look
different
kelly's sexy the way she is jason
yeah redundant
david jackal jacob another cool thing
and having a great need to play diablo 2
again thanks for bringing back so many
nostalgic feelings for this game again
get that ramen killer thank you
i hope i hope
[Music]
that you had a lot of fun today and
maybe maybe yeah you can
get back into it but first continue
watching my stream
and after the alpha maybe you can get
into it again
first priority kia stream then
play on your own
honestly i was i was so mad because i
was thinking like i have no time
tomorrow to
uh privately play three hours worth of
this game again because i gotta practice
songs and stuff
yeah so thank god
thank you james probably you were you
were
my good luck charm weren't you there's a
full function
oh duck quack happy birthday quack
[Music]
you're making fun of me are you trying
to repeat me is this one of those
moments where someone always repeats
what you say
and it's getting like really annoyed and
i say don't repeat what i say and then
you say don't repeat what i say and i
say stop it and you say stop it
don't do that tight team don't have time
for that today
this was fun i'm so happy that you
finally got ramen yeah i've been craving
it for a while honestly today i'm not
craving it that much but i feel like i
have to get it today
it's gonna be yummy for sure
wait i like today's pumping so much i
wonder what i should do with tomorrow's
from now either i just added a part two
to it or i
change it up but there's not many
pictures
that are like usable except like you
know
in-game screenshots which don't look so
good and thumbnails
maybe i'll just add part two to it
ah hey bishop thank you for the pinky
it feels good seeing diablo 2 again i
remember experimenting with different
characters and watching you enjoying it
so much brings me back
excited to play this game again thank
you attention yeah me actually
um same i think i was also trying out
like
at least all of the female classes
uh and just playing around with all of
them
there is a one more or two more that are
not available right now
i think one more because now we can the
female characters we can play the
source sorceress and the
amazon but i think there is one more i
forgot what what that one is called like
but
assassin oh yeah that's that's the one
i definitely tried to play that one too
before
so thank you thank you shadow yeah
thank you dominique
thank you for the pinky yakuza soon and
playing diablo now your channel is
looking different but that's not a bad
thing you are showing how colder your
game tastes can be thanks for the
massage trip
thank you oh yakuza was also
to be honest something i would have
normally not picked up if it
uh if i wouldn't have gotten the offer
um to have a sponsored stream but now
that i did pick it up i was very
excited and i really liked it so
yeah um i'm grateful for the opportunity
and hope we can continue
it soon i will also thank you for the
pinky
looks like i'll be reselling diablo 2
thanks to you do you still have the cd
singing play reminded me of the first
time i ever played the game with my
mates so thanks for the decider trip
you're
welcome that's great so many of you are
feeling that way it seems and i'm glad i
could
um yeah get that feeling back to you
it's great to you know get those old
games back out there sometimes and
maybe also play with friends again maybe
you can get your friends to play with
you too
um donkey shin thank you for the support
looking for the top thunderstorm cyber
cranky for a pinky thank you for this
amazing trip down memory lane this
nostalgia is real i'm certainly looking
forward to more diablo too
also looking for my copies right now
another one
can't stay for the super chat reading
since i have work tomorrow have a good
night and a good meal thank you thank
you
have fun with being able to feel sparse
fabric
thank you for watching the stream and
good luck with work tomorrow
mr casper media is available as an ebook
ah
in the japanese candle kaiba kindle
store and may be available in your
country if you use a vpn please search
any media
2021 uh fifth uh uh
uh march uh i make
make a fifth month and
japanese month system kind of confuses
me kindle version
uh yeah guys if you want to read the
magazine
it's all in japanese but maybe you have
a friend so you buy it yourself and then
show it to a friend who can read
japanese and then they can maybe
translate it for you i don't know uh
it's not free
so if you want to read the interview you
need to buy it but it also has uh the
profiles of all the other like
handwritten profiles of all the other
um whole live english girls it might be
interesting and cute and something
special to have
since at the moment this whole live
english is still pretty fresh
there's not much uh of this kind
of stuff uh so i think it's very
precious i i hope
uh i can get one of those magazines
well the real one not the online version
i hope i can get it sometimes
probably my manager is gonna get it and
give it to me next time i come to japan
yay yes i was interviewed just check my
twitter for more info
um
it has a fan-made recording of exophile
which makes it playable on modern system
oh
interesting playing rockers free on a
guy
listen everyone to this super chat
attention you're wearing me the other
day
saying you have breathing issues just
making sure you're okay i still have
lung issues but you're the cause of mine
you see
you leave me breathless
guess i'll just say i'm glad you're
fixing your health your streams matter
but you met the most thank you that's
very sweet
uh i'm only 89 donkey shin thank you for
the pinky just really quickly want us to
say
that i love you a lot and that you are
precious and always entertaining goddamn
yeah looking forward to the
karaoke stream tomorrow enjoy your ramen
thank you emily
that's so cute thank you very much very
very kind of you know i appreciate the
support
so much thank you i'll do my best
tomorrow in the karaoke we haven't sung
in a while again so let's have fun
tomorrow and hopefully
reach our goal i'm i'm as i as i said
i'm
quite nervous because we still have what
over five thousand six thousand to go
and i wonder if we can reach it too low
if not then well we'll go on forever and
ever and then
just quit with uh while failing but
let's let's try our best let's hope it
works
yeah i've done it before but i don't
know if i can do it again
duck quack duncan dead [\h__\h] duncan
honestly the last time that i did it was
kind of fun it was kind of like
a fun event you know so i was like i
want to do the marathon again the
marathon karaoke
it's like a celebration at the same time
so why not it hits like two birds with
one stone
so that's why i'm doing it but
i'm nervous okay let me refresh one last
time
[Music]
uh thank you
thank you happy birthday thank you
and if i didn't thank you that changed
from widescreen for free was actually
nuts i've never played this game but i
definitely will watch you play it
you never played it but have you seen it
before or was this the absolute first
time we've ever seen it
i love seeing you excited seeing you so
excited to play this i can't wait to see
more also you're out of mana that is
something you hear so
often in this game that's i think that
and full inventory
are those things that you get so sick of
but yeah uh we're done reading super
chat sorry nance kuma we're done
[Music]
definitely heard it before first time
here as well well so a lot of first
timers too
awesome you are uh now seeing a
legendary game
well you've seen the legendary game
being remastered
uh trust me it is uh you're witnessing
something beautiful
legendary okay so thank you guys
uh for support today i'll see you
tomorrow for karaoke
[Music]
and enjoy myself
do
[Music]
you