[Music]
oh
m
[Music]
n
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
can't hear myself so well there we go
kitty
[Music]
hello
hello let me turn this
quiet y what's up what's up
Kiki what's up guys I did I slept so
much and I had such weird dreams and I
think they were also kind of like 7 Days
to Die related and all kinds of weird
[\h__\h] again but less nightmarish more
like
interesting yeah I should write I should
write things
down it's quite
interesting yeah
um so I woke up at like I was going to
wake up at like 700 p.m. but then I
extended my sleep slept till like 8:00
p.m. cuz I also was awake way too long
again like halfast 10 or 11:
a.m. I oh YouTube buffering well so far
my OBS says no drop frames so so far my
internet is still doing okay but
recently there's something weird going
on so I don't know if it will stay okay
I'm sorry sorry if it's going to be
unstable again
today uh we'll see what happens yeah I'm
not getting any sunlight right now um
the only reason why I'm mentally okay
because I would assume that that doesn't
have a good effect on you normally the
only reason I'm okay is because the
collabs have been so fun and the
interactions have been so
fulfilling um so that's very very much
balances it out or like makes it even
better yeah I I'm still not taking my
vitamin D [\h__\h] we're currently I'm
taking vitamin
fauna which sounds like a very good
vitamin to
take uh but yeah um I haven't taken a
nap because there's I purposefully slept
longer to not give myself enough reason
for a nap
uh and not sure how long we're going to
play today but surely not over 4 hours I
added this extra hour so that we could
read some super chats so let's not waste
this time too much happy birthday
jino I do have some Coca-Cola to keep me
awake if need
be and I should be fine like there's no
lack of sleep and I'm very used to this
time
sleep schedule by
now
um but I hope you guys have seen right
before the stream I
uploaded the 500k
Milestone
reward my dance shot fixed angle version
of Mirage I always wanted to do
something like this um I couldn't do it
for Kim
because Kima as you may know I recorded
it at home with my accents and
apparently the motion data was so janky
and scuffed no matter what I did that it
wasn't usable like at least not with
many Cuts in between and even then it
would look shitty that's why it didn't
happen back then um but for Mirage I was
able to just use the motion data from
the
studio when I recorded it there
thankfully this has been making many
things possible although when it comes
to the YouTube shorts uh the solo one
was also this data but the crony one was
extense at home it's I I recorded quite
a few in advance and uh interestingly
enough it's doing quite well it's not so
janky right now so I am delighted maybe
it's a choreo graphy thing maybe Chima
had a lot of movements that would make
it more janky it was more intense
honestly I don't know what your
impression is guys uh maybe Mirage looks
more intricate than it really is thanks
to the backup dancers I really think
that is the case
but um actually Kima is way more
intricate and intense so I
think the tracking it's not so much that
the tracking can't keep up it's more
like
probably like especially the the the
tracker on the hip would often be like
wobbly wobbly wobbly I wonder what that
is I think it's just yeah not that it
can't keep up it's just
too intense I don't know so with Mirage
yeah it's it's very hand focused very
arm and hand focused and those seem to
not do too many issues but I'm surprised
I'm surprised that me me me me me Raju
the hip shaking cuz I had troubles with
the hip tracker before I'm surprised
that that doesn't look weird but it
looks
good yum yum yum Coca-Cola yum
yeah too much joint movement for the
tracker um get yeah I don't know I think
it's something like
that um we got to try try it again maybe
I don't know if it's just like a
temporary thing that's looking better
right now or if it's a choreography
thing should try I should try dancing
Kima again and see if it's doing better
now
no but yeah oh Sean is in the chat Sean
finished up the the model for me to use
at
home and so um converted it to me for me
and uh adjusted it for me for several
applications yeah
so I'm ready for the million
baby I'm ready for
it I'm so ready for it I'm excited I can
I'm thinking should I I don't know I
don't even know what I'm going to do um
in terms of content but maybe I'll try
to teach you guys the dance even though
I feel like most of you won't really
attempt to learn it anyway but maybe I
could go through the the coral pretend
that I'm teaching it to you I don't know
or just do a k I don't know like the
fever night
K I don't know yet I think I think
everybody's happy with whatever as long
as I show off the
model Yeah dance
school I'm trying to learn the hand
movements ah the hand movements they're
so important um they're the point and
the problem is that okay no matter how
good the motion capture is
it's difficult to show it very
accurately I want to if you're learning
it right now let me give you one uh tip
uh the moment
the ru part
starts the I'm pointing two piece like
like okay both hands are in a piece sign
and I'm pointing it
down uh on the side of my hip pointing
it downwards connecting it to a shape
shape an M I don't know if people
noticed that it's supposed to shape an
M that's where how it starts in that
position and then I'm pulling the the
two pieces apart at the first m is a m
then at the the second me I think I'm
pulling them apart one after another me
me me me you know and then I'm bringing
them over at the top on on my head but
then then the PE signs are already
disappearing I think but in the very
beginning it's starts with the m and
then uh one goes to the other side of my
hip and then
wait oh yeah I'm just like separating
them basically one to the right one to
the left H I don't know if it really
looks like an m in the motion capture
that's the problem I don't think it
looks like an M unless I mean honestly
it's not it didn't look too bad but
maybe they're a little bit too far apart
so that it doesn't look like I'm
connecting them
[Music]
but yeah that's what's happening but
don't worry about it like anybody who
wants to cover it you can um I know it's
difficult to learn a Coro from a
3D footage cuz it's never going to be as
accurate as the real people dancing
it yeah those hand are you're a
choreographer
what you're a choreographer was
heyo fun oh smoothie is coming here to
take a seat on my xense shirt again she
likes
it you want to be with me you want to be
with me in the room h i led her into the
garden for a while today and when she
came back in she was so like her fur was
so like refreshingly cold and I hugged
her and then her paws I squeezed them
and warmed them up because her paws the
the the the what do you call the fleshy
Parts again those were so cold to the
touch I had to squeeze them and and warm
them up and rub her toe beans yeah her
toe beans I was rubbing them warm all of
them feels so good I wonder if she like
feels cold at that point or or if she's
not really very bothered by it but her
toe beans are were so cold
M yeah my baby
girl my baby girl I love you so much
wait it's already it's already 20
minutes
in but I want to yap yap yap well okay
before we go let me just remind you
let's look at this next is Ollie at 600k
and we're already like very close to it
it's going so fast I'm so happy I feel
like it's working my Pro I mean we would
get to a million anyway but I feel like
my
promotion is
working my girl cat used to Crown into
bed and warm up her a oh that's cute but
on your back that must have felt like ew
Shivers for a
moment yeah I do think it bumped the
speed a little bit didn't it like it it
was fine on its own on the first day and
the second day okayish too but uh then
it slowed down a little bit and now I
think it became faster again so yeah
it's doing really well I'm
glad and I didn't even realize but
Ollie has her new outfit now so we're
thinking of uh making her use the new
outfit cuz it looks so [\h__\h] sick yeah
yeah looks so
sick your cat's first birthday man I
wish I
really had their real birthday but I
know you guys always say just make up a
birthday no it's not the
same I'm so glad I think I will always
aim for the future to have a dance shot
version just for me for my own
satisfaction you know I really love
watching these kind of dance versions
for other uh K-pop groups and also Jpop
groups back in the day um it's just very
interesting so I want to make sure to
always do it in the future too um
hopefully I'll get you know good motion
capture going for my future songs then
yeah yeah I often like them more than
the official
mvs I I I think it's just like
refreshing and a different angle
literally and yeah I for for people who
like dancing and like even doing dance
covers and so on these are very very
precious and
yeah y dance short at 10 million I was
uh real resorting my originals playlist
I finally changed it to have the newest
songs be at the top top of the list and
the first to be seen on my uh main page
um just because I want people to get
right into Mirage but and
Kima what was I going to say ah and I
saw that duyu has 8.2 million views wow
I can see a future where it might get 10
million
huh yeah that' be crazy I feel like for
[Music]
me I feel like uh looking at the
Japanese members
releases the very successful successful
ones get like 10 Millions here and there
right that's that's amazing for me I
feel like on the I side it's still a
little bit more difficult to reach those
numbers but I don't care I'm really
happy already I always feel very
accomplished and I'm very very grateful
for all the all the people who look into
my music and stream my
music to me like 1 million is already
huge and very
satisfying
yeah very
satisfying I'm going to keep on going my
way when it comes to music I'm going to
keep on going my way and keep on trying
there's definitely times where I feel
like it's a bit frustrating because
music does not make me money making
these things does not make me money I'm
I think I'm generally losing money
especially because I'm putting a lot of
money into the music
videos um I'm definitely losing money if
it wasn't for the music videos I might
not be losing money
but uh for now yeah but that's not even
because it's doing bad it's not doing
badly it's doing like better than you
know maybe the average but um that's
just a reality of music like yeah
royalties and
stuff and well my percentage isn't very
good either but uh passion project yeah
it's really a passion project I just I
love where I'm going with music right
now I'm very satisfied with my direction
and with the production value of
everything I I just really
found my
Niche uh thanks to asteroid and thanks
to kind of
and we I think we've like
definitely became a well-oiled car I
don't know how to say
it n that wasn't windows don't worry it
was actually stupid chat notification
from my best friend just kidding I I a
wellow machine yeah that's it close
enough um yeah building my brand exactly
and I I think it's working and I'm I'm
really I'm really like motivated and
proud and I'm going to continue doing
what I'm doing I I I I had a a rare
conversation with my best friend today
like we don't I think I told you before
we like we're all busy we don't talk
that much but we love each other and I
called her I I was going to call her
today to talk about a possible Spa visit
that she doesn't have time for but we
wanted to discuss it I wanted to discuss
it only to be turned down just kidding
um maybe I'll I maybe I can go with my
sister or so but um I called her and the
moment she picked up the
phone like right before I already
snoozed and then the moment she picked
up the phone I also sneezed in that very
very second the first initial second and
I sneezed and I thought she wouldn't
catch it because maybe it takes a a
second for the call to really get
through but she heard it and the first
thing she said was gide and I was like
ah thank you all right that's all I
wanted to hear cuz you know when you
live alone nobody says gun to you so I
just wanted to call to hear that thanks
bye that was a joke though but that was
so funny we just laughed for a whole
minute after I sneezed and she said
kazun that was
[Music]
funny try thanks for the offline sneeze
um
contribution thank
you yeah 500k yeah we're already well
over 500k I'm a bit stressed
now I don't know how chy is feeling but
our our shorts production
company uh Factory is a bit
stressed we got to go fast I don't know
man six especially from 600 then to 650
that's oh all those I decided to make
those 50k gaps that's going to be a
little bit
stressful no I don't I'm I I have uh you
know the motion ready for some of them
um for the first couple um but you know
the motion has to be cleaned up and then
put together and everything um that a
little bit it's not that easy it's not
that like one click I'm done no
no uh and then yeah the later ones
are not recorded
yet it's fine it's fine it's
fine it's uh yeah we I mean not
everything has to happen exactly at the
time of you know right as long as I
deliver eventually
we'll try to keep
up damn it's already been half an
hour and no no pressure right even the
full dance video was a few K uh late but
um let's read super chats quickly um
before I waste this time completely well
let's keep this up as a reminder that
this did you all watch it I hope you
watch it guys if you didn't watch it yet
watch it after the stream or watch it
now um but yeah um let's see thank you
so much
GD aha that's
stream oh oh oh P also has a tribe n
stream huh
CI and P are doing their tribe n streams
tomorrow today
whatever depends on your time
zone
mhm uh uhuh let's
[Music]
see the corrupted
stream with my blue
screens all right well I'm not that
far could be worse
could be worse I feel
like all right let's
read I know I know what fauna said yeah
I watched the like a
clip I did write her a
message yeah okay let's go Jacob 47 d I
wonder if she saw the moment where I
wrote fauna into my into my crafting
window can STS d py d strike warlock D
strike warlock D FY
d py d dug Hood
D thank you and for the pinky as well
thank you dug Hood we love you Boss I
love you guys too thank you for your
sweetness by the way I think I saw you
sending a big Super Chat to ollie you're
so sweet you're always so supportive and
so so
generous very very sweet you're making
me proud of my
chickens you had a stressful couple of
streams I guess I did did I was
this I mean that was that was one
stressful stream for sure
yeah and that was around the time of I'm
announcement [\h__\h]
Luigi ah the the windows
noises right uh what was it
uh was this
uh was this I had them before the stream
too but
wasn't it in the collab but I
it what was
it it didn't
like ah H talk was after that okay yeah
yeah yeah that was stressful the yeah
yeah this whole week was a
bit uh emtional and scuffed Windows
scuff is gone now and blue screen scuff
is gone now but now I have internet
scuff
bro it is what it is we get through it
ups and downs SI Dan Brandon danash
baseman Dan with
Brandon your profile picture and I don't
think you had that title before what
happened that's that's so funny those
horns must be heavy
a Great Horn
chicken what made you what compelled you
what made you choose this new
self nice
antlers wait you must have did you take
this picture yourself looks very
self-made did you do you have these
antlers at
home so
horny nice wreck
[Music]
I like it it's an unusual chicken to
behold you bought some reindeer amplas
off the internet why for this purpose or
just because you're interested in having
some for like decoration what how big
are they
actually the plushy is relatively big
but in
for no reason other than this G for
real I don't understand you but you're
funny you seem like a funny
person oh amusing am I like to see it I
I want to see this chicken more often
basement dun py dun Nathan cotton thanks
for the pinky honestly pure text stream
would be really interesting stream very
reminiscent of the second Lord of the
Rings watch along when you were sick no
but also this it reminds me more of the
time in winter when I was sick as [\h__\h]
like I always am and was streaming with
my bronchitis and laryngitis and what
was the third
thing there was a third
thing that was
sick was [\h__\h] sick
yeah ligma yeah that was the thir thing
yeah sinus infection right shut up why
is there several people saying
Lima you guys are lost
causes
Cruz Jason Hood pyro Kenny St
py G
spacy
frood thanks for the pinky
Y without sound our boss is amazing must
spoil thanks for the stream bu thank you
very much very very very much I
appreciate it yeah that was it was a bit
disappointing cuz um yeah I think I
wanted to have one normal stream before
the announcement cuz this was before
right right before I
think I think I just wanted to have one
more normal stream where you guys didn't
know
yet and I could just um yeah not worry
about
that uh and then I had to move it and it
became the next day and then that was
known so originally I was going to do a
member stream and just like quietly talk
to you guys about you know the
announcement um but
yeah then it became a public stream oh
well
yeah well thank you though for being
there for me
guys Psy D and space waterful
d yeah
[Music]
yeah
okay the
Dodgers have been defeated once again I
heard that they're
like that they got a whole life buff
like somehow or was it that no no it was
something else but I think that may have
also happened I was something else that
I'm thinking of right
now oh they did turn it around back then
huh well I was just thinking of
something else my memories are um
merging thinking of like something I
read
about I think it was K-pop related that
whenever a
female uh K-pop Idol does the pitch
for I don't know that team or that
Stadium or whatever that's whenever a
female Idol does it they lose there was
something about that that I read I was
like oh that's
funny
okay maybe because they get
distracted pretty female Idol does the
first pitch whole team gets distracted
understandable all right uh the real
balatro stream also has some super chats
oh and these are after the
announcement let's get through them I
have 23 more minutes
minutos y let's
go ooh pretty
lady just like you guys Cruz Dan ja 47
Dan sent Phillip Juma one Dan happy
belated birthday yay hope you had a good
one com D Studio rap thanks for the
pinky the mid four year anniversary was
so much more poignant when tentu sang
chiku taku honestly I don't know how you
kept from
crying new song The Ballad of the yellow
Hearts s is a Eternal am is
forever yeah know I mean I was still
like like I
guess that was a while ago cuz it was
obviously also pre-recorded
and I mean yeah there were there were
moments where I had to think about
it but thankfully I was still like
emotionally distant from it because I
was still thinking oh still got some
time still got some time a little bit of
time at the point of recording
it yeah
and yeah we couldn't even like because I
mean we I couldn't be sad during it
because at when this would be streamed
people wouldn't know yet
so uh which was
on purpose am me didn't want to have the
um fourth year anniversary stream be all
about her leaving and so on and and that
I think was good um but then again the
shock afterwards right after this
feeling of
hi when you just celebrated the fourth
anniversary and then it's like
oh
yeah that also hurts it's it's
unfortunate it's there's no way around
it I don't know if it's better to do it
before or after it's just yeah the
timing is well
well yeah the Whiplash
yeah yeah and I I was like definitely
internally feeling throughout the
whole anniversary streams and all
that like oh man everybody's like the
fans are also so so excited and yeah
looking forward to the future and and
I'm thinking oh man they don't know what
I
know
so yeah that that was a bit rough having
to keep that for myself
and pretending like everything's
okay
mhm but
at the same time I'm glad we were able
to celebrate the fouryear anniversary in
a in a pretty normal
[Music]
manner
no I hope I hope she's happy as well and
I'm sure whatever she will do she will
be
successful and
um yeah I I I I understand it you know
I I get it I understand why she chose to
do this and
um I've said this several times before I
don't think any of us thought we would
do it this long the fact that we have
been doing it for 4 years now is already
I think worth a lot of respect
and you know it's a long time to be
doing
this kind of entertainment job and
I I I think it's it's at a point where
it it might be normal that somebody
wants to move
on
so um I shall support that even if it's
difficult especially cuz we're like the
first gen and having
that uh like kind
of like an end of an era so to say
um it's yeah
difficult that's definitely one thing I
was concerned about but it's bound to
happen at some
point yeah yeah yeah yeah
the Coca
colola silent little
BS
yeah yeah I'm proud of her
accomplishments I hope she's proud of
her accomplishments too
and I'll always be missing her
yeah but she's she's around of course
she's here and she's
there not it's not like
she's just scraped off the Earth
thankfully but yeah it is the end of an
era more or less
mhm I
have not talked to her yet
since
mhm I actually
haven't but I
can she can always hit me up I can
always hit her up
mhm why do I have to fix that I don't
know what to say anyway like it's uh I
don't know maybe it feels a bit awkward
right now I don't know what to say
[Music]
H well well I think I might send her a
message soon soon soon soon
to say some supportive
words Dylan
D Violet myth D Kent s d thank you
cotton gravy Dan thank you h
[Music]
J send her an audio recording of you
giving her a bunch of
kisses I don't know if she would
appreciate
that you booked your flights to Austria
yet no I don't think she'll be coming to
Austria anytime soon
um but someone else
might it seems like I have
doubted uh someone
unrightfully seems like I am getting
visitors before the end of the
year
mhm yeah
no not from
M I'll try my best to be a good host
[Laughter]
cotton gravy danan looking for the top
Dan thank you so much yeah yeah myth one
block that was very important to
me as you know thank you so much mod
arcade d d thank you very sweet Steph
sings D oh thank you k s
d you're welcome zlin dang sir tinle
tanle D thank you
yes I agree
Mar
Hulu
Amia
um a thank you that's sweet
Kaz thank you so
much would be great to see more often in
the future that is true I think we
probably will
H cuz like why not not like I I think
that's just a a very
smart decision for both parties to go
the affiliate route is it just free for
you for 7 days to die today no no
free wait well I would hope more people
would join call is not there we have a
raid
[Music]
today I know that the game adjusts to
like how much we die and so on but will
it immediately adjust the rate to how
many people are online if there's only
three people four people
online will it recognize that hopefully
okay okay thank God
okay I think it will still be
intense because it already was kind of
intense last
time well okay thank God then I'm not so
stressed about
it one thing that might be more useful
this time than the spikes because I've
heard the spikes are probably going to
slowly
get useless with how the zombies
function now on later levels are the
barracks or whatever you call it the the
the holes in the ground especially like
yesterday when we were doing that
digging Quest and all the zombies ran
into the [\h__\h] hole in the ground I
was
thinking well this if this happens
during the raid at the M that's what do
you call it the BS H yeah the vomit
zombies I'm sure there will be more
showing up if I can snipe them with my
machine gun before they get too close I
guess that would be ideal but we need
more holes and perhaps I should have a
few building blocks ready to put myself
up on High Ground
right what can they [\h__\h]
do if I if I got The High Ground well I
guess the does the
vomit push me I haven't I don't remember
if the vomit pushes me
down does anybody know I think I I think
it doesn't push your body they can and
will break blocks of [\h__\h] okay well then
hopefully uh there are already some
modes if we can lead them into the modes
we just we just got to stand behind the
Moes and then they'll run into it I
don't think they're smart enough right
it doesn't but you will panic and jump
that is true that is very true no
knockback
[Music]
right buy some beer from the trader what
does the beer to do I got to check it
out f has been very into the beer
apparently you could look into unlocking
turrets I don't think we have enough
time
really who wait it turrets would be
robotics right do do I have the most in
robotics or is it someone else might be
CeCe but I don't know if she's going to
be online are there only free stream
reservations FAA me and I think Gigi
will show up
though Faun okay turrets will definitely
help I think we should try build one or
two
huh 300% fist damage oh my God but does
she see things a little bit blurrier or
so turrets are cracked
okay I'll bring it up with everybody
then later when's later I think it might
haveen happen pretty
early she has perk that negates it oh
okay okay nice nice nice was that a
magazine or is that a perk that I can
skill into as
well oh yeah there's really only free
streams right now I think gigy will show
up she's just still busy with her
current stream once she's done with that
she'll probably maybe even put up a
reservation M two days left till rate
yeah like not completely full two days
though and time passes fast
but yeah we can't do too many quests
today we got to
focus not lose
focus we have to prepare food and uh
medication
and the Moes and
spikes tap tap
yep tap
tap yeah cuz time pass is very fast when
we're doing
quests and ammo oh yeah ammo ammo ammo
ammo very important okay let me write
this down modes ammo
turrets
mids
okay yeah and maybe the ones that are
participating I should check
what uh armor they have and if there's
any any way ah repair good yeah maybe if
there's any way to improve anybody's
armor still problem is just we don't
have enough armor
kits um and I can't that quickly make so
many I guess but let's check everybody's
armor if there's somebody really in need
of better armor it's probably just f is
probably fine but bibu and uh gigy
should check on their
armor you could make a bunch of preacher
gloves
okay what did they do again was it the
the um zombie 20 30% or something like
that um
damage don't know if I can make them on
like several of them on like level seven
final armor is all
level yeah I'll focus on that I won't do
any quests I'll focus on that but we
really need duct
tape people definitely need arm okay
okay okay let me finish these super
chats really oh God wait can I can I
even
uh
Daniel idle business regulation officer
director thank you for the red jet hey K
this isn't the director talking this is
coming from me H I was too busy to say
this earlier but congrats on your fourth
anniversary I can't imagine what you and
everyone went through knowing the news
about Amy my thoughts go out to her you
and myth and hen that sounds like she
died my thoughts go out to her you move
and Hall and let's chish the time with
had and cherish it going forward m is
wherever however cliche that my sound
but I say that and at the same time I'm
also very dramatic about it so
understandable honestly thank you very
much for the sweet words it's it's nice
to hear you uh right out of
character thank you so much for your
support I hope you'll continue
supporting
us as you can see um I'm continuing to
give my best and uh I honestly thought
that
I would be very uh affected
afterwards and not be able to stream
much but I think I was more affected by
it before than I was afterwards
currently I'm on a [\h__\h] grind thanks
to my own um 3D life and everything like
I couldn't even take a
break yeah my 3D life came up after that
and um my music video promotion Etc at
these
projects uh I'm doing okay thankfully
just because I'm not really thinking
about it much thankfully I'm I'm like
mentally too occupied to really think
about it
much but yeah sometimes oh Ki raided me
gy put up a stream and um raid yourself
girl how about you rate yourself girl
put up a stream giggy we're going to die
without you you better join us you
better join us gigy are you
listening I hope you're
listening please join us your rves need
you I mean they'll adjust the number of
zombies to how many people are online
but still still we need you we can't
just be free
people I was watching the game they
played a little bit and looked kind of
interesting and I was like super
impressed at Gigi's PS skills holy [\h__\h]
she was moving around so much and
jumping and going crazy and still
getting pretty accurate shots I was like
whoa she's kind of cracked
damn sheesh anyway thank you so much
idle business regulation director M for
the sweet words and being so kind and
supportive I'm just trying to finish up
some super chats before I get into the
game guys so I got to zoom through this
now Kon Danish and ghost and danish and
hatch thanks for the word
pink Super Chat thank you thank for the
support very appreciate it La also thank
you for the pinky cherishing the time
with my
oo thank you I cherish my time with you
guys
too but don't worry one thing I can say
for sure I don't have
any uh graduation plans on the horizon
uh and the Horizon is very far like so
far so we're good don't worry
guys D UF D Lou Moonlight D skyim Tracy
d h b anime D gags d d space waterfall D
Gastly tree Dan cotton gravy Dan fuzzy
night bunny Tim per 72 d g domestic d
d what oh
I don't even know if if that's really
why I'm not getting a
reply I think they just generally don't
reply to emails that FL flight D Violet
move D pain pickle D Nathan C thanks for
the pinky I just want to say that I'm
here for the Kata card based Rog likee
Arc looking forward to the future across
the Obelisk slate Spire too oh yeah
wait yeah wait SL Spire 2 I played SL
Spire one right right and the what
slatest P too is it like in the works or
what was it dicey dungeons backpack hero
incription inscription I might actually
play this month ping and Zan streams
yeah across all I never heard about that
before it's being worked on oh I'm so
excited oh my God I forgot about
that H dang Tim per dang Flappy Boy
Thanks for the pinky started out knowing
jack [\h__\h] about cards and already
playing like a to lace nah now you're
basically ready for the whole Casino
night if something like that ever
happens have some complimentary gambling
enabling fun wait you're kind of you're
kind of making me want to go into a
casino legitimately with the girls
someday maybe when we're in America or
so I kind of want to go
now what no no we'll all decide on a
maximum amount of money that we'll
spend and we're all we're all swearing
to not use any more than that I no that
sounds like
fun just one little gambling
night we say like I don't know maybe a
th000 bucks per
person I want to do it I want to [\h__\h]
do it I I only I've been to casinos
before and it never affected me but back
then I didn't have money I guess like
not enough money to really get [\h__\h] up
but it never I never felt like addicted
to it or so or like I wanted to do more
but now nowadays I might be a little bit
more in
danger not just like for Christmas for
um for a work Christmas party one time
and then one time uh like my weird
friend group from back in the day that I
don't go around with anymore we drove to
a casino that was outside of Austria
some country on the
border Nathan
stop don't play Slots no I don't really
I don't know I want to play um roulette
and and I want to try playing Blackjack
IRL I wonder if my brain can keep up
with blackj IRL I got to practice like
it's I feel like it's different when
it's
digital very different slovania might
have been that yeah yeah but I didn't
really like do much at all
there it sounds like fun [\h__\h] yeah I I
want to go to Las Vegas I've never been
I'm going to ask the girls maybe in 2025
hey oh it would be so sick if we had a
concert in Las Vegas next
year going to ask manag man can you
please for no particular reason have the
concert in Las Vegas next year if we
have one thank
you oh God it's past past the hour uh so
thank you naan cotton for the pinky Tim
per say wait I read that one already
flag boy thank you for the pinky uh RMA
B thanks for the r don't cry well that's
difficult thanks for the r Galaxy happy
birthday thank
you Ro for red Super Chat you mentioned
Ana did I ever tell you I got a meet and
great with her at FAL Expo and we were
right next to yours and could hear you
for the wall oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] wait did you hear me
talking to other people then or was I
just talking to myself or the managers
now you know and it's probably why I
never win a meet and greet with you it's
it would be an indirect an
to no I'm not sure if that's the reason
but that's interesting you heard about
that oh [\h__\h] my yapping goes beyond
walls oh that's embarrassing now I'm
embarrassed that's not collab yeah no no
worries I hope you get a meet and great
with me one day I hope for it very much
fingers crossed
M you heard me
talking jino you too how loud do I talk
it's not about how L loud I talk it's
about how loud they turn my volume up
I'm literally in a TV screen what can I
do not my choice or fault bro sometimes
they do headphones though or they did in
the past past Space full dun and you
have more dun okay we're done we're done
we're done let's get into the
game
y I'm in the voice chat I'm muted for
now let me get
this so far internet doing fine but I I
wonder if it's going to stay like that
okay bgm stop
uh let's start let's get into the
server let's have fun today
everybody I have a banana with me by the
way banana shall be eaten at some point
hopefully have it for a reason to fill
my tummy a little bit
[Music]
I'm opening
game
o switching screen in a
moment just in the beginning I think it
shows a IP server IP when the game
starts
up so I'm waiting for that to be over
here we
go even though we didn't get very far
I'm I think it's good that we started
with
uh some
[Music]
yapping get that
yap yap yap out of my
body all right all right all right all
right all
right we know what to do uh one thing
that's not in the notes let me add
it and armor there we go
okay repair K I don't know repair kits I
guess yeah with how fast my gun died
yesterday
oh oh well we'll keep it in
mind
um yeah I guess I'm
ready I don't know which oh
hi hi again hi how you
doing I'm good I'm excited for another
day you're
excited that's good my computer just
died huh how come I still hear
you I don't know oh oh hi people Hi how
are you doing my OBS just died oh no
oh is that why you're running in place
seems like am I I don't know I think my
computer is exploding oh no oh
no it's okay we got time let's see oh if
I can restart this oh there we go is my
game
broke oh gosh I'm going to restart my
computer good J much y
yeah uh bioo yes tell me about your
armor what parts what levels
are uh okay I
wearing assassin boots level three
Ranger gloves level one Assassin outfit
level three and then nerd goggles level
three M okay okay okay I feel like um we
might not get everything
uh like improved but I want to try at
least maybe your gloves or so making you
better ones um I wear medium armor
that's my that's what I leveled up okay
uh but they're all like different armor
parts right like different set yeah I do
have I do have Assassin Boot and
Assassin outfit so if I can get assassin
gloves oh you want assassin gloves okay
yeah I think that' be good
H cu people were recommending preacher
gloves but I don't know it doesn't
really matter that
much pre light armor I think it's medium
to or tell me chat I don't remember but
the preacher gloves are really
good let me see and the set bonuses are
not that worth yeah my preacher gloves
are just on level three and they still
already give me plus 30 damage to Undead
30% I mean I'll take preacher gloves
then if the if the bonuses don't matter
too much yeah I'll take preach your
stuff okay I'll try to make you some
preacher gloves then um might not be on
the max level because armor kits
are difficult oh let me give you let me
give you armor parts I have 10 ah armor
parts are not that important it's more
the armor kits oh okay and therefore
duct tape but yeah if you can find find
any duct tape before the raid that would
make things easier I will give you three
I need 10 for my weapon but I'll give
you three oh okay yeah nice nice nice
that should help um yeah and when fauna
comes back we should discuss our battle
plan for today okay tons of glue is it
just the three of us in hoorde I think
think more people are coming I think
gigy will at least come okay so it might
just be four but but the ZB the amount
of zombies that spawn depend on how many
people are online so we should be fine
okay um I think I'm going to do quest to
load up on bullets then um because I'm
running low on bullets and I want to get
enough Bullets by the hord starts okay
so that way I can cover people's butts
that's good if you find some of my ammo
that will also be helpful yeah um I'll
I'll do quest to get ammo for everybody
okay I think I'll just try to FOC focus
on Crafting most of the
time cuz quests really take up a lot of
time and we're already ooh already at
the end of day 26 yeah okay I will I
will spam Quest while you guys get other
stuff ready
[Music]
okay guess I can make two for now I need
more sewing kids
even can I make those myself so
no
oh ah Callie wrote in my chat I'm so
sorry I wish I scheduled my thing on a
different day I'll make up for tomorrow
don't worry like I was just concerned
that maybe they'll spawn Too Many
Zombies but no it should be fine yeah
don't worry we'll be fine we'll handle
this leave the Nerds got this
yeah I don't the surely Trader
sells
um seinging kits and stuff let me see
what they have not much time left to
reach
them should I go to wreck or
Jen maybe
wrecked boom
boom booom The Clement and their adopted
child yeah bi boo is our first
born got to protect our first born or be
protected by
her on a solo the bear you'll be fine
why yeah I guess we'll be fine it'll be
fine if it if it spawns based on how
many people it shouldn't be that
bad oh
F and left the game uhoh
that's her pattern she does that every
time she logs in really yes interesting
well I guess I'm going to have to pay
you oh I had a quest to give back to him
nice yo 150 times 7.62 ammo thank
you oh she made so many meals okay I'm
going to take some food on the road with
me um yes you did make a lot of
food get this for
fun I will
go okay good luck or make your way
out I could buy a couple of
these but
wait ah
yes he only has one suing kids
ah yeah people if you find seing kits
duct tape anything like that you know
who needs it I will I will
look so sewing
kit did
my bike
go I put it in the Box I think I
did am out of
money onward to Quest
[Music]
[\h__\h] man I treat you that good and you
don't even [\h__\h] tip me shut up
guy he's so rude uh actually uh you're
going to award trade direct right now
yes are you getting a quest or giving
back one I'm giving back one and I'm
going to grab another one do you
actually quickly just want to do one
quest with me though like when I still
have open it's kind
of somewhat closed from here not
really um
sure was he complaining about me not
tipping like excuse me I'm European we
tip here too but just we don't tip quite
309 mm you are amazing yeah yeah he get
I think we we got the same we gave the
same Quest back huh cuz I got a lot of
ammo from him too yeah very
nice all
righty is that the a is that what bike
is this that's not
mine oh that might be my bike oh no I
took the wrong bike this one doesn't
have an extra seat oh
well that's fine then I'll go towards
the quest hello back take me with you oh
okay okay we're just doing I'm just
doing one quest with bioo now you can
join us but I won't be questing the
whole
time I think um there's a there's a
there's my tier three to the north
that's very close to the house if you
got to do that one to the north oh yeah
true
uh we can pick fwn up on the way okay oh
you're already going towards mine you
yeah wait I think our bike should still
our mini bike should still be there fora
oh cuz I took a the mini bike yeah I
took the wrong mini
bike ours should still be
there it's okay n
unbelievable oh no it better behave
during the the ho
night I know yeah well well at least you
girls can hear me right now so let me
actually um bring up something for
today's
raid I think one thing that would be
really good to focus on because in this
oh welcome back so you cut off ah you
cut I cut off oh God yeah I want to wear
cut off I was saying I don't think spend
too much on spikes we should focus on
the
modes oh you're
oh loed uh I can't get
in what the bike I made is is
[Music]
locked it will surely stab stabilize
soon I believe
I was saying I think we should focus on
modes not on spikes because did you see
how yesterday during the digging Quest
everybody was falling in and that was so
op that's true it's true yeah yeah yeah
and now the zombies can probably at this
level really easily destroy our spikes
especially the vomiting
guys so not so much spikes more you want
to loot this house while we wait for
kiaha yes
okay can we fight the boy is the Bo
still
dead where is the
Bo um I think it's in here it's probably
still dead though I
[Music]
think are we back in stream okay okay
what if we make Moes and then put spikes
at the bottom of the mo oh yeah oh wait
is this the is this the quest we have a
quest for the oh good then will respawn
when we start the quest oh I
think okay I think it's
stabilized knocking on
wood oh there's stuff
here okay I'm coming back into the game
hopefully
[Music]
okay I have a book for you oh only I see
oo armor piercing round thank you o you
don't
use4 for ammo I do I will when I make my
uh Magnum gun I just haven't made the
gun yet thank you
mm so the board is not down here it's
supposed to be down here oh yeah it
hasn't respawned it'll probably respawn
when I start the class
yes okay okay I'm getting in I'm getting
in I'm coming okay I'm back we're
[Music]
waiting Let Me
In come on
we
go wait isn't the isn't the raid
starting like really soon no I think
have one more day 28 28 28 at 10 p.m. so
okay it's the divisible by seven right
so yeah but one thing in order for the
modes to really be useful for us we have
to kind of stand behind the modes so I
know FAA you like to really go out there
I'm going out there I
wrong I fought a
bear all on my own she's confident I'm
confident yeah okay I'll stay behind and
then try to shoot them while standing
behind yeah we'll we'll cover we'll
cover your backside
okay where's my
bike where did my bike
go
oh the poor pigs maybe it was a
mirage my bike was a mirage it's gone oh
okay we didn't take it did we no that
was mine this is weird are you girls on
two separate bikes right now or just one
no just just
Bo shouldn't it show up up
there that's so weird I guess I got to
walk home and pick up another bike oh no
wait you don't see the icon anywhere no
oh that's
weird uhoh weird things are a foot today
yeah oh damn
conspiracy bik uh at the at the mini
bike at the at the house yeah I think
the yellow one is our fauna waa
bike yeah I know I was driving there but
I wonder if something happened while you
DC uh well chat is saying I should still
walk towards where I like got kicked out
of the game maybe the bike is there even
though it doesn't show up on my yeah it
might navigation
okay also so fin you weren't there but
I'm going to try before the raid to get
bioo better armor and if you have some
really lowlevel Parts ideally I'd want
to improve your armor
too the only problem might be CH and
head are level one okay that's yeah
we'll improve that for sure especially
if you're going to go to the front
lines I'm strong though as long as I
beer to drink that's all I need just
give her the beer she'll be fine drunken
fist all the way exactly it gives me
300% power ooh damn and you have that
perk that negates the effect right yeah
that's
crazy B
to why doesn't it show it on the on the
big
map I put a lot of resources into that
bike why does the map not show it to me
so
rude I think I was already kind
of in this
area like in
between oh oh zombie
hello it was on the
road I was what do you mean you was on
road was I following this I wasn't
following a road I was just going
through here right
H
you okay I'll go back and look around
you want to go to the house across the
street for now yeah and resty okay let's
go oh I think I I killed the Boors in
here
too
yesterday ah you girls are not in the
party right now oh we are let me add to
you you you uh left when you
disconnected
okay
[Music]
okay lot of corn
seeds corn I feel like potatoes are
better
you can make steak and potatoes yeah I
saw the the stack looks so good maybe
instantly
hungry I know I feel like we go through
the food so
fast I really want to level up enough
that I can make the Sham
stew can have
infinite sham
stew it's not here though why would it
be here here chat are you one guying
me not the one
guy I'm so slow my
stamina I mean it won't re uh despawn
right so maybe just for now I'll go get
the the other bike you could put a
marker on your map where it where it
was so you can come back later yeah not
sure where it really was but yeah I know
the rough
area okay I'm going to walk back and get
the other
bike okay okay unless I accidentally
find the other
bike stamina I want more stamina
it doesn't despawn
okay yeah I was near to Burnt
Forest oh well well we'll find it one
day
yeah it'll just be traveling the road
and boom there it is hopefully hopefully
cuz it was going to be someone else's
bike um by the way generally what I
think we should collect before the raid
is
uh ammo and maybe more repair
kits yeah I'm going to spam while you
guys fortify or something I'm going to
spam quest for ammo for all for all of
us and ammo parts so I can make ammo
Parts yeah yeah yeah and also uh we were
thinking in my chat before we started
today uh it might be good to make
turrets and I think people weren't you
kind of like starting to learn that
stuff no I'm explosing
I'm learning turret but I'm really far
off I think is that
robotics I think I think it is robotics
yeah I need 51 and I'm at 16 oh okay all
right where am I going I'm going to go
towards you girls now okay my quest is
up only me to at the quest Point
coming okay so maybe no turrets this
time then unless we find a lot more
magazines I have I have explosives
though so that will help yeah indeed
okay I have fist so that yeah that'll
help
definitely we'll see oh are we doing oh
boes and bears BS Bob's boes yes yeah oh
we're going to fight the boar again ah
speaking of fighting
FAA there you go I got these for you
okay is is it is the starting
point oh we got to go we got to go to
the library before the rage
FAA the library yeah the one you one I
went wait did you find a new one no the
one that you found oh okay we can go I
think I got well I don't know how much
how long does it take to
respawn probably long maybe after the
rain respawn after the rain yeah
probably oh wait is it over here hop the
fence I can't hop that fence oh you
can't but so
easy I'm I'm hunky
okay ready I've got ammo for both of you
oh thank you I have nerd boots
nerd boots anyone wants nerd boots let
me see if they're better um no they're
not better I'll drop
though we could bring him home and then
give them to someone else like yeah if
somebody joins us tomorrow also without
armor okay clay here we
go play all the
piggies oh no
the poor
pigs do we need more meat should we get
their meat yes always always have more
meat is Handy okay I'm going to get the
meat and the lever oh a
lever
bacon there's a lot of
corpses in here
make cows fat again cattle
[Music]
feed why is this going so
slow
oh hello piggy I'm sorry are you already
upstairs I am in the middle floor
[Music]
or pigs
piggy defenseless
pigs oh hello
sir it's so dark but it's like not dark
enough that I want to activate my night
vision it's like an you night vision oh
night vision is actually really nice
here I've been using it yeah it's all
right I just don't like the oval
shape ah bothers me I want to see the
whole
screen oh wait with my fire it's not too
bad
yeah oh yeah remember curtains and stuff
curtains and
toilets everything is important
mattresses I
suppose sideways egg Vision it do be egg
Vision
huh oh wait we have to look for supplies
too yeah oh didn't
realize ah chemistry station did
somebody open it up and was something
inside or I did what was inside I don't
remember I heard that the chemistry
stations they sometimes have a really
valuable item I think it was like acid
or so oh should I wrench it okay let's
wrench
it
okay ooh steel and forged ingots good
good okay
okay oh okay
I can't find my
thing is it upstairs perhaps it might be
mine I think is on the third
floor oh no it says it's
down oh I wonder if it's like where the
where Grace is Grace is at the board
yeah that's the big Bo no will they
force us to go
there Al say no it's easy now you want
to go there anyway huh yeah we got this
she want to test your fist I already
killed the boar One V one oh
wow it's easy we've grown so much
yeah ooh
ooh
Who what is this more
BS good job
is it through the wall I feel bad they
run away from me I
know it's sad but we need the food I
guess
oh there is another
room I think my satel is in there I
haven't really paid attention to mine um
it's probably not there but I'm going to
take your
path it was an unlocked
door maybe we could have come here
without breaking the
walls
maybe maybe it's on the
[Music]
Roof oh mine's here I missed it I went
his yes where is
he are they on the oh they there
oh maybe we yeah maybe we have to go to
Grace because yeah mine's like farther
away I'm too stupid to figure these out
where is mine does it show on the big
map um oh is it the red dots no no those
are the zombies
it's probably in the basement
huh yeah I see my compass but do you
really think I understand that when it's
moving so fast does it have an arrow at
the top or
bottom
um ah bottom and it's below you oh I
didn't realize there was an arrow
there yes oh another chemistry
station oh the super corn yeah the super
corn is back
who's there I hear hising I don't see oh
yeah they're down with
me I'm busy can you guys leave me
[Applause]
alone stay
down oh this is that type of puzzle that
I hate there's a puzzle puzzle that you
hate it's a a light
puzzle a light you know the puzzles
where you push something and then like
the two buttons next to it oh I love
those you love those I love those I hate
those I'm so bad at
them okay how to get down fa can you
show me how to get down uh down yeah I'm
not sure can we can look around
I only know how to get to Grace from the
outside F come
back where to where you just uh the
stairs look at this did you see this
picture oh my gosh the cat is full of
bombing the
dog cute so cute that's a good one yeah
a good one best one yet I think so too
10 out of 10 I like this picture can
relate yeah can you get to Gra
from here like this
house well we can go from the outside we
know where the exit was yeah I think it
might be locked
though yeah it's locked oh it's locked
from the outside yeah
okay wait oh wait um okay oh what if I
just dig down
ah you surprised me I'm just going to
maybe Dig Down come from
here oh yeah my satula is right there oh
on the ground oh a
easy ah wait
spikes wait is it this way oh but it's
locked I think it's oh it is it is on
this
level ooh metal
spikes welcome welcome just breaking the
walls there's no point putting a metal
gate if your walls are going to be so
flimsy this one isn't that flimsy
oh I don't think I'll get through it
what what about just next to it it just
goes over
here oh ow spikes oh wait there's oh
those are spikes
yeah when the door is too much to get
through just break the wall that's right
to
it less effort are you guys going down
oh yeah wait there's spikes that's scary
yeah I fell into one it hurt
it hi almost there almost there my
satula is
definitely
oh oh
come
on I'm out of stamina
[Music]
ow oh the stairs are
here ah did you
find it was easier like this for me
can't orientate myself all right we're
just going to brute force it okay I
found mine I found
it mine should be I don't know where
mine
[Music]
is oh K oh that was mine too okay I'm
done yeah well still have clear the area
right oh yeah does that include the bo
there's a there's a orange dot that says
to the distance that says below that
might the that's it we can take her oh
there's a there's a w there's a thing
here oh yeah yeah yeah yeah we went
there
before that's where you get to the boore
oh it's kind of crazy in
here oh yeah ammo making fertilizer
oh
nice okay I want to eat some more
food you need food I have
food I'll survive a while longer ah I
see her I won't engage yet I'll let the
Tank come tank I'm really slow right
now I'm very cucumber
uhoh can't run away from the board at us
oh wait hold on let me sneak attack her
once she's asleep I'll get the bonus for
[Music]
that oh ah okay never mind she woke up
she woke
up she already dead Oh no just oh
ceiling
board oh
no easy easy
easy what's inside got some knife book
some armor part I'll let you guys look
at this I'm full I will take the ammo I
will take knife that's so different from
before from the first
try strong have faith biker outfit I
might take that it's medium
armor okay here go there's some ammo for
you oh yeah okay
nice well then I'm already cucumber
uh me too we should go and drop stuff
off yeah and maybe just one more Quest
and then I'll go prepare armor and stuff
yeah I guess we should reinforce the
base yeah maybe make a few more Moes if
possible let's get out of here
yeah we could go to the bookstore I feel
like I got a lot of the books though I
mean maybe there's more in like a
basement or something but it's pretty
far away is the
thing
true feel like that might lose us a lot
of time
yeah need to a shovel if we go like
after the raid everything will
respawn I'm so slow let's
go oh shamway foods and Savage country
seed shipping
grade come on lock Pi do your
stuff let's see ooh
doeses somebody want to take these
things in the weapon
bag it's a scope and Knuckles
mod oh I want the knuckles I thought so
why do want night vision yes okay here
you
go thank
you where is this PO string mode I was
oh I can only have one my
my water you're GNA just switch them out
you know combat use night
vision how do you use the night vision
F
oh
cool thank
you
uh oh Chad is it better than one of
these worth replacing
[Music]
oh let's look at it later chat okay
shall we can we go to the the one that
Wawa had
uh okay it's a little bit can we drop
stuff off at home first it's it's kind
of on the we can stop there for sure
okay where was the bike there
okay I'm so
full it's okay we have mini
bag and they don't take stamina can you
drive the bike over to me and pick me up
I'm driving
it hold on I'm coming
mama hey girl thank
you look
this door is a
little
th
narrow we can't do it there we
go okay I'm heading ahead before you
we're going home
first the
Nerds the
Nerds I'm no longer nerdy
my XP G oh no she outgrew she now what
level are you
anyway
I'm wait where do you see that again
level 28 28 okay yeah I'm 26 oh bio's 29
wow I've been killing
things uh oh yeah came
for dropping
up oh I got so much meat from the
pigs I
know me
[Music]
too okay some
stuff what is this fourth bites damage
mitigation mitigation does that mean I
get less damage
potentially yes for bite Fort bite
fortnite
fortnite I think I'll use one of these
for the hard
night sharp oh maybe I should make a
repair kit
there there's a lot in one of the chests
there's like six there yeah maybe I
don't need to make one
then okay I'm ready I think to go to the
next one okay
[Music]
okay can I use this guys to like wrench
the electrical
things seems like I might be able
to why is this stuff in here
anyway oh we have an armor chest oops I
was yes I'm not organized it's we have
ah okay might not remember cuz it's
new it's for
what uh connecting traps and turrets to
power sources H is this this bottom uh
storage crate F there's six repair kits
if you need one oh I was just going to
bring some in case I think one is
enough for me for now same thank you or
two where do the bones go
just put them in here the ingredients
chest oh
okay
okay connect lights power door okay for
now then I don't think we need
that can I wrench this
yes
oh some of the crops
grew FAA farmer is back farmer f
farmer F it's not much but it's honest
work I have just sold our microwave in
our um fridge online secondhand
so we have no more of
that I'm sure we'll be fine without
yeah are you ready man no more spending
hours in front of the microwave watching
turn my favorite P time it wasn't
working
anyway I think we're ready I'm ready I'm
ready
F get on my bike okay you must are we
going to the tier 2 infestation one yes
it's a bit far but I want to get that
out of my
system let's go road trip
you still have tier one clears too oh
when will we get to those
funny maybe once when you're really
bored for some reason I'd rather do a
tier one quest which will never
happen are we so
fast I love not having to drive you can
just look at my inventory should I start
an Uber business
you should what is that what do they
call you're a passenger princess I
am oh sorry
oops you can stay on the bike even if I
get off interesting oh am I on the bike
yeah yeah I got off get back on I got
off by
accident um I hope this road will lead
us there surely surely
[Music]
surely oh yeah we're close
I love how my arms are around your
waist it's
ticklish she's tickling me I
can't can't can't drive like that stop
tickling me f but where are wait
actually this is not a good
path oh this this is not the place yeah
there kind of a dead end uh H the road
ends
here maybe we just power up the
hill wait I'm doing it I'm powering up
the hill
oh oh okay I'll try to from here might
be
good do your
best come on come on it's working oh the
going to catch up come on come on oh
yeah oh yeah oh yeah yeah
yeah oh no oh no I hope up we're
vertical can't you push us it works just
just uh just have try really just could
pick up my bike for a few meters I'm get
back on get back on it's time to go
down oh gosh it's like a roller
coaster oh ow I'm hurt that's fine uhoh
uh all right foreshadowing I'm a little
scared I'll be careful I I'll get go
I'll go off the gas now and I'll just
let it okay
[Music]
okay on come on come on come on come on
come on back
up all right and I feel like my game
wants to crash so bad oh no it wants you
to crash with the bike or the game
itself wants to crash no the I feel like
the game itself wants to crash so bad
cuz we're doing illegal physics things
okay I made it wo this is
spooky o we made it
too have we been here before this is
spooky yeah does he have any
resources he does I can make some sham
out of this
sh oh this guy too well let me just get
this car wrenched and then
we can
start yum yummy car materials Yum Yum
Yum
yippee my inventory is already filling
up oh I've got I brought a lot of food
just in case let's
go what do we have here
no interesting
oh
oh oh feel like I can get metal from
this
too oh now I'm collector yeah can we
have it oh it's destroyed destroyed oh
watch out behind you can we fix it oh
there's a lot watch out watch
out oh nice hit oh oh oh w w
put stuff in mini bike oh the mini bike
has storage
huh let's go does it have a big trunk
maybe just a small one but better than
nothing
yeah what is my holy hammer called I
should give it a name huh I I shall name
it gimy easy watch
out gimly
my beloved
Kim oh radio
station wo
station oh the keys are here
Keys we found I've never found keys in
any house before no I didn't know they
were actual keys but makes sense
I'm rarely fighting in these quests it
seems I'm always wrenching things oh
there's a air draw will this hurt
me it's kind of far they usually hang on
the wall oh interesting 400
m there's a a roof yeah there's an
upstairs oh there's a ladder
he jumped right onto you
no
nope you guys are so
funny zombies scare me no
more spooky at
all oh did we finish it oh we did it
yeah but oh we did I feel like there's
more to explore and more to wrench oh I
got armor crafting kits oh I think I'm
done with that level maximum level so
you can use that oh no the armor
crafting kit oh ah the ones that make
armor oh okay let's go let's go oh
here's here's some ammo for you and I'm
going to drop the armor crafting kit so
you can hold on to them all right oh
there's ammo for both of you and
there invested cash
invested
cash in here too ammo pile clean my cash
thank
you clear out your
cash
okay I guess if there's nothing else
interesting we could
[Music]
go a pumpkin
pumpkin what the katana K mentioned
Katana Katana Katana K Katana oh that
thing the tempered blade
schematic
[Music]
oh do the keys work only for one
specific door or for every uh I think
it's specific door cuz I had I found the
key in the B house and it opened the
board cage so I think it it's
specific
okay oh do you want to get the airdrop
where is it yeah we should it's not too
far right okay oh I don't know if
they're even
good I think I will go back home and see
what I can start crafting okay you guys
can go home I'll just grab it real fast
okay
okay actually first I'll go to the Traer
but F we can go
[Music]
together do you want to still like get
some stuff
or uh what do you mean like from here
wrench wrench
stuff maybe
[Music]
this I think I need to repair my need
tires
m i mean right now I don't think I'm
like I don't need it that urgently
oopsie uh tires I think yeah they can be
crafted can I get it like
this no I just got some
scraps what World level are
we oh somehow far oh you're 93 how did
you're 95 how did we I feel like it went
way up I feel like the last time I
looked it was think I think it also
depends on Armor maybe cuz you guys are
wearing like high level armor or
something or
maybe you're 91 f is 93 I'm 66 no you're
95 oh I'm 95 on my screen you're 95 oh
on my screen it's 66 so I thought it
would be an armor different but
M oh was that wrong way wrong
way oh it depends on the
biome interesting I don't I don't even
know what that means at
all me neither we're just living our
best life yeah does that mean the raid
will be easier if we go back to the
starting location maybe oh the supply
quate gave me a bunch of books
okay nice books oh oh what kind of books
any I'll bring them home let me
see any need bar brawler level
five no
Barbara traps and
B my German brain
rot yeah you know that song cuz it was
on Tik Tok you probably saw it
it
was yeah you did you know that was
German yeah the the whole song I mean
yeah the whole song trying to learn it
but it's
so you should do the dance
too I want to
see wait oh is this Quest from Trader
Jen I think any any MPC can finish the
class right he
can you have to go
back yeah I think I have to go to both
according to my yeah I think we have one
at and one and j o okay I'll try to be
fast well we can check to see if they've
got anything good for sale although I'm
kind of broke right now same ah yeah I
see you have to go back to J okay okay
but yeah speaking of Tik Tok people I
made a Tik Tok
yay Tik Tok you should follow my Tik Tok
people I'll follow you do I even have a
Tik Tok on mine yet I don't think so
maybe I should make
fun hey funa you you you use Tik Tok
no I look at YouTube shorts sometimes
but you YouTube shorts is literally Tik
Tok but a few weeks late like everything
you see on YouTube shorts is just out
put that was reposted from there but
true so you guys are late to the trends
I'm fine with that I tried to watch
Minecraft Parkour civilization and I
felt like I was losing brain cells and
then my bones were turning to dust and I
seem to years old she was like live
tweeting it last night when
she who was streaming it I was was live
tweeting she was watching the parkour
civilization the movie
oh
Iris I don't get it is it how what level
of irony are we on when we say that we
like Minecraft Parkour
civilization do we like it ironically or
unironically we like it
unironically
yeah uh is that like a level one
unironic or like a level three unironic
oh c I don't know can you be my GPS
um can I I got I got a motor motorcycle
parts bundle you sure no no sorry yeah
wait
yeah I wish I could have the map open
while riding icon on my map is like
backwards it's like facing the opposite
way that you're going
confusing well everybody who has Tik Tok
please follow takanasi
yeah follow Tak
she's got some cool dance things up do
you think a lot of your viewers are are
like Tik Tok
users I don't know they always seem
really mad when I mention it yeah
same I'm personally not a big fan of Tik
Tok either but they're they're all
spamming no no heck no no beef no no no
I see
uhoh looking for some healing absolutely
I feel like some of them are lying
though just to sa
face there's nothing to be ashamed about
also I got I got a m
motorcycle parts box from the Class
M
oh oh I leveled up
yippee she's selling duct tape let me
buy have you have you read urban combat
volume 6 fa
um let me see cuz this one says armor
doesn't slow you down when in combat and
that might be that oh okay I'll use it
then yeah I
have
F yes how much money do you have
1,000 no 2,000 can you buy the
remaining uh duct tapes that she's
selling why we have duct tape at home
but not enough we always need more we
can make more we should instead by do
collector Parts if she has it then we
can make even more duct
tape duct tape at home how much duct
tape do we have at home we don't have
that much duct tape at home we can make
more duct tape but it's difficult we
have so many we have we have bones and
we have so many bones in water so we can
make clue yes better to buy the the do
collector parts does she have them yes
she does do you want me to
get a dual collector part oh water
filter is is 7,000
yeah would be good though I'm going to
get the The Gatherer at least
okay our first uh and I'll get I'm going
to buy tarp our first quarrel between
wives about how to spend our money we
have we have duct tape at home duct tape
home low
quantity we'll make more if we it's we
need to invest our money instead of
spending it as soon as we get it we
don't fight in front of your child I'm
going to doesn't understand
people she doesn't she doesn't
understand dad because she's not in my
position I don't I need much more duct
tape than she knows she doesn't
realize no we'll be fine just wait one
day we'll have so much duct tape
hopefully who is this Kiki I literally
just saw her spawn in front of
meppi
G my third parent is
here I'm eating right we Jo call off
okay where's my
bike over there we're going
to wait don't leave I don't have a car
yeah yeah I'm just trying to find my
bike and then we can go to the other
Trader wait did I sell
something
no wait did I sell
something I sold the magazine back oh my
gosh I oh no
oh my gosh she scammed
me I got so
distracted you something you were
supposed to yeah I bought a magazine and
then I tried to use it from my inventory
but that just sold it back to her
no did did was it was it Jen did you
just you shot your by was distracting I
see it's okay it happens to the best of
us
oh no is G going be left here yes yes no
that's what she gets for leaving us
behind
yesterday she has to walk does she even
have a bike she doesn't even have her
bike oh it doesn't see she have her bike
what we can kill these zombies yeah what
is this r
[Music]
action
baby out of stamina already
okay come on oh I got I got armor
piercing kiaha bullets I'm going to put
it in the weapon and it's armor can you
use those with any uh uh machine gun or
does the machine gun need yeah no any
any
7.62 it's just different type of bullets
so you should be able to use it
[Music]
okay well that was
easy that was
easy I think we got this yeah tonight
well actually soon wait what day is it
wait we have one more day we have one
day uh I will spam quest for
bullets okay we're going to go through
the village here but we're not stopping
for your quest
F that's fine or should we no we don't
have time it's almost the end of
today we really got to get
home we got to make more
modes oh
no oh I should check out if the mailbox
is refreshed could it be could it be or
is it too
early they're empty maybe after the
raid
okay uh you
need F you you answer I need to control
the bike sorry I was in
my my
thing what do we need wait what
resources do we need uh maybe I IR
oh duct tape no duct tape at home suing
kids so but that's just randomly in the
houses I think I think more cloth would
be useful cloth is like I feel like I
have a good am
now but we always need more and also
cloth is helpful for explosives too so
we can always use
more more Mo mes at the base so that
they fall in so a good
shovel yeah I wonder if she can
make iron or is it iron or Steels
shovels
um wait I'm starving um I think wait I
have food Don't Starve it's okay driving
first we have so much
food driving comes
first Kik has ch
good I'm going to make some bulk good
water since we have a lot of water now
oh yeah please
please are you where are you bo boo I'm
at the house oh we should save some
water for glue though yeah I won't do
too many see we have to share the water
for different things
fauna that's why we need the water
upgrade
part more water I put I put a water
upgrade part in the in one of the things
so one of them has some upgrades okay
I'm going to make a third one okay a
third du collector
mhm okay ah you're getting off you don't
want to give the quest back oh I guess I
do it's dangerous to get off while I'm
highspeed driving FAO you're right
you're right my server lagged a little
bit it looked like you were slowing down
I no oh we don't have
cryan are they the yellow ones or the
red ones the red ones we need more red
ones for me to make
though
oh I can get a bunch
okay make sure
toch
cars um here we
are re
we are so
back can you welcome us back friendly
we're still coming back to you even even
after we have other Traders yeah look
here boys got ourselves a real life hero
and now he wants to be
paid I don't know about these rewards
could give these
to well look who decided to show the
face again
I have collected 56 chrysanthemums oh
that's
useful what's
cranum flowers it's a flower
yeah I'm very
slow oh
wrong
spending all my money man I treat you
that good and you don't not on duct tape
I hope no no he he didn't have any duct
tape
sadly food please
F
yes take take this pumpkin
[Music]
pie
oh I don't need this I would like to
confess something I actually don't like
pumpkin pie really yeah it's so good I
prefer like apple Apple's good too yeah
yeah me
too have you read Pistol Pete Volume 2
that um where do I check your inventory
in the books tab
inventory definitely that
way I think I never had pumpkin pie IR
before we never mhm we should try
it I don't think I ever seeum I'm not
too big
on pump the pumpkin spice I'm not a
pumpkin spice girly
D really I
love SP P Pistol Pete which one volume
two no I have not okay I'll get it for
you I didn't ditch father I'm just
looking for the other bike in the
meantime
oh you can ditch me I can walk home it's
fine bike bike bik I want
TP I can't afford it should I spend all
my money maybe they spending my money
glitched out my bike out of this world
and they won't give it back to me hobo
stew hobo stew yum yum yum yum I don't
know what that is
oh no I should have bought beer wait I
can still buy one beer bicycle on the
compass but it doesn't
show the other
bike
rude very
rude are you still at the trader I'm
done okay I might pick you up now okay
I'm just going to be punching
flowers okay wait I want to rench car
really
quick no problem oh no my game crashed I
think that was just a crash not internet
oh okay that's it was just there oh my I
passed my bike oh really wait they like
they don't want you to have the
bike game boy are you doing this
okay
[Music]
well I'll be
back in a moment I'm gonna get that bike
actually F do you see the you don't see
the bike on the map do you the one we
were driving around with
yay don't think I see anything okay okay
no problem I think I see my old bike my
regular
bicycle okay okay okay okay okay okay
game is opening up
[Music]
okay got a lot of
stuff I'm going to make so much duct
tape wait dan has three books of furious
fist by the way that's I tried to buy
one and I accidentally sold it back oh
no oh that's a big loss of money huh I
know she sold it for me to me for 300
and bought it back for 20 don't let her
her good looks and charm for just as
ruthless as all the rest of the
train
ah is it possible to like K Ju Just in
theory is it possible to kill the
traitors I wonder cuz they have like a
skull rating right o the last boss are
the
traitors maybe maybe when when we're
done with the tomorrow we can
check that's scary
though I don't want to ruin our whole
game what if we can't go back anymore
because we ruined it killing the
traitors that's
true okay and can I get a party invite
again oh yes yes
where did you guys see
it the spike was
here we have so many
bones do we have gas cans at
home uh I think
uh maybe I think we out of them because
I filled all the bikes up as much as I
could I have eight of them I found the
bike oh oh
good oh it's not bad okay you're never
leaving me
again it's weird that the icon didn't
show up for you yeah don't know
why okay I'm coming
home preparation time uh oh we really
only have like one day
left 24 hours F I bet I can just punch
them
anyway I'll just I'll make you better
armor what should I prioritize uh your
gloves right
f um no no no I have good gloves it's my
my hat and my chest ah your hat and your
chest and you want the same set I would
assume
right yes okay and then for bio I wanted
to first of all make gloves preacher
gloves I think yes please
okay well I I'm I'm going to go get
cooking going to go
cooking let her
[Music]
cook you have a bit of cloth
now oh me too me too I think cloth is
like okay now in terms of yeah ever
since we started destroying everyone's
curtains
yeah
[Music]
g uh what was it what was it preacher
gloves preacher gloves maybe at level
five
my delicate hands full of
knives
oh despite all the punting they're still
super smooth and nonous yes I don't know
how you do it what moisturizer do you
use I'm infected AR brand
moer what was for an in infections what
was
honey honey and antibiotics there's
antibiotics at the house and
honey I see honey only work uh for a
specific
percentage 5% honey Works 5% at a time
awesome so it'll still work if you're
high percent it just takes away 5% of
the time
[Music]
okay I need to ask giggy to
are you coming to VC
[Music]
soon she's num
noming I want to num nom too
okay maybe I can make a Max
Level but maybe I should be more
careful oh do I have to run all the way
to the on to drink can I just drink
water at home yeah just drink water at
home but expensive though I can just go
to the pond and
drink I don't
know you you've been working hard to get
us water I feel like you deserve a nice
sip
sip without making too our time is
precious okay every second wasted is a
second closer to the hoorde so true
don't waste your time so what about the
duct tape do we have more duct tape at
home we definitely we can yeah I would
appreciate a couple more duct
tapes
MH I'm on
it wait I can make a couple too just
free yeah if we have more glue I can do
we have more
glue um we can make glue we can make
glue with the
water how much water do we have I'll
make glue
okay
I oh my internet died oh no but I didn't
get kicked oh
interesting oh we're back okay that was
just a short Maybe YouTube issue or OBS
only okay
perhaps I'll make I'll make I'll
make I'm going to let zombies kill me
don't be alarmed I want to be full
health for my quest
okay I need moreing
kits damn
um what was that uh fun you said hat and
shoes no hat and chest
okay I'll just I'll just make the
maximum now or
yeah with the
materials oh I'm still infected oh wow
okay second to last it does matter we're
going to do this again
sometime and then I have to continue
with the stuff I
have the steel the steel I even bought
extra Steel
this will be
enough
okay
okay uh but then I probably can't make a
new yeah cuz I'm out of armor crafting
kits oh well for
now seeds
I don't need to make I have so many corn
seeds
already I can't make beer for a long
time cuz I need the chemistry station or
something oh really going to be
expensive yeah
but that's okay I have I have enough for
now yes look at
this I'm out of armor kits now for oh my
thank you for it's maximum
level so that should help I don't think
I can improve your helmet uh but that's
okay yeah and then I got the tanky yeah
oh thank you let me know where your home
B boo okay I'm just doing one
[Music]
Quest my own armor is okay it's
okay oh I can't make potato seeds
yet wish I could make a few more armor
kits she has duct tape
M for
one
wow duct
tape oh the shovels are expensive I
can't too stupid to type I can't
type I pressed some weird stuff again
okay um is hobo do really
good I don't know what's it made out of
you don't want to know don't ask
questions you don't want to know the
answer
to it's the healthiest ingredients for
sure
yes um what's that sound Who whoo whoo
whoo oh oh was that a
tree I put some glue in your chest oh
thank a
little and cloth glue
glue free glue how much I can make free
duct tape with free glue
[Music]
um
oh um oh everything needs water of
course oh but I'm lacking sewing kits
now and suing kits we can't make
ourselves only I have more seing kids
maybe the old house still has some seing
oh can we not craft those no I guess
not
ah
there's some nice minor boots and gloves
for you in the armor
chest in new house
think cuz
her her equipment is probably also not
the best so that
should I mean it's for mining but it's
um decent better than
nothing the nerd boots look
funny okay I'm going to check out the
old
house okay
okay and pray for
for suing
kits they will always be rare items the
r Savage country house cuz they usually
got plenty yeah I did get a few ones
from the one
house oh wa I'm going the wrong
way actually maybe I'll check over
here I'm going to go raid a
house okay good luck
thank you I need you got this I'm scared
don't be scared you're strong I don't
know you're
brave
okay I believe in you in your words they
better be true if I die then I will
cry yes I got gimly and my machine
gun it's just with gimly
it's taking up my stamina so
fast it's kind of bad so I'll use my
machine gun I love how you call it gim
yeah best dwarf
ever oh oh this doesn't really look like
it would have seing
kits face the Bears drink for free I
don't like that advertisement hi hi
hello how is your meal yummy it's so
hard to play and eat
though don't get don't get crumbs on
your keyboard what are you doing the
ants the
ants I'm summoning them
no please ants come eat my
keyboard it's not the place I was
thinking of
[Music]
are we going to be fortifying today well
a little
bit uh the thing is like spikes might
not be so useful anymore because we're
going to get probably more of the vomit
guys now and they destroy the spikes
easily um so rather than that I was
thinking our strategy should be modes so
that they fall into the holes they fall
into those pretty easily and they don't
seem to be able to get out of them so we
just got to lead them into the Hol we
should do I'm thinking we should do Mo
spikes yeah spikes in the modes best
Strat um so yeah we already have some
modes but maybe adding another a row
would or like filling up the areas where
there's no
modes
okay okay I'm going to see around
here maybe this
one does it have a rating oh it has a
rating e Faun what's your experience
with two two skulls
houses easy easy easy do you need help
though I can help no I'll be
fine I've got some more glue for you
that's nice good to hear now much
H better than
nothing six Ste yeah
wow
nice G are you streaming no I'm just
here mhm taking it easy here for a good
time yeah trees nothing else just kill
it I can't use any of the these bicycles
I can't unlock
them and the bicycles or the
bikes none of them none of them not a
single one but I unlocked them maybe I
have to unlock them every time the
bicycles yeah
bicycle I think they auto lock because I
had to unlock mine when I didn't
before SNS SNS
um I'll unlock it for you when I'm back
you can you can mine my God thank you
for letting me use your bike uh it's so
green M she has so such little quality
on her is she
okay do you want a repair kit I'm scared
of hurting her even further I think we
should have repair kids
somewhere think I saw a few I see one
I'll repair her I'll go fix her right up
she can fix her I'll fix
her that's so nice of you to return my
bike with a full tank of
gas yeah I not all by myself I feel so
powerful I knew she was alive just
sleeping I had a feeling
yeah head shots definitely make things
easier
microwave okay I mean we're we're
cooking we're cooking I got cooking mag
stuff I really want to get to the Sham
stew sham
stew sounds
delicious I think I'm far though
am I far wait fish tacos oh my God fish
tacos I can't make them yet maybe
someday you wanted you wanted sewing
kits right yeah okay I'll bring
[Music]
them why some noise oh dog no not dog
you sounded like a dog
[Music]
spicy okay I'm gaining
confidence good you should be confident
yeah thank you so synced up
girls so would you guys ever possibly
need like more wood
I think we okay for
now be useful
with um always good to make more spikes
even if they can be destroyed they will
be a line of defense yeah yeah yeah yeah
this
[Music]
stack and can I how come I can't use
armor plating
mods they I've noticed that I cannot use
them on my chest but but I can use them
on for example the feet I think oh
really yeah damn oh I can't use them on
either oh they don't go on heavy armor
what works on heavy armor oh probably
different plating the heavy plating I
think there's particular plating for
it oh no can't put any armor mods onto
heavy maybe seemingly oh really maybe
it's already strong enough without
we'll see maybe that's the
tradeoff
no I'm crafting 400 spikes don't worry
nice let's put them in that Mo yeah yeah
yeah
yeah what is this
for I never know what any of the
modifiers are
four yeah me too oh I can do customized
[Music]
spinnings I think I'll go to the next
house find another swing kit
hopefully how many swing Kats are you
girls carrying around if anybody I have
two right now okay okay oo the hobo stew
is good
but what's it made out of no don't worry
about made of what's inside our hobo St
can I have can I have the nutritional
facts please I'm watching my
sodium B um 2,000 milligrams of sodium
wow A
little
yeah ooh machine gun parts huh
I don't have any
vehicles to
use can you unlock the stuff at
home
I'm why are they unlocked again I
unlocked all of them
yesterday a I think I think they auto
lock I think yeah okay I I I'll come
home I'm not that far
[Music]
every time you pick one up or use them
they lock
oh oh ah so each time a different person
uses it it blocks for them I
guess
oh ah they belong to the person that
sets it down makes
sense I guess today yay uh we have
enough bikes for everybody to have their
own maybe FAA can use the Cali bike or
so the golf bike okay golf fora uses
golf
bike makes sense it's this one right
okay unlock try
it thank you oh it has like no fuel oh I
can add some I think I have some this
person returned this car with no gas
it has not that much fuel can you unlock
a bike I'll just take a bike no wait I
have I have more fuel I have more fuel
we're trying to
save save the environment everyone I
don't think the environment needs to be
saving we have to thank you it's about
Reviving the environment dead yeah and
we'll die next if we don't save the
environment armor armor armor
come
on what am I
lacking another couple of seing
kits I have two but I'm far away okay I
also still have gles head back yeah I'm
heading back now
okay yeah when should we start
fortifying
H Maybe around early
afternoon
okay put these in here I have time
yeah to do stuff like kill bears
yeah beep those
Bears I guess I could go back to the
bookstore we could go after
though be good to find all the
bookstores I think they can be in in
many
biomes yeah they seem like a good find
yeah have you been in the biome with all
the
special little things the special
zombies special zombies all the throwing
up zombies spawn much more frequently in
there the desert the desert spawns a lot
of throwy upy ones if you want if you
want to real challenge FAA go to go
north into the snow there's a lot of
yeah that's where I was scary creatures
when I killed the bear that's where the
bookstore
is that was the Bear's bookstore well
it's my bookstore
now never learn ever again magazine
section
[Music]
now Finders Keepers
that bear was going after his Masters
and you just ruined his
education so B
then okay I think I'll go back to the
house one more
time oh oh oh where are you guys
going is there a party that I wasn't
invited no I'm just solo some stuff no
you zombies around our house are just oh
walking around the
group looking for something to raid it
seems maybe they're telling us that we
should
not be so easygoing the day has
arrived yeah they're kind of right they
are right it's the day the Dooms
Day oh yeah let me unlock the other
bikes
okay why am I why am I so slow okay o oh
two Forge ah heads
shouldn't we have
[Music]
another mini
mic they're so loud these
zombies someone has to teach them
manners I know D can't even get any
peace and quiet even when the zombie
apocalypse I thought that would help I
know oh
[Music]
ouch gy if you want uh there's
an unlock bicycle or do you at least
have a bicycle I took faas she lent me
hers okay I thought I have another mini
bike
but I don't know where
went but we do have some seat modifier
thingies on the on some of the mini
bikes so we can ride together yes
yay why they are so cute I know I didn't
realize the mini bike had so much more
storage this is so good
really I got to check it out
too how about this house
[Music]
just going to raid one more house and
then I should maybe be able to
make a new armor oh yeah gigy how's uh
can you tell me what level your armor
pieces are a bad feeling for yours I
took I have an Assassin outfit of level
one and cool sunglasses of level one but
I took the mining things that are level
four um wait do your chest piece is
level one yeah what are they going to do
kill me I'll make you a different chest
piece um is there a specific set you're
interested in no I'm just I like hitting
trees and and Mining yeah but those
things are outfits you shouldn't really
wear for fighting but only particularly
for the actions that you're taking um so
maybe I'll make you I'll just make you
the The Meta chest piece
okay trust me
that was
easy I am stack okay I'm ready for the
hord okay I put your gloves into the
armor chest B if you can just Mo the
seing kit somewhere I'm coming home
right now the armor chest yeah
anyway what that oh no you guys oh no
the zombies are no the zombies are not
okay they're stuck in the barbed w
fire they're oh no they're lowering our
Reds get out of
there oh no I'm
fatigued just take a
break
oh good job you made it
give me something
good Hi
[Music]
friend come on down W water's fine they
work
out so we're building an even larger
Mo I mean you don't have to go overboard
but just one a row of modes would be
cool maybe with spikes filled with
spikes Moes filled with
spikes got it oh I have tier four
now your quest yeah oh oh here they
come oh
oh the next Trader is in the Ice Area
ooh yeah up
North I'm excited for that but I don't
know if we'll see that
anymore I don't know if we'll see it
today but
yeah we need to play another
week yeah I'd be up for that but a
little bit of a break would be nice I
want to play some different games too
that's true I've been itting to play
games but then I'm like this is too fun
as well I know I'm
split so true and like you get so
committed to it I think all of us are
like super committed to it so we want to
show up every day possible yeah I'm
[Music]
committed oh wait did I do it I think I
did we are not scared of commitment I
feel like I have to do my part yeah me
too I
know isn't there loot in this house
apparently the Japanese girls played
until day 49 or
so but they didn't play in Long AG go
they they had like several sessions of
several
days so that's how they got so
far we should just continue at some
point yeah are we are we was it going to
do it longer
tomorrow uh yeah we start uh 1 hour
earlier though uh if everybody's okay
with it C already said she's okay with
it yep I'm totally fine okay cool and
then yeah we'll just go however long I
was wondering how long it will be maybe
like 5 six
[Music]
hours really depends when we end
today cuz our raid is soon yeah but we
can still maybe yeah I want to
definitely end on a hoorde okay today
you mean oh I mean tomorrow
because it we might need depending on
how we end today I don't know how close
we'll be to a hord uh tomorrow but I
definitely want to end on the hor
tomorrow cuz I think that'd be like a
nice Bang Yeah agreed yeah I think
that's why we're playing like longer
just to get to a hoorde on the last day
yeah I think so more sewing kids
[Music]
why what is this house how are you going
to fix any if you don't have sewing kits
at
home can't repair
it feel like I'm using so much
fuel it's bad for the environment you
got to
stop it really uses up a lot of
fuel I've been I've been ranching like
so many cars to get some more fuel but
it really is a little bit of a limited
resource so if we can use bicycles more
often or car poool we can car poool yeah
car poool saves the
environment yeah true we need the we
need seed modifications everything on
everything and I'll make a car as soon
as I
can we're not too far cars fit four
maybe even
more perfect in a car so cute yeah
family road
trip road trip to the infested book
store
yeah and we stop at every bear we
[Music]
see k k k come on come on come
on oh but nice
magazine sorry B how many swing kits did
you bring again two
oh she has Forge head books oh need we
still need that very much need those are
the workstation books I think so yeah oh
Dan yeah she does have them does she
also sell sewing
kids we have sewing kids at home no for
real though I really need more if she
sells them please tell me we don't have
SE kids at
home does she we could though
she does I'll buy thank you thank you um
how many do she have two okay please buy
both I bought both okay thank you I love
you I'm expecting somebody's going to
have to Fork up the money for the water
purifiers
though how much is the water purifier
I'll buy remember remember how much
money I invested in making everybody
mini bikes and stuff where's the
gratitude
go think about you come to my to my home
which water thing do you want me to buy
I'll buy it um I what do we need I think
we need water
filters I think I can buy a
gatherer wait no I need to save money
for
beer I have $9,000 on me if someone come
to me wow in
my in my
trenches oh water filter is too
muchy The
Gatherer gather The Gatherer let me see
do we need the gatherer still do we have
the tarp I can't remember if I bought
the tarp or The Gatherer I bought the
Ice Cube I think we need the gatherer we
need another Ice Cube we need another
one I already bought one well we made a
new water purifier oh
okay I'll buy one more gatherer there we
go thank
[Music]
you thinking about what will not stack
probably
well
whatever okay I'm coming home do you
want to ride home oh you have a bike too
never mind I you have one wait do you
want do you want to get on so you save
gas but then how are we going to get
this one back home you'll pick it up how
I
walk what what put it in your inventory
oh is first time today that's so
smart oh your bike is locked Oh see it
locks every
time
okay thank you yeah
I know how much you like being a
passenger princess I Do I
Do is it getting dark and scary
yes I have six Forge ahead
magazines
yay what six for ahead oh my
God amazing you're so lucky
it's all skill no luck 100% skill I
would say those magazines are pretty
lucky and I bought will or whatever the
song
goes yeah exactly remember the name yes
fa something yeah yeah
[Music]
why are they so
rare where are we where are we doing the
defense at Old House
okay that's that spooked
me I just stepped on a zombie and it
woke
up no
this game was a jump scare happy
Halloween happy
Halloween God my heart I'm
old can't take this
anymore okay we're
home
yay thanks for the ride yeah oh you did
make another one okay I'm going to put
the thing in here yes boom
just lots of food wrench everything I
just want to look for I put the sewing
kit in the in the crate next to the
thank you forge awesome I put the
magazines in the magazine
okay
[Music]
D damn that other house gave me false
hope I have ammo too for Yuki waah wa I
put in the ammo
crate thank
you hopefully so prepared short on ammo
this
time bless you thank you oh I have ammo
for you bi boo let me drop crate is full
I think I'll be fine with the
ammo last time I had to share this time
it's all mine oh yo boys these zombies
we're going to kill them before daytime
again yeah so
easy knocking on
wood wood
where that's your favorite word
huh where is it what no wonder you like
fauna so much she's literally a tree
P pulls out my axe
I'm this might be dangerous if gigy gets
drunk and cannot tell
apart happening is that why this is
happening that's why she punches you no
yes it's because I keep falling asleep
I've never been punched by gy that tells
you
something yeah yeah sorry I have um I
have
narpy oh wow that's not an
excuse I just fall asleep and then I
imagine that I'm punching a tree then I
wake up and I'm hitting you I don't need
it it's
tough married life is tough
huh we're going through counseling it's
okay hey shouldn't I be there
too yeah but I I keep beating her I
don't know
I'm GNA be so traumatized when I grow
up aren't you
already a little bit you just can't
close your eyes B boo I'm already I'm
already very murderous it's I get it
from my parents play play on your DS go
on go back to
bed sneak downstairs while you're
fighting by the staircase looking down
into the into the living room oh they're
fighting again oh
no no don't
fight going back home
unsuccessfully should I check one last
time in
[Music]
here
hello
hello musim Mo
zombie where are you I feel like we're
procrastinating again on the board no
don't worry I'm working really
hard you're going to be really impressed
when you get over here oh I you making
modes and stuff yeah once again I don't
have to do anything in terms of
fortification leaving it to the others I
am the Gopher the Gopher what's the go I
thought you were a beaver right now I'm
digging through the
dirt does that doesn't that make you a
mole I'm the little mole naked mole rat
cute why is it empty was someone here
recently
what was someone in the what house is
this uh B bore barnfields recently
everything's empty
yeah probably I mean it doesn't have to
be recently right it's just yeah true
yeah I can never find any small
stones do we have them we should have a
lot I would feel like I can never find
them am I just
blind well you can always Farm them
outside hit some Stones dig for them or
do you have to just look for them no I
think you Stones yeah has five sewing
kits in her personal storage oh we're
taking those be able it should be it'll
be F I'm taking those if she's not
showing up like two raids in a row or so
I'm taking
those she doesn't know how valuable they
are it's okay it's our now no I I I
think a lot of things in the storage
they might like not need anyway so
they're just putting them there for
safekeeping but we're one big team yeah
that's
right and one dysfunctional family if
she does show up again I will make armor
for her so
exactly what comes around com you have
three armor crafting kits in your
storage yeah those are like you know I'm
cing them for another piece of armor for
G and for myself maybe we'll see how far
we get I'm just looking in
everybody's yeah a little nosy yeah what
is what is going
[Music]
on
beo interesting you're very buggy for me
very glitchy yeah her shoulders are like
off her shoulders see too huh
H is that better well you're constantly
in like a shooting and walking
position um but yeah now the now the
should yeah they were floating again
looks
funny looks very
funny probably is hoing too I'm calling
everyone out wait no I'm I'm holding
stuff for my Magnum gun okay so that's
why there's tape in there that's the
amount of tape I need for my Magnum
picking it to everyone's inventory what
the hell are you doing with
this calling hiding stuff from us
unbelievable all I'm going to say is I
don't even have a personal
box
everyone oh we're getting close to the
rid so now everybody's like so tense and
on edge everybody's fighting I don't
like it it's not good for my development
our child getting a part-time job we're
like oh you're not I I'll keep a better
job at your money than you will no I
made this money on my own here let me
put in the bank account for you wait
wait Mom I wanted to buy a new game
games you have to study no how will you
get to College like this question uh the
the
shieldy things that you found did you
are you still carrying them I put them
in the chest next to the forge okay
thank you I was able to make a couple
duct tapes
now
so I can make more armor crafting kits
oh oh I'm getting a good amount now
let's
go looking good oh I'm so hungry in
firsty oh
God oh maybe it's time to eat my banana
banana IRL don't eat the banana put it
in the chest eat the hobo
stew what the
banana
oh I'm really going to eat
it I'm like I can make banana bread out
of that think there's bananas in this
game if there are I'm sure I can make
something
[Music]
oh I could place the timed charges into
the into the Moes so they'll explode in
the Moes
o that might do you have to activate
them I don't know it says timed so maybe
it just oh it's 4 seconds okay I drop it
and then explodes in 4 seconds
M there's um 440 small stones in this
top chest fa what I missed
it I'm just blind I went out and
collected
some too
bad 15 minutes before blood moon what
oh but the will not come yet so oh right
10 p.m. um I think it starts at
22:00 yeah right yeah 22:00 10 p.m.
yeah F what did you drop off from
Shiri uh sewing kits
ohuh you don't have it anymore
right no I put it by the unless somebody
somebody took it maybe no I think I
already took it then you should do
another sweep of everyone's chest I
think I
will someone's hiding things under their
pillow don't it's my game stashes in
there don't take it away from me that's
all I
have I remember grandma sent you some
money for your birthday you have
to
M fun
yes didn't you need bar brawler
magazines they're in the chest oh I only
need volume five
oh did anyone take the stack of forged
iron can I have like 25 oh um what
um let me see uhoh there's some people
outside oh hello
yay the party is starting
yeah I'll let you guys handle
that more
more okay I put some uh forged iron back
in a chest for you and I forging some
more you don't mean steel right you mean
forged iron right no just iron yeah IR
okay that's good um so we're making one
Nomad outfit for there more out there G
ah yes there oh there's a lot
oh oh are they going to try to come for
the back
again
maybe let me know if you need
help I think we got it what am I looking
for oh watch out
it's pain being
melee okay I think we're
good
storage ah
[Music]
more so nice when you forget you have so
many things in your
bike that'll make you happy when you see
them where did we have lever I know we
have lever somewhere oh I have it I'm
just going to make a thing real quick
and then put all the stuff back into the
chest
okay who's out
there oh the spikes hurt can I delete
these spikes that are right outside yeah
yeah please please do I think I put
those there you mean the one spike in
the back of the house that was me cuz I
was trying to achieve something I see
and I have a che nothing okay I'm
putting all the ingredients back in the
chest the leather's in there thank you
so
[Music]
much all right
then can we craft some forged steel do
we need more iron no we need a crucible
we don't have Crucible is
15 yeah oh wait it's money
it's money or me crafting it but until I
can craft it I still need a few more
workstation
magazines
15K did you get the six that are in the
magazine box I already read them I still
need
um 30 no four 40 more
oh I have final 40 more yeah 40 more
books of works
but I can make a cement mixer now which
with that we could make cement walls in
Fury but my next reward that I can uh
make is a chemistry station and then a
crucible so it's very far my chemistry
station's good yeah it will be
good get that in
there and
uh oh it's loading up
slowly
okay okay not enough deal so I
think I have to make a lower level
one which will be good enough
chemistry station will be great to
reduce material consumption
okay everyone donates you'll get to buy
the CR yeah but I haven't seen a Trader
selling it yet oh maybe the one in the
in the next Zone will have it yeah
probably like I it wouldn't make sense
for them to sell it so early in the game
when we I can't even like I'm way too
far from crafting it myself they
probably want to balance that out so
that you don't get it too early
so yeah probably in the mountain area
there's a
chance Bob usually has it Bob really Bob
got to check Bobby more often I think we
could farm that much money easily it
might be worth it yeah yeah the the
higher the tier Quest the more like
Quest we have start giving you like 2 ah
2K now and stuff by the way do we have
more water because cuz I feel like the
the food chest doesn't have any water
right now um there's some in the output
let me put it in oh okay I'm also
cooking some uh good water that's being
cooked currently M actually I'll keep
those hobo stew also hydrates you a bit
oh really yeah this D has everything
yeah it's good uh gigy I have your uh
level five Nomad
chest okay I'll give it to you when I
meet
you um thank you if I were to make one
more
thing what could I make but I'm I don't
have any more
steel what's the time by the
way 5:00 p.m. oh yeah 5m we still have
five ingame hours
wait Gigi do you have a wood splitter
Mod on your axe I do not wait you you
should have this let me bring it to you
thank you more damage to
wood can I just take this bike I don't
know whose this is take it if you can
ride it yellow wait wait take take my
bike if you want since I have which one
is yours
Here Pink
it's locked okay it's unlocked oh wait
let me put this mini bike
back what's your hat again that you're
wearing cool
sunglasses just remind me that that wait
where where's your bike by the way don't
has my bike oh okay it's in the hole
with we're just trading bikes
yeah people your preacher gloves are
still in the armor chest don't forget
about those okay thank you
should we bring
food yes I think
so I'm going to head over to the new
house okay me too I'm going to come soon
I guess I'm I think I've
done enough prep I got enough
ammo we got some well I made as much
armor as I could but with the lack of
Steel it's difficult to make more good
stuff so for now
maybe we're done I think we should as a
group try to get 15,000 I bet we can
yeah i000 token on
me right 9 10 11 12 13 we need 2K more
that's it uh 2K more I think I'm yeah
cuz she has 4K I have 9k or she has 9k I
have 4K so we need like 2K yeah I used
up all my money yesterday for something
what did I buy something really
expensive
what was
that didn't I
buy no not just steel does anyone have
bandages okay maybe I no we are yeah we
need bandages we don't have aloe is the
problem oh I guess it's in the desert
right dang it we have we have three aloe
in the need four to make one bandaid I
have five Band-Aids I'll bring those no
it's okay you can you can use them cuz
you're going to be on the field anyway I
I just might have someone kill me before
the raid starts
okay I have to go to an idle meeting
I'll be right back and I'm going to go
to the new house okay have fun I me be
right back
[Music]
okay actually
this is
[Music]
mine repair kits do we have repair
kits yes there's repair kits in the
thingy
thingy new house or old house new house
there's like in one of the unnamed boxes
oh oh
[Music]
okay ah saw one no three
nice I'll just take all of them with me
for now we might need them
there make a better
sled no it's fine do I have any skill
points free okay
um oh I have four thank you for a m
uh what's where should I I'd like more
stamina I was also working on something
previously was
I over
here
uh stamina what was stamina again
stamina
[Music]
is it is
fortitude and it is rule one cardio m
a thank
you yeah then I need more in
here I'm
back why is my on
Fire H you're on fire do you do you see
this my bike is smoking uhoh is it okay
hold on maybe I should repair it better
go catch it
running oh yeah you want to do you want
to give me my bike back and then I'll
just drive you to the place oh
okay your bike's over
here should I just get more of these
points I'll just do you want it over
here I'll just put it anywhere I'll just
pick it up okay I'll just put it over
here there be something like this oh can
you unlock my bike oh
yes weapons
thank you oh wait uh where okay machine
gun okay you
ready yes I need more of
these okay I think just North yeah just
North okay wa yeah then then would need
skull crusher to we're coming
G on the gun anyway off go I can't wait
for you to see my work
oh hold on I have to take a tea break
cuz I have I have the no nose oh no what
were you eating I I don't want I don't
want to be stinky were you eating sham
sandwiches yes I was eating sham
sandwiches I don't want I took all the
food out of the
chest he want some steak and
potatoes it's okay I still have some I
was just trying to like clear out my
inventory so I was just eating whatever
was in my we don't have to live like
that
anymore I wonder how long
this uh buff
stays getting spooky oh right soon right
soon I feel like we're always down to
the water when we're running to the new
house
oh yeah I forgot I wanted to go into the
desert and punch
aloe cuz I can probably get a pun I have
the perk
now will this be able to go through the
river yeah okay wow
Easy E are you taking a mini bike to
dive into the water yeah it was
right thank God this game isn't too
realistic
mhm all right I'm on my way too I
bringing some some bams and stuff
too do you have beer
FAA yes I have
[Music]
beer drink up and go crazy I am you're
the alcoholic now I know I know I was
afraid for you to come back and realize
I've slipped into bed things have
changed made me
stop it's because you were turned around
when we needed you no we we we don't
have to live like this we have a child
it makes me three times as strong I need
this what about her
future she won't have a future if she
dies to
zombies these are special circumstances
buied I don't need to be I don't I don't
need bullying anymore I learned for my
mother oh my gosh this is scary hit
does it look
functional it does it looks scary if I
was a zombie I would be very
[Laughter]
scared all
right sounds
promising
ooh
yes I am also very scared of
accidentally
did you fall
in almost almost I'm scared to fall they
have the Alo SE here I'm Ying these oh
yeah so much faster with the bike let's
go very nice wait where's Gigi in the
hole what you're in the hole I'm still
digging digging herself a hole
where my head out cool layers do you see
me
yeah
here a gift for you I'm so excited
yay thank
youcome wait take some take some food
this and take what what one more hour
take
this oh my
God so last minute
again oh yeah g I have stuff for you
too
okay where is the entrance oh wow nice
wow yeah that's uh that looks very good
the only problem will be if people go
through these doors and then let people
in again like me last time then you
fall don't fall down no no fall falling
no
falling guess we could have made like
iron doors or so to replace these by
now um G where is gigy in the hole okay
there I I'll put your uh stuff into the
armor chest thank you I will take my
perch
kiaha have some food oh thank you I did
bring a little bit for myself but that's
good okay have a Band-Aid
oh thank
you oh yes can I have one Band-Aid maybe
yes come over
here take this take take one of these
take one of
these thank you oh thank
you thank you wait wait wait take take
take one of these oh thank you
okay all right I'm excited let's see
what this will bring us yeah today you
think I can keep digging while they're
here need
more actually actually finally quickly
kill me let's find her really yes okay
are you sure I'm sure are you going to
spawn here oh wow what yeah I'm going to
spawn
here I got some XP
[Laughter]
[Music]
ooh yeah the front and the sides are
very well protected I wonder when the
zombies come from the back if we'll have
any problems but should I take back
there too no no no no there's one one
line of mode and a line of
spikes it'll be fine we just always need
to have an eye on where they're coming
from but it won't be as many as last
time cuz we're less people so we'll be
good
it's going to start
soon 20 seconds 20
seconds what do these do again damage
mitigation disease
resist I see I see if I go out I have to
eat this and this only if I go out I'll
stay up here if I shoot someone by
accident I'm sorry I'll try to not shoot
you if I if I set you on fire by Molotov
I will I will call out when I'm going to
use the molot smart smart giggy are you
coming out to fight or are you going to
keep on digging I'm going to see if they
bother me down here oh okay well my bike
is oh my bike is in danger will they hit
it I don't think
so [\h__\h] I'm scared to go out now they're
about to
come they could take they could take my
my bike will die oh fun I'm going to go
grab my bike can you give me like C
yeah I don't think you can pick it up so
I'm going to I'll I'll cover you with
shots I'll watch you thank you my oh
god oh it's laging they coming go go go
go go go I'm watching I'm watching okay
no I didn't want to I didn't want
going Scar the p with me my
beard leave my
bike I'm leaving they why in the p with
me I'm going
inside okay okay okay I got my bike I
got my bike I'm throwing a moloto sorry
oh that's gigy wait who is that there's
a lot of them aren't
there lag lag I'm throwing watch out I'm
throwing
M on my
way let me just go in please let me just
go
in the [\h__\h] door
maze okay okay oh laggy all right all
right I'm throwing them all again let's
see he's
[Music]
spitting oh they're they're all burning
and they're dying by the spikes wo
they're dying SP are dying
fire try let's try to always prioritize
killing the police guys first yeah big
big big yeah okay why are they hitting
the trees that's my
job how dare they I know stop taking my
job I like how they're all Gathering
nicely in some
I'm fixing some of the spikes that I
can that's nice of you ouch yeah they
seem to have a hot spot over there yeah
get out these spikes and the trees why
are they hitting the trees I know leave
trees alone is that because you planted
them or do dogs oh yeah they got
[Music]
dog my aim is not the best cuz
I'm made through I'm again final watch
out final watch out okay what's inside
kill him where how did they get in no I
don't know he just wed in a spike hell
no oh hell no oh my God I'm going to put
more spikes over here I think one wave
is maybe over cuz the music calmed a
little bit maybe not I hope that is the
second wave this I'm placing more
[\h__\h] uh should we have stacked them
upwards the
spiks oh it's fine they're coming in
through the the doors they're coming in
through the doors oh they can use those
nah there's not too I don't see anyone
in actually there's some in the spikes
huh in in the there's a few there a few
inside but they're dying from the spikes
inside too that's good all right they'll
they'll die
eventually yeah let me fix some of these
spikes okay New Wave is coming new wave
is coming watch
out what was that just having a
snack ow the spikes are hurting me
too oh oh they repairs oh they are birds
watch out they brought animals uh-oh
wait wait leave me alone leave alone let
me just prepare my arm my hello hello
um okay come back come back come
back okay it's chaos out here are you
okay I'm going to throw I'm good okay
find a run find a run find a run it's a
big wolf thing or so
um oh my God it's inside it's
inside God I I'm taking care of it don't
worry about it I'm taking care of it
ceding out
I'm I think my stuff fell into the
spikes in the mold I'm going retrieve
that Fu [\h__\h] I already used all my he
dead it's fine
okay um how am I going
to get my
stuff oh
gosh there oh gosh thank God
okay don't look at me don't look at me
oh I broke my leg
oh
no they are punching the trees why leave
those alone I
know get a get line get a job leave me
alone get
job like losing focus oh gosh there a
lot of them all right I'm going to throw
fire again run fin run just run just
keep running spray I'm going to keep a
bir okay bird
down keep running F keep
running keep running oh my God how much
fun at Staying Alive with all of that
well I did die
once spray and pray spray and
pray come
on keep running keep running keep
running oh is that where is fa I can't
tell which one's fa Bird Watch Out bir
no keep running keep running I'm taking
a
break good
idea oh no the the the front door keep
running keep running keep running let me
let me try and barricade they're kind of
getting inside watch out I'm resp
spiking I'm resp spiking the entrance
good
[Music]
job how much I'm in a rough spot right
now
don't worry they will die this
Spike nice nice nice nice nice nice
we're doing good we're doing good I'm
dying to spike oh I'm go about to come
through the
door I'm going to throw bombs at the
door just watch There's a Zombie behind
watch out they're hitting him the back
they're hitting it for the back behind
you I hope this is over oh no oh oh oh
my God they're in how are they getting
inour please be over soon parkour
civilization
God I need I need to heal I need a
bandid oh gosh uhoh I also need to
eat let me
try fix our defenses is it still is it
still it happening yes things are very
much happening here I will put another
line of oh God how are they getting in
oh it's broken in the back I okay
okay just get that they're hurting me
wait I'll try to be your uh back up here
okay
ow
wait
car exploded
oh there's a lot coming from the back oh
oh goodness I'm going to throw bombs
again Watch Out does anyone have any
spare
Band-Aids with that bump oh you is my
only
one oh god oh yeah we need some we need
to fix that Gap bombs just I'm throwing
bombs watch
out ow ow what's hitting
me owie owie
popping
Hills let's go P bit my arm is
sprained my arms also sprained from all
this
punching re
[Music]
Spike there are so many coming from the
hill there are okay I'm throwing I'm
throwing my last bomb watch out watch
out it's going close a watch run
[Music]
[Laughter]
maybe I should have made a mod in the
back oh that was that someone else oh
God okay Hammer Time baby although I'd
like some free ammo please oh he Dro
scary drop
ammo oh coming from the back
side I'm fresh and ready to
go no more rain
arm why' the music
stop oh it's it didn't stop oh God they
kill the tree sry
sry are you okay it's only half my
health it's
okay do you have a like a a healing
thingy nope I have one I'll be okay
though I have one okay I can drop it
right here on the floor right here where
I'm right behind you let me take the guy
thank you I'm out of ammo okay I'm not
going to stand in front of you is it
over oh one more one
more oh what wait it's not over it's not
over the hill there's some more they're
coming down the
hill
ammo yeah if we pick some stuff up from
them up to give ammo is it I think it
might be over NOP no here's dog hi
doggles glad you're joining us after
all all that's a FAA is just fine she's
just
fine stop stop hurting the tree you get
the tree down
please those are for me
that W is
mine doggo incoming doggo Running Dog
fast big Dogg or small doggle small okay
good big dog then we we scared we're
very
scared nice
ni okay why did they stop the music I
think it's over now yeah
ow
seems H one more coming in maybe these
are just regular zombies yeah maybe I
think
yeah oh it's so quiet
now wow I actually used all of my ammo
oh gosh me too and I have so much
tacking the trees
let's loot there's birds coming oh Birds
where can't they break the from the back
from the
back the dog
ow yeah it's over good job girls good
job we survived we did that was
definitely the test one yet yeah okay
there's a few more but
wait no no there there's more around
this doesn't feel like the raid anymore
way less than 10 did you fall to the
dogs right oh big wolf coming big wolf
oh no
I'm wolf is attacking trees AR bark oh
dear there's a wolf yep yep I'm scared I
don't know who he's going SC oh he's
going for you
giggy something's hitting me oh hello
hello
I'm so sorry it's okay I was dying
anyway from the spikes at least I know
the [\h__\h] works really
well pleas me alone leave me alone leave
me alone leave me alone leave me alone
there's a lot near you
ah thank you Father thank
[Music]
you oh
oh I'm
exhausted that's why I'm not a tank
usually can't deal with this
stress tank is low stress you just
walk from across the
what okay then I will not real kid I did
not really die guys yeah it was not a
real
death
undeserved so I'm just practically open
they're still coming I know it's okay
one more hour
guess did anyone bring any repair kits
um you're getting attacked by a bird I
did it seems like they're used up ow the
dog too oh my my gun is broken
uh-oh uh-oh I don't have repair kids
either
I'm putting spikes down watch out search
the loot search the loot maybe the loot
has
one yeah I need I need ammo if this
continues strong hold strong 40
seconds
KN
die die die die die level
31 yeah oh there's some stuff going oh
they really hate the trees huh I know I
don't know
why ouch I'm going to die goodbye cool
world
no you have served us well fauna best
tank alive or
dead oh God oh God oh
God good thing there's no get through
here yeah thank God they took that out
thank beo thank you yeah y watch out I
don't want to stab you oh there's more
je maybe a little bit late to it's never
going to end is it over it's seconds 20
seconds it's not
over I'm so exhausted mentally 2 minutes
actually okay two minutes two minutes
music stopped though stopped a long time
ago oh my mini
bike I need to make these modes
better no they were
wonderful I don't know how many fell in
I feel like they were we killed a lot of
them before they could fall in again so
we need to make a mode on the back side
though yeah didn't expect them to come
from there
I need L more ammo for tomorrow I used
up all my ammo yeah need to prepare more
ammo glad found a few for you already
went
collecting the when the when the
magazine has an open book that means I
read it already right yes
yes these are all not really for
me well it's it over over yeah it's over
we won we won we won with just four of
us but that was honestly it didn't feel
like they sent us much less than before
they us a
lot yeah also how do we get all the loot
that is at the spikes I think we might
have to break the spike yeah I have to
break the
spikes okay gy get going this door
is where do we I'm over
bird maybe we can burn it down with a
like Molotov cocktail or so the spikes I
don't have
anymore if I had one safe spot to get
get down there I could Hammer
them Place boxes on the blocks
oh good
idea definitely don't want that to
despawn let me I don't want I don't want
ruin
it at least we got a lot of loot
yeah do you have some
wood um I have 200 on me can you make me
a few
blocks okay just like maybe
10 or so okay crafting right now thank
you oh I'm so full yeah
me too I can't even walk through here
ouch time to get out my bike and let the
bike take things how come I'm I'm like
too too wide to fit through this door
frame you've bulked out from all your
fist training I guess so where do you
want the
blocks um I would like go around the
modes and place them on top of the some
of the spikes to pick up the loot cheers
thank
you let's
see I don't know how that's going to
work can I really reach them from here
found a treasure map oh I got super coin
seeds more of those that's good that's
good I still can't cook anything with it
but hopefully one day
I can't reach it from
[Music]
here oh
no PE Pew
PE is that the block where the
spikes it's the
spikes but that's the block Maybe
a ow ow you okay I'm in the spikes oh
yeah those
hurt hurt even when you just graze them
they hurt oh I got rid of one one block
of
spikes at what
cost oh wait there's oh I see there's
like a lot of loot down there yeah so I
got to get them trenches are we going to
get them the trenches yeah we need to
get rid of those bikes
it's difficult and I don't have an
axe I don't know if we can get rid of
these we can we
can here I got rid of that one block
already that my stuff that's uhoh
goodbye goodbye goodbye goodbye goodbye
hey this smells pretty good just don't
panic
parkour civilization flashbacks I feel
like I just missed a chicken
jump ow yeah I'll get rid this
some we leave it to you
Eggman ow the
spikes oh no my
[Music]
backpack oh no ah
oh I see it okay hold on yeah g to be
breaking a lot of these spikes I'm
sorry my trees is it it's the blue one
down there right yeah
yeah
make at least it gives me wood back
so oh oh oh oh it's two layers of spice
oh really good right yeah so glit don't
glit no I was tting no actually this
time a building block suffocated me I
guess oh no I was testing I wasn't sure
where the damage was coming from we
might we might have to just say goodbye
to this loot no no no no
noack I mean definitely the backpacks
but
yeah uh I wonder is there any axes that
I can use in
here are can we not set the on F
yeah I was thinking that like throwing
in the molotov cocktail or so I don't
think it will burn I had one I have some
in the new house but I don't know if it
will really efficiently
work chat do you have experience with
that dig the
dirt oh yeah we could use a shovel I
guess I'm dying to the spikes
no learn from this why does it keep on
happening can when we dig can we fill
the hole that we
dig or anything I don't know whatever
I'm going to just dig anyway to get Fest
backpack
back stop touching
me
oh well well well
goodbye
goodbye this is such an un I died
exactly where you died so our bags the
same
place
H learn the
schematic oh wait didn't I already know
that one this one
Lear a a it's the nerd outfit that's
where the cage comes
from are you digging naked people hello
I'm so close what if I just jump for it
no no no give me my bag stuck in the
spike it's Spike free are you
good you're almost there okay you can't
pick it up with spikes on top of it
anyway I tried mhm it seems like
so I can't even reach the spikes almost
there almost there should be pretty
reachable now o gy o my
hurts wait is this mine this is mine
okay did it work yeah you can go get
your backpack
yay all right I'll I'll continue with
this
then I'll make sure have the back
extremely
effective this feels so
wasteful let me get out of here and then
restart somewhere else
yeah I want to go home wait the loot
despawned there was loot here like a lot
of it it despawns after a few minutes I
feel too
long oh well maybe mod with spikes are
not the best thing cuz we can't get the
stuff well we did it did save us
probably I mean yeah it was really
effective and I
gra the house anyway so
I think it was still good it but
thinking of it you're F you can take
your bike back oh is it because there
was no mo here thank you they almost
here because there was no
okay oh I was I was
crouching everybody check the magazine
box for ammo and magazines cuz I put
some in there okay um here is your bag
Kara you're with armor right y but
workst is still useful okay I'll start
learning
armor maybe maybe the spike should be
around not in the mode even though I
like the
idea but it's not very practical when it
comes to picking up
loot what about
survival we can survive and get mot uh
mot loot
[Music]
ah
well they had so much ammo in their loot
I want that
ammo I used up
[Music]
everything did you check the the
Box uh well not not
recently I put some in there okay I
picked up I like there's lots of ammo in
here of ammo and I used it all
up I'm also putting uh the 9 mm ammo
into the box oh thank you and some
shotgun
shells have you learned the Pocket Mod
armor Pockets I think I did
yep how what do you need to craft
it uh let's see
armor double pocket mut
um scrap polymers which we should have
plenty mechanical parts we got a few the
the materials that might be not plenty
is duct tape and sewing kit SE kit I see
I see those are good apparently if you
haven't I have a couple of those too mhm
two I think I put two in my armor you
have two m
it opens up quite a
bit but still I would like a bigger
inventory even
bigger good
job motorcycle
motorcycle oh I I just unlocked another
vehicle it seems oh I I have motorcycle
parts I got from a class in my chest at
home but I literally just made mini
bikes yesterday I'm not going to really
go make motorcycles I
think yeah and they need a lot of
Steel I'm not going to we we need get
that Crucible first I think yeah we
should see if we can buy it yeah maybe
tomorrow when more members are online we
can gather all our money yeah I thought
we could get it today if you guys want
to
yeah oh yeah here take my money
good job take all of this really yeah
thank you I'm going to be
digging are you digging more yeah got to
make sure the back side and the other
side is all
covered anything from home we should
take yeah oh sorry you didn't take the
nerd had in the end did you no I didn't
take it I was going to give you more
exp yeah I slipped my mind I was so busy
bgy oh we have more treasure maps we
should do those I want to go on a
treasure hunt okay I'll hold on to them
and we can go treasure
hunting whoa whoa wo wo he you think we
want to go today or
tomorrow anytime I'm just going to bring
him to the new house I'm just seeing
what's here so we can move stuff
over people box has five sewing kids oh
take it take it really did you know that
you had these over here
no a nice surprise found a couple more
sewing kits in an unnamed
chest they go to the armor because the
armor needs it most for everybody's
purpose treasure chests have money in
them that could be good yeah money is
always
good M wait isn't everything supposed to
respawn today or no it's not how it
works who was a crony Cron's chest
okay I guess I'll go back to the house
I'm I wonder how long we should play cuz
the raid ended and tomorrow CI wanted us
to do to do like a a full cycle more or
less
wait a full cycle of seven
hour I don't know if that's what she
meant I feel like it's it's honestly
better if we play a little more that way
tomorrow doesn't have to be yeah yeah it
doesn't have to at least 6 hours
tomorrow yeah six is already plenty how
many how many hours is it from now from
the next
[Music]
day an hour day or or not not the next
time the next time so like 7 hours seven
hours yeah so yeah we could we should
play a little bit more to like bring
that down yeah I think so I don't think
I don't are we Addicted by any chance
maybe just a little bit just a
I'm not sure it feels
like we're we just want to make sure
we're really prepared for that big final
raid
[Music]
yeah we want to make it into a an easy
fight for our girls who haven't been
here every day so the experienced ones
are preparing it for the less
experienced
ones plus it's going to get even hard
yeah yeah right I'm scared of more of
the Wolves showing
up
I de though the the W wasn't actually
bad I just jumped and it couldn't hit me
and I just shot it while jumping jumping
is kind of op I
see the more Shooters the better for
Wolf yeah unless they shoot the 110 that
is tanking the
wolf oh I guess I'm the only one who can
do that to wolves though cuz I have
parkour I got parkour too oh nice yeah
parkour is good if you jump they can't
bite you so you just keep jumping in
place and shooting them from below or
above and yeah but usually when I'm out
there if there's a need for me to jump
then I'm probably already using my
sledgehammer and my sledgehammer will
use up so much stamina that I'm not even
able to jump anymore most of the
[Music]
time bad weapon but I already committed
to it and it's pretty cool I like it
when I can Hammer their heads open and
they go yeah satisfying
my armor is breaking huh do you guys
want to do the treasure chest today then
sure okay but I mean I guess not
everybody has to go we can productive
and split it's helpful a lot of come
because
huh huh H did you not did you not
see I don't know how to describe what
just
happened you
got to show you a clip of it later yeah
someone clipped that I don't know what
happened uh but I I to say uh the area
for the treasure is actually quite big
so and um you know it's the same thing
where when you after you dig enemies
spawn so it
might all right I am bikeless oh oh no
did we leave you there
I I willingly chose to
St I'm I'm just saying I will need a RH
if it is far it's okay I
can uh I'll come pick you up actually
are you ready to come back no okay let
me know when let me know when you're
ready to come back and I'll come pick
you up okay I I'm I'm I'm almost done
fing now one thing I realized when we
were fighting rather than food I was is
more in need of medkits yeah I want to
go get a bunch of aloe from the desert
if we
can I can collect a bunch really fast
okay okay that's a good thing to put on
our list tomorrow or
today yes
beer excuse me
excuse I'm
trapped thank you sorry it's okay small
house
we should knock down some more
walls make it a big open space I got an
Al aloe vera
seed we we have
four yeah I already we're out of a
[Music]
gardening
oops did you need to come here and bite
the walls down please
okay I'll knock all the wall in the
house
yeah yeah I I had to tear down these
walls because I was going for a much
more open kitchen and then that way it
leads into the the patio as well as the
bathroom and you can see the bathroom
from the patio what I was going for
yeah I see the vision oh I don't like
the Privacy you know that's why I like
going to everyone's
chest to hide yeah that's exactly what
I'm thinking we're already in the zombie
apocalypse why are you keeping secrets
you hate us
yeah do we have any repair kits no don't
think so I can make
some okay my bike still has stuff right
what we
got
magazines um Salvage
Salvage is anybody learning repair
tools uh how much do I have in repair
tools let's see I only have five okay
that's more than me so I also have a
little bit around that but I thought
somebody might have
higher don't forget to periodically
check your
challenges oh yeah
[Music]
nothing new except for
one cop zombies yeah I killed plenty of
[Music]
those I need more big mama
zombies is that a thing yeah oh I got
the cop zombies too 10,000 XP wow
wait it give you a rare
item rare item no I thought it
said I didn't actually read it I just
glanced at it said 10,000 XP and rare
item did I get something rare items I
didn't get anything where's my rare
items from the
trader oh do you have to turn it in at
the trader
hopefully any Trader not a specific
one I'll just Lear these all
um I'm so smart in this game I'm so
smart I have read so many books I'm so
well read
wow my brain is exploding and
expanding yeah more books more
knowledge knowledge is overpowered
knowledge is
everything I'm making a bunch of repair
kits for us m
thank you Mommy F corn
Ready
corn corn for
dinner it has no nutritional
value
wait do I need to use a knife to get
corn T Steel am I
[Music]
crazy oh it's not ready oh is did it say
growing I just can't make a better one
of this I can't
read maybe
five it looked ready it wasn't ready
don't want to use a do
it make steel I don't have enough steel
I'll just make this little five one
first and then in the future I'll make
the best steel Hammer I can make how
about that steel is just too rare right
now guys give up
you're too hopeful yeah but we could go
get The Crucible
right yeah indeed GG's generous donation
don't have enough yeah for my wives do I
have the parts I think I do you have my
entire life savings in your hand I do do
you have enough I have I have some more
money I have 10,000 oh if we I have
4.6k I'll give you all my money for one
repair kit okay how about I've got a
bunch of repair
kits where's the B
boo
stairs if he does sell it right now then
we should definitely get it from Bob
yeah I don't know if he always has it
but we should
check ah he here go here you go
turn doesn't matter where chat thank you
oh I have exactly
15,000 but I want to make it at a higher
level
chat I think I'll just make this one
first I I'll be right but I got to wash
my eye out there's like a oh no a a a a
in it OE be right bye
okay I think that's better before I'm
like wasting all the
[Music]
steel so going to make this one
lever
lever should have made this before the
hoorde came but
you know lots to
do oh gosh the steel Knuckles are so
expensive wait the cop zombie reward
might be really good huh really chat
keeps on spamming now that I should go
get it
now so I'm going to go get
it wait take me with you
okay if you don't tickle me
okay I won't tickle you okay otherwise
I'll crash us I promise oh no tickle
tickle your Uber bike is outside oh can
you unlock in the doors what I have to
do that
again unbelievable you need a fob you
need maybe I should just put codes on
everything then I don't have to unlock
it right oh does that work
one11 yeah most common code okay yeah
that it seems like it might
work all
right here we
go oh I see yeah go to any Trader to
collect your
reward we're cop Slayer okay I'm back
welcome back are you better are you I'm
better yes I washed it
out please write me high ranking uh in
the five stars yeah please do I'll write
you back spelled very good thank
you spread the
word what are you looking he he gives us
water filter a cross a CR I'm taking The
Crucible I'm taking the Y wait these are
really good these are super good he also
gives legendary parts and solar cells
you didn't have to buy it no uh it's a
reward for killing 50 cops zombi you
should go to the
tra I I I we only need one Crucible yeah
only one I bought it I'm going to get
the water filter then okay
okay noise noise noise you guys can have
your money your money back okay
[Music]
although
maybe he sells something nice something
else what does what does he have
I mean you sell steel no wait we don't
need steel now I can I can forge steel
with this
Crucible
rocket handgun Parts I would really like
those I don't I'm already is he selling
them I don't know
um no he does not
no I wonder how much steel I can make
right up the bat wait can I give you
your money back oh yes here take take
your money
back it seems some of it is missing is
it no it's okay it's okay
J it mind be it all
combined oh I can also take a water
filter and a solar cell and a
crucible what do we what do we need m i
mean water F would be good or legendary
Parts
yeah maybe giggy can also get a reward
giggy did you kill 50 cop zombies no I
need to kill 20 more well we have a we
have a lot of legendary parts and we can
loot those right so I don't feel I feel
like legendary parts we could make a
second Forge we have three right now
I used some for your guys's armor and
also one for myself I think so we're
down to free what's what's a solar cell
it must be for some other cool machine
but I have yet to find what it's useful
for yeah I guess you can get power but I
don't know what it's used for
electricity okay maybe maybe I'll just
get another water filter let's get a
water filter so yeah okay
all right steel is in the
making y exting steel ah for turrets
solar power for turrets maybe is what
it's
for ah I already got the water filter
though by the way people you were able
uh to make ammo right yes do you make
those in the Forge or elsewhere not the
work thingy
is it difficult to make big amounts
no I might we might need extra tomorrow
you can make bullet casings in the Forge
and then I need gunpowder and the bullet
thingies which I've been collecting a
lot of so okay not too bad cuz like even
with four Stacks I ran out today and
tomorrow you know a lot of people need
probably much more Amo so we might want
to make some ourselves
tomorrow send giggy to collect
gunpowder why yeah gun gunpowder would
be nice where do you get
that I don't
know what rock do I hit for
that uh explosive no iron they they're
saying you should rather collect iron
iron iron but okay but I have 1,000 on
me right now I can get more more more
more after I finish this
moat oh you're already making the next
mode yeah maybe let's not fill it with
spikes let's just put spikes around you
don't like my no I like him I what about
what about one one one Spike you know
instead of double spiking what if I do
one Spike okay so you mean have the path
to two Fields but only one is spikes
that could
work yeah single wall
spike okay ah also they're saying make
free Block tall wall of spikes on the
outside for
jumpers
oh I guess we're going to get some high
jumping enemies
next
[Music]
concerning there we go I wonder if we
have more I'm just not seeing
it iron iron iron iron iron
[Music]
iron oh there's a bunch of gunpowder in
one of our chests
yeah but you you can make bullet casings
in the Forge mhm with the brass I guess
oh with brass and clay and we have so
much of that mhm
so that's
easy so just bullet tip and gunpowder
bullet chip
uh is lead and
Clay oh so you you can make that in the
Forge as well so basically we just need
gunpowder I think that's craftable
too maybe I should put out a second
[Music]
Forge I
could I could maybe I will oh I have a
lot
of I can make some bullets now if
anybody needs any or I'll wait until
till people L on and see what people
need I Mayan we could already put it
into the
C let's throw in
some I
don't I can't make it yet no no not
yet oh I can make high
power ammo too and armor piercing I
would already be happy with just normal
one I think cuz I'm guessing that takes
less
resources okay I'm going to make I'm
going to make some 762 for you first and
okay and then once we get
more materials we can oh yay do
collectors
yay that will be useful yeah we don't
have to boil the water
anymore yeah
I also want to stock up on explosives
again because explosives were very very
useful for that
mhm M sounds
good okay I'm making a second Forge so
that we can um smelt all the stuff
faster the brass and
everything I'm going to put it also in
the kitchen
maybe
here where's my
wrench renovating the kit a little duct
tape oh yeah just put it in put it in
for now I'm just collecting a lot of uh
stuff so that tomorrow hopefully I can
make some armor for the
less covered up
girls so
lud so scantily
clad I would like to go to the desert if
anybody wants
to we could do some quests and I do you
want to get some Alo get the treasure
chest first I have two treasure maps
on there is oh there's one by G there's
one by our old house and then there's
one in
the dead fire
area yeah let's do it okay I'm going to
go to the one by G first and that way we
can pick you up as well you're going
right
away one by G um where is it please
bring me some food and
water okay thank you I'll
I'll should I go to B Boo for the
treasure yeah we should we should all do
the the treasure together cuz it's a big
circle and enemies will
spot okay is it digging do you have to
dig for it yes you have to dig y I know
yeah I need an iron
shovel uh I only have a stone shovel
even for myself I'm coming to pick you
up Gigi okay let me know when you're
here I will come out of my
hole hobos do takes so long to cook but
it's good got to render down all the
stuff you put in it all the mystery
M just wonder what you're feeding guys
what are you feeding us just is it worse
than rotten
flesh um no it's not worse than rotten
flesh
nice
nice how about
BR there's so much clay over there um
sand when will we need Sand and Stone
is it crushed
sand for
cement I don't know should I prepare
it don't have space
anyway trying to forge forge on
ah
okay could craft another
Bellow
um I think I'm ready to head over when
you are Ki Oh
I just looking for six pieces of
wood check the check the fire the
cooking pot I think you can take it out
of there I don't want to cancel it but I
I could just yeah I'm canceling it for a
moment we cancel the water one the water
one no no I already have wood I already
have wood oh oh
okay um is that
that's I got it
just reach into the fire
c h
wood as a phoenix I will be
fine thank you for your I am
here come out your come
out do you like what I've done why is
there a dead when did this dead animal
get in my
um
oh where did it go
I didn't even I didn't get to glot it
how did it
die it just died and disappeared it's
not
fair although are we waiting for them to
arrive going there keep working on your
hole here I'll give you I'll drop some
food in your hole Yeah
yummy sorry I keep on I'm going to drop
with some BL water in your hole so that
way you stay gobble gobble gobble
yeah okay that'll make me happy thank
you you're
welcome okay okay okay uh um uh yeah I'm
just putting a away a few things and
then give me two one minute one minute
okay BL you bless you bless
you BL
you I can make seeds potato seeds
[Music]
now it feels so expensive though you
need five potatoes to make one potato
scene and I feel like I get seven
potatoes back so it's like only net two
potatoes what a waste I
know
[Music]
oh okay I'll just leave it
behind ready to
go this
okay although I don't know where to
go oh you didn't take these five sewing
kits in my
box me uh yeah in the old house yeah oh
no I guess oh I'll just bring it with me
just in case okay but right now it's not
too urgent probably tomorrow I'll be
making a bunch of armor but then uh
until then I don't need it are we going
towards the old house now or where where
am I going yeah old house there's a I
don't think you guys can see the where
the treasure is but it is by the old
house okay okay is this the right way no
no is this the right
way yes
okay
what are we going to run out of fuel oh
maybe I feel like we are should we take
our
bikes we can always rch a car on the way
and get more
[Music]
Fu where's the gas station when you need
one
yeah what is the save the environment
huh
GG I'm going to use a plastic
straw somebody's saying we should do the
last raid in the snow biomi because it's
more fun apparently for some reason oh
it's more fun you mean more more
My yeah I don't know she works so hard
on her hole Yeah I think we should just
stay there at least for this last raid
and if we do a second season then we can
resettle in the snow biome maybe yeah
but I mean the Wolves the wolves from
the snow biome still came over here so
but we didn't see any bears at least
yeah Faun hold your breath okay
okay there you
go if I was there I would have tickled
you that's
eil what happened to my caring husband
you just you're just so cute when you're
giggling but I'm
drowning if you hold I just want to see
how well you can hold your
breath it's very concerning I I I feel
like this some murderous
[Music]
intentions yeah but only towards fauna
like what's what's with what's between
you two that I don't have with gigy she
doesn't want to seem to kill
me yeah can you explain
yourself lust
oh I'm out of gas but there's some gas
in the old house I
saw I think unless I took it all uh no I
took the gas in the old house no I
already put in my in
my bike thingy there's no gas in here
okay next car we see I'm going to wrench
okay I'll help you there there's a car
by the house okay you might be able to
wrench that
way 6%
gas I have 15,000 clay in my inventory
everyone you that is a lot Clay is good
for making yeah that' be good for making
bullets and stuff but we already have
several thousands of
clay are you still in your hole no
yes
yes I like it in
here come on come see son come
[Music]
on it's okay you you get to for you get
to dig another hole I'm taking you
somewhere you can dig
too okay you like it so
far it's very nice thank you it worked
really hard where's the extra hole it's
on on this side oh yes you have you have
made it longer beautiful why does B have
a floating
plate do you see what I see oh
yeah I like glitch or something yes Wait
f do we have a to no that's just be
boo yeah yeah has friend all right I'm
going to come here follow me I'm going
to bring you somewhere where you can dig
more
okay favorite hobby but I like what
you've done with the place thank you
I'll put spikes outside of the hole and
a little bit inside are you going to
remove those spes that are there
no they can stay for now as we got a
little bit of can I can we can we siphon
gas out of mine no no it's okay I fill
it back up to 30%
okay oh mine's at 30% as well maybe if I
don't step on the gas it won't use as
much huh yeah does does it work that way
I'm not I'm not stepping on it now and
it doesn't go
down or very slowly
maybe I step on it oh yeah it goes down
right away oh oh but oh not that
much I'll just we're going to have to
walk home no no no no no the Traders
have some gas maybe we can stop
by no no or just rench more cars we'll
be
fine okay it is close
by so aha okay okay did stand right here
okay stand right here I'm going to
stand right here this is the this is the
width of the thing okay okay wait did
you take your money back okay you don't
want it you gave me more than I gave
you must have given you some of some of
B Boo don't oh it's okay I deserve my
child's allow
it what nothing don't worry about
it going to your
college question College I'm doing I'm
getting a because of you you told me to
get a so I did that's why I'm putting it
in your college fun you'll see it once
you get to College okay I believe
you all right F I got some money for
your alcohol
addiction what oh thank you but Papa
please oh no don't worry sweetie we'll
get it we'll get it back we'll just go
to the casino
and how how deep is the treasure
uh if you hit rock that is yeah that's
too far okay but girls I was um I wonder
what you think about this before I
started the gaming portion of the stream
today I was um discussing with my
viewers how I would love to take a like
a trip with everybody to like Las Vegas
or so and have a casino
night play some Black T and
someome but we all have to set like a
maximum budget just so that we don't
overspend Gamba
Gamba I'm putting it all in yeah but a
maximum budget maybe maybe like you know
$10 okay okay that's very very
controlled that sounds good you can't go
a scent over
$10 and then in roulette we'll always
just bet on the same thing over and but
if we if we each bet on something
different then that means one of us will
always win sure for
sure wins will they kick us out is that
cheating you're you're outside the
border now oh no I'm just diing for fun
now oh my shovel is going to not hold up
for that long I've got repair kits M
okay always Stone
here oh okay
the the got
smaller okay which which way towards
bble towards B okay
yeah I'm standing pretty much in the
middle of
it we have to dig in a circle or just a
line I think it's within the circle it's
somewhere within the circle perimeter oh
this better be worth it yeah
yeah I'm enjoying this how many
Treasures do you have I have two maps so
this one and there's another one in the
fire fire light the fireplace but wen't
there zombies going to
spawn what happened spawn last
time huh maybe that was a natural
spawn
maybe oh he you wait the time when the
uh spawned are you referencing to the
time where we had the digging Quest no
it was I had another quest in the ice or
not a quest but a treasure map in the
ice place and things were spot in quite
a
bit we already dug so much where is this
TR yeah we
did imagine if this was our
mode we could just move
here I have 200 spikes on
oh go 200 is that what all the wood was
for was this your like Grand Design
wow it wasn't planned to become spikes
it just so happened that they became
spikes I have a plan got smaller yet can
you help out you connect this tunnel to
our thisel this way towards people
towards people again where are
you there this way yeah yeah
so until tomorrow's forn night gigy I
want to see a connection between these
tunnels can you do
it these are our secret
tunnels it's absolutely necessary for
our survival okay once I get an iron
shovel I'll start working on it it will
be our emergency exit tunnel yeah yeah
they'll never know yeah we can bunker up
somewhere here
these are the secret Denver airport
tles conspiracy are you very familiar
with the Denver Airport Denver
Airport I've looked into okay I need a
repair
kit okay what's special about the Denver
Airport here go the horse with the
glowing eyes is very special and
interesting we could take a field trip
to Denver Airport and check out the
horse on the way to Las Vegas yeah oh
wait oh I don't need a repair kit for
this sh shovel nice all right oh I guess
you don't yeah Stones yeah ow
awesome Denver is pretty close to Las
Vegas amazing let's combine the trips
wooho let's go see the horse and then go
gambling yeah it did give me Las Vegas
Vibes same are I
guess are we still in the perimeter yeah
we're still in the perimeter it got
smaller but you're still in it
okay this is crazy this is crazy this
better be good this better be good
y'all we could be questing I could be
digging the actual hole
[Music]
wait when's the next day
3 4 the the wall is right right here oh
so like fwn is right on the edge of it I
see it oh you see it it's right here oh
it's locked we have to hit it hold on
let me let no I can uh lockpick it one
second
yippee big
[Music]
this better be worth
it what's
inside this oh 5K okay it was worth it
oh 5K money 5,000 5K money yeah that's
not bad is that it was a lot of stuff
okay here I will drop some it gave me a
lot of materials for bullets actually oh
God
and then here's some kiaha bullets
thanks yeah it gave me Bullet and um and
weapon parts and 5K so that was worth it
that was that was totally worth
[Music]
it no it's all right it's all right was
pretty good pretty
good let's get out of this hole oh and I
got I got gold too gold gold gold and
apparently that's worth gold is extra
money okay got even more money okay that
was worth
it all right do you want to go to my
second one yeah yeah okay uh I don't
know if this thing has any fuel in it no
no it doesn't only the full car run down
oh but those parts are still
useful all right lead the way all right
Ro chest
I'm
here I Let
Go U okay I'm on I'm on
it I'm on
yay close to her
face all right
um we're
[Music]
going west for a while we
BL
eyes
yeah we could check out the bookstore
too oh yeah books books it's in the
snowy area it's Northwest from
here you want to lead the way um let's
go to the treasure first maybe okay and
then see how close we
are wait can I share the way point is
that a
thing shared way points wait
how I'm going to stop by Trader W to get
some fuel too oh
okay so we're going to get the trailer
RCT is on the way okay but I don't I
don't think my mini bike is going to
make
it same
oh do you see my Waypoint now oh
apparently uh CU you shared it but I
have no idea where it is yeah you shared
it but I can't I don't see
North I see it yeah I
see B
north north of Home North of home
oh
what north of the new
house oh I see it okay I see
it I don't see it but we'll go there I
guess I do want to go to the desert too
which is in the opposite direction
it's okay we need to stall for time
anyway
yeah we do mhm you
mean we need to install longer
today I feel like we could and I'm not
just saying that cuz I'm
addicted anybody really want to do it
like 7 hour
stream well it's we need day 35 for the
hord day okay we should save around at
least 4 hours is maybe for the
tomorrow so we should probably we should
probably stop at 31
yeah oh I got a challenge oh we got some
gas I got some gas yeah me too me too
thank you car for your
donation free guas refuel can you refuel
it or do I have to do
it let's see G can you make us some
gas
yeah creates it I think I did it okay
make get some gas please this looks good
would you like some steroids what about
the car right there I don't have a
wrench though oh I don't have a wrench I
have a hammer does that work I don't
think so does a hammer work or does it
have to be a wrench
probably a rench oh
well I'll guess where's the Traer at a
genen no I'm going to W cuz re am I
going the right way fun uh yes
okay I can't look at the map while I'm
driving just follow this road the
direction you're going
okay and at the fork take a right okay
okay nice oh you know the roads now no
I'm looking at the
map she got the map app out yeah I'm in
the the passenger seat
navigating passenger princess but we're
stopping for
CS oh nothing inside okay give us the
guess fill up our TS give it give it you
greedy little minivan
oh
wait the house is here you can grab a
bike if you want no oops sorry I didn't
mean yeah I like sitting here oh you
know what how how full is this one oh
this one's more full okay we're going to
we're going to swap swap we're going to
swap time to swap
bikes oh hold I have to mod this one so
it has a seat hold on I'm going to drop
off all my clay okay put put it uh next
to the forge
[Music]
okay so much clay yeah inventories oops
I got off wait
sorry sorry it's like you're trying to
become an action
hero can I Craft on the back of the bike
oh I can't I wish I could the back seat
making cloth Oh I thought maybe I can
check out oh yeah let me store some
stuff
[Music]
too we're going to JMA right now
huh no we're to we're going to we're
going to Rack not we're going to pass by
this house so we can drop stuff
off right I feel it's close right over
there
in the The Forest of
trees home sweet home the Clementine
house
yeah we have any
water we should have a lot we have a
little bit oh my hammer is
ready Yi
new I feel like every time I come home I
just get stuck doing stuff so it's like
dangerous like that here I'm going to
get rid of these
walls aggressions are being let out
again I want no privacy in our
house why are you worried about cheating
when you have two wives I'm worried
about my child hiding stuff in her room
you not door I need my door I I'm taking
your door I need my privacy my door why
do you need a door to hide stuff from us
I GRE she doesn't need doors yeah yes
she does not need a door
door actually take away all of her
furniture all the take away her bed too
she must sleep take the
bed anything you do in your room you can
do out in the living room
too I'm running away from home I'm going
to my friend's house I'm not when I turn
when I turned 18 I'm out of here dang it
I don't W what is that
screamers oh
oh
time
to so many of them give me some give me
some good thing we opened up the place
good thing would have been punching each
other
yeah they're breaking our walls you see
that the
kitchen oh my God
you through the
stove oh she's there huh in the back
okay W wo wo wo wo wo
ow what's
happening maybe I should put some spikes
outside this house too oh more there's
still more
coming oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh like a
mini horde mini wave yeah mini oh
more and now it's
daytime how exciting come on come on
stamina please hold up hold up zombies
please wait for a
moment oh my God I have like five 10
zombies on me
help and dead
no back of the house kind of Y back of
the house
okay oh my head
hurts oh wait honestly uh I might leave
soon cuz um I've been streaming for 5
hours and my head
hurts okay we have been here for a while
we we we can um stop since it's day 30
yeah 5 hours isn't too bad and we
started earlier anyway I do want to like
give the other girls somewhere you know
time to play we should like do
everything for them yeah
yeah even though we'd love
to do so many
things
yeah but surely a season two will come
one of these days and then hopefully and
we can go to all the biomes that we
missed that we didn't see yet mhm go do
all the things that we still have
available to
us I'm going to build a mod outside this
house too
uhoh you just want to dig no I just I
just feel like we need the
protection that lady busted through our
wall do you see this she did don't think
she didn't take our oven because oh that
one that's yeah there's no window or
anything
there Place something
there she broke
it building block you're not the beaver
anymore you're the mole fix
it need a fix her my Mo life Mo rat once
I go back to hitting trees what am I the
beaver again yeah
yeah it's a gopher now our house looks
stupid our my wall doesn't
match look at it we should paint it
keep those and make things for
[Music]
people we have a lot of forged
steel that's good yes what does it take
to make them anyway God uh what what
does it take to make for Ste anyway just
iron as well so it's it's the same
ingredients as for making fored iron but
it takes a couple more but yeah we're
making
plenty I'm going to make some more have
50 yeah is that too much what how many
50 50 50 sure we'll make more we'll make
more I didn't somebody have a lot of
iron with them
gigy I 1,000 in did we need that into
the forge you yeah it goes into the
forge that's fine oh okay okay
okay the more the
area I need five leather do we have any
we do it's in the CH uh next to the
forge take take
okay I need
to the for is burning
me sorry a little bit of warn hot
I'm crafting an iron
shovel iron
shovel I'm making level five
Knuckles
ooh I have level one right now I'm
skipping a
few I hear something why is there
another zombie they can't get a nap of
us
best alive so chill like no one else
plays with us when you're offline please
play with us now did I not oh right you
have to use the the
bench feels
good ni
oh 50 50 stamina per
hit
wow good stuff she did right yeah
okay did you upgrade yeah a better
Hammer nice I didn't make a max level
one I I wanted to save for the next
steel Hammer so for now I just made a
good iron
Hammer but
eventually season two will be my hammer
Life season in full bloom my hammer
life oh my head hurts I really really
hope that we can keep our
[Music]
character
son my
shovel woohoo what did it a break or you
made one I crafted it it what kind of
shovel did you make my iron shovel my
level five iron
shovel you like it okay let's see how
fast dig a dig a mo around this house
too see how fast you can do it oh my God
two hits on this block that's pretty
fast look at them
playing right yeah
that's is how it
be I'm hurt so much oh no maybe we
should force it we should just all log
off for your health but I need to wait
15 more seconds for my steal but I need
to I need to go to the trader to check
the items by the trader
though but there's also infestation
quests on the way that I might want to
do on the way to the tra no more quests
no more just going to the train then my
head oh God oh
God where's the zombie I can test this
out
on you you know where you can test it
out on you can test it on on this tier
four Quest that's I'm right next to
oh oh you're far
oh wait my mods I
[Music]
forgot
um uh
I'm
dying don't die don't die don't
die thanks that was all I need not
allowed yeah no don't die you're so
[Music]
sexy okay I'll think over it again I'll
reconsider
it it be a waste of such a good butt
yeah that is true press for on Mirage to
look at her
ass I think they all already did but
thanks maybe we can get some more I
actually I uploaded the dance version a
few hours
ago to watch it
yeah watch my EG press four in that one
um I think just press four go get to a
butt I think in the dance sh it might
not align perfectly we we kind of
purposefully shortened the song in the
official music video by like one or two
seconds so that it will align
perfectly I don't think it works for the
dance sh but it's more about you know
the overall video than just pressing for
on that one that is
true I do love dance versions of songs
right I love watching those
[Music]
too he it does work still oh it works
all right
oh perfect four always works no the boar
isn't
[Music]
here I just wanted something to
fight the really really big one you guys
kill it again
yeah mode
now I can give maybe we should just AFK
on the server for maybe 10 hours no
respa everything not it's not
productive yeah wait what the what what
didn't
respawn the book The oh the boar
oh
sad I have to go fight a bear in the
tundra it's the only way that bear is
trying to get his
[Music]
education wow I think that's we're
reparing and giving learn up on fighting
[Music]
them yeah these are still
good for
tomorrow
then I have a point available
[Music]
maybe one more in
here was worth
it what' you get I got handgun Parts Jen
was nice also she has a lot of fuel for
cheap so I've just stocked up on a bunch
of fuel for everyone since I feel like
we'll be needing it that's
good not a bear
two
points okay I'll save up still pretty
good
though it's not going anywhere that is
true the game is not going anywhere it's
true we'll play tomorrow yeah we'll have
play
time after we're playing right
now we could play tomorrow but also
we're playing right now
what was that the one
uh Commando
boots should I make these two
chant the weighted head mod for your
Sledgehammer weighted head
mods why are we still
online I'm ready to log off at any
moment yeah if you tell me to log off I
will we can stop any moment right yes we
have power over
it
sure I can lock up any what is that is
that a mountain lion wait I can't fight
the cat I can't those are
dangerous very dangerous are they but I
don't want to fight it cuz it's cute oh
there's a bear I can fight the bear oh
are you saying are you saying the bear
is not cute no the bear is cute too but
I have a weakness for cats and oh that's
that's the one thing that you will not
do in this
game
understandable what is this CH what is
this puff puff
do you
know how do I fix
it a SNK uh oh what I forgot to bring
bandages I'm going to
die that bear toughened up since the
last time you saw it did I forgot to
bring
bandaids
no it's over
I I mean I guess we need to find more
bandage for you so
like I'm Invincible nothing can kill me
nothing will ever kill
me I am so
strong oh I didn't bring anything I
didn't bring any food
either 2
granny to find this bear there's another
bear
[Music]
well I mean if she's fighting your
health is very low yeah but I
live I will never die I'm Invincible yes
that's what I've learn as long as long
as you believe it it is true
yeah I should go to the I mean you're
you're you're fighting bears right yeah
okay I was
yes why am I missing
oh one
more
no duct tape
it's the usual cycle of you need more
duct tap no I made a
couple but you know probably we'll need
more tomorrow for the other girls well
now we have lots of water so should be
should be better okay yeah we improved
our situation we
did okay Wawa treat herself with some
nice
boots we girls we like shoes you know
yeah yeah shoes oh my God
shoes love shoes pretty pretty How many
pairs of shoes do you guys estimate you
own
30 yeah I think I'm around 30 what I
want to see your
shoes maybe
40 I I have like uh
like eight pairs but like five of those
I bought into pan so I like
recent yeah bio you were really decking
yourself out in Japan with new stuff new
clothes a whole new face it's the
way you know those TV shows where
somebody gets like a complete make over
in terms of cloes like fashion
everything bio almost did that huh
no I pretty much did that because
because I got I got like the the hair
treatment and then I got the nails and
then I got the new wardrobe in ja yeah
nice treat yourself that's how it feels
Japanese fashion is just on another
level I dress like a pretty princess now
yes I don't know I feel like you go
outside and everyone's dressed up and I
can't go out looking like a rat
there I'm really excited to meet you and
see how you dress and everything it's
always so interesting to
[Music]
see we'll
see what I dress what our first time
Vegas Vegas let's do Vegas trip I want
to go Vegas but I'm going to wear my
pretty princess
stuff I was saying I'm kind of hoping
that if we have another Ian con conert
since we already had East Coast West
Coast maybe next middle of the country
kind of Las Vegas we're not going to
hope for
Europe you're like come on let's go
gambling I would love to but I don't
know if whole life is is it Vegas west
coast is iteg it's pretty Coast West I'm
pretty sure oh yeah I thought it was
more
middle I mean it's more middle than LA
but yeah there's no ocean touching Las
Vegas yeah yeah so
weegas Cleveland
Ohio
concert
Cleveland oh let's go go Ohio oh it's
it's 6:00 a.m. over here it's time to
end it oh
Ohio I I'm happy with what my progress
I've made some extra stuff I'm ready to
end it yay I will do what's good for all
of us me to me too I almost ready give
me like 5 minutes I press trigger good
job that's the first step you know what
this is what we need and now I'm going
to leave this call too so you will sit
in silence and think no that's too sad
okay I'll wait I'll
wait I'm almost done okay okay looking
over my Forge are you okay are you ready
to sleep Forge
CH let me put some weird how like you
log in and nothing has changed like no
time has passed like the next time you
log in like your stuff is still cooking
I'm glad it is I don't know I'm like I
feel like I should log in and I should
have like 18 hobo stews ready you know
no but that would be concerning cuz that
would mean somebody else logged in when
you weren't online and let the time pass
that cannot happen
we have to be online at all times that's
true okay I put some brass in the Forge
let's cooking I'm going to log out doing
it I'm doing it guys goodbye game see
you tomorrow for the last time it will
be such a sad farewell but a nice one
too yeah it'll be bit sweet but we did
so much mhm
[Music]
well it was quite the ark
run egg I'm a run egg okay I am the Run
egg what run egg oh have you heard that
no that phrase no it's like something
you do with your friends when you're
like like getting somewhere it's like
last one there's a rotten
egg rais them somewhere oh have you also
successfully left the game vao yeah yeah
it's like last one in is a rotten egg
I'm the rotten egg rotten egg
laughing is there similar phrase in
German to
that a thing probably when somebody gets
left behind or stays behind on
purpose have to look it up foul as I
yeah but do we ever say that like
that I don't know
ah well well well we were so strong SP
it's the exact
same that's what somebody in my chat
said rotten egg oh but probably well
rotten
hos whoever
podo podo
J whoever p
H I heard that before the last one will
be bitten by the dogs oh oh yeah that's
a good one you hear was bitten by I was
bitten by a dog so it it worked out
careful they're going to eat you
up I'm almost done I think I'm almost
done well I want to say thank you girls
it's so nice even though four people you
know small group but I think we did our
best we did
well I'm happy to spend time together
our family the Clementine family yeah
just a little
abusive little toxic family
Dynamic we will get through this
together it's it's normal to get a
little bit toxic in a zombie apocalypse
it's a very stressful environment after
all
yeah had a dream about you what did you
dream about I dream that we were in the
zombie apocalypse and you were sad and I
was comforting you and I was hugging you
and then I turned into a zombie and
started eating
you where did you eat where did
you did I just smell so good I mean I
couldn't help it I I turned at that
moment that was my time to become a
zombie what part did you bite first I
think you're neck oh spicy vampire yeah
vampire in the
gym okay I'm done oh she doesn't want to
hear the parents love stories what you
want to hear don't this is how you were
made
I this is how me and your mother met
no people it's the birds and the
[Music]
bees
that's marriage this is how it
started okay I I've logged I'm I'm
logging off now are I'm gone we'll see
each other tomorrow um 1 hour earlier
than usual yes Mark it in the
calendars and we'll hopefully have a
good last final
episode
yeah let's pull the noobs through
it yeah
with with the Seven Days to Die God
[Music]
[Applause]
Pros see you
tomorrow see you bye bye
[Music]
I'm
suffering that was good that was really
good good day again a pretty dramatic uh
raid it was really only the first day
where it was underwhelming but that's
maybe like a warmup rate
understandable yeah I'm almost full
level six armor I don't want to go too
hard because I got to probably make some
armor tomorrow but there's some hand me
downs and uh we'll be fine they don't
need the best
armor you know the the the most
experienced ones need the best
armor but let's see hopefully we can
gather a bit more armor kits tomorrow to
deck everyone
out deck them
out but I might give someone my nerd hat
for the
last uh r so that they can gain more exp
although I mean there's no point if they
don't plan on like playing again in the
future hopefully everybody will join
again one day motorcycle tomorrow no I'm
not going to focus on that I'll focus on
Armor crafting we don't need
motorcycles but I think there's still
One mini bike that doesn't have an extra
seat can put the extra seat on
that um for more Mobility
need to focus on getting ammo yeah lots
of ammo cuz I ran out again I thought I
would be
fine but because I thought I would be
fine I I was shooting a bit miraculously
but also they were just so many spawns
the it barely feels like they um wait
how many were we last time actually
might have just been five or six so I
guess the difference isn't that big
that's why I didn't feel very different
but that was a
lot I need more ammo to spray and
prey eight full
Stacks um unless unless I'm a little bit
more careful with shooting but I I was
already
trying a little
[Music]
bit a stronger
AK47 H yeah maybe I can try but I have a
B Hammer now too so if I ran out of ammo
I can just run out there I survived
decently as long as fauna is out there
you know as long as there's not not just
one person out there it's manageable put
a scope on it the one thing that annoys
me with my AK-47 is that there's a lot
of like there's a word for this but I
don't know it by hard when you shoot and
then you know the recoil yeah the
[\h__\h] recoil what do I have to put on
to make the recoil go
away I hate The
Recoil the for grap don't I already have
a for grip on
it maybe a better
one better
stock the stock helps I think yeah but
not enough huh muzzle break Fork grip
better
stock stock of full grip
mod I thought I already have one
on Muscle Break mod muscle mod I don't
okay musle mod doesn't sound familiar I
don't think I learned that
yet and a a book is there a book that
just gets rid of The
Recoil that would be
sick I tap to shoot also you have to bur
yeah I mean I I I noticed like when
there's not too much enemies I just you
know try to give them smaller like
PE like more more
controlled and then it's fine then it
doesn't bother me too much but with the
hoorde bro I got to
go you
know yeah I just need more bullets and
it's fine I I wouldn't mind you know
running outside again and hitting some
with the hammmer cuz it's fun but damn
my stamina and damn the when they hit me
when they all o when they all come at
you at once but I imagine we might have
a few more running outside tomorrow
hopefully a little more people who are
suicidal let's
go increase strength I don't know how
much how many more levels I can get
until tomorrow need extra skill points I
don't mind putting it into to fortitude
yeah I think CI will run out she was
quite motivated last time to run out
too grind Quest well how much time is
there to grind quest one or two
probably and at the same time while
grinding quests Gathering more materials
for armor
kits uh
yeah yeah and
uh could maybe put some money together
to to to buy an extra Crucible or
someone else will get the zombie cop
reward and get us a second Crucible so
that I can make even more steel but all
of that is like Min maxing towards the
future not really necessary for the last
day of
course yeah five 4.5 days you think
we we left you uh us 4.5 days or
so hopefully lots of people join
tomorrow starting and
uh 8 8 a.m.
J okay I think yeah sorry I just a
message to the others telling
them where we left it off and where when
we continue
tomorrow yeah I feel really cool as the
blacksmith making everyone's
stuff definitely helped to upgrade
update some of the girls armor for H
night very
important Hol Plus app just made a post
about your Tik Tok oh nice of
them did they just repost what I wrote
before or did they make their own kind
of
post yeah I'm so useful blacksmith
engineer I'm making bikes I'm making
armor making lots of things their own
post oh I see I'm the KY opan for this
game a little bit a little bit we're all
Kyla the combination of the Clementine
family together creates Kyla
one Kyla
equals four of
us yeah all right my head it's hurting a
little bit less than 10 minutes ago but
it's still kind of hurting so I'm going
to leave you guys behind going to put up
the last stream
reservation and you guys until
tomorrow's
stream please watch the dance video If
you haven't yet check it out check it
out thank you thank you for watching in
German we say have
v
ah meow had fun love love group cute
group good
family good progress good
game good fun I think really one of the
biggest reasons sorry I'm yapping again
but one of the biggest reasons why I'm
having fun is because it's PVE not
PVP cuz that just makes everyone work
together and it's wholesome I like
it Kyla not fast gr Well yeah if we all
play the same amount of
time and Kyla wouldn't be able to just
play a lot while everybody else is
offline yeah then then she would
probably not be that much ahead of us at
all you know she'll probably just be you
know as addicted as bibo and as
actively questing and everything as beo
but around the same level yeah for
sure
true in a controlled
environment that's why rust wasn't as
good my rust I think what I had a late
start and everything that played into it
um but
yeah yeah I like it more when
everybody's like friendly and we work
together against NPCs
now but then the PVP element did give a
really crazy fun finale where everybody
tries to kill P
Senpai that was interesting
but we could also just kill a big NPC
boss
together
yeah yeah yeah all right then goodbye
guys andj in for the second time
see you tomorrow and then somewhat
normal schedule will resume
[Music]