uh first of all since I'm alone here
after all you guys will have to help me
okay
is it gonna attack me is it a wild boar
please don't kill me now listen here
little [\h__\h]
how fast is it is there like a back view
and I remembered
how is that this one wait I'm on the
whole server right that looks like a
random what is that what's up for me but
who are you you're honest someone said
turn on stereo mode so is that damage
Teresa
Teresa where'd you go it's a long way to
army man what is this does someone's
base that looks like self-made how
dead body but I can loot
it's another whole life member don't
look okay yeah she's listening
don't I'm I'm no I'm new I'm
it I Heard a Voice
yes are you here to save me
[Laughter]
oh my god did you shoot me I was just
I'm just trying to see if you were you
know paying attention
you lose [\h__\h] no don't do that sorry sir
it gives me a heart attack every house
needs a foundation okay house is done
yay
what now now uh usually so what people
do in this game is if you press G oh
look at the map and then do you see the
water treatment
is
okay I got it I got it we're so scared
oh man what are we doing again ah we
wanted to get me a kill oh
[Music]
there's a helicopter right above my
house close the door go away
was it flying that low tactical news
drop a bomb on it and fall on the ground
no my roof is okay though fine
just a large one huge what do I place
how why is it so stupid why can't it be
easier I want it to be up there
and that's way too long make a ladder
let's put it as high as possible
um
[Music]
let me it won't let me now I'm too close
to one what am I supposed to do [\h__\h]
scuff I paid 40 bucks for this little
basic rules are so [\h__\h] stupid but
I'm gonna I'm gonna get used to it you
know I'm not gonna complain about it no
no no no no I have an adult if it lets
me place it here oh should it be closer
just in case would that interfere
feeling
it's getting dark now I can't [\h__\h]
ride on my sign again don't look bright
enough you're not telling me that the
floor is interfering right maybe it's
just too big I don't know what what what
what what what what what what what what
what what is the matter
[Music]
successful first Rush stream I I saw
like we did a lot of holy [\h__\h] I I
learned fast don't I fast learner
takanasi kiwawa
[Music]