[Music]
K It's the final
day where
here I'm I was going to run to the the
desert you know it actually feels like I
was just playing this game like we just
ended yesterday and like no time has
passed my whole existence the past seven
days has been revolving around this game
it even haunts me in my
dreams but here we
are for beating a bear I need
Aloe where do which one one of these
mfers is
Alo um is that a dead
rabbit that's a piece of
wood the small one this
one oh my gosh we're going to have so
many
bandages okay let me join the
VC in a
second I don't know what the plan is I
don't know if my timer is accurate if
anybody has a better
idea let me know please tell me
in
jst terms at what time the rain will
start I'm
hungry I would ask you to do math don't
ask me to do
math gra Yuka Yuka too is Yuka good
just past three wait what do I have a
set to I have a set to
one 100 p.m. that's what I have it said
to yaka y
y yo what
the
okay roll with the 1 p.m. okay but I'm
definitely going to forget about the
timer and then if it Chang I'm not going
to know okay let's let's join the the
VC mother yeah mother she's not
mothering right
now what oh mother mother why am I
mother why am my
mother just because well in this in this
family you are my mother am I do I have
to be I'm TI like how this this seven
days to die wasn't meant to be role play
but somehow we kind of turned it into a
little bit of a roleplay
fil yeah
naturally we just fall into our roles
maybe because we're destined for them no
I don't want to be destined for
mommy no said
Mommy every day since for the last years
the voices have been in my head they
won't leave mommy this different this is
different here you mother mothering this
is this is different cuz I have like
three so you're just part of
it oh
okay people where are you um I am
heading home but looting houses on the
way m
want some stuff what are you want to be
FAA what I want to be me I want to be
FAA so
inspirational you know what you know
what I'll call
you thank you thank
you we'll make it a thing don't
[Laughter]
worry uh I have paint brush what do I do
with that can I paint something paint
the house very important before the
finale very yeah that's priority mhm
yeah call her call her one punch
fauna oh oh my God I can make the walls
wooden we can make this like a cottage
cor house guys oh my God I love Cottage
core let's do it it's it's like a ooh
rotic Chic oh my god oh W hello can you
hear me yes we can hear you yes that's
good at least at least you can hear
me game kicked me out rud oh no oh no
that's
rude come back come back I thought I
thought I was going to have the internet
Cur cuz my internet's been a little
funny so I was like
scared really they don't want us scary
right they're afraid of us qu they
probably heard that it's the last day so
they're
like make it long make it long kick them
all out I have a question are we going
to protect these house or the old house
for the raid the old house okay yeah the
one with all the spikes we we dug we dug
our D dog some some Moes in
there check it out it looks very
intense yeah oo I'm ready where are you
I am nearby why because I'm getting I'm
getting
Stones oh okay okay wanted to show you
this new interior design oh I'm
coming my leg is broken oh no has it
always not
been every single
time I think we have
splints at the new house but need to
okay more time
one me it's easy it's kind of like I
mean I have heard you know when people
like dislocate their shoulder or
something then they more prone to
another injury maybe that's what it's
like with you at this
point your your leg sees a pebble and
it's like ah I'm here s my queen hello
look
look oh my God this is actually so
cozy right is it the paint yeah it's
like wooden wooden paint it's paints
everything fake wood this is so
pretty good job oh was an interior
designer before before the zombie
apocalypse happened
really sucks so even though I can't live
my dream job anymore you know what I put
it into the world whenever I can wait
what did you paint let me see
this yeah oh cozy was was there a
different all the walls were like like
this before where the candle
is I'm standing where I'm standing turn
around turn around turn around like this
oh another wooden oh
co oh yeah that's
nice I love it she totally
noticed
yep maybe with the the type of person to
lie when you go up to her and go like do
you notice the difference do you do you
think do you see what I did yeah it's
you did great
sweety it's actually very so proud of
you you can see the concrete over there
and see the difference
people okay sorry I got distracted do we
do we do we do you guys want to do
something do we or should we wait for
the others actually I guess so want to
wait for Callie to un I I am home by the
way K welcome home welcome home I have
something for you that I think you will
be better at using at the final raid oh
oh oh thank you hello 15
hi how did everything going yesterday it
went good it was
funny funny it was funny it was funny a
funny raid
yeah may have been more dangerous than
the
zombies really please what was more more
dangerous than the zombies sorry the but
the defenses we set up around the house
was more dangerous than actual zombies
oh jeez was it around this house no old
house still it's is holding up wow
that's crazy I saw that you guys have a
Dugout around this house though oh
that's giggy can't stop the goer did
that
the the mo yeah this a good use I guess
does anybody has any extra clay by any
chance in the chest over here follow me
follow me I'm following you wait that's
cilia
what okay this
chest thank you so much hey ladies did
we find any shotgun parts by chance yes
they're in the the parts weapons Parts
chest in the new house thank
you weapons Parts chest here we go we
also have a couple Mini bikes by now and
the forge has
grown and yeah by now the zombies that
show up are a little bit more dangerous
we have crazy direwolves showing up when
you see one of those it's so over you're
probably get over you just got to jump
you just got to
jum oh they're so
scary just a big b could do the
trick right so I want to try to improve
especially the armor from the girls who
have the most shitty armor right
now I won't have like enough armor kits
probably to get everybody like the most
amazing armor
but some parts at least yeah um I'm
assuming L CeCe your armor is probably
pretty bad and Callie's maybe too how
how much level is it yeah I think so I
think mine's might be better than us but
it's still not the best
okay though I have a few hand me downs
at least uh there are for example
there's level three preacher gloves
which already give you 30% Undead damage
oh very there's also so many armor in
the armor chest yeah so there's there's
where the hand me- Downs are as well
just so somebody take the level three
gloves and the Commando boots can we can
we this this uh sorry boxes anything
right oh yes okay take take take mhm
okay I'm going to have a ton of
bandages that's good like at least 30
but maybe more oh did you did you
collect all that aloe I'm collecting it
right now nice nice so did farming work
yes well sort of maybe not it's e to
just go out into the wild and punch
plants oh okay now that through
that I'm here I can find some
leather and duct
tape hiah no no I died
again but usually it's like two times
and then it doesn't happen anymore
so so
is duct tape still like our diff most
difficult thing to get like a high value
commodity yeah duct tape and uh forg
steel but yesterday at the end of the
stream we were able to get The Crucible
to forge Forge
steel okay yeah we can also make
glue like C glue as well we should have
a good bit of
water things are getting
better little by little
but still we still need all of those
basic materials anyway yeah get it now
let me see so just do some quests and
and raid some houses and then you'll be
able to collect plenty I think ammo as
well ammo very important I think cuz you
run out of those ammo so quickly at I
can I can craft ammo if anybody needs it
I can craft we have some materials to
craft right now too as well M nice also
please let into your team
oh yeah send me team request please
party
uh also I think one of the most uh
important things for me right now is
sewing
kids you can't craft those right there's
no way to craft them no crafting but the
sometimes the shops sell them too so
I'll keep my eyes peeled if you keep
your eyes peeled for uh shotgun shotgun
parts how many more do you need shotgun
parts yeah go to the trailers the
trailers should be selling some Bob
wasn't selling anything today well go
check check Jan and wrecked because they
sell different things I think I saw
shotgun parts but I need to save my
money for my handgun Parts
understandable
understandable Okie doie repair kits
also I think we'll need repair kits yeah
repair
kits important is
important mhm
Okie
doie sounds good and at the water yeah
we have lots of water now oh
nice uh I'm also cooking some purified
like the good water I'm cooking that
right now oh yes legendary good water
didn't you want hobo
stew I love me some hobo stew hobo stew
now
oh also there's apparently another Traer
in the snow have you guys found him yet
I just got the class for him so I know
where he is okay let me know if he's
he's still in shotgun parts uh sorry K
where did you put the hand meons is it
just
in uh wait they should be in the armor
chest there should be preacher gloves
like on the right side unless somebody
else already took it and I if I took it
already uh took some gloves
okay the Commando boots are good too
Commando
boots where did the nerd hat
go ah okay now I have a nerd hat for you
oh might have to repair it soon
but thank you let me see but yeah I'll
be making more armor don't worry okay I
picked I took the commander boots thank
you kiaha are we bringing for you thank
you all right here's some sewing
kits where do you where do you want me
to put them oh the forge you have seing
kids let's go the forge okay
okay F
five
yo nice thanks for the party invite
actually I'm just going to go up to the
trader the new one anyway uh right now
so that way I can see what he sells
okie dokie okay maybe he sells seashells
yeah buy the seash seash you guys are so
silly I knew immediately where y'all
were going with
that I need duct
tape okay I I think I can I have some as
well if you need oh
El glue and cloth here's some glue
you have glue let's go glue would be so
important right it's I'm cooking glue
right now okay so you you can grab it
when it's done there's five that's
cooking
yipp yipp she's cooking all
right is it okay if it blueberry pie wow
yeah super yummy blueberry pie in the
apocalypse is pretty
impressive chefs can do anything
that is very impressive my hammer is
called gimly and I stand by a forge
making
armor I am
gimly shotgun is going to be so good we
can get
it I think there's books in the old
creepy church people no just you
[Music]
the
floor fell into
the I'm going up north to unlock that
other traitor trador not traitor he's a
traitor kill him
backstab if somebody has more armor
parts I also need those for more armor
crafting tips to make more armor I put a
bunch in there in the chest but maybe
you've used them already they are very
ni necessary if you put them in like two
days ago then I definitely use them yeah
probably okay I got a couple for now I'd
love to get a fancy new armor for myself
at some
point um I want to look real fancy even
though this I can make your stuff I just
need more
materials right so maybe we all do a few
quests today and
GA some
[Music]
material we got to we got to go to the
library too yes oh yeah there's a
library I
forgot books books
books our reading is so vital I know
we're all a bunch of
readers
closed we very we're very literate and
very educated it's pretty impressive I
love reading I mean honestly if you are
in a zombie apocalypse and you're doing
okay survival wise there is nothing
really to do other than learn
so just
power I mean probably there not going to
be any smart friends around what are you
going to do yeah this SP
time
nothing well originally we said we had
like a stream at home right with the
computer so even if we can't stream
because we don't have electricity we
could act as if it we do well we can we
can actually make electricity talk to
ourselves oh we can yes we can we there
solaru how we connect to the internet I
don't know I don't want to stream by
myself no it's okay you'll you'll we'll
sit around the PC and we'll be your
audience oh okay yeah we all for each
other it's like a little you
know pretty good yeah it's like a l
party but everyone else shuts up and
only one person talks I like it sounds
good to meuh
man
um tell me when you guys going to do
quests I am grabing one oh oh yeah I
also have one treasure map that I
haven't done yet and it's good to do cuz
it gave me like 5K and a bunch of weapon
parts so we should probably go dig up
that one too ooh
5K that's big money
yeah yeah okay well I'm going to head
towards the fauna Quest actually cuz
there are two quests over
there are we going to start questing I
guess we can yeah we can might be a good
idea when's the next raid I think day 35
4 and a half
hours
okay
while 1 p.m. day F 5 I need more iron I
need everything I need to wrench cars
what time do Traders
close pretty sure 9 oh 10 yeah I think
it was 10 minutes before 10 p.m. hurry
hurry
hurry go go go go first okay so are we
Hing to pH here three
Quest I think so okay
o um there's bicycles outdo by the way
and mini B
will probably join
my do you know I think that's yours
Kelly it's is are you there already can
I just follow your oh yeah just come to
where I am okay pray I don't die how did
you get there Celly bike ah you bicycle
or bike uh a bike okay good good you're
using your bike it's so fast yay
oh I'm sure it'll be fine any scary
zombies come I'll stand on top of this
truck
easy oh
gosh as this is right
behind oh the new trador has six shotgun
parts
bro dang it we always finds the one that
have the ones that have the shotgun
parts but he's going to close like any
second and kick me out yeah can you can
you buy the Stu I'll pray somebody has
them
tomorrow that's an ambulance but still a
good idea yeah ambulance truck same
vehicle really what do you think
to my head right now she my oh oh not oh
now I thought you meant IRL No She is
totally IRL what do you mean oh yeah
totally IRL what are you talking about
cute how are you balancing her like that
does she like put her
how manys do you need balance I need
four wait no three hold up uh oh I have
them you got them yeah three shotgun
parts for your boy thank you I owe you
what what do I owe you give me handgun
parts or money okay give you the money
from this Quest that would have paid for
the shotgun parts appreciate that you
know we're going to have to put it on
credit cuz I just bought for steel okay
I'm I'm coming to to the quest too by
the way so okay I'm almost there
I'm some of my cut I think I am hearing
Fox the world has opened up since we
have gotten bike
pedal driving the bike will be fast yes
yes you think we can get a car today is
that far I wonder let's see how far we
are from that
we should you guys should do lots of
quests so you can get this new Trader
where I'm at and maybe he'll give us a
car yeah I bet he gives a car oh
oo and you think he GES car cuz I I
literally just got motorcycle parts he
gave me motorcycle parts so maybe the
next step is car parts yeah car parts
but not a car but I need to learn how to
make it first make a car in the oh you
can I you I think when I went to the
forge I I got the I make the four thingy
so you can't make it you need to get the
magazines first I'm at 47 out of
70 with 70 I can make the car oh so I
need 23 more
magazines okay we'll we'll look out for
it yeah Library oh can you guys bring me
some food because I forgot about it and
then I have some I'm coming to the
class she probably be here quick if
she's using the bike yeah I'm Ying I'm
gas
gas let me know when you're
ready
okay
craft oh some Banda down here do a quick
raid of a rando house oh here's yeah go
go loot some stuff while you're waiting
that's that's good stuff house you can
actually loot the house that you're
raiding because it's going to reset when
you start the quest anyway really yes
clever and then we know the layout right
away
yeah it's pretty
cool wow what a gentleman I'm
scared feel like that's somebody I went
to school with there Rando photos are
very frightening it's right oh no alarm
no alarm W wake up
up W
time no that's okay I was happy to wake
up early
today I surprised I woke up without any
alarm I
[Music]
feel I'm I'm ranching a car nearby let
me know when you're done okay I'm just
going to try to get some food cooking so
we have some when we come back good
mother she's mothering what what what
level is your
wrench sorry what what level is your
wrench cuz I found a level 4
one oh mine is level three if you want
to take my level four wrench I can give
it to you oh okay I can give you my
level three wrench okay if you want to
switch then you can wrench cards too or
do you have your own
easier no I just have the level for that
oh okay I'll take it gladly
oh challenge
complete ah by the way the girls who
weren't online yesterday have any of you
um uh in your
achievements have you seen there's a
second window of achievements and if yes
have you completed the 50 50
cops 50 cops you completed that by any
chance why what does that give you it
gives you good stuff actually it gives
you like water filters and usables and
like useful stuff and I think
potentially maybe all of them all of the
Zombie Slayer ones give you maybe good
stuff maybe not
sure we haven't tested it yet properly
no I can
see thank
you that's a lot of zombies uhoh any
help it work I think you will reach the
50 cop zombies today at the final rate
for sure yeah for sure that's awesome
wow and then we'll have to to do season
2 I asked about it and they seemed
receptive oh do they at least know how
we can keep the characters and stuff um
when I mentioned it to them they seemed
to think it was possible okay yay ni
yeah these to let's
go okay I think I'm
ready okay
[Music]
probably bu lots of food cookies
y
okay bike is over
here cuz I feel like yeah we can go
further oh yeah the work
spe uhoh we haven't even set up turrets
and uh electricity yet that's like the
next step yeah what about I feel pretty
far
off yeah let's pretty far away but
turrets would be so
nice you're RA in the same house as me I
just ran away from someone ran towards
you cuz I was like who can protect
me me I'm to save I forgot to take off
my mod off of the wrench if you can take
it off it to me later okay thank you
down don't won you shut up close the
door for now
quick ranching session on the way on
fuel always
always got to it not just the fu it also
gives me iron and I I'm actually out of
iron I think so okay I'm here by the way
[Music]
okay yay we're coming we're
coming wow inventory is already full
what it's full bandages
have
bands
a you'll get rid of them
yeah but maybe we can try to save most
of them for the race I know I feel like
I I don't even have enough I have like
20 right now but I feel like that's not
even
enough I also Parts by the way kiar if
you're trying to make a big
Sledgehammer oh sled Parts yeah oh I uh
yeah oh wait I think I already have
enough but might maybe need more I'm not
sure not
sure dang I blew him away God I can't
wait to see the next
shotgun yeah grab those parts from you
biu I'll I'll uncute you if you
want have some
money put it on my tab
please how much can I buy off your
current shotgun off of you when you get
your new shotgun sure empty absolutely
you can
or handun parts if anyone finds any
handgun parts please give people handgun
part I'll keep it in M
terrible where where are where are
they okay we have
arrived oh one second before we start
the quest can you kill me because I'm
about to
die no hesitation a no hesitation watch
the sunset n forget all of that watch
out watch
out rest in peace I'll miss
you
soon world too soon who's going to give
the jatin their jet packs no one
no I'm
coming thank two class we can do here
there's one for R and one for fin yeah
that's why I came here cuz there's a lot
popping
off all right time to blast them I am
ready ready I'm Hy I'm ready for
blasting make sure to check everywhere
sewing kids could be
everywhere slash the curtains the
curtains have clo we need that embrace
your inner loot Goblin or your outer
loot Goblin everything very much an
outer loot
Goblin it's very obvious also I put a
bunch of food and medicine and kar's
trunk if you need anything and water
trunk
yeah your spacious trunk Bountiful
trunk oh
yes am I
head like Tut on
[Music]
my's head and
on whose mission is this ra oh R you got
to start the mission oh okay sorry it's
okay
yipp yipp
yipp by the way
you's got it
they're upstairs a what this is my
natural
posture just you're just always
ready somebody loan me some money I want
to buy some beer anybody anybody got any
beer
money money I always have beer
money bother you for 300
coins for some
beer yes here I am I am here I give
you here you go oh no thank
you doesn't go any lower I'm trying to
look for stairs down but I got beer for
you here oh you got it for me thank
you so benevolent it take a while oh do
we have to go up oh yeah
stairs oh we're retrieving supplies in
this chest I didn't realize yeah I'll
come back to
this we get up there I wonder
well that doesn't seem
good great now I can see where you
are oh I prefer not to hit my friends oh
are you on fire uhoh uhoh I'm going to
die I'm going to
die come on man what's going on
oh no the damage that bad or was it the
fire fire oh gosh one more
fire more take some take some Band-Aids
out of the trunk some bandaids yeah I
have some Band-Aids put a Band-Aid on
Plenty now a gun oh oh is that my I'll
get the next mission
oh oh it's okay we got a lot ofion Sy oh
we've got supplies if anyone forgot to
find look for your Satchel like I
forgot uhoh yeah you got to it's a it's
a fetching clear
supplies can I not get in there I'm in
the
floor I'm blind I can't I can't even see
the oh there it is okay a lot screaming
going
On's here
scream oh there is
aine nice good job nice oh no don't
please
fire fire she's on fire fire fire
they're on fire
TR who wanted hand
part okay found need to Cle it's not
clear yet have you guys seen the
basement yeah I think there's a
basement can we use this chain to climb
down or am I going to
die uh
99%
oh where is my
statue down I'm not ready I hear zomes
upstairs upstairs a
basement
a yeah oh this is easy to break oh I
found a oh this
it's outside birs
birs just
boards behind oh coming up not mine
See
Fire be careful to the fire I should use
my arrow yeah no the fire is no joke
okay we cleared it nice
no I I didn't find my
supplies got to be in there somewhere oh
B there's a safe where I am oh where are
you ouch I'm on fire on the second floor
the
office second
floor uhuh I just look oh yeah F have
you read have you read this one yet you
should read this
one oh I have not in the thank you never
encumbered night yeah I read it already
it's so good I'm on fire your
crazy God where's oh there's the sa
[Applause]
okay found it Miss at night Missions at
night the
food oh
I danger where are you I am the basement
color
floor could use more she brownand I'm
Brown she's at the floor floor level I
also need food
please get the Yum and water if you have
water I have I have thank you so
much thank you there's also water
there's better water in the
car car car wait come back come back oh
take some
food ah thank you I really need it
thank you so
caring oh my God why is it
so here there's
water here I have this for you this for
you for
you okay fail this time no more five
thank
you thank you
woohoo
ah yes for you thank you who's learning
electrical traps I'm learning
it doing nerd
stuff I am doing nerd stuff oh I can
make an electric fence
o raid that'd be very helpful what if
dire wolves come during the
raid
fine oh there were there were two there
were two that came during the yesterday
and I killed him just fine easy so
they're killable yeah a
hammer all right where's the next one uh
as Fest one is
nearby let's go to
it I need to do I need to finish the
quest so I can pay weo back which way
that way I got a debt to beu right
now I owe her money I don't like going
people
money don't we on the electric fence
well don't tell the zombies that I want
them to be on the electric fence
wrenching oh there's a tire you say this
this resident's name
Raa which one it is
PTI let me check is everybody
here no one sec I'm on my way I think I
think it
went here everybody nearby I'm going to
start the quest chance
neighbor woo
okay oh
wow there's a lot of stuff going on
there's a lot watch out by the way
[Applause]
easy s oh there's a bird
vter Hing me did you hit me twice no
only once only
once a zombie all it's that thing
there he's dead oh my
God yeah yeah yeah yeah
take care of your
house yes please can I have one here you
go thank you so
much thank
you thank
you everybody should take some bandaids
there's some in the car bandage bandages
help you
oh help you stay
safe don't whack the zombies with this
don't whack them with
it don't whack them with it because then
the light on fire then the light you on
fire hey really that never happened to
me before oh it'll happen really uh oh
oh
yeah oh God there's this green one
there's a shred there's a
hul sorry got a lot of swamp it's sweet
that your head still first go how you us
too is is how you me too
Shrek
boy I mean Shrek is actually nice yeah I
Shrek I'm Shrek he's cool he's
chill wobble wobble W wobble nice belly
physics can I for you too or is it just
me
oh wow he just will not
die it's all right he's rag do now oh
wait no he's
still still alive
oh you got to come to where I
am yes did you see this
picture oh my gosh they're huging pretty
adorable yeah cat's Hing picture a you
think they got away wish this might have
been the best one we we found the best
one yesterday but this might top
it kitty cats got away
safely don't make me think about it
cie
I'm hope Got
Away sure hope they're living the best
zie they good at running away though
oh oh
hello some good I
help
oh no oh Yik oh that's a big one hold
[Music]
up oh man he dead
nope I like the glow in the dark and
that combined powers
did we clear it seems like clear yes we
did complete
[Music]
ladies yeah he should be open now I
still want to like just make sure to
thoroughly loot the house for stuff
still um destroying the bed there's no
quests around here destroy the
Everything Must
Go this is
good oh I the bathroom curtain no suing
kids
though
why don't forget the library yeah is the
library close no it's in the snowy
area oh okay we a quick Traer run get
some money to give to bio there should
be more I never forget you GG for the
for the redirect that was very
sweet
welcome you guys ready for some last day
Raiden
yay I was looking forward to this I hope
we get 10 dire wolves
today oh boy
cursing the big ones we saw that one
time where we died like 20 times oh the
snow possibly yeah yeah yeah okay well
we hopefully we won't get those you're
going to be fine okay I have stuff I
have stuff for you guys
shotgun okay likely to get bears oh God
here you
go and here you go I got armor crafting
kits too oh thank you let's oh and here
you
go yo so much
ammo nice anything
else is following me
okay come over here we'll save you come
to front of house I'm in the tree now
want the hobo stew but where where are
youone else can make me a hobo stew you
need a hobo stew we got some hobo stew I
would love a hobo stew got some hobo
stews if you have a hobo stew what's
what's with your specific interest in
Hobo
St she just really likes them I just
think it's your
do you know what it's made
of you really like telling people that F
huh what don't worry Little Missy I know
what I'm getting into okay
okay okay I got a bunch of cloth yay
that's good we need sucessfully clo
declo this
building wonderful probably make it but
I also want to give some gift duct tape
too oh yes and then this should be I
think I owe be about this much is
oh hold on okay I have not a single spot
in my inventory left let's go to the
trader
um this way my
bike wait do we have another Quest here
oh didow just pick it up I see oh I gu
me
one ooh hey I'm I'm definitely down to
down to
help I have 9 mm ammo okay okay okay I
didn't see like my inventory is such a
mess I can't tell
shotgun oh I just need one more shotgun
part now if I want to get the level you
owe me
1,350 okay 1350 no problem I almost have
that much here I'll give you what I have
right
now I have 93 bucks so I'll drop it on
the ground for you
Duke's Casino token they're using Casino
tokens as money that's silly harly yeah
you think Duke is like the final
boss we ever meet him Duke yeah I was
saying that I think the
Traders here you go as a freebie present
o a freebie oh nice shot 95 shotgun
shells now I have
491 cool it might not even be enough C
it might not even
be the shotgun fire so
slow please please take
these yes uh what is 9
mm what's that for so much I got my 9
[Music]
one9 oh oh no payment needed AP9 is that
is that I give it to you that goes for
like armor and stuff I don't know I
think it's stronger version yeah but
what's 9 mm what's that for B uses it
uhoh oh it's tall okay
okay thank
you well I left some ammo behind you you
make me some of my own
[Laughter]
weapon should I take these and then you
make me some um ammo for my weapon what
what ammo do you need B I have have an
IR and I have a shotgun oh the whole
crew is here at Trader JY oh I just gave
Callie some shotgun ammo so you can
split with Callie maybe put some more
ammo here I have too much thank you
welcome pleas get away from me Cece
please just get oh I just G me stuff
motorcycle parts thank you I I take
these thank you and
I put
yours here oh thank you oh $400 d right
now we always looking for some
adventurous Souls oh I would kiss you
but you know apocalypse and yes for
you for me take those B boo I will be
help good money good money very pretty
can opener you've got there are you
talking about CeCe Callie she is very
pretty Callie take these yeah sure oh
thanks thanks Callie thanks and she
probably can open a ton of Cans really
well yeah anybody needs a a repair kit
good good but we will we will need them
yeah I give okay I'll keep it I'll keep
it there the gun but yeah that's too
okay I
to repay you back here very effective
nobody cares thank
you I appreciate that you don't need to
pay me back though I want to be
nice Band-Aids are for
everybody what is Cil thank you for
looking after us far cilia yeah yeah
that's for you for me yeah this one I'm
here I'm here
oh behind you oh
yeah oh thank you T I love T how did you
know right did she know
my wa okay yeah have for
you
this oh okay is anybody else learning
armor
crafting I've started I think armor
crafting is something generally
everybody kind of wants to learn
I'm maxed out on it so everybody can
take the magazines
down to be for steel Kiara at The
Crucible how what do we need to make it
uh it's just iron uh as well just same
as for forged Iron same as for forged
steel but just more of
it I take these oh thank you but that's
why I keep on wrenching cars and stuff
because they they also give iron and
anything in houses that looks like it's
made out of iron or steel also wrench
that so that you get more more more nice
can never get
enough cool I got to make 3 for steel if
I want level two pump shotgun so yeah
we've been trying to make as much as we
can but it quickly runs out so what what
did you drop that to I don't know I
should close
oh no ST I have some mods you might be
able to use for your Club if you don't
already have
them oh definitely thank you so much I
will take those oh metal spikes metal
chain metal chain I definitely feel like
I can use on the I think I can use it on
the bat it might be a club only thing
though I don't know maybe not how do you
actually write that ah you have to
choose spikes or or um chain it would
seem but thank you though I feel like
maybe if we can make bats for everyone
I'd love to make bats for everybody or
clubs for everybody oh that' be nice
yeah bats and clubs are different yeah
they're de to me they're the same thing
in my brain is a bad you don't have to
think too much about it you just use
your fists
yeah yeah Jan I want to learn how to do
how to make drones but I haven't you
need
electricity or something or electrical
electrical skill I think maybe I've only
going into robotics I've been trying to
do robotics but you for the Drone you
need 76 and I'm only at
16 it's like end game stuff yeah you see
do you want to change club or you coulds
but I'll give it to you here Club I'm
learning Ranger and hunting if anybody
has magazine I think there are some at
home in the book shell oh wait I already
yeah Cron's not in VC today
guys okay okay she's just chill she's
chilling though she's here so are we
staking it out for the final
day um I'm going to be back in one
minute I'll be right back okay
[Music]
okay maybe we can invite crony to the
team I do worry I hope that she maybe
she'll maybe she can like try and get
some of the
EXP from our battles she can come along
with us who's who's uh leader right now
oh we might have to split down cuz we're
six already oh we're already six six
seven yeah in total we we're seven with
crony yeah that's mon I guess oh I tried
to invite her but I think six is
Max oh wait she's doing Never Lie never
Li that's crazy let's do
it nice we take another
Quest I'm like that hot Final Fantasy
mechanic
girl she's so cute that one from from 15
Cy or whatever her name was
Cindy Cindy Cindy
Cindy where are we going F are we going
home or um I don't know I thought we
were doing more quests yeah I think do I
wouldn't mind my inventory is still
completely
full to drop it off at the other
house no
cuz yeah there's a pretty close Quest
over here
storage so are we splitting or are we
going go together
no we're going out together
okay going into the deserted land should
so
this yeah J just going to put up got
check tra today
too see if they have any shotgun
parts I'm back so uh what is it the the
bottom one has shotgun parts
uh no Bob Bob has shotgun parts
and I think snowy guys inventory reset
so you're going to have to check him
again but Bob definitely has okay I will
go find Bob uh toward which Quest are we
going back to the L Quest or a bom I
mean I
found uh there's there's a bunch of
quests near Bob if you want to come by
Bob okay Bob around Bob's area there's
quest for Callie Kiara bio fa yeah there
oh that's a lot oh yeah I do have a
quest there huh okay maybe the closest
one first the one where Callie and wa
have a
quest here to
clear we can do that one really quick
and then we'll go south is crony going
to run
there oh gosh pick up crony on the back
of their bike perhaps uh I need to make
more seed mods and more bikes uh let me
see maybe I can pick her oh she's like
oh she doesn't even have a bicycle I can
give her my bike is she running oh
no I have a bike too you have a seat I
have a seat so I can go pick her up okay
yeah pick her
up people will pick you
up oh I thought B was picking up oh yeah
after B picks her up I will so which
Quest are we doing right
now the one near
Bob oh mine okay C me me out wait did I
go to Quest I went the wrong way you
need to be GPS wait I thought we were
going to Bob I didn't realize we're
going to this
one oh did you guys go south no no we're
not going to that one I want to go
towards it's over oh well we were going
towards Bob but everyone else is going
to the other Quest I see them in the
distance wait where are we going where
do I go who do I the to the where people
is right now
bi boo I think wait are we going to the
one North or to the one towards Bob
which one are we going to where you are
right now bio stop I thought we're going
north where are we
going is or is that not where the quest
are okay we're I guess we're going to
call first and then and then Bob and
then point
today communication issues
it
happens
Time Imagine walkie talkies over over
wait this reminds me of something over
oh here we go again hold I'm not going
the right way am I I know I can't tell
okay that way that
way what's your favorite TV show over TV
show I
think I hate picking but I like The
Walking Dead because that is very syic
right now very topical very nice over I
haven't watched it yet over you should
watch it at least like the first couple
episodes a pretty good over we'll do
over oops I'm sorry I got off the bike I
pushed the wrong button use it I was
doing stunts you like dangerous things
huh moving
[Music]
dangerously okay here we go party time
all right I'm
here yay Cron's learning the wonders of
the
bike uh I can exit the group so crony
can get some XP no everybody's in it's
all right part 2 3 4 5 I can't count
wait how is that possible I don't know
it's crazy wait okay so when you guys
register the quest ready oh people Oh I
thought six was the Mex ah I
thought the following party members are
out of range B can you come closer okay
I'm thring some
things I'll be there in one
[Music]
second she hates
mailboxes when they're empty I hate them
there's a personal Vendetta against them
why is there nothing inside
but IRL I'm scared when there's I I I I
avoid my mailbox actually way too much
and my anxiety like opening the
letters there's no reason for me to be
worried about it I can just pay it but I
just avoid it anyway I don't want to see
like
bills yeah same really shouldn't but
can't be helped bills scare
me can you not do that
sir getting a bit tough
her the freaking hul to get him I got it
the green person beat
you oh that's a strong
guy he reaching into my
guts
hello I'm just looting
kind
of what's this damage oh
oh that was
unexpected why does it take time God
we're coming in full
force people I found a safe can you
lockpick it okay don't go
uh uh can you find me on the map it's
yeah second floor in the closet second
floor I'm on the second
floor find me I'm a king oh what are
those
oh oh yeah we might have to go the other
way know if we find any shotgun parts oh
we got to crouch to get down here
hurt me anyway okay I'm here po yeah in
in here in
here okay good luck thank you
de oh
wow protect the
safe fire fire like the fire oh dear oh
dear oh my God I hear so much violence
behind me are you okay uh yeah I'm okay
they're they're they're they're going to
die soon it's going to be soon so you
can focus on the on lockpicking I got
open it yeah there wasn't very much in
it though oh man get some
money money is always nice dang
it oh oh we did it oh it already nice
right yeah easy I do think if we go
south there will be harder quests which
might be good
yeah hard is always good wait big
hitters who's who's uh big
hitters okay I'm going to than okay one
sec
guys thank you
nice oh yeah close by Quest
thankfully wait I didn't pick my thing I
wonder if we can scavenge these oh she
she come here behind you
uh take
this
[Applause]
[Music]
some that was really scary are you good
I'm okay oh why is she in
here it think I can though thank you so
was this one where we had to like pick
up something
or no this this was just a clear nothing
a clear I love clears cuz they're so
easy not easy but confused simple
straight M okay I got a lot of cloth
nice yeah I got some too cloth for the
cloth God for the duct tape
gods and sewing kids though I need
sewing kids we'll find some maybe at the
next
houseo do you want
bombs a do you want bombs
yes yes thank you take take this too oh
thank you and um take take this
too oh thank you not cuz I in my pocket
or anything
ohly she's so
selfless okay well done what is the next
Quest my nails in this game are kind of
on
girl you know they're
[Music]
[Applause]
painted oh I didn't I never even tried
out the new horn on the
bik hold up wait is does colie still
need a ride no she has a bicycle
now need does anybody have an extra seat
oh Ro uh come come here sit on me I come
hold on
uh get on okay
here oh is it full
y oh nice it's
100% yeah I filled it up okay so we're
going south to Bob now right around to
the quest kiaha you don't have a hat on
let's go baby yeah I gave my nerd hat
to on to
[Music]
me my other armor is strong enough to
handle being hatless wear my preacher
hat if you
want does it smell like you press the
wrong
button I will wear it when we get off of
it all right it's not the drinking hat
is it it is the drinking hat oh I'm
firsty as hell
we have water too though if you need to
borrow it first a different
s are we going to the Traer right now no
oh I think we're going to the the the
the two quests that are on the way to
Bob yeah okay but we could do something
okay I turned in my orig my quest by
accident that's fine
though it's fine I like to knock out a
bunch of them at one time if I can
but I like I like you know hoarding
completed class and then getting them
completed once and you just get
reward feel nice I can't wait to see all
the little
packages outside
and
delivery oh this wasn't the popping
pills and going be fun
isn't this where we dug ourselves a big
hole before oh yeah isn't it yeah that
traumatizing it never ended thank you
for I probably should have got it was
nice
hello
g g what's
up you can you join the party I gave you
an invite is it
possible uh
M yes yay wow
no I think the difference is that the UI
just it just I don't know you guys'
colors are kind of like I don't know
hard to see but that's
it okay I'm satisfied with one car oh
this is a Mor Quest nice so I got to be
the one to start this
one wait almost there okay
wait do I have the same Quest deck or oh
oh yeah
probably yeah you both have the same
Quest
nice will we be making our old house
very strong is that the goal yes it's
already strong I will head on over and
keep
digging the mission is that okay it's
okay I love
digging that was good good oh cron is
going to get a lot of money too I hope
ow what a
welcome Get Him Father get
him you can
pay in here be careful behind
you they should let us use shopping
carts as like motorbikes and then we
just each other oh sewing
kidso yikes
yikes where'd you find the sewing kit uh
in the on top of a shelf I'm looting
here I'm looting
everything look I've shot a single
zombie oh another SW kid I found shotgun
parts oh you did
I need thank you Kiara oh don't thank me
I'm just finding things well thank you
for telling had
those no problem we're all sharing and
caring of course I will end for free
funny this gives me
[Music]
R oh wait there's supplies oh yeah yeah
yeah I found steroids oh great
nice those are nice you can carry
anything that you want for a while Mega
Crush yeah pump yourself
up I'm getting very
heavy
no for these bullet cases I can't get it
yet don't worry okay I'm just going to
throw off oh we have to find supplies
I'm see I forgot they were on there so
much loot in here though I know
yeah so worth
it I need to find my watch
reverse is a
piano so
beautiful
yes is that also Cima yeah they're
communicating
wow I feel like you actually know how to
play it no no
no I
doing I have for you a few things you do
behind you thank you oh y big hitters my
favorite bag wait do you like shotguns
need to go down some yeah I'm a shotgun
user there's that too I'm over cucumber
I wonder if I've read this before Oh Oh
It's one of
these thank you
have you girls already found a way down
show them your base SK shut down is
they're down I need to go
up oh yeah mine's down
oh watch
out you shot no you didn't there another
one another
one out they get in there oh this way
yeah open up the door com in
classic what's down here oh oh somebody
stuff there think my stuff was still
downstairs maybe mine is upstairs but
where is
upstairs
roof how do I get to the
roof jump a meth
lab that's crazy wowow good job where's
Mr White where is he
Jesse we have to call does this lead to
some secret boar again or so really I
want to fight a boar just a weird
lab oh my Satchel is
here
what I have have you read
bar brawling five no that's what I need
that's what I need the most five I'm on
the
roof the last one I need I can play
Block B hold up on the last day you
become the strongest oh my
goodness oh thank you I
need there's some there's some FKS
[Music]
upstairs oh it was thank youcome
believe I need
up
my I put myself in a bad situation ouch
it kind of hurts upstairs I might
die I thought you were so Invincible I
believe in you you can get brus you got
this yay fin take it take it here you go
thank you I'm so excited thank you so
[Music]
much oh my
goodness
uh well the area isn't clear
yet no oh I
wonder I get hit point recovery for
every punch now does anybody have lock
PS by the way no did you find another
save yeah there's no there's a reinforc
chest here so we can just Bonk it I
suppose very very over incumbered can I
give you some of the like stuff like the
sewing kits and stuff uh yeah the sewing
kit yeah I I have no space in my
inventory but the sewing kit already
takes up a space so I can take out okay
okay I'm trying to run up after you but
I'm very
slow I'll come to you I'll try I think
you're there hello okay uh so what you
got here glue do you have a glue stack
oh no I'm I didn't mean
to or iron I iron yeah iron I can take
iron iron iron maybe on the roof I bet
the zombies are on the roof there's only
one I got it you got it okay we I do
have a glue stack oh you do okay here
you go cloth do you have a Glo cloth
okay
oh I reached my limit Quest
here K has the same Quest here so we can
read that one I can't take okay
okay yeah wait this
one take take a fish thank you I'm
almost
mad I can't get out of here who did this
this is how nerds things using our our
brain
muscles if something's not opening just
hit it over and over again yeah that's
called using your
noodle there you go strongest ner you've
ever
seen wait that's what called using your
noodle yeah your brain friend oh yeah
your noodle my brain
noodles
here oops I'm out of commission I don't
have any stone I can hit with my though
oh I have stone wait do I have stone a
lot of stone I have one stone I
wonder like
500 oh
dang thanks okay nice it's bad oh what
is
where is everybody on what floor are you
shot shells a
quest yeah I'm also at my quest limit
didn't know that was a thing
oh oh I don't know if I've reached mine
yet this is by the way B Knife Guy oh
thank you I needed I think I can make
machete now maybe oh nice
O Let's freaking go does anybody have
Howes there are antibiotics or honey I
honey also have honey in the bike I
think yeah there's hone Traders also
sell higher level
antibiotics the bike oh I have oh no I
have vitamins never
mind I only have .9% infection
so that's pretty low until it gets worse
yeah
should be fine just a little zombism as
a
tree yeah teen tiny bit do you that this
is lo her hair looks
funny I'm trapped
inside yeah I love fauna's
armor she looks so scary scary like a
Golem that punches people
for
sure I'm finally out I've been I feel
like I've been stuck in this building
for just couldn't find my way out ready
to go back
in oh no oh we're going back in again
okay um oh yeah I'm dropping some things
on the floor please take when it applies
to you dropping big hitters on the floor
dropping cooking magazines on the
floor what was it the parts to a yeah
dropping shotgun parts on the floor I
learned to make fish
tacos who wants tacos for day you can
make fish
tacos Tac
Tuesday yumy I'm dropping can they wait
it's literally Tuesday yeah maybe not
where' you get the fish from I don't I
don't know can e fish at all if you find
caned
salmon hey who needs shotgun parts there
we go I do thank you okay welcome now
where's Big hitters somebody oh nice
okay oh just kidding it's not so we
going back to the tra and then we go oh
I think we're doing this one more time
oh okay okay activ it I have a quest
liit what does it
mean probably can't do this question oh
I guess I have Quest limit too can we
still do the quest of limit voice let me
try three two one uh the following party
members are of range oh that's
fine okay we apparently we still can do
the quest if there's a limit it says not
available until uh 20 minutes later 20
iname minutes too bad usually it's way
worst mhm so is that 20 seconds no
that's 20 okay so the class is basically
you won't get progress for the like the
next Trader unlock but you still get the
oh that's from Kiara that's from crony
wait Kiara sorry this is from crony I
stole it cuz it was on the ground and I
got scared
oh two Springs and 34 steel this this
this glue duct tape did you want
arrows I think you're using bow right
yeah yeah I'm using the oh thank you so
much that's very helpful let me know if
you guys find Springs by the way I need
Springs Springs I think we have I have
Springs how many you need have gi for
you how many two
here thank you thank you everyone's so
beautiful in this thank you thank you
for the two
Springs and now I need is 34 steel so
we're just going to have to make it at
the 4 the quest now yeah okay it one
more time with full inventories and this
Quest feels kind of wasteful if we have
full inventory then we can take
everything I can take some more things
you can remember you have a mini bike
store mini bike has a lot of stor yeah I
know it's
already
full maybe I find more sewing kid give
the head this dude's very strong
all I found steel Club
cards o I might need those
actually I don't think I'll get the club
that high level this this go
around I found handgun Parts people oh
yay thank you this is a great place yeah
this has everything it's like it's oh
it's a store
right it's like a store
oh this time we have to find supplies
did we have to find supplies before I
don't even remember I think so oh
okay shortterm
memory glue chenging for
now y'all this is so good there's a
bunch of glue
here by the way a good idea will be like
give the same um items to one person
because there's
but that needs us to be organized and
look at us you want I can handle the
stones no sorry the the clo
fragment okay and uh stone wood and
everything like if you want I'll Dr them
oh I actually put most of them in my car
in my mini bike part nice oh I'm
starving oh
somebody we can organize better when we
do question so we can optimize the space
yeah you're
starving at a time like this Y in this
economy way exactly in this
economy that's why I am
starving
CL
lag this seems useful right
now I also am a bit hungry not going to
lie FR there's still food in the in the
bike I have one hobo stew left oh there
is there is for sure I saw that's the
end of the quest we just had to retrieve
the supplies mhm oh okay I fell into the
hole oh
yes can you uh get out okay yeah K came
and is helping me what a legend okay I
got this Sur I I totally came for you
yeah I know you were you had like 0.2
seconds um reaction time there there's a
locker that needs Bing appreciate it in
the
roof oh I have one lockpick uh let me
see if I
can you could just Bonk it though oh I
could use a lock pick yes M what kind of
things do you have in your
inventory uh I have polymer
cement uh Rotting Flesh um um Nails
Le
iron uh cloth fragment
brass Clay Wood I to get to
VI behind you behind
you
oh oh okay the tow there was a reason
why I asked you those questions thank
you I thought you were in front of me
for some reason okay okay
whoa your gun is
[Music]
loud but so functional a big
personality yes I don't see the Satchel
icon on my map I think if you're at your
quest limit there is none oh oh okay oh
I was at my quest limit and I have it oh
no no wait use I'm going to
die no I'll protect you made a mistake
ow
dang
it I made a mistake now I have to go I
thought all the zombies were
gone it's okay we're we're learn we live
and we learn and we die and we learn I'm
lost holding the bag trying to fight for
my life I'm just going to climb to bi
Boo from the
outside oh God more trouble than it's
worth down the
hole Yeah I'm glitched I can't see what
like the distance from
my
supplies I feel like it's due to the
quest limit but I don't know wa let me
let me
Focus down no on this
level
see
okay okay
the run back is
crazy did anybody have their Satchel
before on the the main the the the basic
the zero level if yes where was it cuz I
think they repeat location
shoot
oh in the oh mine was in the basement
last time maybe I'll check if it was in
the basement now we still have to find
it without the
GPS oh gosh all right I'm going to go on
the roof
roof I should just follow why do I never
think mcraft just
falling that way that Way's an that way
but of course there
is are you kidding I don't know where
mine is either oh there's one
here for anyone if maybe it's here
K some one right there no not
mine okay don't know where mine is
either but it is on this level hey bab
what I got a lockpick for you oh okay
I'm coming back upstairs where's the
roof I'm lost the roof use Minecraft
block oh the roof the roof is on the
main the main hall you just have to jump
on the you just have to jump on the like
a I got stop in the meantime the what
does exclamation point crossed out mean
it means you reach your daily limit but
that's okay you can still get the
rewards gota that's what it me it just
doesn't progress the uh apparently tier
up Traer thing I'm oh I think according
to the voices in my head but maybe I got
one guide you never know all right
here's one lock sry your check right
now feeding you wrong information it's
me what did I just
destroy I can't find it it's
over I is broken okay time to smack it
all right well at the end of the day it
always goes back to
bonking well it's definitely time to
drop off some things at home and clo
after all they're
clo oh yeah then maybe home oh yeah
they're totally closed
now should we just leave without finding
this I think this is impossible without
like the radar it feels impossible
it could be everywhere um I found one
where I am right now if you want to
check that one there's one in the
garbage shoot that I found there there's
one in the behind the next to the
hole always goes back to Bonk Bonk ain't
that right
chat love
boning punching can solve anything oh
yeah do have any stone Callie me oh did
your did your just break no I don't
there was some down in the shelves but I
didn't take it okay have fun
boning I don't know if it's worth it I
the supplies I don't know if I'll do my
best it's fine I think it's worth it
there there's there's quite a bit of
stuff in those chests W yeah
wa my game laggy there's a satchel over
here where is over here I am uh in the
corner of the pharmacy
room oh bed there
stuff oh my God I'm going insane I
I I see it but I can't you can't touch
it are you in the garbage
shoot no it's
like like I tried from every
angle just can't get to it it's it's
elusive hates me can you break some
walls with your
axe uh that would take like 30
minutes true could have five 5,000
Health oh it's night time now I can
carry stuff again oh
yeah longer encumbered I love night time
yeah no longer encumbered at night time
it's so
[Music]
good what it's a it's a perk from a book
you have to learn it but it's so nice
wait what what perk again it's one of
the
nightstalker magazines it lets you not
be encumbered when at night time oh ni
how do I even get
out oh okay this is this this is mine uh
B did you check the one at the hole the
hole where's the hole okay come with
me I was just where you were
actually strength shotguns for oh STR on
eternity later actually don't come with
me I have no idea where the hle
is uh you know the hole on the floor the
that that leads us downstairs
yeah are you also still in there yeah
I'm on the roof over here still looking
for the
I don't know if I'm going to find it
though do you not even know if it's up
or down but I think it would be here and
it's not showing you the meters either
no yeah it doesn't show for me
either did you check in the underground
cuz mine was previously hidden quite
well in the underground oh like on a
shelf on top of one but it's okay I
don't need to finish the quest yeah it's
okay I feel like it's going to take too
long we could just go home okay if it's
if it's here though how do you get off
the dang
roof um well we got to get up here
lad just
jump I found nine sewing kits for you
Kiara oh wow this has been so lucrative
oh my I opened it up and Magnum rounds
for B boo
yay I'm very cucumber though okay I'm
going to make you a letter
stairs
go once we get home can you guys anybody
who has glue and Claw fragments and
sewing kits and duct tape and armor
parts all of those into the forge chest
please and I'll get cooking thank you
you're welcome okay there was one
here make it home no thank you it's okay
we could just go home okay let's go
here's your Magnum get out of
here oh I'll the house I'll give them to
you there yeah I'm going to go there too
now time to bring all this
Lo okay oh people my
GPS
GPS I'll go the right way for sure I can
make it I have hand remember resarch
some duct tape for parts I'll meet you
outside G cat me outside how about
I'm making a moat and a zombie just came
down here but there's no spikes down
here
yet make sure to only make one row of
spikes down there so we can pick up the
loot yep otherwise so much loot
despawned last time okay you go oh this
one thank you
yay get him in trenches
yeah dire wolves can jump though and
there are jumpy ones so we got to
prepare for them
too since the right wait
maybe if I go to the
right I hope I can meet the snow Trader
today wonder how many Traders there are
maybe like let me let me put a marker
there and then maybe I can share the way
point with you de that would be cool if
possible how do I share a way point you
might not be able to it might be
impossible
somebody who has been investing in
shotgun
crafting
things yeah can you make one for crony
cuz she been she has been investing a
little bit into strength and she wants a
range weapon doesn't have to the best
shotgun just anyone you know I can make
one similar to the one I'm using right
now okay it's still pretty
good
awesome so many shotgun
users oh F figured it out yesterday you
can share way points that's all yeah I
put a wayo down I don't know how to
share it but I put the Waypoint down for
the snow Trader guy let me see if I can
find it hello to share way points you go
to your map and you click on the way
point and then you click on the the icon
there a bunch of people standing next to
each other which says share
Waypoint oh smart fun with the
strats comes back shares knowledge
doesn't explain okay I think I it
doesn't elaborate I mean shared marker
books with
you oh we're in the tunnels yeah I know
it's our garage I parked it in the
garage oh good nice
won't get bird poop on
it yeah that's never
fun hard to clean off the
windshield
okay what a lovely home
here I love my
home it's a solid home it's home homey
yeah oh God I'm the tunnels
too
hey welcome to the tunnels the heck no
thank
you Dum my loot cozy in here I got some
things you will like I got to make more
forg
steel
sick steel Club parts that's big I'm
going to need those later I'll put them
in
here oh I just need three more handgun
parts and I can make an
[Music]
SMG I'm going take uh some of this
forged steel if you guys don't mind may
I take 30 forged
steel okay thank you I'll make it up to
you guys I'll keep cooking more
steel hold on that is hard for me
there we
go nice 10 hobos I believe
you oh what what do you think they made
what do you think
that what are the nutritional facts of
that hobo St can you curious I'm I'm
very particular about my diet could you
like tell me exactly is it ethically
it's very nutritionally balanced oh okay
yes no
questions only answers thank
you what's this Advanced muffled
connectors yay I'm home
[Music]
yayas tape
oh G did you see the wonderful interior
design vaguely did you do something new
to
it
yeah I guess I didn't look hard enough
what did you
add so many it has we have wooden wooden
walls now very pretty why would you do
that cuz I wanted it to be Cottage core
don't at me Cottage Bo oh why you such a
hate we are out here working the entire
day we come home with for yeah I'm
working very hard too in the mines where
where where I don't see it I don't I
don't see anything we're not staying at
that home oh I have to be so far away
from my family to work at the I'm here
okay okay um back we never see him
nowadays make her such a better one if I
have a few more shotgun parts
you were here then how you say messed up
sorry I just like feeling like I'm there
because I miss
everyone a a that's sweet we miss you
too you should come into this hole with
me I'm good okay don't
worry okay interested in that oh there's
arrows my chest if you want some oh
thank you I get it did everybody drop
off their glue and stuff and clo and I
put it in the next to the forge Kiara
Forge chest yeah okay thank you anybody
have wood oh never mind I I've always
got wood I
do never mind night why so laggy
here
submit I will drop off what I have thank
you the garage I got four glue that's
got to be worth
something glue
that is worth
something
yeah all right I'm going to try and find
I have machine gun parts I don't know if
you use that if someone uses
that uh I do I don't know if I still
need some but yeah oh actually I might
need it okay I'll bring it to you might
actually my crafting table machine gun
here behind
you um
if you if you get a new weapon can I
have your hand me down yeah okay nice oh
okay if you're going to take kar's hand
me down then I'll give my hand me down
to crony yeah that
okay yeah I'm fine with either cool
where's the cron just want to shoot does
anyone need steel Club Parts steel uh
I'm going to need them I think so
probably put them in the box I'll put
them in the
box which box
what
SEC yo okay I'm going to start cooking
soon I'm already cooking constantly is
the door locked yeah what is a door
locked crap crap crap more
more I feel like even this will not be
mod that's crazy oh someone's making a
rifle in here what is
this somebody cooking a gun a
rifle yummy what what kind of rifle is
that it's a shotgun it's a pump action
shotgun
who SL
crafting oh
enemies okay screamer in the house oh
that's no good I want to shoot her but I
don't want to shoot you girls good job
how' she get in here what was that I may
have left the door
open so okay we're welcoming visitors
generally uh when is the coming day 351
p.m. 3510 p.m. okay a lot of time then
the lights really turned off all right
uh cron here's some
ammo hold up it's going to take a while
hold on I can make
more is the other one used can get you
more that should help I have
plenty I don't know why I separated it
like that that was
weird good that we have two workbenches
all right new gun needs about four
minutes to
cook so excited is that the best one you
can make or so no uh there's one level
higher I believe M where is the food
chest I have three points there any
where it is it's in the
middle
fire I think by the Yeah the fire
oh natural healing might be good
but Olympic champion actually I don't
think I want this club after
all
Club crony he a
club I'm crafting
PS uh where did it go uhoh where the
heck did it go I just need one more
Point Olympic champion does anyone still
have armor crafting parts
let's see I want not on me
currently maybe we can search the
Traders tomorrow see if we can find some
yeah she should have to look for more
shotgun parts see if I can make the
twins a strong shotgun
too so I'll look around tomorrow
oh actually it's about to be the next
day
convenient
it what level are your feet and
hands probably not so good yeah I think
yeah I want them to run around with a
shotgun it could be
hilarious I am worried about getting
shot by those
too gra armor for oh
okay
four should go shoes too the Springs
need to be in here your
sandals let
don't let her
cook just a bit longer
also I also have primitive armor by the
way my Ranger stuff died it's gone it's
done
for okay um if I can I want to make
better stuff do I really get armor parts
from these things too chat even Lev I
think I need a kit repair
kit a ranger
outfit I need I'll find out level one is
really unnecessary I'm just going to get
rid of do
I mean yeah the rate is day 35
yes I wonder if the pig
respawned you want to go fight him I'm
going to go fight him
cool go punch him fist him fist him real
good I will
yeah
leave to fist the pig we really have
enough meat though what we need is
I'll get grass from that
stuff I need food so I'm going to take
some oh we need a more Balan diet yeah I
don't know how to get
seeds
seeds there's so many zombies at our old
house uhoh I'm not equipped to to
protect myself the boats I'm
trying into the boates this r
o fall fall into the
M yeah shouldn't they be hitting those
spikes though we have a lot of broken
spikes haven't haven't repaired
yet I
see scrap scrap I can make cornbread
too scrap scrap scrap it
on I'm scrapping the whole armor chest
pretty much because all of those armor
parts are low level and they and they
give me armor parts back when I scrap
them yeah I think that's better use for
now no
Pig no Pig p stickier [\h__\h] Pig had
that he's done with you yeah I guess so
he's had it this will just give me grass
I guess wonder if we can make stronger
tools as
well my pump shotgun
done yippe y have fun with it I'm
excited oh three mods I can load three
mods into it
nice see what we
got someone more worth repairing and
selling
scrapping but not these
right it's good to clean up I think and
then I'll just make everyone The Meta
combination that I
have
cuz they probably don't know what they
want either long
barel use S key ni it's
okay stick
I think that's
it
okay need to read this one
though okay let's start
with tell me please what up the what
armor parts you have currently I mean
what what's your armor on what level my
armor is pretty random right now I have
an Assassin outfit level three mhm I
have preacher gloves level tree and I
have Commando boots level treat
mhm and the nerd cockles level two Lev
two okay maybe a hat for you is most
important right now I
think if I could get uh something like a
ranger outfit would be nice if you want
Ranger outfit okay I think I think it's
better for me I'm not sure because I
used the bow
I don't know I'm not an expert hey Kiara
make me something cool too please I'll
be you back I just need more armor P
we'll see how far we get with this well
I'm a part you can you can take care of
my first because I am more like a
support no no no no no you you need
armor more than I do trust me and that's
not that I'm not trying to be mean but
Calli what uh then tell me what are what
are your pun what's what's your stuff
right now what level uh I'm I'm using
primitive because the Ranger stuff that
I had broke oh no oh what level there
there's a lot of armor in the armor
thing oh
yeah no I took it all and I scrached oh
because it's all useless it was all like
level one and they give me Alor Parts
which I can make to make more armor
crafting kits uh is there specific set
those
are some tank Ranger's fine too I think
ranger set
yeah are you sure I wonder what would be
good for shotgun what do you guys
think I'll let you
know okay I'll let you know
biker biker that'd be pretty cool ask oh
I have I put a biker armor in the armor
chest ooh biker so if you want a biker
outfit there's one in
there yeah I mean I fit the bill I've
got a spiked bat and a shot but it's
just level one I better make you a
better biker outfit and scrap this one
yeah I want to be a biker bad the
Bon head to the bo thank
you okay I don't think I can make you a
max level one but maybe four or five
level good it's perfectly fine uh sick
wheelie sure I am a biker
can't wait to make a
motorcycle what oh mini bike is mini
bike not good enough for you
no I'm excited about your motorcycle
possibilities too yeah I can already
make one but I feel like it's kind of a
waste of my resources right now
understandable we need more resources
maybe in season two everybody will be on
bikes and
cars biker
gation
yay yay let's go okay let's start with
Callie's
setup
um uh I'm getting boot just in case we
need extra
food never have enough food we have
work
[Music]
uhoh I can't make stuff don't have le
the wheelies
not Ranger outfits or handguns and
rifles AKA Sheriff type handguns and
rifles
mind um
lever what's best source of
lever BS and
stuff pigs I wonder oh I can probably
the little ones might have
respawned
M you be scrapping couches
too so far leather couches give weather
the Harrison nearby have fancy leather
couches you can scrap yeah our neighbors
are not using their couch anymore
yeah uh K how many
um um vehicle Adventures do you need uh
another 2
23 okay I'll buy this one no not yeah
everyone counts every single one you
really wants to kill those BS oh armor
armor parts we need that right then I'll
buy that M armor part is he selling
lever too three four leather let me
check you know I I'm going to the tra as
well let's see what I can
find I need more handgun part
I do see sewing kit do you want me to
buy that too yeah yeah the more
marer I can go to that be happy in my
backpack okay let me get them oh Springs
did you need Springs s oh Springs are
always good we have a lot of home though
we have a ton of Springs oh we have a
ton okay and shotgun parts did you need
that
still what was that shotgun parts yeah I
was about to buy I'm right behind you oh
oh you take it then that was
oh let me just buy this and then put
them somewhere you can never get them I
still owe viu 400
bucks
or need two
more you're at the old house right now
yeah can you check if there's any
leather
anywhere okay thank
you oh
I already know how to I already have a
metal chain
mean could still learn it
though shouldn't have brought so much
stuff there's a can of salmon in here
for the I can make fish tacos fish tacos
nice love
T there is one
leather oh well let's take
it Crucible is so expensive oh my gosh
it though we already got it y yeah
zombies is a mini horde by the way
outside mini
horde oh
yike I can probably get how much more
can I get oh maybe not that that
much want you stupid
me mini for outside the
[Applause]
house might need some
help I'm now away I got to meet
tra to do that Quest if I'm able to do
it I have they're breaking our doors
though oh I'm calling oh that's
bad our po
door La yes how much money do you
have uh
1,500 can you um buy the vehicle
magazine that he has yes of
course we're so close getting a car I
have one vehicle magazine what
if people goes to a bank and lock we can
get 10 to
15K
oh I need Lo pixel cuz I'm like totally
out of I'll see if some Traders are
selling them welome but I've never seen
an ATM in this game
before I've seen sometimes in the
grocery stores I think so I
think I've seen some
[Music]
Bank nice I still have 10,000 on
me money right now no need any more UPS
here this
way okay I think hord is
over okay how successfully
defended wow when we all go
[Music]
away thank
you we going to raid this shamway
building maybe that's the final mission
that we
do the Sham way Factory yeah it's really
high level huh yeah it's impossible
which is why it would be a perfect FAL
mission for the season probably lots of
food in there oh yeah all the yum
yums I mean we can try if you want to
have know what it's made out of you just
feel like they're just churning zombies
through a wood chipper in
there I hope not I got to know the
answer to
mystery I need to go to the second
Trader oh my God so far
away yeah they do be spread far apart
you mean Trader J yeah oh come with me I
can pick you up on my bike okay uh
you're still at wrecked I'll come over
to
you yes I'm the wrecked feet you'll get
a taste of this mini bike
w Wait am I going the right way no
probably
not it matter how come I still don't
know the
directions It's Kind difficult I always
use the checkpoints because I get lost
all the
times do we have is
cool Jen also has shotgun a little bit
oh she does hell yeah yeah two Pi up I
need some money though I'll grab them to
thank you for letting me know I'll go
grab I can buy them I have I have quite
a bit of money really now I owe now I
owe you money and bi boo money there you
are yeah get on baby let's go all
right okay oh hit the house first oh can
you get on I'm
trying it says repair or
honk oh okay unlock it for you then to
the there you go now you can get in I
think are are I think are we using cloth
as fuel on purpose are we who where some
someone some put cloth in the fuel so
I'm taking it
out o our precious
resource burn that save the
clo it's okay cloth isn't my most needed
resource right now
but before you know it we will run out
of
it oh Jen just said thank you so much so
kindly we should protect her she so nice
she's nice boobs Honestly though I I the
Traders have so much space like such a
big
base it's
insane see should give us that base we
should take it over actually yeah it and
we should like yeah I mean we like
there's so many of us there just one
traiter in each of those we can you
think tried to do that
before yeah yeah are they
Invincible yes they are you cannot kill
it should it would be really fun like if
they allowed that but it's really really
difficult what if she has like insane
defense kill all the Traders and it's
over yeah what if you kill one Trader
and then the other Traders are like I I
won't sell to you anymore and then you
have to do a long line of quests to
explain there was a mistake and that you
were overtaken by G was a mistake though
was it actually no but they don't have
to know that they don't have to
know no it was not a
mistake of course not we shouldn't kill
J though we should kill the guy with a
MCH with the car parts then we can have
a car
wonder how how we can make lockpicks I
wonder if there's a
way probably is a
way cuz then we can if somebody could
make a ton then be go rob a bank and it
would be
sick I'm I'm uh I'm trying to put more
skill points into the loot
stuff so every time I get like a per
percentage more
oh you can do it
K I see this trle
yeah your Uber is doing her best let me
see please give me good rating I give I
give you the best the best rate I would
hope
so uh yeah you have to have want to see
you rate rate me on your phone before
you leave the car
show now I feel treated
though so I'm not going to do that
anymore well then I
shall I shall crash you into this
mountain ah my bike is too
good don't do
it I hope you feel sick I hope you bom
it from
Dad I will lock people I aimless what
are you doing hello I'm going to the
traitors oh okay thank you for the ride
though very kindly you're welcome duct
tap still good manner I heard
that
beautiful
glue glue maybe
coold might be useful
[Music]
B what what why did you want
coal oh I wanted to make some good water
but I found it but don't don't use coal
don't use coal or cloth for fuel by the
way cuz I found in there do you have a
good use for coal um I coal is for the
good water that I was making in bulk and
I think you make you can help me make
bullets I think it's one of the
wants like gunpowder or something like
that I'm not sure okay cuz I got gun I'm
making but yeah don't use it as
fuel got you
[Music]
understood
do perhaps
uh Le no of course
no duct tape no glue no wow have you got
anything for me
lady no NOP no no no I really got
nothing
much have two lock picks so far yeah I
don't know how to craft them I want rob
a
bank would be cool yeah if only were
that
simple where's my other Quest supposed
to go
to
uh I
guess have I not seen Bob yet thought I
did together yesterday the only one you
haven't met is
[Music]
hug go
there is there a place you want to go to
next otherwise I'm going to Bob yeah I
come to you okay okay I'm putting two
vehicle adventures and a shotgun Messiah
into the heck yeah books box that be
taking a
shot and then shotgun parts as
well go does anybody I put them before
you on the floor thank you what what are
you going to do next somebody else oh
I'm very I'm feeling a little bit
aimless right now I just went and got I
got got a bunch of seing kid and glue do
you want to try to gather leather okay
by killing animals animals I guess and
then you need to use like I think the
bone knife do you have a bone knife no
but I saw some in the chest okay I think
that's you have to use it and then you
got to maybe find leather couches and
stuff but I think just going for Animals
is faster okay and better okay I can do
that realized I have absolutely no lever
and without lever I can't make good
armor let me see
crony there is a lot cookies I'll do
that thank you that would be
helpful perfect yeah animals faster
right they do give quite a bit maybe try
close by to our new house there's the
the bores
and bores and corn place oh right yeah
there's a lot of bores in there oh what
was that again K there's 77 leather in
this crate oh okay but that's still
probably not quite enough a bit more
would be good right F can you mark where
the the your favorite places the the
bors the B it's literally just north of
the new house you'll see it yeah it has
a big farm okay I see it if you scrap
office chairs also you can get
leather okay okay sorry but your office
chair has got to go oh no good very good
very good chair
real and then I'm
putting AR I'm going to the neut trator
oh cool
arm I want to meet him too go business
building for office chairs I'm putting
armor pots into the armor chest okay
thank seven and glue and okay okay
noise too bad can't makees why would we
be able to make that
huh leather out of a good ide yeah
that's not a bad idea you can make
leather out of humans I probably human
leather that is
true
huh it's technically a thing huh cool
this is so
chill gross I'm going to turn on the
radio driving through the radio
show are you back in the tunnel CeCe no
I'm I'm we people fell earlier the
moat he's going to get a lot of lawsuits
from all the holes she's digging where
we're dying falling
into I didn't put any spikes in that one
so it's okay it's not so bad
yeah could be worse yes could be spikes
in make sure that you
sp stay there do bears have leather do
you think I think so yeah probably just
got to use the bone knife oh my gosh
this place is dangerous there Bob for
talk to
me what's wrong with you is there
lag
yeah M oh yeah oh god oh oh
no oh my God I just melted into the
floor as everyone does when there's a
bit of
lag
interesting I got so much glue for
you really yeah I I don't for got a lot
but o oh motorcyle
Parts than nothing
should I got motorcycle parts bundle
yeah why
not oh B you're here hello
up how are you doing a he gave me
vehicle Adventures
T I'm shopping a bear look I already had
these things anyway
God bears are so scary well if scary why
hug
shap no that's it's just not true if
evil why friend
she why did they ever make teddy bears
bears have always been frightening ter
terrifying
creatures of Destruction they have
always been so cute looking and you want
to hug them yeah I want to hug them
you aren't you very durable hug them was
this a baby bear or
[Music]
something I think I
one oh did you did you find you killed
the baby let's try another bear I don't
know was it a baby it did seem a little
small oh these must be small Bears right
I know it was a
child you killed child killed the child
child
Bears you killed two child Bears them
kill more kill more isn't there a bigger
bear oh you're killing their there's no
way that's the same bear I fought
before he do the B not respawn there's
no bores here guys yeah maybe they
don't I is there something specific you
want to do cuz I'm probably going to
just go back home
I'm sorry puppy
dog you a dog I need we need the Le
right my quest nearby oh my
goodness okay it's a South South East
Southwest yeah yeah yeah can't anything
but I'm
looking this tra we
are days away right now yeah you are
you change your opinion quickly about
me
Chang you B I saw you going
down back
upun
part try harder G why are you trying to
steal her from me what's going on huh
why does no one like
digging it's really fulfilling you have
KY while you're at it maybe make some
like Towers like platforms for shooting
in every
direction you think I can do it um I
think Place uh yes it's around this way
okay I feel bad every
time for killing the the animal
yeah W okay I can it's okay they they
had a really bad life they didn't like
their mom bear they were like oh man she
never lets me play my video
game B killed the mom bear
yesterday that's why they had a bad
life messed up do you guys have an idea
where there might be a different Farm
does anyone know have one on the map you
think I'll die what if I just lead them
all out there's spars in the Tundra do
you can
find oh okay was this the
prison planning to die huh
well might as well give it a shot right
yay so satisfying every time where could
there be leather oh this is also a
satchel class by the way oh okay okay
keep my eyes open and peeled we'll do it
the coward's way oh
oh that's a lot of hissing oh
hello M I'm already so full again what's
going on o weapon shops are
good
really all of these shops seem actually
really this is kind of awesome wow I can
make my SMG now y
good okay we're going to the tundra and
going to try to kill some beers
do they give have you tried yeah they do
okay okay I don't know how much they
give I have 29 right now that doesn't
seem that
much I feel like sofas might give more
leather than bear a what if we find what
if find like office
building yeah leather SAS tons of
shotgun
range yeah we were looking for leather
for k
[Music]
nice I'm the only one in here so it's
fine to be a coward
ooh oh no it's a kitty I can't fight the
kitty I
found is it a big cat let's
go H where's the rest of the place I'm
alone so where's the rest of the place
okay for cowardice maybe some we
downstairs again where's the rest of the
bad
guys
rules oh yeah there's some people
here boy we killed a bunny success I
hope a bunny has leather I'm not
sure right watch out behind
you Easy
[Music]
E more
trash and need to find my my bag yeah me
too my distance just casually solo
leveling don't worry about me oh this
place is way bigger than I thought oh
there's a lot watch out there's the rest
of the place oh you over
there oh
no
Blockbuster need some head shots
what are these called again I heard
about these ones maybe we
leave reload reload oh he woke up
again yay
yay this feels like the W
baby door combat's my favorite combat
oh my God oh my God be
careful I should have reloaded at that
time at least there's no vomit zombies
oh my God oh my God how many lives do
these have yeah it's very strong they
keep on getting back up
again Phoenix like qualities
there's something in
here
hello only 1 minute for it will not die
no nice nice
nice let's go maybe I'm the gun
yeah this place is Big I'll loot it at
the end they're
sing Oh military chest ooh hunting knife
that's better KN in
[Music]
way interesting was someone making a
machete I you made one okay so you don't
well I'll go keep the parts just in case
you want to upgrade it
[Applause]
do F I can't believe I got out of that
oh oh I think I found a better wrench
for
you for me yeah it's a ratchet I think
it's like the
next how here
[Music]
over
there
what what's going on Callie there's a
bear trying to this the biggest bear
I've seen in my life trying to enter the
shot range and he can't get through the
door
[\h__\h] stay safe Kelly I can kill him kill
it kill it yeah there's a lot of Le
right there that's probably the grandpa
of of the Bears that oh you already did
probably the grandpa of the Bears fun
has been killing
when family has been wiped
out this gun is insane let me see if I
can make one of these for Fu Moko that
help yay behind you behind
you what weapons are fuok using shotguns
I believe oh
okay shotgun
I I'm he wasn't a part of the mission
though he just heard the commotion
ouch ouch ouch ouch maybe all the
enemies are dead now no they're
still a
guy I got a okay now it's
over y now we need to find our loot
Satchel did you guys find find I haven't
got my Satchel yet oh Kiara here take
this it might be it's probably better I
also have something for you I think how
about all the this oh thank
you cuz it says 9 mm I'm guessing that's
good for you here take this
tool
oh oh ratchet coming
back does it work the same
way there must be a place I have
I have too much stuff so yeah I wasn't I
wasn't going to be cresting anyway but
yeah I'll be driving back what is a
robotic SL I found a shotgun choke mod I
don't know if you need oh that yeah
maybe if you could grab that for me I'll
definitely take a look at it okay oh I I
literally found a turret I think this is
a turret oh nice I don't know a whole
turret oh it's a melee turret it's a
punching
wow wow tier four CL nice oh yeah Quest
right now actually yeah I found a
turret I might need some help
hereo oh what do you need help with
there's still a important looking
chest that needs to be cracked
open oh oh my
God smashed your skull
any dudes up here oh
you oh yes almost missed all of these
dead
yeah oh
boy there's got to be something good in
here got to be something good maybe a
whole
helicopter or a whole
car how's the orange mole doing is she
having a good time digging orange mole
how are you
doing I'm I'm docking down trees
Now where's G orange
orange I have some stuff for you
yay if you could bring a delivery of
food and repair kit okay
blushing B my
eyelashes yeah I'm walking very slowly
to
you I see you does that hurt
sometimes can you take this thing for me
take this yeah we'll take it and this
thank you this bird for digging oh my
God for digging um take this ooh wait
what else do you want repair kid take
this thank you why don't you take this
to too I want to open oh my
God ooh some chili um take
these thank
[Music]
you is there anything else you want do
you want some
testosterone yeah yeah yeah some
testosterone I'll take exract Harvest it
from
there go what did you do this maybe the
poor bears o thank
you do you want to look at my what I've
done so far yeah give me the Tor is
there a bear here okay so bad I have
laid Spikes all outside and I'm planning
to make them three tall they're all
around now uh-huh so don't fall in
there's a dog yeah don't fall in all
right I'm going to die and then what
I've been working on for the past
hourish is I finally made the mode on
the back side and it's too wide and very
deep I see uh do you see it I'm hold on
I'm going to come over I'm really
slow I'll just take my bike over okay
okay okay I took the rest barely let's
go do you see it down there oh yeah do
deep it goes all the way around
wow and then there's a little entrance
you can walk into the house here but
you'll probably die to the other spikes
I'll get rid of them actually these are
useless where is the exent you have been
busy this is impressive I've working
really hard thank you I feel like this
is going to be no
problem I I'll be digging who much
better let's freaking go good Lu than
you thank you me
too that was awesome good loot doll
Harden chest what get more wood now this
item needs repair ah hey uh would anyone
with a lockpick love to come get a ton
of really amazing loot at the shotgun uh
you are going to need to smack it that's
what we did you can't wait at the
shotgun
Messiah what the shot Messiah yeah no we
we we just did a tier four class and we
had to smack that chest so you're going
to have to smack that chest okay are log
picks not allowed oh it's allowed
but we don't have
any I can find my S have you found yours
uh you haven't found it yet did you
check your
radar
uhoh there should be a there should be a
satchel
icon oh my god there a mannequin my arm
and if there's an arrow down or up then
that means you have to go up or down
yeah we're going to be here a while I
can't see the that you talking about uh
do you have a bag icon anywhere like if
you look around there's bag oh yeah I
see it now yeah go close to it yeah yeah
yeah okay okay okay let me just go and
on the top right of your screen there
should be a meter thing going up and
down depending on if you're getting
closer or further away all right I see
it now
okay oh it was so close when I was
like yeah I couldn't see it it was sorry
it was so small I
mean yeah I know this chest is going to
be worth it guys people do you know the
exit uh yeah I can't find it is there
usually good stuff in there H maybe that
way yeah this
way brute for it should be here oh I
found it yay
oh do you guys need back shot or can I
I don't think anybody's using that
ammo okay leave it
there I'm going to go to the tra and
then go
home yeah I'm waiting for you l I'm
coming
out for the
ACC can't take the stuff at least I got
the lever I've got a bunch of stuff I'm
going to drop off at home hey Kiara are
you able to make lockpicks by chance uh
not better than anybody else I think ah
yeah I don't have it unlocked so I canot
make them sadly lock pick uh yes oh it
is at the
workbench actually I feel like I've seen
it some lockpicks in our chests too
there's like two I
think
h l are you good L I am looking for a
way to go out I can't you have to go
through the the weapon shop uh because
we went or jump the found
it yeah 25% we're practically halfway
there 25% halfway we oh yeah you found
it I'm finally
out into the bike oh back back back back
oh there you are let's go home about to
the quest Bob let's go yeah
hello
welcome almost end of day
32 we're getting closer ladies we are
closer to Quest tomorrow should be
fine ah CeCe I might have a hand me down
if you're
[Music]
still h what
happened I I just fell into a canyon
with my bike she could fly in this game
she's so used to it she could not I was
going to say uh if you're still
interested in using machine guns I have
a hand me
down I think yes oh sorry I yeah yes
please I am currently looking for
leather and I will maybe you can put it
are you at the house uh no not right now
but you'll get it by the time the raid
happens for sure nice thank you I just
found a thingy so I read it so that's
really
nice my hammer got
[Music]
faster how do you heal
concussion uh painkillers oh
okay which is not how it works in real
life
but okay I guess just put that on there
I'm sure it'll
work yeah this gun is super
op very
exciting might go for the money Chad
seems like we found something
cool
y I want to make one for other
people
H yeah take them okay I can buy a cash
register you can buy it
[Laughter]
don't in the shop I have the trade
routes Quest yipp
yay but not today I think not today Q
has unlimited shotgun parts I wonder if
he has other unlimited uh parts for
weapons and
suchu you has unlimited shotgun parts
wow that's op Unlimited
baby so I can make more of these really
powerful
guns 56 and hand them off
to
by
hello how you are you okay I'm doing my
best oh
no don't don't force your voice too much
yeah you can dig all the way over here
connect it do you see it yeah yeah yeah
yeah let's go on the other side and then
we can meet GG or it's here it's please
don't if I use my back I will dig and
meet you
guys
okay my back could do
it are we still defending at the old
house yeah it won't
okay it's still staying strong think
about my hole
actually I would like I would like to
make a vault can we maybe go to the
new wait what what's the tunnel for the
new house
H it's the garage ah it's like a secret
secret
lab
feel bat's doing it faster classic not
the sp's Hur oh
no and the spikes are a little dangerous
yeah
a we're already halfway I got a
sh we just hit
once oh my God
what am I going the right way
now cron and I have been hitting a
hardened chest for 5
minutes my
be worth it it'll be so worth it F1 no
here four quests are
[Music]
fun we don't have much
food that's dangerous too everyone's
dangerous stop Escape doesn't work I'll
take you out don't
worry this was definitely worth
it yay
thank
you you can also I'm trying okay come
here you see these spikes over here oh
you're still in the hole oh
yeah it's working as
[Music]
intended
okay and then wow you see all the spikes
outside yeah it was
impressive these [\h__\h] I'm trying to make
them three tall so if you can put these
spikes and then make them like this
three tall all the way around here's all
the spikes I have on me I have to
restart my game okay
okay
M let go in the house and gra some food
first though before you
die work
[Music]
if anyone
has Springs I just need a few more to
craft my SMG are we Adam Springs I
thought we had quite a few quite a
lot did you check in all the typical
chests I'm looking right now it's not in
the Forge one I think there might be in
the other like random looking
chest I I I saw like 50 or so I know
someone else was using spring to though
so they might have used
it oh oh never mind it's in the vehicle
test I found it okay y
[Music]
i there is a safe
here oh my gosh it takes 30 minutes to
make an
SMG yeah we have time we have time we
have
time 30 minutes yeah 30
minutes
all I've broken my
lockpick oh shoot let's do that one I'm
coming back louder take your time I'm
trying to find something to drink I
think I can get from the bending oh I
have I have H Waters with me oh thank
you I'll get some of your
water I'm almost back someone else can
use this baseball bat
this is a good may maybe be way better
really
okay people can you uh make ammo I feel
like the time is getting closer and we
will need ammo of all kinds probably I
will start to work on
ammo need
everything's this cor sign
maybe
H like
that h
yeah how do we get it we can't quite
make it
Stu you can take these building blocks
and you can stack them on each other and
you can pick them up too again where's
my bike building there is a lot of
shotgun ammo in the you'll be tall
enough to put them on top I'm pretty
sure okay thank
you thank you for help me I don't know I
don't think did you a let's check around
the
corner I can't even run anymore dude was
my car hey you guys took the same
Mission I just did I think he took my
bike we're not too close to the I know I
haven't took your bike I can't no he
took it he took it oh is
the you guys are speaking of sing the
same Quest that I just did that I just
soloed yeah was it
head finding a moment to mention that I
soloed
that this
sick I found we found silver we actually
found this was actually worth it it took
10 minutes but I almost died I found
some we found some armor CS more if
anybody wants to go with me to dig up
treasure the treasure might have money
and I will
dig yay G want to dig G okay we can
bring full Moco too can't share with
tempered blade I'll
come up yeah I'll pick you up I
mean it's okay don't worry about it I
don't know what I don't know if I even
BL can handle them
awesome can you some water ah yeah of
course though right there you go good
water my bik we can just like walk
around I don't know and loot something
around what level is your shotgun cie
can um the one I have
now two okay okay is it double barrel no
it's a it's a pump action hel give that
one to someone though yeah I put I put
another double barrel shotgun in the
chest so someone can use that cool
there are lots of dire wolves just
running around in the snow by the way so
just be careful oh my
godic
at maybe it's okay
though I need to put some more on that
corner one
down like that yeah that's probably a
good spot for it
okay I'm ready bio whenever you are
okay con's using a shotgun right cor
there yeah cor here
uh there is a really good shotgun
in a corner time to
it that's a big boy
where are we Whispering it's not the
songs you can hear
okay the can't here no they don't have
ear
holes just have to make them ear holes
then yeah with my shotgun I'll gladly
oblig
absolutely right this
way let's continue going around the way
[Music]
uh the the house is the most
important it's
Troublesome how much of an upgrade even
is the level six compared to level
five try to make with the Lea Kiara nice
I'm put I think they moved to do Quest
or something tell you guys when I move
myself and talk to you so that you don't
think everyone in the call is ignoring
me so I'm muted
out it's significant 12% that's like
nothing compared to my moonshine though
my 400%
[Music]
moonshine why are they ignoring
fun they're not they're not just need to
drop some things off real quick it's
stack so 12 * 4 that's true 12 * 4 is a
lot we'll be fine two damage we'll be F
eyes Haven
adjusted the I don't even have
any
there right
now zombies are pretty brave for a place
like that though
no oh yeah oh do you want to do this
tier four clear Quest too be boo
a yes let's let's do that real fast just
really quick easy you guys are close to
it out okay uh Let's do let's do the
treasure first so that like we'll give
Callie some time to come over yeah yeah
okay sounds good I'll make my way over
there in a sec we'll dig your
[Music]
treasure
oh you want to get it
I'm sorry
piggy what do you do to the pig drive by
drive by oh no Are we almost there we're
almost there okay I thought we got stuck
in the in the spikes
ourselves okay wow it's okay so stand
stand right here mhm and
then this is the priv oh no
yeah we in G G can you come here where
are you really far we on the
map I don't know if I'll make it you you
might make it this might might be diing
for an hour what are you digging for
Treasure wait can you hand me the
map oh I can't uh I can't you use the
yeah it's okay cuz I have
a mod I think that makes treasure
smaller oh I think I have a treasure you
have it too it's that wide even with the
the mod yeah I have I have the treasure
Hunters mod um D if you go to the new
house there are mini bikes there that
you can use to drive to us
the mini bikes yeah if you if you go to
if you walk to the new house there are
mini there's a mini bike at the new
house which you can use to drive to here
can I dual moded is it dual
moded um I I don't know I don't
remember feel like I shouldn't I don't
want to leave the puppies at the house
alone with all these spikes there's also
there's also multiple bikes so you guys
can both take bicycles if you
prefer okay there's a lot of bikes at
the new house I think as long as it's
spiky regular here are some more spikes
I'll get a bike for
us
100 that doesn't make Senseo I don't
need
here can't I do you think it's better to
dig down maybe I don't know maybe maybe
we can get lucky
is that stone that's Stone accident it
shouldn't take that much that's
no corners are kind of funny
huh maybe I'll start from directly
middle a present
we should have brought some juice to
drink make the diggies oh oh digging
from the middle actually helps okay
that's good it does
it I think cuz it Doesn't middle of the
radius uh do we need do we need bones
for
anything yes
like well we probably have a lot but
they
are they are super
useful I'm
trapped it's okay I got it I got it got
it
yeah know
too far away down
iron hey I could have sworn we had
regular
[Music]
iron why does have some big F and scary
s it is don't give me the poo
poo I have tea if you get the Poo thank
you I'm
gambling you know where it's oh oh I
found an ATM what did she say we can do
with an ATM oh ATM yeah didn't Kar say
something about an
ATM I don't know the bank or an ATM
I think
she the
money let me
see where's the iron yeah where's IR two
meat I think we should eat to
meat I have oh it just look like a big
metal it it the circle is getting
smaller so we're doing something
okay let me see what armor they
got I'm scavenger outfit I'm halfway to
the house ni wait only half way to the
house are you walking yeah I'm on foot
oh
no let's see let's see who's first first
they getting to the house or we fting
the treasure
yeah you going T in there yeah oh it's
different armor oh maybe my hat's in
trouble no my hat F they were really
cooking with this treasure digging mini
game huh yeah really they really made
something here
hold on my shoes digging in general is
like the worst what do you
mean what do you no no what what do you
think about digging huh it's great and
what about earlier when you said you I
feel like that was so I was just saying
I was just saying no one likes digging
with me I just don't know why you took
it personally yeah it was
personal
good what's wrong with digging it's yeah
it's look they like digging
too tiring
though is not tiring digging
is down down with the
digging what's wrong with with digging
take it said we're getting close yet
hold let me check
the nothing's wrong with digging you
should come and join us we're still in
the center we're still in the center we
iron than I
thought although I think we're getting
close to the end of it the [\h__\h] Maybe
maybe let's
see they not going to be zombies that
can go through the cracks of the for
these we need steel
though PR
good can you guys still hear me yes yeah
okay my power flickered and my screen
turned off
no what oh I think oh oh oh oh don't
kill
we're still thirsty and hungry we're
thirsty hey guys how do you make Forge
steel it's not iron is it wait hold on F
I'm broken are you broken should I stop
digging broken no you can keep digging
I'm just
broken I see we need iron we really
don't have iron now
ra may I take your
iron think she's in the other call
oh
cute I'm going deep right now I don't
know where I'm going you can mine
it yeah my great Stone axe
why is there like a fog around them
there was it always
there maybe it's because it's 3
A.M I don't want to go to the tunnels
maybe they
poison
okay where the rocks
at a rock somewhere just like a grand
pirate hunting treasure
Adventure yeah I'm so wor right
now you you still haven't seen the chest
no hold on let me let me let me check
where you are for a
second
um now let's
just
oh I'm here and all these bikes are
locked no all of them there's one
bicycle that's on locked how will I how
will I bring f a moco
here all right okay I will help you guys
dig and then I
will give M the bike so they aren't so
stuck in that one the house God some
iron is a new house further away now no
we're still using that house but a lot
of people at the new house for crafting
and stuff I see but it's not that far
away right this is going to be the bad
it's not super far away
not there a little bit of a
them Crucible use Crucible is a spike
than a Donkey Kong
level
why in the movies there's always just an
x on the ground and then you dig and
it's right there is it cuz I'm not you
have to put the iron into the smelter
okay go oh okay you right on the border
now so where is the
treasure please make the
steel okay can we out this place from
here go
down where if if you see Rock that's too
that's too low okay
yeah sometimes there's like tunnels of
dirt who's Judy
Witch good J wi oh yeah I remember
seeing
that driving by her house oh it's got to
melt first
gotcha okay I understand how it works
now okay yeah we don't want to be too
close cuz it's dangerous oh G's almost
[Music]
here there's a gigantic Mountain
separated in eyes I'm climbing it like a
goat well the Traders have a bunch of
iron
so
Oh's kind of weak
so it's going to repair
it has to be
close okay it's a little close a little
scary what this view
SMG I'm not going to touch it wait is it
done already no it's 6 minutes left okay
it said we're getting close again fa
where this way this
way hold how am I supposed to get out of
here I think so we'll figure it
out I'm more excited to think of the
zombies that could get through
this what kind of talented zombies are
there out there maybe where are you guys
nope I see the holees never mind
It
Up Stand Back Kitt check out my iron
shovel I want to see Iron shovel my iron
shovel just just watch me all of
this one this take a different direction
there you go wow you're so good at
digging yeah yeah I know
wow oh my God wait wait again pick up go
in a this way Direction okay okay okay
go in a this way
Direction wow it's so
fast I think in in one more I can
upgrade my shovel and I can kill these
blocks in one hit would that be
impressive yeah it would be really
impressive mhm everyone would want me
they' be like ooh you can dig dirt block
in one hit blushing oh wait okay this
way
Direction
ow did you get hit oh
no what is
we above
us I know I worried about that
too don't worry I'll take up
I was going to repair my
bike oh I found
it and now now we have to smack it open
wooo oh
boy still
[Music]
thirsty did you get
smacked well somebody's bik got repaired
so cute congratulations to
them does anyone know how to make a bath
baton a bon I don't but I have a
baseball there's there's baton Parts in
the in the chest in the creat at home
yeah I can make one oh I can make a
normal one too I'm looking
for so I I made this thing a while ago
it's called Uh yay it better be worth
itula mod so I'm looking for a
St St baton I'm pretty sure I saw
something like that in one of the chest
there was really no money in this last
time there was 5K do you want my 10,000
and you can pretend like it was okay no
I got there was a lot of Amal in here
though so that's good nice there's my
bike let's see how I
oh old cash is Apparently one to one you
sell old cash for the coins yeah I
didn't know that but oh okay never mind
it's okay there's money in
here oh Callie dot dot dot me c I
know may I someone's bike got a nice
repair I got ammo
and weapon
parts okay should we go do the tier four
tier four clear okay let's do it coming
I'm coming I'm almost
there okay if you come do this tier four
I'll give you these shotgun parts oh
really I love shotgun parts I'm making
shotguns for
everybody just I need steel I can't help
but but see the cie is like just pretty
far from the FL as it at no I'm on my
bike you understand I feel as though
you're moving in the opposite direction
wait what you're not in the snow area no
no all right go do your
quest I thought you guys were doing the
quest that I soloed I saw it no wait
wake back do you want to do the quest
with us
okay I was going to return to my hole
but through here we're forcing you to
get out of the house yeah quick quick
family
activity let me actually get some rocks
first hello
[Music]
hello um I've heard we run out of steel
again and iron again but it's because
I'm trying to make a a shotgun for oh
yeah I use the fun steel to make my SMG
that's currently cooking mhm the thing
is I need that for good armor too and
now I want a giggy yeah are you finished
with what you doing no I'm still still
thinking not that
I did you know that uh when you find an
iron or stone on the Overworld oh yeah
there's like a deposit underneath yeah
there's like a whole iron vein
underneath apparently usually yeah I've
got some IR you like 15K of iron do you
want me to get you some iron yes please
okay thank you
Angel punched I'm bleeding out wait I
you wait wait wait take this take this
bandaid the St
apart here take this the be time stop
Beaver time don't don't die you can keep
some
Band-Aids I don't want you to die okay
okay you just what everyone up to what
are you doing let me in you let me
doing a quest real fast okay quick Quest
cron and I found you now now Stacy at 20
leather oh okay okay that's good that's
good
Now look for leather thank you I put
them next to your also there's like nine
weapon parts now in the weapon
box I'm
a thank you
you're supposed to open at 4:00 a.m.
open up H oh my God is there a zombie
There's a Zombie outside but I'm scared
I want to go in here without you oh
where are you sorry I was just having a
toilet break in
there maybe we should make extra T at
this I am the strongest in the
game I can finally put my stuff
there yay all right Lads I am now
Olympic champion level strength
one
more in the corner
down a th and make it
taller wa on fire burning another one
there yeah that
was maybe here his voice is so edgy oh
do these valves not do
anything it doesn't turn it off they
just Bur it looks oh dear is that the
only one in
here you got IR Maxim
[Applause]
security a usually they don't sell uh he
might be selling forged iron and forged
steel oh yeah he's got 76 forged steel
okay that one there a little bit it's
apparently quite a waste
it's inside I don't know what it is I
can't get any closer huh it's on the
back
door back door oh oh okay okay
reinforcing on that side I already did
maybe there'll be more like a dog light
oh F this way he's like you're going to
do that Quest alone
okay no bi still definitely has so good
with
this the shotgun I have what you have a
question that's at the sh Messiah I
didn't know oh okay can you this what is
this oh my gosh filling with water wait
was that you I'm so
sorry sorry bad sa you I'm so sorry
that's green he's
green I got over zealous with the puning
how improve the level of a
weapon the level of a weapon oh you have
to craft higher level of the weapon you
don't upgrade the weapon you craft it oh
okay
right you jump across oh my head is so
days from
that Jr you need a med kit I first a kit
I'm so
sorry I'll just leave need them out here
wait do we go to the water room this
one oh I think oh all right uh K where
where's the weapon the
weapon
oh you going to get
back uh maybe it's not an idea I should
have something to drink people there's
zombies yes yes oh
here do a quest I can go for a quest
nothing finish reinforcing everything
now okay we can split like let's go to
VC to if you want to do quests okay I
don't I don't have any quests but I can
join a quest
okay okay I'll put this stuff back in
here okay I wait I'm dropping you the
weapon here okay thank you you can drop
it in the chest funny though okay okay
enjoy thank
you there's no new vehicle thingy I
think in the box and some other stuff
okay thank you okay I'll be right back
one minute and then we can go
I can supp if somebody
wants did you uh carry anything
interesting that I might need uh you can
check everything like pretty much
everything on my chest you can take
it oh should we do Quest or should we
try and search for
items the Quest for someone Quest
okay owie okay good job I can come back
and hand you a bite once I get out of
[Applause]
[Music]
here
B it'll be so
fast B probably
no let's redeem
both let's make a there's a lot of
zombies in here yeah
very
possible I wow you took a shot to the
head no
problem over there did you punch me get
did I punch you I'm sorry you your I
might die I might die hold
on take the first assassin thank you
[Applause]
I'm so oh no no I don't think it was you
I think it was a
zombie you're okay it is like a 50 50%
chance it was
you yeah this way boys now we're not
hungry but we're thirsty they're already
on fire they don't care we must have
really k for the bike outfit did you
want a full set or did you only need
specific Parts um I mean full set would
be awesome but if you could only make
the main armor
[Music]
T you can you can climb this rope over
here and there's like a next
area no I can't find it it's gigantic
yeah maybe go back to where we're
putting down the does the biker set need
a lot of leather Kiara cuz I'll bring a
a bunch more leather if you want it does
but oh yeah I mean more is probably
going to help okay I'll pay you back how
do how do you climb it I'm not very good
at rope
climbing W what was it
um is very
peaceful can you not jump high enough
maybe not I never invested in parkour I
can probably make a
wait I can't make a block here here
don't
worry how do I put it on the ground be a
parkour Pro no don't say that you can
train I'm going to parkour
prison can you make
[Laughter]
that yay
the Rope
okay W there we go thank you
y too chunky to climb the roope there
man why is the music so Terri if you
guys have any Spears please let let me
know say what for Spears
oh Spears
here we can help by making cloth right
right at least the
fragments do you have duct
tape
lagging I think I gave it to
KI what do you need it for crony asked
for it in chat oh there we
are uhoh uhoh I'm scared to fight with
the lag
I don't want to punch my friends to
[Music]
death
FL W we're still not done I guess not
are you guys still digging oh you're not
digging
no that that ship is sailed back to
the oh so many oh they came into the
wall they scared let me stand in the
doorway and protect you I'll thank you
you're so strong
underground I know exactly what those
fists feel
like that's so many oh my
God yay good oh now we're done yay
there's a pig
outside you outside already yeah you go
on the ladder and it sends you right
outside so you don't have to go through
that
again
oh come over here Lads I might
[Music]
die come
home I want to
check I don't know maybe
H die Pig someone can be I guess maybe
not
but wait do you learn handy land
J yeah I've been learning all
the what about armor wait bio was
learning armor
yeah I've got some stuff no you guys
left too ear
ear there's a loot room we come back can
you give me uh I might need some help
yes
okay that means there's a lot of loot
right or is there just a chest that we
need to hit no there's a lot of Loot and
I do not have a lot of room something to
loot the cars uh you mentioned ah oh
yes yes yes also by the way you're
constantly crouching press
Ctrl she you're walking everywhere
slowly cuz you're
crouching how do we get you how do we
get to you oh go go yeah down here down
here there we
go okay there you go wow a lot of stuff
yeah thank you I go loot stuff
around have fun thank you oh yeah do you
want to come I'm I'm thinking about
going to an area to to SC gav wait okay
when cars aren't
completely together when cars look
complete they will also give gas so
those are nicer to rench L okay that's
cool she follow you I'm waiting for
crony but then I already have one of
what should we make it anyway what were
we
making all and now it's time for
the magnet 7,000
[Music]
working very
hard going fast yeah
yeah who's he here I thought we cleared
the place
out
close ooh legendary a bunch of good
stuff what did I
yeah we
are just make them
these where do we normally put bullet
casings
mining okay go ahead
yay there's another treasure map I know
how much you like
those stop
they're probably sick of the the
treasure you want to do another treasure
map here's the you can hold it oh thank
you getting sick of the Treasure by now
huh but the treasure was it giv us a lot
of ammo and weapon parts though so it
was worth
it be sure to take your steroids and
your vitamins do you have more space FAA
yes okay you can take the treasure map
on the other T yeah you you can look at
the treasure map now
oh who is doing like Tech and turret
stuff cuz I have a you can craft robotic
here take this you
chill thank you oh and you know what
I'll give this turret to you
oh it thank you
oh I think this can mine for you maybe
oh really I think I think it breaks
blocks or something I think you're
sitting on something sir or
doors oh that's his
guts
IR oh it can punch zombies too punch oh
we we should set it up like outside the
yeah yeah when the when the cord happens
you how to punch zombies the auto Fister
yeah yeah oh did you did you have did
you have any more tea I have
this te was that a supply drw you oh
there's two of them there's two who did
it did you hear that sound it was like
yeah it was a plane it's a supply
drop uh uh Kelly Do You Remember where
that one sham food thingy was yeah the
Sham Factory the Sham Wow Factory yeah
where is it on the map oh remember where
it was it's in the desert I it's between
the desert and the desolate area yeah I
can probably find out where it is yeah
we can go home first okay since home is
on the
way damn I'm in so Lov one out here
pretty
intensely I should meet up with the rest
of the
crew can we go talk to re okay the way I
wreck okay guy sucks yeah he's going to
we a quest yeah ah money money he owes
us
money yeah he owes you big
time especially for all the mean insults
yeah get wrecked I hope I hope I have
enough gas to make it to
wct we can always wrench some cars on
the way
yeah all I should make is not that
bad H is my best friend
now I love snow areas
though be nice these are kind of bad
okay we're
here
yay I'm so
slow it's not night time I
know so many things in these Pockets ooh
water filter that's nice do we already
have a water filter we do need water but
we can always need more okay it's a
little expensive but I'll keep saving up
for
it how do I get rid of weakened
armor a you have to repair it I need
water I have my hat
with or we'll get long just you think
you're pretty smart now don't you here's
your I have un first I think I'm
silly okay make a run to the house
I don't know if this works with my
[Music]
thing try
it you going to buy some food or just
stand there like a goddamn
idiot let's take the roads oh still the
cash and gold a I should sell the gold
that's right I do have golden
let me do that real quick
maybe is
better okay I repaired it thank are you
dropping of things for me oopsie oh I've
just dropped off a bunch of random stuff
I found I found some
steel is oh is there Iron among it
too no I think I left the iron at the
old house okay you definitely need that
is there a lot I was tired of it maybe a
th000 okay that's good that's good I
want that are you walking cuz you can't
Sprint I'm I'm this is my sprinting
skin I'm full I'm very full maybe pick
it up walking oh no the hole I'll head
back and see uh-huh Callie did you find
it will get some more too random than
you what the oh hold I need to buy gas
real fast Haven G there yet okay I'll
just look around in the yeah I'm still
in the snow area I'm heading back to the
house though okay okay no
worries unless you want to yeah okay I
can wait for you let's see we can you
want to come with us then yeah I want to
go with you okay going to raid the the
Sham Factory I'm going to ride my bike
home since it's so close I will see you
there
heck yeah also I have a treasure map if
anyone wants toas later yeah of course
of course we were just waiting for kie
okay of course of course I was come back
home then counting you
in
oh of course of
course how will I do without my big
cat I need her to drive she's a big
car what the crazy cat
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah guys you know what I
realized the other day what you know is
a pink she's pink and she's called
panta she's a pink she's like the she's
like the Pink
Panther that was the first fan art I
made of
her yeah
L every once in a
while didn't know that's why I'm telling
it are you saying you never thought
about it it's a joke right realize a
joke right just what I very sarcastic I
hope why are they gaslighting
us we're just trying to have a good time
and you're trying to Gaslight us me
don't take everything personally I'm
taking it personally I'm going to HR
about this
good imagine today we have a meeting
because I was gasset by them about Pink
Panther
gaset I
whaton can't believe you would do that
to
her that's why you said that I'm a
furry a lot yes she's a furry did you
get your new gun
I did SMG let's go 30 minute craft yeah
took 30 minutes the old 30 minute
craft my five minutes craft my favorite
not the 5 minute crab I love minute
ladies I have the first motor by G ser
and it's huge it's huge I want to see I
want to see show show no gas in it this
better be like the fastest thing ever I
have no gas in it right
now I have a lot of gas for you kah it's
crazy structure painted look at the SE
in the
back that's so cool with the this this
this is like T coated with
the oh yeah the biker build really suits
this the is though the animal head is
like eating the light in the front yeah
that's
Co that is
a I'll have to fill it up with some gas
and we'll see how fast it is you have
gas yay I want to have thank
[Music]
you we
can okay no rush but let us know when
you're ready um Kelly all right I'm just
I'm just cooking some steel real quick
and I'm then I'm on my way I'll do class
with you guys too now that I'm done oh
we're going to the Sham Factory oh I
want to go sham Factory okay let's go
want to come yeah come let's just wait
for call for seconds yep I'm just
putting away some ammo I've got a ton of
different ammo here I need to organize
some stuff at home first us too anyway
yeah I think
we're uhoh I think we have quite a few
raw meats oh it's more that we don't
have any
ingredients to make a good food oh I
found some po that's about to change at
the at the Sham at the Sham Factory
we're about to raid which is why I need
to open it come here for a second yeah
take that mind I don't know where the
thank you we can just keep them in here
just easier to just
oh motorcycle not quite
I'm going see
right where are my shotgun no one else
is making shotguns I don't think right
no I don't think so you are a
provider okay they're in here I see
they're in the weapon parts box
okay it's about to be real
sad are you putting gas there yeah put
everything inside here oh thank you
yeah oh I want to see the speed
now
yes have
a to cook some meat is it hard to make
this an extra seat for the mini bike
yeah if you give me more cloth fragments
I can make one how many do you need
maybe 100 would be nice
100 what what do you need to make the
motorcycle you crap this thing
uh I would need a bunch of
[Music]
things
ches I have the handle bars and two
wheels yeah
um coming you probably are missing the
motorcycle chassis if you look it up and
you can see what that needs let's go all
right are you ready
everybody the
Ware Factory people ready yeah
your the almost ready sorry was yours
the pink one your old one my old bicycle
or yeah um my mini bike mini bike no
crony is using the old Mini Bike now it
doesn't have this the seat anymore cuz I
put it on my motor bike oh that's why
okay okay no worries is it okay if we go
to the factory with you guys of course
yeah okay we're just ring over to where
you all are right now so o that's fast
hit
that it's so fast I can probably
stop is it really that quick yeah and it
it gets curves really sharply w i can
drift I can literally drift oh
[Music]
drifted
dto
dri oh my god oh is's
cooking's oh yeah I'm
hungry everyone's yeah the problem is we
have like no potatoes I don't know how
to get more potato I have two potatoes
here you make
one two potatoes little bit more water I
think the Sham if we go to the Sham
Factory I assume there's going to be a
lot of food there so maybe this is a
good
opportunity for you oh is that from me B
for
you my go
thank you're welcome thank
you
welcome I wonder I made
some chest pieces I don't know who to
give them
to are we out of rotten flesh there's no
way right really there is
way uh what's on your
chest I mean I mean no no I mean your
chest your armor uh what did you wear
for the top again so I am I have an
Assassin outfit which is not really
useful what level three kind of SC okay
uh switch with this and give me the
Assassin one oh thank you I give you a m
now
mm there you go
bye does anybody have any rotten
flesh please don't throw it away it's
very important here here here I have six
here you go put some into those like
white boxes let me
see keep the other one for
[Music]
[Applause]
or oh did I make my nerd hat
oh
B okay um don't mean to rush I'm just
I'm just checking is everyone ready
or pretty much
ready okay I didn't I'm just trying to
get some stuff
us after
everybody I think F Mo are on their way
they're just on their
bikes okay okay take your time it's fine
I just need you what are you doing just
trying to find their way to the house
the way to the house oh yeah you see
them North oh I'm digging don't worry
about
me yeah do not worry about me we're
heading over there right
now I'm going to pick up the iron gigy
I'm coming over with my motorbike okay I
have 2,000 on me right now oh let's
go do you need help do you want me to
pick you up or the we just we got a
little bit lost on me better
[Music]
sings we'll just follow after you cuz
it's more
expensive oh I have so many explosives
for this hoorde so ready okay I I got
a I'm a crafting bundle not that here
the water oh my God Armor chest you mean
a forest in the middle here the the the
chest the boxes the middle I don't know
what to put it I'm a crafting kit you
mean or what did you get I don't know
it's never seen this before it's like
I'm a crafting ble is a red box a bundle
bundle I think I
think oops oh man I did a
mess this is going to be the sickest
raid ever yeah I'm so ready we're going
to fight so much
food yeah I just need a little bit more
food
God this outfit a the biker outfit's so
cool thank
you the weird goggles though of the
position is a little it's the mor Gap
the mor Gap call is it going yeah we
love the Gap there's something wrong
with this guy uh B do you need sham for
the Sham food you can eat the Sham okay
I'm going to eat the
Sham the sandwiches give you a t that
look so fast some of them do the the
sandwiches give you a
PO
wao free spikes Rose nice I have 4,000
iron wow
wow give me me where is it um I'm in the
hole here let get
it wait can I get a ride let get out
a flip
too where we going here take all my iron
oh there you are I fell into the Okay
jump to the left thank you so much okay
okay find you can take this bike if you
want or do you have your own oh I can
come with
you oh no I only have I don't have a
seat if you have a bik you can use your
own bik oh okay never mind
okay I was just
lazy me
to okay
let it's not even that bad lead the way
someone wait where where are we going
you
factory I kind of know where it is one
moment let me Mark it this is a biker
gang yeah I got another thousand Iron
where from how are you producing these
so fast I found it
it's so good I know that it's around
this area so I'm inside the house right
now
almost we really are the nerd biker gang
yeah we this way does this mean that I'm
the queen of the
nerdc
[Music]
fast always 500 km ahe we ride as a
model gang model we ride we ride we
ride have
again sorry 351 p.m.
okay we got time plenty of time F it's
okay behind oh no I I'm just following
Callie she seems like she knows where
she's going
[Music]
danger
zone all right so it's not Church such a
scary
place but I think it's here cuz that's
where the town through through the Sham
okay update it's actually 4,000
iron
what found a lot in that hole all right
good I have two forges I'll be cooking a
lot of iron now thank you no problem
pretty wait G do you want to see my
motorbike I want to see it you can even
get on and be the first to test it
oo oh my God so
cool wraps my arms around you it's lock
let me lock oh
sorry for safety you know yeah I can't
let zombies get on oh at so
W it's so fast look I can drift that's
awesome you're our gang leader our biker
gang leader with our cool hat I am yeah
I know exactly where I'm going oh my God
so you do are you
sure okay get off
and okay actually no damage is being
suris get me out of here get me out of
here I'm try I'm tring I'm trying I'm
try it's fine it's fine it's fine I can
do it ladies it's this way I found the
right way okay you found it no oh no
okay okay okay okay okay I'm diving into
the spike I'm not taking any damage
interestingly
enough is the bike taking damage
uh no we're F that's good that's good
that's good that's good thank you okay
okay
yay might have uh given the Trap some
damage it seems borrow some that's a
strong bik she went she went this way
okay she went this way follow me through
the mountains
ladies TR you oh we really are a biker
yeah so we ride into the
sunset the air brushing through my shins
I want
to forever so how it like a
children is this like social structure
depending on who has a
motorcycle or
bicycle mean yes this is why I'm the
motorbike Queen she is the queen
okay wait fun fun what does that make
you back
seating I'm the I'm the sigma I'm not in
your hierarchy the sigma yeah let's go
yeah she's on a little bit of a
different level cuz she got she got back
seat rights to my motorbike
too found it ladies I'm going to need
some borrow some gasoline by the way
before we get out of here bicycles
really are the best huh we don't even
need gasoline y just our legs all right
shamway Factory ladies oh this is the
fact here it is before it gets too dark
but it will become night so the zombies
will become stronger so this will be a
great challenge for us it's okay die
over and over again cuz it's not a yeah
not a
quest oh G we can take him but who wants
to
die nobody off the
you want to die I can help you I can
help you with that yeah we can help with
that if you really want you guys are so
helpful but you know sometimes you have
to do things on your own I don't want to
get carried my own I see okay I kill you
without
asking okay let's go in
ladies who
me oh
god oh wow this is a good weapon I'm
excited okay office
guys we need the leather oh yeah the
chairs Boy chairs
with the H everybody else will get
double okay it's
okay L the L so otherwise they just get
clo which is nice
too I need
I'm soorry okay you're allowed to shoot
me cuz I cuz I stabbed you too many
times
yeah you to the body just in
case this is crazy no no here's my
number so call me
maybe maybe I will okay maybe yeah let's
break there's a hole that goes
underground too oh boy hello yeah really
shocked me you gave me a fright
sir oh he's still oh there's a lot of
boxes everywhere here that's in of
Me Okay help help bring on too oh Bo
suffered a deep watch out
[Music]
band I have
bands everybody come get some bandaids
before you
die
[Music]
lady I want to
Z a peek big hits I'm going to go ahead
and use that what is this wait everybody
come get bandaids
a bandid we could bandid that's f it
doesn't matter we have band one thank
you everybody need for their
o get get
get oh my
God fire fire
everybody's walking
forward that was awesome good jobob
everybody good job
everyone you're good I guess we can
clean the place out after we kind of
kill everything yeah yeah
yeah looting along the way is not a bad
idea yeah okay let's stick
together ow how much more this
[Music]
way I do be a little hungry I was sing
this right I'll use it
now oh there up here here yeah let's go
out the way I see
we can't hear you with anyone shooting
yeah any again watch out watch
out fire
[Music]
people hello
boys
pictures hello oh a bed roll was up here
what the a bed roll
[Music]
here time
the ground
is yeah that's not that is not great it
does not Inspire confidence what's in
here par scary of them scary of them
scary of
them those look like they're going to
[Music]
break not this
way kahua if you needed I have 6,000
more iron oh my
gosh you need more iron
let me turn off that fire though yeah I
[Music]
saw okay where where are we supposed
to more iron I you can't turn it off yes
I have 7,000 more if you need it okay
I'll pick it up later okay do you need G
do you need any armor by the way I'm
good okay oh
nice
I that iron is saving me right now
gy I'll get you so much more this hole
has so much iron in here I have 8,000
now don't worry
I want more creepy I don't want to shoot
you okay I'm just going to
owo is there anything you like to have
in terms of armor to uh uh let's
see
uhoh I think I'm fine with my
[Music]
oh when you come can you bring repair
kits though how many
maybe I I think I'm going to thank
you bye
bye okay uh I am infected does anybody
have any
on not on me but maybe at home I
think okay there's a big dude
I should be up somewh I thought I would
have enough turns out I won't remember
to scrap chairs ladies for leather yeah
as much as you can
okay nice shot thanks anything El
mind if
I
punch this is a new
area oh hello he dad he's dead dead
thank you he's super
dead where's the big chest in this place
is what I want to know there's got to be
one yeah there's got to be one at the
end somewhere this place is huge though
I will
say nice oh hello boys uhoh there's one
there
one what
what light T the light come on friendly
fire was such a bad
idea sorry about that it was a little
hard to see it's okay was
[Applause]
just got to find
where somebody
somebody Friendly
Fire I need that I found
it this is full of good stuff that we
need to scrap or not scrap gather rather
there's another CH let's get that
one yeah oh yeah big
by the ground
maybe armored up I'm going to use that
okay where did you guys go I I we're
still in the building oh I'm not in the
party anymore can you invite me again oh
yeah uh I I just did everybody fall
through the floor just now okay is that
a zombie or is that thank you okay yeah
I don't
know these doors are locked we might
need to break them
no there's a there's another way there's
another
area yeah we can jump on down did you go
downstairs or you still on the same
level oh we can go
here it's a shame tomorrow's the last
day today I have 177,000 ironon now how
are we going to smelt it all yeah I
know what a
shame where are you did you go down ah
oh oh There stairs way okay I found you
yeah that looks like nowhere uh there's
a b way there's a staircase on the side
of I'm on the other side of this
wall the bars hello
hello okay it's okay I see you booo yeah
show me the boo way you have to go
outside first I
see some outside parkouring yeah gotcha
got to exit through the window okay I
see and then up
here
okay cool nice find
we
z o this looks super creepy Up on the
Roof
uh hello oh there's a lot of Min here
watch
out maybe we can Le the zombies on them
time to shoot time to shoot what are you
guys we can leave them on on the roof
mines on the roof one if you come over
here we can lead them past the mines and
fight
good
Miss for you got it okay
oh
found I found you
no found you not now now it's not the
time for a ping pong at the
door ping pong ping
pongy
thing
get
Stu I I think if I step on the mine I
won't
activate let's have some water M oh okay
s
[Music]
good this angry s dang is there no
treasure oh maybe there is there there's
another way oh down here ooh let's
follow everybody
mum not too
big watch out for the mines this place
is crazy it's like a maze it is yeah
uhoh how we going
to you crouching Again by the way yeah
yeah yeah I know I'm just like TR no
not no you g you can
I a because everyone tell
me weird why would CC keep lying to
us am I lagging right now yeah the the
the server's kind of laggy right now
with all the a lot of zombies it's a big
area watch out watch
out oh gosh it yeah like flying and
floating for me
nice I'm going to go home and craft
stuff okay
[Applause]
okay I think everybody else is
downstairs now okay we're going to
follow K up by then okay just be careful
because it's a very very far drop seems
to be I wonder how we get in here people
there seems to be an area here slow as
slow as you can oh behind you behind you
behind
you if anyone
passes by me cuz they're on the way can
they take all this iron off me oh
there's a pack of wolves
outside I'm going to run to take your
iron does anybody have a craft repair
key there's a bear
too you with us though there's Bears
let's stick together okay I'm going to
try breaking this open with the stick of
dynamite okay okay stay behind M stay
behind do your best I out the
zombies oh you have to activate it and
then throw it there you go there you go
there you
go out okay we're going a little
hurt somebody somebody's here good work
good
job that's
crazy wait have we already been here I
think we've been here before Oh hey good
job good
job does anybody have a repair eat by
any chance I have one where are you I am
right there I also have one thank
you thank you so much I need to repair
my spear spear spear that's tons of
leather are you girls uh coming back
sometime soon or soon I think I thought
I think we almost there's a bunch of
stuff here here oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
okay oh there is a green guy
grey okay cuz I'd love
to it's
over how do you get over there I get it
now he's in my sights kah I'm coming oh
boy I have a wonderful gift for you oh a
10,000 iron yeah it's all Iron don't
expect anything else
got a stump
bike my bike can
fly oh there is some stuff in here there
a bunch of
stuff look might as well take everything
oh and a safe too yeah take
everything I don't have lockpicks I
don't know if it gave us anything oh sh
I should have given this lockpick to
[Music]
bio monster well I guess we're so many
trees
yeah I this is an easy one to break did
I plant those are you planning on
getting rid of those trees maybe the
trees are the tanks
no it's going to be hard to see and
shoot the enemies for all that all those
leaves oops are you here by the way yeah
okay together one second let me get out
of my hole okay I'm not getting close to
that right now
okay get smacked are you ready yeah I'm
I'm ready Bring It On get smack oh
that's wow that's a lot of ir it's
20,000,000 oh we're still
hungry thank you you're so
crazy back to my hole I'm missing
something because this feels a little
bit underwhelming for how big this is
there I hope there's good stuff in the
safe like
Runing
[Music]
probably ow someone hit
me I have not moved my my hand oh wait I
wonder if there was IR uh lever you
don't have any lever do you g promise no
I've not seen an animal in
ages
sorry except maybe for some moles or
what shows up down there little earth
worms and other little mole rats are
down here too is that what you have been
feeding on as
Wells I eat
them let's crack it open sorry I opened
it um there's nothing there's big
hitters which I'm going to read because
I am the club oh steel club quity and
then iron arrows I will take those just
in case wants those that was all that
was in there not
very
disappointing what happened to
her search the garbage angry
s a steel
Club wait wait here here B where'd she
go there one inside here there's an area
we haven't been
to is back there
going to let them in right nah it's
better I'll give it to her later oh
there's a do still maybe there's a angry
angry dog outside everybody's angry oh y
excuse me oh you I go up can you wait
just a
moment you there still quite some
enemies here so I wonder if we didn't go
this way people this way
yeah this is where we came this way oh
they come in from outside I guess and on
this side Spawn from the outside so it's
night time probably is night time oh
you're not a friend don't like this
flickering
light let's hold the twi
up okay oh he's back up
[Music]
crony shot
it's there's another one thees dirty
today I deserve
it get get y yo yo y we going to die
let's run away let's run
away stay in the brightness of the
fire good so
blind how am I doing it we need to have
some water too water if we can have some
water too that' be a good ide is This
Server really laggy for
any strange okay so I'm that one right I
think uhoh oh God there's like an
exploding guy like a red green guy it's
over for
me
run where is everybody there here all
our
[Music]
friends
nice oh I want to find the dog you want
to find the dog I want to find the dog
and kill it yes it gives good loot I
want to find the dog my bik are you the
DI yeah the the D
okay's
together
that that was it eat have that was it
I'm
walking
crch
somebody the other guy
have you guys been collecting some
leather on the way
for all kinds of
chairs does it help with our
light uhoh get away get away get
away okay maybe don't shoot the
ground no Panic somebody looks a little
bit see behind you you C oh there's a
lot of
them me XP there's a one of
them just trying to see if there's
something here since there's a where the
Sham sandwiches at he's
running he looks like everybody else I'm
so it's getting now do we need to hold
the Tor up maybe not it I'm kind of
slow
down I think it's morning now so we
should be okay yeah okay okay we're
chilling okay where the Sham I was
promised there was like no food here
yeah this was
insanely misdirecting I feel like we
should have just done a
quest yeah it's okay you live and you
learn yeah
you you're home I am home I have a
present for
you special
alcohol thank
[Applause]
you up here though stop giving her
alcohol but it will save us it will will
it save our family it
will back together not mentally but it
will save us physically yeah our
interpersonal
relationship all that matters is that we
stay
alive I'm happy to do more snow quests
with anybody who wants to do the snow
Quest they're a little bit
harder any we can
help bu of you guys are doing great I
actually I want to make you a thing
really quick though to make it even
better
you guys will be even more helpful once
I make you my special
present bandages oh we can make
bandages yeah medical stuff so uh FAA is
just getting meat not is on the roof
they say oh we really need more than
just let them take care of it apparently
the loot is on the roof yeah
I'm will take care of we need like
potatoes rotten meat rotten meat okay R
meat potatoes and mushrooms mostly and
eggs eggs are good too eggs oh yeah I
wonder why we can find that maybe just
houses no eggs are like in the nest on
the way oh right yeah up
[Music]
no okay let's go
on amazing
could use one of these I'm
basically oh yeah there is a cave of
mushrooms oh
yeah I think we might need potatoes more
than mushrooms for now where do you
think we can find potatoes I don't know
is there a potato cave
ACH I mean they are in the
ground
has I am hungry I'm starving I'm going
to I have three rotten
flesh I'm also I want to go home
together with everyone I don't want to
go on our own
H should we leave the factory
now
[Music]
yeah the food
at where the food
good good good good
good trust her she's a
doctor
okay I think I'm going to go try
and
Scavenging people panicking means it's
pretty
bad I'll go this
way okay hold
up let me go back home up I think
up
by new
house does anyone else want to try
targeting houses in order to find food I
found the room with the loop the problem
is the room is also full of
zombies wait in the in the sh Factory
help yep oh okay okay oh should we go
back should we go back I'm going it's
okay I think I can do it you can take
them I also need more claw for bandages
okay maybe not okay hold on okay well by
the time I get there the situation may
have resolved itself
but okay we're coming where are you
people I I I'm at the roof okay the roof
how did you get there I'm
coming maybe let's head back to the new
home we have done 4 180s Mory yes cuz I
can't decide where to go
out wa is she no I I think I think it's
fine I think I got it you got it the
last 180 I'm
[Music]
doing PR I can get home I'm pretty sure
I can
% gas should be fine he'll make me turn
this bike
around ladies we have 40 IRL minutes
left until the raid until the zombie
night okay I'm fine I cleared the room
it's good oh you're good yeah I'm good I
will finish my weapon time I'm sure so
we're going to the old house correct yes
I just need six more forged steel and
then I can make it for
them we got plenty of those now Y is
anybody coming home with L soon I am how
about cloth anybody got
cloth
pieces I'm
going I can try to go get some a little
bit
I'm home and see if I can reforce as
many as possible I don't have lots at
all small houses and we'll try finding
cloth as well ah we have cloth
fragments the cloth fragments can be
made into cloth I think so yes cloth
fragments is what we need we got a few
hundred that's good wow
okay maybe I can make my Ste CL did I a
little while here we go the world's a
bit brighter now I mean that's enough if
I was using it alone I
think
uh can I make I also have I guess having
more iron is inconsequential Gigi did
get like 17,000 yeah we have we have
plenty of that now it just takes a
little never ask for iron ever again you
w even need to ask this got it I have so
much for you oh wow
honed I'm going to make it so you're all
relying on me for iron and then you'll
never know what it's like without iron
and then I like drip feed it SW yeah
until you you like desperately need me
and your B we already need you we're
already obsessed with you I guess I'll
never stop collecting iron
then the leather put the not a ton but
it is a decent amount hopefully it'll
help you and some glue as well thank you
I actually need to make duct tape there
a lot of supplies here with this gun I
need duct tape where should we put the
cloth fragments um can you put them in
the medicine box medicine box okay thank
you f
medicine looking
for maybe this is the
medicine I know it's kind oh the cooked
food and medicine one is good okay okay
this will be worth it I promise can I
not make
them I have some more medicine we can
put in here
too what else do we
have
whatever okay good I don't that go in
the medicine though does
it we have two Lether where should put
the leather wooden duct tape I think
Kiara wanted the leather you can put it
in the one by the forge probably Forge
chest
yes
chest this one's making iron I think
this one's making
steel storage chest oh the fire chest
yeah yeah okay I just need 20 for what I
want to make Maybe
[Music]
oh need
40 okay it should be the chest in the
kitchen nice okay thank you was somebody
making a yucka smoothie yes and also
duct
tape I was making a smoothie oh okay
I'll give you the Smoothie oh you can
put it's not for me necessarily it's for
anybody you can put it in food chest or
you can drink it if you want
oh there's so much cloth fragments
there's couple BL oh
no am I going that's the
one okay what time is it 7:30 oh plenty
of time to go check for steel I'm sure
we're forging steel right we're forging
steel well right yeah I need some for
Ste look like they all kind of go
[Music]
antibiotics we making some yum yums oh I
need to oh I need to
eat I'm going to
die wow my favorite hobo stew thank you
for cooking this hobo
stew thought I thought it was a
sculpture is it not a sculpture there oh
it is indeed not a
sculpture I thought it was a
dog things
taking
this chest for
explosives I thought it was a robot
dog flowers
is where are we do we have any food
I'm going to have it
make
okay
[Music]
I we can't get that
far just for now so if everybody can eat
the grilled meat before the raid and
then save the good food for the raid I
think that would be
ideal please eat the grilled meat first
you're going to have to eat a lot of it
but it's
the oh there's a I'm not sure how long
feel like an hour 30 because this stays
an hour and then is it that long till
the rain it really it might be isn't it
on the 35th you should be able to I
guess so
so never mind yeah real life is kind of
quite far oh oh 1 hour 30 minutes hour
and 30 shoot hold on well we still have
a lot of time maybe I'll go for some
extra
Quest could have played longer
yesterday that's that's what I'm saying
yeah we should
have it's hard to do math that's good
though we've got grab the
Ste what are
these sorry were youing soon yep I'm
making them for
ammo
byebye oh oh maybe not yeah cuz I got to
make
steel and I was wondering if I could use
this to make steel if possible and then
maybe we could make bullet casings over
here
how much Ste you need I have like 100 in
my pocket oh my god wow that's crazy
well to make the gun I wanted to make
it's like
40 okay yeah wait let me make oh but
they're off for the day huh they're
offline
oh dang it oh oh they just left what I
didn't even realize yeah what they left
and oh oh here let me I'll give the I'll
give the guns to Cody then let me invite
you back to the party I think they now
oh yes please I might go since we still
have so much time if somebody's still
doing quests I might join yeah I could
do some Quest yes
please okay I do I I was making some
armor so I got some stuff to give to the
weakest
links whoever that is and I did make
some repair kits oh did you I was about
to I have nine now that I'll make some
more I think we'll need a Ben yeah steel
Club how do we make steel
Club also need a workbench for this one
this one actually can be made pretty
quickly well let me know whenever you
guys are on your way to a new Quest okay
what do we
meet
potatoes
potatoes what do we meet guys which
Quest we're going to
do get some
weapons oh
not sure which one yet I like the snowy
Quest though I think they're good I want
to go there too I don't think I've been
there before I still need to open up the
trader route you have to open the trade
route or can you just talk to the new
Trader no you can just talk to him
okay but I still want to open it up I'm
pretty sure that's fine yeah might be
good might be a good
idea
actually
W I got Auto auto turret really I got
two auto turret I got two SMG Auto
turrets
o in the
fin I spent like 10 minutes opening a
chest it was so worth it oh that sounds
like it was wor auto turret that's yeah
auto turret Auto I need a
wrench heck yeah I'm coming to the house
then and then
maybe I'll make some 9 mm girls who are
using 9 mm ammo is it only B it's only B
but I could use a lot more I'll I'll put
some into the queue for you thank you
cuz I'm also making ammo for
myself guess I could make some shotgun
shells too shotgun shotgun
ammo you I don't know if you're able to
but I would need uh steel
arrows uh
I have iron
arrows R I haven't looked into arrows
yet
um that's a bit too much baby I I
already makeing armor and
stuff maybe I'll wear the
no what I
doing wait
[Music]
ammo it looks cool but I look cooler oh
have a treasured map I probably want to
look
into I don't know it's if it'll be any
good though hey viu did you want
molotovs yes please
okay how much cloth do you
need um a lot but I think I'm I might be
okay now put a lot in the
chest which chest in the one in the
kitchen by the forge if you want to take
it Cece are you using
batons I wanted to get a uh I have a
stun baton level five oh yes I can give
it to you yeah because I have like a mod
extension thingy for it yes yeah it's
it's really good I think you should have
it thank
[Music]
you okay I'm coming home to store some
Loot and we can do clast I'm ready
anytime I'm going home to maps are based
on where you far
fire oh if you read it in a higher level
you get better loot okay maybe I'll look
at the treasure map when we're in the
snow
[Music]
area thank you very much for the
redirect that was nice I'm sorry I
couldn't make you guys the shotgun I
wanted to make
you but that's okay just it's it's in
it's in your heart I deliver it to your
heart
we're ready for quests I'm going game
stage
190 oh yeah I did should we be worried
about that I murdered a BN
of should I don't
know hey Cron's at 94 though so that's
kind of it it also depends on where you
are because I am still at the factory so
yeah
a I see it she's in the Wasteland I'm
making a few more repair kits just like
maybe
oh I need repair
kits repair kits are always
good near the area head to the Rally
Point should I head to the Rally
Point should wait for everybody where is
that
doing um I just see it on my screen it's
1.6 k no that's a that's a tier one
Quest that's a tier one Quest okay I
don't think we should do tier
one how many people are using shotguns
in
here a few crony
okay I'm in need of a little
fuel just a little fuel we'll find some
fuel
surely any gas cans
you're right CeCe I might buy you uh let
me drop off this weapon for
you oh
oh watch out bird bird uhoh it's always
the freaking
Birds okay take
this a little
nice thank you yeah you happen to have a
repair kit I can buy off of you you can
just have one here some
be what hat are you wearing I'm wearing
the nerd hat still
Level uh four I believe do you want a
higher level nerd hat or would you like
some different hat sewing kit and um
sure I could use a higher level nerd
hat Co turret you prefer nerd hat over
anything else do you
um well that's the EXP one right oh yeah
yeah yeah I would prefer the EXP okay
I'll make you the max level
one using up one legendary part wait do
we still have an hour and a half we do
and we've been going for 4 and a half
hours we we timed it I thought I thought
one day is one hour but I gu yes not is
it longer than that I think it's longer
than that I could keep playing Let me
let me I'm fine just I'm definitely
staying until the H though yeah we we
prepared too hard for to not have a h at
the end yeah definitely hope we get a
season two we're working on it it seems
possible so I would love that let's do
it
I really want
to can I have a better heart if mine two
do you want the EXP hat or a different
one it's fine okay just should be
stronger maybe yeah no problem thank you
I'll make you level five wa I think oh
I'm a crafting
[Music]
kid I kind of want to get mods from my
spear feel like this is still not enough
bandages I have five on my hand
personally right now so I'll just use
those I think I'll be fine with
five for the raid yeah
I I'll forget using them anyway
literally yesterday I only used
one I just forgot about
them oh be back very
quickly okay where are we going to do
[Applause]
Quest how about the snow area I will
keep recommending the snow area over
yeah we can do we can go to the snow
area since it's higher here um I have
one up there tier four clear that one's
fun bioo it's a fun one okay it's a big
shooty
one shy
FL I'm trying to make ammo for everyone
right now thank you thank you thank you
thank you I've got lots but I'm going to
I'm going to use all of
it this shotgun is amazing that's why I
need the paper
oh here here you
go oh wow okay then I'll just focus on
shotgun shot and 9 mm yeah if I could
have a lot of 9 mm that would be great
[Music]
fuel oh also there is about 200 shotgun
bullets in the weapon ammo crate right
now oh let's go awesome I'll split that
with cool I I'll probably
give it's poo don't
mind po B po tell me about poo do not
worry about poo tell me about popo popo
is the little green bird flying next to
me I'll send you a photo of him seen him
I didn't expect him to sound like that
yeah he's really good at baring
he's so talented let me find a photo of
him yeah I want to see I want popo too
okay what is Popo's
personality um silent until the
Barking then not silent yeah then Not So
Silent wait I remind me please of the
levels of each of your armor
l oh she's you muted L she said she's
going to be right back a while ago okay
she's looking at me in game
oh up I have telepathically sent you a
photo of popo into your TMS let me see
ooh let me see boo oh my goodness cute
[Music]
so
rattie where's my anv though does popo
like being called a
rat I call Popo ugly so much I'm like
come here ugly I love you ugly one and
then Popo's
like hold on I got a
[Music]
sign hold on oh here's even more for you
seven love paying my taxes do you have
any more gunpowder or or nitrate uh I
have bullet
casing I don't need those necessarily
but
yeah
beta
done
now let's see which Quest is that I
don't want to do T one clear can I
ignore it
H should have made more
9 where's the quest I
took we're wasting gas purple oh sorry
guys I'm back I am back welcome
backc back so my hat nerd hat oh thank
you yeah but tell me the rest uh I have
the armor is level four and the glasss
are level three and the boots are level
three m i
see take
these thank you you're welcome and and
the the ones you
have now can you just drop them on the
floor the old ones of course of course I
didn't even see the bir hold a
sec aren't
those I'm those are the old ones okay
yeah those are the old ones good should
I oh wait is this supposed to be on the
forge at all
times yeah wait oh well I think uh if
there's nothing cooking is anything
cooking cudot uh let me let me
check that's a cute that's a cute little
bird there cute know what happen it's a
cute bird very cute
birdie I'm jealous of your cute bir is
making stuff I know it's so so fluffy
it's uh it's it's like smelting the iron
pretty sure it's not forged
iron uh then that has to be done
manually like first you put in the the
raw iron and then it loads up the forge
of the iron and then anytime you can
cook the forged
stuff once the iron is like loading up
there's like a count on the right side
how much iron How much brass ET is
inside oh here's here's two workstation
books oh thank
you haven't seen one of those in a
while 38 out of
75 uh girls let me know when we do
quests then I I'm just organizing my
inventory right now first okay
[Music]
H think a
second the bathroom huh
oops more chairs to turn into a
leather there's a lot of
them wait this the does the fire not
just like if it's burning does it save
the time and then
or is it just like wasting fuel if
nothing is cooking in it or is it
converting it
into oh it is wasting but the forge is
not wasting if it's just
running I
see oh he wants to come in
there's a steel club and a pump shotgun
in the output of the station the
shotguns for crony uh the steel clubs
for me
though you
good oh these look like I could scrap
that who's screaming calm
down CH it's not that big of a deal why
you said eat the meat like the basic
meat eat the grilled
meat the you might have to eat like a
whole stack if you're really I'm working
on it I'm e a whole stack right
now the red tea oh no money it's hard if
we had more eggs we could make better
food if we had more potatoes but farming
is so
hard cuz you have to spend five potatoes
to get two seeds and then it's not
efficient yeah or to get one seed five
potatoes to get one seed and then you
get seven potatoes back so you only get
net two potatoes and it takes forever to
grow that's not
efficient is the farmer armor expensive
to craft
kiaha uh farmer
outfit the whole outfit hello and maybe
just the chest I have a hat
already uh depends on what level you
want it on cuz I will be running out of
lever if I make this not again not again
not again not the
bear bear brings lever maybe just level
one is okay I'll make you at least level
three okay you need help you're
breathing very
heavily but I need
I I'm ready for quest now by the way H I
am uh finishing a solo Quest and then
I'm I'm ready to go
[Music]
okay I don't know I have to wait the
boots are better farmer
boots okay well they also need most
important they need to say
materials but there's the D
yeah welcome back welcome
back I don't want to do
that let's make level four think I can
take
him okay we'll see maybe we'll get more
leather is AAR on our
way I got
your uh farmer boots thank you surely he
can't get in here right is he dead I'll
try to get us better
seeds there you go I do love cheese I
don't know how much time we have cheese
Gr stuff I love cheese that leather
though we need not much
time I should be able to grow a few
potatoes at
least m mushrooms though a few
mushrooms he's a big
boy uh I'm putting 61 of Ky wobble
bullets in the for chest I feel bad oh I
found you give me so much
ammo yeah I I just found
them oh did you a I think it's you found
the the 20 bullets that I put into the
ammo
chesto did you did I they're gone now so
I oh yeah I took them I took them yeah
yeah yeah good Cy there is a bunch of
shotgun ammo in the new house so make
sure to get but I found a bunch of those
too I found everything except my own
people I have another unrelated
present take oh thanks thank you if you
need more let me know okay why am I
[Music]
using
yeah and and
beo this will surely
help think I have one more right oh
thank
you it will help it will kill one zombie
yes the one head shot
Mak a difference D do you want to make
metal
spikes yeah how I I have a I have a mod
SM for metal spikes I want to make metal
spikes yeah
okay should I run back to the old house
is that I'm at the new house oh should I
run back to to the new house I can drop
it off for you I'll come by and drop it
okay
well oh
well oh I'm
hungry I Got No
Seeds there's there's almost 400 uh
shotgun ammo in the shotgun or in the
ammo
chest oh hello farming is a
[Music]
scamell cool M
but h must be another way
around
yeah
o uh why do I have this
a what's in
here that looks
good oh he W me
oh
sh I just you're my favorite
clust I wanted
separate
[Music]
hello chill this isn't about
you there's good way to get
eggs there's got to be a way to raise
chickens or something like that right
too late to raise
chickens
yeah should totally be possible
right doesn't show
up is it the finally time calm to make
this
but only on level two will it be
better
Ste I wish I could take the
photos wor I'm coming on your
direction I'm also going to head in that
direction oh okay me to wait wait fun
I'll I'll I'll carry you you give me a
ride of course I will thank you fine uh
just give
me one more moment okay do we have this
house yeah there should be wood in one
of the middle chests you can also check
my own chest I should
have can I use your
gunpowder you have gunpowder in your
chest Cy can I use it yeah for making
ammo for everybody okay yeah ni you got
some good stuff wood in L Ro
[Music]
chest or maybe I deposit there's 84 wood
in the top middle chest top middle chest
ah thank you I am blind as always me too
okay D I'm coming to drop by a present
for you D please make are you eating
something no yes
oh I just ordered for two I was hungry
Barrel had dinner
time oh means lunch time it's lunchtime
no never mind I read it wrong it's the
mon the club you don't actually make
metal spikes
[Music]
I'm that's really
oh there was more wood
too hello I mean if we can put it on the
clock we can put it on the
ground loud loud very loud very loud in
new house very loud
yeah oh I'm punching our house must
defend oh beautiful
house did he fall
[Music]
zie still the house
um probably she's dealing with it she
will handle
it okay
100 thank you
who is vomiting at my back door oh oh
sorry I got
him battle music stops okay I think I
think I think I can uh in 55 seconds I
can go
okay should we take this guy with us
when it's time oh there's still dudes
this guy but the Mele turet yes we
should I did it though so that's oh yeah
yeah do that just you know they keep
coming they let the door
open
oh this is going to be
rough okay okay I'm all over the place
I'm like everywhere oh nice
lucky hello
for what's this about
Ammo have one of these more right
there do you need any more forged
ahead yes yes you do many many many
gotcha I figured as much I wasn't
sure okay put good
enough mission complete oh oh hey what's
going on
I'm helping I should I should just stop
I need to stop I need to stop crafting I
need to stop crafting the mission is
complete so we can get out of here I'm
heading toward the snowy area Okay
anymore I think now I need to claw my
way out of here bring we have the sealed
shipping crates
too oh and this okay we found
a should I bring you clo the thing can
you bring me should I bring you the the
the should I bring the pump shotgun at
the steel club with me sure if you're
coming to the snowy area yeah I'm coming
there will crony be there I wonder
thanks oh if you're using Club do you
have the mod for
spikes metal spikes mod I do have one
okay well I have I have a schematic for
you can make more I'll give it to yeah
that's cool I'll take
that since it's not placing
spice okay got a bunch of cloth if
you're still available to make the seat
oh right now mhm I am quite far away so
I don't know if you have
something uh
yeah I
think we can exchange the cloth I have
enough to make it right now and you can
give me the one
you uh G um okay we are coming home but
let me see how far we are the zombies
were not too
far um but you can also it's up to you
it's up to
you uh depends on if I have enough
leather
honestly I might be missing one leather
oh okay now I might need you to come
over unless I find leather here okay
M on the
wall Lea
Lea wall of course not our most needed
resource now is lettera and potatoes I
guess potatoes
potatoes coming to help
me why you end it up there drop from the
ceiling other office oh I see there it
is oh there you go I hope
H hello are you two right now traveling
with two bicycles yeah
oh okay so much good stuff in here to
you do you have room in your inventory
by
chance yeah I have space there's a pump
shotgun too oh my gosh this will be
great to arm people see if you can carry
some of this stuff I I can carry
everything okay I got here too so if you
need any hands I have hands awesome yeah
I'm very cucumber at the moment so okay
I like
cucumbers really no what I love they're
so tasty yeah cucumbers are kind of I
had a funny story I was at a grocery
store and I was buying chili oil and
this like man who looked like like a
like a wild like Lumberjack kind of man
that kind of man came up to me and was
like did you see the tick tock cucumbers
too
sometimes
cucumber yeah and she was like
Nationwide thing everybody wants eat
cucumbers because of that specific guy
which sucks because there was already a
cucumber shortage so I'm mad at him for
exposing how good cucumbers
are I was not expecting this like
Lumberjack Mountain Man to be on the Tik
Tok cucumber
meta go get the Dire Wolf he's over
there
cucumber the gate over there okay my
favorite is the one where there's like
this guy when he's just in in in a like
a lake or something and he goes
sometimes you just e an entire CU he
start in the I think he dropped I want
to see what the loot is I just want to
look at it oh he
dropped
oh oh shoot I'm sorry I'm I'm I'm
waiting for the lever delivery to make a
seet mall you want biker gloves I sure
do want biker gloves okay hold on well
let's clear this out first yeah Lea
delivery from who uh CeCe crony gang
okay they're pretty cuz then they can go
around faster cuz I think yeah they also
join the quests
maybe
yeah don't worry we'll we'll catch up
super fast if bike and then we'll wait
though for the ones who aren still
behind so catching up doesn't mean
anything yeah I feel like I should go
look for stuff right now CU I'm not
doing anything I'll just go on my bike
and then and then if you find me on the
way you can pick me up okay
easy what is in there already red
shotgun Messiah CE mhm how much
7.62 ammo do you have I currently have
uhoh
outside uh oh God the lag
strong
150 okay uh C I'll give you some mine
take that thank you when I see you I
will but don't be maybe until the raid
maybe focus on close combat so that we
don't waste too much ammo on the quest
okay we'll do
uh-oh excuse you do you have any mods on
your
gun right now
no I don't I haven't found any gun mods
actually there's a lot in a chest that
might work I have I have all of the
recipes nice are there
actual oh yeah actually you can probably
take of these should work for you g I'll
take the ones that should work the wall
you want to kill you I'm so sorry I'm so
[Music]
magazine Callie call take this here
oh shot shells so sorry about that
worries yeah I'm ready got Le for
you that was
fast oh okay can you H me
leather 236 cloth what two sewing kids
you want you want to be hit yeah o
machine
[Music]
guns oh oh armor up actually you can use
if you want it's okay I'm on steroids
for 19 minutes I put rotting Flash and
food stuff into your food
area Okay in 1 minute your seat mod will
be finished yay and ah ah wait wait come
over to the middle uh I I chose some
mods for you for your gun for your rifle
thank you and then here's some ammo but
don't spend too much before the raid
okay thank you welcome shotgun but I
wonder what materials I need let's
defend Row's stuff okay there she thank
you got it uh 60 forged steel a lot of
Steel take this schematic cie oh thank
you hold on just a sec drinking some
water oh lots
of that's
good I have some ammo for you kiaha I'm
just going to put everything in this
chest the shotgun was for crony right KY
yep it's my gift to her and this the
steel Club is for you yes oo
okay giving I'm giving her the the
shotgun right now and some other
stuff
okay oh gosh they're coming
in good job on all right um we got it
all I think we're ready to go do you
want to head towards here for Bio in the
snow
sure I'm going to stop
[Music]
allers we can did you take any quests
you took the shotg Mah Quest right yeah
no that's the that's
tier
tra do that
singlehandedly kind of destroying our
house though
no not our beautiful house got our
home on Earth well the turret is working
it punch this
lady needs to work a little bit better
it's not good enough
no up the the
side oh my God it's electrified wait
it's
crackable just stunned
she broke the house oh no does someone
have wood to fix
that oh no that bad I'm sorry you guys
no just the two blocks are gone no
worries oh someone who died me we had
two
dead ah
casualties oh so many dead bodies oh my
God dead bodies everywhere dead bodies
everywhere are
youw
oh
man um but at least your seed mod is
finished woohoo woohoo wait CE CE see
I'm going to put it down here on the
floor if you pick up your your bike then
you can put it on there in the modify
window
okay uh it was
this one no that one's
lock oh wait uh you want to put it on a
mini bike right oh yeah do we have a
leftover mini bike right no I think we
had
one it's here here yeah let's see oh
yeah M mine probably my old one I guess
yeah for sorry that's still locked I mus
it no actually no it's not who who last
used this one uh crony right oh
yeah
[Music]
crony you got to unlock
it so that we can put the seat mod
on
yeah how's it going Gigi are you I'm
checking out the farm I'm looking for a
eggs now oh thank
you I also have um 100 claws you would
like a 100 CL I kind of need Aloe now
okay it's in the desert go the start
punching we could in the
desert where is she oh there ah do we
happen to have repair kits oh wait we
have two extra Mini biks
ouch ouch ouch ouch
ouch hello hello just parking my bike
across the street near this mountain are
you guys near oh you guys left me alone
no here come here come here you come
here you come here I'm coming Callie
while we wait let us loot the place oh
yeah you just want to loot it while we
wait well it's going to reset anyway so
you might as well Lo the place okay I
think um it's over for
me where would I find repair do we have
any or is it
over it's not over till it's over I
thought I can pick you up if you want
kids no no no no uh uh uh CeCe yeah it's
the other mini bike I don't know who
locked the other bike but uh there's one
mini bike that's locked by me I'll
unlock this one okay or
wait lock no it's un un locked it's
unlocked yeah if you pick it up then you
can put the seat mod on so I pick it up
take and then
I
modify okay
oo yay now B did you ride off without me
I did you can you can pick me up though
okay are you on a bicycle or yeah I'm on
a
bike uh where is the real goal here Ru
is
okay yeah what be is where the quest is
I'll wait for everybody to get here yeah
okay looting
beforehand CUO in oh I should have oh
thank you we did it thank you I'll catch
up bike
Queen uh how longten do we need
oil H every now and then but you can get
it from like in uh car that are still
intact um when you wrench
them who's making these noises I hear
scary sounds out here too oh I meant
bicycle bike noises that's us who
spamming the honk noises oh Callie I
have level five biker gloves come
here these instead thank you what should
we do with the old on nice probably
probably give to someone else yeah you
can yeah good find
uh what was I going to do see it is
worth it to loot before you do the quest
true yeah extra get extra goodies mhm oh
are you you girls waiting for me it's
me I lost my backpack
honey it should show up on your
map yeah yeah yeah yeah I just
responded oh yeah oh y'all aren't too
far this be super easy with all of us
here sure oh my god do we have anything
for infections with
users have those I only have
vitamins I too am very infected oh are
you we need honey at 4.4 yeah do you
have honey with you I don't have any
with me
but I'll find a tree stump on the way
and hope we'll get lucky he's close
thank you guys when is the rid again uh
uh on this game day yeah
22:00 on this day yes this day 22:00 oh
then we just reached we just passed
midnight so yeah okay I think is about
an hour in real
life yeah yeah okay I think I'm going to
go on a quick like 5 to 10 minute break
I will be back h house just going to get
some food I'm
starving okay food see you in a bit
have a good
break oh there's fauna hey I'm here
fauna uh I think it's going to be the US
right fa what gloves do you have I'm I'm
coming I have you're
cominger fire
gloves probably fine biker gloves give
melee damage bonus do I think my Raider
set is good for me I also get melee
bonus oh okay
good um if anybody has um magazines
for treasure hunter let me know treasure
hunter okay oh yeah there is such thing
as Treasure Hunter magazine everybody
needs to take Band-Aids
R thank you everybody stay Banda take
these thanks I'll take Mand let's
freaking go B
boo takey these thank you
if only I had a
GPS follow the Road North wait oh you're
going that way no no well I I wanted to
go north but I can't find a road that
goes north it's a bit of a windy
road is there an actual Road uh you
could have just taken the road from the
same Road North all the way into the was
that road there's just the one from our
house oh no yeah yeah yeah there's like
an intersection and then you go up I'll
find area yeah I'll go there
now we'll probably need
food I could use
some okay here's some
food thank you how about
water thank you for the mountain guys C
Water bottled water I need I need water
ooh pure mineral water
what's got all the goods thank you IO do
you need water I have water okay dang it
I feel like we've finally really gotten
into the groove of the game and now
we're going to stop playing it D we're
so efficient
now I got so good yeah def the first few
days were pretty rough yeah it was
hectic but once you learn the
stuff is for
one up does anybody use axes how big
this map is just for chopping wood oh
okay uh here's a level four axe for
chopping wood stone or steel or iron
iron H I only have a stone still oh
maybe G would like it yeah maybe giggy
has gy what's
your uh axe
like uh um I have a level five iron fire
axe oh okay mine's level four so that
yours is bad
okay is everybody
here we will wait got
cre yeah more baseball bats still Club
time it's so beautiful here I know it's
my favorite area
area no that's not is
chill
dioles no not yet Are there many
here yeah dire wolves are easy now
though are they yeah they they really
are they really
are just never mind he's not
open the traitor oh yeah you'll open
tomorrow probably by the time we finish
this to be
honest a quick one I'm here oh hold on I
found I found some loot boxes in in the
place that we're about to Quest let me
just open them real fast thank you
uh oh you ran off okay my mods
off okay I'm coming back on my club real
quick brand new
club I know I don't need to drag them
but just let me drag
them where did I bring this wait kiaha
do you have
Band-Aids yeah five okay
boy you think it's strong water I'm fine
right now why don't you take one a bite
of food would be nice okay have some
food
thanks yippee I wonder if it's strong
okay are ready to give them to crony for
sure let's okay I am starting woo
I don't like
the microphone right off the bat oh yeah
big
lag oh hello he's really having a bad
time at the
[Applause]
club nobody likes to have a bad time at
the
club I always have a bad time at the
club that's why I don't go to clubs
anymore I mean that sounds like I ever
went to clubs but I really
didn't I know what I like and I know
what I don't
like
avoid the uncomfortable
spaces
greed oh wow yo Raider outfit level five
are you for real oh we just crafted that
bra for free
this is making me mad this
place
wrong what St happening over
here yeah what what St
happening I I someone
else hey they sprayed my
knee ouch do you need cas's again
it's just too fun to use the
club I know the shotguns better
but
you're who's doing that to me thank you
I'm bleeding ah okay hold up not
anymore fa's bandage makes it better
yeah thank you haven't touched a single
enemy
yet yeah I'm sure more will come out in
fact there's some up here or around here
some workers
just taking their time
oh don't run past
me f what level of cooking are you by
the way should not even Max by now no I
wish I'm
only I'm only
magazine ah F wait take these
what are these magazine surely I will
get an electric shock if I try to rench
this right
chat possibility the tra oh there's a
high
probability no they're scaling all the
all the freaking
walls
wow but that's 10,000 not worth my
time how you get out there
all the we have oh this is parkour oh
no
W using these blocks for good
Minecraft actually it's these they don't
have much HP on these Gates we can just
there's a there's a whole on ceiling on
the roof right
here that's the the chest that I
hammered out for a long long time oh
help thank a lot of dudes oh hello uhoh
that's lag bad
[Music]
lag sorry dog go away dog Sorry by
dog we did you did it
oh lock wait let me let me lock P oops
how difficult is it to kill a
bear um you got this
okay you're probably fine that's totally
going to do the
trick
really okay there's more stuff back here
too oh wow
good uh here's bullets with you follow
bullets with Callie thank you also
there's a safe back here level five nerd
outfit wow
Wy unlocked it I think he will do a
better job though which one where back
here where I am I'm a little far in
but I'm dropping ah there she goes I
going to drop some ammo too oh I was
muted I said does anybody have some the
nerd outfit or I can use it thank you
you can have it okay it use it thank you
thank you that's so
cute yeah right I didn't even need to
make it where is
she
prob you're shorts you're both short
cute oh that is
cute I have style I would definitely
go around like
that
100% it's going to be cold in the snowy
area for you no problem who's cracking
it open oh safe uh what's in it do you
do you use iron Knuckles
F no oh okay I'll give them to
anyway
uh here's some arrows
F do you want to help me wrench to save
okay I can wrench too wait you guys have
Salvage ability wait it's already open
yeah want
materials okay oh it does give you
stuff although I'm really I don't have
iron problems anymore chat I don't need
this iron problem Days Are Over yeah
thanks to
GG again I have ammo for you bar
I I have
too 9
mm thank
you Callie I have a book for you oh is
it a shotgun Messiah book
it's shotgun weekly yeah sh weekly let's
go thank you B you might want to learn
this schematic this might be useful for
drones
later uh here go thank you thank you
don't forget your ammo
B oh there's some 9 mm so nerdy oh thank
you thank you oh thank you what does it
say yield R armor crafting
also and then here's explosive explosive
weekly
oh here oh thank you oh some baseball
bats I can't kill this bear uhoh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh fight
harder fight
[Music]
harder I shot it with so many arrows oh
no you did what you
could yeah ranching the cars makes more
sense need the
gas are we going to a different quest uh
the Traer is open so I'm just going to
take my stuff to him real fast okay good
I get on motorcycle I'm already at the
tra I'm already there
stop why would you do that I want to
flex my B my my motorbike to you I do
want to ride on your bike where's this
entrance to this guy was it here you
just got the doors won't open for you is
the yeah it's messed up what why what
how dare he not open his doors oh
because you you don't have the class yet
for
him oh coming in anyway what are you
good are you breaking down the door make
sure spend your reward on more guns and
ammo oh is that
easy of
course
okay can I put this on my knuckles
[Music]
H wow he's seen some [\h__\h] huh shine my
little flashlight at
him hello let me talk to you doesn't
even need batteries
please there o another infestation Quest
a cigar that's
it oh I need
these oh I need Pockets I need
antibiotics do we have antibi we don't
have antibiotics do
we I buy these from Trader J man Mak oh
he's not selling antibiotics huh don't
get yourself killed I'm also infected
yeah
okay was bunker
Buster against
Stone B have you read Pistol Pete Volume
7 before let me
Che I'm going to heal myself yes I'm
done okay
maybe these um could be
good how do you when you have different
kinds of ammo how do you choose which
one you're using or does it is there no
way to I don't know I don't know how to
make it use my piercing
ammo hold R to when ah holding it you
can choose what you're reloading I
guess I see okay can I
[Music]
Ste I
can I'm looting his stuff you're looting
it he doesn't care I know he has a sign
that says you loot I shoot but he
doesn't seem to enforce
it I don't know I I think he might
there's some ammo over here ky dropping
just a little bit of ammo for you thank
you oh yeah we can L his stuff steal his
stuff there's a there's a lot of ammo
around you stuff oh let me drop this
wait k we here yeah oh two times shotgun
shells behind you thank
you cute C ni
sir very
helpful I'm lost yeah
this K face I can't believe these just
letting us loot him yeah he's nice I
guess he's afraid of us appreciate it oh
can I use this Forge no I guess
not he thinks we're super destroyed
Forge has a forge
head what a man he's got a couple forg I
have a forg ahead for you too the cement
mixer also had a forge welcome
back welcome back hey welcome back I
have consumed
Zoom I wonder did the other Traders have
the that kind of stuff I think I put it
away oh yes everything I need all of
them should have destroyed benches and
stuff I guess so I never tried touching
them I thought they would like get angry
at
me what's the worst they could
do oh yeah guys does this work on
non-machine guns too oh it's a schematic
again
steel maybe a couple more shotgun parts
I bet we be good steel is at home plenty
of it I know we got steel plenty of
Steel that's good for shotgun parts I
think we also have enough shotgun parts
I'm not going to spend all my money here
you kidding me we might have something
[Music]
yummy
H
cucumber does he sell sell good stuff
I'm so cucumber I think his stuff is
good it's better than the other
Traders he's cool this guy is cool who
dropped that do you guys remember when
we would get
denter I still get sometimes
you sometimes you got to eat the
sandwiches you know yeah sometimes so
hungry okay Alo cream I don't know about
all that I just don't know all right I'm
running back to the house unless did you
guys tell I running back to the house
take a quest all right I got the
quest I took one
too there's quest to the West FAS and
Kias is to the West yes to the W take
those real quick we probably do quick
yeah first cuz it's on the and then
Kiara okay a where are you I'm coming
okay gigi are you still at the old house
yeah I'm not going to eat the you
kidding me
okay you can look at my
work very excited to see that's the sole
reason I'm coming don't worry
yeah getting picked up by a hot lady
with a hot motorcycle yeah I like that
[Laughter]
I don't even know how to activate it how
do
you x
x
yeah hey you got to
go I I don't have my hands on your waist
anymore though I'm just sitting in the
back spacious chilling can anybody give
me a ride oh yeah I can give you a
ride covered I'm outside here
no now
I oh this the wrong way actually why did
I follow
people West West West you got to go oh
this is nice this is luxurious mhm we're
really fast now
yeah you are the queen of the biker gang
I am I provide all the bikes I'm jealous
I got to get a
motorcycle H season two everybody will
be in
motorcycle next step is every one
motorcycling cars hey I'm driving here
[Music]
oh I think lag must have happened again
yeah I didn't see anything through the
mountain six I think we're going to the
church up the hill yeah there's a path
there's a path look at that ready for
there's a little oh there's a bear kill
it kill it a bear go go go
go
oh wow oh I got to level up from
that leeching
exp
y oh wow wow lot of stuff okay if only
was here we could renew our triple vows
take this
no oh that's my I have to go to the
church why do people renew their vows
was one time not enough like do you for
romance I got the wooden they want to
have a big party again yeah just have a
party sometimes you just need a party
for no reason sometimes I wake up and
I'm like good job me Party Party Time
yeah but breaking myself because I just
want you to look at how in love we
are oh so you're just trying to show off
yes what happens when don't have time
for a party anymore and then you haven't
Reed them in like 4 years it doesn't
matter anymore we're still in love it's
okay we'll do it when we
die you say
so the exclamation mark is over here
okay where
churches there's always wacky [\h__\h] going
on
here
wait where you guys
going oh we're following I just to
church to church Cathedral why is she
biking over there what about me guys
where you guys headed I don't know where
she's going where are you
going everybody red wait r
yeah R is here wait here okay where I'm
I'll take the wheel wait oh oh
yes I was looking
at is everyone here
[Music]
yeah
woo woo ooh wow ooh
oh boy watch out there's a
[Music]
hole check it out
holy you like it you know what I do yeah
it's really cool go all the way around
it's it's it's F it's great thank you
big mold wao what the heck wo good job
good job
work really hard on
this you're you're impressed
genuinely genuinely impressed by
this I love your weapon
War it's over yeah you fall down it's
kind of over shotgun is very op it don't
fall in the trenches when you're in the
battlefield cuz you will not be able to
get your stuff
back oh yeah
during the ho be careful cuz we
definitely won't be able
to in the dang
catacombs oh wow found the catacombs the
catacombs no cats though a
man get you
my thank
F said you stay down you hear that
sir listen to
her here's the
[Applause]
cat I hear a lot of no I don't
see it's okay they're they're up
here how do I take off a weapon mod that
I put on my weapon uh you unequipped
your weapon and then hit modify and then
you drag it
out oh it's not letting me it's like
it's locked
something okay unequipped I think I'm
going in
circles don't love me oh there's
bookshelves around too I just if you
don't mind I mean I don't really know
how I would to say about that cuz you
know I okay oh I fell into a hole do not
fall into a
hole no uh haven't may you avoid any of
that I hav remember which way I went
yeah she's fine she's
living open up
FBI Takashi Kiana is here what are you
hiding oh maybe
nothing oh it's a book where are
you what did you
oh do you see okay come to the when
you're facing the house all right Fallen
where you're at right now fallen I am so
lost oh my
God I
was they're never going to come
here why would you go this was thinking
is this the most impressive thing you've
ever done I think yes I did not sorry I
was trying I'm soring to
M
Oh that girl get out of
here
bad what do you get out of here
whoa oh who okay I opened up a
big here oh no did I punch
you okay
oh it's a
secret oh my God this is a
lot
oh get out of way before I get myself
hurt Hammer
Time Time another
[Applause]
one we just Disturbed a big zombie
party yeah was it a wedding oh behind
you
beautiful you can look at though I just
took
uh I
think loots and forgets immediately what
she took I think that loot is more
interesting for someone
else and I'm full where the zombos
at
zomos I'm very full there's a still a
cooking magazine up here I have no space
for it
oh I'll read cooking
yeah you still got to make us more
delicious food wait I picked it up off
the wall with the one slot but that one
I don't know maybe if you can pick that
stuff up too pick it
up I actually have two
magazines this oh I'm actually done with
the fist I don't know if anybody else
wants to read them
nice I don't really I don't really
aspire to be a a Fister so maybe gy
should be reading those there
yeah it's her Destiny shut up where did
you die shut up G how did you die
somebody behind this wall it sounds like
it oh yeah of
cool whoa who was here before where's
your loot should I do I need to break
any of these spikes for your loot no I
got it are you I'm at the top of the
church
Jes on the Roof oh there's birds at the
top of the church ah that'll do it who
would have
thought get down oh
here
oh this is cool how
climb that bird was the last one
okay wait where's where's the big area
with loot cuz there's always got to be a
big area with loot so we got to find
that maybe up there on the roof you
think maybe how do you get up there
ladder ladder
on wait I think I see something
suspicious that might have surely
there's a better paff but I just don't
have
eyeballs oh gosh oh I feel like I'm
going to fall off the roof it's slippery
no be careful it did feel
slippery I found the loot oh where was
where the loot it's it's in the it's in
the tower at the tippy top I know it I'm
going to need help though cuz I'm almost
out of space okay not sure how to get
there I'm bird forcing my way in right
now with my hammer through the walls
it's very scary up here
oh I think it's okay there's no bades
left but it's so
slippery I'm the jump King what oh
this how did you get there B I'm I can't
find the right way I'm on the roof
though more let
me no I'm not no I'm not without dying
what I hardcore broke my head my entire
leg I oh did you miss the jump I saw
that you didn't see
[Music]
anything I'm maybe from there I guess
over just going to have to be encumbered
B I see now I think
yeah I'm
coming
Oho I'm here welcome to the
stash o what's in it lots of stuff
that I have no room for actually I don't
have much room either but the mega
curtain me c it spans two
stories this curtain all the
clove the heck uh who's learning wiring
electrical I'm learning sort of
okay and electrical trap crafting yeah
that's
of oh I found another Millie robot
turret
level have a friend EXC we're going to
be so decked out for defenses for this
hoorde nice yeah yeah should we start
preparing about now yeah
yeah okay I guess that's it people right
I did you did you take the stuff out of
all the boxes yes you did okay cool EMP
mhm uh how to I guess for here
again lockpicking I probably
[Music]
should
oh robbing some Graves again
ha like that I found another shipping
crate nice that I have no space
for yeah I got to
eat then I'll probably head back to the
house well we do there was one more
Mission wasn't there h i don't have room
for the next mission going home might be
the best idea
then I too am cucumber the max
the trador on the way
so yeah yeah I think they're mad at me
for some reason I'm not sure why you but
why H why are these zombies so angry at
me after I robbed the
[Music]
grave taking a shortcut we're taking a
shortcut WR does that damage your bike
by chance yes well it damages me
I got some you so mad
bro chill I like shortcuts I like cying
too no
problem 50% carrying capacity huh oh you
woke up again didn't expect them pretty
resilient there's so many graves for you
choose one guns knives ammo explosive I
knew you had so loud great work are you
still fighting
FAA no I'm headed
home how how with what how on my on my
my little bike why why why why
why I got to get going I got to get
home stuff to do yeah I'll I'll catch up
to you
now I'll make you Reg read that you took
your mini bike or
bicycle the worst decision I built this
to impress you why I am impressed I'm
very impressed but you don't like it do
you not like
motorcycles they're they're bad are
[Music]
they this is like
this like a married man in the middle of
chist is getting himself a motorcycle
while his wife wants a
minivan why didn't you get a minivan for
our family though they said I don't know
man I just really like them like can I
not just make one of my dreams come true
for
once you can you can you're free to ride
your motorcycle all well I thought you
would be happy about it and appreciate
it I do and then we sh
to the desert to get a bunch of Al
really
fast wait my
turn we can do that let's see uh we sell
all
this okay we have plenty of these do you
want to ride home yes please okay I'm so
happy me too oh no oh oh oh oh oh sorry
sorry I we need robotics Parts I don't
think we do do we
let's I don't think so I'm going to hold
on to I'm going to hold on to them just
in case though because I'm going to be
so mad later on if it turns out taxi
driver I'll leave you a good review
later yes please Uber good review thank
you here
shovel can I have a discount you where
it go I don't think there's really
anything that I need go here I feel like
my timer's wrong
again oh no can someone
make eight metal fences and railings
they seem to be pretty cheap but they
need a forge and I'm at the old house I
can probably make some why why just
thank
you uh because I'm making like a small
Tower and I don't want us to fall
down a snipy snipy tower
[Music]
snip
nice that would be very
useful how did I bring break my leg you
br your leg radiated a little bit I have
a
splint I also need honey again H that's
a comfy right yeah isn't it look I have
a you have a drink to the side so you
get thirsty you can drink yeah
exactly I'm eating right now yeah the
the Uber come it's like the high the
high effort Ubers with like you can play
games in the back and stuff yeah like
you need any Advil any
[Music]
iofin any
mirax what does that one do I don't know
I never tried it wait isn't that LAX do
is it LAX oh yeah good thinking
vibo yeah that is what that would
be I'm getting really hungry
too you know who's also getting hungry
zombies no I mean
IRL zombies getting any banana today no
no banana
banana you just have like 20 minutes I
think to get a snack IRL oh no I'll just
mute myself and eat my Pringles
Pringles yeah yumy you think this is
high enough
snipy Tower pretty good yeah looks good
please please please honey honey honey
honey honey honey yeah honey gotcha is
real honey
gotcha
good
actually meat I'm out of
meat okay the IRL hunger and the in-game
hunger
are unbearable oh no intense H I'm
pretty hungry too I have not eaten today
not at all today or no no birthday well
typically I don't oh me neither but it
is like almost 2:00
p.m. it's like 10 p.m. for me oh and you
haven't eaten all day all day it's
normal no no it's normal it's normal
just kidding it's
normal huh uhhuh no that's just my
normal routine some dang it well then
again if you go to sleep you won't
really need that energy
so I just playing games I don't really
need the energy I need the carbs until
later yeah we you playing games games
doesn't take that much energy yeah just
the mental energy I guess just checking
out some things Gamer's eating schedule
thanks for all the amazing work on it
I'm so glad I have things to say but I'm
waiting till the
end but I've been having a time speech
speech speech speech speech speech
speeech speech it's before spin spin SP
before the raid oh yeah let's do like a
motivational a
motivational thing where you go down the
line on your horse and we like you're
dying not this day
yeah it is not this day it is not this
day what say you you know all that
stuff Brothers
Brothers yes that's right for the
emperor for froto in the ring
[Music]
yeah for Middle her yeah what
you oh huzzah huzzah huzzah I don't
think we need
here we have enough steel for me to make
my gun oh I need to make sure I can make
my gun in time let me get that steel I
just put a 100 Steel in the chest oh
heck
yeah thank
you o
crunchy
ooas I made a rot salad yesterday oh
that sounds really good it was
yum was definitely yum the ladies
enjoyed it
[Music]
call can you take the shotgun shells out
of the chest no I haven't taken them yet
you should take them on the floor too a
little
bit shotgun really quick cuz it's going
to take
time SP is shooting at me she's killing
me what did you do to make her mad is
the question she didn't like it exactly
thank you she was flashing at crony no I
wasn't away and then she kept running
after her I wasn't I was showing her my
bald head do this side here
y it's very blind trust cannot carry you
far the
ammo shot don't worry I believe you
thank you I'm screamer
I
hear got no time for
you
okay oh she's in the
pit yikes I got
you where's every
oh I'm
coming oh the turrets doing work so
cool dang it when they ragged allll it
doesn't mean they're dead I got to
remember that that's not
work this two is birth RP what are you
talking about nothing know I want to
know I know I sound incredulous but I
just want to know what does that
mean I don't I don't
know I I say it GG
say it I know D D they told me to say it
I didn't say it of my own will GG is
always app say what this this Che is
birth role
play wonderful what put on your head now
okay
sorry this needs to be another chest um
be able to do you need grenades yes
please okay I'm going to give you some
grenades gig are you the only one using
arrows I think ra is too I am using
arrows I have exploding arrows but thank
you oh oh oh I'm going to put a picture
on yes take these exploding arrows but I
need to explain to you how to m
knowingly use specific
armor if you are on your bow I guess you
press R you hold R and then you choose
the ammo you're shooting with now make
sure when you're using the exploding
arrow that there's not any funo or so
around who could explode in the vicinity
why not take this beer I have
beer Bo boom boom
yeah I'm excited
yay the stre I hear you do you want
rotten flesh in the ingredients chest or
elsewhere yes in the ingredient I have
the shotgun mod for you you do what kind
of shotgun mod I'll take shotgun choke
mod oh that's a good one you can go
ahead and put it in the mod chest I
think
it okay
nice thank
you some St they're still fighting out
there huh are they I still hear some do
I need to go help now how do you the
piercing I wonder I guess no what are
they
attacking maybe a tree or
something oh a turret oh yeah I think
they're quiet now can't find them
anymore turret's doing
work baseball bat
[Laughter]
oh maybe inside
or in the no huh not in the M could they
be on the roof could they be why why
would they choose to be on the they
might be deep in the maybe or maybe cuz
they're
smart oh I found
it it was in the M oh okay I'll be right
back
heuck fin
armed and
ready okay I made a lot more
gunpowder who who's worried about their
ammo not being enough I think I have
enough,
okay call you think you got enough ammo
yep I have plenty I have like over 500
rounds for a shotgun it's just a lot
sure that's enough you don't think
so it depends are you going to meelee
too well M Mele I'm just going to do my
you know
Club
ammo and in terms of uh armor do we have
anybody with a chest piece below
four probably not at this point right I
don't think so I made it for nothing
where's my
mini I have a forged ahead for you I'm
putting all the boxes all the books in
the Box
the can use
this where's CR right
now should I made my bow pink it's so
pretty yeah yay nice I've already read
the shotgun
M cup
pleas work
good idea decked
out look like got an electrifying
stick it's why are you trying to hit me
with it I'm I'm I'm 5 m away from you oh
sure 5 me is right next to me ladies
ladies I just wanted to show her my
stick I don't understand she's hitting
me with her stick I'm not
okay I'm going I'm going to the whole
house okay I'm going to head there soon
too me too everyone can see my houseing
fence thank you
one but I can get it myself we at the
house welcome back I got it thank you
can you bring us food okay
food thank you what did you want for uh
steel iron uh it's called let me see see
it's called metal fences and railing it
needs iron and
Clay
uhhuh how
many five 10 10
okay I'm
course um I'm going to try to get
some more aloe can I borrow somebody's
car oh is in like wait you can use our
bike where is
it somewhere outdoors in front of the oh
is this it wait yes the the cool one
thank you I will be right
back you will definitely be right back
with that speed yeah K would you also be
able to uh give me any
armor
possible because
I time for this I don't have time for
this do I it's already not yeah it's
already we probably should go I didn't
realize what are the levels on yours CC
I don't have that much time anymore but
let me let me know uh the levels on my
we have enough band don't don't forget
to breing oh I'm going to I'm going to
grab bandaids and healing items from the
the new house
uh so shoes gloves and shoes put be nice
I'll give you a better uh chest piece
too
um oh I wonder if I can make it
[Music]
so we're looking organized
that
[Music]
was
some here it's almost
time doie doy doy
[Music]
doie everything I've
got yeah everybody bring your A game
level four when I have a level for
example in my skills right and then it
says like level one level two and then
the third one even though I have skill
points it's like a lock how do I you
have to uh level up your main stats so
whatever attribute it is level up the
attribute stat and it should be unlocked
as it
a better so for this one okay I cannot
make more than that I I don't have time
I don't have time no problem think we're
good so for this
one and how do I know what the heck uh
uh so it should it's the stat on the
very top of the page so the same page
that you're looking at should say a
tribute whatever oh okay so level that
classic
going back to the original house the
first one that we all found
together it all comes full
circle the house that we built together
the first one we found together I want
to set up like three different turrets
hopefully that'll be good
too yeah for
sure no dos we're going to do
[Music]
it no don't want to break a leg oh no
don't bring a
leg I found a
chicken there food at the old house I
suppose yeah no did somebody pick up all
the food and take it to the old house I
think somebody else got some too cuz the
empty when I I'm bringing all the the
health items but I I didn't bring food
oh maybe I have all of it we don't have
that much hopefully it's
enough cuz I'm starving share with each
other for days K I
have what did I put them in did I make
them oh God oh God oh God oh
God come to me I put the food in the
food box in the old house okay thank you
very
much
[Music]
W here we
go what do you mean here we go I mean
what me here we go very soon you better
get over here almost I'm I'm almost
there oh this
scary you'll be fine snip the
chicken you're heartless where should we
put our bikes I where do you think your
food comes from I put the bike inside
the house if you can drive it into the
house I would suggest doing that okay
we'll do what's abrasion is that what I
have right now oh you need a band
oh yeah okay that helped I think oh my
God it's so well
fortified I wish there was a way to
shoot for maybe a okay in the in the
food box I'm also going to put some
healing kits you fall did you fall my
God she fell she's dead it's
over getting to here I don't know how
okay guys got don't be very careful my
backpack oh no oh no be very careful not
to fall you'll be able to get it out
that
I I'll get it out get it out that's why
I said be very
careful oh was the one thing to not
do stay the
bik I wanted to ride the bike into the
house but I should have just picked it
up
dang it oh God oh God well at least I
guess it might not be able to turn on I
was just testing it out good test I'm
here what are you using again I'm using
a bow do you want to come with me on my
tower on my snipy tower yeah yeah
yeah come here come here all right oh
okay your backpack should be free are
you sure the spikes kind of look a
little TI oh God it work that's a nice
place
a eventually I'll go to the field and
fire
everyone okay wait who's that oh people
right behind you is a dead chicken if
you want
to scavenge the dead chicken oh Jesus oh
Jesus I'm going to die wait we have more
healing right over there I I put the
healing in the ingredients tag
okay God how do I pick this up oh man
Callie call did you fall again we can we
can pick up the it's fine it's fine the
backpack for her I know it's hard it's
fine all her Loops in there it's okay
she it's on the top this time it didn't
fall where's the ingredients chest that
was the plan wait you don't mean at the
new house do you no no no in the in the
in the old house where know it's going
to be very good the mortification wait
did you take the ones out of the healing
chest yes okay here's my bag oh are you
in the old house or new house old house
okay uh
it it's in the food chest wait we had
way more didn't
we uh is that all we have CeCe CE CE yes
oh I have some in my inventory I can put
some more in
uh thank
you we have like
six I think we did I thought
so that's all that's all I
found
else I am so ready maybe I gave a lot
out maybe see hair kit
is crony
here not in the
VC can you leave real quick I want to
build rail
links is
that he had the better shotgun did you
make an even better one no it's just a
level two pump action instead of the one
that she
has y
says crony I'll go find her my
hero she up there she might be up there
oh nice
fence trying but I kind here in the hole
it's kind of
annoying oops she was behind me behind
me can I pick up stuff that I've built
or do I have to destroy
it I honestly don't know
pick it up um but it might it might be
effective who claimed this land maybe
the person who claimed the land can pick
it up only maybe oh who claimed the land
I don't know who claimed the land who
claimed this land whose land is this
whose land are we on who land are
we Kelly is this your land I mean kind
of can you come and pick this up for me
pick what up I
fence in the middle of nowhere a fence I
didn't put a fence down no I put it down
but apparently you might have to pick it
up oh okay hold up I'm coming I can
break it stop stop don't
break I think she got it okay we've got
lots of food and Buffs in the food chest
check out and make sure you have food
and water and heels and everything I
think we're
good no okay let's break
it us can break it yeah you can break it
I jumped too high why you sto
me cuz I wanted call to pick it up but I
don't know if she can me do we have
Towers like this in the back too yeah
because you claimed the land so we that
you have to
like I'm going to get down a bit
more more of a lower
shooter dang this is well fortified yeah
really are kind of broken honestly I
can't survive to any
horde this the SPID it's just there's so
many if we had one more week we could
have iron
spikes yeah yeah we could make sure to
eat bites in the in the chest those will
give you damage reduction how long does
that go on 6 minutes oh okay it's in a
chest
okay four go I will yell before I throw
my fire F okay nice okay
right here we go you can try to drink
recog too it will increase your range
damage but I don't know if it makes you
drunk oh is it starting let's
go
[Music]
fin let's freaking
do they're coming from the back the back
kill back kill back kill
okay I put a trench back there too
there's a
trench oh
oh boy
oh go go go something it hurts you you
are so like uh you're blending in with
with the darkness it's hard to see you
see the green as
well wait why does this make me drunk oh
my go I thought I was immune to this no
the alcoholism it's just not beer well
that's fine I can do deal with this it's
the first time I us I think feel
new oh
gosh oh that's okay that's F I must
watch
out there's a lot of cop zombies
spawning
H that's the problem what are you
arresting us for what did we do what do
we do oh my I have you guys are totally
not harboring a criminal someone got
inside
uhoh that's not good I definitely close
the door not inside yeah close the front
door if you
can you should be close I mean someone
got inside I I'm looking at
May so
far why are they all coming from
there he he going to blow us oh God
I'm going to fix my spes I have repair
kids too if you need some I'm
seeings like a can't
wait how are you trying to do this I
click on it and is
for I have
six walk on the field with
my I'm fire watch out okay still in fire
run they still coming from going to blow
Watch Out w
oh I forgot to bring my
antibiotics can you can you give me back
I'm I'm outside right now but okay
zombies are on the
[Music]
back I'm taking a med break I can't see
oh is that setting our spikes on fire uh
it might be but it it is also helping
Kill the
Zombies
that yeah it is I just one yo that range
on his bomb is
crazy oh is this not what I
mean
cine what is that what even is
that what is
that oh this one this
one I don't want to use that
one where are they I can't see the back
okay it's so hard to see we should light
up the area
yeah you think they're changing where
they're coming from yeah they all want
to come from that side today I don't
know why they're switching it up
yeah it's like they
know nice does it kill them when they
sparkly or oh they're coming from the
front now now you want to come from the
front really really they're testing all
our defens I see how it is
there I
want you're always there
everywhere oh
that's
naked
naked I
think I'm going to slow the Run possible
hello
keeping keep running keep
[Music]
running it's good when you're
Mast can just shoot it right like a
hurting
dog just run in oh no that's easy I'm
sorry pun
you keep running
tell keep rning we need to dye our
armors just so that we can tell each
other apart that would be a good idea
actually spray spr spr oh gosh
they yeah yeah I'm thr a water
oh that's good that's good that's good
that's good oh my arm is
broken
no that's why I'm punching
arm it is getting very laggy yeah it's
so laggy it is
getting spray and
spray this
lag oh
[Music]
God is it the fire
it can't handle L nothing's moving
nothing's moving we might we might die
cuz uhoh oh wait wait wait wait so
we back coming back coming back at least
it's not just
me I going to I'm going to pause on the
fire throw now oh God what's
happening I can't please no fire ah
because
my that makes sense
oh God R the
[Music]
leg do good ridiculous you need a
cast I think I'm okay is a cast better
than a
splint definitely oh as far as
I freak it
away I wonder if this is any
better right now the lag is
I'm sorry I'm punching at
everybody bad bad bre far help
me oh my
God where are
you are you dying there I was dying but
I'm oh
lag lag
lag I'm really drunk right now so don't
walk in front of me cuz I'll almost
certainly hit you by
accident I'm just dring and
pun you get kicked out of the game I
got
no man that was
de This Is How They really beat
us
crazy would be the only way to beat us I
hope you get back in yeah come
back I'm doing my
best oh yeah
me let me know when you're
back thank you
shi get him get him
F when the next enemy come comes please
look when I when I Boop them with a with
the thing they fly away I've seen it
I've seen it it's amazing it looks so
silly is somebody out there right now
can oh they're coming from the side the
side okay be good to loot in between but
not enough time oh I guess so yeah they
might that quickly I think it will
spawn for the first raid it wasn't too
bad I can Loot and shoot I don't mind me
too lagging from too many spikes oh
there's a cop inside no it's okay it's
okay that no pain he already fell into
the oh into the pit a pit he fits into
the
pits how did he get in there I
wonder
okay good he definitely struggling to
load it's like wow there's a lot going
on right now in
Ser right
duct tee duct tee maybe there's a way to
St from the server somehow for season ah
he's
[Music]
jumping
jumper okay there are definitely enemies
with jump long
time I'm so good right
now how drunk are you how many fingers
am I holding up I don't even
know bird bird bird bird bird dead
oh another bird I want's that oh my God
it's on my
porch help that a bird oh no I fell in
the hole the bird wait oh that was easy
I'm so sorry I thought you were zombie
oh
no look for the
Hat I'm the bird who wants to be heard I
have night agent so everything is in
black and white so I can't tell who's
wearing white oh that's
okay oh my god oh wo wo wo welcome back
welcome back thank you I'm so sorry it's
okay yeah come from the side let's get
him bird bird bird bird got
it oh they run through a little bit
without lag I feel like I would shoot a
little bit
better so the blame is not completely on
me it's okay we're doing
good we are we
are back
up thank you guys
might be
concussed definitely good to have L you
killed
yourself no don't kill yourself yeah
maybe do that
seers like in Minecraft that can
collect yeah right a zombie
fall there's definitely like something
like a farm that you can build but I
don't know about if there's hoppers
Chad are there
hoppers need Hopper mod for the game
wait are you in the group for
XP oh yeah let me let me reinvite call
think that wave is
over get in the party than you is it
over the wave is over like four waves or
antibiotics yeah all right now are we
don't tell me what St the music stopped
but it stopped yesterday too and we saw
wait no it's still going it's still
going it's still
going which side is it this time loot
loot you can I did not see any
antibiotics in the chest yeah
already one in my chest next to the
laundry can I have it yeah take it take
it oh the music stopped which chest
my chest is next to the
laundry
laundry H yeah in the basement floor ah
that real laundry it's over is it it's
over you really think it's over the
music stopped yeah no extra zombies that
was we so we are strong they need to
spread them out a little bit
more they always end early and we're
getting like no freaking loot I have so
much stuff
left
H I wish we could get the loot somewhere
I got some loot but it's next to the
spikes right
there oh right yeah that makes sense I
can I can try to jump okay I
jumped giant crat someone someone did we
did it
good
job that looks like a person we did it
we survived seven
days we're so good y good job the way
our Fort is fortified by now is kind of
[Music]
crazy this is foress really really
fixated on how
to fortify this
place they could barely touch us
yeah can't tou this yay
Yi
see do you want to tell us some words
yeah let me blow my
nose don't
[Music]
cry it's okay well well well well well
well well well well well well well well
well well well deep Victory feet my my
soldiers my soldiers yes um soja
boy soja boy tell
him um thanks for playing want to go up
there thank you talking down above
everybody uh I just asked for the server
to be made and tried to figure out they
so I don't really I also asked for art
to be made that's all that I really did
but to be honest people people joining
in you guys made me very happy joining
in the server you know I wanted to do
something more casual
G um I wanted to do something more more
like casual just play a game with each
other kind of thing instead of like
something that was like super hardcore
RP or like a hardcore server seven days
in a row was pretty rough though I think
time we'll maybe space it out a little
bit seven days we die seven days yeah
but it was it was a great time and I am
very very grateful that you guys um made
time to be here CeCe are you good CeCe I
think you're dying CeCe
CE I just just had such
acetic czy no I tried to get some loot
sorry that's okay understandable um but
yeah I'm very happy because um even with
you guys I feel like um why am I say
even why am I saying even with you guys
no you guys how do I say I feel like we
all got a lot closer
[Music]
and I know how to get close to to people
very easily without doing things like
playing games and stuff like
that people together I feel like yeah it
was just fun playing a game together
yeah yeah
yeah let's do it again thank you for
[Music]
organiz wait wait can we somehow take a
group picture maybe if we're on our
bikes we could yeah then
yeah let me get my
motorcycle Kiara's got the cool
motorcycle oh no she worked hard for
that mot oh f
it I don't want to die
no my sweet get out of my spy trap I
don't know how to get out it's not meant
for you perhaps okay excuse me I'm
scared I'm so scared right now excuse me
all right I'll go here here here wa wait
wait wait take this thank you
thank you made it you made it this is so
scary
scary okay I made it yeah
hey all right let's line up our bikes
yeah maybe with the house in the back
yeah yeah that's a cute idea let's do
that can I have my SP
my you have your
what
get might be the wrong that you have oh
no this one's mine
it it it has my storage in it yeah it's
mine does anyone have space on their
bike I do you can get on if youd like
can you unlock oh okay oh wait I didn't
unlock it was the other
one okay I feel like I'm in an
mmpg the cash Shop Mount that is like
super
expensive how about we I think we're at
the wrong angle guys I think if we want
to get the spikes we got to do do like
here get in front of it and then back
into it so right here and then back it
up
down just do not back into the spikes
it's very
important I'm scared okay it's not the
only one without a bike right now and a
bike partner should have brought one
more I think there's one at home but oh
wait I have I have a bike here on my
bike I got a bike oh you got a bike okay
oh okay I think I can get a good shot
like
thisis watch out for the
[Music]
spikes I can't maneuver this
thing wait wait I really can't I don't
know how to get him to position H okay
uh you got to back it
up back it up back it up really bad at
that I'll do a big turn or like oh yeah
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah I wish I could
make the names go
away if there's a way to do that don't
erase her
names they just kind of overlap we all
look the same the turret is kind of in
the way you all look the same never
mind this is really
[Music]
difficult I have an idea why don't you
pick it up and position again and you're
so right you're so right that so smart
Okay easy easy
here oh
perfect oh wait it's locked again it's
locked again okay unlock okay there we
go y oh we looks so cool in my picture
oh
[Music]
my seven di to ride seven seven ride
to ride s days to
ride we are exactly seven right
now Riders
to it's eight right yeah we're
eight wait girls follow me in one line
let's ride into the sunrise
[Music]
in the
backgound whats like thank you
everyone thank
you
y yay
they all
off yipp well technically this is
[Music]
sunrise don't die don't
die to
die I guess that's it fun
yeah goodbye
like bye
everybody be some I will
the oh yeah let's see let's see catch
you later everybody ha thanks for
playing you thank you girls it was a
[Music]
pleasure a lot ofun I enjoyed being your
armor did a great job I'm looking
forward to my
motorcycle next season
yeah next
season yes a little bit different times
maybe yes different probably different
time all right bye everybody M
bye
peace we've made it to the end these
corn fields remind me of like the very
first day when I was dying to the same
zombie over and over again on the bridge
that feels like a million years ago but
it was only
7 days
ago in
reality thank you guys for watching I
feel like this might be the the most
consecutive days I've streamed ever in
my
career eight days in a row I feel like I
never do that I always take days
off so it was very fun and I'm I'm very
glad I've been here all seven
days I do need to recharge I'll be
taking a couple days off and then I will
be back to normal I'm going to do a big
Super Chat catch up and we'll be back
into the swing of things but this was
very fun thank you for
watching thank you thank
you okay I'm going to head out I had so
much fun playing with all of these
lovely ladies it was a great time I love
games like these they really scratch An
Itch in my brain also punching was so
much
fun okay thank you guys bye-bye FW I'll
see you later bye
[Music]