[Music]
up
okay
can you hear me
hey can you
can you hear me does it sound okay
does it sound good
i turned off the medium so you can hear
me well
um hello
does not sound muffled
[Music]
what oh my god
okay okay okay
happy thing the announcement well
doesn't even need to be announced
anymore because i already opened up the
membership
wow wow wow wow wow
membership okay let's turn to bgm.com
hope the museum is not too loud um
welcome
everyone to the kiara
fan club please always
write it out completely because
otherwise it turns into something else
[Music]
but the thing is right now um the
microphone
is mounted to a tissue box
because my uh usual
mic arm is apparently not
fitting suitable for this microphone
so it's not on a tissue box and i gotta
look down to talk into it
maybe i get closer maybe that helps a
bit
welcome everyone hello hello
[Music]
do i sound better please please tell me
i sound better than usual
please it sounds so good really it
sounds so
really i sound so different
eh i sound different
do i sound different
sounds good are you really kiara yes
i am
i don't know what to talk about the
membership is exciting and the new
microphone is exciting i don't know
what to talk about first okay then first
things first let's talk about the
membership
i guess oh my god thank you for the
super chat thank you
[Music]
membership um today
i have started the membership now
um um thank you guys so much for joining
oh my god
i'm so happy you guys joined you don't
even know what's gonna happen on the
membership
um let me show you this
don ah i have uh
created a sheet for you guys to
understand what i'll be doing
basically uh there will be only one
one tier uh the
which you are all joining and so this
single tier
comes with the following
perks okay and
by the way background image is drawn by
my papa
papa and membership content
so you know the usual community posts
like uh
some news some early access information
um some maybe some uh
photos or like you know some some
exclusive things that only you guys get
to see
and um then i made some emotes and there
will be more coming soon you see them on
the right side
um i i made those me are you proud of me
guys
i made those i found my pen actually i i
i bought a new pen and then i found the
old pen after i already bought the new
pen
oh well uh
and um so there's this hello emote
and then there's this shook emote and
then there's the
lovey-dovey emote and then of course i
think i
i only could make four in the beginning
but i think after you get like two
members you can make more and more and
more and more
but in the beginning obviously i had
zero so i only could make four
but i made one for papa because
i thought okay if i can only do four in
the beginning
then one of them has to be for papa
so whenever my papa comments on the
stream which he does very often
you're welcome to spam the popeye mode
as much as you can or when i'm like lost
in the game
and i shout for papa like papa
save me and then you all can spam the
papa emote
and yeah the others and there will be
much much more
and yes i want to make like a dunkicin
emote as well
so for the super chat rating you have
something to
spam there as well and yeah i hope you
like them and for the
for the tears like the new ones are eggs
now i hope this is not too dark uh i was
look tissue box falling over oh my god
gotta be careful um the
i hope this is not too dark okay so you
start off as an egg
then you hatch after one month that
would be so cute can you imagine all of
you who joined today
in one month you will all be hatching
wouldn't that be so adorable oh my god
you'll be like
hello and then
after two months you'll be a real chick
a really hot chick yeah yeah and then
after six months
you'll grow fluffy and strong and after
one year
um well
well let's skip the one year and after
two years
well yeah
that that's just the circle of life uh
i mean we don't need to say that
the egg
ends up being that chicken in the bucket
maybe it's a different
um maybe it's fake maybe it's fake
chicken
that is in in that bucket you never know
there's nowhere it is written that that
is the same egg and that is the same
chicken
no no no no no it does not necessarily
need to be that
[Music]
all right um but those are
the tears that i thought and the tears
not the levels i guess
that i thought of and oh my god i can't
wait for all of you to hatch i want to
see you all hatch
um
[Music]
there will also be votes on future games
so when i'm like oh i don't know what
game to play next i'll let you guys vote
on it
and um i are you hearing me fine when i
when i
do when i'm like a little bit more away
like this and i look up do you guys
still hear me fine
because i'm like trying really hard to
stay close to the microphone but
then my then i keep on looking down like
that and that's not so good but
but here you hear me fine too right
okay awesome awesome
people told me i need a cloud lifter
uh for this microphone but i'm not using
a cloud lifter
and i'm not even that close right now so
it's all cool
i mean i might be generally a bit
quieter than usual but
i don't know should be good should be
good
awesome okay so votes on future games
and member only streams and for the
member only streams
we would be doing some chatting streams
some normal chatting streams
or watching movies together oh i really
want to watch a movie soon with you guys
or teaching german yes yes
i told you guys i don't want to speak
german on stream
it's embarrassing for me thank you for
the super chat i'll read all of them as
well
later later and what was i going to say
crispy yay thank you
uh what yeah teaching german so i don't
i don't really like speaking german on
stream
but and i also don't think i'm a good
teacher so it might not be a really
serious
lesson and it will also not happen that
often anyway
so but i'll teach you some i'll try i'll
try to teach you some gem and i thought
it would be interesting and fun
and so we will do that
[Music]
and so apparently for karaoke
when you don't leave the archive then
you can sing much much more songs
because you don't gotta
uh care about the copyright and stuff so
i'll probably be doing some karaoke
streams on uh
member only as well it seems there's
many songs that i want to sing
that are kind of hard to sing if you
leave the archive
yep yep uh yeah so
i hope um i hope that's a worth it for
you guys i
there might be some more things like if
i can think of more things that i can do
for you guys
um i also take uh suggestions if you
want me to do something specific for my
membership
does my voice sound so different
um so yeah there might be some additions
in the future
but they will most likely all stay on
the same tier i mean i saw some
um other members like not only in ian
but generally in japan
whole life japan some members have like
uh higher tiers where there are no extra
rewards
but still it's just like to support and
i was thinking i don't know if i should
do that like
i guess there's people who would wanna
join that
but i wasn't so sure maybe in the future
if you guys
want me to add such a uh level then
maybe but for now we'll go with this
it will only be one one uh level for fun
good for now i can't talk
yeah yeah i think that's what i needed
to say
and by the way it's the end of the month
now but apparently
when it comes to memberships the month
starts
now today for my membership so
i have like one month from now to
fulfill
those promises oh yeah i didn't say
though how many
membership streams there will be um per
month
honestly i don't have like a
fixed uh number in my head but
i'll try to do it like at least once per
week
and so the membership only streams will
be like
one of those things that i wrote down
there so for example next week
i might watch a movie together with you
guys and the week after
i might uh teach you some german and the
week after
we might do some chatting and the week
after we might do some karaoke
and maybe the week after we could also
play some games together if there's a
game that we can play together
oh yeah and if you want to suggest me
some um
if you want to suggest me some ideas for
emotes you're also welcome to do so
uh however there'll be a lot with my
face on them because i
i drew the base and now i can like make
endless
uh expressions for that so
i'm gonna probably make some new ones
very quickly
and of course a duncashion emote maybe
maybe a light stick emote for karaoke
streams
well my image color should be orange
right yep
anyway anyway
ah yeah oh my sword and my shield oh
[Music]
smart idea maybe my papa can send me the
3d file
[Music]
okay
but what will we use that for when will
we use that ah the shield when people
are
bullying me and the sword is well when
people are bullying me
well i guess that's one way to use them
oh my god thank you all for joining the
membership i'm so happy you guys
like think i'm i'm worth
worth it thank you
i don't mean that thank you
oh thank you so now let's talk about the
microphone congrats on the mic thank you
so the microphone um
so previously i was using a microphone
that i borrowed from cali and she
uh it was a really good microphone and
i'm so
grateful for her uh giving it to me
like oh she's such a sweet sweet sweet
kind person
unfortunately i still don't know what
was wrong maybe some settings i don't
know
but it never really worked that well for
me
yeah and so uh
after getting like a lot of feedback
about how my mic sucks
uh i was like okay well
uh i'm gonna buy a new one now so i
bought a really good one i bought
i think it's called a sure sm7b or
something like that
it's a really good one really really
good
i hope you notice how good it is
and i bought uh an audio in the face for
it and i was kind of struggling with the
audio
interface today uh that's why i was like
oh maybe i can sing blah blah blah
and also i don't have it mounted to the
i have it mounted to a tissue box right
now
so it's kind of hard um but it it
low-key works
i guess it does its job
sounds really good it's really clear and
i think
today we can already compare it because
i'll be singing
a few songs not so many but a few songs
for you guys
and one of the songs that i'll be
singing is one that i sang in the
previous karaoke stream so then you can
compare
how much it changed
um yeah i'm glad you guys like the
microphone
i hope i can do some stuff with that
like i wanted to do
um i wanted to do like the german
storytelling thing
so uh i'll either get that started next
week
or the week after uh cause i'm a bit
busy next week there will not be so many
streams next week unfortunately
but i'll be as active as usual
again the week after but next week is a
bit difficult
[Music]
but well yeah yeah it should be at least
like it should be at least four
streams next week no yeah this
no i think this week i streamed did i
stream and
i think i streamed only i only took one
day out first
but next week i gotta take some days off
asmr
no um no
i i don't wanna do asmr
i mean i don't know if this microphone
would even be suitable for asmr
but i mean this the storytelling that i
want to do
maybe gets like a little bit close to it
because like i'll be like speaking
softly in german
but you guys might think you cannot
speak softly in german but that's not
true
speaking softly in german is totally
possible
you just gotta speak softly
german is not such a aggressive language
as you
guys might think yeah well yeah it will
not be asmr but
i'm not i'm not i gotta be honest i'm
not the biggest fan of asmr
that's why i don't really want to do it
yeah maybe yeah no no
no no
do you guys like asmr that much that you
really want me to do it
[Music]
no i mean
i won't say hundred percent i mean who
knows maybe in the future
maybe you guys can get me to do it
in some way but for now
nine nine
nine if anything
if anything if i'm gonna do that it will
be embarrassing
as hell so that will be membership only
all right so you got that
thank you everyone for joining the
membership yay you are all part of
the tiara band club also known
as kfb
do you like those emotes
i do like them all right
then um should i leave that up here i
don't know
maybe i should
one more thing since i
i thought it would be fitting today
actually my papa
is the best papa in the world so he also
gifted me a new microphone
papa
do you guys remember that
microphone png that i used last time
it got a huge upgrade
please welcome
made by papa kiana microphone
[Music]
see it says holo mike
this is my new microphone that's the one
i'm using right now just kidding
well basically if you could say that's
what i'm using and it says
kiara and it has my bird sticker that
ina made
and it's really long it's really long
but it stops there
it's really long paparika
and he even he even made it for all the
other members too
isn't he the best papa he made five
microphones
so we're all like partner look now
[Music]
today i shall sing for you
isn't this perfect new microphone from
papa
a new microphone that i bought
double double new microphone
wow amazing
yay new microphones
thank you papa
so
i shall turn on my echo
[Music]
do you hear my beautiful angelic voice
echoing through the halls of
the ancient ones
no echo what
what what oh
do you now hear the beautiful echo
uh going through the holes of the
ancient ones now
do we hear it now do we hear it now
yeah okay all right
well now we good now we're good now we
good
double double new microphone here we go
please tell me if the audio is uh too
quiet or so
uh oh damn it tissue box is in the way
and cannot type on keyboard
uh wait i don't know i'm not playing
audio yet
i shall play audio now
test test
wait was that too loud
no no no was that too loud
kind of loud
audio is fine really
okay i'm gonna be checking the chat
while i'm singing if you change your
mind
yes
[Music]
my
me
[Music]
um
m
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
wow
[Music]
my
is
[Music]
oh
bye
[Music]
who here was here last time
when i sang the song and
and do you think it sounds better than
back then
you can do a direct uh
comparison now music was louder god damn
it
yeah i kind of saw some mixed opinions
in the in the chat so i wasn't sure if i
should
erase it or lower it but oh well
it was much clearer oh thank god
you know i really suck when it comes to
technical things
so uh i was really uh you know
things weren't uh going so well every
time when i like buy
something new technical and i try it out
and i do it exactly how you're supposed
to do it it just
does not work yeah
oh well i think i'm gonna sing one more
song
if it's okay oh sure
well let me drink some water
yeah um a bit louder huh
my own microphone um now here's the
thing it's not the maximum now
i don't think that it's so quiet that i
need a cloud lifter
no no no i will not buy i will not buy
one for now
but yeah i'll just turn down the bgm a
little bit then
also it's also an issue of um
due to me using the the
tissue box the microphone is a bit
a bit further away from me than i would
want it to be
so once i get that uh new
arm thingy for the microphone then
it can be super close to my mouth so
that i can almost eat it
[Music]
and then everything should be fine but
i'm i'm i'm glad i think it's not um
too bad now now
what's what's with the a's is kuda in
the chat or what's happening with the
a's
i'm searching but i don't think she came
you guys confused me
so if that was a bit too loud and i hope
this will be
fine
one second
no no
youtube showing me ads again no
no no no no no i said a
well then why don't you say b
if i say a you say b
no
yeah yeah the ads
i got i got myself an ad blogger but
when i do the ad blocker then other
things don't work on youtube it's really
annoying
our next song will be
um an idol song probably
maybe you don't know that song but i
really like that song so i wanna sing it
holiday
[Music]
goddammit
my
[Music]
yay
foreign
[Music]
my
hey
[Music]
yay
is
[Music]
new mix sounds so good thank you
thank you very super chat about that
song i know that song i would have to
check like we have a list that we go
through and stuff
maybe for the next time i'll definitely
consider it i'll check if it's available
yeah the song the song the song let me
let me put it
and sorry i'm not writing it down today
because i'm not singing that much anyway
today
but let me put it in the chat box if you
can't catch it
there you go if you can go for it that
was
yay mitchell holiday from matsura
i hope you liked it
good good uh way of testing out the new
microphone i'll be listening to this
after i'm done thank you for everyone
who is still joining the kiara fan club
thank you
thank you thank you
yeah probably because i'm a little bit
distant from it maybe that's why it
sounds a bit hot i can like
i could oh i could get like really close
like this
does it sound still hollow maybe because
i'm part of hollow life but when i get
so close
i don't move anymore eh yeah
right maybe i can't i can't be this
close right now because my mic is on a
tissue box and then i stop moving
yeah see i can sing like this but i'm
also then
like really uh you know when you when
your back is like the shape of
i don't know a banana
hello life yeah that's why it's a hollow
mic
that's that's why it says hollow mike
just kidding
i i ordered something that you can like
put like a
like as a screw that you put between the
microphone
and the mic arm so then i should be able
to use it for that
yeah then my arm that i have right now
yeah
okay and
i think um i'll sing one more song
and then we'll uh already uh be done for
today i'll just be reading super chats
after that
hope that's okay um
next song is a bit more quiet song
no no no no no no no no no
nine nine nine
uh no i would love to rick roll you guys
but
this is not the right time for it
okay next song is like i'll post it in
the chat
so so that you guys already know
is it okay if i sing a quiet song
oh maybe i should make a number nine
[Music]
m
oh
[Music]
foreign
me
la la la la la
[Music]
m
me
[Music]
i sang a pretty sad
song i hope that's okay
[Music]
i'm not so good at singing this song
because like it goes pretty low and my
voice doesn't go that low
so i'm kind of struggling when i sing
that song but i really love the song
because
i really loved the artist of it and uh
it's just a really
nostalgic and emotional song that i
really like
thank you thank you guys oh i can't sing
such love
songs higher songs are much more
suitable for me but i'm glad you liked
it
oh me too water
[Music]
actually this time i didn't prepare one
i would have to ask my magic quickly
manager are you listening can i sing one
more song
that one that was on the list can i sing
one of the
songs on the list manager son are you
listening
okay he said yup
i mean i sang two songs that probably a
lot of you guys don't
know i wonder if i can sing that one
that one must have been on i'm pretty
sure that was on the last step
pretty sure uh
wait uh but maybe i think one more that
i i know for a hundred percent that is
it okay if you sing one more that i sang
last time
i think i sang that also last time
uh is it okay uh
yeah okay i i asked you guys now
if it's okay that i sing one that i sang
last time
okay then i think this one uh
i also don't know probably this one also
doesn't suit my voice but whatever
[Music]
enjoy
yay
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
foreign
do
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
yay oh man you guys your comments are so
sweet i
keep on looking at them while i'm
singing and i'm like oh
i'm so happy that they enjoyed
this oh i'm so happy thank you
thank you did you like my asca
imitation
i feel like if you want to see it that
way
you could think i look like oscar
langley don't you think
i want like an original black suit
don't you want to see me in a black suit
as well
an orange orange black suit with some
blue and white
accents wouldn't that be dope
[Music]
huh
and now i'm now i'm excited i want to
sing more
manager can i sing one more
thank you okay i'll tell you which
song it is
wait wait wait
i'll tell you which one it is it's a new
one
this is really this is really the last
again it's in a japanese idol song so
probably again a lot of you
again don't know it i'm sorry but
i'm educating you again with uh
good good idol songs
so uh
i never really sang this one
like seriously before so i hope
i hope i hope this one will be good
also my my voice is a bit rough today oh
wow
a little bit will get through it
actually for this song it might be good
if my voice is rough
next song
i put it in a jet
there you go
[Music]
thanks for telling me it's not good
without echo
oh yeah better
[Music]
my
is
[Music]
m
foreign
[Music]
i can't sing the song damn it wow
oh
[Music]
sorry i couldn't sing the song so well i
didn't really practice it
um
could have done this one better we'll
practice for next time
you know this song you have to sing
really aggressively you can't do that
[Music]
it's a really really classic really
classic
morning musume song have you guys ever
heard of
morning musume
my favorite favorite idol agency besides
whole life of course
so now
that's it for uh today's celebration
announcement
stream uh i will do super chat now so
you
if you want you can stay if you don't
want to stay you can leave i guess
one more thing i have to say i told you
guys i will be playing genjin impact
once it comes out i have to say
due to reasons of the
adult world i can
not play it so i wanted to start
tomorrow
but yeah unfortunately no more against
an impact
i came out today i guess so yeah
yeah i was really looking forward to it
but
[Music]
so instead i wanna well i'm wondering
what i should stream tomorrow
um i think we'll stream fire emblem on
on tuesday again but on monday we'll
play some fun game maybe
maybe i'll practice some mario kart
tomorrow
um there's no no helping it
in japanese you say
when something is wrong and you can't
really explain why
you just say
you
all right now let's turn on my ptm
sunshine oh yeah i gotta resume mario 64
as well
uh i'll be doing that too next week so
next week we'll have
mario 64 fire emblem
and maybe mario kart and maybe something
else
now it's
super chat time thank you everyone who
joined the membership today
and thank you everyone who also donated
to today i will read
your super chats i'm i'm really glad so
many of you decided to join my
membership thank you so so so so
so much it really means a lot to me that
you think
i'm worth your investment but
even if you're not a member i'm sure you
will not miss out
on too much i'm just glad if you support
me by coming to my stream
as often as possible all right
where did we stop last time
[Music]
scrolling scrolling scrolling scrolling
scrolling scrolling scrolling
okay i found it
as always you are welcome to spam
together with me
the
thank you for joining the membership
thank you guys thank you
hello hello welcome welcome to kfp
you are now an egg
i hope you don't crack
okay here we go
uh actually there were two super chats
after i already ended last
stream so i'll read those too
thank you
especially when there's japanese names
in between
v gamer 311 thank you quick question
will you marry me just say my username
again at some point if your answer is
yes and i'll get the message and
right after that he donates again
no i am already lowkey married
so i don't think this will work out
but thank you thank you very much eleven
winter flat packaging general pekkalin
general fecklin thank you major people
thank you and mention people thank you
captain pepper jackson
okay i'll stop reading your one one
dollar super chats if you do so many
okay i'm sorry
it's either thank you
today we are blessed by this beautiful
voice show your support and love as she
showers us with her sweetheart
thank you
[Music]
congratulations on getting membership
set up can't wait for a glorious tension
to dominate this world and spread her
wholesomeness
thank you yes let's dominate
the fast food empire
membership for this month that was not
necessary
oh thank you
[Music]
did you see the sexy pretty peculiar
panties
well yes i did
she showed it like for a second and she
was like nothing happened
but i was like oh my god i every time
she shows that part i don't know
how
i see her as an idol and i look up to
her
but when you see that part
i don't know how to control myself i
don't know how to
say no to either
why are you calling me bottom left you
guys look at it and then tell me you
also don't
tell me you know what to do in such a
situation when
the super cute bunny girl shows you
her butt and it
looks that good
we are we are all bottom left okay
whatever
adam caught
what's this application for you sound
amazing marriage when
mary is with you i'm guys i have callie
please accept this but thank you so much
thank you thank you that was not
necessary there is no application fee
for my membership
thank you thank you
[Music]
remember
thank you so much thank you i'm glad i'm
so
i'm so relieved i'm so relieved finally
finally i'm not the one with the bad
microphone anymore
finally i'm so relieved
thank you they know thank you
congrats i will never cancel the
membership oh thank you
you're talented and you're my favorite
creator thanks for bringing us happiness
i love you singing voice
smile streams i love you please don't be
too hard on yourself
thank you i'm so sweet i love you
thank you thank you
[Music]
i can't read my own name yeah yeah very
happy for you
thank you thank you so much i'm so sweet
of you
i'm so glad i'm so happy that it works
and it sounds okay
i gotta listen to it later thank you
thank you
[Music]
yes
brandon you and after you get your fast
food empire going strong i was thinking
your next step could be a line of casual
dining restaurants with a weight stuff
staff of lovely ladies in uniform
similar to your outfit what do you think
i strongly agree but until then it will
still take some time because
um you know it's hard work to build up
an empire
especially when most of the positions
are you
have you guys seen that home page have
you guys seen the competition so good um
i they they took all of the information
that i did in my
uh super chat opening stream
i retweeted it on twitter i think
yesterday or so
yeah yeah yeah looks really good looks
indeed very good thank you for
they even like they bought a domain
right because it was
dot-com so it must have been like a paid
domain
yaya
thank you for like putting so much love
into it i don't know if you're watching
but yeah
that sounds so crisp really thank you
actually if i if i i can hold my
microphone
and then get closer to it
if you want because actually this
position is a bit uh
hard for me because i keep on looking
down and my throat hurts from looking
down
and reading and she also let me turn on
the air conditioner where is it where is
okay why is it so hot in my room
okay do we do asmr duncan
okay i will hold my microphone maybe you
hear some noise now one second
i will hold it who holds their
microphone like this
it must be very noisy oh my god okay
it's a bit heavy let's see how long i
can do this do you hear me well
eh is it no noise
wow nice good microphone
all right thank you shin
well i'm still i'm not doing asmr but
yeah don't drop it
[Music]
please thank you from canada thank you
oh yeah canada
and i'm so glad i got to hear it live
new mic sounds great emotes are 10 out
of 10 cute
hope to become an egg soon i hope you
became one already
thank you so much don't we all want to
become an egg
and then hatch and then become the chick
and then become the big chicken and then
become the chicken leg and then become
the kfp bucket
thank you for the super chats i'll be
reading all of them
don't you all just want to be eaten
someday
i will one day eat you if you join the
membership now
i will eat you one day
become my kfp bucket
i'll be raising you for two years and
then i shall eat you
it's nine
oh my god what is she saying panic
what you don't want to no why not
why would you not want to be eaten
by a phoenix
i don't get you guys i don't understand
what you want from me
thank you thank you after two years
wouldn't the chicken be rotten
[Music]
no because it says special
special chicken kfp chicken does not rot
which in itself is also kind of um
disturbing and concerning but um
you guys don't care about that with
certain other fast food chains do you
you don't care about this with certain
other
fast food chains where the food doesn't
rot after a year
huh i'm just doing the same thing
a true effect
just ignore that fact okay even if you
know about it just ignore it and keep on
eating
kfb employee number nine thank you
so that's what you do to your employee
after one year well i sold my soul to
cali so it's okay
thank you you still get soul to kelly
about your kfp
employee well i mean get the best of
both worlds
thank you hazel berry thank you devil
joker red ram thank you
she sells seashells
helps you more five dollar super chat or
five dollar membership actually i don't
i'm not sure
uh how do i i don't even know how much
youtube takes from the memberships
i don't know do they take the same
amount i wonder
i wonder actually i don't know but good
question
heidi talks don quixote you're german is
nothing to be embarrassed about
it's really cool and beautiful you being
try
[Music]
trilingual shows that you're very
intelligent thank you i mean
see there's a discussion about that if
that's true or not i'm also not
sure i mean i think anyone can learn the
language if they do their best so
it might not be an indication of them
being intelligent
but i i would not say that i'm
completely stupid okay
i am not completely stupid
the wild bear thank you
i'm really happy i'm able to catch one
of your streams although my job prevents
me from seeing you live
most of the time your archived videos
and the times i am able to see your
streams make me smile thank you kiara
thank you that's so sweet thank you
i'm glad you got to watch this one pro
go
red one two three thank you
so
[Music]
of the membership fee too so i guess
that it doesn't
change it's the same i guess
i don't know i forget all these numbers
i should know these numbers by heart
but i don't really care so much about
numbers so
about those money numbers so i don't i
always
keep forgetting them i don't know how
much they take
thank you thank you to mozzarella
relaxing fox thank you nice boat thank
you
so bad
[Music]
sweet and goofy you're the buddy that
can make can put a smile on a friend's
face and the glue that holds the grip
together oh
god is a goose from top gun of her life
ian don't worry though she's
she comes back to life after she dies oh
that's an interesting goose maybe it's
not a goose but it's um
maybe it's a phoenix
thank you shane thank you so much
that's very very very very sweet
kaito thank you while you took my first
super chat and membership goes to you
you really go i can't read today oh my
god what's happening
my mouth is not moving the way i want it
to
it goes to show you're really something
special among the other girls thanks
for always making me smile in love thank
you
so sweet thank you zombie sauce
[Music]
[Applause]
am i the only one who's having these
issues reading names
yeah you're the one who asked who made
the song request i'll
remember it for the next time i like
that song i listened to it a lot a lot
of times when
um i uh when i was uh
younger yeah i wanna sing it i will
check out if it's on the list
that we have oh probably it's it's on
there probably it should be fine
thank you lord kanestra thank you
i tried thank you i gotta go and uh do
the sleep thing now but i'll watch the
archive later
later also you can make an emote that
says crips crisp so we can spam it when
some crispy moments arrive
thank you i'll think about it there's
many things to do but the thing is like
with words
i feel like it's so hard to get the word
in there if it's like three letters four
letters
i feel like it still works but as soon
as it's like five letters
oof how do i get all of that in there
uh
i thought you guys were spamming the the
egg emotes but it's just
at the end of your name because you
remember
was like why are you spamming the egg
mode now did i say something
no you just um you just have it besides
your name now
looks so cute you little eggs
you small little eggs
you're so cute i wanna paint you
i wanna put some color on you like on
easter
you're such an egg you are such an
egg would judge a smart smart baby egg
now you know it will be even funnier if
i play that game uh
heart is broken egg is two or an egg is
broken hardest too if i play that now it
will be even funnier because i'll be
playing with
your lives with your lives i shall be
playing
i shall drop all of you hey
okay next stream will be heart is broken
egg is too all the other way around
just kidding just kidding i will i will
take good care of you
i will be careful i'll um
try it i'll try not to drop you guys
you guys are so so sensitive
i drop you and then you break why do you
break so easy guys
unbelievable
nicole
okay let's move on ex
have my new microphone do i sound good
muna do i sound crispy
thank you for coming muna senpai
luna do you see all these eggs in the
chat we can make some scrambled eggs out
of my members
if you're hungry better not eat me let's
eat my members
let's crack them and then make some
scrambled eggs or some fried egg or
something
yummy okay
hi
[Music]
also joined membership everyone is so
sweet
it's crispy yay i'm so happy
it it has been a struggle with the old
microphone because people
said i i sound like i was using a head
headset but i wasn't
i was using a good microphone but oh
well
oh well i tried thank you
thank you
humor
thank you and kfb staff member reporting
war new mic sounds so great couldn't pay
for higher membership
well there is only one membership so
here ah okay that's what you mean
because there is no higher so you paid a
little plus thank you so much
so this is what i was thinking like um
for the people who want like to
support me more than that one tier
because i only made one
one level for the membership i guess you
can just donate whenever you want
to and i'll just uh
keep it at the at one level
[Music]
foreign
thank you for the songs and for being
you your phoenix fire is a light in all
our lives we'll be here to support you
for it all thank you
you guys are so sweet i love all of you
i want to kiss you i want to kiss you
little eggs i want to kiss all of these
eggs
thank you thank you
oh kissing asmr here we go
i'm gonna fill up
i'm to throw up i don't want to do that
i don't want to do kissing ass tomorrow
it's so embarrassing
i'm gonna after the stream i'm gonna go
into
youtube studio editor and i'm gonna cut
that little part out there when i kissed
you guys i'm gonna
not because i don't like kissing you but
doing like
kissing asmr oh no that's so
embarrassing to me i can't i can't have
that public i'm gonna cut it out
i'm gonna cut it no no no
no you shall not replay that no no no
i'll put the
stream on unlisted right away and then
i'll cut it and then i put it back
kato
too embarrassing yeah those sounds are
reserved for cali
she can hear to my kissing sound if she
wants to
having too much fun here senpai arigato
thank you
prime thank you thank you oh
i discovered the recipe for the secret
seso sauce it's made from tears
listening to you sing
[Music]
that is so sweet you guys are so good at
flirting
seeing as you're playing through fire
emblem have you heard of
or tried language no
i can't recommend it enough for an srpg
oh it's a strategy rpg
to try out also seeing karma from tales
of therapists sometimes
i doubt that it's on the list but
i can check it out never heard of that
one
i uh actually yeah so uh fire emblem is
my first
strategy rpg that's why i have not
really heard of these
before but thank you
peach girl tv energy
[Music]
how do i read that i had that before
um that's that's in in that super cool
lead speak what does 5 stand for does it
stand for g
does it stand for g because it's like
t h3 l i guess that's a zero zero
l zero five it's an s oh the last
okay oh my god how did i not see that
how did i not see that
the last dancing f-o-t-r
thank you the last song actually made me
tear oh what
i guess you're talking about what i said
really
how how is that possible i i i
i'm not that good of a singer oh my god
thank you i'm
i'm glad it uh made you cry almost
thank you your new mix sounds great much
better quality thank you
i mean i mean i mean like i don't know
making someone cry with a song
i think is like a huge um
it would mean that that person is like
insanely
i don't think someone who is bad at
singing can do something like that
i don't think yeah you know when you get
shivers from certain people singing
because they have like some good uh
vibrato or something vibrato how do you
say that
something like that i think that usually
makes
someone get shivers and that may be
combined with an emotional song maybe
make someone cry
but yeah i don't know although sometimes
i cry when i see
certain idol groups performing on like
huge huge stages and i'm like oh
i wish i i wish i was up there
yeah i do have those times and that's
not necessarily because they're good
singers but just because
of what i'm seeing i guess
[Music]
here's my first ever red super chat
you're my favorite whole life member and
i wish you all the success in the world
and on the world with a certain reaper
if i can make a
request for next time could you do a 24
7 cinderella it's an
idol song that will make ya go proud
okay
i will practice it
good request very good request i think
probably someone in her life definitely
sang it before
so i probably should be able to sing
that thank you
thank you
so thank you for giving your first
time to me
maybe you have already also become an
egg
let's all become eggs
very high quality mic nice thank you i
want to listen to it i want to end the
stream and then listen to it
[Music]
not
stop
would be so weird if this microphone
wouldn't actually be
an improvement i would have been really
mad really
[Music]
um sapphire kitten thank you
a new mic sounds great thanks for being
you and working so hard your streams
always brighten my day and i hope you
enjoy them as much as we do thank you
thank you so much it's
i don't know if i said that right
trilogy would be great as a jrpg for you
i've seen that one before i am
interested
it's a fully realized world where
special girls called rey vattiel
can perform magic with songs that
include a language is made for the game
it's a it's an easy game mixed with
visual novel
interesting i'll check it out i've seen
it before definitely
thank you
thank you and crimson 870 thank you
nailed those songs i'm looking forward
to more karaoke streams with your
beautiful
beautiful voice thank you oh my god you
all are so sweet
strong stroking my
my sad ego thank you don't don't do it
too much
i'm i don't know how to uh
you make me blush don't do it too much
don't say too many good things
although although of course i'm it makes
me happy but
it's the ego
thank you out there
wait wait the wild bear said i in the
future i will be expecting hacking into
the gate or will have changed
we'll have to change the world line ah
yeah
i really want to sing it on stream but
um
wow my my hand is feeling very stiff
after holding this heavy microphone for
a while
um i'm gonna try my best to get
the permission for it
maybe one day i'll be singing it
who knows pudding
for those people who don't know that is
the the opening song
of steins gate and steins gate is a
created basically by my papa who
designed me
that's where the connection is that's
why i keep on saying i wanna sing steins
gate songs
or even blackrock shooter songs even
those songs
in blackrock should i also cannot sing
at the moment
[Music]
oh well oh yeah maybe if i don't leave
the archive then i can sing it
let's do that sometime soon
i can't help it i can't
[Music]
819 again thank you for the creation
uh not great what's the word what's lord
what's the word uh
uh hello english english dictionary
uh how do i say generous thank you
thank you for the generous super chat
again
papa please forgive his next costume
draw her in a plug suit
i'm secretly awaiting it too i'll talk
to him about it
i mean he kind of often draws stuff that
like fits that style
so i wouldn't completely um you know
yes it might be possible who knows but
i don't wanna pressure i don't wanna
pressure my papa
and he's busy
[Music]
i've been going for the roughest part of
my life but being able to watch holo yen
and especially you have
really helped me through it thank you
for being you and bringing such energy
to all your streams
oh
dan i'm so glad i could help somehow and
the other members too
please i hope you will feel better soon
and
i know how it's how it is to go for
shitty time i think we all do
and i know at the point when you are in
such a
um situation i know it's
you feel like it's when
somebody says it but let me say it
it will get better i know i know i know
i know
i know i know i hate hearing that i hate
it so much but it will always get better
i know i hate it too never said that to
never say it to me
never say that to me i hate hearing it
but i'll say it to you
it will get better at some point
joey draws thank you
us into your idle health and maybe we
can share ours i'll grab a six piece
bucket for takeaway to snack on for
super chat reading oh not so sweet
some of you guys just write the sweetest
super chats ever i love you
thank you that was the end so i will be
uh
refreshing now let's remember that one
refresh quotient
[Music]
scrolling scrolling scrolling scrolling
scrolling scrolling okay
continuing
oh singing magnet with cali cardboard
cutout would be pretty cute why would
why would it have to be a cardboard
cutout
oh you know you mean like me singing it
to her we could just sing it together
i mean she's more on the wrapping side
but i'm sure she can do some
singing i i'm sure you mean that famous
vocaloid song
magnet
yeah let's sing it with her
thank you
thank you thank
becoming one of my favorite youtubers
keep up the good work have a good rest
of your day music was good by the way
thank you so so so so much
thank you
[Music]
there there's no escaping papa he is
always watching
me
[Music]
i'm happy but also i'm scared
i'm so happy that he's always commenting
and so
active i really really appreciate it
it's
a comment
told him to keep on commenting because i
think not only me but you guys are also
happy when he comments also a lot of
people on reddit
also keep on mentioning how my papa
is like a big part of my stream and like
uh
i saw that one
papa horowitz let it talk
i wonder if he checks out the reddit
sometimes there was this image
of um a certain other beach river
uh being uh like lifted
by that youtuber's mama and then next to
it
was papa
kind of lifting me like a baby but
actually throwing me
in the air
so it was kind of trying to say how i
don't know what was it trying to say
how he treats me as as his daughter
he saw it too
i think he's doing a great job at
parenting
[Music]
he's doing a great job
i really appreciate it i was always
raised with a lot of freedom
so it seems all familiar throwing me
around in the air
seems very familiar
obsidian when are you and your wife
going to do a music collab i really want
to do that
but next up is a really intense
rap battle where i will definitely lose
because i can't
i can't rap
but i will try anyway just to have some
fun with kelly
i'll just have to prepare something
freestyle is definitely impossible i
just prepare something but
probably take me like one week to write
one verse
yeah but we'll have a rap battle someday
for sure
am i saying the name right thanks for
being an unrelenting stream of
positivity oh
this karaoke stream was tons of fun and
definitely gave me a huge boost
really did it
because you keep on surprising me with
these uh statements
i can't believe it i look forward to
seeing your continuing rise
hashtag kfp will rule the world yay k
f b k s p everyone k f p
k f p k f b k fb
yes thank you so much
i'm glad you enjoy my streams i try my
best to be
entertaining thank you joshua be drying
video i can't eat most fast food due to
medical problems but
what are you talking about it's healthy
but i'll support your fast food chain
anyways keep up the hard work your
fantastic chicken
thank you for your support we are a
webby very healthy fast food chain
very
huge donation thank you at first karaoke
stream that was just talking about
ramstein and since then
when alberta tweets stream about to
start i hear a song
here comes the sonnet sister has to
stand for an island
from him i can't uh think of the melody
for that one i i
i i've heard of ramstein before i i
think i know that one that's like
that
and i don't know what hi is that how he
went something like that
it wasn't that see i don't know how that
goes
oh my god but it's really not my type of
music
i don't want to sing it
but uh thank you so much
for the generous donation i really
really really
appreciate it thank you thank you
i wonder if this person is from germany
or so because of
paying in euro and mentioning ramstein
ramstein
v gamer free eleven thank you so it's
okay to marry multiple people in fire
emblem but not now
oh well if i emblem it's also not
possible as far as i know
so no it's not okay amperture
engineering danke
piccola what are you doing out here with
all this booty
double cheeked up on a saturday
afternoon the sun is still out piccolo
tell that to piccolo senpai
yes one day i will sing 99 uh luff
balloons
in case you can't tell you're my
favorite whole life member
i love you thank you
art thank you who's your favorite
morning muslim member and what
generation is your favorite
you're amazing canada hope to hear more
hp songs from you
um from the members that are currently
in there
uh my favorite is oda
because i just oh i love her i love her
singing so much
but i have to say um i preferred
the i preferred morning musama the most
when uh for example tanaka elena
was in it and uh takahashi
[Music]
uh so how did you call that
era again i don't know what was it was
it platinum or something
oh yeah it was platinum oh yeah oh you
guys know that's amazing there's there's
this morning muslim fans in the chat oh
my god how exciting
[Music]
is
yeah it was a good time wear some good
songs
i mean now it's fine too but i have to
say their their music style
changed quite a bit it's very electronic
now
so i like electronic music
but for morning music i don't know it
changed too much
yeah and my favorite group from hello
project was always betty's kobo
and uh smileage you know but mileage
also changed and where is kobo
disappeared i also really liked cute a
lot but cute also disappeared so
all of my favorite groups are gone
i used to go to a lot of concerts a lot
of hello fragile concerts
i'm so glad that there's people who know
hello project
in in my audience that's fun
that's fun
ayaka's english lesson oh my god it's so
nostalgic
uh although you guys remember
oh man that's so nostalgic
wait did i just say the name right it's
been such a long time did i even say it
right
[Music]
um
see other people know it as yada naika
well i know it as balalaika
yeah i know you guys by me singing that
you guys think of yalanaika
there's it's two different songs
foreign
i know both of them but you guys you
guys should know the original
appreciate the original wait i like that
is the original right
funny although i really liked that one
i really liked that yaranaika
when it was uh hyped back then i kept on
singing it
jonathan gutierrez thank you reynold
how can i join your membership multiple
times
um unfortunately that is not i mean i
guess it's possible in some way if you
make a new account and so on
with a different uh different google
play account
but i'm not telling you to do that
please don't do it if you want to
support more then you can always just
like now
for a super chat thank you so much for
your support
brian g thank you
again 24 hour cinderella uh
recommendation interesting interesting
thank you
[Music]
do you promise not to drop me like an
egg as broken hearties too
i'll i'll try my best to not drop you
guys
if you don't drop me then i will not
drop you
let's carry each other wow that's some
deep
[Music]
that is so deep that's some deep
sorry i really slowed down i'm really uh
slow paced right now really chill
i'll be quicker now
tomorrow
250k subs soon really
hopefully it's going a bit um
ever since i started fire and blam it
kind of slowed down
but it's okay i want to play my rpgs i
don't care
i want to play my goddamn rpgs and no
one can stop me from it
yeah it will be my my my is the special
thing about me will be my chat point
i'll be playing rpgs until you all get
sick of me
yes rpgs are the best games
yeah christopher langler thank you in
chat panic thank you
luis diego danke jkh monkey thank you
woke up in time for the last song
congrats on the membership and looking
forward to catching more streams in the
future p.s new mic
sounds great thank you so much thank you
this month thank you soon extra crispy
mike enjoyed the singing very much today
thanks for the streams gives me
something to look forward to every day
[Music]
dennis jairus thank you my throat is
dying
let's see if i can drink and open the
bottle or the other way around with one
hand
blue protocol i played um
the closed or open
ghostbuster i think did i play the
closed beta or the open i don't know
but i played it and as an as a huge
mmrpg fan
and a huge bandai namco tails off fan
i was super excited for blue protocol
and but
huh it was um a bit confusing
here and there
i will definitely give it a try again
when it comes out
but i had some problems with progressing
already in the beginning
it was uh oh i don't know it was weird
and it's so it was like you know how
usually in mmorpgs you start out with
these quests and they lead you through
the world and it's easy to follow
right and then later on okay it might
force you to grind a lot
but with blue protocol i don't know
maybe i did something
wrong but i felt so lost and right from
the beginning in the first couple of
levels already
it um forces you to grind
like crazy and leaves you kind of
i don't know how you say like in the air
uh but i don't know i'll try it again
because i just really like um
i don't mind the grinding itself at some
point but from the beginning it's weird
but um uh they made changes
interesting yeah i'll definitely give it
a try again just because i really like
the art style i really like
tails off games and it's like you know
it's kind of a tails off game as an rpg
and an rpg yeah
okay if they made improvements i want to
try it again
i'm excited and yeah against an impact
unfortunately
i cannot play anymore because of
because of the yeah
things dennis jairus
you sounded great with your new mic i
needed to skip the stream since i was
outside thank you for existing i'll
support you till the end
thank you so much there will be no end
because i am eternal
oh tales of horizon are already
requested permission
it should be enough time to get
permission until the game comes out
because
up until now there's still no release
date for tails of her eyes
but eventually
i hope because i'm a huge tails off fan
if i'm not gonna get permission i'm
gonna cry
but this is all business you know
sometimes things don't work out
sometimes it doesn't work out the way
you want it to be and then you have to
accept it but
just for tails off tails off is like the
only game i cannot accept if i don't get
permission
i'll accept it okay i'll accept it if i
don't get permission but i'll cry
don't worry about the song lisa senpai
sang it before it several times oh okay
okay you mean that uh
cinderella song all right
thank you sadist nicole thank you morgan
mogalo
colonel i always i i always read that
colonel but it's kernel
caramel senpai dankeshin kramputi
tangashin sniktor
nora thank you thank you spaghetti and
pasta
so one more time i'll refresh in case
something else came also thank you again
for everyone joining the membership
thank you
okay i will read the last couple of
super chats saigon
thank you so much this stream goes to
show yago's dream is still alive your
voice is amazing kfc 48.
[Music]
oh you should have instant feedback
enabled for your mic so you know the
quality while streaming
but that is so confusing it's so weird
to hear my own voice in the headphones
like it's usually delayed if it's like
in real time okay but i don't know how
to make that work thank you
and tell your tale thank you you're a
wonderful person full of love keep doing
what you're doing and continue to be our
beloved fire chicken
thank you thank you so much thank you
that's so sweet you almost deserve a
kiss for that but i'm too embarrassed to
give
you guys a kiss again so no jj montalvo
thank you
udon eater thank you
hi hey kia i was wondering if you can
give us your biggest yeah boy
i would very appreciate if you can
thanks udon eater
yeah boy eh my biggest one
i hope i don't uh disappoint you but
three two one
wait how do you say it do i like say it
longer because you guys in the chat are
saying it like yeah
boy how am i supposed to say it
yeah boy as long as i can okay but which
one
both of the words have to be long how do
you say it
[Music]
is that how you imagined it
i just a boy
no this is how this is how it stays take
it
take it or leave it okay
hope you're happy thank you for the red
super chat
relaxing fox thank you shin sanji
skipper dankeshun
is very young i finally caught up on the
stream of the cute phoenix continue the
good work and stay amazing
thank you so much thank you
thank you i really appreciate your
support
alvin lim thank you soon we can finally
listen to you voice in hd and it's so
cute thank you for joining her live and
bringing all this love and energy to us
i will be here to stay all the way and
never unsubscribe
thank you i'm happy to hear that
a loyal employee i see thank you
maybe one day your picture will be on
the wall
that yeah boy was worth it ah
thank you wow double red super chat just
for that yeah you get another one
and get another one yeah
why okay that was weird
that was weird but thank you you don't
need to send another sippy chat by the
way
that's just my reply to your second
super chat
dear lord you guys in your request
dear lord
can't make you guys happy i already sang
it before you guys keep
asking for it
[Music]
thank you yeah
one day one day full version
it's 99 uh
famous german song
99 and the english one goes a little bit
different
yeah 99 red balloons
and why is it red balloons in the
english version
in the german version it's just just
balloons
that is a balloon discrimination i must
say
balloon discrimination
thank you how about my faith
thank you just happened to tune in after
a hard night of care
giving for a relative with cancer oh
dear
well how do i say otsuka sama in english
all the translations don't seem
appropriate for me
in to me in english but good good work
i guess it sounds wrong thanks for
lending your phoenix warmth to all of us
viewers and for working so hard i wish
you all the best
with your unofficial marriage thank you
so much
thank oh thank you for the hard work i
don't know it sounds weird but thank you
i i respect what you're doing
for your relative i think it's a good
thing
very good thing
thank you thank you for introducing
impact to me you're welcome i would like
to play it too but
just you go ahead maybe mage thank you
miner 49er two zero one
dark souls or bloodborne not really
my thing yeah uh
cali will definitely play that i think
but
for me not really my thing i like more
like you know happy games
with uh bright bright colors
chef jefferson have you and other
hawaiian girls
consider playing minecraft if another oh
yeah we already talked about it today
actually uh but i never played minecraft
before so first of all i wanna just try
it out one time by myself
and then we i think we're gonna make our
own server whole live en server
and uh because like the whole live japan
server is already so
filled and busy so we're gonna build our
own one i think
but of course i will not
er let people take the chance away from
from me
to be introduced to the whole life japan
server
by the one and only
that is my dream that she will give me a
tour
through the japanese minecraft survey
hololive minecraft server and then we
shall go on a journey together
so we will have the english uh server
and the japanese server i think
that woman is too shy it's okay
i will get that woman to do it for me
i like how they it keeps on uh some new
people coming into the stream
and then they're like surprised by the
new microphone quality
welcome am i takana
or maybe i'm someone else
[Music]
new microphone yay and
thank you
watching your stream while listening to
some dojin albums will you play some bad
games in your future streams
what do you see as a bad game what is a
bad game for you
i would prefer to only play good games
but if there's a bad game that i like
yes i will play that too
huh what would be exoge what's a what's
a bad game though getting over it
well yeah i might as i might do it at
one point one time sure sure
i i mean if that's a if that's a
if that's a bad game then i did already
won before oh no
the the egg is broken hardest too
wouldn't that one fall into that
category
so yeah one every once in a while i
wouldn't mind uh playing those kind of
games you know
it's definitely exactly
see oh yeah yeah i don't mind i don't
mind if there's a
some that look fun yeah luciano
can you give us another asmr kiss please
too
no nine
no way especially not
for for two us dollars
not saying that you can like buy my kiss
but you cannot convince me
with that
nine
fine um not saying
that a bigger one would make me do it no
hella embarrassing
try it i'm just kidding
okay we have reached the end again
i love the streams and the new mic
sounds great thank you have you ever
played
pso2 what
what's pso2 what does that stand for
chat
what people asking for canada a fantasy
star online no i did not ever i never
played that before
no no never never
and but interested yes i would give it a
chance
okay uh see when i don't turn it off i
never
i never get to the end but let me
let me uh open it
one last time
because we got a few more
okay there we go gotta go quick before
there's even more coming in
i think what you mean i think i know
what you mean the one where i said i
think i know what you mean but then it
wasn't but i know what i thought you
meant but then okay it's this one okay
now i know what you mean thank you
thank you six six screen runners seventy
seven danger shin
v gamer three eleven i'm a little tired
but can you just pretend i said
something super wholesome and emotional
oh that's so sweet thank you so much
i'm so uh wow i'm so touched by that
thank you um thank you i don't
i can't believe it um thank you
we don't either thank you yeah boy
i quick quiz quick quick thank you
have you played the dot hack games
before they're one of my fav i've heard
a lot about them but i have not played
them yet
another game we can play together seraph
thank you
what are your thoughts on the star ocean
and valkyrie profile series
also never played those and but
also would not mind giving it a chance
thank you luciano dojin thanks
is that uh but that red super chat is
not
specifically asking for a kiss
he's just saying he's from russia he's
not asking for a case are you asking for
a kiss excuse me are you
dennis jairus are you asking for a kiss
i am asking
for it
i hope you're not i i hope you're not
wait i'm trying to check the chat if
there's a reply
i can't say one
have you guys seen one i don't see him
replying
it's so fast now uh
oh my god my eyes are dying
i don't see it oh i saw him say yet
really
really he said yes why did he say that
where did he say that give me a
screenshot
eh damn it i have
i have summoned it i have done it to
myself
but if i do that the stream might get
banned or something i've heard of asmr
streams getting banned
well i haven't seen it oh well let me
end this
and then i'll see what i can do
it i would not mind
i would not mind that is actually very
nice because he leaves me the option of
not doing it
we'll see let me get to the end of this
that was very nice oh we're very nice
what a gentleman
blue slime thank you and shiny ajax
i already explained this before kylie is
my wife
pekura is my idol oh my gosh
no i'm thinking you're asking for kisses
god damn it
i hate it shiny ajax thank you
psycho fire to uh twenty free duncan
i'm not sure leave david alone
okay so last i i'm refreshing for the
last time everything that comes after
this
will not be red
so
yeah why did i stop here
tris boa macho b
danke dennis terrace
thank you um
hmm
[Music]
did you hear my neck crack
please tell me her dad
[Laughter]
i'm a bit stiff i'm a bit stiff i could
use a massage
okay now everyone is laughing
[Music]
okay that's it that's all you got
i hope that's satisfying tentacle seven
three three six thank you but this kiss
counts for all of you who asked for a
kiss okay
i will not do another kiss
maybe one more because there's a bunch
[Music]
ah no more kisses no more kisses
no more kisses
i want to listen to that neck cracking
again oh i could do neck cracking
asmr i could do that
i'm good at neck cracking
i could do a neck cracking asmr
let's do it yeah wait let me
put down my microphone maybe i can do it
again with the other side
okay you probably heard a lot of
there i'm sorry
okay
oh that was just one i wonder if you
heard that
could be pokemon
yeah that's just the life of a stiff
phoenix who could definitely use a
massage no
kisses just pecks and undying phoenix
neck cracks that's
that's like a like a poem that's almost
like a poem
you wanna hear my fingers crack oh
[Laughter]
they keep on coming keep on coming i
honestly have some problems with my neck
i
i really have some real issues with my
neck
yeah well
thank you guys for coming today let's uh
and let this end now it's been a long
time of
chill super chat reading
hope you enjoyed it and welcome again
everyone
to the kiara
fan club which sounds like a really
lame name until you realize
what it stands for
kfc
but no i can never say it out loud
it is always kiara fan club so
see you tomorrow i still have to think
about what time to stream
and uh blah blah blah
uh i will probably be in one of those
later streams again
where probably a lot of you are not
awake as usual
ah thank you i really had fun thank you
for joining and
i'll make some more emotes as soon as
possible as well
and we'll get started with the member
streams
as well as soon as possible nope
that's it i think i had my fun
goodbye kiss no no
no one more than question
okay everyone who joined
chiara fan club
thank you
[Music]
hope you enjoyed the new crispy updated
takanawa
bye-bye
no more jesus never again
never
[Music]
embarrassing
you