[Music]
[Applause]
this is
assistant
[Music]
[Applause]
questions
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
wow
wow wow wow
she started
wow
[Music]
hmm
well
[Music]
I don't want to be human today
I didn't want to be human yesterday ever
can it just be cat
[Music]
wow wow
mood bird
oh I'm not a dog I'm I need I need to be
more like when I see a bird I need to be
like
[Music]
you need to make funny ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
hi
I'm cat
[Music]
ch
uh
[Music]
um yeah
wow wow
um
I ate two croissants today
[Music]
too many no that's that's a good amount
of consoles
[Music]
I speak
I I try to speak bird I don't know if
it's successfully bird
yo guys
[Music]
tomorrow
but I finally I finally literally like
one minute before the Stream
I finally was able to
finally
set a date
for my wedding with the air sorry I mean
[Music]
for the next whole talk episode
same thing nah
[Music]
and finally
it's about time oh my God
28 months oh for a moment I thought you
met 28 months since the last hello talk
episode
yeah
thank you thank you 28 months
28 months
ah so we're gonna Read Super Jazz today
because I have to read super chats
why on Earth is the Twitter icon
the famous dog
why
so confused is Twitter or not
a bird platform anymore but a dog
platform
[Music]
oh
late late April Fools
that's quite a bit late on April fools
it would have made sense today it makes
no sense
but yeah I heard yeah I heard why
uh-huh personal gain in Charmed if you
use your magical powers for personal
gain you're because you're gonna become
an evil witch
okay
so honestly not a good thing to do
saying
I just watched the finale of the first
season of charm damn I did not realize
that I think it was the last episode or
the first of the second season I think
it was the last episode of the first
but I didn't realize that that one
episode you know where they go into the
future and I will not spoil it much but
where they go into the future and then
Phoebe is you know
well
not in a good position
I don't think this episode would happen
so early on I thought that was way way
in the future my God that back then when
I was younger that episode was really
scary and I was so worried but it was
kind of really good like a good season
finale and really thrilling
subscribing ah everybody should watch
this show yay original chance here I see
I'm not the only one
that was Royal TV show from 25 years ago
well some people honestly could get
upset and I mean nowadays there's surely
people in here who haven't watched it
yet and maybe want to watch it just
because it's so old so they haven't seen
it yet
so you know
oh now I'm in the second season hmm
haven't been like binge watching much
though like mostly like one episode or
two per
um
day or every second day
[Music]
I fall asleep so fast these days which
is a good thing
okay start watching and then
with my katos
oh lunchbox
too don't spoiler me I really don't
remember anything I mean I remember I
remember the like single episodes
uh content once I see it I'm like ah
this episode but I don't remember it in
like that order
that I'm watching it in now the actual
chronological order which is really cool
to watch it in the chronological order
yeah yeah
oh hello
meow meow meow guys
how's it going Sabrina the Teenage wins
that was good too yeah yeah
talking cat well
The Charmed Ones could probably make
their cats talk too if they wanted to
with a spell
but they don't need to rely on a stupid
cat oh did I really just say that
[Music]
some tacos for dinner
um
I yesterday I made tuna pasta you know
with some leftovers from the pizza and
it turned out so good
the pasta turned out so good
I even have leftovers
I didn't even want to make that much but
yeah
jenma is preparing for the stream
tomorrow
[Music]
ah guys yesterday
oh God it already feels like two days
ago
I went after that stream I went to sleep
as fast as I could I had to eat first
but after that
while I was still eating I threw in a
melatonin already
I tried my best to fall asleep as
quickly as possible
and I still I didn't get much sleep I
had to get up at 5 50 am
and then the recording was at six
and the first the first recording was
still okay-ish around the end of it I
already was like feeling groggy
and then second recording I'm like oh
[\h__\h]
all right I'll try that
yeah
and then that ended and I'm like oh
finally I'm afraid
and then they say oh oh we have one more
short thing to record please
and I'm not even the only one we're all
like yeah what what there was another
thing
at this point already in like four hours
passed
it's almost 10 am
um
[Music]
but I I I I don't need a coffee machine
I even have instant coffee here for like
my mom when she visits
but I don't want to drink it it's
disgusting
[Music]
yeah but that was just a short one it
was just like like 10 minutes after that
so around 10
I quickly throw in
one pancake because I'm also really
hungry and then I went to sleep
after that
oh man
that was so exhausting
oh well I didn't even it was I was tired
I didn't even sleep that much afterwards
slept like maybe three hours after that
catch up on some sleep
[Music]
you will see you'll see
we will see in the recording
I don't know I tried to be energetic I
don't think if you don't know the story
that you would notice that I was that
tired and sleep deprived
I don't think you would know
[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
we were actually trying that before the
stream and then of course and my brother
was like of course you can just install
it normally I don't know what you mean
I'm like no I am telling you it's not
gonna be that easy and he's like I'll
just have to why it would have to be
like a game from five million years ago
to not be able to play it on Windows 10
I'm like you don't understand
that will be problematic and then he
like we didn't have time he had to go
somewhere for
um apartment check
and then I started trying to install it
and then of course problems popped up I
couldn't just I couldn't install it but
I couldn't
um start the game
yeah
so I tried to look for Solutions but
they didn't work
and then my brother came and then he was
like oh whoa whoa
so it didn't work
I'm telling you all that's why I needed
your help
when he tried to fix it but we didn't
have enough time
maybe maybe
tomorrow he said he'll try again
um
[Music]
no we already tried that compatibility
we already tried that
um
but play blah blah it's annoying
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I already
tried
[Music]
that give me some time oh we'll make it
work we'll force it
[Music]
I know
I know I really tried those things
um
[Music]
already dried just buy an old PC
um
[Music]
yeah well
it's not that urgent anyway I have quite
a few quite a few plans
already for this week I'm already booked
out anyway
why
why why why why does it make you go Doki
Doki
what are you talking about
why are you making things up huh
[Music]
playing some sport
oh
[Music]
I really should just become a cat
anyway I want to finish
[Music]
um
today
and I will do whatever it takes
although I don't know how much is even
expecting me
I don't know if I can do it I should be
able to do it
I should be able to yeah
where what did we last read
who knows
[Music]
ah
I have to read
Fire Emblem
part a first
already read ryza
[Music]
yes I did oh no there were no super
Chats on the riser
I should turn the ones from today off
too
[Music]
okay
I
turning them off
all right oh baby
ah
Metroid
part one
I think I already read that
[Music]
I think I did
yeah one and two because two I read
first and then one I read last time um
thank God okay
um
[Music]
okay
uh thumbnail
[Music]
this one
with the yellow eyes wow
hi
guys
tomorrow card opening stream
with Jen ma but only her hands
no voice only marvelous she's just
acting as my hands because I thought if
they send it to me it won't come anytime
soon probably and I won't know when it
will come anyway
so
[Music]
um
she will be my camera she will be my
hands and I will react to it and maybe
we'll be even luckier thanks to
her magical hands no I get them all like
she'll send it to me after they're
opened
um
[Music]
because I'm drinking lemonade right now
I found some lemonade on an Asian
shop
I feel like such a weeaboo
[Music]
I was like oh why not
ah you can hear the ball
feel motion
[Music]
what
ah I hate you guys
[Music]
um
tastes like cotton candy
[Music]
let's go see
I'm still playing with ball what is the
balloon
okay let's watch the short that I
uploaded yesterday
um
mmm
yeah it's good yeah I thought it would
be nice to have like a
compact short version of it as a short
so I asked how carrot can you please
make me a quick shot thank you
and then
and then I got an extra
for some reason now I have it came with
an extra that I didn't ask for
[Music]
came with a corn pelation
I haven't watched it yet
we can watch it
[Music]
wait
yeah yeah that's exactly what it is I
didn't hear it yet but you probably
heard it and then you already know
I just need to
Usher
what is this I might I will upload this
as a YouTube short too
probably
all right let's do this
foreign
corn
ER
corn corn
corn corn corn
mice mice
ah
sometimes it sounded like coin
that was a corporation that was my joke
by the way Concord said I have a
compilation of you saying corn do you
want it and I said you mean a corn
pelation
[Laughter]
I think I said corn maybe one too many
times
in that one
that was a lot of corn kind of corny
Corin I was dancing Corin but now when
you listen to all of them
like one after another then it doesn't
sound like corn anymore sometimes
[Music]
corn like croissant it doesn't it
doesn't work because it ends in a in the
end
Castle
[Music]
on
doesn't feel right
corn
corn Club
corn cob
wow
[Music]
hi okay so now that we put that aside
wonderful wonderful wonderful
[Music]
we will now commence the Super Chat
reading believe it or not
corn
[Music]
ER
yeah hey it's only been half an hour and
10 minutes of that was loading food and
then five minutes was meowing
hmm
[Music]
new season of marble what the [\h__\h] is
marble
[\h__\h] is that
and how why do you assume I watched such
a thing
[Music]
Mrs maisel well you you wrote it
absolutely incorrectly
you wrote m-a-b-e-l
[Music]
oh
you missed the meowing yeah
I don't watch it yet is it already out
oh my God [\h__\h] I want to
I want to
put it in the freezer
I want to have it
in small bites no no I can't once I
start I cannot have it in small bites
but
[Music]
um
okay okay let's read
you guys will be shocked by the amount
of super chats I will read today
[Music]
um
Tech
thank you
thank you for the recipe
[Music]
thank you for the big support broken man
thanks for the pinky
[Music]
that was a very like um
here was really happy you also felt a
nostalgic heart tugs I felt that to
start the first are free yeah I did hope
you enjoy the game in your own time and
I'll be enjoying this last summer
Adventure at my own pace yeah
I think that's good then you won't be
like stressed to finish it on time like
we already always
on the same like or not not
be spoiled by me and so on yeah yeah
you're 40 hours in oh
[Music]
um well you probably also
go for everything very slowly to get all
the details soak it all up like a sponge
um
I think I did um decent progress in the
first stream actually
y'all
okay
[Music]
um
wait
I will I will give myself a little bit
of a
Advanced start here oh
[Music]
so
Pandora
[Music]
snatch what does that mean
I understand thank you for the support
thank you soon
thank you
oh thank you guys
old fairy tale monster
[Music]
may I believe
thank you for the pinky
[Music]
uterus more like uterus
is a quote by Iron Vader in a phylum
stream eight
are you
are you exposing iron Veda for something
he says
to have it there forever
to have it be memorized forever
I said that in Discord
you're just a messenger I'm Invader why
did you wrote that on Discord and not in
my chat eh why you tapped Out of My
Stream anyway eh why any of you tapped
out y'all should be tapped in
let YouTube know that you're watching
the Stream
[Music]
um
uh-huh okay
well you may some of you may have some
legit excuses
but I don't care
I don't care
I need to turn on the lights it's
getting dark but it's already getting
darker way later than
a month ago
[Music]
I stepped on oh
laughs
I stepped on egg
you will not understand why
stepped on an egg
[Music]
don't question it
it's Easter is close there are eggs
everywhere guys don't question it
they're questioning it even though I say
don't question it why don't they listen
to me don't question it
so high for the collab oh yeah well let
me tell you the participants if you want
um unless they suddenly decide to not
participate uh it should be
me Cali
huh
[Music]
are the participants
and yeah I know this
I am nervous quite a big group yeah I
think it's a good amount I feel like 10
like a full member
count would freak me out more
I'm I'm glad if it's not too many
um
oh my god when you say Kali and then
fauna one after another it sounds like
California
that should be if they ever need a
couple like a group name for collabs it
should be California
[Music]
what if Callie and fauna go to
California
that would be amazing
California mind blown
now if you never noticed yet because
normally you never say these names one
after another these two names
specifically
um
a rare pairing y'all
[Music]
on Friday yeah July what ah is that
is La in California
[Music]
I guess I live in California
I just I should not because I've been
there before
[Laughter]
what do I know
[Music]
silly tension no you silly
California Girls
[Music]
they're Unforgettable
pink hair green her
um
cuties on top
I think would fit Cali well too with her
whole shower vlog
like calcini with a cowboy hat on Kelly
[Music]
I will see myself out now
okay
um
foreign
this is important what is the best corn
to put on pizza I think I reacted to
this and then I was like what do you
mean best corn there's only one corn
what do you mean and then you guys told
me about the uh white corn and also
about the glass gem corn and I was like
whoa
yep that was very
very enlightening for me
[Music]
um
did you guys know there's one more type
of corn did you guys know this one is
called popcorn
[Music]
it's white too and it's really like you
know crunchy
um
yeah it's kind of nice with salt or with
with some
I don't know caramel what's all
kettle corn yeah kettle corn good tool
indeed
yeah
candy corn candy corn is a really sweet
type
of corn
that you see a lot in a certain season
that's around a Halloween
for some reason it's just a grows more
during during Halloween
um
yeah it's very exotic it has very
tropical colors after all
a corn dog
may sound to you like it's another
um
under category of corn turns out it's
actually just another under category of
dogs
that's where people often make a mistake
it's not a corn dog it's a corn dog
yeah yeah
they bring you all
okay can we stop falling around now
[Music]
thank you
Kevin
it's an excellent questions
oh thank you for that's not a rainbow
really but it's like all kinds of colors
and crazy
[Music]
did I read this one
this one I read didn't I
I kind of already reacted to this
yeah the ark survival one
do you want to play with a cat how about
Ark survival uh-huh
uh sure sure thank you again AL
[Music]
um
I will move on from that now Memento
Islamic fellow sent a a proper rainbow
and you were almost not interrupted
amazing
oh no need to read out loud why why are
you so kind to me are you Jesus
okay I'll read it quietly
[Music]
oh
you can have either of those numbers
[Music]
okay I will read this out loud after all
I've never been the type that stays in
one fandom for too long
I thought that same would happen here
because after a few months I began to
climb out of the rabbit hole but out of
all the channels I Still Remains up to
one
I killed orange I know
I don't mean really I love you I know it
may sound a bit odd but I've never been
a committed fan of anyone
damn
but then kiwawa
pre-home life I never bought any merch
memberships super chats went to another
country for a concert or even bothered
with a Twitter account
I love you because you love me
and when I discovered this kind-hearted
strong sincere hilarious compassionate
hard-working businesswoman who runs kfb
has amazing voice
and gorgeous dance moves
I want to cheerful her
I only stayed and kept watching her life
because of you and I'm glad I did it was
an amazing journey and a love for look I
look forward to what the future has in
store I'll try to do my best to keep up
thank you Wawa I love you
where are you where are you
you're so sweet
makes me so happy and so
so sweet where are you where are you
where are you
are you here
are you not here today
[Music]
is there I can't see it
say one more thing scream I saw you hi
thank you that's such a sweet message
and then it makes it really special
knowing that normally you don't really
you know get interested and hooked
to people like that
and then you got
you know to a point where you only had
interest left in me thank you
I love you
[Music]
I was your first two oh
nice
um that's so sweet
um
that's a really sweet message thank you
so much you can take even number that
you like
um
and congratulations on your
on your uh
Revival
um
[Music]
did you guys see moonme is gonna reveal
a new outfit this week oh this week
right oh
oh oh
I know what it looks like
[Music]
I like her outfit very much it's very
mummy
um
and then today was Kelly's birthday
I'm glad she got to do the
something special
after all
I attractive rip her up makes you
concerned oh
ah
yeah that was sweet I was watching on
standby
and I like you know I mean she probably
just did it because of like maybe budget
reasons and Studio reasons and all that
that's why she maybe kept it more simple
this time
um but I like it this way I think it was
for I think others maybe agree that it's
nice to have something more chill and
loose
and
life and not everything like super
perfect it's like refreshing to have
something like that you know for the
first time in a while well do you know
how to book I mean I never really
properly tried
[Music]
no
but I I mean that's I I've told her I
may have told her to do that
because she told me beforehand
that she will ask us for dance moves and
then I was like um how do I tell her a
dance move
without being there in person so I
thought of dance moves that maybe
um
could be recreated
just by saying one word
oh
yeah and her dancing knew how it's Vogue
so it was a good reference
[Music]
yeah I was I had some more ideas on my
head but I just went with Vogue because
she was already saying that was
difficult
[Music]
Tana
is it right that you just
recently played Sims one
is that correct
[Music]
we have Raiders you did
okay
I'm trying to get my CDs to work
um I might message you
after lunch asking how you did it
because I'm having some issues
I've got issues
[Music]
no I can't see them on hyper jet I just
saw High Raiders how where are they
coming from
[Music]
where you guys from
I never see that
[Music]
okay well finally admits
uh-huh welcome
[Music]
see I never get because of my streaming
time I never get raided by Hollow
members
[Music]
I do get randomly rated by a non-hollo
member non-hollo people though
thank you
[Music]
why was I
here
I'm baby
isolated lower yeah
Martin
[Music]
I would say give Medford Fusion a try
Upstream since it's on the VC it tells
you where to go a lot it would be a good
test to see if you'd enjoy the
side-scrolling games the size 12 games
thanks for more final intention also
that 99 luck with falling animal guard
earlier that was great
I don't know about playing that
[Music]
what we see you mean you mean switch
online
if I have to download or buy anything
black
it's a switch online okay hmm
but I don't wanna
I don't wanna
[Music]
it's fine thank you
I just want to be a cat
um
[Music]
domini is so hard to drink out of
because if you when you drink
and
[Music]
you know how it's easier to drink when
you don't cover the whole thing with
your whole mouth yeah and leave it
little live a little space on the top
yeah but the hole is so small that then
almost no liquid will come out
this this bottle's hole is specifically
is really really small but then when you
want more
and you put off of your your whole
mouthful that's also I don't know it's a
little
um
stupid
[Music]
and the marble I mean that's another
issue
that's a whole another issue oh my God
the bottle looks like a skull
[Music]
from a certain angle
huh well anyway
[Music]
um
this movie is indeed very cute I've been
cuddling much with smoothie and chunky
wonky
[Music]
I I should have gotten myself less cuter
cats whatever that means but I I should
have because
even after many years
I still can't get enough of my cats guys
[Music]
whenever I see them I have to touch them
and once I start touching them I can't
stop touching them
I just
pet them endlessly
count why am I cats so cute
[Music]
um
how tragic yeah
foreign
a nice problem to have
shave them to avoid Temptation I will
never ever ever ever do that
you have 50 first date syndrome of them
[Music]
no I have two million first state
syndrome with them
[Music]
they'd get cold exactly quickly anyway
this one's done
mmm
I could never shave them no
no
okay next is Diablo
open beta
which doesn't have many super chats so
no problem oh I'm tired guys why am I
also tired for [\h__\h] sake I need to
become a coffee drinker
[Music]
my name is
why am I so tired but okay this this
um
night though I also couldn't sleep well
because you know my brother was sleeping
here
and my cats also got noisy
so I woke up so first I woke up
sometime I like after sleeping for four
hours and I woke up because I had to go
to an island meeting because that was in
pain I could have forced myself so often
I just forced myself to sleep more
but
this time I was like nope nope nope nope
I will call now
so I went to adult meeting I came back
and then even though I was tired as [\h__\h]
I couldn't sleep anymore after it took
me like one hour to fall asleep again so
I lost an hour
then it felt like two two hours or three
hours later
um I woke up I woke up I think a couple
times but I woke up one time when I
noticed my cat is moving it was meow
meow meowing and I think my brother was
awake and my cat was meowing at him
asking for food and I was like what what
why doesn't he give her food when he's
already up to make her stop but he
didn't and he later said
um
well
you're the mommy you have to give the
food I'm like well he would have given
her the food she would have shut up
and I could have slept normally
because
you know she does that when I'm sleeping
she wakes up sometimes and she's like
meow meow meow food please and then I
just try to ignore her and then she will
go back to sleep after a while but when
there's someone awake
[Music]
she will be a little bit more
you know
Unstoppable
[Music]
um oh God I'm so tired
hmm
so I woke up too many times
at night and that morning
[Music]
kind of tired but it's okay we'll we'll
get through it
my cats have an automatic feed up for
this exact reason then once I always
they always have Kibbles but you know
smoothly ones
um wet food specifically
and I was thinking about getting a
specific wet food feeder
[Music]
but you know
I might get it I was thinking about that
before I left to Japan because it was
making me go crazy
um
you have to however always fill that one
up before night time because the the
cooling will only work
for night for one night approximately
so I can only ever do like one
[Music]
uh feeding at a time
yeah it has to be cold so the wet food
feeders are
kind of special
[Music]
foreign
you have to cool it ah
I need more energy
ah
but maybe I just need to take a lot of
vitamins
so I was looking for it and I mean most
most automatic feeders are just normal
ones but there are some
some
for wet food
[Music]
ice bucket challenge
Over My Dead Body
I did that once in my life
[Music]
when it was popular
what a stupid idea
remember when everyone was doing the Ice
Bucket Challenge
[Music]
I did
it was cold but it could have been worse
because I've I was I was not I wouldn't
say I was like fully soaked
I think I was like
partially soaked
but it was cold it was definitely cold
[Music]
all those Trends back then
now those don't really exist in anymore
now what you have now is your stupid
dances on tick tock
that are you know it's always always
different dance apparently but you only
really know about this kind of [\h__\h] if
you are on Tick Tock thank God thank God
thank God it doesn't infiltrate the rest
of the internet too much
hmm
[Music]
aha
extra life why are you calling me cringe
[Music]
Road
oh
my God is
me me me
[Music]
thank you
I need to do some time outing
I don't I don't think I ever did
planking I don't remember what that was
[Music]
Captain meow
foreign
[Music]
exactly what it is
okay next next so we're reading simple
chats from Diablo stream
[Music]
sir 956 Vanishing for the pinky
can't stay to watch for long due to work
Miss kiwala but sheesh so happy playing
Diablo's Necromancer is a good character
to play hopefully I can drop in
Midstream while at work again but if not
I hope you enjoy playing the apples
well thank you it was so good it really
was good I'm looking forward to the
actual release
um
although yeah I don't think I'll play
Necromancer than even though it was fun
I want to try something else because I
feel like Necromancer is such a
mainstream choice now because
everybody's like an incremental is the
coolest so and the strongest everybody
comes from necromanta
hi
okay what are you doing here
and as I said I wanted to give that
option to someone else because if
otherwise everybody goes for Necromancer
and that's not good we need a balanced
team no I'm doing it out of like
the goodness of my heart and me wanting
to have a balanced team so I give the
Necromancer to someone else who it fits
more to thematically okay
okay yeah
[Music]
yeah I'm just consider it cookie yomu
game number one
player kiwawa
[Music]
let's do druid
or sorcerer I don't know thank you
anyway aliera works
in the monster Envy duncano Mike Duncan
the monster Envy again the monster Envy
Duncan
next already temporary 67315
foreign
[Music]
the skeleton jittering is a bug
shouldn't be showing in town
[Music]
I feel so lucky that I'll be meeting you
at anime boss and all the uh yeah that's
this weekend too yeah the fire in my sim
can heart princess heart as on your
debut the happiness outshines me being a
little nervous first time doing a great
meet you at school oh first time oh
don't worry
I'm very used to
first time meet and greets
so
yeah maybe you should write down some
questions you want to ask me
in this private environment
[Music]
yeah yeah
ahead of time otherwise you'll be like I
forgot what I wanted to say you should
write it down
but also please consider that there will
not be endless time normally it's like
what three to five minutes
um I don't know how much this time but
probably around that three to five
minutes
so maybe practice a little bit
to see if you can squeeze it all in
[Music]
I only had two minutes well it depends
on you know
the
convention or the system
for my birthday meet and greets I gave
everyone more time
as much time as possible
[Music]
okay yay so look forward to it I'll see
you there be careful to not get sick
until then yeah
[Music]
yeah and maybe wear orange
customer support Johnson temporary
Duncan not little donkey thank you GM
Lemmy thanks for the pinky thank you
your enthusiasm dedication and positive
energy have been a constant source of
joy and inspiration to me for two years
now thank you for everything PSU fancy
dress is my favorite outfit in all of
her life and four plot is my favorite
cover oh thank you
oh yeah I use the four blood fan art for
the thumbnail
looks really good right it looks fitting
based
I gotta say like uh I'm recently I just
felt this today before the stream but
I'm recently like uh
I know I have the luxury of having many
different outfits but
it's been a while since the last one and
I'm kind of like um
I don't wanna see them anymore so
where's the same you know what I mean
maybe it's different for you guys
but for me
I want something new but it will still
take a while
[Music]
I've got nothing to wear exactly
yeah for real for real
that's how I feel
nah
it's like in
um
foreign
[Music]
I want my next outfit the one from last
year
but we're getting there
we're getting there I'm thinking now is
April
Maybe
end of May
[Music]
if we're if we're lucky
maybe
um
it's not that far away anymore but if
you consider how it should be 2022 hmm
[Music]
foreign
I wish I could just go shopping buy new
clothes put them on and say yay
[Music]
it's making me fall asleep too patsy huh
slap face wake up koala
whenever
[Music]
and James McPhee thanks for the pinky we
understand the struggle Tango thank you
I think that's about the
the eShop closing
thank you thank you
thank you thank you for the pinky thank
you for your sacrifice stand so now that
you have bought it you have ensured it
will be re-released for the switch
I mean I already knew
beforehand that that will eventually it
must happen how can they not
especially since wasn't there like some
statement that they're not planning
a new console
yet
so
that means chances are they are going to
make
more and more
um remasters for switch
feel like that's a lie
maybe they're just trying to distract us
and more ports
they always say that
oh
yeah I mean
they can't say anything until they can't
say it so yeah
but Martin you don't really have an
uncle who works at Nintendo right
[Music]
right
because it says you have an uncle at
Nintendo I doubt it
everyone has one of those it's a very
ancient joke oh why is it from people
who claim they have secret information
that they're leaking and they say I got
it from my uncle at Nintendo
probably uh-huh
yeah I got an uncle at uh Nintendo too
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and then
the Pokemon company and a PlayStation
why the [\h__\h] is there no what's it
called
e free
[Music]
this year they canceled this big event
right and they're not even doing it
online this year I mean I wasn't gonna
really watch it but whoa
nobody wanted to go
[Music]
what do you mean no one cares about you
free anymore surely many people do
Oh you mean the the the the game uh
companies don't care anymore I thought
you meant the visit like the normal
watches
[Music]
they'll just do their own events
oh that's kind of sad hmm
I wonder if they'll ever try again
because if they don't care this year
they probably don't care next year
[Music]
yeah I mean PlayStation has been doing
their own right and Nintendo has been
doing their own
[Music]
I don't know about Xbox what do they do
yeah stay to play
hmm
I do it too
not a hotel
[Music]
um
but they can still all come together in
the game awards right that was that's
always kind of cool
[Music]
at least one thing
that's also Riggs dull
[Music]
how could they not let tonic win
[\h__\h] cats
[Music]
about
um anyway
um yeah
I was like when I saw those news was
shocked
that big event
go bye-bye very sad
[Music]
Xenoblade 3 did not win it is rigged
um
[Music]
Summer Games first why
I mean why why would they like
not why are the companies okay with a
newcomer event that no one knows
and didn't go for one that already has a
name for itself and is hyped and all
that
yeah
and then it's cheaper
okay
did they have to pay a lot of money for
e-free
to be showcased
[Music]
damn
not like they don't have the money
game companies but okay
all right well I'm looking forward to
that I guess
um
stay a while and post chat
still while and listen
we're done with the Diablo super chats
now we're gonna read the super chats of
the super chats literally
[Music]
foreign
because why not
it's also not many though
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chat I'm
two years old
how time flies you truly saved my life I
wouldn't be here if I hadn't found you
you drive and passion inspire me to do
better for myself I will continue to
support you while I do my best to make
sure I'm here for a long time love you
thank you bye
oh
[Music]
that's a long time thank you for staying
with me for so long
for the sweet sweet message I'm so happy
and I could help you and that you found
me thank you for finding me
thank you it's Destiny Rowan Rowan's
destiny
big kiss to you love you too please
continue supporting
forever
yeah Forever YouTube algorithm yeah but
it was your choice to click on it
um
hmm
asion
um
[Music]
for the pinky my body is still trying to
adjust from Japan but it was probably my
favorite trip ever oh really
is it that Germany
foreign
did you not go to Germany
maybe you didn't go did you go to
Germany
ah maybe I didn't
because otherwise it would be Germany
[Music]
otherwise it would be Germany
I don't think I'll ever have this urge
to travel again if not for you yet
another way you changed my life for the
better now back to the normal kfp shifts
I'm glad I can make you guys travel
traveling is fun
I just looked up like uh because like
you know when your phone when you swipe
to the left it tells you like recent
news
[Music]
and like really weird often but
but it was telling me the flight plans
for Austrian Airlines for summer for
like holiday destinations which one
which new ones they added and then I
just checked in general which ones they
have
for direct flights
um
and I got really curious I wanna go on a
trip
I want to go on the four day vacation to
a random nice
cheap European destination
[Music]
cheap not cheap
I mean don't worry I don't think I'll go
in April or maybe I will no but I I
[Music]
want one place I was looking at which
isn't even uh uh wait no no it is it is
it is Europe even though it's like down
there
um
but it's like so far but I think it
belongs to Spain
one of the places I looked at it's kind
of cool it says it's warm for swimming
all year round
[Music]
so around where Morocco is
one of the uh Spanish Islands I think
[Music]
yeah coronary Islands
but I don't know there's many cool
places I could go to
I just wanted to be
[Music]
in in a in the reachable distance
the wind Island wind Island
[Music]
pretty rocket what do you mean window is
it very windy I don't want it to be
windy
[Music]
coronary islands are perfect for our OG
Hollow bird why
[Music]
technically Europe even through is on
coast of Africa yeah yeah coast of
Africa
[Music]
is also possible but I feel like a lot
of people go to Malta for partying
because Bob
Cannery
it's not me though I'm Phoenix
[Music]
oh my God iron Souls
you should yeah everybody gets normally
with a job vacation day so you should
take some vacation days and go and go on
a trip go go go
go go
Kiana
[Music]
vacation
um
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah right it's really late now huh
going to Singapore this June oh
Singapore
never been there
what about staycation eh I'm am I not
constantly on a staycation by working
from home
[Music]
more or less
going to depend September to meet a
friend that sounds great have fun
September is still freaking hot in Japan
though so be ready it's so humid
foreign
[Music]
today I hope it's not too late can I
take a phoenix burger here is my money I
want to get Burger in driving through
because Kiwa will put me in the usual
room
should run while drifting away from Cuba
well you better turn on the
you're a Beat
bgm as well while you do that
[Music]
ah Phoenix Burger
not too bad you made your order at
kiwawa's office and not the drive
through counter
you stay here
you know what same you will stay right
here with me
no drifting away
[Music]
Al thank you for the pinky and some more
of red one too not a again not a rainbow
but an attempt was made
boss I finally got your message let me
try again you care about your friend you
want to make everybody happy and
laughing enjoy a good time with everyone
do you like romance do you want to get
to know your other partner better
no actually I don't like romance at the
moment
[Laughter]
you can enjoy it with your lover or
friends or play lonely like me lucky you
haven't sent me the game you need is
Deadspace free
why
before I leave the Super Chat I want to
communicate with every kfb if I leave
the Super Chat of the friends any kfb
I'm sorry and want everyone to know that
I respect our boss and Eric FB oh don't
worry about it
carrots just the game we play what
scream scared Justin betray do you do
you
do you feel the same
you're trying to
change the lyrics up to you
it's just a game yeah perfect music
Perfect lyrics everybody go listen I
always respect so much I never got the
lyrics wrong yeah no no those are surely
exactly the lyrics
I think I must
reject you again I'll
I don't think that really has anything
to do with Romans and if it even if it
did I'm not really
interested in Roman's games
or Romance
hmm
sorry I guess there must have been some
miscommunication
sorry Al but thank you
laughs
[Music]
yeah like visual novels and stuff no
generally I don't really care about that
are you here
ah did you just call me a chicken now
[Music]
you little chick
no
oh I'm tired
[Music]
and I will sleep now
that's right I mean yeah
[Music]
I'm tired
okay
[Music]
um I read the superchato
okay
I was driving but listening to the
stream and kept hearing shot in Florida
which got the song from the musical
Avenue Q
in my head oh I don't know that also the
songwriters for Avenue Q worked on the
songs for the musical episode of Scrubs
oh that was so good that was like such a
good episode I love the songs from that
episode
foreign
[Music]
I was so lucky to see you on day one
yeah Lucky Chicken I was one of the cafe
shown yeah
yeah now you can have my face on your
file
everybody can have your face on their
file now
exposed you were amazing and beautiful I
screamed so much with that day I lost my
voice but it was worth it hope I get to
see you on stage again I was so glad you
went to see Unica I made my day also I
heard from one of your streams you want
to do and add for your album
one or two things about billboard and
yeah
I wanna I I I wanna see
what's possible
uh
[Music]
um
I am I I had to run to see Unika because
it's just once every hour right and like
I was like
I went there
and then I
I missed the timing of one giligiri
so I was like okay I guess I'll have
lunch first so I went to eat lunch
and through that I skipped I guess one
more
but then made my way for the next one
and then
and then I ran
and
I was like on the opposite side of the
crossing but I had to cross several
crossings that all had different timings
for the
street lights for the light thingy
assault oh my God it was like oh
literally I ran and the moment I arrived
on that like Corner that's when it
started
just in in time
why did the kiwama cross the wow wow wow
Street
um
perfectly timed at as if it was on
purpose
and then
you know it only takes what a minute
so I ran and I came all the way for that
one minute thing and then it was over
and then I'm like well what now
what now hmm
just walked away
hmm
[Music]
it was cool though
I hope maybe even though it's expensive
I hope maybe we can do something
I don't know
I don't want to
uh
you know trouble you guys too much but
it would be really nice
in a good advertisement spot because you
hear it from miles away when I was like
still
[Music]
um
eight or ten minutes away from it
walking distance realistic distance
I heard it already
but I heard like something else I heard
like uh K-pop trends
on the billboard I heard it I didn't see
it yet
I was walking towards in and I was
hearing it hmm
[Music]
yeah it's really loud
um
[Music]
foreign
yeah
I mean if you live in Tokyo then you
understand how significant that
or how famous that spot is if you don't
if you just came there as a tourist and
you may not really get it
but let me tell you it's a very well
known place that's for sure
come on two months
[Music]
my mother
no
[Music]
merch with a meet and greet Lottery will
fund and add like that fast
yeah but I don't think I can do it like
that like logistically speaking
um
so yeah the idea was maybe do a GoFundMe
basically
I don't know I'll ask management what's
possible once we get a little bit deeper
into album creation
[Music]
yeah anyway thank you pong for all your
efforts thank you soon I'm glad you had
fun
[Music]
foreign
I understand more Japanese than I
thought if it wasn't for you I don't
think I would have been a skin to learn
a new language but I'm growing more
confident each day thank you for sharing
your passion with me you're welcome oh
you were in Japan too
and in Osaka
and what avaji island
damn
I don't know about the island really
sounds like you had a good time
give me her I'm happy for you
yeah hope you had a good time maybe you
even saw some Sakura
[Music]
kiwawa studying Korean series is
inspiring as well
I'm very serious about it now y'all
[Music]
I'm so [\h__\h] tired
thank you guys
[Music]
awesome mood
I finished those super chattels too
next is
Metroid Prime part free
how the [\h__\h] do we wake me up
can't wake up wake me up inside and wake
up
[Music]
call me
and wake up wake me up
[Music]
ah
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
Festival Austrian
falling to the temptation of corn but I
held back I believe corn will not
Triumph corn has no hole to My Immortal
Ashi this is a Warhammer joke
hi Kiana well hi to YouTube right so
free I don't get the joke but you should
have known you went into this
of the commitment of knowing that your
joke will not land with me so that's
honestly completely on you
yeah
[Music]
anyway thanks for the little tip on your
painting
soon the Jolly Rancher thank you for the
birthday
I wouldn't really say I am an employee
more like a visitor from afarland ah
I remember you
hey and I just wanted to let Kiana know
she's really cool and nice and I
appreciate what she does and what she
stands for thank you Kiana your true
homie
thank you very much I think there will
be more instances where you can see me
even if you're not an employee so look
forward to it and thank you for being so
nice and welcoming to me thank you
[Music]
potato cat95
um
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
did I ask you where
I think I did because you talk about the
sauna culture
did we just talk about sauna culture
after that because I know I reacted to
your super chat but did I also ask you
where and did you say in Spoke
it was probably in school again
it's okay there's no need for me to last
again
I lost my ski gloves somewhere how do I
get company reimbursement well
well
if it isn't the consequences of your own
actions
no company reimbursements will stop you
lost
while skiing that is not a business trip
don't [\h__\h] me lies
trying to deceive me unbelievable
can't be done concerned the camera
creating great victory in Duncan
thank you guys
[Music]
this must be a joke
was this a joke
because of what we just said before
this person's asking for permission for
a family trip we're going to Europe and
in spook for a day any recommendations
[Music]
it must be a joke
and release you could sequence break the
game and get plasma about the spider
ball
I had to jump on parts of the wall but
those have been removed from real I
think I saw this already
let's jump as soon as you landed on the
planet
damn but like in order to find these
kind of things out you already have to
like look it up somewhere right or just
spend hours testing these things out
just play it normally for [\h__\h] sake
thank you
very much nonetheless
[Music]
that's my favorite part
who's my favorite part
since you mentioned not getting any
bounties here's a bounty for you but I
don't even like Bounty the chocolate I
don't like that one
foreign
no one does well I'm so hated we never
hate coconut yummy too
thanks for all the one more time the one
with the engines and the cute animal
loves to appreciate you boss thank you
so very much no Bounty though please
give me KitKat or
or
Twix it was also fine Twix is great Mars
is like okay Snickers I'm not really
interested on
actually oh yeah milk Away really yummy
too
but I think we talked about this before
that like certain
of these bars are different
and
uh n a compared to Europe I think
yeah which ones was that
[Music]
foreign
yeah those were different
[Music]
weirdly
done
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
oh
that's sweet Nathan cotton thank you for
the pinky don't apologize for such a
tangential word from the heart are often
what need to be heard the most ah I
think yeah that was about alcohol and
all that
um
thank you very much Bruce Jenny Lee
Duncan unit
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
nice
um
next one has
a bit more Super chance but that's the
last big one and then like three more
small ones
oh let's do this
[Music]
um
sorry guys I don't know
I think when I don't get
sleep in one go
um I get [\h__\h] up and also
when I don't have a nap before the
Stream
oh no I cannot give our energy
[Music]
I hate people who tell me to go to sleep
early because it doesn't have [\h__\h] to do
with that as long as I get a decent
amount of sleep so shut up
hmm
it doesn't matter also I'm an adult
I live on my own I have a job where I
can make my own schedule so I can decide
when I will stream and when I will wake
up okay I'm an adult
I don't need to sleep early
okay
also that recording the thing is I
didn't know the recording time until two
days before and then I already had my
stream scheduled and I already knew that
the stream on the day before would be
super long so don't blame me for that
[Music]
yeah I it doesn't [\h__\h] matter if I
sleep eight hours
but sleep at 3 P.M at 3 AM versus
sleeping eight hours but sleeping at 11
PM
doesn't matter okay
[Music]
yeah I'm not working at nine to five so
whatever
[Music]
she's sassy
not taking any of your [\h__\h] now
[Music]
oh good part good part
thank you
[Music]
boss I'm doing a lot of research on your
stream I found a terrible truth you
don't like horror games
where'd you get that kind of information
from
crazy
I don't want to face it but the truth
doesn't speak
instead the recommendation has to be
changed alright horror games are not
recommended from now on yeah
[Music]
yeah you see what's coming
do you want to go to beautiful island do
you want to see two girls solve puzzles
together
you can also invite your friends to play
with you I've accepted the game you need
is Resident Evil Revelations 2.
thank you
I I think that's a horror game or a
thriller game
anyway this is the last one do you want
a good story did you want to see cute
girl do you want to see them fighting a
monster do you want to explore unknown
world I have accepted the game you need
is blue reflection okay out
finally
how did it take you so long to finally
give me a recommendation that I am on
board with
I played blue refract through rule I
can't say it but I played it before it's
on never played the second one though
but you finally
[Music]
that's so proud of you you finally
understand my taste
[Music]
second is a lot better
um
[Music]
well I'm not gonna stream it but you're
finally getting it
yeah his algorithm is he in AI is he
a-i-l-l
hmm
[Music]
yes
achievement unlocked good job L yes good
job a-i-l-l
[Music]
wow I'm so proud of you you finally got
it right
[Music]
now you just gotta go in the same
direction okay
don't
go back
move forward okay and you can't go wrong
if you move forward
[Music]
into the same direction
what do you mean question mark what do
you mean
what's hard to understand
no
are you purposefully misunderstanding me
[Music]
I think he is
go go straight go straight go straight
go straight
[Music]
oh my God
thank you for the pinky balling yo I was
balling I was Panic Ballin thank you for
watching the Metroid Prime play through
thank you
soon
okay
for the pinky here is your Omega pirate
Bounty my lady nice Victory the Carefree
space Federation Branch thank you again
with the Bounty but I forgive you
because you I didn't read super chats
until now so how could you have known
thank you anyway thank you
no
[Music]
yes
for the pinky
ignore those people your wonderful
fabulous kind of amazing kind and
amazing
who cares maybe too much
I believe in you believe in yourself
thank you for the sweet support
foreign
[Music]
I hate these kids they always step on my
grass I am not old I'm just saying I
mean I can be cool too at my time
Michael Jackson beat it so cool oh no
I'm not I'm oh no I'm getting old oh
don't worry I'm listening to Mozart
I'm more behind in terms of music than
you are it seems so don't worry you are
just right here
[Music]
you have to leave early so I'll just say
now it's been super fun watching you
play this I'll see the certified camera
reading another great game in about also
love something maturity on your art tag
that might make you smile thank you I
did see it and it was really beautiful
thank you so much for the support please
keep on drawing
and goodbye
Jacob's attention come cobbler thank you
soon
[Music]
this part hits so hard
it's so good so good
[Music]
[Laughter]
yo
so good
miserably happy dance
you can do it we believe I did it thank
you I did do it
thank you it was suffering but we did it
thank you for believing
if we're staying there so long
foreign
[Music]
I know it was frustrating for me so
surely it was also some somehow
frustrating for you guys thank you for
watching nonetheless
[Music]
missing you for breakfast thank you
thank you love you too thank you thank
you thank you very much
thank you for the words of a chance
whatever you decide to do you have never
disappointed me ever I'm so happy you
came this far happy with tears I am to
see my Oshi play my favorite game oh
it's your favorite game too
love you boss I'm sorry
so frustrating but my ocean is tougher
than this guy let's be rid of him yeah
[\h__\h] him thank you
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you guys in the chat thank you
the bottom down
[Music]
bottom
can I sample this in an original song
it's old enough I don't even need to ask
I think
let me uh because I just titled this
track Mozart one I don't really know let
me ask my friend she knows everything
I'll send a voice message
hey bosses this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
bow
[Music]
perfect
I know I could just ask Shazam but that
would be boring
[Music]
I think my friend my friend will be
thrilled to receive this
is
[Music]
it would be so cool because you know
I've
I've the Kpop idol group I've released a
song like previously where they sampled
some famous old Melody
and that was like literally the
catchiest part of the song
[Music]
in their dance break or so it was a
sample
yeah so if you change it then you know
it would be really cool
you know
[Music]
sorry I'm so sorry this is so good
okay
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh my God so I can't this is a problem
once I start playing this kind of music
I can't stop I can't stop don't worry
Gerald I wasn't done with your super
chat I just got my mind interrupted
[Music]
oh
my God
[Music]
okay let's move on
take a 47.
oh wait no I did already move on I'm
sorry did I really not give a kisu well
but you got one now that one was for you
right because I felt like I read this
already
did I because it's again about Bounty
that could says nice job cute Bounty
Hunter here's your Bounty for
eliminating the Metroid Prime now maybe
I didn't and it's just another Bounty
chat
the Carefree space Federation
Impressions deal we have medical timkins
on standby ready to retreat your current
fingers with feeling kisses Ah that's
more like nibbles probably but yeah my
fingers were very cramped
it's in Chihuahua
Pro Gamer having little chickens on
standby to fix her hands after string
that's so cute little nurse chickens
Ohio
[Music]
good good very good very good good job
Mozart that was pretty decent
foreign
[Music]
for a beginner like me you know who's
not used to this this kind of game you
know I think I did good thank you
thank you Lord thank you soon
[Music]
ah Bronze Age pepper said watching your
journey of branching out genres to this
class it gave me the same feeling as
watching your portal gameplay proud of
you boss thank you
[Music]
thank you for the pinky hey boss who
made it we collected the Bounty for the
Metroid Prime so how much will be our
cut of the bounty for real
was it worth it what what reward did we
get monetary reward how much
how much
how much was it
also does Metroid and I make sure this
Samos get any cut of the game sales huh
I'm literally making a game about her
hopefully she got a cut
up
it's paid an explosion not again oh no
oh Samus please don't accept these Shady
offers anymore ever again
[Music]
became winner nice shooting game
exploding thank you
I will miss the ball shape it was a good
shape to be in
it's almost like
it's basically a really tight fetus
fetal fetus
fetal fetus fetal
fetus positions
fatal position
[Laughter]
[Music]
great job on beating the game thank you
for being so sweet
wow
[Music]
thank you for watching
throughout
stream staying until the end
ing soon
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
all right this is two parts apparently
all it took you a while to write that
yeah you did it I knew you could do it I
know it was a very frustrating fight for
you but I'm so proud of you right now I
need to stop this now
like yeah I know never gives up thank
you so much I'm not sure you love this
game as much as me but thank you
playing it anyway
I never thought it would happen to be
honest I love you no
no sudden sudden kokuhaku I also naked
dog is up for all the big backseating on
for calling your pizza oven a waffle
maker
you know the back sitting I needed and I
obviously needed it thank you so much
for the help and sorry I maybe didn't
you know give it enough love as it
deserved from your opinion but yeah I'm
glad I could make some people happy
playing the game
thank you so much you you horny little
[\h__\h]
hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
croissants
[Music]
um
thank you for the pinky
[Music]
uh comment Angel proud of you for
continuing fun fact by sheer coincidence
the design of Medford Prime during the
last cutscene is extremely similar to
the main enemies in Fusion which came
out the same day as Prime what
I would think
release two Metroid games at the same
day
Oh you mean same day but like a couple
years before
it was really the same day
[Music]
Nani
completely skipped N64 and they wanted
to make up for it wow
wow two games to buy
released on the same day Dem
but different stories and all that right
learn something new again
the more you know
Kevin don't listen for the words of a
chat congratulations thank you
indeed congratulations were in order
after
that
hard hard work but it was it definitely
took so much less time than expected in
that last episode so I'm so glad
and I don't know how I would have taken
that kind of frustration after I don't
know 10 hours of streaming
versus six hours six and a half hours of
streaming
[Music]
thank God thank God thank you Kevin
for luck thanks for the pinky comments
versus
I'm so happy I got to see you finish it
I had a lot of trouble in the GameCube
back when I finished it ah YouTube
Metroid has a tendency to be a bit more
challenging than other games in
Nintendo's catalog oh
yeah yeah yeah
I can see that Nintendo games normally a
bit more difficult a bit more easy on
the easy side for little little Gamers
like me
thank you doll for suffering forward
with me
full heart tank and the captain
Oh wait what
full heart the personal drilled is
said they're drawing me in the zero suit
kiwawa all right
Mamma Mia
that's gonna look very nice
I will have to save it and keep it in a
safe place
well if I ever hi if I ever play another
Metroid game
I have to this kind of fan arts I have
to like keep for those special occasions
the wallpaper this month is perfect by
the way thank you
yeah members wallpaper is up on the
community board now in case you guys
haven't downloaded it
you can download it for 30 days so make
sure to get it before it runs out and
this month is very special because I
asked pomo's artist
[Music]
I was like what should I commission oh
and then I got the funny idea maybe I
could commission for most artists
they were really open to the idea yeah
and the little reference to Pumba was my
idea and they were also very open to
that
they're like hell yeah of course I'll do
it we just gotta make it
um stealthy
um
[Music]
yeah it's not only cool because of Polo
but generally for me I used to love
contact collection
and my favorite characters were the
characters that ichizo sun designed so
so yeah
for me this is like a trophy
the same one my my favorite ones
IE and
um God it's been so long
uh
she
wait oh wait
I think was one
yeah
was one of my favorites I think she was
the red haired one right
point
[Music]
and then uh which one was the white
haired one
maybe she doesn't
[Music]
I think so
and then oh wasn't there like a
blue-haired one ah um I think maybe that
was her
[Music]
they all had very similar names foreign
colored hair and color because it was so
cute
I love the red long braided twin tails
[Music]
I love them
oh
yeah yeah
is the freaking cutest you guys don't
even get it
you wouldn't get it
[Music]
so that's another reason why I'm like
really happy that you know that was why
I was already happy when I started they
were the artist of Paul Moon I'm like
it that's so cool
because they drew all my favorites uh
characters in cancola
what a legend
[Music]
and now now they draw my favorite girl
in ninja Sanji
hey yo
[Music]
that's why I had my eyes on her right
away
love at first sight of her artist's name
no that's not only that I like her
artist but I also like her design and
her personality and you know
it's just so cool to see
you know
an artist that you followed for a long
time make a YouTuber
same with okay and many other
um especially whole life English artists
I feel like
especially
because we got a lot of fgo artists so
many people many uh foreign non-japan
whole life fans they played fgo2 and you
know
like oh [\h__\h] that's an fgo at this let's
go
yeah
really cool
um
I have a PRS poster next to your kiwala
poster nice perfect
[Music]
really nice
get
tall really nice
choice for artists
Red Jewel salsa yeah like I would have
[\h__\h] died if I was told hey your
artist is red juice I would have been
like
what
I would not have believed it
oh yeah
yeah all of them they're also iconic and
godly yeah Mika Picasso what the [\h__\h] oh
my God
[Music]
saying
that's one reason to be happy to be in
whole life if I was an indie I would
have never gotten my hands in such a
crazy artist
I would have never had the funds for
something like that in the first place
it's really expensive I hear
to get your own model and all that I
don't think I
I would have had the funds for it
I don't know if I would have ever become
a veto but if it wasn't for whole life I
don't know if I would have ever tried to
become an indie
because of money issues
at least not right away with the first
hype
maybe after like two years maybe I would
be like yeah
yeah I kind of still want to do it I'm
kind of late to the hype train but I
want to do it
and then maybe become PNG tuber first
but then I would have only had like two
viewers and three viewers and probably
never get enough to really
you know
have enough funds for getting a proper
model
I would have been stuck forever probably
yeah
[Music]
yeah the dark timeline don't worry it's
not a timeline it didn't happen
[Music]
don't
although
no I remember
actually
before whole life I was like
kind of like working with a company
that isn't a beatable company but they
had some kind of mascot and they wanted
to turn that mascot into something like
a YouTuber but in 3D
and actually they already sent me
like some like Tech to test it out with
um
my can trackers and I tested it out
because they they were like saying hey
don't you wanna you know
maybe stream with this
and I couldn't get it to work but I was
like you know we were thinking about
doing it
yeah but it wouldn't have been like my
own designed model or so it would have
been just you know
that but I guess yeah possibly I would
have ended up doing that
yeah and then maybe work myself my way
up
so getting my own model one day maybe
like Crunchyroll V2 but yeah something
like that
but yeah small unknown yeah
not really something with a big backing
either but they're just like you know
doing it for fun basically and I would
have gotten it for free I was just you
know already working with the company
and they knew that
I did this and that
so you know
that was at the same time when I was
auditioning for a whole life
and I was like oh
wait they're accepting me yeah what do I
do about this other thing now
[Music]
that I haven't even started but they
were hoping for me to do it hmm
and I think you know this may have been
just because it was uh
the first gen or so but
I remember I think they told me oh we
can work something out you can do both
but I didn't do it because I ended up
being so focused on kiwawa
wanted to give
everything put all my focus into this
rather than splitting it
um I believed the moment I started that
with this I was like oh okay okay I'm
I'm only going with this now
nice
[Music]
I think you chose the right one
yeah yeah yeah definitely
[Music]
very blessed and honored to be here
every day
[Music]
and now back to Super chance
and where was I
uh here I think Andy car
Productions
17610 question 17 questions
I think your expectations are different
than ours we want to watch you play and
learn and get better no good movie has
the protagonist just walking around
merrily smacking around everyone 24 7.
and in the end you always win and you
finish the games yeah
yeah
I always commit to the games that I
start
I feel like
I don't know I feel like it's lame if I
just start them and then quit them again
so no matter how difficult they are
I go through with it
yes sure out of the 50 games that I
played in two and a half years
pick the one that I didn't finish write
it in the chat and blame me for it
the one out of 50. sure sure okay
foreign
guys
you don't have to do it that was not me
asking for you to do it
who the [\h__\h] finishes Animal Crossing
that's the game you just play forever
and ever
hmm
you know what I ordered today
[Music]
toast lamp
that one's on Amazon scrolling scrolling
scrolling
[Music]
found this cute toast lamp
it's like a toaster
base
and you know when you
like push the thing on the side of the
toaster
that's when the light goes on and the
light is the toast bread
it's so cute
I'll show you when I get it it's cute
it's a little like desk small desk lamp
it doesn't work as a toaster
[Music]
I already have a toaster what is good
normally I don't get this kind of like
Kawaii cute stuff anymore because I want
my apartment to look
um mature like the furniture inside
but this time I had to
have to
couldn't resist it looked so cute
it's not pink no
the base of the toaster is like green I
think
I ended up buying a couple things
I bought like a cute
um like under mat and uh like a long
narrow uh
uh hand rest
you know more cute stuff for my PC table
stuff
the mat has cats on it cute cats that
are eating bread so you know I I chose
that first and then it recommended me
the toaster lamb so I was like oh
this actually works quite well because
the mat that I'm buying is cats like
hugging and eating bread
so it thematically actually really fits
[Music]
and so you know combined well
Sana would be proud of me oh yeah bread
bread yum
[Music]
okay before I get tired again
I'm close to the end
um
thank you you need to chat ultimate
[Music]
I'm so proud of you for all the great
things you do like singing and dancing
reaching out to other YouTubers in and
outside of hollow and in general just
being a badass oh thanks for trying the
games we recommend even if they're out
of your strikes don't quasso
oh yeah Metroid
generally woodloops have been something
I would probably normally consider it
was just because it had sentimental
value to me as well from being nostalgic
to me so you got lucky there guys
don't think I'll you know play games
like this all the time now no no no no
no no no
[Music]
yeah and then I found out she was a hot
orange bird lady that made it even
better
[Music]
but now because of nostalgia I'm trying
to get Sims one to run we'll see how
that goes
thank you Taco Tech thank you for the
sweet words
glad you enjoyed this game too much
thanks for the pinky 17 hours isn't bad
time is always high on the first
playthrough
yeah yes it was fine I would say too as
a streamer I'd take more time with games
thanks for playing Metroid Prime and Joe
you panicked a bit but it was fun and if
you wanna if you want more Ridley you
could always start up the first five
minutes of Super Metroid uh-huh
[Music]
he seems to be showing up a lot in
Metroid games huh a well-known character
Dragon hmm
oh thank you for now he triggered me a
little bit too much so for now I don't
want to see him again
he's even in Smash Bros oh like as part
of the map
like a Samus Metroid themed map
I can imagine him just throwing up what
as a fighter
ew what the [\h__\h] why would you add
no
[Music]
no no
you could have just added some other
game franchise that people were asking
for
no you gotta have two sandwiches and one
[\h__\h] riddling you kidding me
oh my God
[Music]
the fans really wanted in the game yeah
well maybe the Metro fans but other fans
of other games maybe wanted something
else
[Music]
they were really like biased I feel like
deciding to have so many like Metroid
things in their game
free Sam assist oh my God
there's a Dark Samus why
he consistently pulled as one of the
most requested characters well you can't
trust poles of course they're rigged
some fan bases are more like
manipulating than others when it comes
to these kind of things
[Music]
it is what it is
pool was pretty normal how
Dy
yeah okay whatever sure sure Ridley has
all the rights to be there of course of
course
yeah yeah yeah
foreign
[Music]
ERS will never get remade
because the franchise isn't successful
but also Japanese fans hate Crystal like
a plague for some reason what
fortunately there's a fan project we
make it in full voice acting and all
and adding more Crystal content
what
okay first of all why
do they hate Crystal
damn wow fans really really
excited about that huh
onion onion
yeah
that's sad but I I I only play Starbucks
Adventures but yeah I've seen people say
that
people expected a Starbucks game but
this one is so different from other
Staffworks games so it wasn't really a
Starbucks game apparently to me this is
a Starbucks game because it's the only
Starbucks game that I played
yum
sleepy eyes
[Music]
um
Maple Leaf thank you for the recipe chat
truly the strongest Phoenix anytime we
get to see you on stage is a fun time
the great Orchid ultimate Idol thank you
Supreme
[Laughter]
yeah
so dramatic are you like
announcing me to fight
somewhere in a boxing match or so
cute
in the orange Corner we have the noodle
arms but she will charm her enemies with
her cuteness the one and only fiery
Phoenix with her candy corn sword
and the bell that you cannot unleash but
if she did she would certainly win every
match takanashiki
whoa
yeah
that's me that's me
that's me
so intimidating
oh man
um thanks for the word to protect
congrats even if the birthday life is
delayed weeks or months I'm sure it will
be great and well worth the wait really
great news Central I'm happy for you
unrelated perhaps it's time to settle
sorry the rest of the message got
unfortunately deleted
I don't know how that happened
but yeah let's hope that uh birthday
life will not be delayed too much I mean
there's still a chance but the fact that
they mentioned that it would could be
delayed makes me think that it will be
delayed we'll see we'll see
let's hope for the best
I want a proper birthday life and
nothing less
I will settle for nothing less
[Music]
I don't even care if you play that one
why did you mention it
of a chat and she was so good at being
funny love you if you are what did I say
that was so funny
you
thank you love you too
what did I say I'm so funny apparently
[Music]
yeah this video oh wait sorry that was
the next message looking for a tough
thank you
it sounds like something chickenpox what
was I playing
thank you that was the Super chats from
this
foreign
which means we only have a couple of
short ones left Hallelujah I'm so happy
I'm so happy
yeah finally getting this out of the way
[Music]
you guys gonna fall asleep to this one
next is the Uno or not so much Uno more
garlic phone collab
where I have to say it
my thumbnail was the cutest
animals
[Music]
okay
only a couple ones here
for the pinky just caught up on
yesterday's Super Chat reading I just
wanted to say congratulations on getting
you a pretty birthday book yeah so hyped
for you to finally get a full-on
birthday stream like you always wanted
can't wait for it thank you I mean last
year's was uh quite high quality as well
but the thing is if I do it at the cover
Studio
in Japan then I can invite many Japanese
members
and you know that makes it really
special
so I'm looking forward to that I hope I
can get some nice gifts
do some fun songs together
[Music]
don't wanna be all alone wanna make good
use of that opportunity
[Music]
thank you for the pinky no complaints
that's my department oh that's my
department thank you for taking over
that it's NATO thank you for the
vertical chat another birthday saved by
your stream oh and potential hard to
believe a year has gone by love what you
do you're awesome keep up the good work
hope you have a good time with Uno I
didn't but okay this collab is gonna be
great thank you
happy belated birthday
I mean
we didn't play UNO but I think we still
provided entertainment so
hope it was good thank you Natsu and
hope you had some birthday cake and
treated yourself to something stay
healthy and stay happy okay
[Music]
74 Duncan okay
this has been a pinnacle of switch Uno
collabs truly an authentic experience
so true so true thank you
Minx thanks for the pinky this is the
most Uno stream of all time
because what would would be if not Uno
when there is no Uno
but at one point I had two Unos on my
screen at the same time
oh that's pretty impressive I was I
would say I was quite prepared you know
I had my my other Uno ready right away
I was trying my best to make it work too
I deleted all my friends
[Music]
could have played Monopoly too right at
the spot
I was so ready
yeah my faces were covered
[Music]
Ubisoft was not preparing down I was
prepared
okay
um
for the pinky as well Gotta Give support
to the scuff I mean collab looking
forward to Uno thank you
there never was and you know
thank you though for waiting and
chilling with us while we were trying to
figure everything out
[Music]
I'm confused why did we even
ah I think we started I was just gonna
ask why did we start the stream when we
didn't even
when we weren't even able to play the
game but I think we were all in the
waiting room but once the stream once
the game started that's one way
when Nina kept on getting kicked out
yeah I mean could have tested that
beforehand but
we were we were like actually I'm I'm
glad we started on time because
until the very last second before the
swim starts we were
um still like preparing everything at
least the three of us that streamed
because I was trying to set up like the
Discord reaction thingies
and all that so and my my stream layout
blue
and I was like
oh and then we had to some of us had to
uh even though I thought I already had
Uno it didn't work and it made me pay
for Uno again so I had to install Uno
again
um but then oh yeah first I was like
[\h__\h] uh I need
I need a steam card again I don't know
where my steam card codes are the last
ones that jenma got me I don't know
where they are and then I was like can
somebody get me Uno and then pomu paid
for my Uno and I installed it and we
were like oh maybe it doesn't work maybe
we need to get it on the switch but then
we went back to the Uno on on PC and
then back and forth and then I wasn't
the only who had only one who had issues
right after Nina was getting the same
issue and then we were like oh you have
to download and buy it again yeah yeah
ah
it was a journey
we were trying so hard to get everything
to work in time
and it was definitely not ready in time
I'm [\h__\h] oh no
um
and the fools at Hollow were not paying
attention for they have scheduled
another unoco out this week and I will
just go as horrible yeah yeah I saw like
discussions
uh of you know them planning Uno
and
it's like looking at it silently and I'm
like okay good luck I
I wish you the best
hope that works out for y'all
um
[Music]
a couple Japan members also had Uno
schedule a couple hours before you girls
but they had to change the game because
it was also not working
oh today
[Music]
they need to get their [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
together that company that made UNO
online
my God
[Music]
yeah next time I would play if I really
need to play Uno I will say we should
play The Clubhouse games one
at least that one works
you memorable man thank you
um where was I
um
clappy boy thank you for the way to the
chat I hope the stream will be over soon
Maya my body is on the verge of
collapsing from laughter this
constellation is far too powerful for
safe viewing if there's ever a next time
I'll better brace myself thanks also for
the reminder that you actually are sick
artists no I'm so [\h__\h] uh when I'm like
under stress like that I I oh God
I draw the shittiest [\h__\h] I need time
I need to practice like regularly but
that will be maybe in five to ten years
where I get properly into art again
thank you Flappy boy doll
glad you enjoyed it so much I have a
good time too even though I mean for
like streams where stuff was happening
and we had technical issues and all that
that was the
the most like
Restless
and fun
and just you know lose and carefree
scuff stream that I ever had
like normally when stuff like that
happens especially with collapse I get
stressed out and like oh [\h__\h]
you need to do something otherwise the
viewers get mad blah blah blah but in
this case
I was just laughing the whole time
at the ridiculous situation
hmm
[Music]
yeah yeah I even started Googling oopsie
that was a big oopsie
ah
yeah my thank God nothing's that
interesting on my like browser
things are interesting huh
there's like Twitter Drive
some some
resources from Japanese sides
and there's like stuff on there like
websites that I haven't that I've
visited maybe once in half a year
like that font and playboard I visited
yeah
that font maybe actually both for this
size I visited once in the last year
I don't know why they're even on there
I never I think there's other sites that
check more why is he no YouTube is there
huh
surely there's another site that I visit
more than these two
weird
I didn't pin it
did I mean I don't really look at it
hmm oh yeah audio stock for example why
is audio stuff
Maybe
if it's pinned maybe it's like pinned
from a long time ago
ah no I don't need to play Boards I know
it doesn't have like
it's not even
I think I think one of the things is
that it's not really up to date either
[Music]
I don't know I don't really care about
it maybe in my beginning days I checked
it more but
foreign
[Music]
so it didn't really have much meaning
but look at this
I was a big relief that nothing
embarrassing was on there
[Music]
and my my suggestions also weren't
anything embarrassing and you guys got
really amused by wheel and Papa Roach
Last Resort lyrics
actually so Papa Roach Last Resort at
the reason I recently
um
looked up that song is because I was the
song came up in a British show that I
was watching
just for a few seconds and I was like oh
wait I know this song
I know a song what is this song so I
looked it up and I listened to it but
when I looked it up it recommended to me
an updated recent version from like two
or three years ago
with like a different featured artist
that replaced some of the verses
and it was amazing yeah Jared Johnson
yeah
that new version was really cool
if you haven't heard it before you gotta
listen to it
why was I searching wheel that was right
before the stream I was looking for a
batsuit like something to use for about
the wheel oh hello
but I was in the middle of talking to
the girls on Discord and preparing so I
was multitasking and I opened the
browser and all I could type in was
Wheel I was like oh we need a wheel so I
type in wheel
it works like when you type in wheel
you'll get a wheel to use like that like
an online do-it-yourself wheel
a randomized wheel
you get exactly what you need so it's
enough but yeah it works
hmm
don't know why everybody questions that
so much
hmm
just try it it works right yeah
[Music]
and next is the pizza stream Mamma Mia
oh my God I I saw like uh
I took a sneak peek and I saw the super
chats
in the beginning where Gilmore Girls
role play Super chats I'm like what I'm
fix it to read this
let's go
soon
here we go Rory says is this what Kiana
is making the corn cob Pizza Suki says
this is going to be great I can't wait
to take notes Lorelei says Suki are you
sure people will eat a corn cup Pizza
says who doesn't love corn Lorelei says
just give me a coffee and I'm happy
Robbie says who knows this could be
become a new Gilmore tradition to make a
corn cut pizza every April Fool's Day
Luke says why was I attracted to this
loreline says maybe you can sell krunker
picked out the diner look says
okay never mind anyway let's take our
seats I don't want to miss this Luke
says am I the only one who's noticed
chickens are running this place number
that says they're all working hard oh oh
we should hire some for the dragonfly in
Barbie says why is there a disco ball in
the center of the place Lord I says
that's for dancing for to favorite night
honey now shh I want to see the corn
called Pizza where he says I had to
stream might get delayed for one hour
Luke is like what why Suki says they
probably took so much time with trying
to make good dough whoops
that they are forcing it to get decent
in three hours with a lot of these even
though ideally you don't want to use any
except for like the tip of a knife
that's just my guess though
Suki knows what's up because she
probably already made pizza before
[Music]
or maybe she just copy pasted what I
said
I wonder who this is
who wrote all of this
um
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
for the rest of the chat I'm just going
to send this while everything is happy
and my cat is being held and there's no
cursed Pizza on the screen coffee
potential
I really want you guys to at least
accept the fact
that it was genuinely good if you're not
gonna go out of your way to try to make
yourself fine
make it whatever but at least accept the
fact when I say it was good and my
friend also really liked it like was
also genuinely surprised that it worked
so well
please just accept that it was actually
really good because I put so much work
into it and if it wasn't really good I
wouldn't say it was really good but I
put so much work into making it really
professional Pizza even though it was
April the 1st okay
I still went so hard on it yeah I got a
good oven I got good ingredients
[Music]
um
believe me
you gotta buy a pizza oven because of
that stream I think that's a good
investment
but be careful with cleaning it like
reads the cleaning instructions
normally with pizza ovens you're not
supposed to
um wash the plate
at all the only thing you can do is
scrape things off and be careful
um
and like heat it up to maximum height
everything that's left over there you
just burn it to ashes basically and then
scrape it off that's all you can do
be very careful you you're gonna damage
it if you do [\h__\h] with it
hmm yeah no water
I mean the the instructions of mine says
a damp towel would be okay but my friend
has more knowledge and I trust my friend
because you're not supposed
to
put anything wet
it's not not really self-cleaning it's
just self-burning
maybe maybe a damp towel would be okay
but um
[Music]
I'm not gonna risk it for now
will you be able to do the dough alone
in the future I think so but probably
not so well
because yeah
we used my kitchen machine went like
for a long time
uh but
then
my dough still had to be like
I don't know how to say it
uh needed by hand
with a good technique for another
additional half hour to 40 minutes
I mean surely I can do it myself but I
don't know if it would turn out that
good but I I I should be fine I think I
remember the process
hmm
I'll just yeah ask my cats they're
needing professionals at least smoothing
is really good at kneading
[Music]
oh but the texture is so fun the dough
texture is so fun
oh and it's so funny like when you add
even the tiniest amount of water into
the machine while it's mixing
when it's already like
um a certain
shape you know the dough
even the tiniest amount of water like
just one drip will make it suddenly lose
its shape and go like
who's break dancing inside the bowl it
looks so funny it will absolutely lose
control it looks so funny
dancing doll in the bowl
[Music]
only for like a moment and Dennis
like shapes itself again
after it's soaked up the little moisture
to handle gonna be careful not to add
too much water
there's like a pizza app that my friend
used while you can calculate
uh depending on how much dough you want
to make or how many pizzas you want to
make and how many you know ingredients
you have how many ingredients you have
to use
it's really easy to use like it will
calculate how much water you need and
add how much time you have to
depending on that it will tell you also
how much yeast you need to put in and so
on
foreign
I gotta get that app when I wanna make
pizza myself
thank you
[Music]
thank you where was I oh yeah thank you
simply thank you
thank you for all the pinky yeah let's
say oh no the final pours her special
apple juice onto your hand which makes
it Glow she tells you each finger can
make a human live 100 years longer if
you pick their nose
laugh
which human Hollow members noses will
you pick
um
none
there's not even a need to add 100 years
because like that's torture you think
you want to live forever but
ah
in a hundred years from now world is
probably gonna be hot as [\h__\h]
or like no let's say like 50 years from
now from now plus 100 years from now
let's say we were in an age where you
live another 50 years naturally anyway
and then add 100 years that oh my God
this 150 years from now oh my God that's
like no thank you
100 years is too much because then oh my
God you know just what you'll stay
like old because you don't even it
probably doesn't extend your your years
of Youth either
so oh it'll just be grandma grandpa for
a long long long long time
and your your body will continue to Sag
endlessly and at 199 years old you will
look like a [\h__\h] puddle possibly
yeah no I don't think that's a really
good quality of life ever
because if you already I mean some
miracle humans at 90 are doing pretty
well but others are like bodily
functions wasting away at 90 already so
imagine that at 120 130 140 in how much
pain you could be or like
[Music]
ugh so yeah maybe not
I don't want to force anyone to live so
long
I don't know what I'm talking about it's
the fault of that Super Chat what's
onions
[Music]
everybody freaking the [\h__\h] out about me
cutting the corn cob the way I did
chill I had everything under control
don't freak out
Coraline Springs little Binky hey boss
can't be Italy representative here
unfortunately our newest kid Pizzeria
branch in Naples was tortured To The
Ground by an angry mob after reading the
menu here's the insurance money Carla
guys come on come on
my Italian kfps you must understand
first of all the corn cob edges were a
joke but second of all they worked
pretty good first of all I tried my best
to make a pizza worthy of the blessing
of Italy okay like I used really good
flour and I I I did it as as originally
accurately as possible I got a proper
oven for this
thing yeah
and hey I made no pizza and tuna Pizza
is acceptable okay maybe some other
things I did wearing that's acceptable
like the corn cup edges but come on come
on
no complaints for me thank you what the
[\h__\h] was that sound
[Music]
maybe that was my brother
let me check that scares me
foreign
[Music]
thank you
well I don't know what it was but I got
movie I stole her from her sleeping bag
oh
[Music]
now my brother he
uh
he probably like a few hours ago
came back just to pick up his uh luggage
I said
make it quick when you come back
I think he already did that a while ago
couldn't have been this late
already 10 P.M
[Music]
oh well whatever
yeah maybe noise was cat related
[Music]
yeah
where was I uh yeah
um
and not pinky sorry orange but your icon
made me think it's a pinky
and thank you I'm glad you enjoyed the
Stream
egg on pizza oh I never tried that
two colors
greenwilder thank you for the
day
ah that actually made me kind of worried
if it especially now reading it again
without the context of it being the
first of April
Queen Wilder are you here this was a
joke right your Super Chat was a joke
right like why would you tell that to me
while again using money
it said hi there sweetie this is green
Willow's Mom I just found out how much
money my son has been spending you this
super chats with my credit card and we
had a long talk
you won't be hearing from him until he
gets back from his grandparents Farm
yeah no that must be intro that must be
a joke come on but I mean part of me is
like a little bit concerned
why the logic why would you send the
pinky in order to tell me that foreign
Last Wish from greenwilder maybe to make
sure because I always say like I want
you guys you know listening to not just
disappear and I would be wondering where
did that person go maybe maybe from the
goodness of their heart not to make me
worry his last wish was okay Mom I won't
do it anymore but please please send her
one last pinky which it has to be at
least a pinky so that she reads it for
sure just let her know where I went give
her an explanation so that she will have
closure you know there's there's a like
somehow I can imagine that could have
happened
oh
and she was like okay fine that's the
last money you'll be spending and you'll
paying that back to me every cent of it
Rescue Mission yeah
[Music]
a wild imagination ah
a little bit maybe Brandon thanks for
the pinky and looks delightful corny and
hot oh the pizza looks fine as well five
stars on Yelp thank you it was really
good I want to make another one
but it's so much effort and for me alone
it wouldn't really make sense because
buying like one one
um
container
small container of corn
for one person there's 100 left over
a lot of the other ingredients too like
tomato sauce like the smallest container
for the tomato sauce
was like
double the amount of what I actually
needed for four pizzas
so if I just want one pizza for myself
it's so not worth the effort
look
I'd have to make several pizzas
and yeah okay I can make a couple more
like two more maybe
put them in the fridge but still
[Music]
but I thought maybe for next Christmas
if I'm in Austria
uh
I think we'll probably have some other
Foods too but I might just try to make
some pizzas for my family
hmm
could be kind of fun I'll ask okay what
do you want on your pizza and then I
throw it on there and then I'll I'll
cook it for them
and then they'll be like my God that's a
gorgeous amazing Pizza
can I come
Emily only but your chickens or your
family
secretly put a corn cob on top they
won't no no I think they would like it
like we all love corn I think so
um
you just have to open your heart man and
just give it one bite and you will
understand
questions
not unknown thank you for the pinky
hey I just want to say that you're
amazing you are the cutest and best
YouTuber ever I love you so much you
always will be my one and only on sweet
froggy Wawa wrong Channel
Frankie Wawa has a channel
not dad also you guys have been saying
floggy Wawa is gone
I I don't know where did she go I hear
I called her guys
don't worry you're not in danger anymore
all is well
you're safe
she's there
floating again Zoom
[Music]
that was quick yeah
she's been gone for a month
more than that because you haven't seen
her while I was in Japan either
whole cow
because that sounds like
the gamer Korean dances
and thank you very happy with new camera
me too me too
I'm basically done one second
one more I think
yeah
oh
the end is right there
oh my God
I'm gonna cry it's like I'm running a
marathon guys
ah
a few meters broke water at me guys
throw water at me like in the marathons
hmm
it's the eye of the tiger it's the
thrill of the fight rising up to the no
no no no rivals
[Music]
no no you know what
foreign
[Music]
yeah I named this Persona Jazz even
though I didn't play persona
[Music]
thank you
um
[Music]
I already read this on stream thank you
it was April the 1st you should have
known
next time be more prepared maybe fool
some others for Revenge
again
sorry
[Music]
it's pretty what
what what
'd you say
um
[Music]
thank you
convention
thank you again soon
[Music]
conditions
and chose the hero
thank you
[Music]
and now this is Mrs Fire Emblem thank
you indeed I am
oh I guess this stream had
some switch it readopian
I guess this stream has some super chats
too
um
she did that yes
[Music]
now before I shut them off
let me see
okay okay
here we go again a little bit more come
on
thank you for the pinky Kila working
hard as always okay please let me
reimburse you for you crap
oh my crap
you mean uh my breakfast crap thank you
it's not that expensive though
I will put it towards the
Pizza crap because that's kind of a crap
and it was more expensive thank you
Jacob 47 ounce I'm sorry my I'm already
like [\h__\h] numb but thank you for the
pinky
for short games we're playing with the
next month close friendly how about long
live the queen it's like a princess
maker with cutesy Game of Thrones
elements
let me Google
no
no no no
[Laughter]
I'm sorry but no
no
play something else
we'll find plenty I might ask you guys
again though
all right
[Music]
um yeah foreign
I'm buying a digital version anyway
because I am a lazy piece of [\h__\h]
when I saw that there was a digital
version after all I was like okay well
well will you still do a stream about ah
no I don't think I'll do a stream about
it but I can tell you now give me one
second
um
okay
[Music]
um
you got a job now no it's congratsun
okay I'm done for real for real
um
okay
so I don't know how we're gonna do this
um I guess I'm gonna play the audio
because the audio is fine
I'll tell you or or
I don't know should we time like do you
guys want to like watch it
um I don't want to show YouTube because
maybe I can yeah maybe I can
hold on live English
um
[Music]
shush
uh which one is it
uh life life
because I wanted to tell you which parts
I choreographed
very important Desu
okay okay
um
let's put this over here
[Music]
oh
oh no
hmm
[Music]
oh baby
for all the Curious can of Peace who
wanna know because
um I'm gonna say no
kind of proud
let's see
so we start with
baby
this song
[Music]
hi hi
that part was my idea first of all
because that originally had Korea but I
was like why don't we just go like hi hi
I mean that is nothing special but of
course that was just me doing my thing
don't add a note you look right
then it means
it's just the choreo from the
choreographer
[Music]
give me
thank you
[Music]
and most of this we just kept the same
way
[Music]
thank you
foreign
okay
they're still not the part that I that
was my idea wait for it
[Music]
and that's so cute
because you know a choreographer son was
basically like yeah just uh you know do
just you know
do something whatever just you know sing
it and I was like eh but I want some
more interaction between us and so I I
thought this would kind of feel like
perfect with the melody and and it just
fits so well and dancing around each
other right so cute right
[Music]
this this kind of these kind of Parts
whenever I was like at the corner
um of
the like the edge of the group
I I I I I feel this not only here but
like in previous experiences when
dancing uh with people when you're on
the edge and there is this moment where
there's like two beats of you look to
your left side and you look to your
right side but oh hey I have the one on
my right side we have someone on my left
side and they will look at me maybe at
first in the first beat but in the
second beat they will look away so I
will just be like hahaha
nobody's looking at me but let's just
see that nobody will know I mean it's
just just look like you're part of this
[Music]
thankfully gooda looked at middle and
the first video didn't make me feel too
awkward
[Music]
yeah it's already a while ago isn't it
okay
um now here normally
uh no when we were like you know
practicing this teacher was like oh well
yeah what should we do here uh she was
like checking her the original choreos
and then I said I have an idea I have an
idea can I can I make idea so and this
is this part is my idea where we go to
the cameras and wave at them
but
[Music]
the thing is in the practice we
in the practice the original idea was
that we
um run all five together from one side
then to the other side
until here we run to one side and then
it repeats so we run to the other side
but then when we were like rehearsing we
realized that the studio is you know
quite wider than this place where we
practiced and that running from one side
to the other is gonna take a while so in
the rehearsal we decided to split it but
yeah okay
um I think the first group like Ina and
the Cali uh was still fine going there
because our original Direction Where We
already like practiced to go was already
there like they just had to do it the
same way they always do it but me and
gura were split to the other side to
make use of the whiteness of the studio
and that was such a sudden decision that
we ended up not getting it right
and then we first ran you don't see it
on the camera but we first ran to the
site where Kelly Ina I'm aware
thankfully we weren't caught on camera
but then in the middle of it I was like
oh [\h__\h] could have come and then we
rented the actual side and we arrived
kind of late as you can see and we were
like [\h__\h]
uh
well accidents there's no accidents
there's only happy mistakes what what no
that's not quite it
yeah so that was that I I didn't I just
shared like one or two ideas there ah
[Music]
I think that loading screen was
partially my idea
um
okay
now this this is where it gets more
interesting
the last two songs
yeah this was basically The Courier for
this was created
uh with the camera in mind
[Music]
the whole time we were standing all on
the sides out of the camera shot uh
and you know the timing was important
for everybody to go right at the right
time so that there's always somebody
like passing by and it was like an
emotional movement you know like elegant
I know it almost looks so funny when we
were practicing
so dramatic guys
[Music]
oh all the drama oh
pink and here basically
we were most of the time we were
standing in the formation
um
you don't see it so well here but most
of the time we had three lines uh as the
formation
so front middle and back and then
um
in this case was like kind of behind me
so she saw me but I also had her in the
corner of my eye
so whenever we were in a formation like
this I feel like I was always
syncing up with the
person that was next to me
so sometimes that was Ina and sometimes
that was Ahmed and in this case you know
we do the spin
hand movement and it was from there on
it was a contest of who can lower their
hand the slowest
because uh Sensei was like you just do
this one movement and then just let your
hand go down really slowly and slowly as
possible you can do it as long as good
as singing
so it was always just like a contest
I'm the slowest
[Music]
rehearsal
oh good I would sing this and oh my God
I would melt because it's so pretty I
couldn't I had to stand still but I
couldn't stop myself from swaying the
whole time
[Music]
on time again
I think Amber was always like
checking me for the timing
[Music]
That was supposed to be like
one after another like a domino ah okay
here uh this is nothing so special but
um basically since it was just like it
would stand here and sing but I
I especially when the beat hits
I wanted it to show so I added little
dance
see I'm riding in the sky and then I'm
inviting you
I'm looking for the lost souls who've
gone astray and now dance to the base
but nothing special really
[Music]
and here oh the brave all the braveness
in my arm did you see that it's so great
this this step
um
this one okay it always looks kind of
like
um like mixed because teacher said don't
do a full on idle step just kind of do a
sway so everybody was swaying
differently which is fine but that's why
it looks kind of like you know not so
synced I mean okay I'ma started with the
wrong foot but besides that we were
always just like swaying differently
[Music]
it wasn't supposed to be a fully
computers
idle step
this was also slow contest
okay please look at that again is there
like a like a a hotkey that makes me go
back 10 seconds on on the keyboard on
YouTube
I feel like there is
look at me Jay
yeah okay thank you look at me and Ina
we were like after this chorus
we were always so in sync I wish there
was a camera that showed us at all times
because it felt so good I I saw it in
the corner of my eye every time we moved
we were so in sync
now look after we like when we start
moving
[Music]
now down down
oh that feels so good
and luck Kelly is singing we're doing
some more moves
I'm so proud of everybody like for doing
so well I look oh this is like my
favorite part
because our steps we take the same like
distance in our steps me and Ina and and
oh oh it feels so good
[Music]
there's so many close-ups maybe someday
you can see more of it I hear we're
supposed to stand in like a diagonal
line I don't know if it's noticeable
[Music]
Inna is walking a lot in this Oreos
Our Song
[Music]
in my walk place has anyone ever noticed
my walk in this moment because I thought
I was very sassy look look at me
[Music]
assassins
oh okay dance break I had fun with that
I wish it was longer
[Music]
I put like 200 more energy in that than
it showed
[Music]
itsy
okay here this part that's coming up I
made up completely because again
otherwise it would have just been
standing there and singing and I didn't
want that I wanted to show especially
because the lyrics Do say I'll dance in
burning embers your loves giving links I
wanted to do something I but again I
didn't really have like confidence in
making a choreo and I asked the teacher
can I can you help me but for a
different part actually and then I was
still not like confident with the level
of difficulty so and with the style of
it so I came up with my own parts for my
solo Parts yeah
[Music]
nice
chorus
[Music]
I don't know the lyrics after all
those last part
like we've [\h__\h] up so often but this
time we actually did it right I'm so
proud
among them
Stars
yeah
so mostly my my solo Parts yeah one more
song
just so you know exactly
it's so nice to re-watch this
wish we could do it more often take off
and fly ah
this song and many other songs like uh
Chinese money story too
why
so many whole life songs
always start
like with the beat for the first Beat of
the Music
it's actually kind of rough sometimes
not ah the longer we wait the stronger
guys
[Music]
oh
this fight we would like you know we
moved to a position then we raise our
arms and then immediately we let go and
then we like dance in a circle like a
cult ritual anyway that always was a fun
move in in practice and like teachers
said we can do more interactions and I
was like trying to do like high fives
and stuff with gura but I I don't know
later on it was like I felt a bit
awkward to continuously do that uh yeah
but it was fun I like this part
yeah
and seeing us walking again
you're such a walker
[Music]
this part
this one I think I'm not sure I may
still be doing it in the wrong direction
I actually I couldn't do this one
properly and then they should the other
girls showed me quinoa it's like this
this direction out to the outside I'm
like what do you mean I uh what what
from the inside to the outside
whatever it looks it doesn't stand out
so
I don't know if I did it right
[Music]
very bouncy
okay now comes kiwawa Dance Part solo
part I made all of this up because I
wasn't happy
[Music]
except for this she told me I have to do
this
and then went back to me
yeah so this is where I asked the Sensei
to give me something with more dance
involved and
um you know a short time couldn't come
up with something nice so overnight I
I decided I'll think of something and
this is what I came up with yeah yeah
yeah because it's like a fast part and I
I just wanted to show off in the few
solo parts
um you know that hey I I am the dancer
you know it's just so you know
but it was a bit
how to dance there because the girls
were all super close to me
we stood in one line and you know then
they moved away a little bit but still a
bit difficult because I couldn't dance
too big with my Flappy arms
[Music]
that was that was my idea but yeah I
think I always confused almond with what
I wanted to do
yeah
sorry yummy
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
wow
that was my idea at the end there that
we would all go
um since Cali is kind of the loudest
here that we would go all to the middle
to Cali and jam with her and then go
back and the next group would come to
Cali and jam with her and you know
that was my idea
[Music]
bye
yay yeah so I tried to insert
some more choreography where I could
squeeze some in but generally you know
we requested
or like I I also asked for it not for
myself but for the others I asked for a
more simple choreography so that we you
know could learn it easily together but
they all did so well and I'm so proud I
want to do more of them you know more
stuff like this please
I want to learn more with them
um
um yeah I mean because I
got the choreography to be just
genuinely simpler for the sake of all of
us I wanted at least my solo parts to be
a bit more refined you know
so I did I did that same for uh
something else before I feel like
something else was there where I was
like
[Music]
um
yeah I'm glad that I got to do some
input not only for my solo Parts but
generally you know like uh at the end of
the song of Chinese my story and like I
got to say let's go all together from
One camera to another and wave and then
go back stuff like that having some
creative input was nice yeah yeah all
right then
now that I got to tell you this
hey
my homework is done tomorrow if all goes
well we're starting at 1pm my time 8pm G
no wait
no wait 10 pm 10 pm right 10 p.m jst a
free PM my time
I guess I'll make a thumbnail now
but at least I finished all the super
chats yay yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
let's go yeah
uh denma but yeah actually I I think I
saw something I wanted to use yeah yeah
okay okay thank you guys for her uh
listening to KF podcast bye kiwawa where
she only reads super chats endlessly for
four hours not even
thank you foreign
hopefully it will go well let's open
some cards tomorrow
you guys gotta tell me which ones are
the good ones because I don't know which
ones are the desirable ones but I guess
all of them are desirable because
they're all gonna be whole life cards
hmm
the shiny ones okay and the ones with
the signatures yeah
um the signature ones are the the most
desirable
I'm sure
hmm
okay
okay I'll see you tomorrow
thank you so much for listening bye bye
[Music]
back to being a cat
laughs
[Music]
foreign