[Music]
K
A
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [Music] [Applause] [
Applause] [
Music]
DET
[Music]
A
D
[Music]  ]
[Applause]
[Music]
til
DET
[Music]
[Applause]
Yo
[Music]
Ah
[Music] [
Applause]
[Applause]
Stuffed in a bag  In a world like summer, everyone
We're all huddled together in the warmth of each other. We've slipped into it like peanuts,
smiling as we rest on yesterday's
template. Even when we're chewing on the table, even when we're in a picture, we
can't go that far.
[Music] There are so many
things to hide, so many things to keep hidden,
and a book that won't go away.
Just the truth that I'm here is
like a peanut stuck in a river of ghosts, and I'm instantly rejected by the world.If
that's all I want,
let me be by your side and be with you.Even if I'm shaken and stepped on, I won't
crack.  It's like it's because it's not there.The difference between being
on top of the place where you were born or in the ground is the
only difference.The world is so bitter that it's unforgivable.The pouring
rain shuts down the world.Sometimes I want to
shut up, but I'm making a noise on the other side of the window.  I
can't find a single star in the sky.The day is
like lightning, and I'm full of big mistakes.I'm improvising my
daily life as a first-timer, so let it all sink in.I'm full
of secrets, I'm full of next steps, and I
won't leave anything behind.  My
daily life is filled with the feeling that there is no such thing as normal, there is no right answer, but I am here, and I am here with
you.
Even though I am here with you, I am able to hold on to this one truth. I
am savoring this one miracle of God.
[Music]
Ah, it's like there was something I told you, and it's
like a reverse dance. Love is a fascinating
program. But it's getting tougher from here on out. My
identity, that's the identity of the thing, the
identity of one person.
Don't wait.  It's one or two
shooting stars that fall and fall
[Music]
Jump into the chest that nestles close to you due to the weight of the stars that overlap
Jump into your shining identity Lange pride [Music]  A
quick burst of bullish madness, and then a
state of betrayal and tears,
lalala, summer, enough danger, and the end.Focusing
on the two of us, hidden.I finally found a mysterious
body.Love
is the exact opposite of the
program.It's the opposite of what I'm going to get from here, my
identity.It's the identity of hope.  I do
n't want to let you carry your identity alone.It's one or two of your
destiny.I'll be happy right away.As I lean into the weight of the falling shooting stars
and
those
stars, they burst out in my chest because of you.
Diving into your heart Carving out your
identity
[Music]
[Music] Let's
laugh at the sadness, let's live,
marionette
If the shi swings, how about some coffee? Rudo
Aldore I can't dance well, with the pain
and the pain and the sadness, I say
goodbye
[Music]
Kiss dance  Let's despair, let's be greedy,
Shadow, don't think about unnecessary things, let's become one, let's be good, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's
good to
be human.
[Music]
Hey
In a life where I laugh even though I want to cry  I
hide my true heart and pretend to smile
[Music]
Ah, I can't do well. Melt and melt my bones, lies, and anxiety.
Let's go to sleep.
[Music]  Let's
move on and get used to each other
[Music]
Don't think about it, just take the steps and
let it happen
[Music]
Shau Let's laugh together just for now
Shadosu Let's forget everything just for now and fly and
dance together Despair
Desire  Do
n't think too much about it, let's become one. It's
okay, it's
okay, it's okay to be human. It's okay, it's okay to be human. It's okay to be human.
Lalala
Siranranranrararanranran [Music
]
[Music]
Chan-chan-a  Chitty Chitty Bang Bang Chitty Chitty-
chan Chitty Chitty Bang
Bang Chitty
Chitty Bang Bang Chitty Chitty Bang Bang Ah Chitty Chitty-chan
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang Chitty Chico Moshishi
Everyone is capricious, and when it comes to
harsh words, they
get up, and Pika gets angry and climbs up the mountain.I do
n't know.On
the weekends,
Akira-chan and Chitty-chitty-banban
do nothing, and
enjoy it.Chan-chan, Bang-
ban, freshly
made, and Chan-chan, Chitty-
chitty-banban, are stupidly silly.  Minsu
Pasta
Eggs I
don't need them even if I don't have them
[Music]
Zipanipti
Takase
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music]  I wish I
could stay a
little longer, just a little longer
How long will it last?
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang Ah Chitty Chitty Chitty
Bang bang is Chitty Chitty Bang Bang Ah Chitty Chitty Chitty Chitty
Bang Bang Ah [Music] [Music] Even if it's hard to see the animal that comes out of it, I wo
n't do it Even if it's hard, I can't do it '
Cause I can't wait I'll lick my throat and go
[Music]  Let's
do it, whether it's good or bad, let's try to get into it.Let's try to get into it.Let's meet with the breakthrough Suge, and the next time we meet, I
can't get over it.I'm crazy and my heart is straight.What's
going on?  I can't sit down, I can't
do it, I can't even sit down, I can't even sit down, I can't even sit down, I can't even sit down, I can't even do it, I can't even do it, I can't even sit down, I can't even do it, I can't do
it even if I want to look at the animal that's so useless.  Come on,
hit me, come over me, go crazy, go away
[Music] It's
boring if I don't do it. At least I wanted it to fly forever. If only I could be known a little better, I'd like to be happy.
[Music]
Even if I don't want to see the fallen animal, I'll do it. I
can't wait, but I can't wait. I'll ride it until I'm done. I can't stand the animal. I
can't even wait, so I
won't talk about it.  I'm
waiting for you to open
it.
All the diving maps are completed in a 1mm gap.
Today is God.
Mental Challenger. A little bit of
sentimental. I can't see the big 123.
Even if you're a pigeon, don't touch the cat's chest.
Go around the globe.  It's over if it's not me
[Music]
Nede
Roulette It's a little too fast No no no no
But Senodate is fighting now Le is a formula
Challenger Ha is written
Automation  I
love you so much, I want you to fall in love
with it. You know Mario. Even if you manipulate Lady, that's not a bad thing. Become someone who isn't me.
[Music]
[Music] A
man of bones digs up and
finds the source.  No, I'm
going to become a replica of Tsuki no
Mi, I can't even see the real thing, I can't even see it, it's standing up and touching, it's
going to be big, it's squeaking, I'm
begging you, even if it's hard, I'm not going to make it into a cat's chest, it
's not me, it's going to be big  I ca
n't see you, mama.
Grow up and get excited again. The country
is gone. But don't touch the cat's heart.
Grow up. It's over that I'm not you.
[Music]
I want to do it again.  I want to be connected from bridge to bridge.I
want to tell you with my fingertips and words.Maybe I want to
say it.I want to
say it.I want to do it both ways.It's
just that I'm
wrong.  I
don't know if that's the case,
but I
want to play with my fingers and words.It
could be my mom.  I
want to do both. I
can't move.
Discommunication
by Bashon Luti
[Music] It's a
problem that will never end.
It's over in the blink of an eye.  My
feelings are flat right now,
and I have no intention of doing anything with them, but I
want to be tied to them.  I
want to
do it, I want to do it, I want to
do it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I want to say it, I
want to say it, even though I don't know what it means.
I want La Deida because you're all about me, so I
want to burn brightly
[Music]
Papara
Papara Kage na Ki
[Music] You're sneaky
and sneaky, aren't you? My feelings are getting shy It's like toying with me, but I shouldn't chase you
Even though I'm winning, I can't do it  Once you take a step forward, you can't go back.I ca
n't take it off.I'm looking forward to playing with the leaves.I
want Dada.If everything about you is deceived,
that's fine.I'm shaking more and more.
Show me a secret love that only smiles at me, so I'll give you a glare, and if you don't give me a second glance, I'll never see you again.If you'll give it to me, I'll burn you on the day of love on purpose.I'll make
you cry, but the pain will disappear as I gently look
back at the beauty.  My heart is so tight that my
breathing stops and I become uneasy. I
want to throw all of my thoughts away, but I don't
struggle with my unpleasant, difficult, and dangerous wishes.
That voice is taking me
to the love.
Lala, I want to burn
[Music] Every time your
mouth
gently smiles, I'm
swallowed,
and I'm told to touch the world of the road
[Music]
Daryl, I'll leave it to you until the end. If I break down,
that's okay, make me even crazier and
show me the depths of your heart, just for me.
Embraced by love, I
want to keep my life sparkling
[Music]
Papara
Papara Papara
[Music]
For example,
even if your eyes are wet right now, I can still hear your voice calling out to me.
The day with you
dies in my memory, like it's melting away an old picture.
In this world where if you stop something, something will spill out. If there's a light that says, "I'm sure the spring breeze will be like pine blossoms."  The
flowers of love will bloom as we reach our destiny
[Music]
If our wish for separation comes true, I want to live in our world again
That kiss, the
sun turns over, and the
flowers of water also
have a fragrance.
In my heart, which is about to die when I forget about you, I let the beauty of the love I have just learned bloom again. [Music] If I could stay with a heart that does not decorate the spring breeze like pine flowers, I would
not be able to touch you.  Even if my thoughts shift, I
won't forget.
If there is light that can be collected one by one, I will
turn it over
and make it bloom with the luck of turning it over. I will give you the flower of love.
[Music]
It's like a movie, it's
like a movie, it's like a movie, it's everywhere, it's a
road full of mistakes, how
many people get redone, what's wrong with it,
what's not good with it?  Tell me that much. I
made a misunderstanding. There's nothing I can do
about it. It wasn't like this. What was it like?
When I think about it, it's annoying, it's not like this, it's
not a bad thing, stop it now.  I wonder
when I'll
be able to play the leading role.
[Music] I
don't want to go on a journey or carry baggage, but I'm not even going to be
discouraged. I'm
going to start walking through the brightly shining streets of the city.  Well, it's
worse than not. It's not suitable for me. I
wish I could stop now, but I end up repeating it tens of thousands of times
and waiting.
[Music] It's a
false misunderstanding. There
's nothing I can do to stop it. It was true back then.
There was something that happened, something that happened, and
before I knew it, I was going to tell everyone again, so there's no way I'm going to play something or someone.
If it doesn't exist, just rewrite it. Look,
I'm always the one who's in charge.
The day of death will
come, so I
'll applaud and smile. I want to change it. I like the way it was here.
This
was weird.
[Music]
[Applause]  ]
[Applause] [Music]
When in the world will
you realize that the one who hates me is me? I
wish I had a friend who has gone silent.  It's
better if it's easier. Not having expectations
won't hurt
me. Even just the fact that I fell in love with you
changed everything and
started to hate me.
Love
is so powerful.
I've
been reborn. Please fall in love with me.
[Music]
When do people
start to be called adults? I
don't even understand myself, and I don't
want to do anything,
but I can't
meet you.
Maybe I'm looking
forward to my feet. It's a
gentle thing that makes someone fall in love with me.
[Music]
Unless I meet fatefully,
my heart won't move.
If I miss this love [Music], my youth will
be over. I don't hate me, I
fall in love with me.  It's a
desire that makes me want to turn to the side I felt in my heart.
Even if I lose everything, I can only see the front. I'll
go with all my might. I want
an answer, even close to my passion. I
fell in love with you,
but everything repeats itself.  I
started to sparkle.Does
even the fact that I met you have power?
I've
been reborn.Please fall in love with me.I
won't make you regret it.Please fall in love with me.
[Music]
[Music]  I
made it on my sleeve and just put it on there as a love.It melts in a flashy way.I
cut through the wind as if rolling over the moon.I
embrace all of the valleys that grow stronger with each passing moment.If I can't choose, if I choose, I'll
let out a roaring voice in the night.
What are the echoes of even that distant scenery that is covered with tears? It's
okay to remain as you are, no matter
how dark your feelings are or how long it takes.
[Music]  I'm the
only one left, and it's so pathetic that I can't let go of the flashy colors as long as I tie my body together.No matter
how difficult the times are going to be, I'll hold out my heart more than my words.I guess I
came this far to run away from all the dreams that hurt.
[Music]
If you can't choose, you should choose
If it's dark like a flower that sings and burns with a beautiful voice, then the
world that's too ambiguous will be ignored, and if it's as vivid as painting the morning after the night,
then no matter how deep the regrets are, no matter how expensive they are.  limit
If you want to drown out all the rest and make it all fluffy, go
ahead and get ready, even if you smile, do
n't love me.Sometimes it's boring when you wonder if you can make your hands sound, right?
Until I explode with drinks
[Music]
[Music] Let it
resonate and take it out, Hae
Baba
[Music] I'm
going to repeat the winning number of the previous one.  The one that
starts bubbling is the one in the book.I'm
not interested in anything.It's all over the place.It's so full, it's so
clogged,
it's so full of tears.
[Music]
Looks like you're tired of the usual New Year's Eve Let's all jump at the moment of New Year's Eve
Well, it's impossible to get everyone together. There's only three minutes left, so I'm
preparing just in case something like that happens
. You can create a world uniform just by drinking tea in space and time. You can
use that medicine to call your seniors. Call me,
call me.  Call me, call me, call me, call me, call me, call
me, call me, call me, call me, give up. There's
still plenty of Lily. Don't say 2023 is
lame. Next year, it's Udoshi Peko.
What are you doing? What do you think you're doing?
Question: When is the first sunrise? Do you know?
Color photos are relatively recent and serious. It
's this year.
The world is changing. It's
okay. I
won't miss it. Ah, I
mumble. Do I have to wake you up?
Flare,
Captain Noel.  No, why don't you chase after someone?
It's the end of the year, so
we have the luxury of being summoned by our karma,
so why not go east even just a little?  I'm
going to age faster than
everyone else. If I keep going like this, I'll get an office. I
can fight,
fight.
Sorry for the inconvenience. Thank you
for your company. [Music] Well then, I'll go. 864
[Music]
3210 Oh no, it's okay to do this.
Teku seniors are so cute Wow
[Music]
I'm strong even in Lela's radiance Meki-kun, are you reaching me? I wonder if I can reach you at 1mm,
charge my phi, challenge me, accelerate with all my might
You do your best, give me the biggest smile Sit down
Chine,
everyone, everyone, Minami
Min
[Music] The
theory that Ridako Minmi felt that she was waiting for a while, and that Dambi David made her feel like a daddy.I
do not accept objections. Words of viewing
Master, I've been watching the review from here Lyrical
Mo Let's
jump over this stupid wall and
go to a world that no one has ever seen.
Maya, it's crazy. It
would be great if we all gathered here with smiles on our faces.
[Applause]
I'm
just having fun.  The way
is the power
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I
want to show you the me that you love, but I'm a
little surprised, and I'm
worried that I can't do it right.  It's
not all about me, but I want you to find me.
If I were with you, I would be happy. Please
remember that I'm no good when I'm full, but I'm adding to my tail. If your
heart is small, it's
important that you come to me.  I don't feel like a place like that.
Chachakora
doradora annoying
[Music] It's a random
day. I
can't laugh at anyone from Daigo, lol. Here it is.
Sexy world,
I want to be honest, I don't want to be sexy.
[Music]
So let's
open it quickly
[Music]
All the countries are shaking in the darkness.
The words that echo with the Cerberus theory are bursting out and going crazy. My
paradise heart  I'll
reach that point, and from now on, I'll continue to unleash my mysterious
power, and the world will smile, too. When I
sing, Papa, we'll be together.  I'll
take it as it is, I'll let you fall into the darkness.
Let me hear you, princess.
Don't dream.
Let me hear it.
[Music]
I want you to fall in love with the roots even more. I'll
always say that softly to you.  I
can't let it go. I'm so obsessed with it. I
want to love you forever and ever. My heart and body
are dyed. I'm floating in the river. I can't talk anymore. I'm
definitely dying.
[Music]
[Applause]  I
love
you even more because I'm a star. The
music will never stop, and the music will never stop.
The caressing music of the universe will
surely never read.  What I've always
wanted to be is
not
Ku. I'm the one who goes deep.
Then I'm the star.
[Music]
I'm the star.
Stella
[Music]
Happy New Year.
A
[Music]
From the fearless ha,
revolutionary music, anti-war national symbol, two-party rolling evil 3
Running through the ICBM feeling,
those boys and girls from the Warring States period are floating in the air,
lost in the thousand cherry blossoms night, your voice won't even reach you  This is the
3,000 world where I am in charge of Noriko Banquet Steel. I
can't hear you lamenting the darkness of the world. Is the sky of Sera
facing Kasaso's battle?
[Music]  The
appearance of 100 battles is proof that we are going back and forth, and
he and he and all of us
gather together, and with the heart of a saint, we pass through all the questions with
ease,
and at the end, between the big applause, a thousand cherry blossoms
disappear into the night, and we see you.  I can't even hear your voice. I'm crawling through the
streets. I've
thrown 3,000 people into the darkness of the world. I can't hear you.
Give me hope. Launch the vanguard.
[Music]
[Applause]
Those boys and girls who run through the Kanjo line and are doing well Sengoku Musou
Yuki Nori Senbon I
'm lost in the night and your voice can't even reach me Here's a
song Hari Jumped down through the middle of that charge and disappeared into the cherry blossom night I'm
singing you and I'm dancing here  Hiroshi
Hit the seaweed
[Music]
Happy
New Year again. It's New Year's Day, so I decided to appear in a furisode.
How about last year's furisode?  I'll
be wearing the same kimono I wore in New Year's Shinbun.When I
actually try it on, I
feel a little more relaxed.Also, please
take a look at the stage too.There's
such a gorgeous stage.
Let's go.
This year, there are rabbits everywhere,
so there are rabbits flying around.
There's a rabbit, and there's a rabbit in the back, too.  It has
Mt. Fuji written on it, and everything else is pretty. Also,
there are flowers and Kakumatsu (Kakumatsu) on the other side too.
Look, there are also some magnificent trees.
With this kind of feeling, it feels like it's already a happy New Year.
On the top of the page, it says Spring.
Look, there's everyone, the baby doll, the rabbit, and the
cute and wonderful New Year's stage.
Thank you very much.
Oh, and it's not exactly this kind of clothes,
but do you remember this look? It
was in the newspaper looking like this.
Ankimo and Anki are both very happy right now,
and I'm also happy that I got to appear on New Year's Day.
And this one in the back.  Well, let's
take a look at it.The obi looks like this
, it has a very mature look to it,
and
the pattern is actually a flower, starting from the bottom.  The colors are
gradually getting brighter and brighter.
Kamishiro is also very
cute and I'm very happy to start January 1st with this kind of Nefuri.
Also, Florive is celebrating its 5th anniversary this year.
Five years ago, I
never thought I would be able to wear a long-sleeved kimono,
but I ended up wearing one without sleeves.  I
learned how to properly cut a long-sleeved kimono, and I gained a lot of friends, and now I'm able to
create wonderful programs with such wonderful staff.I
think it's because of everyone's support that I will continue to do so.
We will do our best, so
please continue to support Hololive this year as well.
Now,
since it's a new year, I hope we can give you lots of happy news.
Okay, let's go. First of all,
this year is the Year of the Rabbit, so Pecola.  It looks
like she's thinking of something bad. Her name is Hatta All Humanity Usagi Family. I
wonder what the plan is all about. This
is scheduled to be streamed on the official Hololive channel from 7pm today, January 1st. Everyone, 7pm.
Please keep an eye on the schedule.Next, we will
be holding the Hololive Creator Contest 2023 with Pixiv on Friday the 13th of this month.Illustrated
Swimsuit Costume Design Scenario with Hololive Theme  We
will be recruiting creators for the following 3 items for about a month.For details,
please check the official tweet on January 13th.Next, click
hereThe
Hololive Idol Project First
Live Bloom, in which past Hololive members have appeared, is currently being used by amateurs.  It's currently
airing on Bloom, so
whether you've seen it or not, please take this opportunity to check it out.For
more information, please search on the Ama homepage.
Tomorrow, January 2nd, Mikochi's New Year's costume
will be unveiled. It looks like they
have a lot of things planned,
so everyone, please check it out
. And then,
this is Seimatsu Mercury's second album,
Specter, to be released on Wednesday, January 25th.  This
is Oto's second album, and it
includes a total of 11 episodes written by gorgeous creators such as Ayase Seki Gakudan.Pre-orders are currently being accepted.Moreover, Hoshimachi
Mercury Second's internal shout-in
Crisis will be held on Saturday, January 28, 203
at the Tokyo Garden Theater
Tickets are currently on sale at Spawn For more information, please
check the various official websites.
And next,
this year too, we will be holding the Holo New Year Cup sponsored by Tokoyami Dad.
We're all looking forward to seeing who will be the strongest
, and please check out the winner of the small fry cup.Also, there have been
many announcements, and it
's finally the end.
From around noon on January 5th, my friend E-chan and
Spring Nodoka-chan's Hololive staff
will be broadcasting a look back at the year-end and New Year holidays.There will also be behind-the-scenes
stories from the staff's point of view, such as Masu Go Horokuru Holo, Countdown Live, etc.
Information on the year-end and New Year holidays can be found here.  Let's catch up on the broadcast!
Check out their Twitter for details.
So
please continue to support Florive Productions this year.
[Music]