[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
sorry i was doing my stretches
can everybody
hear me clearly
my skull
[Music]
down
hello
we are making cookies today
my dream cookies where's my other golovk
on it
oh yeah okay
um shouldn't be too difficult and
shouldn't be
taking too long either actually because
i realize i realized i looked up the
recipe and it's basically just throwing
everything together more or less
and i'm putting it on parchment paper
and then putting it into the oven not
even for that long only like 25 minutes
or something like that
sorry
um so yeah no glue
no hot glue no no no no
of course not
you think just because of that one time
that now i'll be making everything with
hot glue
[Music]
guns
no no no kiwawa wants to be serious
about this kind of thing you know
ah
[Music]
no hot glue cookies no so
i uh i don't i don't know why exactly
i suddenly i think i must have been from
some video or i don't know i know i
think
i think my my chocolate i don't know
what to call them chunky chocolate chip
cookie
uh craving has started well
actually uh my setup has really improved
today in some ways
um very comfy right now um
my chocolate chip chunky chunky
chocolate chip cookie
craving has started a while ago when i
think it was when i was at a bakery and
you know sometimes they have these big
ass cookies
the chunky chunky chocolate chip cookies
and i ate it and i was like yeah these
are so good wouldn't it be so nice to be
able to make them myself because they
they're pretty expensive if you think
about it
so
i asked you guys when was this like a
month ago
i asked you guys thanks for the
memberships and the renewals i asked you
guys
uh
if you guys have any like recipes that
you swear are the best
chocolate chunky chip cookie
recipes that you guys have a lot of um
how to say uh
[Music]
confidence in
and then a lot of you guys
sent me some recipes and
i'm sure all of them look great and i
would like to maybe if i'm not happy
with the first one
then i might then eventually i want to
try out through all those other recipes
but i think
if we're gonna do this right then i
think with this recipe we're gonna have
no issue yes so the thing is
i
went to
um a hotel with
um
rmt
uh a long time ago before her life
[Music]
hotel in england england the only time
that i ever went to london to england in
general
and we stayed at this hotel that i think
it's called uh doubletree by hilton
and the thing about the doubletree by
hilton hotel chain is a worldwide hotel
chain you may you might might know it
it's one of the
different hilton hotels um
if you go there and you check in or not
only after checking in but like
every day you can go to the reception
and they give you a freshly baked hot
cookie
[Music]
chunky chocolate chip cookies
i know
and we were so into those cookies i was
it was [\h__\h] cold uh when i was there
was winter time and um i i was like
every time when we were like outside
singing i was like i can't wait to go
back to the hotel to get me that hot ass
fresh chunky chocolate chip cookie man
because they are so good
we were so so crazy about them
yeah those are magical and i need to
tell us
looking forward to it every time and
when i was asking you guys for recipes
someone sent me
a recipe for that because i
i thought it was impossible to ever eat
that cookie again without going to the
hotel but apparently they share they
shared the recipe
uh at some point online it's still
online for that famous cookie how did i
know it's the same well it's because
it's shared by them
yeah i can't believe they are sharing
the recipe
not keeping it a secret what the [\h__\h]
if you tell me that recipe i don't have
a reason anymore to go to this hotel
you are basically destroying your own
business by giving away this secret man
but okay
um for me this is great i want to try
recreating that cookie um i think i
didn't really look at the other recipes
but i think it's mostly like
similar
uh ingredients let me take a look the
recipe is in english
so
this time you guys
can look at it and tell me if i'm doing
something wrong um might have an issue
with the measurements because they're
english
but
maybe we are digest so it says the
following
um
we stop this makes 26 cookies wait i
don't even know if i have
i can't i at least can't bake them all
at once if we make 26 cookies out of
this
but it needs a
half a pound butter
what's what's half a pound
[\h__\h] i'm already i hope i have enough
butter i bought one fresh thing butter
thing
how much is
half a pound
what's that in kilograms
250 gram okay i gotta look at how much
is in my butter
okay uh
softened two sticks
half a pound butter softens two sticks
what does that mean two sticks
what what is guys what does that mean
[Music]
this is one one sentence
two sticks
[Music]
what
what does that mean
that they want
200 what sticks you mean a package yeah
250 gram times two or what
like like a block or just 250 gram but
separated in two sticks
that's that's a weirdly specific
uh
request
okay
okay and it says soft and so i warm it
up a little bit in the microwave i
suppose but not so much it melts just a
little bit i suppose
this is what i'm getting from this 226
gram okay okay okay so as far as i know
baking is easy as long as you follow the
ingredient list recipe yeah yeah
and then we have
free food that free fourths
am i saying this correctly afraid of a
fourth
no no free for free free forbes free
forbes free forbes
free forbes
free
forbes yeah yeah
uh free for a free free fourth cup what
three four
a quarter three quarters
of a cup but like what cup
what size cup huh
i
i am once again confused of of by the
way sugar
um
three fourth cup three
quarters cup plus one tablespoon
granulated sugar
what
what wha wha
wha what what does that mean
[\h__\h]
one cup is around 250 milliliters
huh 960 grams okay okay
the cup is unused yeah but like there's
all sizes of cups
uh
i have a i have some sort of
measuring cup let me show you maybe this
applies let me let me let me put on my
oh my cooking sleeves
[Music]
shut the weight
i know camera is on its way just need to
be patient
um
but today might not be so exciting when
it comes to camera because i'm just
throwing [\h__\h] together into this big
bowl
uh so i got a mouse now for this left of
an extra mouse i couldn't use my other
mouse this is really stupid but it's so
simple it makes me happy um
the other mouse at my pc i never brought
it over because um
because it was like
put together nicely with you know the
cable binder thingies
no no not not casper
uh thankfully no real mouse
uh and so i was always
it was really shitty using my fingers on
this laptop on this touchpad but now i
have a mouse so a lot of things are
easier so uh camera reveal
safe okay
[Music]
hi
i yay most of the camera today will be
showing you this part yes yes this is
where everything will land in and then
we'll mix it which by the way i hope my
mom mommy are you watching right now so
i'm making cookies and this thing came
with this
and number one this let's call it number
one
number
oh sheet
number two
and i had another one that my mom knows
probably uh
oh no the outside is pretty reflective
but the inside seems fine it's just
channels don't worry
uh i don't know what to use
for
um
[Music]
no i i didn't bought by the mixer for
this specifically but
num number one is the dough hook
number two number two is good use two
yeah i i assume that it's going to be a
pretty sticky uh
thick
uh
[Music]
cookie dough
cheese for ah you guys say
what would i do without you guys
my mom didn't reply to me i'm not sure
if she's actually watching but usually
my mom is always watching my cooking
streams too because she must be so
worried about
what i'm doing
okay um
in that case i guess
let me
do that
i think that's how it was supposed to be
done
wait wait
maybe without the camera
[Music]
what am i doing wrong
i did this before once
uh
there's like uh
[Music]
i wait i know i know i know turn it
right yeah twist it twist it twist
twist it
ah it's in
it's
in
is it supposed to have so much
space too
wonderful
twist it twist
twist
[Music]
i feel like i'm getting closer though
uh maybe how do you counter
counterclockwise
[Music]
push up twist 90 degrees
push more and then turn it don't break
it uh
uh
instructions i don't know where they are
we don't have time to look for them no
no no no no no
[Music]
ah i got it
i got it
i i did it
yata
[Music]
by the way this is the the measuring
thingy that i have this thing
it has uh
it has
liter measurements it has milliliter
measurements it has cup it has cup
measurements
it has a half and a one and a one and a
half and a two and a two and a half and
a three
but we need
three fourths
[Music]
so we gotta think about that and then i
have one for flour
and a gram and sugar gram which is
pretty useful i would say
uh yeah
a success i have a measuring cup let's
go
yes yes
okay so the hulk the hook this reminds
me this reminds me of uh
this one reminds me of a pirates hook
like a bus buster hopefully i could i
could put this on my hand and now i
could be like
a pirate i'm a pirate what is that [\h__\h]
on the floor gosh it's such a mess
i am getting a kitchen extension
i'm getting a kitchen extension uh by
the end of the month so i'm really
excited about that
oh wait i can get rid of the
pinned comment now
okay
[Music]
oh i'm rolling around with my
with my um
office chair right now i brought it over
to the kitchen
it's much better than that stupid other
chair that i was sitting on it was
really making me feel stiff that empty
cup you don't know what miniature cup is
energy cup is uh
i'm gonna show you
nancy cup is uh when i left japan nancy
um
uh gifted me to
two cups from starbucks thermos cups
as a farewell yeah yeah and i'm drinking
out of it now iced tea actually it keeps
it cold at least
wait i can show you here
hello you see that
yes
nancy cup
oh
it's a
sakura design
but you didn't see the starbucks logo
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
you want some cookies too i could
instead of instead of
chocolate chips i could add cat kibbles
it looks pretty similar i think
i think they would like it but yes no
don't worry i'm not that stupid
we're not doing that
we're not doing that don't worry but i i
was thinking about it
maybe with different say
cat safe ingredients one could make a
cat i'm sure there's someone who made
that before one could make a cat
chocolate chip cookie where the
chocolate chips are
cat kibbles
[Music]
self-made cat treats
cat cookies
[Music]
just don't eat the wrong ones yeah
don't worry like
don't worry about it shut up
i know what i'm doing
the outside of this one is indeed
reflective but this is a different kind
of reflective it's not like a mirror
understand all
so shut up
[Music]
that's why i'm not showing you the
outside of this bowl just the inside
yeah the blue one
[Music]
i don't see anything
no no no no
no do you see me right now
no you don't
so
yeah
where i don't know
i'm meow oh i think you saw my cat
but as a reflection you don't really
[Music]
[Laughter]
general if it's not that yoga let me
know
oh my god my cat what are you doing up
there get down from the kitchen counter
smoothie
[Music]
she went into
a a spot that
she should not be and what the [\h__\h]
that's so cute though i gotta take a
picture wait let me take a picture
that's cute
[Music]
wow
that is absolutely adorable i kind of
want to leave you there cause that's
just too cute
[Music]
i don't even know how to get her
okay she she has a special
uh permission to stay up there because
it's just too funny
she's like um on the on the upper
kitchen counter you know the
the the one where you
put stuff in the one
that's mounted to the wall
yeah in the cabinet she's there's like a
good spot for a cat to fit just right in
yeah in the cabin it's so cute oh my
gosh
how the [\h__\h]
incredible okay let's see what genma
says
oh my mommy's writing to me on discord
good to know good to know
she's there if i need her okay uh
yes yes very dangerous i understand i be
careful thank you she says it's okay
oh mommy also says number two so you
guys were correct
number two is the right way to go
okay
so wait let me get the butter
let me add the butter
[Music]
oh perfect
the butter is 250 grams so we take
almost the whole thing
just
rip out a little like leave a little bit
bite
[Music]
my cat has decided to just observe me
from above just put the entire thing in
here
a little bit
and
less than the full package
uh okay well
uh
okay let me let me read the instructions
[Music]
i'm gonna read uh what instructions
so it says
cream butter sugar and brown sugar
in the bowl of a stand mixer on medium
speed for about two minutes
cream
what does a sentence mean
cream butter
[Music]
so cream is a verb in this case i have
to cream them
butter sugar and brown sugar in the bowl
of a stand mixer on medium speed for
about two minutes okay
okay we can do that we can do that we
can do that
cream yeah whatever that means that's i
think that's a weird choice of words but
okay and
makes them all are you coming down
smoothly
be careful
[Music]
be careful wait a second
no you're staying okay
but let me um
i guess
cream the butter
no not cream the butter but make it soft
let me open it up it's a fresh package
yeah yeah okay okay make it creamy i
don't understand i think i understand
yeah
let's make it creamy
okay
my dearest butter
so if this whole thing is 250
then this what's half of 250 125
so this is 125
[Music]
uh
i'm trying to measure it without
measuring it
[Music]
uh that's 250 that's 125.
how do i get to 226
probably with this is 150
125 and that is 250.
then my brain is not working
eyeballing i want to eyeball it
a butter is not gonna be a problem we're
gonna measure the rest of it properly
[Music]
uh i did not preheat the oven let's
preheat the oven
300 fahrenheit degrees
big 420 okay 300 just just what any
specific setting no okay
300.
i'm just gonna do the basic london
oh
oh it only goes up to 250 maybe it
should be a different one
[Music]
maybe
maybe uh
the one with the the one with the
ventilator the one
oh wait what
oh cells
oh oh oh you're right that's not celsius
i was thinking in celsius oh
wait so what what's 300
150 170
why is this
recipe so english huh
uh
100 175
170 okay 170 i believe
um
that's so low okay
170 equal
okay so preheating actually let
me do something
[Music]
okay
for some recipes i know that uh
they ask you to have the the thing that
you put the whatever on
to be cold before putting it in the oven
and in some cases it doesn't matter i
wonder if it matters here i didn't see
anything about it
but right now it's outside so it's going
to be cold
what 150
okay okay okay
don't worry it's just 30 right now but
okay 150.
150 it is
what okay
okay okay 150.
so uh back to the butter
[Music]
so i'm looking at
looking at this right now
let's help me guys
if this is 250 gram and we need 2
26 or something like that
maybe maybe around here
[Music]
one more
what do you mean sticks
um
90 percent
[Music]
that's
62.5
what do you mean what are you what
[Music]
what do you mean with sticks you just i
don't want to use my scale
i don't know how to use my scale
what even then what is a stick
uh
i have a scale but i i never really used
it before
just half it
and i'm gonna i'm gonna scoop it out of
there is that your towel yes yes that's
butter
uh
rectangular
well does it really matter it doesn't
matter does it
what does my mommy say
[Music]
is
so apparently in in england or maybe
also in america you guys are selling
butter and sticks
oh you funny people you're funny people
[Music]
we don't need to have them it doesn't
[\h__\h] matter
what for it's gonna all be one big mess
dough in the end
okay
so
i'm gonna
i'm gonna put in
[Music]
oh it's already getting pretty uh soft
uh you see that the new marking that's
that's what i'm gonna leave
and do you think that gets close to
i think it does i think it does
i think it does
more
that's that seems about right yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
close
yeah okay wait so um
should i mommy should i warm this up a
little bit i don't know cream butter
sugar and brown sugar in the bowl of a
stand mixer on medium speed and if i
just put it in there in like little
pieces
it's already [\h__\h] soft so i think i
think we're good
just gonna scoop them in
it's gonna be fine
[Music]
all this butterman oh my god
you're gonna tell me that my knife is
reflective next
oh my god i see your mixer from a
different angle
okay well then you see nothing now
we shall
[Music]
you guys hear it on bgm right don't tell
me this is this is
all silent all this time
just stops on the butter we need at
least five times
i thought this was a serious comment
read something there okay okay okay
i thought that was a serious comment i
mean i can give you maybe some tangents
sure but
it's pretty soft it's like a
stretch
strike
fake strike figure
i always buy this type of butter because
the other butter is always too
too stiff too hard i always get the soft
butter so it's already soft by default
yeah my cat is so cute oh my god
uh the burgers the burgers today my
business is cookies talk to the
talk to the sous chef
for the burgers
i think we got the butter down
[Music]
okay next up um
sugar and brown sugar must also go into
the bowl bowl and that is
uh
three what was it
three quarters
[Music]
of a cup plus one tablespoon tablespoon
is a small spoon right
but my problem is i have
only up to three
in theory though it goes up higher it's
just it's just it's not marked um
but there that should be four
if this is if here is four
and then this is two fourths
then
then this is free forks
is
tables oh tablespoon is a big spoon oh
okay
[Music]
and
how much is
three-fourths of
a cup of sugar in
in graham
does someone know that is there a
a translation for that as well
[Music]
115 you guys are amazing you guys are
amazing
really really
oh 150 okay
okay that's not even that much
so dad why is it that plus why does it
just not tell me an exact measurement
why is it
three fourths plus one tablespoon that
is so stupid but okay
okay i do uh i have my crystal sugar
because i think this is granulated is
krista
it's not the powdered sugar it's the cr
for we call it crystal sugar
i think granulated means that then so
uh
yeah yeah yeah okay okay 150.
[Music]
this is the right sugar
yeah
[Music]
oh i hope this is gonna turn out good i
hope they're gonna turn out good
that is
indeed
looking like 150.
[Music]
what where is it yeah i think it is okay
okay okay okay
they'll turn out great just gotta
believe thank you didn't you say you
don't have
i have a scale but
i'm use ah no no no for this i only have
to use my measuring cup because as i
said it says gram for sugar specifically
on the measuring cup and gram for flour
specifically on the measuring cup it
goes up to 1 000 for sugar and up to 600
for a flour do you know what i mean
and then i have it for water for
milliliters for milk and so on
eh
manuel are you sure
oh wait but i also have to add the the
the tablespoon right
uh wait is this so many people said 150.
it's 150.
goku said so
[Music]
wait let me look at let me look at this
one
[Music]
i think
i think the cup measurement is not
accurate on my on the back here makes no
sense somehow
wait the question though is
the sugar that it says here
is that do they mean powdered sugar or
crystal sugar granulated sugar
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] okay i'm bringing out my
measuring cup
am i measuring my measuring scale oh
[Music]
man
okay
[Music]
i'm not sure how to use this
yeah they might mean granulated but now
i'm confused okay how do i use this
again um
[Music]
i didn't measure the cup but it's
already in there let me get a different
something
[Music]
okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
uh 150 okay most people say 150. okay ah
ah 170 is a millimeter is done and i
don't want another hold up okay let's
put that in here
i'm putting the sugar in a different
container for now and then i'm trying to
figure out how to make the scale work
uh it worked a while ago when my mom was
here don't just
hello
mommy how does my scale work again
[Music]
oh my mom is typing i'm tipping my tips
on
now
mommy says i just have to poke it but it
doesn't react
don't tell me the batteries but
but i only used it once was it on the
whole time
nah
come on
talk to
me what kind of battery is in there
anyway
let me take a look
it goes off right like it turns itself
off like i think
we should
i can't open it
[Music]
ah
okay i do have another battery like that
and if i need it but
i don't wanna it has to work like this
batteries are a [\h__\h] light
this is
my conspiracy theory to you guys
they sell you batteries
but then they don't they don't work they
only work for like one day
what does that mean guys
they bamboozle us
to buy more and more batteries
it's a it's a huge conspiracy theory
yeah uh it's not working
[Laughter]
it's not working
but you know what if one of the 70 was
really in milliliters then let me just
re put it back in and see if it reaches
170 thresholds in the milliliters
let me see let me see
[Music]
in my cup i mean
almost
[Music]
um
let me add one tablespoon right one
tablespoon one tablespoon
one tablespoon
or no
nah
i don't even know where the [\h__\h] i put
those batteries so i don't think this is
gonna happen no camera is just currently
not on because nothing is happening but
there is a camera i already turned it on
and
away though
it's not just poking it there is a
button mama
mama
okay i just need to blame someone so i'm
blaming my mommy but okay so this um
so that the cup is
92 gram but then i i think i can reset
it
[Music]
don't change eh
okay now it's zero okay okay okay okay
okay okay now i fill in the sugar
wow
and it's 154
how much do they want 150
okay pretty accurate guys i would say
and now i add one tablespoon
one tablespoon oh my god i'm making
cookies
[Music]
i have the power now now that i have a
measuring skate my cat oh god i thought
you something fell down from the from
the from the thingy but it was just my
cat so you have decided to go somewhere
else now wonderful
wonderful you freaked me out man
so i'm adding uh
suddenly there's just
a smoothie
colored object
flying down
[Laughter]
it was my cat it was my cat
[Music]
okay
okay so
now i need wait let me fill that in
[Music]
oh i hope i was supposed to put it all
in at the same time
and then three fourths cup
so 150 again
uh of a packed light brown sugar now i
don't know what that means packed light
but i have brown sugar
[Music]
i don't know what packed or light means
but i just have brown sugar
this is a really fancy recipe
what does packed light mean does someone
know
not compressed
okay yeah mine is just
not compressed yes yes
[Music]
doesn't matter doesn't matter
sounds good enough okay okay don't put
too much in
[Music]
you do compress it what does that mean
packed means you compress it light is a
type of brown sugar [\h__\h]
well
normal brown sugar must do the trick
i was looking at the i was looking at
the shelf in the supermarket and
honestly i didn't see anything that's
called light brown sugar
in
at least not in german if it said if
it's a direct translation then honestly
i didn't see anything like that
um maybe it's a different term but i
just have brown
which i think is brown sugar
oh i am sitting straight you don't have
to tell me that now i know i'm not even
a cat i can't even not sit straight
right now
yeah i am okay so uh one three fourths
is the same so it should be 150 again uh
don't turn yourself off
okay we start at zero
zero
uh brown sugar seikatsu
okay
to 150 we go right right guys
150 right
[Music]
is brown sugar heavier than the other
sugar
40 50
56 58
[Music]
it's not coming out that nicely
19.
[Music]
it's kind of like stuck in there and has
formed a block i think 100
we're gonna get there 110 120
and 40.
[Music]
oh
152 for some reason now but okay
that's fine
okay
that was easy
so yes
brown sugar
okay
[Music]
so
now i will turn this off because i gotta
mix it it's gonna be really loud because
the microphone is really close
and it says it says
it said something about creaming it
cream butter sugar brown sugar in the
bowl of a stand mixer on medium speed
for about two minutes
i don't know what medium speed is
supposed to be
but we'll find out two minutes two
minutes two minutes
two minutes two minutes i kinda wanna
show you but let me try first without
showing you um
so i put this how does it work again
like this
okay
uh and then so i have one two three four
five six
so i would say medium is free
maybe
yeah
okay
it's gonna be loud
i'm scared wait it's not even plugged
though
is it no it's not plugged
[Music]
oh damn in cable is
um
[Music]
oh
okay please don't electrocute me
[Music]
okay
why are some of these
electric outlet thingies so tough
okay okay now it's now it's connected
i'm scared let's go two minutes
[Music]
i'm scared
one two three
four
five
six
seven
eight
nine
ten
eleven
uh
[Music]
is
your face
oh good idea good idea good idea
let me just
move the sides into the middle
but it's looking nice
it's becoming a creamy uh mass indeed
yeah yeah
okay
excusable it's kind of noisy in my
kitchen
okay one more minute one more minute
[Music]
look
one minute probably about that
okay
okay enough enough of that what's the
next step add eggs vanilla and lemon
juice
um
wait what sorry one second
i didn't screenshot the thing properly
let me open it up separately
yay
there it is
add eggs vanilla and lemon juice
blending with mixer on low speed for 30
seconds then medium speed for about 2
minutes very specific or until light and
fluffy scraping down bowl
what
okay and eggs vanilla lemon juice so
uh eggs
was i think two eggs aloe eggs
two large eggs i have excellent [\h__\h]
is that a problem
is
maybe maybe the british l is a austrian
xl
[Music]
no no problem right
egg size yeah we don't want to
discriminate
um
no discrimination of egg sizes
no no no every size good size
[Music]
who's a good egg who's a good egg a
yogurt egg you're a good egg
where's that egg who's a good egg
[Music]
it's gonna be fine you're gonna be eaten
by me it's an honor don't worry
though we're gonna see this all right
[Music]
calm down
it's gonna be fine
big egg
[Music]
no space here oh [\h__\h] i should have oh
[\h__\h]
wait wait
wait oh god oh wait
wait wait wait my egg is spilling
[Music]
i need to lift
ah okay okay
egg
[Music]
okay
uh kind of operate with uh with um
gloves i don't want to do it with gloves
to be honest
[Music]
egg has uh joined the cookie mask
number one
number two who wants to be the lucky one
you do you want to be the lucky one who
wants to be the lucky one
do you want to be the lucky one
[Music]
do you want to be it
yeah
still so young
but you are the chosen one
your destiny is becoming a cookie
[Music]
oh my god
join your friend at least you're not
alone
at least you're in us together with your
friend
yeah
check the weight
[Music]
check the legs
okay
and so that was um
a
egg and then one
it says one and uh four of teaspoons
vanilla extract okay okay a teaspoon
measurement i can do
teaspoon teaspoon
but what the [\h__\h] is the fourth of a
teaspoon
man they're already so tiny how the [\h__\h]
am i supposed to measure a fourth
huh
so one teaspoon and then a little bit
eh
yeah okay uh vanilla extract ready where
did i put my uh
where did i put that
vanilla extract
[Music]
cat hairs on my gloves hallelujah
vanilla
rip those eggs
and they were younger than you you're
already a chicken a full grown chicken
and you see those younglings die how
does it feel to you huh i mean those
i will i will
i can't tell you one thing guys those
eggs were never really alive i know it's
it's shocking
it's also
they don't come from kfp
i would
never
not
give my eggs the chance to live
they all need a chance in life
because they're all meant for great
things
they weren't alive to me
yeah i guess they could have if they
would have fertilized them maybe they
could have had a proper
life surely um
anyway i'm using
i'm using
i hope this okay
it says uh
bio which means uh what again i forgot
[Music]
vanilla extract
so that should be fine
vanilla extract organic oh yeah organic
only in my kitchen if i can
yeah
okay
and what does it say oh do i have to be
quick in between the mixing steps i hope
not
one and a fourth
uh
[Music]
help me out guys
oh it's pretty thick
so i would say that's one
uh
why not a spoon
and then a bit more
maybe that's one-fourth
honestly i think for vanilla extract
it's good if we have a little bit more
because
you gotta love that vanilla taste
although i i don't remember i don't
recall those cookies really tasting like
vanilla though you know what i've almost
wanted to add
maybe i'll do it after these ones
succeed i want to add uh
orange um
something like orange something that
makes it taste like maybe orange peels
or something
cause i've eaten
cookies before with a slight orange
taste
and it's so
good
it's so good
yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay that and
one fourth of a teaspoon
freshly squeezed lemon juice
it's not freshly squeezed but i did buy
lemon juice
um
in you know in one of those bottles i
hope that's fine
one fourth that's like how much
[Music]
i'll just put in like a little bit
it's not a full spoon it's not even
[Music]
whoops
oops that's the cap of this
[Music]
it's a chicken's heart no it's kidding
just kidding uh wait i got it i got it
i've retrieved it
okay
it's ridiculous that i bought a full
bottle of this [\h__\h] when i only put in a
tiny tiny tiny squeeze of it
and it's gonna go bad
probably soon so it's all going to waste
unless i drink it
out of the bottle directly at the end of
the stream maybe we should do that
ah oh you know what i could make um
there's a there's a popular drink
[Music]
a simple very simple popular drink in
austria uh people didn't really order it
where i came from originally but i've
come to know more and more and more
people who like to order a soda citronet
uh which is just a sparkling water with
a squeezed lemon
yeah
that's it so maybe i could use it for
that
[Music]
lemon juice should be going good
good for at least are you really really
squeezed almond squeezed lemon juice
like that
is it good for so long
sounds refreshing it is very refreshing
mmm it's very popular my friends always
order it
it's yeah like a weak lemonade just just
a little bit of uh
lemon taste not too strong not like a
lemonade
not like a full on lemonade
okay everything is in now i think that
everything for now uh it said
uh eggs vanilla lemon juice blending
with the mixer on low speed for 30
seconds and a medium speed for two
okay you know what i'm going to use my
phone now to count maybe
wait 30 first
30 seconds
and then two minutes
we can do this we can do this
okey dokey
[Music]
um
one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
nine
ten
eleven twelve
thirteen 14
23 24 25 26
nice switching to medium
oh timer time and timer timer uh
go
it sounds so speedy but it's medium
it was supposed to
end up looking
fluffy until light and fluffy
light and fluffy is the key word
19 20 21
is this really medium
i hope this is
we're fine 41 now 42
that's medium okay
[Music]
can someone play some eurobeat
drifting in the 80s or 70s
do you have that eurobeat hinatory remix
right now if yes can you send it to me
on discord i don't have it on this piece
uh laptop
you can even send me a youtube link that
works too
one minute sixteen one minute seventeen
eighteen
she has it she has it
we're gonna use it next time we mix
okay
um
half a minute
it's it doesn't quite look fluffy
but
20 more seconds
10 10 more seconds although i should
probably end it now because i started
early late i started late
is that fluffy
i don't know it really looks just like
juice
did i do it wrong scrape sides
[Music]
was that supposed to do that in between
um
[Music]
so now
the sides are indeed still kind of
sticky
is it supposed to be like that i wonder
scrap scrap sides mix a little more it
didn't say mix it more in the thing but
[Music]
mix a bit more
yeah there's no flour in there just yet
okay
[Music]
uh i guess i'll mix it a little bit more
but wait what does the the next step say
uh
a scraping down
bowl with mixer on low speed add flour
oats baking soda
salt and cinnamon blending for uh about
45 seconds
you think i can add all of that so
quickly
i think i'll
only mix it for 45 seconds
er okay
um
so i think i prepare everything
before i start mixing again
[Music]
and put it all in my in my mixing cup
and then just pour it already mixed
together into the rest
i hope that's fun add spin add spin and
spin but there's 45 seconds like what
the [\h__\h]
yeah i'm gonna prepare it
[Music]
put it into separate is it okay if i
just put it all in one bowl
uh
flour
flour how much flour two
two
and one fourth cups flour help chat
two and one fourth
a quarter one two and one quarter two
cups and one quarter
cup of
flour flour flour flame flour flour
280 180 okay okay okay
i shot
[Music]
280 gram
oh yeah
uh 100
200 250 was it 250
[Music]
i think you guys said two did you guys
say 250
[Music]
180 okay
thank you
oh 288 oof okay
is that okay is that too much how exact
do you have to be
and then we have
we have some i have some half up looking
[Music]
rolled oats i don't know what road means
but i have oats i think i think i looked
it up when i was in the supermarket and
rolled oats translated to half a flock
so that is half a cup of rolled oats
you guys are already looking at the
recipe aren't you
45 gram okay so i reset it to zero
my scale
zero and now i add a 45 gram
they wear like bigger um rolled oats and
like smaller ones i wasn't sure which
ones to get but i got the smaller ones i
hope that's
not bad
ah oh oh well
wait how much was it 45 45 45
okay
[Music]
that's 42 i'm gonna leave it at that
it's fine okay and then what was the
other thing
um
baking soda
and salt and cinnamon it was like a
pinch of cinnamon and a pinch of salt so
let me just pour that in right now
this pinch is a tiny bit right just a
tiny bit
okay i hope that's not too much it was
just a tiny bit
and uh
cinnamon
oh wait one teaspoon oh then i might
need a bit more
[Music]
okay
a teaspoon of sugar and then uh cinnamon
was a pinch cinnamon was a pinch
cinnamon is just a little bit
i hope that's considered a pinch
[Music]
teaspoon that yeah yeah don't worry
don't worry i didn't put in a tablespoon
and then
uh yeah one one teaspoon of baking soda
i bought one package
by the way
uh in german
we call
baking
soda
natton
i think
it's very confusing i almost i knew this
before but i still almost bought
uh in german
bak polva which is baking powder because
we don't really i think unless you're
like baking a lot as a hobby we don't
use baking soda that much
um
[Music]
in in austria i think
i feel like in in america you guys use
baking soda for everything like i've
seen like people use it to clean [\h__\h] or
to cook [\h__\h] or to to make a face mask
or to wash their hair like you guys use
it for literally everything it's
fascinating but we don't really
we don't really have that baking soda
culture to be honest if anything we
would use it for
baking i guess but yeah it's called not
on here it's kind of
um hard to find in the supermarket at
least for me
it's not much
not big big uh
big in the shelf
baking soda culture
by
north america
at least in in my brain
it's a north american thing
because i see all these youtube videos
yeah you can use baby soda for this and
that and for this and that it's
fascinating so that's a teaspoon
a teaspoon let me use the same teaspoon
i used before
[Music]
is this okay
it's just okay
[Music]
it's very flat
or should it be a bit more
okay
[Music]
ah oh i already put that one in okay
well the rest is in uh this this cup all
together i think that was it um
on low split speed add flour oats baking
soda salt and cinnamon blending for
about 45 seconds don't over mix and then
remove bowl from mixer and stir in
chocolate chips and ones ah we're almost
there but i have to um i have to cut i
have to
uh yeah cut
make the walnuts small um so we'll do
that once everything else is done i
didn't do that yet
okay
uh okay oh my god so
low speed 45 seconds oh dear oh dear oh
dear uh
okay
okay low speed
is
lighting
20. this is correct
i don't think
[Music]
is
yeah a few more seconds
love it
there's like part of it is on top of the
mixing thingy but okay okay okay oh it's
looking like cookie dough it's kind of
looking like cookie dough i'm gonna turn
it off and one
two
three four five don't over mix don't mix
don't over mix don't do a mix
oh
is this how it's supposed to look like
you see this
and i'm supposed to put in the walnuts
and the chocolate chips with uh my my
big spoon perhaps
i i will show you the consistency it's
like
this
this is fine
[Music]
looks good okay
um then give me a moment
and
um i don't have
enough space here
okay how much how much walnuts was it um
one what what the [\h__\h] are all these
cups one cup and three
quarters of
chopped walnuts
[Music]
uh 220 grams
okay
[Music]
these are
i only have 150 grams so
i guess i don't even have to measure
them
i didn't think that it would need so
many
[Music]
all of it goes in
yeah
i hope the walnuts are not that
important
so i will chop them uh i wanna
how small they should end up but okay
i'll be shopping i'll be shopping on my
chopping board
chopping board goku shopping board
[Music]
yeah it's for for texture for texture so
i think i think i think it's fine i
think it's fine
they're gonna be
fine
i don't think it will make that much of
a big difference let me actually uh put
some things away because it's getting
too crowded here
gonna put things away
what am i gonna do with all the oats now
i don't eat oats
at all like
they taste boring i guess they're just
gonna make more cookies
[Music]
gotta eat more cookies make more cookies
special
eat oats
no but i guess you can put oats in like
like smoothies as well right
[Music]
i think i've seen people do that before
and then this can go this can go
and this can go
[Music]
whoa
okay
[Music]
i would be a cookie
oh
i'm sorry
i'm not an oatmeal fan but i'm sure
there's like so many people in the chat
who would love to eat you who's up for
an oatmeal cookie right now
raise your hands
i'm sorry
i wonder if the cookie dough is gonna be
fine it's gonna probably take me a while
to cut all of these
uh
[Music]
cut all of these um
walnuts
do that do i need to be like stressed
out about this
there's a lot of nuts here
oh
choco banana oatmeal
no need no stress okay have you got who
here has made cookies before themselves
cookies like these like not not not
basic boring cookies but chocolate chip
cookies like these the ones that i'm
making
you guys want to see this
you can see a little bit
[Music]
only a little bit
only a little bit just
[Music]
what kind oh oh i don't i only have like
i didn't there was not much choice for
um
for the chocolate chips i wanted bigger
ones but i only got these
[Music]
so
yeah
i hope they're good i wanted better
quality
it's just a supermarket brand quality
that
[Music]
i'm not good at
doing this chopping the walnuts
i think it will work out
that doesn't look like fun
[Music]
can i freeze
some of this dough
[Music]
can i like
kind of like
put some of it away and make more
tomorrow yeah or like not freeze but put
it in the fridge and make more tomorrow
[Music]
can i is it still good tomorrow what if
i okay so someone said 465 gram
[Music]
is 465 gram how much i would need i only
have a hundred so
that's like less than half of this dough
you're supposed to chill this okay this
is probably good
[Music]
i do have like a cooking chocolate which
i could chop up i don't know if that
would work too
i do have cooking chocolate you know the
bar is of chocolate
[Music]
i suppose that might work
that works
but it won't look so pretty
because like this has a proper shape and
the ones that i would cut would probably
look like [\h__\h]
it will work it'll be fun
do something okay let me see let me see
let's see
my dad
i want to see
[\h__\h] i thought i was just looking at the
packages and i thought i have one
package
why would that not be enough i didn't
realize that this recipe needed so much
[Music]
i'm not sure if this is really
the proper chocolate for this because it
says
first of all it's uh
foil milk it's milk chocolate but it
says curvature
which is usually used for like um
glazing chocolate over a cake or
decoration
like i think it will melt
very quickly
because the others
these ones they say
on the packaging they say
they say
um
they said something about out there like
oh yeah back fest
there is a sign that says back fest
which means like
uh it uh if you bake it
it will
it will survive
which is how i take the
the let's see what my mom says has my
mom shared her thoughts with me
oh damn it i forgot to use the eurobeat
[\h__\h]
[Music]
how i'm from with the flash cup oh
[\h__\h]
yeah that's what's good okay my mom says
that the cougar turret chocolate is fun
it's milk chocolate though and the other
one is salt bitter i generally don't
like bitter chocolate but this is good
so we can mix it
so i just have to chop up this [\h__\h] too
okay
i'm gonna turn off the camera so that i
can make a mess
[Music]
okay
i have to cut the walnuts
these walnuts
these walnuts specifically
are the ones that i am cutting
not those walnuts
but these walnuts right
[Music]
these
walnuts
[Music]
um
it's valentine's day guys oh my god i
completely
i
i don't know but yesterday was more like
valentine's day for me because i was
making those valentine's day cards today
i don't really have that
feeling anymore i feel like it's not
valentine's day anymore
and also because of the release of today
that felt like valentine's day to me i
don't know
do you guys have the same feeling
yeah i'm not in the mood man
where is the valentine's day moon
where did it go
[Music]
exact same feeling
does this look okay to you
i still didn't cut a lot of them but do
you see this
you see this does it look okay i think
it looks okay
[Music]
i'm just gonna put it in a cup
for now
looks good
should it be a bit more chunky there's
like a lot of like small
parts but hello
okay
[Music]
i spilled
i spilled some of that
okay cutting the rest that kind of uh
left my chopping board
yeah i should have chopped this
beforehand sorry guys
but did you guys enjoy dorian
have you already found all the
references in the music video
because you know kanauru likes likes
kana uru
likes to put a lot of references
in the video
i i found a lot of them
[Music]
you you tried
it's it's so good because like it makes
you want to re-watch the video many
times so hopefully
dodi ming-chi-chu
will be replayed over and over and over
again and i think we should say instead
of streaming stream don't mean to we say
streaming choo choo
[Music]
it's easier
to do
[Music]
changed her profile
picture yay
so nice of her
[Music]
i'm matching again guys i'm matching
again
i'm constantly matching with someone on
twitter nowadays
very nice
yeah we're gonna change it after a month
though i think so
this time it's not like
whoever changes it first
don't worry
we don't want i don't want my heart to
be broken again so we have a deadline we
have a one month deadline on white day
we're gonna change it back
[Music]
we have matching profile pictures crazy
it's it's uh
it was it was bound to happen eventually
so
yeah yeah
yeah she said oh it's good that she
changed it first she knew that her heart
was gonna be broken because i was gonna
change it for this
for this um specific
song cover but but no
you could have told me enough i didn't
even know
it's okay oh guys did you also see this
schedule schedule very exciting for this
month so we have whole talk with judea
senpai
we're starting with the third gen now i
might go back to the
missing members
that i have yet to interview from
previous generations we might go back
there eventually but for a while we
might stick with 3rd gen
um
yeah
and uh
i'm looking forward to collabing with
senpai again because we were talking
about oh let's let's collab again but i
was like what should we do and she was
also like yeah i wonder what should we
do
and we we're both like oh let's think
about it and we couldn't think of
anything
now
this is
this is another collab on my channel but
yeah
uh i'm i'm glad to have kudera senpai
over
once again
and
uh
hopefully we can learn a lot about
footage and but she's so sweet
[Music]
so sweet i hope she's gonna give us a
musical performance as well i hope so
and um mo no pony will be on my channel
by the way it will not be monopoly
madness first i wanted to play monopoly
madness because the trailer looked fun
but then i didn't i don't know if i
already told you this but i looked at a
gameplay
did i say this during my pokemon stream
but i looked at the gameplay and i
figured you know what it actually
i eventually want to play it but
the gameplay actually doesn't look that
much fun so i i decided to play the
normal monopoly than normal the monopoly
plus version
yeah
monopoly plus
on pc but it's like you can play it
everywhere
yeah yeah but for like if you have like
a
playstation or a switch that where you
want to play it on then you need an
online membership and stuff which you
don't need if you play it on computer pc
yeah yeah once again pc is superior
oh the reason why i invited those
members to be honest i wanted uh to mix
it up a bit more because i know i collab
a lot with these
girls
maybe not that much but like with inna
at least
but the thing is like i've i i wanted to
have gouda in the collab and then i
figured well
it would be a pain in the ass if i would
invite uh
um
like australian or japanese time zones
because then we have like the whole
globe again and so i only chose
girls with like you know um
time zones of the western hemisphere
wait wait not hemisphere
you know over there over there somewhere
around
uh north america
yeah that's that's why i chose those
girls and uh i also wanted to ask crony
but
um
she didn't reply in time so
and i think her pc i i'm not exactly
sure of her pc state
so that's dad and then sana bay and so
on
there
they live in
a shitty time zone at least if we
combine everyone
um but don't you worry guys i want to do
another monopoly
collab eventually where i have
um
other time zones covered yeah
she sent her pc in today oh is that so
[Music]
yeah cause since i'm like in the middle
in europe
um
i can collab with an a and i can collab
with uh
like
sea and all that
but mixing both together is
someone has to suffer so i didn't want
to do that
um but yeah i
i put some members together
and i i would have also wanted to invite
ame of course but amma is so busy right
now and and she won't be there for
uh the day where the collab is happening
so yeah another time another time
there's always another time and the
thing is with amen
i wanted to also do a collab to
celebrate the dreaming tutu release but
uh
i didn't want to stress her out too much
schedule looking busy as [\h__\h]
so we're doing it once she comes back
and i was thinking
of doing a vr chat collab with those
models that we used in the music video
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
and then i wanted to teach her um the
dreaming to dance in the video it was
immersion is gonna be ruined but maybe
you notice it by the dance moves it was
not us dancing
so i want to um learn the choreography
until then and then teach her in vr chat
how to dance it but then again i was i
realized um
that i couldn't monetize the the song
cover so i wouldn't be able to monetize
just a little bit of the inside talk too
real maybe
but then i wouldn't be able to monetize
the stream either so i was thinking
maybe just um
do different songs it doesn't have to be
dreaming to two maybe maybe i just teach
her different dances
yeah uh
maybe like
i know that dance by heart
yeah
okay am i done chopping these [\h__\h]
walnuts or what i think they look good
i think i think it's okay
i i don't know why i'm doing this on top
of my
parchment paper
sounds like so much fun yes yes i
thought it would be cute because it has
a nice connection to the
to the purpose to the music video
[Music]
and we can make good use out of those
new models that i got commissioned um
i sent uh the model maker preacher
preacher
i sent her a design
of school uniforms how i wanted them to
look like
and
then
she made them
i think i think it's a she i might be
wrong sorry if i'm wrong
they made made the models
uh
according to my wishes yeah they're
specially made
for this music video
uh for sure
i made a big mess
[Music]
uh
it's a big mess what this works this
works
okay okay okay
all right
all righty i got the nuts and i got the
oh now i have to cut the
chocolate
wait
[Music]
let me get the bigger the bigger cutting
board
wait so the chocolate is
the extra chocolate is 200 grams so even
if we combine them we don't quite get to
uh where we want it to get but it's
close close enough 300 gram total
so i'll i'll cut it all
[Music]
but i don't know how i should cut these
should i try to
i wonder if they get smaller when i bake
them
but i guess i'll i'll cut them into
rather than just chopping them randomly
i'll
try to
cut them into a specific size
five to ten millimeters
[Music]
they do get just a bit smaller if i bake
it just get some chunks
wait a second i'm having some issues
here opening the stupid package
[Music]
don't be such a [\h__\h]
i should take off my gloves for this
part
reduce the cookie mask
is it actually safe to eat cookie dough
i know people keep on talking about
eating cookie dough and there's cookie
dough ice cream
i think in moderation it's safe right
in moderation i think i think i think
that's good
so
oh it's so oh it's so
hard to cut
[\h__\h]
[Music]
eh raw egg not safe but then again
there's people who drink i i've met a
person before who is like very very
sporty actually a celebrity
and uh
for breakfast
not only for breakfast i think like all
the time
he would eat several raw eggs and drink
them just like that that's that's all he
ate for breakfast crazy crazy crazy
crazy not mister yodo not me yodo
yo
those are so
hard
[Music]
okay that looks chunky very good i think
this might actually be
good adding that milk chocolate
different kinds of chocolate
i've seen cookies being sold like that
they have different
kind of
chunks in it
uh
it's the mix of eggs and flora oh that
that's that's dangerous
not a hotel
[Music]
i suppose i shouldn't make it too small
otherwise the whole cookie is gonna be
like a chocolate
mess
yeah
this is probably fun
very slightly dangerous very slightly
dangerous my quality plus you have today
oh it's so fat and soft i love it nice i
want i want mine too i don't have mine
yet
[Music]
actually
i've i'm supposed to receive a package
from my company
like already it was supposed to arrive
days ago but i wasn't home and a
neighbor
uh
received it instead
and i haven't been able to track them
down i hope they didn't steal my package
but i've been going over there like
every day
ringing the bell and nobody opens like
several times a day
in the morning in the evening
during noon time all the time just can't
get a hold of them
i wonder what's in there it might be omo
cat merchandise it might be the plushie
i know i'm not sure
i i think it's almost merged though
probably it's just too big
ah the bigger the better the bigger the
better
yeah
for chocolate chunks
i think the bigger the better
can be pretty chunky
merch yeah i think it's probably uh uh
yeah the omo camera chairs are wrapped
today nice
[Music]
yeah oh the omo cat uh thing that i told
you that i wanted to do um with kelly um
is probably happening at the end of
february
[Music]
you know the
thing the thing the thing
the review the fashion
uh outfit
coordination review i need to figure out
a proper title um but it's gonna be us
reviewing
[Music]
uh how you guys combine
those clothes that you ordered with
other things and how you
style theme
[Music]
i hope i know that a lot of you guys are
maybe a little bit shy but i hope that
some of you guys participate anyway you
can totally censor your face and all
[Music]
if you feel a need to
sorry it's really loud
i'm making chunks
[Music]
i already saw some cute people
posting cute pictures of them wearing
the merchandise already so i hope they
will be participating
uh in the actual
event
[Music]
and guess what
omoket herself is gonna be part of it
too yeah
the creator
she's gonna um judge
together with me and kelly
yeah
we asked her if she wants to be part of
it and she said yes
[Music]
exciting
almost done guys sorry i could do this
faster probably but
i'm slow
i'm slow very slow
oh
noodle arms no no no no no no no no no
no
no no no don't you say that while i have
a huge ass knife in my hand
don't you dare
yeah
[Music]
okay
so
[Music]
you
oh it's a [\h__\h] earthquake in my
kitchen
[Music]
said the cat here that's the catcher
a few cat hairs
i'm strong
actually um actually actually this week
um
my physical therapy is starting again so
looking forward to that
yeah that was kind of a break in january
because
they kind of [\h__\h] up scheduling my
my appointments
good job but okay
but now i'm going back
have i been doing
my exercises properly
maybe
[Music]
every once in a while
but even when i don't do like all of it
um
like before the stream for example i
just did like
five minutes it's better than nothing
right
and hey i went skiing which was a whole
[\h__\h] workout
for a couple days and i went swimming as
well so i would say that kind of um
is even better than doing my
when my thingies
[Music]
no
don't you agree
[Music]
are we sure
okay
oh my god
i need to wash my hands but i'm done
cutting the chocolate
uh
now i only
i don't know what you know when you cut
this kind of uh block chocolate
there's like a lot of tiny
tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny
tiny pieces of chocolate i don't know if
i should throw them in as well but it's
like so tiny i don't know what will
happen if i throw them in there
um like yeah slivers
slivers
it's it's like
scrapes scrapes of chocolate
thread them in
wouldn't hurt to throw them shavings
yeah
stuff like that
uh should i find a man okay okay if you
say yourself
[Music]
oh sure
it's like melting while i'm cutting it
okay and then the package of the proper
chocolate chips
the ones that are not milk chocolate but
you guys are seeing the recipe
uh what did it say again
i'm not sure if i even bought the right
one that they wanted in the recipe but
uh
it was not dark chocolate what did they
call it again okay no irl there there
was you just came too late but i might
uh turn it on again in a little bit
it said some type of specific chocolate
ah yes semi-sweet oh that's 56 percent
cacao oh is that so
uh this one has 50 so it's about right
actually good good job me
okay uh hand washing time b or b
boy
[Music]
okay
the moment we've all been waiting for
[Music]
we're finally gonna put the chocolate
and the nuts
into the cookie dough
and then we're gonna put them
on the part parchment the baking paper
the parchment paper
yes yes yes and then we're going to
throw them into the oven
nuts
nuts walnuts
these walnuts into the cookie dough
we're gonna throw them not on the ground
but into the cookie dough
just gonna put my
gloves back on
and the
paper the baking parchment paper yeah
it's really messy now so i'm going to
change it into a fresh one
[Music]
it's time it's time
i'm excited i hope they taste good oh
yeah by the way um um it didn't say
anything about shaping them so you just
put like a
like
it will shape itself while it's baking
right i just have to put like a little
bit of a blob onto the paper
i suppose
yeah just a
drop
[Music]
a
it says three tablespoons per cookie oh
okay
three tablespoons
[Music]
wow
wait a second
[Music]
i have to clean the spoon because i ran
out of spoons
all righty
camera i
think i can
turn you on
oh
yes
my cookie dough doesn't even look like
that much but yeah okay
[Music]
it's time
there's a cat here there he saw that
[Music]
a tiny tiny cat hair can i lift that
even more though maybe i should take
that off
how do i take that off again ah there we
go there we go
[Music]
no
see all of that that just dropped on my
parchment paper
oh my god
can i just drop it in there it's just a
little bit
just a little bit okay okay
okay
okay here we go
so i'll just
put it all in and then i'll
mix it i'll mix it
[Music]
very creamy but there's so many
ingredients in there now
oh i think i think even though we still
don't according to the
according to the recipe we don't have
enough
chocolate and not enough nuts
but
the ratio looks good to me to be honest
[Music]
it looks totally fine to me
i'm so hungry
[Music]
i can't i can't i'm done
did it really say three table
tablespoons let me see
[Music]
portion dough with a scoop about three
tablespoons ah onto a baking sheet lined
with parchment paper about two inches
but the fog is two inches i don't know
i don't want i want i don't want them to
stick together we want to save a safe
space in between but i wonder how many i
i can even get on this one plate
two thumbs five centimeters two thumbs
five centimeters five cent really
okay you're gonna be the judge of that
guys wait uh uh
two tablespoons
three tablespoons so
oh
wow they're gonna be so amazing
okay
maybe you if i put it
here
here here here then you're gonna see it
okay
one really three
two
three
three really free oh my god
really
[Music]
three
it's gonna be massive yeah
[Music]
three tablespoons about so maybe let's
make the third one a little bit smaller
what the [\h__\h] is
it's a cookie mountain
okay
um it's i positioned it kind of
awkwardly there's not much space on the
left side so that's yeah an awkward
space but okay next one
you go
here
[Music]
there's really not that much space on
one of these platters
that's like two and a half almost
[Music]
i dropped some cookie dough
that looks ridiculous
that looks insanely huge is this gonna
be like super flat and small once it's
baking
[Music]
this is huge
although i do remember
the cookies that i got in that hotel
they were pretty [\h__\h] big
they would expand like crazy that's what
i'm thinking
it's kind of dangerous putting them too
close to another let me give them some
space
i think i really won't put too many on
this
one we gotta test it out we gotta test
it out how wide they will become
and then i can always make more later on
fresh fresh out of the oven is best
anyway you know yeah that's better i'm
just gonna make like five and then put
the rest into the fridge and then i can
always make more later right
sorry
was that one that was one i think
one
[Music]
i didn't chill it but it didn't say
it didn't say anything about chilling
[Music]
cool um yeah didn't say anything about
chilling but it does say that i have to
cool it for one hour after baking it you
really think i have that kind of
patience are you kidding me
hey i want to eat them stream
i want to at least try it on stream you
think i can wait that long
eh
[Music]
it only takes like 25 minutes to bake
them
but it's taking one hour to wait
in only seven minutes
why does it say one hour
i will wait like 10 minutes and then
give it a taste no matter what this
recipe says
also
big chunk
yeah i'm gonna help myself with that
knife
[Music]
cookies i'm so excited
i finally know how to make amazing
cookies yeah
yeah
waifu material
you may united
[Music]
many you may get it
i can become
a wife now wife and for life
cookies man fresh cookies imagine
imagine coming home after a long day of
work and you come home to the smell
of freshly baked
fresh out of the oven
chunky chocolate chip cookies oh my god
oh
if that isn't a dream come true
then i don't know man i don't know if i
should put another one it's five on
there now but it's kind of awkwardly
spaced so i think i'll just go with this
i'll just i'll just go with this
so um
yeah you won't really see what it looks
like i'll take a photo for twitter for
later
[Music]
okay
okay it's going in the oven
[Music]
let me turn off the camera
okay
should i put it like in the middle guys
or very at the top it didn't say in the
recipe
[Music]
uh middle middle okay
let's go
20 minutes so
[Music]
it's 35
35 okay
okay okay
until then oh no not 35 like 40
40 okay 28 p.m for 8 40
8 40 p.m
20 minutes
wait a second
[Music]
oh my god i only have eight percent left
don't know
bake for 20 to 23 minutes okay let me
actually turn on a timer
uh timer
no no no timer
[Music]
for
minutes because we have no patience yes
okay
we've done it guys it took me way longer
than i should have if i don't stream
then i can probably make them faster
[Music]
how did it take me 20 minutes to make
this unbelievable
[Music]
impossible
closer to reality 20 minutes from canada
to read one separate hey
in theory i could be reading super chats
now yeah but i don't like reading super
chats with this setup because it makes
me feel uneasy
and 20 minutes you mean two hours
what do you mean
no it's 20 minutes what the [\h__\h]
why am i well you're not the only person
who said that
i'm not waiting two hours i'm waiting 20
minutes
[Music]
looking at the metric version of the
recipe would have helped
that is true as well
i think a professional baker can oh yeah
two hours making them yeah
yeah
a professional baker didn't
could have probably done this in 10
minutes
or not even a professional baker but
just someone who focuses on baking
yeah sorry about that i didn't expect it
to take that long either
during my sleep oh i have another one
here right i have the christmas one in
obs as well
i don't have much on the laptop so i
apologize
but there you go
btmu
is this better for now
[Music]
how many did you make there's five five
in there right now
oh
they're already like melting in there
i wonder if i can give you an angle
uh
looking into the oven let me see if
[Music]
of course from the outside
yeah it is an impatient waiting vgn
[Music]
oh the cable the table is so short
uh
if i do
[Music]
you're not saying that i oh oil oh no
what is that
ah
[Music]
trying to do it in
studio mode but it's not updating
uh uh oh i think
what the [\h__\h] is that
okay
[Music]
oh no
photo would be funny i think maybe from
now on only photos
oh it's looking like a melting snowman
oh no
[Music]
oh no which is probably a good thing
it's supposed to be like that so we
could be good okay i don't know the
webcam is kind of acting uh weird though
okay
let me take a photo 15 minutes left
oh but yo my my oven looks the the
window the oven window looks so dirty ew
let me open it up for a moment
[Music]
oh
it smells
amazing
let me try to quickly send that to jen
moon
[Music]
look at these
look at these cookies
well jenna is gonna be like kim kimmy
[Music]
look at this
where are those
[Music]
i know safe to show
they they are melting quickly
i think they're good to show
look
this is what they look like right now
although oh yeah
the one in the middle is starting to
touch the one on the bottom on the top
uh left
uh it's moving in
quickly
yummy
those two are currently already touching
oh well they'll have to be they become
one big cookie then i will learn from my
mistakes
they can touch a little
a little bit of touching
is okay okay okay okay
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] they're so big
why the [\h__\h] did they tell me to do
three tablespoons
they're huge
oh my god i wonder if i would have
chilled them
chilled the cookie dough in the fridge
if it would be like less melty now
[Music]
american but
but then from
although i guess the hotel originally
comes from america huh
i suppose so
but i went there in england
[Music]
they are
mutating into
a chocolate chip pizzas
oh that reminds me guys so i was at
supermarket and i saw you know i have
this this this uh frozen pizza that i
eat all the time right um this um
tuna tuna frozen pizza right right right
right yeah yeah yeah
and it's very simple but
it's still delicious and today i saw
this tuna pizza that was always the same
for many many years it has a new recipe
now it was written on the packaging that
they're using a new recipe
uh
so even the packaging was updated and it
looked so
fresh so i was like oh [\h__\h] it looks
even more delicious now
so i bought
the tuna pizza and i'm gonna eat it
tonight
frozen tuna pizza uh it's going into my
oven and i will taste test it and see if
it's better now or if it's worse now
oh my god
they're pizzas they're cookie pizzas
yummy
[Music]
oh
i took another photo
i only have six percent left on my on my
phone batteries yeah there
[Music]
six percent this yo dude is that
living on the
what do you call it
living living on limb on the limits or
so
also so they have um
they have kinda become bigger and bigger
i'm so proud of them they grow so fast
living on the edge yeah
for sure
let me show you an update of my children
[Music]
in my nicole
i don't know what that is i censored it
but
we shall
um
the top left ones are best friends so
they're touching
and the bottom two ones are insanely big
but i can't wait to eat them
i can't wait
[Music]
how much time do we have left
10 minutes 10 minutes okay okay okay
beak
wait in 10 minutes they're gonna be even
bigger
oh but they look so good
oh my god they're majestic yeah they're
chunky chunky but that's that's they're
supposed to be that like around that
size i think if i remember correctly
they were pretty big when i got them
in that hotel
this might be normal add pineapple
yes it's looking like a pizza i might
add some pineapple
next time only put four
it was wise of me to to not put any more
on there
there's barely any space
i had i had a feeling
that looked that much dull
where we're getting uh to a dangerous
amount of dough
add tuna and pineapple now tuna and
pineapple should not be mixed on the
pizza
that is
no no big no for me
so how's everyone's valentine's day
going huh
add corn
[Music]
no i don't have any corn right now
how are you valentine's days guys
[Music]
i
i ate lasagna oh yeah it's monday i
should be eating lasagna but at least
you're eating it for me
[Music]
uh
wait
let's see
single awareness day
lasagna it's monday it's monday monday
is for lasagnas
like the chat is going so fast i
i can't
spending it with kiawa that's nice yeah
i'm celebrating it with you and that's
about it have no one to love
what is love
baby don't hurt me
don't hurt me
no more
[Music]
yeah that's very sad
don't worry about it
i'm i'm basically also alone i only have
my cats with me
we are the same you and me
[Music]
and but at least at least we have
chocolate chip cookies
and pizza
today's menu is chocolate chip cookies
frozen pizza and maybe ice cream um for
dessert
that kind of sounds like i i just am
trying to get over a break up or
something
yeah and it's a breakup with nino my
inanes
oh man but this is just my normal diet
though this is just normal
it's like my whole default diet is a
break up
food
we like to call that in german
or at least i call that first present
it's a word for fresh it's a combination
of
frustration and uh eating
yeah holy [\h__\h] my laptop is so loud this
laptop is great but it's so
noisy it gets so noisy
the ventilation
damn and it feels like it's like
overheating
insanely but it's just on the table
right now i don't know what the problem
is
gaming laptops being like that
yeah it's the alienware laptop
it's huge it's heavy it's huge it's
noisy
but at least i guess i can stream well
with it i i hope
so
they always run hot oh oh really is that
normal with them
wrapped up on the table where else would
it be
where else we've been
how's it looking all the cookies
oh my god
oh it's smelling out of the oven oh my
god oh my god
[Music]
now
me
too we do have a drooling emote don't we
oh my god
oh
it's weird when gaming laptops are not
all
okay then i guess i don't need to worry
about it
[Music]
is there anything anything i wanted to
talk about
me think we talked about monopoly we
talked about the schedule talked about
uh
[Music]
whole talk
oh yeah the members only stream i'm
planning to do the audio stock idea
and the one where we get a track from
audio stock and then i make up a melody
and i make up lyrics together with you
guys and we create a song
that fun idea that we had
gonna be after holo talk like a couple
hours after probably
like 8 p.m my time or something like
that
[Music]
yeah it's gonna be fun because like
i yeah we did that with uh city
rendezvous is what we call that other
song that we made
oh wait it said something about when the
edges are brown and the edges are
starting to get golden brown or they are
already golden brown wait turn on my
phone again oh three minutes left
they're looking they're looking fine
uh
let me see the recipe again
and or until edges are golden brown and
center is still stopped i think we could
already take it out
golden brown cookie check i think we
could take it out already
[Music]
to let them cool properly yep yep yep
yeah i have no space in my kitchen right
now [\h__\h] one second one second let me
let me make some space
[Music]
the cookies are coming
okay i'm taking them out now oh the
smell
[Music]
don't burn your hands
oh
[Music]
there we go
oh they don't they don't look so
photogenic on
on the
on the picture but
i mean they look fun they look they look
better than what aqua simply created
today
sorry akola senpai
i'm sure it tasted good
[Music]
five percent left did you guys see when
she made she made kato shokura
but
it looks weird
but i'm sure it tasted good
i'm sure that it's often the case like
things look disgusting but they taste
really good
okay
here are the cookies
after taking them out of the oven
um i'm letting them chill now it's 36
now let's give it a try it on in 15
minutes perhaps 10 to 15 minutes
[Music]
yeah i took them out maybe two minutes
too early but it's okay probably we
should here it is
what do you think
[Music]
that the
the the middle one is connecting
nice texture texture really
really it looks kind of like i don't
know
is this supposed to have
to look like it looks very uh raw still
at least in this photo this was right
away after taking them out
immediately they emerged yeah
yeah the amount of chocolate looks
really good on those ones
maybe and this one is kind of hidden
inside
yeah
would eat out of ten
maybe put them back in for a little bit
but now they're already cooling i think
it's too late now
think they need a little ew
check inside
can you like put them back in i put them
back in for a little hey really
okay check them out
[Music]
uh
they do look a little bit like maybe
they could need a little bit more time
okay then let's wait uh like three more
three more minutes
two to three moments
[Music]
look at that from
google gaga into
m cookie
[Music]
interesting
that's my dinner tonight
together with the pizza
[Music]
the hard work is paying off i think
i wish i could send those cookies to you
you guys want to know what um idea i
came up with
for
a stream
that i need
the other members help with
i
right before the stream i had this uh
idea out of nowhere
i kind of always wanted to do this with
viewers but i figured it actually might
be fun to do it with talents
with with whole live english members
um
[Music]
i
what's in your bag
stream
so i asked the members to send me
pictures
of what they have in their bag
[Music]
and obviously if they don't want to
participate they don't have to
participate and if there's something
embarrassing in there that they don't
want to show they of course don't have
to show it and they could even like i
don't know put in a huge chunk of cheese
in there if they're bales for example if
they want to be funny um but yeah i do
want to see some some i don't know items
like i don't know makeup
lipstick or whatever
so maybe some girls bring
power banks with them do you guys always
bring a power bank with you i'm the type
of person who doesn't ever have a power
bank with them but always uh
always
takes the power bank from my friend
i'm like ugh [\h__\h] do you have a pool bag
with you and they're like they're always
like yes of course i do you can have
mine
i always use other people's power banks
the same as me
[Music]
all the time
cookies look fine
uh maybe in 30 seconds i'll take them
out
[Music]
i'm the mom friend i have everything
yeah i feel like it will give us a good
insight into the girls
uh into their personality perhaps as
well
seeing what they have in their back some
some girls really have a lot of [\h__\h] in
their bag at all times like for real you
would think that they're like
moving houses or something
i used to be like that these days i
don't have that much in my bags anymore
but you because now i i mostly carry
like smaller bags but i used to carry
like huge bags
and and i had so much [\h__\h] in there all
the time
nowadays it's not that bad anymore but i
i i i
i'm interested in seeing the other girls
uh insides of their bags and then
showing you guys on stream um every
maybe we can do a guessing game we can
look for the items that they have in the
bag and then you guys can uh guess oh i
didn't think about that yet i just
thought about that now
and then
we'll have
[Applause]
for example
okay i'm getting the cookies
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
cool okay okay okay they they don't look
uh much different they look a little bit
browner um
i guess i'll take another picture but
i won't send it i will show it on
twitter later because i only have four
percent
[Music]
okay
phone you can rest for now
and now the cookies will rest
which
okay yeah
yeah
but i also wanted to do
a video where uh you uh stream where you
guys send me
[Music]
uh
where you guys sent me
where you guys send me pictures of
what's in your bag
but i don't realize a lot of um
uh
men don't even carry bags so
yeah
[Music]
super chat
i carry a backpack ah i guess if you go
like to university or something like
that then you probably carry like your
laptop in your backpack and stuff but
i rarely see men with with bags outside
you know
how do you how the hell do you carry
what you need
only in your in your uh
pants pockets all the time incredible to
me how do you manage to go out just with
keys a phone and a wallet like my wallet
is so big it doesn't even fit into uh
by far it doesn't fit into my
into my pants pocket
yeah i think uh
usually
wallets from
men are usually smaller
and women's wallets
purses wallets are usually bigger like
mine is pretty big it barely fits into
my
into my bag
whenever i need lipstick i don't know
man i don't know maybe a bottle of water
and
um
good question
it depends where you're going
um
uh
good question actually what do you need
i i usually bring my passport
uh
what do i bring so i usually recently
when i you recently always bring is my
keys
my phone
my passport
my
uh wallet
[Music]
my
co co co
thing certificate you know what i mean
why password uh
because like i have to
i don't
i don't have a that's my id
that's my id i don't have a driving
license so i use that as my id i have to
be able to prove that the name on the
on the certificate is me
yeah that's what eu people do if you
don't have a driving license most people
have the only other like in in germany a
lot of people have something called
that's a personal housewise but
personality otherwise is not very common
in austria
um
so the pasnado's advice is like a like a
one
card
like a normal normal id card
but in austria we don't really use that
but recently
um
so uh health insurance cards
have
uh photos of the person on it too
actually i was sent one of those so i i
think i could probably use that as an
idea as well
i'm not sure
my health insurance card now has my
photo on it
i think it counts as
such a
personal id now but i still always bring
my password because
um
it it works
[Music]
yeah
risky to bring password around well i i
never lost it before
i never lost it before and and the thing
is like for example when i lived in
japan
and i needed it to be always able to
prove that i have a visa um
yeah it was necessary but not that
anyone ever checked it but
you have to be able to show it at any
time so
i had it with me all the time
but besides oh yeah i think i and
nowadays i don't really do it anymore
but i used to also always bring uh some
like perfume
[Music]
uh
and sometimes i would bring some makeup
to fix my makeup but i'm not really the
type of girl like i i had i used to have
some really girly friends who would
bring especially in japan who would
bring their whole [\h__\h] makeup
collection
to
school and to shopping to disneyland to
anywhere because they were so fixated on
fixing their makeup
every 10 minutes okay not every 10
minutes but maybe every hour or two
and i would look at them and i would be
like you did not change
at all in this past hour you look
exactly the same but they always fix
their makeup for selfies and stuff and i
oh i kind of feel like
maybe i'm not girly enough maybe i'm not
a perfectionist enough because i i i do
my makeup once in the morning and then i
go out and then okay maybe until the
evening
i look a little bit worse than before
but usually it it doesn't wear up that
easily and that quickly so
i i never really fix my makeup maybe
maybe the lipstick
but that's
it usually my lipstick is [\h__\h] strong
so it won't change
throughout the day
cookies now the cookies are not in the
oven i'm waiting for them to cool down
in my makeup right now yeah it's barely
noticeable that i'm wearing any makeup
at all right yeah that's because i'm not
wearing any makeup right now hey
um
i don't wear makeup when i stream
because why would i i look beautiful
like this
yeah
yeah honestly i'm
not really the type to put a lot of
stuff into my bag at least not nowadays
but i used to bring more that's for sure
i woke up like this i literally did
[Music]
doesn't callie put on a lot of makeup
no not a lot no no
i think
kelly wears less makeup than i do
when we went out like you know when i
also would actually wear makeup
i did wear more makeup than she did
but
but she uh she likes her eyeliner
[Laughter]
[Music]
emo eyeliner
no no not clubbing when i say go out i
just mean going to a restaurant or
something like that
it's now the face mom
[Music]
and her nails yeah that's the one thing
that she's very particular and very
girly about that i have i have never
never had my nails done ever before
but kelly
that's the one thing that she is super
girly about that she always gets that
she always gets cute nails done
i kind of want to try it but then i feel
like the
like what am i doing it for like it's
not like i'm gonna show it to anyone and
and then i don't like the transition of
when it wears off if it's not stick
stick on nails but like if it's painted
onto your own nails i don't like the
transition of when it kind of starts
um like disappearing
and it just looks ugly so i guess you
have to just
in order to not have that just get rid
of it completely immediately with nail
remover but
yeah i don't know i don't it sounds like
a big pain in the ass
but i used to when i was younger when i
when i lived in japan before before her
life
um because there was a time where i
lived in japan before whole life i used
to look up to
those decora decora nails not pecora
decora
like
japanese girls
i don't know if it's really in fashion
now anymore but it used to be at least
in fashion back then like really really
chunky and like not long nails but at
least they had like so many like cute
cute decorations on it like uh
very very cutesy and harajuku style
decora
nails
rhinestones it's just
way
like really you have to imagine it
not like
western style but like japanese cute
style
really cute [\h__\h] nails
i always wanted to try those but back
then i didn't really have the money for
it
so
i didn't get
nails done ever
i think now even in japan
simple nails are
more
popular i think but i don't really know
i haven't been around
decorah is like a
actually it's kind of a
a fashion style like there's also like i
think decora
lolita if i'm not wrong
where you put like a [\h__\h] ton of pins
on your hair
like children style pins
are the cookies no they're not in the
oven uh we are waiting for them to cool
down tickle yeah decorate decoration
decoration decorate that was the word
yeah dakota
all right i was also looking up to all
that was like lolita
fashion styles
but i never never really tried it before
oh no i think no i i tried it before but
like only like a cheap
cheap um lolita
dress
um only the cheap ones not the fancy
high quality ones i just googled
decorator nails and i will sue you
what wait what comes up if you look up
thick on our nails why will you sue me
nails
yeah that's what i mean
why are you suing me what did i do
aren't those [\h__\h] cute that's what
i'm talking about that's what i wanted
when i was younger
i still kind of want it now though a
little bit
look it up guys
[Music]
[Laughter]
why are you suing me
[Music]
i didn't i'm not really a fan of course
you're not really a fan
you have no taste
they got shocked at how fabulous they
look
[Music]
possible
wait i think we can try cooking now
maybe
it's been definitely 10 minutes
spelt it wrong oh oh they spelt
correctly according to the comment
the pink is hurting it doesn't always
have to be pink but
japanese girls like to over decorate
things
somehow
i still remember the time when um those
those folding phones were popular and
and uh old girls had like a million
keychains attached to their garage to
their phones
i used to have that too i had like a
million little keychains with plushies
and stuff actually like [\h__\h] huge
keychains like not even considered
keychains phone charms anymore
attached to my
nowadays there's nothing attached to my
phone because there is nothing to attach
anything to
oh but i remember i i remember one more
thing um
i had this before
um
this was also quite a while ago a couple
years ago when
and
uh
smartphones started becoming popular
more and more in japan but they also did
the same on on non-smartphones but like
the folding phones they did the same on
those two but they would like
uh glue
a [\h__\h] ton of decorations just like
those nails
onto the the back of the phones
not directly onto the phones but like on
the case
how do i wait
maybe i can find a picture
[Music]
okay
oh
oh yeah yeah yeah
let me
[Music]
i love this so much and i had a phone
case like this for a while
look at that it looks like a [\h__\h]
cake or something
like cream and then cookies and all
kinds of stuff
myself
i might have to
get out afterwards
but i wanted to show you never mind i
wanted to show you
how can you hold the phone
no problem holding the phone
it's a bit chunky
very impractical no
it gets a little bit dirty though
my brother head went no [\h__\h] way
nobody way
who cares it's cute yes [\h__\h] cute
don't worry i don't have this anymore
these days also it would it would be too
cringe and stand out too much in austria
but
it used to be
super popular back in the day
need a big bag for that brick of a food
yeah
oh
okay
i will taste the cookie now
let me take one
[Music]
you're huge they're like [\h__\h] cookie
omelettes or something
the whole plate takes up the whole place
[Music]
okay okay
okay
it feels um a little bit moist still
on the back at least
oh and it's
i think the texture just by touching it
feels about right oh
okay i'm digging in itadakimasu
cool
okay it's still um
a bit
soft
um
i think it might need to cool for longer
but i think it was supposed to be
kind of soft still
[Music]
the answers are crunchy though
they are
very good
actually
um
i wouldn't mind
[Music]
uh using
this amount of walnuts on purpose
because i feel like the walnut taste
is
um
not too strong but it's close to being
too strong so this is about right
[Music]
boom
wow
[Music]
the chocolate
very good
it's however
[Music]
um
in some spots it's like literally melted
it hasn't
it hasn't um
solidified yet
[Music]
but that's actually not a problem it's
actually good
[Music]
chocolate ratio
chocolate to cookie ratio is pretty high
it's
oh my god it's like
so much chocolate i don't know if it's
only this spot but
that's a lot of chocolate holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
how did i manage to get so much
chocolate in here
[Music]
oh my god
oh
it's a [\h__\h] chocolate pizza
ah
um
go
[Music]
yo
i need
i need to um
[Music]
charities with
bff and rmt
they would love these cookies
it would almost be a crab no it would be
a crime to just eat them all alone
[Music]
oh man
put them in a cute bag honestly i need
to put them in a pizza
box
[Music]
oh um god
the bff and rmt know each other
yeah because i had i had bff over before
when
i lived with rmt yeah yeah yeah
i told i told them we should all go
skiing together because um not only rmt
is really good at skiing but bff
is also
insanely good at skiing
so
[Music]
they both have expressed
um
that they want to go skiing with me
again
or for bff it would be the first time
oh if they taste the same as the ones in
the hotel it's hard to tell for me right
now because it's been so long it's been
years
um but i think probably yeah
and they really do taste amazing
so i i think this recipe
gets a 10 out of 10 for me from me
[Music]
10 out of 10.
i rarely give things a 10 out of 10 but
this is a 10 out of 10.
[Music]
um
i think
[Music]
i think i might want to chop the walnuts
a bit
smaller next time i don't
i if you like nuts then you probably
would like them if they're chunky but i
don't like them that much
i mean i i can eat them and i don't
think they're
ew disgusting
but biting into them
[Music]
it's a little bit too strong on the nut
taste maybe
chunky nuts
they could be a bit smaller
[Music]
it takes me ages to finish one cookie
they are huge
also i found the cat hair that's stuck
in the cookie
i can't i think i got it out nice soup
[Music]
sorry that was really loud
i think i might make the next batch
smaller because
i like how crunchy the edges are
[Music]
i want them to be smaller so that
there's a bigger crunchy ratio you know
what i mean
and i don't want to give some of them to
my friends those turned out so good i
want them to taste these
[Music]
things
yo
you guys should try that recipe just
look up um hilton cookie recipe and
you'll find it
the actual um hotel is called
tree
yeah
it has british measurements though so be
aware of that
add them to the kfp menu
you know what we could make a cookie
burger so the the buns will be the
cookie
i don't know what we put inside maybe
just ice cream ice cream we're gonna
make an ice cream sandwich
[Music]
oh my god
i got too excited
this with the new ice cream
[Music]
cone
ice cream
that would be amazing oh my god
ice cream cookie burger
ah
hell yeah
uh does anyone now know how long these
are good for after after baking them
probably not
that long huh
[Music]
maybe uh two or three days
10 minutes yeah because they're gonna be
gone in 10 minutes
i feel like cause they're self-made and
not from some store they probably don't
um they they don't survive that long i
would say sealed maybe a week
it won't last a second
i need a cookie box i need a cookie box
now
like one of those grandma cookie boxes
oh yeah
i don't know if you guys
had those typical grandma cookie boxes
but
back in the day
my mom and and my grandma they had those
big big rounds really old-fashioned
uh tin i think they're made like out of
tin yeah tin boxes
not a cookie jar we didn't have cookie
jars we just had the tin
cookie boxes
and as
there would however rarely be cookies in
there
when i was really tiny maybe there were
some cookies in there but in later years
there was always something else in there
[\h__\h] bamboozle
round
round always round
like why why aren't i never cookies in
the cooking boxes and suing supplies and
photos and other random [\h__\h]
what a disappointment
what a [\h__\h] disappointment it's how
you call that fake advertisement no what
was it what's the word again
getting my [\h__\h] hopes up
[Music]
it's illegal
how dare you bamboozlement thousands
were advertising at false advertising
mommy are you listening to this still
wait i got a new dm is that from my mom
oh
oh my mom says three to four weeks but i
don't trust my mom when it comes to
um
expiration dates
she she eats anything i told you guys
[Music]
i don't believe that
maybe
maximum two weeks i'll give it maximum
two weeks but they'll be gone by two
weeks anyway
[Music]
mama don't you know his best
so
[Music]
often not always
good that i'm not in the same room or
apartment as my mom
good that the only way she can
say something back at me is discord
aggressively tapping
[Music]
but it doesn't matter if it's
good for three weeks because they're not
gonna survive three weeks yeah
but mommy
next time i see you
ah you probably wouldn't like these
cookies though they're probably too
sweet for my mommy probably i'm not sure
mommy if you want me to make them i'll
make them for you
you want but they're very very
very sweet very chocolatey
i think she would probably like them
without the chocolate
because she does love
walnuts
she loves
or maybe by now she hates them
because she's had too many
but she likes nuts
choco pizza
what if you freeze the cookies
interesting font
make it look back check oh yeah my mom
does like dark chocolate
and she does still love walnuts
apparently
my mom my mom used to the thing about
the walnuts is my mom
used to have a
a walnut tree i don't know if it was one
or more
but
she always got like
buckets and buckets and buckets of
walnuts
from those trees
when the season was
on oh seven okay not just one 17
17 walnut trees
she used to have
um
17 you can imagine how many [\h__\h]
walnuts you get from that
she would
once those walnuts were in season she
would make literally everything out of
walnuts she would make walnut pesto
which i did enjoy
very much
but
like like she would she would bathe in
walnuts
yeah
she made everything out of walnuts like
i wouldn't i wouldn't wanna
i wouldn't wanna eat so many [\h__\h]
nuts
[Laughter]
but very healthy
[Music]
oh apparently now the trees are
uh unfortunately sick
um and i don't think i don't think she
has access to them anymore anyway but
um
yeah adisu would love your mom
when are the moments in season again
would be funny if it was november
i don't think it was november though i
think it was a bit earlier sometime in
in autumn i think
um i would i would go visit my mom and
like there would be so many [\h__\h] nuts
everywhere and she would only make
things out of nuts that would be like
mom
please
please no more nuts no more walnuts
[Music]
walnut
bread
cake
walnut
noodles
pizza
walnut
smoothie
walnut sandwich
walnut okay i'm just kidding this i'm
just making this up i don't even know
what she made anymore
oh my mom is saying in the future it's
gonna be um berries instead which i'm
looking forward to okay if you are if
you have um
so many
an equivalent of uh berries
uh then
i would be very excited that's that's
way more
charming to me
than walnuts
although i did like that walnut pesto i
love me some good pesto
berries mummy likes that no they're mine
they're mine they're mine mine mine
yeah my mommy has a big big garden but
but i want some berries on my on my
balcony too
so mommy said that she's gonna help me
um
make my balcony ready for planting
planting berries
i want to go to the balcony every
morning and pick me some fresh
strawberries
because the strawberries at the
supermarket are always [\h__\h]
although i did get some i did get some
really good looking strawberries today
at the supermarket they looked
they looked
like they were like i don't know
pregnant because
don't you like
okay that's
i understand that that's a really weird
thing to say but i mean because like
don't you say when when people are
pregnant you say oh you like you're like
how do you say it you're like
shiny
you look so um
no no you look so
uh
glowing yeah glowing glowing those
strawberries they looked so vitalized i
don't know
and so healthy
[Music]
glowing that's the way that i was
looking for thank you now you know what
i mean
okay
well guys
uh we have we made the cookies
and
now what's left for me to do is make the
rest of the cookies but i'll do that off
screen and tomorrow is my day off so
i'll be eating cookies all day and maybe
delivering some cookies
yeah
now eat them all alone there's actually
not even that much dough
i said 26 cookies though
i will see those were five cookies i
don't i didn't even eat the full cookie
yet it's so big
enjoy your day out thank you thank you
you guys do you know what you can do on
my day off
you can
study me
[Music]
you can stream dreaming to to continue
to watch the music video please and
uh yeah
stream the choo choo
stream the choo choo yes
stream dreaming 2 2 streaming tutu
photo of the
next
now
time to find more references exactly you
think you found them all already
probably not time to watch it again
i found a very certain
there was one specific um
hint
uh spoiler in that video i didn't know
he would put it in but there is
something in there that you will only
understand afterwards but i i found it i
was like oh you sneaky little [\h__\h]
you sneaky sneaky
but
it's so vague that now you would have no
idea
what it means what that it even means
anything at all
[Music]
later on you will understand
hey
a little a little something
yes
it seems that i'm not the only one who
likes to hint and spoiler things ahead
of time
anyway actually uh yeah today was the
one year anniversary of heart challenger
i
forgot to mention it again
but but but but
but we already talked a little bit about
it yesterday anyway
[Music]
one year ago
my
second
single my second original song heart
challenger has been released one year
ago
[Music]
one year anniversary yeah yeah
so
if you haven't heard it yet or you
haven't heard it in a while then i think
besides dreaming choo choo you should
also stream high challenger a little bit
on the side again maybe we can finally
get it to 2 million
it definitely deserves 10 million but
you know
you know the algorithm you know it
so please give it some love it deserves
it a lot of
love went into that music video and into
the song i would be very happy and
appreciate it if you could stream heart
challenger and dreaming to do okay thank
you thank you very much
[Music]
and for the rest of the night i wish you
all a lovely evening thank you for
coming today to kiwawa's kitchen once
again we made some delicious valentine's
day
cookies on honestly valentine's day was
just an excuse for me to make these
but it turned out fabulous magnificent
divine
majestic
and very very chunky
cookies
a big big success indeed yeah
thank you everyone for watching today uh
feel free to try out the recipe yourself
as you have seen it was literally just
throwing together the ingredients and
then
putting them into the oven that's all it
took
that's all it took to make them very
easy you guys would probably do
it much faster than i did
[Music]
yeah once again happy valentine's day to
everybody
have a nice evening and i love you all
so if you think no one loves you that's
not true
that's definitely not true i'm sure
there's someone who loves you
and if you're really sure there's no one
to love you i love you
i love you um
definitely all of you deserve some love
in this world
don't
fret
don't be
sad don't be
don't give up
love will come to everybody eventually i
think
it might it may not be in the shape of a
human it may be in the shape of a cat
[Music]
but
that's still love
or in the shape of a family love
who knows it could be anything you just
gotta open your eyes
accept it open your heart
hmm
yeah
happy valentine's day who says
valentine's day has to be about
being alone or being with your boyfriend
girlfriend
doesn't have to be it's just another one
of those
um
days where people try to sell
[\h__\h]
right yeah
commercial commercial day
don't worry about it
you're doing nothing wrong
[Music]
but it's a it's an excuse for me to make
chocolate cookies so i'm thankful for
that
[Music]
thank you guys for watching today
and in german we say florin valentine's
dog
and alfvida zin indeed i'll see you guys
on wednesday
i think
i forgot what we're playing on wednesday
it might be pokemon it might be
something else
i forgot
thank you thank you everybody thank you
thank you
thank you hope you enjoyed the stream
thank you for your love and your support
everybody i'll be reading the super
chats in the next
next possible stream
[Music]
oh thank you thank you
while watching
netflix bye bye
bye bye bye bye happy valentine's day i
love you all thank you chickens for your
love i love you guys i love you guys i
love you guys
[Music]
bye bye
ending
[Music]
you