[Music]
[Music]
me nnn
me
nnn
yeahhhhhhhhh
na
me
n
[Music]
n nao n
me
nggun
goo
form cabin no me  Hongo 4th place
[Music]
Hmm
yeah I
was in
Yeah yeah
[Music]
Oitan
me
ten hmm
hmm
[Music]
a
I'm
good good
uuuuuh It
's a blue wear seed stone
Wait a minute
No,
first of all, the blue conquered cure is maintained. 1 I
mistook it for tomorrow's goods. Financial ripe It's
right. What is it? s day is b to Japanese Aum type Now everyone is Mayumi-san.
Bugs come here Japanese is attempted  Today,
Japan is limited, so it's a little bit good, but I think it's a
bit of a live English, so it might be a bit of ...  It's
going to be abolished. I've always wanted to do it, but it
was too soon. I
decided to do it today. There are a lot of Japanese people.
Unfortunately, it's a
bit...  If I do it at this time, I'll end up overlapping with a lot of people, but I hope
everyone enjoys the window. The
next era is not going to be a spanking job. I'll
help a girl who looks like a schoolgirl.
Surfing & Star Hara Aboul blowing Aa Ball 4
Star
Nice to meet you
After all, I think that the shadow of Japan is rare, so it's my first time, so I'd
be happy if you could see it,
but a
little bit of people please
come  I wonder if there's a store that's worried about me. I wonder if everything's
okay.
Ah
[Music]
Yesterday, I was wondering if the rain would be a new beginning. Some
people may not have noticed, but yesterday, I
was in the middle of a rainstorm. And then...  I'm
going to share that with you and answer
all of the questions.  I
foresaw it myself, and it was my fault, but, you know,
most of the tea is probably 50%. I
have a
question about Pekklar-senpai. In
addition to the thick exclusive, the core material is not that much of an island, and the
rug yoga is good and scattered, but this is
it.  I think that there are probably a lot of Japanese listeners who like Tekura raw pie,
but other people are also asking Baek Rasenpai's questions, so I'm just like, "Didn't you get a question?"
And
about 40% of the questions
were about the language,
and the questions were about the amount of mutual support, and I almost
had to write the tape,
but I
thought, "This is bad," because I did
n't write the paper.  If you're having a nosebleed all the time, that's cheap. Well, maybe everyone is expecting it,
but I'm sure it's
weird to talk about my senior. That's right, that's what my dad said, but from that chat,
I'll have more original questions.  The day I might have picked it up,
hey, the
quality is also
...
Who would you like to collaborate with if that collaboration was released?
What kind of collab would you like to do with Baek? What do you like about
Baek? How did you find out about Ekura? I like Ekura's sandbag stream.  What is it
? It's always the same,
but I'm not
sure, but I'm sure
I'll be able to do it. Ivan Chocolate Fashion
Family is the sponsor, please stick it on, Oe, Jack,
as Pink Revise, no
way, a quiet, so Philly  To Steam, I wonder if
it's Pekar Sepa 3D blowing 4, Kanyan, it's warm in the corner, but it's not amazing, I
want to see it from home, but now it's my own distribution,
a by cutter between, I guess I saved it too  But it's not a quick one. I
think I have a lot of different laughs and turns.
That's right. I'm often told that I'm a life lover.
What should I do? I'm not good at it.  I
didn't mean to do that, but
I guess Baek has seen almost all of my senior's archives,
so  I wonder if it's because of
that influence. I do
n't want Spekura-senpai to think that he's trying to imitate me.
What should I do to pay him back
? Ah, he told me too, why should I make Baek look like him?  How to pay for it? Hold on! It's
not that, but I'm a bit mad.
Well,
today, I
think that most of the streams will be about losing, but
thank you 10 So let's
do it, Summer Khan
[  Music]
Eyes and eyes are Gyuu Abijan Didn't you hear it? A landslide victory New car There was
also a beginner
BGM Hey, I played it all the time, but it's a self-immolation, no, my
head, I
mean, ah, there were a lot of questions  Hey
[Music] I'm
sorry to those who weren't asleep in that square, but I'm sorry, I read everything properly, I
read everything, Hagatsuka Wood Festival Fashion Park, let's go to the first viewing, or, in,
something horror, already, Pecora, the morning session  I
saw your name. That's all I can think of. Ah,
uh  I
'm in. Woo Papa,
math is lively nx 3 a.
I'm not feeling well, but that brightness makes my heart feel happy. Thank you. I'm
also looking forward to a collaboration with Tenku-senpai.  Dam, this is a
question, isn't
it? Thank you. I won't push myself too hard. I'm looking forward to it too. I
often hear people say that they get energy from watching my broadcasts, but I wonder
if that's true. I can't really imagine it.
Well, my
senior, Susumu Nagai, gives me energy, so I think it's better to think of it that way.
Okay, this
is a question that doesn't have the senior's name in it. Let's
use it. There are not many of them. Ah,
ana
Hello,
Gara-chan's Japanese is mixed in and it's easy to understand, and her
reactions are cute, so where are you looking? Thank you, Coop. Do you ever
eat Japanese food, Cha-chan? I'd like to know what kind of Japanese food you like from the food investment.  I
'm always looking forward to seeing Chara-chan doing well. I'll continue to support
her.
Well, I like the value of the food.
For example,
Tontatcha Travel, how to eat yakitori, yakitori, yakitori, I wonder if it's called eating yakitori in Japan. But yakitori is a
barbecue, but it's completely different from the foreign barbecue.
So I think yakiniku is Japanese food. Well, Japanese food is grilled, and I like yakitori, but
yakiniku is good. I like yakitori, but yakiniku is good.
That's Japan.
Yakikeika, that's why.
Tabunne. English.  If you do that, it becomes a barbecue, but the taste is different.
Well, if you've ever been invited to a barbecue in Japan, I've
never eaten barbecue at the Miyamiya family's house, so it's going to be fun.  I
was expecting something like a proper barbecue,
but it was just yakiniku. I love yakiniku, but I
thought it was a barbecue, so I
thought it was barbecue char, and it was just yakiniku sauce.  I
used meat from a yakiniku restaurant.  It's
not a barbecue, it's the outdoor yakiniku in Kansai. That
's what happens in Japan. I wonder
if Valkyries think that all yakiniku is yakiniku. The
barbecues are different. They're
both somehow attractive.  I think
so.
I love muscles, but I was expecting something different.
Wow,
what? Look at the two pillars.
There are so many
Japanese viewers.  5 people will wake
you
up with a charming, nice kamen, yay,
push up the barbecue,
ender jab soon,
so my sister loves pork cutlets,
but my favorite is pork fillet cutlets,
dan, I
used to like that pork cutlet, so I stole it,
well, well  I didn't know there was a pork fillet
cutlet in the past, and there was a certain, what should I say? I don't
think I should call him an old man.
Isn't there a gentle way to give birth? The boss recommended that I have some fillet cutlets in the middle of the day, but when I asked him what they were, he said, "
What's this?" and I ended up
only eating fillet cutlets in the middle of the day.
So,  A great 33-year-old
man who is grateful to Anna. I
have an image of him being older than that. No, I
have an image of him being older than that. I'm not
sure ...  I think I can get away with calling him Mr. Teru.
Anyway, I love ramen, but
I have a hard time slurping it.
So, I'm really embarrassed to go into a regular ramen shop.
Hey, how long does it take you to eat ramen?
Everyone can finish it in like 5 minutes, right? You
finish it in a flash, right?
5 minutes, oh no, 3 minutes,
but I don't think it's 3 hours.
Sometimes I can finish it in 30 minutes.  That way of
eating is the norm. Well, it's not a fork and spoon, but
it's okay.  It's
said that the farmers who grow really slowly grow, but I
don't have that feeling. I've
never noticed anything about Nobita's views growing. I don't know if it really grows or not.  Well, I think that
if it grows, it means
that there will be more sides and therefore more to eat. It's a
good thing that it grows. One and five are good things.
Oh,
iOS re Dinger noodles  Ingredients Cansparks West Sai author
Prada Enai House y Spei collection Wooden chairs How to live 5 immediately Rose arch is 5 and
Daichi Prefecture Soi 11 ast Farm
Well, that's how it is Wood Well,
let's go
Next time, definitely Pekrasen again  Licking the tube.
Hmm, 8 is the wrong size.
What was your impression when you first spoke with Noh Min-woo from the Farlive family?
Please tell us what you want to do in the future or who you want to collaborate with.  The
impression I got when we first talked was from my hometown, Ando. I
remember it pretty well.
That hunting turn money,
first of
all, this person's way of acting is interesting, and the
words that he uses are really funny, and the
first person I thought was an interesting person was Kari-chan, and the
first person I really
wanted to be friends with, I liked this person.  I really thought that I would borrow her,
and the first time
we were alone, I fell in love with her appearance and
thought she was the type of person I would really love.
So, when I first heard it, I
thought it would be well-received from the beginning, and I thought, "This guy is
really
naughty and naughty, and the powder really
helps me somehow." And
who is
it? Well, if we're talking seriously, I'm
kind of busy.  He's really helpful, even though he
's
always busy. He always
makes things feel real for me. This nude statue is a
good one. For example, the loading screen, the first screen, I think the illustration is
from the old  The animation was made by Hakari-chan.
I also drew the video for my debut book.
Well, they added animation to the roof, but the
real thing is the floor.
I said it's fine if it's simple, and
it's fine if it's rough, but that's really a crane wing.  I was
told that I would make it until it was confirmed, and
when I received the 4th and 5th, I thought, "Even though it's out of stock, it's much better than I expected," and I was really
happy. I really love Kari-chan. I'm
busy.  I was really sleeping and I was trying to help her.
Well, that was it,
but I thought the other flowers were lovely too. But at
first, I thought I was quiet.  I didn't know for a
long time. Oh, she's cute, but I thought she'd like to reveal something. Eh, I didn't know how to
continue at first.
Ina-chan is amazing. Itoi-chan is also quiet and kind.
Yeah, from the beginning, I didn't think this girl would be popular.
So Ame-chan
was a reliable person from the beginning.  Is that
right? I think we can get along well. It seems like fun. That story. Well, I thought it would be easy. Hmm, I'm not going to watch it. It's a scary story. Hmm, ah, ah, that's right. I rely
on you. That's true.  I thought, Amelia Amelia-chan is really reliable and responsive. She
might be the most responsive.
Amelia-chan, yeah, it's amazing. I
always think that Amelia-chan is great.
For example, this layout is like that girl's.  When I made the layout on the washi paper, I was really worried
because I was so bad at it and
didn't know what to do. Amelia, the manager, said she'd make it for me at first, but I had to make it myself.  So she
gave me all kinds of ingredients,
which is
why I call her "gy" in Japanese. She
gave me a lot of non-vector side dishes.
Sop Yun Soi I was
able to make this because he gave me a lot of vector material. Hmm, I
wonder if it turned out well.
A: What I want to do in the future, or what I want to do with 4 to 3 this time, is this, um,
people who want to do this are
originally talking about V  I
guess I've only collaborated with Ina-chan and Kari-chan, so I'd
like to collaborate with the other three, Usani and the two of them,
but I don't know what the content is yet.  I can't think of one more puff, I
put my own in, there
's no Ann,
well maybe salmon chan sweet hosting is arm tasake
check tarer a
az top bar is also full a
woman sleep mhr aaaaaaaaaaa power b younger then
Web Zuberi Te Body Stagnation
Nn Haa
A
Amano Other 1 Other than the question of who you want to collaborate with, I saved that story, so I'll talk about it
separately.
Thank you for coming to the three. Next
[Music]
Two Moons
Uh-huh,
Boo Boo
Data  It
came out, huh?
This is not the name of the senior.
Guts! Um, Ate key,
good.
My Japanese, oh, this is not Japanese? My Japanese is not yet musical, so please forgive me.
Question Sukari-chan is  Unfortunately, he always rejects Kina-chan's affections. In response to this,
Beko-senpai is always kind and has been
using English a lot recently. He has been drawing pictures of machines and brains. That's true, but even so, Chara-san
Kai-chan always says that he is married. What does that mean?
What does that mean? Fans of Kai-chan have been saying this lately.
I
want to marry Haru-chan. I
really love Peck-senpai, but I don't have any desire to get married.
Ah, I
just
want to be friends.
And,
uh,
from now on, I
want him to think that he likes me.  My friends
are related, so
that's the pattern. The
senior at the roots has always been the one who has been
catching that admiration,
so he has a slightly different way of thinking. He's
a little different when it comes to hunting and Aqua Super.
By the way, it's already morning, so I'll read it. I
understand now that it's a parent-child relationship, but I'm
sure that my senior is really kind to me.
Well, I was really worried at first, so I wondered how I should deal with him.  I thought
it would be bad if I pulled it out, but I thought that
my vowels were drawn during the broadcast, and I
thought that "Please take care of me" was standing up,
so it was a
success.
Next
[Music]
Uh huh.
Yes, it came out, haaaa, my choice, I had no choice,
Ekura-senpai, I thought there was no quality that had nothing to do with good,
he did it a lot, but it was always like that,
ahhhh,
right now I want to see the 3 p together
Seriously, I went to see the 3D at home. Oh, wait a minute, the pen. The
sound is basic. I just want to
see it for a moment. I want to see what's going on.
Just for a moment. What are you
doing? I'm not good at "look, look"  I
wonder how I did it
.
[Music]
Ehh, a,
yeah,
cute, nice, I wonder
if they'll do a lot of them from now on,
eh, eh,
a,
[Music],
a, you've got all kinds of expressions, there was,
hey, let's focus on the de facto abolition of the sutra,
pa,
gas morning car model,
and  I
think there will be an opportunity to collaborate with 5 Japan, but if Chara-san collaborates with Baekda-san, why
would you want to collaborate with your husband? Hayate
Down Collaboration Minecraft Hut Certain Again  I'd like to ask you about various things.
Well, this is also something that I've been asked a lot. Well,
I've never played Minecraft,
but I wasn't really interested in it, but my
senior  I've seen a lot of streams and when Senpai does it, it's kind of soothing. I can
watch it for hours. I
want Senpai to introduce me to a hood server and we can do something together. I'm
looking forward to it every time in Minecraft.  I
want to be taken
to the beach and I'm looking forward to getting that trident.
But there's one thing, I know a lot about Sepa so
please don't make me explode, please don't make me explode again,
I've
seen Ebi Dartriet, all of it, all of it, all of it  A
random collaboration is fine, but I want to do something together.
The one I want to do the most is probably a game. I
want to compete with Pitter. Well,
I saw that the character of the Pekar line bar was abolished with Pitter Anglerfish.  I bought
it,
so I thought I might buy it if I could live in the mountains,
but I'm practicing, but it's difficult to breathe, and when it comes down to it, I
can't find the words to say.  Right.
Hmm, it's a little difficult, but if it's the best I can do, I'm just buying it. I
don't know what to say, but I
wonder what will happen. Let's have a contest next time. Apa, I'll
practice. Um,
yeah.
[Music]
Thank you for always making my streams so fun.  I
have a question. I understand that you are at home. I don't think you need to write it.
Cha-chan draws illustrations. I used to really like drawing illustrations. I
drew a lot of them, and I
had a dream of becoming an illustrator.  Back then, I was
always told that I was really good at drawing for my age, but then I
started doing other things and stopped drawing,
and now when I open my eyes, I realize I'm my age.  I think it's normal,
so it's not special anymore. It used to be called special, but now it's special. I'm not good at it now.
Well, someday I'll be
very happy if I get some work as illustration data again.
Kilo?  Hey, I want to see it,
um, um,
uuuuu, I drew a loading screen just in case, but it's pretty bad,
it was scattered, um, I wonder if you call it in Japanese, it's not the normal one,  I
drew it cutely and small, but I'm going to
try my best and draw it a little
further. I drew it for the first time in a while after I went back to the countryside, so I'll study a little more.
If you practice, you might become a town village. It's increasing day by day
.
It's
a little small English translation. Cats.
Ah, I'm
good at it. I'd be happy if my dad told me that, but I don't do that.
Flattery 4 car
i. Well, that's how it feels from Sony.
Hahaha, that's right. SD character, Noah. No, no, there was August on the Jing screen.
But this time, I'm going to get serious and hold something other than a proper one for the first time in a while. But I always have a background
or English class. I'm
not good at that Niigata and I hate it.  My dad's medical background is so beautiful,
hey, it's
cool and I like it.
Hmm,
for dad,
as expected for dad, papuwa, it's just too amazing, if
dad told me to watch the movie Torisu, I'd be like,
[music] I
can't believe it, I'm bad at it  I'm
happy, but it's
really different.
Even Mario would have been fooled.
I'm praising the bus in that direction. I wonder if it will grow. I'm
praising the camera net. It's another chance to be praised.
Ahh ...  I
want to draw you,
but I
have to practice.
In the morning, which one are you
better at, Japanese or English?
Me too, I was
thinking,
maybe I
'm better at Japanese.
I have a pronunciation
bar, Arashi, um, special price aircraft carrier, but it's not English. My native language is German, so
English should be closer to German than Japanese, so English should be easier for me,
but for some reason,
Japanese  It's a little bit different. I think
Japanese is more
difficult. Sometimes English is so weird.
There are words that I don't know how to pronounce.
As for the sounds, English
is better than Japanese, which has a lot of words.
Yes, I guess it's about the same. In the end, the balance is about the same.  Torii
Trilingual Bird Bird Bird Feeling Paris Ringer
But it's about the same
Pimai Ngushumachap New Sparks in
Bar
Finger Charm Nice Plantation Pita's support District
Players are harmful Spain
aturn
Hmm  Let's
answer the question with the checker.
Service shot please.
Kitani is stuck. It's in. Ah, what? A flood of
service shots. Let's
give it a good one.
Service shot.
Move, four shares. Ah,
this is me.
A little bit.
Let's give it a go. Dam service shot. Uh, turn, yeah.  Yeah,
this is the ad difference after all, isn't it
? Mom, here you go, ran, here you go, please, ok, please take it, kyuppa, I thought it was a shame that this place isn't seen very often, I thought it was a shame, no, this is nice  Isn't it good?
[Music] If you
ask me what's good about it, there are many different things that are good about it.
This fishing season is good and the little squish in the socks is good. Good
girl and miniskirt.
W-w-w-w-w-well then, the miniskirt on the right is nice and this no
belt rule is
really ec up down
tape tape and the pink colour of her nails is nice and
this room is nice too and, how should I put it?
What is this? What can I say? Um, what
is this part called?
Hmm, next to the "trying hard" and "eating"
part, what is that?
Do you know what that is next to the belly button? Is
it a belly button wing?  I
wonder what it is, I sent a respectful
message to the US Vogue.
Why did a strange image appear? Ah,
but it's certainly possible that. No, no ...  My
hands are shaking
. It's completely silent. It's
amazing. It's
possible. It's
perfect. It's great. The shape of the hips and waist is so
good. It's a very good
book.  Papa
Domon Ahhhhh
Paparo is also h
In the comments, I said that my dad made it for me. I
like the firewood, too.
But it's not just this naughty part.
It actually has my favorite part in it.
How do you do it?  So now, when my
dad came, I took off the fabric and immediately c
Pink tone is my favorite, I
think. I
hit the universe. It's
not this. It's
like the universe is reflected.
It's a beautiful sound. It's beautiful, isn't it?
Ohh ...  I
wonder
if it
was a good service shot? I wonder if it
was a good feeling? I wonder
if I like it again? Ah,
I like it even more. I'm
going to pets.  Sho
I can't get any further than this egg talker. I wonder if it's a
cake. Hello, there's a taker. No scam. Chicken cough
match machine is a bit different, right? Chicken cough Ah-chan, what made you interested in Japan
?
Your Japanese is so good that I want to study English hard.
I was asked this question a lot. There were a lot of people who said they were studying English hard. So
I became interested in Japanese people.  I
wonder what the trigger was. I was exposed to a lot of different influences at the same time. I
got a game that was on sale from my mother.  I was
doing a share video and I was like, "This is what this girl and this style,
this style, this atmosphere,
this RPG type game, I've never seen this before, so I thought this is really my taste, and after doing
some research, I found
something like this  I knew there were a lot of them,
and I knew there was a Chanro called JJ RPG.  I was
really into Decelz, so I've loved Thesz ever since and have
done almost all of them,
but I'm not sure if this was before or after, but I'm pretty sure now  I
think it was the same timing, but
later on
in the library, I
found the German one, the Tengame, the Goddess, the German one, I
picked it up, and the picture was really  I thought it was cute, and at
that time I also liked the illustrations from Colored Tales, and
from there I
started drawing illustrations myself, and I
wanted to learn more about Japan and other things.  After that, I got really into Japanese idol culture,
idol music, and Hello! Project. I was
really into it.
In English, I was obsessed with it.
That's how it went. But it was so long ago.  I don't really remember which game or which manga came first.
That's what I mean. Good luck with your English studies.
[Music]
Which one should I choose for first place Germany?
Right now, I have saved 71 out of 7, but I
haven't progressed past 10.
[Music]
Poo
[Music] I
think this is a common problem for Japanese people.
The result is that history is so good that Chara-chan has been working remotely recently.  Maybe it's because I don't go out much, but I'm feeling like I'm completely naked
more often. So, if you have any methods of relieving stress, please tell me. Please
continue to post more streams, thank you. There are two pillars, right?
I think the biggest problem for Japanese people is that they work too hard
and end up with too much stress.
I've basically been living at my own pace, and I think it
's something that needs to be done, absolutely needs to be done.  I've
been living quite well with that, but recently,
I've had a lot of stuff piled up,
especially a week before and a week after the fire, and I've
been really stressed out.  For various reasons, I have a lot to do, and then suddenly,
when so many people come and see me, I'm really curious about the prefecture.
I'm the type that I look into things and choose from a variety of options,
and the number of responses just keeps increasing.
To be honest, I don't know how to relieve stress. I'd
like to know more about it.
If it were true that they weren't around right now, I'd be able to relieve stress by having them comfort me,
but they're
not around right now, so there are some adult reasons.
So, that's
one thing, and that's also a good thing.  I don't know, I'm depressed
because of the stress level, but it's hard not having a cat, so I guess the only
other way to relieve stress is to
watch Netflix for hours.  I watch it for hours and hours, and it
's interesting, and I learn a lot from watching it. I've watched it many times, but I'm currently rewatching Friends. I
guess I get energy from watching Friends.  I want Lean Nico to heal me.
Not the Lens Beast Veil, but the older friends.
Ah,
everyone knows that.
If you haven't seen it, I
recommend it. It's a cat. Thank you. Bach. I
want to see a cat.
Actually, I took a nap today, but I had this dream again. I was happy when I came.  I
thought he was slacking off on the course, but he was just playing Macrasa
Ah, he's
good at answering questions from Aiter Anji
[Music] I'm
trying to make something like
this ne-yo
5 example I'm 4 challenge specified Mi-
and board  I love it so much Allah version of Charge Plum
What kind of cutter do you
use me? I am the last Phoenix left in this world If you
use me in cooking,
there will be no more Phoenixes Are you okay with that? Are you okay with that?
No  Don't you think so? It's a waste, isn't it?
Please stop the chicken up of the pattern Japanese interview. It's
not chicken, you know that, right? Daddy
? I was often told
that I'm the endless wind dew grass.  That was so amazing.  You might
think that you can eat it as many times as you want because it respawns after you eat it once, but that's not true. Is
that psychology?
But no, I've lived for hundreds of years and
finally that child is
a.
Take it out of my lungs again.  I get up
But if I get put together, it's 4-4
So you don't try to eat me
It's a waste, virgin Oh, I
'm a phoenix, it's a waste It
's not tasty
Burp Plop
Plop Plop
Enter Hmm Hmm
Pooh  Part
[Music] I wonder
if it was a connection
Ah, yeah, I
got a lot of high-value questions Good
evening I always watch the abolition I'm currently living in Canada and studying English, so I just
put it in between, huh,
nuki, ah,
a, yeah, everyone  I
am working hard on raising and lowering my English. I am
often asked to give tips on how Japanese people can use English well. I
don't have a dental clinic, but on the contrary,  If you want to learn Japanese well,
please tell me the tricks to use it.  Can
you use things like "cha-chan"? It's a really good read. Yes, I know. The trick to becoming able to use English well is to learn it. That's not right. You just have to get used to it. I'm Japanese.  There
was only one way I learned Japanese. I didn't use any language skills or have any teachers. There was only one way I learned Japanese, and that was
through conversation or communication. So if you do that every day with English, you'll
definitely become fluent.
But you really have to use it every day. You can talk to yourself. I
think it's fine to do it every day, or you can use Skype. You'd be a good kid if you could give me some chocolate.
Or you could do some English broadcasts on YouTube or something like that.
If you do it, you will be able to
improve your pronunciation.
If you come across a word you don't know, you will immediately write it down.
When I learned Japanese, I didn't know that.  Whenever I came across a word I didn't
know, I didn't take notes because I was lazy and thought it was too much trouble,
but I would at least look up the meaning and
try to use that word right away.
And then I couldn't get it out of my head. Well, maybe I'm a special case.
Yes, I don't think there are many people who can memorize things that quickly.
But it's
better to write it down so that you can use it when you get the chance.  I
think it will be sweet, and the communication part is drawn.
Yes, even with such bones, the 5th frame is
difficult. It's difficult, especially for me, for example, the other child,
for example, I
tried to learn Italian, but the pain is like this.  Well, it didn't really sink in at all,
and I
wonder why. And the
other thing is, I didn't
talk to her. And the
second thing is, I wasn't interested. So, if you're
not really interested, you can't remember it.
And there's no conversation.  No,
I'm
collecting the number of people. Is
this it?
Did you learn something from what I said
? I think you learned a little bit.
Interest is the most important thing.
Interest and motivation are key.  I
think your Japanese is really good, but sometimes I
feel like it sounds like a Kansai dialect. Have you ever been there? Well, I'm
not here now, but have you ever lived in Kansai?
Well, it
wasn't for long, but I have lived there.  I wonder
if that was the influence.  I was
always speaking in Kansai dialect and people would
say "5" and tell me I was a patient. I
didn't even realize it myself, but now I don't say it much anymore, but sometimes I say "5" a little bit.  I
think you and him will probably say "house" when you introduce yourself.
That's typical of Kansai. "
house
" is it. Really?
But it was more popular in the past.  I
was like, "I like Osaka, I ...
If we continue with this question, the
most popular color is ah, I'll
search a bit and see if it's 8.
Hmm, I
shouldn't have saved 71 items.
[Music] No, it's
white.
This one is not it.  No,
aaaaaaa,
a
old hag 1
[music]
ana, eeeeeeennn
, that's good,
ah, wait a minute,
hmm  I can't
find it. I wonder when it will be. It's fine.
I
didn't save it.
But there's one thing I can't find here either. I have one question.
Where do you want to go in Japan? I
like that machine.
After I changed my clothes.  Where have you been?
Where do you want to go? I want to go to Hokkaido. I
want to go to Okinawa. And the
places I've liked so far are
Arashiyama and Kyoto. It was a while ago, but it
was really beautiful.  I've
seen a lot of places, like Hakone, Enoshima, my mother's Itoshima, but I've
never been to Hokkaido, so I
want to go there. I
want to go to a hot spring.
Well, I've been there quite a bit, and my
brother wants to go on a tour.  Hokkaido
has a snow festival, right
? I want to go
there. And Fukuoka is my favorite place. Unfortunately, I'm from Fukuoka,
so that's why I
went there to eat ramen.  I do
n't like going to ramen restaurants, so I
went to Ichiran. I
like tonkatsu the most. By all means.
[Music]
Then 333  The
list is calming. I don't think anyone will see me even if it takes 30 minutes, so I
won't be told that I'm late with eating this person.
Eh? Yes, that's right. He didn't answer this question.  But I was able to answer, so that's it. Yes, I
was asked this too, but I'm
tired. Summer. I love the song of the caregiver.
Eh, there are a lot of scams. Um, it's a lie. Seniors complain about sitters. kk,
expenses, adk, out  But that statue, did you know? I
want to know in the
future. Do you want to collaborate in the future? I'm rooting for you, mother
. Well, I don't remember, but
maybe.  I guess it's Noki,
after all. I know Kiriki, this girl is funny, she celebrates with 5 balls and keeps holding them. Um, I'm just standing there and looking at the senior Pacal. Ah, ah, down. And in the future, the cards will be like that too.  I feel like I have a new opportunity to do something like that. I
want to do another 3D broadcast someday.  I
want to do it together.
I'm in.
There are still a lot of questions I haven't answered, but I've included them in the questionnaire. I want to answer about 32 questions, 3 questions,
but
[Music]
Answer 4 a Is
this
it? I like this one.  It's
a bit long, but
one head,
Dandandandandan
[Music]
tan,
hehe, it
hurts, there's a
character, it's lame, e, the latest 1 series Kiha, it's a character version, thank you, I
can sign up for a membership  I'll join
if I can. I might be able to join soon. I
wonder if there will be an announcement tomorrow.
I'm a big fan of Fukkupa-sensei, who is Canon-chan's dad. He's a
dad who is delicious.  I
started to like Fuke-sensei's butt in Rock Shooter.
I also like Kiha-chan. If you don't mind, please tell me which catcher has the best pitching ability.
Thanks to Kiara-chan who speaks both English and Japanese, I want to study English.  I think so. Yes, there
were a lot of people who felt the same way. Good luck. I
would be very happy if Cha-chan could have a fun transformation in 8. Thank you. I'm happy.  You
see, when the song Black Rock Shooter first came out, I also listened to it and
loved the blackness of it, the air raids, the design, and
then I watched the anime movie.
What do you think?
That was the one that left the biggest impression on me,
but I also really like the design of Altena from FJO,
and the design of Seiryo 6 that they've been doing recently. I
really love it, but my
favorite is
Papa's
My favorite is
from the exercise - I think I did it.
It's something called someone's style. I
saw a cute scene. The glasses are really moving. I feel anxious.
That personality is interesting. My
mother thought it was interesting. Ah, you know, it's
really cute.  Noazu has a really nice body, her
hair is smooth and silky, her wings are beautiful, her eyes are reflecting the universe, she's
cute with two hats on, and her smile is just lovely. The scene is
a bit bouncy, and the
belt is from the Fallen God series.  I'm wearing it, but for some reason it says I shouldn't use it.  I wonder
why it's so mysterious. I feel
like it has all kinds of secrets. There's duct tape, but if there is, it's amazing. It's a
scene that makes you wonder why it's prohibited to use duct tape. Wow,
it's a really strange collage.  I'm holding the hand that cuts off the Marinu region, and it looks like a
really delicious area, so I
want to eat it, and honestly, I stopped by to eat, but when I see it, I
like it, it's interesting, and the weapon looks strong,
no,  It's not a toy, it looks moderate but it's certainly strong. I heard that it's the real thing.
Then, the
Transformation Angel's Nest is not supposed to be transformed, but
if you reply, you'll become a real Phoenix.  Do you
know this? It's sad. It's gone up. It's not
good. If you like it, please try it.
Ah, haa. Thank you for the question. Well, it hurts now.
Simply open it.  I wanted to praise you because I like your design. I don't
really like myself that much. I'm in love with myself.
Don't chase me,
chopsticks, I'm really in love with you, but everyone is different,
because my dad did a good job, I'm
going to live like this, I'm not just being arrogant, but I want you to
understand, isn't it wonderful?  This body is so
nice, I have no choice but to say nice things, I have no choice but to say it,
if it looks so cute, it's only 4, I'm so happy
, thank you for the pressure
, the pattern key,
please take care of Gara-chan, one more thing
Typhoon:
A little bit, yeah.
Phoenix:
Hmm.
Oh, let me answer this one. Hey, is this it? Ah,
yes, I haven't had much of an appetite recently and I haven't been able to eat breakfast, but Killer has breakfast n,
what do you usually eat? Well, this changes quite a bit.
Basically, that sweet thing.  I wonder if I eat a lot. I tweeted about it today too. In the
morning, I spread it on my face and baked a Rakshasa. I do
n't think there's much Nutella in Japan. It's sold in stores, but there aren't many people who eat it.
I recommend some kind of chocolate spread.  But the other ones sold in Japanese supermarkets  It
tastes completely different from the chocolate spread that is not Nutella, and it's definitely better.
So you just
put poison on it and eat it. That's right, and then
that
Gragradolla Japanese Gravure idol is a little different, but I see
Have you ever heard of "Yuzu-ri"? It's German. I
often eat it in the Meiji 22nd year.
Hmm, it's hard. I
like to eat things like scrambled eggs and knee-high socks. It's super. I like black people too.
Basically, I put bread on it, but I highly recommend it.
Nutella. Oh, right, I've been
making it a lot recently. French
toast is already sweet, but I
also put nutella on the French toast. I
also put fruit like bananas on it.  Strawberries and that too, and at the end you get a sugar
meal
book.
Super delicious sugar, I can't do both, but French toast, I remembered it, it's amazing, it's
simple, French toast,
Ninuterror, it's
poisonous, Don,
Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah, If you
eat this,
you'll
Even though it's such a great idea, making French toast in the morning is a
bit of a hassle because it takes a lot of time.
But making it yourself is
way more delicious than that French toast face. If you'd like, please
try making it. It's amazing.  It's easy.
What is
it?
First, you have
toast the bread. First, you have toast the bread.
Then you
cool it down. That's what the village does.
One egg, third grade.
How much was it? 150 20 250 450 How much was it?  But then, eggs,
Sato, and a little regrettable brother, I like to mix it all together, and now I like to
put in a little bit of cinnamon and mix it up, and a 8, and then
through it, and then Pangga,
that  If
it still doesn't get hot after that, put the egg thing on top of it,
and if you receive all of it,
you
see the sponge, you receive it all,
about 8 minutes.  I
think I forgot something. I think it's right. I said "Yaaaaa" and
made the customer say "Yaaaaaa", then I cooked some more and
put the sound of the temple on top. Ah, that's
right. I saw this on a youtube tutorial and that secret thing
first.
That toast was supposed to be the role.
If you do that, the final product will
be better. I don't know if it's a relief or not, but that's the only way I've ever done it. Lily: I do
n't like maple syrup, so I don't use it, even if I have it.  Ah,
there are cheeks that can be leveled up even more. I
put nutella on it, I put fruit on it,
and many more.
Bunny ice cream. Let the bunny
put ice cream on it.
One minute for breakfast. Ah,
this is the best.
Ah, I quite like sweet things. Hmm.
This is also often eaten with Euro rice, Ryoko-sama's
b I eat Tupperware March machines, but I also love sweets.
Kids in the morning, what are you talking about?
That's four times as much. The
strong ones have ice cream for breakfast.
Eat French toast with Nutella.  That's
right, I
recommend it.
There it is--- I
wonder if there's just one more question left. I'll bear with the "maybe not" question and say if it suits the question I absolutely want to answer. [Music] Nontan tan tan tan tan! Everyone, it's French toast tomorrow! There it is--- You'll definitely not regret it, and it's super healthy too.
Super healthy
Oh, this is it, this is what I definitely wanted to respond to
A-building
Happy birthday! I
don't know your name, but congratulations!
Cheonggye Atsuta P Air Lee Seong-gye Ba-sa-shi J
Song Potter Car is here!
Calculation is not a
home  Featured snow was also in German. This is it.
yeah, good, yes, it
was German. It has the same melody as Happy Bus Stop, but the lyrics are a bit off
.
Rain letter, please.
Wei, well, let's do it already. The
chat is really fun.  But when I talk to everyone, I
want to finish it by Daisy time, Japan time, so I'll
read the chat, and I'll
chat a little while I'm at it, and everyone can chat a little more.  I really
want to do it,
but I'm free to do it at whatever pace I want, but I've been told to do it however I like,
but I think I need to read Coupy a little bit.  I
wanted to do it once a week, but I
thought I'd try to do it once a month, so when I was able to do a collaboration dinner, I thought I'd do it
with a lot of collaborations between all the seniors in Japan.  I think that the scene
where he talks is the one where he wants to do more, so I want to open a clinic at least once a month.
I think that it's a bit unusual. I think that the Japanese people's dental survey is ...  I want everyone to enjoy it, I
want everyone to know about Live English, I want
everyone to support us, and I hope that we can connect the five English shows and
Japan Live Japan together in a smooth way.  I
think
that
I have been
told a lot of things,
but I think that I have to do what I want to do, and
if I don't do it, I won't be happy.
Well, there were a lot of people who supported me and said things like that to me.
Well,
that's it.
Thank you for all your questions. I talked a lot so I
couldn't answer all of them.  I didn't have it,
but I think I'll be doing a Japanese-only stream next time,
so I'll make it
to the best time possible. Well,
where are you tomorrow?
[Music]
That Suan Funa Ichi Pucha Na
Sakura Yen Tomorrow's stream is
...  Wait, where are you? Yes, why are you wearing this?
Help me! It
hurts! Huh
?
Cha! Huh? What,
what did I drop? It
's morning time, tomorrow at 6:22 Japan time, Building A. There should be a
notice or something, there should be insurance,
right, tomorrow?  My new microphone arrived so I'll use it tomorrow for the new microphone.
Mickey-san, my
mixer audio interface should arrive tomorrow too so I should be able to use it from tomorrow. That's
really, really, really, my microphone is crap. Actually, this is what I'm struggling with right now.  Because people say it's really shitty  I
spent a lot of money on Minecraft and got a microphone from Kari-chan,
but I think I'm doing something wrong. I'm not using it properly because I'm not using the settings properly,
but it's okay so I bought a new one. I
should be able to use it from tomorrow.  So, overwintering
Eto
If you can use it, then tomorrow at 9 o'clock, it's a
big announcement, so ok I
think it might be 4 at the same time Well, it was good, so ok
Everyone was really excited, but I thought Abe on the microphone was a waste. That's
right, the other day  Everyone listened to the karaoke of that song -
that was amazing. I can only sing Japanese songs, so I can't sing them well, but I'm
not very good at singing English songs. I'm not sure about the investigation rights, but I think Japanese songs are better.  It's easy to sing.
So, I've been singing a lot of songs, like "
Peach-colored Unrequited Love" and "5 Seconds Before I Seriously Fall in Love" and
"Even When I'm a Mother or a Grandmother, I've been singing a lot of songs, like "Blue Bird" and so on,
but I'll be singing them again tomorrow.  There are some old songs that I want to sing, but I want to sing them again with a new microphone.
If you like, please listen to it. There is also a unique announcement. That's
the kind of girl. Hahaha.
Ehhhh. OK Andrei, three, squishy, another,
thin movie, an amusement park, ahhh, left wing, continued  There's also a collaboration with Sarueshi Nashita.
Um, at 1 o'clock Japan time, I'll be collaborating with that dog's channel, Ina-
chan's channel. Ah,
Venture Kensomachi, this guy talks a lot. Um,
when he chats with CarSpa, he speaks German.  Is it
okay? I
always say that it's only Danke employees, but
if you'd like, I'd
be happy if you could type Danke Shun-tei in hiragana or katakana. I'm
desperate. I
wonder if there will be a lot of Japanese chat today. I can't think straight now.  I can't turn around, how is the child moving? One more cup of Ness's antibacterial
drink. People, that iced tea's chest. It
's okay if it's just the house. It's called "Tanke Shun", but please be male-oriented. Let's
make it a broad-based night today. Oh,
but there is also  I think some people will leave without opening the door.
Thank you so much to everyone who watched and planted the seeds. I
watched this at this time. Thank you so much to all the seniors in Japan who are doing interesting streams.
Also, from now on, I'll be streaming the second part.  It's been a long time, but I'd be
happy if you could see it.
Also, on behalf of everyone, Maidou Papa, by the way, it's
pronounced as Akacha. Eh,
Higashibata-san, as always, the first one is
not... I'm just a person, but I usually use it.
Hey, there are a lot of English names, so I don't add 3. Um
, it gets mixed up, so what
should I do? I'm not used to seeing it, I'm not used to adding "san" to Japanese names in Zuppa Chat, so it doesn't look weird.
If I don't help, I feel really uncomfortable. You're not
calling me. Oh, I'll
just try it. I'm so used to the usual flow, so it's difficult. Eh?
Is it a fever or a first bullet? It's weird, isn't it? It feels rude in a situation like this. Come on, I
have to put it on.  I guess it's going to be a big help in the end. But the English names are coming out one after another. It's
really difficult. Ah, it's become a bit of a problem. I'll
come up with some ideas.  It
feels good, I'll try it naturally, I'll use a 3-tiered car, n
,
Ah, I'll give you a thank you in German, the
arm is strange, this is a
magnet, 810 kinds, father size, Shun-san,
warming up, shu, airo, 13 cushion  Me Game Figure Division Machine Moment Soul Fu
Shall is nuclear power plant Ocha Pinsplode-san entered I
thought this person told the Japanese people and people Rank
outside the company
Chana is Pekorintan family week to bear Chikihisa-san
danke  Gathering Sonobe Clean Danke Repair Day Game Winter is not
Danke Gathering
Ethos Sakagawa-san Danke Car
Snow Bell Acid Residue Junsu Bankruptcy Tanke Shusai Number
Danke Car Sansatsu-san Handshake Meeting Day
8 Rear Yoshikin Short Term End Old It's Really  A Japanese-language
episode where a Prien participant and a member of the Hornisse team were called. Even if they were called by their first names, it would
still be the 7th specification. Yoshika. It's
so confusing. Kotonoha-san's handshake and even Ako-san's tail.
Turn up the ventilation fan, Mr. Udo, the participants, Orange Medical Group, Mr. Shall, Mr. Tan Kishu, Mach
Tony, Mr. God, short-term season,
152 volumes, the third bullet, no erase,
8 insurance heroine gathering soldiers, thank you for infiltrating the other day  Thank you for this. I'm sorry I
can't mourn you. I really want to retweet it, but I'm afraid this might be bad. I'm
sorry, I really liked it. Thank you, my sister. I'm sorry, I really liked it. Thank you, my sister. I'm sorry, I'm
sorry. ...
It was like a dad's drawing of his daughter, and all of them came together and drew a really good illustration, and I was really happy. I'm in it too. I was really happy that the other countries were so good at it. It seems that they saw "Amitaka a puppy". That's good.
[Music]  ]
Only the car
c d e a Only the 3rd Kesha Carrot flavored Yatsuhashi singer definitely the forehead person Just now Nepeku Ah
Senior's raise
that thin one time when I opened it I saw this name I
wonder what he's doing now I'm
there uc  It's definitely a window view. Ah,
what is everyone doing now? Are you all
still looking at the window? Everyone is like that. I wonder if that window view thing is over now.
Sunbird,
that's amazing - I could never do that, it's driving me crazy.
Thank you for the one window.  Ah, it's
over. Aren't you going to prepare it? A
a It would have been better to start at 11 o'clock in Japan time, but the function was already decided.
10:00
Mom, it's a
waste to only do it here now.
Maika, it
was only one hour a day.
Seriously? Good
timing 8 It's
starting again Seriously, it's happening again
Wow, hurry daddy It's
like a Mike Raiders' Garden But I'm watching it at my own pace in the archives
Okay
22 Taste of the gentle Miyoshi Kihide
Onnya one-stage slope bran weak?  Yuda decay patch app respectful Fraw-chan peace
pal how ball eyes should be Pippi rose character
study
aaaaa
6 polyp taaaaa Amagumimuracho look Jimmy Choo is rain wig ara ikezu
english  and japanese Cheen election
3rd tank employee cancer's Japanese is very good and wonderful. Please continue to
let us hear your wonderful Japanese. Thank you.
danke Shunmanya-san, Danhatatebun and Poi-tan makeup
Welcome to the match. danke  I wonder if it's happening. I've seen about two.
Today, the third bullet, Keiharu,
Kazumaki Riwo-san's related person's 8000 steps, Dondon is Wide Share Prince Plaza, that
compensation starter check air, it's going to go to the regular
version, Fuwaa w Anan  It's been 22 minutes, what kind of road is the actual battle score?
Danke Shuun-
san, voice actor Sanpei Ufu
Danke Schen Zombie Sausage 3-stage house spring lunch station service has come, so is Seikai-san
Danke Shun Ah, I
might want to write about my favorite things from Papa's works  I think it was a response to Yuna,
but if you say it's blue, that thing, I think it's from the anime, if you say it's
not enough, I
really love it, the ski
design is great, everyone is really good, I
thought the chain was perfect
Second place rank 5 Ah, ah, beach, 3 model change, Hiro Asaya,
festival bot 3 bullets, erase cotton, 3 bullets, shun, carbonated, reporter, convenient, ah, 3 places, gya,
Yuasa, convenience, mother-in-law, special, wifi, career explanation, next time, mint plus, top, garden
chirp Niissho Paint Fa Bingo is short even
Sakura Say
Watch Center Pin Eyes Python Man Paste Electric Hame Me from Pen Q 3 is titanium system
J-san Sumi Kishu top Soil cutter surroundings Killing Muse Boy  Subcontractor collection Soup Tama-
san tally p Mashimaru Just showing it makes the customers smile, so it's
amazing This is the first anti-makeup
Friend Nagato-san Landlord End
Cap Papa Weak Last Spring Yamay-san Tank
By the way, if you call me "
san" I'll beat you up. If you call me "hocchan" I'll call you "
hocchan"
Yes, I understand, it's that old man, but is it
okay to use the old man? The old man is standing up, isn't it the same state? I wonder if it was Danke, the car cap and the pape are erased, the mid-term budget Danke collection is no good, and those who don't have a thread are oil soba  I recommend it as a Japanese food. I've
never eaten it before. It looks oily.
There's oil on the side and it's cheap. What does that
mean? Pack.
Warm-up employee cap. Chiaki-san never eats it.
Mania 3rd grade car-kun Akashi is 3rd grade.  Step cosmetics
4-1 Sanyamaki line Atara
no, I
want the name of the White Lord 6 Rama time, I want it
forever, I want it forever, if there is no degree of the Lord of the Inushi, it's meaningless, if you
don't know, it's
delicious, n,
change, sosandankeshan,
Grappler cracking, cracking  3rd incarnation support 3rd short-term Shin
Ananaka forever
we are dinner ios turn off the view nei delicious today cha peace
shop Tsubaki ponzu says to Xu Ning Linji door 1 touch the place  The
girl in the episode is also a buster from the Kesha family. The
horse's body is just a line, Jas is skiing, Dankeshen, ji, Danke car, it looks
like a hairpin,
8 notes, 2
hours, thank you for the action, that's it, um,
Roman old man before too  Did you make it?
Exploration 1009-san is really good at being in between the Koreans.
Thank you
very much. Bankisha anywhere Cero-san, the flag bearer, His Majesty Echo, how many articles are there? I wonder what you think. This is the number of articles, but Takeuchi  I can't read the end,
Takeo titanium, empty titanic acid residue, around the
favorite 043 tank, failover, Minami Kyushu, Sassan, Shu Yong,
8 about cat, what a week, distributed learning
, this, only sedan, car, type hexane,
Takeo up
photo, bankruptcy only  Space Cat,
are the three black spots boots?
That or
that?
Toe cap is good March is science mountain only car
printer Dankeshen absolute area is the oldest, isn't it?
If it was a pamphlet that said that the tail was born around the egg-laying season, it would be bang bang, so it's a secret
author
morning open before dating button charcoal Kishu  I loved my mother Takushu,
sugar deficiency syndrome combined book 13th edition late,
everyone is now at that service time, I'm super
grateful,
women have blue hair after all, love, I can do it here, but Danke car,
Mitcha 3rd edition reporter,
Mania 3rd grade, Shun and  Carbonated luck only meat m-san Danke collection
Electric off green onion increase Santan family Shun
Kohei Kaga-san is energetic starring Die or 3-tier family
Ishikawa-san only I fell in love with the place again I love Kariya and Sessha I'm a
uke daddy give birth  Thank you for giving it to me. I am also very grateful.
Bankisha
Kura Pura Bakibaki-san read it all the way up to the end, so who is it? I chose it. I'm
glad.
Thank you very much. I
thought the name was beautiful even before the first transformation. I also made a wooden mold in Japanese. I did
n't go to the mountain and noticed the tidal flats.  It was a
huge success. I think it was that tweet. I tweeted something with my name up.
Before my debut, I had a
line from Stein's Gate. I didn't notice that it was from Stein's Gate.  I didn't get it. Did you notice that I put the
matching "I want to give it to you" John in the tweet
? I
wonder if you noticed. It took a while for him to notice, so I thought he must have said something great.  I
was told that I was being rude, but I didn't say it. I
just put in that line from that day of the leader. I was
surprised at how many people understood the makeup in the third volume.
Ayumu-san, warm surroundings.  Eyes of the reporter n
Sun is only support
Totan Minamikishu Shirochi egg-laying steamship
Assets only car
Hydrogen only photo
Hototogisu Dandan reporter,
such as long fees, this is an ally h or 8,
Furya usage fee
, Ru embezzlement Miya-san, end employee, Phoenix mountain only employee, sister-in-law Sesa-ni only car, Pudding 3rd round
makeup Sash-san Dankeshen swing 3rd round Kyosen junior  Kaga-san is difficult,
so I'm glad to see him in the short term. I'll
update it. Someone might have come, so I'll
update it. I'm
glad to see him in the short term.
Music]
From me, so
here it is.
Yes, Suzuki and well,
one charge does not stop, Kishuzu 2-kan only, it was the state's birthday, the person who sent it individually
was a bit of a Shuzan, oh,
wow,
congratulations again,
deleted  It's just
carbonated, it's a clever bread, it's a master, it's a ward, it's a mountain, it's a dream, it's a
good luck ...
Ice-chan Ken, by the way, pizza is not good, line Ai-san, I guess,
Yuta-san, only one, mo 3 shots, Shun,
when, Shifu-san, Charcoal Kishu, especially chicken, remaining bullets, makeup,
fluffy landlady, station new contact, two San San incarnations
The tail is still Anko-san Danke car
Our company car Cheek Sheep-san only support a 8 Ah
Daja I can't breathe Ufu
Kakukaku Kagoyama Takuhide Ramenman 3 take Shen Mold
Killer Tandakken Demon God Walking Place Mountain
6 Cent Ya Do it how you want  Please, please, please, the next latest song that I have prepared is going to be released.
Thank you so much for your support. I'll do my best.
Nyankoromochi-san, make-up, chat, san, how many models of Volkswagen did you steal?  Santanya Shun Potato Three
Great Battles
Good Adventure Battles in a losing streak Rabbit Yupopo Moon
Danke Employee
Japanese Hanshin and how to mourn Good luck Horo Yanu  I
wanted to study English after watching it. Everyone said that. Everyone was quiet.
Alvin-san, 3 models, Mr. Nkan, coffee, turn 3, Kishon, Yamakamigawa-san, only, Mr.
Nakuma, Mr. questionnaire, car mother, mtm, calculation 3 steps, house  Car
, sound wave uncle, tanke collection, ul, egg laying song collection,
yamiyazan handshake, danke, moment, danke, master, so-like, 3-stage, kashun,
origami, 3-round, Edo Daisan, Kishu, mechaka, power generation,
3-stage, kashun, Japanese delivery, a, do
n't worry, Lotte, rather, I'm the one who speaks English  I'm making a study edge, so I'm learning English there too. I
think polite language is difficult, but I'm a
dividend person. I have a
lot of Nishi 3rd generation hereditary meisen. I have
10 days off a week.
[Music]
Single item uk Danke Schon Hatsuka thank you
Hmm, I can read Nihongi. I
gave birth to Major 6, thanks to Shun Nefkrai 3 Dan family.
Ami Mami Japan has been abolished. From now on, Keyna-chan will be able to work freely and as herself.
Please wait for a year.
What kind of image is it? F-san
moved it.  Thanks to Tojun and
Setsumi-san, I can now move around energetically and in my own way. I'm really grateful. Thank you very much. The festival battle, Goma Tofu-san, Oya Shun, the sun is shining brightly, Mika Haruki, Ah-chan is here, and thanks to that, I can see the comfort of the house.  It has
become my motivation to study English.
Please challenge yourself to do what you want to do. Thank you. I'm
happy when I hear things like that. That's my goal.
That horse,
building A, I'm going to take the Japanese here so that everyone can see it and have fun.
Thank you for watching it. I
guess it's like
watching it with a kick like a bridge.  Sunset Ro
I want to be like this If you like it a lot
There is something I like
Erika-san's Spring a
Singularity-san's short-term season
Leather light 3-stage collection Sky-
flying slash only Gen
Nonta Senator is here for the Passion Law too, Killer-chan, I'm
rooting for you, so please do your best, Grameenphone is abolished, what's the matter,
thank you, warmth, surreal, 4,
Bouri-an-chan, Yamaki Toshi-kun, digging 3  In the stage, the surprise attack is Oku-ya 3rd model, and when the
pro ship is mixed in, the 3rd stage standard tree is only Eru-san gathering 8
Komeda Susume-san Thank you, Tondanke area was very fun, so from the nutrition ken and
Japanese-speaking area
I think that the roots of the split bridge burger are that Mobis is also full of fun. I think it
would be good to split it in the Otani style. I also think that.
3 models
a,
ah, read it, what do you
call it?
Can you just use this one?
9 What? Kana Naginagi What?
Shun Key 3rd stage car Ah,
blue, let go, handshake, touch, you can call me by my first name, so
erase the burnt Aoi Tachibana  Is it
okay to have a new Aoi-san and aberrations?
Follow Kiyo-san Danke season
Ebatchiki-san Danke Shunperu is already in the middle of the spring I
want to understand the truth of the universe, but the spawning season anniversary 3rd stage family support Ren-san Danke Shuu
My  Please call me by name. I chose it. The 3 big names in the week today were abolished and it was really fun. I want
money for paintings, and I want to see tomorrow's Cocosis and the microphone thing
separately. Ah, I'm sure you've told me a lot of things.  The
shot Kesha Unu Pudding 3rd shot standard 4th shot after 3rd shot Kishu Choi John's Henin 3rd stage Kashun
Danke Shen is what the price is so crazy. The
face is so cool.
Well, only the radar is Shanghai Prefecture, the erosion control lottery machine Pearl Pan is easy  It's like a book.
3 minutes in the middle of the day, Star Skapoipu 4 If you make it a name-based movable property immediately, super immigration will be possible.
There is a battle race bar jump and enjoy  So it's easy to fly through the door hatch, no
mix, no
Theo is an office worker,
no buzz, no water, a little bit, imimi p, chai, Friday, Saturday, King, Wi Prefecture, please, a
new start, ummm,
danke, the end, Maverick-san, I'm
drunk  I'm searching for
something good, Tachibana work,
Dankeshen, I hate the way you look,
thank you for the fun half before going to work, I
have hope and motivation, next time I'm working on a scrap job so I can't see it  I think it will
come again
Andy
Ato difficult sensor
Peko Land exclusive sheet metal worker
Landlord employee Pinter is saved March Newcomer Tournament First Spa Chao Can Chan Newz Thank you
Doctor Pepper Powder Thank you I have to buy it again and I can open it
Chan, this is the last update I think, because I
was looking forward to hearing the sound again.  I
want to support this energetic character even more now. Thank you.
Touko Risu. I think it's hard to make people enjoy the power of the character even after 2 minutes. If you have to, you
can do it. I'll try my best to walk.
Well, about that.  I've been thinking about it a lot, but I think I'll go in this way from now on.
Thank you. I'll
take it. The
following is the
part where I take the ramen. Tsuda, Shun
Tanya, and I'll take it.  I
wonder if there is one. I think it's best to eat it for 2000 yen.
Thank you for bringing it. I
want to eat ramen.
39 Seina Ah, my
dad is so kind. This
photo is so
good. I'm just so
kind. A
volcanic bomb that made me feel so good.  I like Cure-chan's bright smile and movements.
I know that she's worried about something difficult, but I
'm working hard to make sure she can continue her activities on Oni no Hi.  As a fellow fraudster, I
can't help but look forward to the lifting of the ban.
I'm
wondering if I can talk to people at the cafe if the ban on talking is lifted, but I
don't want to do it myself, so I'm thinking about going myself.  I
thought maybe it would be better to wait, but
it's difficult.
But Senpai doesn't really invite me to collaborate. I don't want to make
him collaborate. Yes,
Senpai
won't invite me to collaborate.
[Laughter]  I'm
a little worried, hey, ah,
nnn, I'll think about it,
strategy,
strategy meeting,
danke, surrounding price decision, Southern Kishu, supporting the 3rd gold, singer, around the rank, Japanese, love, ride,
thank you very much,
fashion show, a band, curve owner, ran  Chapsal ah
1 ipo Toyama Kinjiday
danke shu phoenix san rakutoshi's last I
think this is no more I wonder if it's
okay
a little no what's up
today was really fun everyone is the eastern army wonder 1 kiko denou general election ti  1 Jose Now Young
Star is suitable for flooding statistics are also available.
Anchor pigs other than the shrine approach will appear.
Thank you very much to everyone. Tomorrow we will gather
at the steam meeting. B Yeah yeah yaa ...
Place Hebu B Bar Cebu Good Big Zam Carry Menu Front Fund Purse Book EP
Buy Location Wish Mr. Tarkin Sheet Music Shorts
N Spen Tee Tomorrow Karaoke
Farmer
Important Announcement I think the water surface is rising, but the
announcement  There is one! I'm
waiting for you all.
Amoy Lunbao RB 1. Go straight up to the mansion called "Inches of Arrogance"
and then 1000 yen for 6 N. The
final greeting is in German again, but I wonder if anyone remembers it.
[Music]
n o
blue fielder dee
dog a
[music]
c yotsuba nyan
ooo there are people who remember well
r 4 meu riser member windage otsu za pa grass powder zoom web
e 280 Biter Cody Success Guitar Amazing Hori Mizuki
Everyone writes well what you hit or copy and paste it. You're
good at German. It's on youtube.
Can you do Lifetuber?  House YouTuber Burn
Ah Order Complete
[Music]
Oh
by Ah Ah
me
Good job
[Music]
N
ni
Oh tan
Just now the time was started The
one who was started Hahaha
My that Pupeko's speech 6 is
safe p
n  I
had
it for
4 days.
nd
That's it, I had it made and I was playing it. It
's up there a little bit.
By the way, there are already people who have played this screen.
That's how I made it, I
wanted to go
, I
saw a few
tweets,
I had a
fake year attached
[Music]
Walker, I mixed it up, I won,
it's
not a station building  d 3
[Music]
One
BL
ME