hello everybody hi
nice to see you guys sorry for the short
delay but
we're here and everything's working well
[Applause]
[Music]
the gang's all here congrats on the full
crew
let's go
because we're all here together maybe we
do a little self-introduction oh sure
yeah that makes sense maybe from right
to left or left to right
first we
[Music]
how do you feel about winning today
[Laughter]
how many bottles of water can you live
simultaneously
yes one look at it
but it's obviously 15 liters of water
right 15 yeah
yeah that's a lot how many how many
bananas can you with
bananas yeah i mean
at the same time
seven
seven oh come on
yeah they can hear us yeah i think yours
is a little quiet because see how the
mic is yeah oh there we go yeah you kind
of got your you know head turned away
from this match
doesn't like sound okay guys
i have a max volume of six don't worry
about inna's ring it's because i'm
eating it slowly but surely she's
growing back i'm fine eating it like a
donut
am i looking no can i see my
shoulder oh
i think they would be able to yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
why are you doing this you know
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
it there she goes
um she's looking kind of like that's
sexy
second contestant oh round number one is
[Laughter]
[Music]
how do you feel about winning today
uh i will be first from the bottom yeah
as usual wow but um
i am ready okay how many cucumbers can
you hold it one time
yes
i think
in his mouth is not working but i can
fix it really quick so uh let's
introduce the next uh yeah future
competitor oh yes hello um my
my name is mori callipe
and i do
i do some i do some things um
like
i i don't [\h__\h] know do you have sing
no
not wow
definitely not but i do wave my arms
around
definitely not one of those but i do a
couple things and i'm glad to be here by
your side today you guys that's all i
know yeah
i'm happy to be here i'm with you all
last to join the party but it feel it
feels good i'm excited i'm feeling um
i'm feeling confident
most people are betting on you oh yeah
well that's a fool's errand because i
may lift but i think that there's some
surprise strong people here they're not
likely muscle more no no no no
colliding
kilogram dumbbells on each arm like
curls is all i do because i'm like you
know you got to get a little card look
i'm betting on you what is that in your
pounds i will bet three cookies on the
ground
yeah
how many cookies yes yeah
all right the next future contestant is
me
[Music]
yeah well i just realized before the
stream that i'm the only one who is
left-handed in the group so
but since they're wrestling with the
right hand i would have to probably
wrestle with the right hand too
otherwise it doesn't really work
we'll see how that goes but then at
least i have a good excuse if i lose at
the end yay
yeah
and also i'm live today now but once
it's my turn you guys get a little bit
of a sneak peek of my 3d
again but not too much not too much it's
a little bit it's just a little bit yeah
it's a sneaky one yeah all right ina is
back and she's bigger than ever
oh she grew up yeah it's a good size
yeah
and then currently fixing everything at
the same time streaming and moderating
[Applause]
thank you yeah we set everything up we
prepared we're only a small delay this
time so i think we're doing pretty good
so far and i'm excited to uh get in the
ring you know in the table table ring i
guess yeah yeah watson's the one i'm
most afraid of to be honest
yeah lifting all this heavy you know the
all the wires that we have right now
watson how many bubbas can you lift it
one time oh maybe like three or four
bubbles
yeah i mean you weren't that heavy
i could you know i could handle it if
you had if you gained another 20 pounds
or something like that because i'm
currently only five pounds
yeah
i bet i could bench press like with
kiara i wouldn't i wouldn't
you know what once we get into the
suit
and then maybe you could try lifting me
okay oh that'd be fun
christmas
oh is there music i have music
[Music]
uh
i hope the audio levels are good
um i think if we just uh stall for about
five minutes we'll be ready
yeah we're almost ready to get broken
use thunderdome that's there's very
little music
music is good level okay
okay
all right i didn't say how much i can
lift i can lift um two cats at the same
time even though they're really heavy my
cats are pretty heavy
yeah your cat's incredible they're like
monkeys they're chunky little like
fatties but like they're no no only one
of them is a chunky little fatty oh yeah
one of them is very slim
and like yeah yeah yeah
so
i don't know but the problem is i'm
gonna be riding on it today so i don't
know
but we're about to figure it out i think
that she's talking to the ancient ones
right now so she's a little bit like her
body is kind of fresh
okay
she's killing me while she's doing that
oh there he goes oh oh her head what
[Laughter]
yeah i did think of a punishment game
and a winner game this is not really a
game but whoever loses
will uh will
massage shoulder massage the winner
[Applause]
just a little bit yeah
somebody the winner gets a massage isn't
it lovely i want to win yeah you need a
shoulder massage yeah the dancing so
much i need the massage the most
i would like uh i would like a lower
thigh massage though uh i don't think
anyone's going to touch
that
what what what's wrong with my lower
thighs oh wait no you mean your calves
okay yeah i mean my pals sorry are they
calves are fine well even like oh my god
no i think we're not
a nice
a nice squeeze and turn yeah yeah just
just make a skin burn thank you
no no no no you know what i'm talking
about girl
skin burn thing where you put your hands
on the arm
in different directions
in german we call that
which is
you know that's that plant that when you
touch it you get the burn oh yeah that's
the word for it oh then
when now what's up
shrek
hi i'm surprised
what is that yeah poison ivy is it
really yeah is your choice in that view
that sounds so dangerous nettle i think
i mean nettles
yeah you can eat those
i think they're very healthy and you can
make tea out of them
does it burn your smell too
i think something is interesting
let me look it up
[Music]
good for
allergies
stinging nettle has been used for
hundreds of years to treat painful
muscles and joints
eczema arthritis gout and anemia so it
actually really works
it's a miracle plant
[Music]
when you have no fingernails there's
like oh
[Music]
no that is one of my nightmares
hold on we're almost ready
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah because they were they didn't have
them in the first place
[Music]
i'm almost or almost ready just we're
gonna start our competition shortly this
whole this whole idea is very ambitious
to begin yes yeah yeah this is extremely
delicious i like heard the idea and i
was like are we really going to do this
we're almost there no i believe you i
believe i believe you'll make it work
and then we have to change and then
we're going to take some time again it's
going to be fun stop stalling but you
know
what's chad say yeah taco says
that says
we believe in you girls oh
please don't mistake inna and buddha as
the table
hey
hi
i'm a commentary
[Music]
i will get it done
again stop giving them the stuff call me
a table
call me an elf one more time
sorry
an owl
[Music]
wimbo
is the best one it's me gumbo
well gumbo is actually a shrimp dish
it's yummy mm-hmm
tasty i love gumbo
don't where's the delete key on this
thing oh my my german
laptop um this one and for entf thank
you stanford and fandom which is german
for deleton
[Music]
you're facing the right way yeah you're
looking at the yeah
no one can see it girl you gotta you
gotta move the arm around a little bit
okay
yeah kind of a little bit more to the
other the other way the other hand or
the other way
uh pull it in front of your face put it
in front of your there perfect okay yeah
perfect
it looks like you're just pointing at
yourself though
you know what gouda's girl's back of her
head always reminded me of
that i'm not sure what it's called i
think i think
yes
the mushrooms
the mushroom kingdoms i love it
another japanese soup
[Music]
i always think of it
mushroom but it's just blue
mushroom
ice cream
wait a minute oh yeah watto
[Music]
just maybe not today
it has to be replaced with something
like this that we can only do when we're
in person exactly
yeah plus you guys want to see the dice
right we're not going to use a hand can
for the dice no thank you
today
[Music]
but we haven't all forgotten i still
need to do the recap first let me let me
rename the [\h__\h] oh yeah
okay we're almost ready we're getting
there yes we've almost pulled her back
yes
she said
she went to the dark side uh yeah the
void
[Music]
what's dancing
um
[Music]
going you're good you're good alexa
please yes yeah okay yeah we do thanks
now just uh this okay before it breaks
again yeah let's go
all right sit down
sit down get him to bring her
[Music]
all right ladies let's go
oh are you ready to rumble
ready don't break any arms okay please
don't worry
don't hurt each other
[Laughter]
[Music]
hold on
we have the one the only gumbo spicy
shrimpy gargora
[Applause]
shark and in the corner that isn't the
one that gar rimbo is in
it's more like in the middle the one
with a tentacle grip
on the other side of the parallel
universe owned by the ancient ones
written about in the scriptures of some
super [\h__\h] mysterious book in some
secret library under the sea we have the
one the only tentacle taco master
takoyaki from
[Applause]
it's
[Laughter]
all right
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
is
says
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah we haven't decided on the pairings
yet so yeah i guess it'd be good
we can weaker a bit more i can go last
time
is the winner so it should be somebody
plays the winner so good point did
anybody get to win
yeah play the winner of this round i
don't have a bracket kiara told me to
make a bracket i did not regret
everything
i was busy
[Music]
[Applause]
is uh out for now we'll be back
[Music]
yeah
hi
[Music]
oh
you know how is your hand feeling now
would you say you still have like all
the power left in yourself or did you
lose something against
but wasn't it automatically refreshed
while holding hands because it's so good
wow
why losing your strength you were
automatically replenishing it at the
same time
uh our livestream uh we'll be we'll be
kiara and i will disappear for just a
moment oh my god
this is your
[Music]
you have full house
chat when i want to ask the winner she's
looking at the chat now
are your backs changing are you still
betting on the same people huh do you
regret your life choices
[Music]
you should be more confident against her
you need
we're just rotating it quickly yeah
ah them happening can you give the taco
duchess who were missing you so much a
little hard pose
thank you that's your face it's supposed
to be hot maybe a smaller one with this
like this yeah with it
[Music]
yeah it works all right so the next stop
if you if you guys are curious i'll turn
the music down just a little bit now
that we're in between matches
next up is uh gonna be inna versus cali
and gooda will join us shortly in the
commentator stands
[Applause]
hold on one second discussing very
private serious matters
okay we're back
so actually i wanted to say something
about cali because yesterday
surprise surprise we went together to an
arcade
had a lot of fun and i
was looking at
it was actually booked youtube again
the
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah so we want to borrow the other
one the one that kelly was using
[Music]
all right oh i love the challenge you
want to help me with the zipper
oh
just kidding
with the
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
there's too much
actually that one doesn't matter uh it
doesn't matter
[Music]
all right
give me a flight
[Music]
i think i got it i don't know what to do
with these yes uh all that's missing one
second it looks correct oh my matrix
heads nina is patting my head again
then
[Music]
next is
is
[Music]
okay
don't be afraid
[Music]
i don't know wait how do you move it
again
put the finger on it
[Applause]
it's fine
we should be in criss-cross okay almost
completely
[Music]
move as little as possible but i can't
help it
all right
and there's
[Music]
is
mom i love you and then
[Music]
okay this looks i mean i think actually
i'll just make cali a little bit bigger
now
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
yeah that's good yeah it looks good so
yeah
[Music]
oh
that's okay
we gotta get ready
[Music]
a little bit okay we'll fix it fine just
floating away whoa
okay wait stop moving
[Music]
hold it
all right all right all right all right
okay
ready are you bouncing somebody
all right
okay i'm ready
okay
and it looks good that looks good enough
good enough yeah there we go okay
okay we're ready ready
okay
you're gonna give us a three two one go
mm-hmm yeah
yeah you do
it the death we battle did i spy
wow
it again wait i feel like that might
have been unfair
[Music]
it takes a lot of time to get this stuff
off so
yeah
[Music]
the rematch because cali
okay all right we're ready okay sort of
wait
please english this time
your journey was very beautiful all
righty you love me
okay
[Music]
that's
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay yeah i guess maybe i should go
against callie
[Applause]
um
[Music]
[Applause]
she's peeling her skin off
[Music]
oh
free from the rainbow
[Music]
oh yeah i need to give you guys a
clapping
i
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
i should be a literature writer for free
[Applause]
[Music]
it's like skin
all right the live tv is gonna get hit
for a second so i can bring in up on the
screen and callie's dies or should i
don't worry
no no
it's a little it's a little yeah
[Music]
he's playing
this is the chaos
so kelly would you say that inna was a
very difficult opponent yeah yeah i can
feel the fighting experience yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
all right
[Music]
isn't like
crazy
now you can
sorry guys uh i'm just trying to
multitask
we're back though
at least some of us are back gonna join
separately
oh yeah sorry
it's okay i want the boy to uh yeah
all right boss you should be in
maybe
i'm sorry
[Music]
come
is
[Music]
all right
this one red is me blue is cali i know
it's a little reversed and then would
you you're just gonna show it and line
it up again hopefully is good
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
legs
all right no moving anymore
[Music]
[Laughter]
you look good um you just have to line
us up rotate
i believe in you guys
down right click right
left click
right click it's yeah you just keep
dragging
drag
should i do it
okay i've used this before plenty of
times sometimes
[Music]
really cool yeah it's like it's super
wide oh is it just white
can we re is it
we hide the source
oh no that's fine it doesn't show
anything how do you read
[Music]
teamwork baby
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
all right we're still adjusting but
we're almost there yeah you guys gotta
count down in english
nice all right
okay everything's beautiful round number
three we have collide with maureen the
previous winner versus the one who also
a lot of people are betting on
stop
you might have to adjust some things as
we're going just so yeah yeah okay okay
three
two
one go
she really wants to win i've seen it in
the video
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh
[Applause]
[Laughter]
well i just went against cali
[Music]
and then i'm going to try to okay all
right
[Music]
is
that was impressive
you guys they were both holding pretty i
mean
um
celebrities
because i don't have to move right now
uh wait that one is uh
wait uh that's blue blue uh
oh man oh there you go there's that one
oh we don't get a falling apart oh hi
you can move me down a little bit
as much as i know i wish you could see
one
oh what was it should we do a i think we
should do it
you can hide it for now okay you should
do the caramel dancing from your loading
screen okay
[Music]
[Applause]
three
[Music]
i think there's just something wrong
with the soup oh
you wanna try again let's try this yeah
one more time
three two one
uh
check your arm
oh
wait
yeah yeah oh no you are here what now
look at my leg oh this is this oh
my bad look i forgot this is wow
oh
what
that's how i was like
[Music]
yeah you guys gotta i guess technically
a little preview of the karaoke there
oh girl what are you doing this is a dpi
it's insane okay okay
does use a really high
skin smells like because she's a gamer
a
see chad told you yeah no stinky glasses
yeah girl actually smells nice
okay well i just assumed that with the
whole stinky hoodie thing that we were
going with here
i'm not the only one all right you know
that it's not just me okay
listen
hold on
[Music]
i'm dancing on the table
all right the next the future winner
[Music]
under the table she's got it
okay that works
i'm gonna sit down though so it's gonna
go i'm
[Music]
[Applause]
we're all sharing skin bags oh no
sleeping bag
is what you mean
you got it thank you thank you
is a sword yeah
yes
yes i am a sword but um one might think
i'm uh i'm a shield fighter because i
you have my shield in my
head uh-huh kiara is so cool yeah ame is
really really strong
but she's really strong yeah your face
was really impressive was the same when
i was playing air hockey
no no air hockey you looked you didn't
look like you were suffering you just
looked very passionate
i guess we get really into air hockey
it's like even though i lost it still is
a lot of fun because i i just like
sometimes i just play against myself
yeah that's cool
i actually also before caleb
i played against alan air hockey and i
was so bad i was screaming constantly
and i was obviously won
[Laughter]
[Music]
i think it's kind of the first time
facial
expressions rotate
[Music]
no i'm happy i'm happy to be here hello
everybody does this work and well then
they're adjusting i think um
it's fine cool just you have to look
that way now okay you have to look this
thing out that's right
okay i got a um
with my right hand though i'm i think
your arm's a little broken oh um
it's a little smasher
[Music]
all right
yeah dance for them while we do the
robot
[Music]
all right
jazz
yeah like that like that
yeah you'll be fine i did weekend watson
hi weekender
yeah yeah for sure
[Music]
[Laughter]
they can see under your skirt
[Music]
stuff like this
very well prepared
nerfed me did you pop it out oh pop off
no no pop it
oh yeah i'll put uh-huh
yes
okay looking for santa's respectfully
looking
okay let's see hold on give it a second
pop it oh she's
[Music]
put your elbow on there okay all right
oh yeah it is although i'm looking
confident i'll let you use the other
hand
um yeah yeah you think you can win when
are you yeah
[Music]
i'll try
okay ladies and gentlemen it's the match
you've all been waiting for wait
[Music]
ready
three
two
[Applause]
[Laughter]
because watson isn't holding the table
when we went against each other neither
of us held on to the table
okay it's a sheer it's just
she's still using two be confident okay
okay you don't need to use my body
weight okay which is practically there
anyway you don't need
my what oh my gosh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's get away from the corner of the
table just in case okay
really they're about to do like
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
she's flying like a bird
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh
okay okay i'm gonna hide you both you
guys can rest for a bit okay
[Music]
i need to give you um an interview
like i don't know again so i can look at
this one
i think if you put it um you can put on
the table like right here
all right so uh so let me see
how are you feeling about your uh
i was about to say win but then i forgot
the evening i'm waiting i'm winning
because i
got to touch uh
the genius behind all of this
i shook her hand now i'm only missing an
autograph
i mean no doubt no definitely um that's
great what are you looking forward to
most in your challenge against gura
because you know that she's gonna bring
that shark
power sharks have a lot of muscles i
think
[Music]
i tell them why you had to open a pack
of brushes
[Laughter]
it's not like that it's because you know
actually the way she tried to open it
like rip it open it didn't work for me
either i had to open it differently
so but um
i don't know is there
what it is it is what it is
i
i'm not sure if i can win against scuda
she is she's a predator
so
yeah yeah
yeah effects predator yeah
i've learned that that is a thing
oh um
what do you want to say to your fans
right now to my fans yes
how's freddy ki wawa looking
it's been a while she's as cute as ever
yeah it's a nice light in here very
flattering lightning
npc for the beautiful bathroom yeah
thank you very nice i should be in
[Laughter]
all right here's what the gamers say
cute you are pretty looking amazing just
as expected
so cute spicy i just move over here 3d
kiara
true chiaros and those legs oh thank you
cute love you tensha i love you too
all of the commentators are back on the
screen
yes
my
girls a little bigger
does it taste like cotton candy yeah you
know wow
oh my gosh you've infected me with the
water
once that we played that yesterday in
the arcade
[Music]
yeah we like coached each other and like
cheered for each other and every time we
played we got better scores
actually by the end of the day when we
didn't have many credits left amen was
trying i would i would like to think she
was trying to get uh some plushies from
the
crane game for
[Music]
yeah unfortunately we we wasted a lot of
no
no just the thought that's what counts
the fault is what counted
yeah kingdom
yeah you shouldn't do it which is why
you shouldn't play stackers i used to
play staffer all the time when i was
young and i had um
they had a stacker game and so i went to
the stacker and then i stacked the
blocks and it got to the ticket point
and i said nah i'm gonna keep going and
then i kept going and then i couldn't
get to the major prize and so i was like
oh okay never mind that and so then i
played again and i got to the ticket
part and i said yes give me the tickets
and they didn't give me tickets
it was broken yeah we looked and it was
broke
and i'm like well maybe i could have
looked there first oh also we played a
mario kart uh it was uh ina me oh man
actually i in the second round you
played twice in the second round i won
against you
yeah
i think ina got first place in the first
round with all of us yeah and then it
was only us two
yeah it's pretty different
it's very different yeah they have
different items and yeah it's nice with
like the actual wheel like the feedback
on the wheels so nice
i think now i deserve my driver's
license
i just saw that
um i was driving very safely
okay come here
hold on
get in the pit
get into that
unless you're scared
don't be scared
she just shakes her head
like there's not enough room to throw
over if there was like um
like a mountain or something like that
and you're like in a field yeah maybe i
could like you know twirl her around and
throw her over the mountain but not not
today
that may disappoint
is there a different one i don't think
so i think i can throw her in a
different oh yes the eat the chocolate
it's a little is the other one no does
it matter it doesn't matter
[Music]
it's time ladies let's go
i guess so yeah yeah go line it up i
have to sneeze
[Music]
the pressure
there we
[Music]
are you ready to see the shark and the
chicken face off against chicken
[Music]
yes chicken i said chicken
what about goldfish
after the chicken then the shark is the
old fish
oh i don't know oh yeah
that's cute
all right all right
are you ready competitors
no yeah oh about our videos
can we just do rock paper scissors
i'm ready we already did rock paper
scissors how about how
yeah but i guess you're going back
can you really pull your hand all the
way back like that
[Music]
can we make a poll or is that just too
much
oh yeah who do you guys think
[Applause]
i don't know well kiara was pretty
strong when i went against two hands
that was so that was two hands
all right all right
we're ready
ready three
two
one
eight
[Music]
now you're in your element will she win
or will there be defeat
[Music]
we are
oh
[Applause]
[Laughter]
depending on the hand which means i will
massage one shoulder you will massage
your shoulders
oh yeah i forgot about that yeah who's
the winner oh don't we have a win again
i think we have a pretty uh unclear
we all get to wait
i guess we all massage i don't know
what's going on
i'm already ready to massage callie oh
yeah but actually both of you guys are
ready to massage and can't help yeah
can you like put her in the middle yeah
[Music]
i don't know yeah
okay
[Music]
quality massage thanks ladies appreciate
me oh wow you're good
wow
actually it's good yeah
oh let's put over there
oh it's warm
okay you made it warm
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god i love these ladies i feel
wonderful
my shoulders are so hard they're like
rocks i didn't see my goodness
no
yeah yeah
stop
you're not gonna get no tickles i won't
react i won't give you the reaction you
want
yeah i've got lots of them every time i
go to a massage they kind of seem to
ignore the neck most of the time
[Music]
this morning next yeah
thank you oh my god you feel so nice
holy [\h__\h]
god now all the wrestling was worth it
wasn't it
it feels so nice
[Music]
i'll get stronger until the next time
wrestling message
he'll look good
how do you know how to find them i can
feel the heat as you like
hit the knot
i want it to be on
what really is
oh my god
or something
my zeus
[Music]
yeah that's okay don't push yourself you
guys you guys
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you so much you guys you did a
great job
and in about 20 plus delay minutes yeah
on cali's channel you have the karaoke
[Music]
and i'm gonna make them cocktails and
mocktails yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah i have a movable image that you can
put into obviously
yeah
so i believe that there's gonna be life
by 30 minutes we said so we can uh we
can uh set everything up probably yeah
yeah yeah look forward to it
yeah thank you for watching
[Music]
yeah i mean you guys might have already
followed it but i just want to say it
officially um so
like one of the reasons we got together
uh was because
at this place we were recording
something very special
and it has kind of been uh more or less
like my part has been completed i'm done
recording and it will be
finally a 3d birthday live concert on my
channel on the 6th of july which is the
national fried chicken day remember it
yes yeah i've practiced so hard i'm dead
so hard and everywhere all everybody
involved also has been working so hard
on it i'm gonna set up this amazing
amazing environment uh to record it in
and it was a lot of work yeah
so we really want you guys to see it
because it's literally something we put
together with you know these members so
i hope you guys are gonna be there to
look at how
incredibly
talented we are oh all together what is
this oh
[Music]
birthday i don't know the time yet but
uh keep an eye open uh i'm i i worked
really hard for it too um
[Music]
[Laughter]
you