[Music]
[
Applause] [Applause]
[Music]
[
Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [
Music] [Applause]
]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause
] [Music] [
Applause] [
Music]
[Applause] [
[Applause]
[Music] It
came suddenly.
Of course. A
countdown.
[Laughter]
Please.
[Music]
Or
Thank you for the chat. Like
this, Ok Google.
[Music]
I also write in my usual voice. People say that. Really,
really, when I get excited, it's like a really
loud machine gun talk. It's true, it's
true. It's not loud, it ...  So I
can't get it on the microphone.
That's why I'm positive.
[Music] I'll
try my best to mix in a little bit of Japanese English.
After all, I'm the representative of Passion English, so I'll do it.
Seniors, introduce yourself in English. That
's it. [Music]  [
Music] There's
not much English in it.
Well,
I'm Little Devil. [Music] I'm Takanashi.
[Music]
This has happened twice. Second time.
Time meeting full time.
[Music]
TNT YouTube
okay. It's going round and round.
But Fish YouTube
Go for it, go for it, it's like it's coming and going,
like Yakiniku
[Music] At
that time, my senior
really liked my hands, I think that was really impressive, they were really smooth, but  I wonder if so. My
hands have been really bad lately. They
're so smooth
and soft to the touch. I'm
going for the smooth technique. I
hear it's cute, but I'm wearing gloves now so you can't see them. You're right, my
gloves are really beautiful. I can see a little bit.
Turn on the BGM.
[Laughter]
[Music]
BGM Pichian
Hey
[Music] Let's ask a
question
first.
Okay, okay,
so we can get to know each other better. I
asked for questions. It seems like you're
not really involved. It was a
bit awkward. There are still some.
How long will it last?  Up until now,
until the time we had yakiniku, we
hadn't really talked at all
[Music]
so I felt a distance between us
but then we met and
he was incredibly friendly so I think he was the same  It
was hard.
Yakiniku.
Now, I
like it. I'm sorry. Please comment.
Okay. So, I
have a question. I
came in a little bit in English, but I tried to translate it into Japanese. [
Music] I
love Disney. Oh, right. Disney.
[Music] I
don't hate it. I'm
jealous.  I got it
[laughter]
[music] My
favorite
Disney movie is
difficult, isn't it
Rapunzel Rapunzel
I also liked Rapunzel
Carr Remember Me is not here It
was I
don't know
What is that different BGM stopped why
loop  No, it
looped, it
looped,
Disney, yeah,
Remember Me, and then each of them, look, look, look, Chrome, I don't know, new, glad I saw it, I didn't notice this, this is
interesting,
but
[Music] The one where we
go to a world where everyone has disappeared
[Music] I see, I
see
Disney song
Wow,
Disney song,
E-mon,
what do you like the most? I
like it in general.
[Music]
Disney, if you go to DisneySea, your
favorite attraction is
Traction
Japan,
where are you going first?
Beauty and the Beast  The
Beauty and Baseball Museum
is just a normal place to just look around. I have
n't been there yet.
[Music]
Disney
Sea is not like that. It doesn't come out. Ah, it
doesn't come out. I've probably never ridden the characters.
Prime Minister  The Soaring Soaring
was a vehicle that was created about 3 or 4 years ago, but it seems to have become popular recently.
[Music]
[
Music] It's not like you
go up in the air or anything, you just
watch videos.
[Music]
It's like traveling around different worlds.  I
didn't know that
it didn't fall or anything. Yes, it
's quite interesting. I
want you to ride it. The one I like the most right now is
not a jet coaster. I'm not good with roller coasters.  I
like broadcasting, but recently I
like watching it more than riding the ride.
[Music] I
'm scared, my heart will fall, but it's okay.
Land and C are
dreamlands, so my heart won't fall.
Japanese Japanese sounds better now.  It's really a
dream country so I
can say that
OkOk
thank you
That's a good question
Thank you somuch
Ah, what should I do? I
just saw a story about a senior trying to learn Korean, but I
can't speak it at all. I'll be around next week.  I'm planning to
have private lessons one-on-one every week for about four months, so I'm going to learn Korean, so how many of
your words can you
speak? I'm sorry, I speak four languages. I'm
originally from Germany,
so I was able to do it normally at that school, so I can
speak Japanese.  I'm
self-studying and I
'm thinking of trying to learn Korean next. German is
difficult, people
say it's difficult.
[Music] I
missed you. How
long are you staying? Come
on. I'm leaving now.
How big is it?
It's about this big just for the pose.  If it
had a tail, it would be nice if it was a little
longer, so cute
[music]
Because any cat can become a munchkin, so if you
talk to WhatCATISS [music], it's like this, naru, naru, naru
[music], it
doesn't talk, it talks, it's quite a monologue  It's really bad. I've been
saying this for a long time.
[Music]
[Music] I
had allergies, but I do
n't think they're that strong. I used to have a really bad cough, but it seems to have gone away. I
don't have one now.
Maybe it's not related to allergies.
Maybe it was something else. If
I were to become allergic to cats, I wouldn't be able to live anymore. It's
okay, it's impossible.
There are allergy shots and stuff.
So if you really love cats, you can
get an injection and just put up with it.  I live with a cat. I
see. So why did you want to learn Korean? Because you already have
three languages. I
like Korean music. I
like K-POP girl groups. The
girls are
cute, aren't they? They're really
cute, and they're good at dancing.  They're
really good at it, and
K-POP dance is really
fast. Korea is really cutting edge. Actually, my
single that I released today is
in the K-POP genre. The
clothes are like that.  It reacted to two colors, white, like,
this is cute.
[Music]
Scary scary scary scary scary scary
Yeah, that and also, well, I
just like Korean TV shows and food and stuff, so well,
well, well, well, and  It's a little
similar to Japanese because it has a lot of external parts. I
think it's a little easy to remember, but the pronunciation is
not that difficult.
Yes, even though it's written as G, it's
pronounced as K.  There are many things and it's a little hard to
understand for me.
There are many things, so I'll just go through them. I
have a lot of Korean friends,
so I have a lot of Korean
friends in Japan. I
have a lot of friends who are online and play games, and they're all Korean.  I
only learned simple game reports, like "Let's
go right and left" or "Right and left is not me,
orange orange,
extension"
or "Let's go" or "Casual Chakacha"
[Music]
Eye Eye Eye [Music]
Music
[Music]
[Music] I
met a friend  We're friends and rivals, you
know?
[Music] The
battle of APEX is
still to come.
[Laughter] I've
listened to it, so I'll sing one song.
OK, I'm not singing at all, so that's bad, but it's
okay. Um, let's see.  Let's
start with Stardust Stone. OK, I
did it properly.
[Laughter]
Thank you.
[Music]
Thank you for your hard work. But this, you can
see it. Yes, it's
not small.
Wait, this, make this 100% bigger.
This triangle, this.  OK
[Music]
Then I'll scroll twice
[Music] I
made two of those so it's okay
Hard mode Hard mode
OK Master Dust Song I'm singing it for the first time in a while so I
don't remember either It's been a long time since I last sang it The
old Chasing somethings
Thank you  I don't remember the part of the person I don't remember at all
Yeeeeeeeyyy
Please give me a lesson
[Music] I can see your
smile, the same as always
[Music]
That's the screen that
lights up with my own teachings It's
not a polite face, I'm so
cowardly that morning sickness
will be the same someday  I want
you to accept the truth, everything
In this accelerating world,
we're running away, the
snow has come
If this is our destiny, I
'll fight, I'll find myself
[Music] I'll
raise my voice
[Music]
To myself, as much as I can  Just by looking at my feet,
I know with all my might
Can I touch you?
What will I do with you? I call out to you as I feel, and
accelerate We live in a world where we
won't stop walking towards my house
[Music]
[Music] I'll
stand up
and fight, I'll aim for it, so I'm
amazing
inside
[Music]
It will turn into strength, it's
difficult, it's okay, there's no problem, it
's not like that, it's my own guidepost
[Music]
I'll keep it in my heart, living in this accelerating world
Here comes the
voice of those who
want to compare, close by If this is my destiny, I
'll fight, I'll find it, the
reason I am who I am I always
want to be myself I
don't have wings to shine in the present If I'm going to give it away, it's
too loud, the
volume's not right I always stand at this volume
No, no, no,
this is a bit
rough, so I'm
actually
streaming it because I'm scared, so I'm sorry
[Music] It's
tiny, it's
not super tiny
[Music] I
feel like it's true, huh, the
streaming isn't like that
at all, both are completely different,
amazing  It's completely different, that's better.
Ok,
it's super small, I want to hear my voice clearly.
[Music]
isHEREOFF
Karaoke collaboration, it's been a while since I did it, about a year
and a half or two years ago, at the house of porridge and money.
But I
was laughing the whole time. It's
okay to be too silly.
By the way, I'll add some background music again.
This one feels just right.
[Music] It's a
song that was in there, right? It's a
strong song with Flare-senpai and Senpai. I
really like it.
Pale
[Music]
Senpai Kanata Senpai
Which do you prefer, cool songs or cute songs?
If
I had to choose, it would be both. I want to sing both, but which one do I want to sing?
Lately, I
like cool songs. I like to listen to cute songs, but I
also like singing cool songs.  I
like both. That's
true.
In the past, I only listened to cute songs. I
like idol songs by Hello! Project. Of course, my
seniors
only listen to cool songs.
[Music]
Japanese rock or foreign rock. Japan,
yeah,
foreign countries  English is difficult, but you should listen to foreign rock too
.
Yes, it's cool.
Lesson 2 is
Whatmusic. I
actually want to go here.
[Music]
Just the name.
[Music] A
famous rock
group. It's
totally different. I don't know it. Then I do
n't know it.
Someone Queen Queen Squeeze A
famous really old person Yeah yeah If you
listen to ACDC songs you'll know
[Music] I'm
in a hurry I'm fine I'm fine It's a live
stream
Um, yes, I
changed this again so there was, but that
Korean hot dog
What  Korean hotdogs are like those stretchy cheese hotdogs,
but they're not just like that, they have potatoes
and stuff on them and they have a
sweet taste, it's kind of hard to eat, they're
like the Korean style ones
[music] they're
not the ones with the sticks like this
There's a bar, but it's potato potato
[Music] I'll
post it
Hotteok Cheese Hotteok
Lie
[Music]
That's the
best skin I like Korean
Where did you eat it in Korea Have you been there?
Pervert I
went there last year alone
Translation and transmission are,
Amelia Watchon's mother, who is one of the first generation members of my family,
lived in Korea.
[Music]
So we became friends and she showed me around. She
showed me around every day with Navi Sensei.  And then there's the
amusement park in Seoul and stuff.
[Music]
Korea itself. I've
never been to Japan, but it's a
scary place.
[Music]
Lotte World was fun. You
can go even when it's raining, so it's
kind of indoors.  That's right, it's great, it's amazing, it's really
good. OkOk
let's
[Music]
How
did you get so good at singing? You're not good at singing,
and the
way you produce your voice doesn't sound like that.  [
Music]
So I said, thank you so much, that's why I
started to like you.
Wait,
YES
[Laughs] For
a
long time, but there was some kind of trigger.
[Music]
When I first heard Hello! Project's music, I thought
I wanted to become an idol too.
Austria  I lived in
and I
was trying hard to learn Japanese.
When you find something you like, you
want to learn it. I
know, I know.
Ah, what do
you like about Netflix? Netflix [laughs] Fashion set, when I hear about Netflix, I get that feeling.
Please turn it
on. I talk a lot. I
love Netflix.
[Music]
Right, at the end, there was something
like a high school party,
dancing. The guy was dancing with a straight face. It
was kind of a buzz.
Who do you like?
Of course, that guy.  That's
not a wolf girl, that cheerful pitiful one.
That girl
is cute. That's surprising, because I like cool songs,
so I thought I'd like cool ones. I
like the character, so that girl has always been
kind.
Who is that
wolf? She's a little kind.
[Music]
[  [Laughs]
[Music] The
shows I like
have a similar theme.
All of my favorite dramas.
[Music] We have the
same experiences.
But
Fantasy Dog can
use magic. You
like live shows, right?
[Music]
Netflix
X
I haven't seen it, but it's pretty interesting.
[Music] I
like fantasy stuff too. I do
n't have it, so maybe I haven't seen it. Do
you know Game of France?
What is it?
[Music]
If it's Japan, then yes, Japan.  So where can you
watch it? That's right. You
can watch it on U-Next. Check it out. And then,
try buying it on Blu-ray.
There are 88 seasons. It's
long.
Really long. The episodes are
about an hour long.  It's the same as the Netflix drama,
but the final chapter is terrible. It's not popular
in Japan. I think I said I liked it. It's
just that it's not being promoted.
But
Yabe suggested that we should never call our juniors seniors. We should always call our juniors seniors. Especially Koyori-chan, she's
very professional and senior-like. She's very
reliable.
[Laughter]
[Music]
No, I don't.
[Music] I
also have Netflix. I
guess I
won't watch Amazon Prime anymore. I think
Netflix's original dramas are
too interesting. I don't watch Amazon Prime anymore.
That's kind of weird.
[Music]
Heatstroke-like daily life.
Everyday
[Music]
I love it
[Laughter] It
's more like Mash.
It's just that the Stones' final episode,
everyone was so angry, so it's
like a gossip show.
Well, I haven't seen it, but a lot of my
friends  I liked it.
It was like a woman's journey in society. Basically, a woman in society
has a mother who has raised her daughter alone. The
two of them are amazing and
get along like friends.  That bitterness is really
interesting, and then from there, the
girl goes
from the important part of Tinature to the part where she goes through
all sorts of everyday things that you
don't see in fantasy.
OK, I've
seen it before, it's not that long, about 3 hours, but it's
long.  I fell asleep a long time ago.
[Music] I
watched it at home for three hours and it stopped. Well, I'm sure.
[Music] It's a
legendary movie. But even though it's legendary, they say it's interesting
. The Lord of the Rings is really interesting, you
know?  Well, well,
he's going to die. Well, it's more interesting to
die. I said I like that kind of thing. [Music] I want this guy to die before I get emotional.
Before I think, "Oh, that's nice." I
think that's
what the game is doing.  I'm
killing off the people I like one after another
Not quite, not quite
[Music] You
're chatting away but you're not singing That's
true
Which one are you going to sing Umm, is
this a live performance? Well, I'll
ask you to do this one
But here...
[Music]
This one isn't color coded either. There are
people who are.
If you search on the internet, you'll find it.
Which one do you do? The
one with the pink hair, the
pink Kirby, Sheryl, right? OK, Towa,
Senpai in
[Music]
I,
too, use the romaji to write
the colors.
[Music] There
was Japanese
[Music]
Then if it's something like that, just
tap it. I'm OK. What do you do when you sing together? It's the
same thing, double
tap.
[Laughter] You
don't notice the touchhapping.
[Music] It's
okay, let's just do it.
Finished, let's go! It's
strange, but it's
okay,
on the contrary, it's okay
[Music] If you sneeze in the middle of the world, it's inevitable that it will become cloudy somewhere [Music] The
door lock should not be left unlocked
[Music]
Strange things are
strong when we talk to each other
[Music]  I
want to survive, but I can't live anymore.
Now, guided by the constellations, I
found the moon. I want to remain. I'm
left behind in the end. I'm
caught
by my large body, so I
don't get sleepy.
[Music]
OkOk, I
said it at a high volume.
[Music]
Heading east.
Deep in my bones, a
ray of life still lives If I
lead it out, I'll meet you in the
countryside, where I want to live, I'll wither away in the sparkle
Until I show you my true body, I
won't sleep
[Music]
A life that has been granted  But now I want
to go, I want to end up in a warm, nice place, next to you, in a hotel room. I want to
show you my true self. I want to hold
you in my arms. [Music] I want to light my breath. I love you. I want to wake up.
He's
going to go alone. He loves you.
[  Music] I
still want to live, I love you,
I
won't get sleepy until I try
[Music]
Hey,
something's right, thank you so much
[Music]
I can't stand it, I'm the
type to cut it off at karaoke
[Music] It's
not that, but I get it, it's
like that when it's streamed  The
intervals between broadcasts are scary because they're long,
5 minutes long, this song is 5 minutes long
[music], it's just a
good feeling, isn't it? People are
writing things like that,
do
n't be so serious about what you really think, no no no  The
contrast is good.
[Music]
I know it's not allowed, I
know the not allowed button.
[Music]
Good ones are not allowed.
Borderline, there must have been
a few good ones to sing. I
think this is it.
Have you ever used it?
[Music] Maybe
this is
something you can't do.  No, this is not it, but this should be OK. I
feel like it was beautiful.
That one is more popular. The
song is good, but this is a song for the five of them. I
really like it. It's cool. Even though they're young, they
have a great voice. It
's OK.  [
Music]
[Music]
[
Music]
[Music]
OK, I'll try my best with my feelings.
Wasn't there something like rap?
I can do it, it's okay. If I
don't sing, I
forget.
[Music] It's a
Bloom song.  I
don't like any of the songs on the album.
This is
okay.
[Music]
It's
Japanese. By the way, Towa's life is
important. It must have been really hard. Thank you. Thank you. [
Music] [
Laughter]
[Music]
If it's too loud, please tell me I'll adjust it halfway through.
Right?
[Music]
Let's clap our hands.
Ours.
[Music] I'll draw you
closer. I'll
catch up with you. I'll show you how to get back.
[Music]
Hey, I'll
connect you with sparkle. Because I want to keep looking at you.  So
raise your hands
[Music]
Thank you for your support
[
Music] We'll create our future [Music]
[Music] So let's go
together
to the other side
[Applause] We'll
come and shake up this warm world
[Music]
[Applause  ]
[Applause]
It's been a while, everyone's getting excited and clapping, it's amazing, everyone, it's crazy, you know, an hour went by so quickly [Music] Let's talk a little more, and leave an impression there for about 10 minutes, until our lives run out, OK, when we're gone  I love life,
so I'll extend the encore. My
senior, yeah, I love dancing, I
love dancing, I love dancing,
how can I get it, the sound that I can get back is, by the way, I'm
really stiff,
so I can't move at home either.
[Music]
When I learn to dance, I do it myself.  Do you learn by watching videos
? Or do you learn from a teacher? The
teacher first makes a video and sends it to you. So you try to
imitate it a little,
but it's faster to have the teacher teach you the finer details.
That's true, but Chiara is
basically overseas, so she
currently has five original songs, and the choreography for
each one is
not from a Japanese teacher, but
from an American teacher.
Since I can't meet them, I always
remember everything from videos. It takes a lot of time alone at home, and it's
not that hard.
I'm forcing it into my head, but I can't keep concentrating. When
there's a movement I can't do, I
don't stop there.  So sometimes there's a rhythm that you're not good at,
like, "I can't fit this rhythm in," and at those times, a teacher can be a great
help. I came to Japan and
made my 3D debut, and I
did some dance lessons with the Miffy members.  But it was good, as expected, there was a
teacher there, it was
good, wasn't it? It's helpful to have a teacher, it's
helpful, but there are many things, but also,
when I dance in that video, I
can do it at my own pace, so I
think that's true.
So today, I'm going to do it for just 10 minutes. I
'm sure I can remember up to this point,
but I think that's great. I
want to dance with you. I
want to
practice. It's really fun to practice.
Because you were my guest.
[Music] I'm going to practice my
body a little bit.
I want to fix that stiffness too, that everyday
isolation.
[Music] I
know,isolation.
Sticking your chest out or, for example, tucking it inwards.
[Music] That's
amazing, that's amazing, it's
dangerous though.
[Music]
I'm also stiff, so I'm
not good at that either.  I wonder
if that will get better if I do that stretching. Bending is hard. My
body is so stiff
that I can't bend. I
really
want to do it.
When I had a teacher,
how long did it take to learn dance? It usually took about 3 hours.
That's right.
[Music]  ]
But it actually takes, well, three hours, not three hours to
finish, but three hours to just go over this
three-minute song, and
then practice it at home for hours.
That's right, everyone is so great, so great, so
cheerful.  Oh, oh, oh, oh, I
want to ask one more thing.
[Music]
The name is interesting. What is
this? It's not just a 'Waifu'.
Twice. Oh, I
see. I was curious about it. Toua-senpai is making it.
How did you
get interested in it?
What was the trigger? And  How did you
get better? I'm not good at it at all.
When I first went out, I
wondered if there were any experiences overseas.
For example,
milking cows, picking flowers,
riding horses, and other experiences like that.  I
liked it, but
when I went out, I happened to have the opportunity to try making a herbarium. I had some free time,
so I
thought I'd try it to kill time, and it
turned out to be pretty easy. Just put the flowers in and add the oil, and it was done, but it was stylish.  I
was making something like that right now, but someday when I read Towa-senpai, I'll
definitely ask this question, so please say the same thing again. I'll definitely ask this question again,
so please take care of me.
Hello, hello, and something
similar. Do you know the terrarium?
What is "Plarail"? I think terrariums are
probably
focused on cuteness, but I wonder
what it's like. I
know this one. Ame-chan
makes a lot of them as a hobby. I know.
This one is really stylish.  It's nice, isn't it? I
just love watching this video. This is
stylish, isn't it? I really like it. Actually, Ame-chan
made something for that art festival.
Everyone should go and see it.
Yes, I made something. I made a herbarium.
[Music]
[Music] I've
posted it on Twitter, but
what is it for?
[Music] I
made a doll of
this live English. I put up a picture of everyone in it. I'm lying
about the live broadcast. I want to
see it. I want to see it. People will think I'm weird.  It's
cute, isn't it?
But I think it took a long time.
[Laughs] I was in a
difficult position, so I left it for a month.
Then I made it. It's
cute. I brought it back to Japan.
Our seniors,
us girls.
[Music]
Like  People say that what To-senpai does is girly. I
like beautiful things. I
like beautiful things.
This, this, this.
[Music] It's
cute, it's a present. You can
give it to anyone. The
Hololive logo is rainbow-colored.  Right?
This is kind of sad, so it's a bonus, right?
[Music] I'll
sing one more song and then it's over. I'm
singing three songs,
Stardust Song,
Lion and Brook. I got it.
[Music] I'm
not going to go all out.
[Music]
Or
OK,
what should I do? Then I'll give you the OK from my senior.
[Music]
And I
don't even say "batchiri" or "batchigoo" in English. I have
n't been looking at you all this time, so I'll
have to guess what I'm thinking.
You wait,
princess. A
trap in a speech bubble.  There's
no way I could understand that I
won't be fooled by sweet words I
can see right
through you It's simple, is
n't it? I
can't win over a man who plays tricks on me
[Music]
Next stage,
what should I do with those eyes?  So dazzling,
like a Cinderella
show, showing off your desires, it makes my
stomach churn
You're already done, I won't satisfy you
until the next, next, next
Ok
[Music]
Google
[Music] The
more you expose your desires to catch a cold, the more the
world drifts away  You,
you,
everyone, everyone is on stage
[Music] The
reason we're here is that the stores and the trump cards are in the hands of the city, each
with their own head and heart, I
made a mistake, it must be
deep,
you're being manipulated as you wish, is
n't it simple, the game of
negotiation
By turning everyone into [music], I
was able to understand the form of love
[music]
You laughing at the end, and the
two children accelerating are my
favorite stage
[music]
[laughter]
Song 2  People's voices
harmonize beautifully.
Seriously, let's sing together. I think it matches because our voices are so different.
When this guy's voice is different, he often
drowns it out, but he drowns it out. That's why he says his
voice is deep, because it's
low and
deep.  It's amazing!
When I sing with someone with a gentler voice, Tora's voice is too loud so I
always have to turn it down.
But I feel like the bass can hear Towa-senpai's voice. It
's well balanced. For songs that everyone sings together, it's pretty well balanced.  So it's a
combination
[Music]
[Music] The
white hair accessory and the black
hair accessory are real
[Laughter]
Beautiful and cute, aren't they? Thank you for the flowers.
And then, senpai, that really,
really, really good request, I
was in a hurry.  But in the end, it was
only decided last night.
Thank you, that's interesting.
I don't play APEX or FPS games,
so I don't think we've been able to do any collaborations like that. I
think the reason for this is that we don't have very similar hobbies.  I have Netflix
so I'll
send you another message
next time, so please trust me. It's
hard to confirm if you've watched it properly so let's watch it.
Thank you.
[Music]
[Music] The
popular soap season has been decided.  Let's talk again later. I'd
like to watch it together.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
[Music]