oh
honey night is fall
[Music]
it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
dancing
alry so emotion
[Music]
feel it R me
there feel it like BR me
[Music]
oh honey
feel it R BR me
[Music]
intoxicating DJ keep
playing dancing
[Music]
me
feel it R through me
[Music]
K
KY kick the ball kitty
key kick yeah kick to kick those
balls am all right dressed up
again of course I did I had to hello
everybody everybody sorry I'm a little
bit tired because I didn't get much
sleep and then I took a little nap and
the nap
was um you know when you wish you would
have had more time to nap but surely it
was
plenty so that's that although I had
nightmares and they were literally about
streaming uh and coming too late to the
stream and some other weird [\h__\h] so what
the [\h__\h]
man and having the wrong format in my
stream
and having to stop pause the stream and
hoping that that doesn't like me
changing the format hoping that it
doesn't affect you know the fact that
it's a short stream that that actually
works and then I don't have to put on a
new
reservation OBS nightmares yeah now uh
first of all I need I got to do a
starting tweet I forgot starting now
second of all I have a sandwich so I'll
be eating in the beginning
yeah
okay second thir of all
uh I was not able to prepare like a live
stream that like that's not like like
actual real TV but not not what I had
before like um like the Stream So to say
so I'll still be a little little bit
behind but I think honestly it's good if
you guys are that far ahead because um
every time you said there's a goal it
makes me look very closely at what's
going
down and I like analyzing that I like to
be actually there are you watching saos
TV I would or do you think ORF maybe is
a little bit
ahead let's see where can I watch
in wait it's not on their website huh
[Music]
yeah I'm watching internet channel here
H just just generally if you're not
watching on TV you're going to have a
little bit of a delay like 30 seconds or
so
yeah BBC in UK is broadcasting it live
well but that's still going to have like
a delay
right
uh let's see H okay I found the I found
the I think did I find
it no what is
this thef stream is there not way
here is that
it wait has has one right not on
o what's what was the other one what was
the other one there was two right
okay I'll just go back to saos
TV I'll just go back to SOS TV s
s Austrian
greeting okay so we're going to watch
Netherlands versus
Austria and I've heard that even if we
don't win we are still going to be
qualified
uh just on the lower end but that's fine
as long as we
qualify but I don't know man who knows
we we can maybe pull off um a tie or so
we got to do we got to do a poll again
okay who will
win
Netherlands
Austria or
Tai or should we do z0
Choice nil
nil that's a tie too but that's a
different kind of tie in my
opinion
okay okay the poll is up I I will not
have it running as long this time I
[Music]
think and let me put up the names oh
oops see that's what was the
here magnetic
um
Austria
Netherlands
hey you know in Japanese they say orand
oranda like I think for Holland and in
German we say Holland I think right or
no neand wait no in
German no yeah we say we say yeah we say
Holland or
neand I don't know what I would say
what's more common not sure
so in Japanese they say oranda which is
more towards Holland and in English you
say
Netherlands interesting this oh Holland
is part of Netherlands well that is
interesting that they call a whole
country you Holland
orando
lowlands Netherland it's not very low
because it's above Austria more
northly okay wait wait wait I'm I'm kind
of like my brain is like
BL we have two more minutes to the start
I don't have the stream open
yet it's right in front of me though
don't worry this time I'll I'll turn on
the timer at the right time for sure
okay yes okay I have it on but let me
wait what what is this wait that's not
okay going to get ads
probably yeah ads let's go
ads countown
that's my
ads
countown
sick pretty
sick
count okay I'm so excited I'm so excited
I I what will I say what will I
[Music]
say I want to
be optimistic and say Austria we
win judging by how they did last time
they're not bad
really um but I'm going to say they
won't win but I'll be crying if they do
I I probably will be crying I've been
watching like football clips and it's
been very emotional okay it's been very
emotional times for
me and yeah I did not Leed Austrian Anam
[\h__\h] I
forgot uh are they playing it yet I
still have ads what I think the ads up
for everybody right everybody who's
watching this let me just get the lyrics
for the
[Music]
F
lyrics
okay oh oh they're making the flag
with small Flags
cute I Believe In You Austria even
though I'm betting against you I don't
even know man I don't
know Neverland is strong I
know I'm behind what ah wait it's not it
what do you mean it started did I miss
the
anthem it's it didn't start yet but they
look like they're about to start they're
very much in position I missed the Anam
I can't it can't be proofed that I
didn't do my
homework what do you mean by five
minutes nah five 4 3 2
1 and oh go okay that's now it started
for Me Oh you mean five minutes ago was
the him oh my God you scar
me okay let's [\h__\h] go come on come on
let me eat my sandwich though
[Music]
they're singing
already maybe they they can sing the
hymn for me one more
time you guys can maybe stop your
broadcast for a few seconds to catch up
with me
maybe if it works
kick off now you behind me that's
incredible that's
incredible wait did we wear white last
time too I I don't think we wore
white but this is uh nice because it's
easy to
differentiate yeah we were red right I
guess they have different sets because
they also want to be easier to
differentiate between the orange if they
were red it was would be
hard
M
hold okay so
far Austria seems
motivated the host says the atmosphere
is like
oh oh I mean they went for it obviously
not a goal cuz you guys would have told
me yeah but they went for it already um
now he was saying it feels like we're
playing at home because the
Berlin Stadium feels like it the people
there probably lot of austrians
there it very much feels like we're
playing at
home they're in Berlin
second try and a go so fast there not a
repeat
right okay okay and they're
aggressive de
motivated Neverland seems pretty passive
a just doesn't need to lose High
okay like a 5 zero would probably [\h__\h]
us
up does Netherlands have a a famous
player that we should be scared
of a couple many
[Music]
but I
think vanik
vanik wait how do you how do you say
van how do you say
uh Neverland people how do I say
it van Van
Dyke
really I was going to say um I think
from the last match I can tell that at
least Austria
isn't like they don't have only one good
player they're balanced you know when I
was venting about you can't just build a
whole team
off
of one player being good and everybody
else being
incompetent I would say that applies to
Austria that everybody's pretty
competent cuz we had goals from
different people last time too
okay
okay good job
sabita okay they went aggressive again
so far I don't remember any anytime
Netherlands trying to go for a goal
against Austria
look for who I don't want to see I'm not
looking at that I'm not looking at that
I only saw there was a goal oh my God oh
my God wait I'm going to cry for was no
left I'm not looking at that I only saw
that was a
goal you guys are too close to austri
side go back to Dev inside don't don't
be so you [\h__\h] don't be so
close okay okay okay we're going back to
the left come on come on come on come on
oh the captain the captain got the ball
oh eight whoever your name is she
guy wait yeah wasn't that an orange man
wasn't that an orange man who did that
he wanted to block it but we were going
for that we were going to get that ball
in we were going to get that ball in
either
way going to
cry what
[Applause]
[Music]
what the
[\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h]
bro see I'm telling you Austria is
definitely not a boring team to play
against
look at the Walk of Shame from the Malin
guy the Walk of Shame when
you when you self
gold oh
[\h__\h] oh man sorry
I'm oh my God it's only been seven
minutes I I I need to save my
energy oh Shame
Shame oh my God [\h__\h] my
voice it's let's go it's let's
[Music]
go don't underestimate Neverland well so
far you haven't been showing me anything
that I should be
overestimating this will will age
[Laughter]
badly
nice [\h__\h]
nice Austria first of group oh yeah I
see it France Netherlands Poland are
below us get underneath me
M it seems like in the past matches that
I wasn't
watching there were a lot of extended
time goals that changed everything
so you know I know it's early but I
didn't think we would get a goal so
early Austria with them early
goals Austria probably found out that I
was doing a watchong last
time and they were like oh okay we need
to entertain this girl in her audience
we're not going to play a boring match
not like the
others so they know that I'm watching
holy [\h__\h] audience is not happy that
we're on that side right
now but safe safe
safe
sheesh yeah milin scored for for
Austria maybe Malin should join the
Austrian
team
mhm austri has anime girl buff exactly
it's so funny to see the goal on the
little menu that pops up with the name
of the person who scored but it's on
Austrian side even though the name is a
Neverland
player that is uh
embarrassing there's like yeah like 30
40 seconds delay depending on where
you're watching because I'm watching in
a live stream like an internet stream
stream official one though and those are
quite behind
sorry I'm sorry K but the dut shell
Prevail um show me then show me where is
the
Prevail where is it
I can't see it from
here is it the 40 seconds delay is that
the reason why I'm not seeing
it but I can tell nevland after that one
goal is already playing even more
defensive and aggressive they want their
own goal now I can tell
they're
mad mhm they're coming for
blood isn't that a [\h__\h] ton of austrians
in the audience well I guess I see more
orange on the right side of the stadium
but still even in those orange seats
there's a lot of red and
white hey f f
f let me
see he just like absolutely crashed into
him like a car accident
Man funny how he lost his
a moment
ago oh
yeah the white shirts and the red shirts
are for Austria and the orange ones in
the audience are obviously for
me
obviously
oh oh oh they're running to Austria
go no
way no nothing one person in the chat
wrote one
one but obviously nothing
happened wow w w wow you can't get us
you can't get us we're protected at all
costs let's go go what what what
go now you're just lying why the [\h__\h]
you
lying
go no shut
up why you always lying why the [\h__\h] you
lying shut
up oh
bro we lost the
ball why' you lose it why' you lose it
Austria that's a goal hell of a goal
shut up fre zero how can it be fre zero
how can it be
41 how what's happening in those 40
seconds
delay what is happening
wo Austria
[Music]
fast oh we're already in half time [\h__\h]
my sandwich and me were already almost
finished oh he huged the ball because he
fell on it
no
no he protected it like a
baby Babble Buble
if Netherlands
wins PR lost the ball it it was it had
too much power too much energy to stop
it that close to the corner yeah yeah
yeah I was going to say if Netherlands
wins I will eat strop Raffin tomorrow
which is more like a reward and me
breaking my diet than a punishment
but thanks for the membership
welcome yeah if orange wins then I'm
also kind of winning exactly thank you
no I never tried dipping my straw
buffle I have one good
friend not good friend okay that's
exaggerating I have one friend or good
acquaintance in the
Netherlands
um she's really sweet and I'm meeting
her I'm meeting her uh this
weekend she probably doesn't give a [\h__\h]
about football
so we're probably not going to discuss
[Music]
that nowah she's not a YouTuber no no
go AA go take the ball and go come
on press kicked the
ball out of
that Neverland con
invention of ball
kicking to give it back to Austria white
ball white shirts it belongs
together yo Netherlands just doesn't
have it so far
they just don't have it so far I mean
come on if you're watching this
objectively Austria most of the time is
doing the the
balling and the cooking and the
attempts I mean come
on it's been 20 minutes 20 minutes is a
lot it can be a lot I mean it can also
be a lot to Netherlands to score some
goals you know of course
but I'm just making an observation
that we are playing well very
well very
well the Austrian fans are excited about
every ball
touch they like to touch those balls
okay ausan fans kind of mean every time
the orange touches the ball they're like
whistling
loudly stop that come on let's be nice
hey what's the
wrangling
fondik
fik he was wrangling my man my Sab it's
a man who gets the goals you know he's
the goal manager
he's the goal manager don't touch
him I don't know what his name how do
you pronounce it I don't know I think
the yeah good Lo yeah good Lo very
original chant
Austria I think the commentator said fun
fondik
actually good L yes good L yes good L
yes get
L I actually can hear and tell what that
chant means wow you guys a lot of you
guys don't even understand this German
magical mystical
language you wouldn't know fine then
keep your secrets you may think but
who oh white keeps the ball white keeps
the ball we're still we're still on it
we're still on it
I lost it kind of what was what happened
you tripped or
what okay slow motion ah yeah he slipped
on the ball and then oh
well his friend took over but
still
no let's go good no they're saying let
yet gets
lose here we
go yeah okay okay okay run for it run
for It Go Get It Go Get the ball no
don't give it to orang no take it back
take it back take it back it's my ball
it's my ball I personally signed it oh
they're pissed oh oh nevet starting to
get
pissed hey is France playing against
Poland right now uh
simultaneously I don't like it when they
do things
simultaneously
bro France Poland still
z0
interesting
interesting who plays after this match
it's it's to prevent cheating
what what where H how whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa
whoa
Mar m m what do you mean so close I just
saw that now you're reacting kind of
late or is there something else close
coming up because Malin just first he
shoots an a self goal and then he misses
the goal
so
closely oh my God truly a kfp oh I
almost feel bad for him
like Malin wants to redeem himself but
it's just not working out best austram
player the
secret now it's not so bad yet that you
could say that if he does never funny
thing like that then it's time to say oh
sabita I think I started to recognize
sabita wait was that sabit though no
maybe not I need to remember these faces
so I can call it
out last time we had mulad uniform this
time I don't know if you just saw that
but uh that guy in the white uniform
um that's a reference to our
Kaiser
Kaiser did you see
him not king
kaisa um Emperor
Emperor I mean we don't have one now but
you know he's uh referencing I think
France Yosef France the emperor I think
the last Last Emperor we had I guess
probably [\h__\h] the
legion [\h__\h] the legion I'm not
supporting the legion oh the wrangling
the wrangling of the men's it's guys
love between two guys am I right guys am
I right wow wow wow ouch ouch ouch
ouch Vima took that man down with him he
was like if I die I die with you my
friend my Netherlands friend oh M was
that Malin again trying to get the ball
in
[Music]
again that look like Malin again yeah it
was milin is
aggressive he's not accepting the self
goal he's honestly trying to redeem
himself holy
[\h__\h] the baldman the
baldman it's always the
baldman kicks ball in heads ball
out
bro that's Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat Pat patat
Pat
Pat Marin is molding oh Marin has the
ball again Marin Marin might be the most
dominant player in Netherlands team
right now just out of sheer desperation
[Music]
bro ball goes
out F fin oh my [\h__\h] god that would
be amazing if we are going to the next I
I think it's pretty
certain thanks for the membership
renewal and not renewal first membership
yeah welcome actually I want to say
everybody who's not subscribe Please
Subscribe because we are going to win EV
way
today o ball possession 51% not
even as much as I
thought we are about to reach
uh 1.53 today and we just reached 1.52
recently it's going fast right now I'm
so happy I'm so
[Music]
happy yeah it's actually going so fast
right now for the first time in forever
it's very very
unusual my growth currently is up by
160%
legit I proudly showed it to jenma I
showed her look jenma are you proud of
[Music]
me it's been like that for a few days
now so
G show kfp let's go towards that 2
million so that I can get a 3D
outfit I I saw the light at the end of
the
tunnel
whoa subscribe for more football watch
alongs yeah but I'm hoping it I wonder
is the next Austria match going to be
while I'm
away is it going to be right away like
this weekend or so do we already know
like when are the next matches might it
be this week cuz
I I don't no I don't want to miss
it I don't want to miss
it this week is really rough but I I
hope I can make it next week if it's
next week then okay
okay worst case I'll do a Twitter space
if it's sometime this week at a time
that I can watch but I just can't
stream cuz I'm uh only streaming
tomorrow then I'm gone for a few
days thanks for the membership gift 10
press let's go throw it towards
White oh
stop two attempts okay no goal but good
tries good tries I like the aggression
but sabit just threw that ball so
harshly on that
shoulder ouch ouch ouch it's like a
attempt he made an attempt on
murder you might think maybe they have
some issues behind the scenes those
two half an hour guys so half an hour in
it's 1 nil oh a
Neverland you cocky
bastards I love you though Neverland
you're cool you're some cool people over
there if asusta finishes second finished
second what do you mean finished
second what does that mean second in the
group then it would be on Monday
okay will we know right away uh By the
time this ends will there be a plan when
the next Austria match
happens second place in group
mhm okay if France wins today austri
will be second ah okay and then we'll be
on Monday okay
cool you will nobody end okay nice nice
nice can make some
[Laughter]
plans damn I'm so busy on the weekend I
don't think I can focus on on soccer I
really hope it's next
week oh we're having a yellow for an
Austrian one oh oh oh oh yeah but it
happened the moment chat wrote it
but POS is discussing he's like talk to
my hand
oops wait what what
did what did he do porch didn't do [\h__\h]
what was that they barely
touched I don't get it they tou just
touched tippy
toes explain to me what was the problem
because of the studs well both studs
touched each other no
toe
story you can't raise your foot that
high oh they both did though didn't they
cuz they're their feet touched which
means they both play uh place it that
high another yellow
he wait for Posh again let's see let's
see oh
is
that let's see Man Down yellow
for
Austria
[Music]
okay
yeah that looks like it might hurt
M that that I will admit that was legit
yellow
cards but not saying that was on purpose
there's some things that are on purpose
obviously like some tackles but that
wasn't on
purpose no
steppies he he deserved that but he
didn't mean
it okay they couldn't get a goal in
again
yeah if it was on purpose I would have
been a red but it was obviously
not okay they're switching out
Netherlands dude that's not the one that
got stepped on
though
saavi kabi going in
Austria looking happy oh no wait that's
orange isn't it that would look orange
actually oh time is continuing right
even during the
drinkies it do be hot yeah
always hydrate we should hydrate too
hydration
check that's so sweet that they get a
little drinky
break M nice nice very
considerate okay they're coming back
bomla this orange is so bright it's like
literally my kind of orange a
very strong fiery vibrant darker kind of
bright orange
close oh something close
happening dark bright orange yeah that's
what I
mean that's what I
mean aric come on stop wrangling the
orange
man oh oh oh oh oh a whistle oh oh oh
oh careful you ran over the goalie
man he [\h__\h] runs over the
goalie I like that
replay whoa actually okay his own his
own um
teammate kind of fell right over his
head almost landed on it so that was a
bit
worse no what what what what what what
are we getting a really close
one oh [\h__\h] okay but it's not happening
there's no goal no your goal
okay
Sab that was
close
sa I'm out of it I
he he took down arnovich the goalie took
down arnovich with his
leg boo boo boo boo
boo he almost touched his balls
bro that was so close I think we can do
it we can get up to uh two Z yeah we'll
bring it
home we'll bring it
[Music]
home you know I wouldn't call it a foul
but it just um
hey hook what the [\h__\h] you should be
cheering for me now you had an excuse to
not be cheering for me when it was
Poland you don't have an excuse now
that grass looks
unreal is it real it looks too unreal
unreal tournament like Vima had a
chance that's okay wima next
time it's not real grass
a g come
on K come on you were that was
partly okay but you you fell a little
bit
dramatically it's real grass but never
maintained that's what I thought like no
way in such an expensive match that they
would play on fake
grass surely it's like better to play on
real
grass ball is on the
outside fake grass cause injuries oh
yeah I'm sure it like kind of scratches
more it's probably not as soft h
H when you fall on it that's not
good oh oh oh something is that Malin is
that
m m on the
ball what do you mean 2 one
we're still on on one
nil it was
close oh oh oh you're talking about this
one oh you oh you're talking about this
attempt oh I think you were talking
about that second one that I just saw
not the one
before oh
oh well never
it's sweaty spaghetti they're dropping
their spaghetti it was offside
regardless oh yeah because uh for sure I
yeah I
understand Neverland lands folding hard
it's not good to fold spaghetti it will
break apart don't do it without I will
be angry
what are they
singing oh they already stopped so you
probably don't know what I'm talking
about no wait they're still
singing yeah that OD kind of sounds like
like a chant laa
[Music]
laa there singing Seven Nation Army no
way that didn't sound like that Seven
Nation Army is more
recognizable and I kind of think
Austrian fans are too lame to sing
that laa don't we call it
[Music]
laa uh the
La wait what is this
word wa
yeaha
huh is that actually an Italian word for
wave or
so it does laa it does
oh Raa her name kind of means the wave
then if you pronounce it like with the L
instead of the
r
cute cute
[Music]
cute yeah I love how she pronounces her
name so
Italian that's really new because
everybody we have all kinds of names but
we pronounce them either English or
Japanese or so but her
name the way she pronounces it is so
Charming ra ra
P it's just automatic because of her
accent she's so cute
Ito what's Paul what's Paul in
Italian p
[Music]
b pal
mama what's plus two what's plus two ah
minutes I see it now yeah I just started
O Come on come
on we're almost done with the first half
and Austria is not losing so far I can't
believe
it I can't believe it we're so good who
would have
known yeah
[Music]
people will be so scared of
Austria
finally paying me some
respect come
on now good job good job
it's over oh we have break break started
they're chilling they're not even using
the full two
minutes oh no they're doing uh I thought
they were already leaving it
early they're just getting ready for a
shot no way what go
corner you guys are trolling me again
partially some of y'all
Austria is
stalling Austria is
stalling okay corner
kick oh
yeah
yeah hop Time Hop
time
y y y y y
sit down Neverland sit the [\h__\h] down and
watch from the cheap
seats yeah sit down take a break cry a
little bit and then cry again later
you're going to spent the whole night
crying like little CW babies while we're
going to be
celebrating oh my God I'm I'm like damn
I can't believe this I can't believe
this
[Applause]
we're actually winning we didn't even
have to like we're actually already
through but this is better it I
mean dep depending on how well we do it
decides who we play against I guess
maybe we don't want to do so well maybe
want to play against someone who's not
as
good tell me tell me what other Chan is
that we're going to play against some
someone
scary your placement in the group
matters okay I guess it adds
up like if we don't go into this with
that many points and then we don't do so
well in the next round there's a chance
we don't go into the next round right if
we do if we go in with more points
[Music]
Maybe if we win the group we play the
second of group F or if we play second
we play the second of Group G G of group
e k we will win I know I
know if it stays like this Austria plays
turkey
o Spain if you lose o what's better
what's better turkey or
Spain to play
against I don't know they're both good I
think we won 61 against turkey who's wi
Austria better against turkey turkey W
overly H is turkey also in the better
groups or are we getting is it like the
good ones are getting teamed up with the
worst placed ones or or the good ones
are getting placed with the good ones if
you know what I mean like the ones with
the higher
points Spain is the are good they're one
of the
favorites okay stay away stay away cuz
if we lose and we play against Spain to
me that means they pair up the the bad
ones and the good ones yeah oh [\h__\h] what
that's really how it
is that's mean that's so mean what is
that that is so mean
how does that go
usually can't be going so
[Music]
well yum yum I'm drinking
M yummy yummy M what was M again in in
English what is that
again M mango mango M it's not milk not
not really
whee yeah I'm drinking
[Music]
whee it's it kind of feels like I'm
drinking a milkshake I really like
drinking whe drinks
recently I've always liked it but right
now oh God the news are [\h__\h] uh
depressing they're playing news right
now instead of ads and they're
sad let's go
protein is it 15 minute break I guess
so pretty long I hope they can I I hope
they can regain their energy that they
had in the first half and show the same
energy in the second half
maybe with some switches of
players perhaps if need
be but I'm I'm scared the second half
could be the Redemption Arc for
Netherlands uh and Marin
specifically uh I don't think he wants
to go home with that on his
mind that we W because what happens with
Netherlands are even if they lose this
time are they still also proceeding
probably right they didn't play so badly
until now I guess yes
okay most likely I already qualified
okay well the both teams are practically
kind of
qualified is everybody just already
qualified who is there somebody who's
already out pretty much like Poland
probably
right Poland's out right po oh a a a a
wa is only Poland out so far Scotland
too okay a the Scots the
Scottish oh I I was um I Heard uh I I
like peek into the new member streams a
little bit and um I peaked
into uh elizab herbs stream and she
called collabs collab collabs cab
collabs Co collabs
was interesting
pronunciation I I just want to say she
doesn't seem too happy with the herb
nickname does she but uh I asked her
when we first got to know each other I
asked her can I call you herb it's
shorter and I think it's genius with the
first few letters and she said like yeah
you can call me anything so just putting
that out
there herb herb e r b e r b e RB e r b
BB
she's just about it yeah probably
probably probably pro pro pro
probabbly collab
probabbly now that's not how they would
say it probably Pro probab
probabbly
probably probabbly probabbly
probably Calli says you and CC sound
very Sim similar
Kelly Kelly I think what she's hearing
is similar
accents just because there is a similar
accent I don't think our voices sound
alike at
all at
all and even the accent I think hers is
stronger come on I don't think my accent
is that
strong her intonations and her accent is
more uh stronger than
me but yeah it's generally like probably
reminding of me when you hear it because
yeah we that's just how we speak uh
English some speak it with less accent
and some with more but you can
definitely hear like similarities that's
just how like when I I can tell apart
when certain countries speak English I'm
like oh that's that accent that's that
accent you can tell that apart like when
there's a French person speaking English
or when there's an Italian speak person
speaking English and so
on yeah that also has quite the accent
thanks for the membership
welcome yeah but that's fun having some
some interesting accents yeah now now I
cannot be the only one made fun of for
not being able to pronounce like TH or
something like
that make her try to get out of Sicilia
uh like try to make her uh say
FES I wonder cuz I used to say ties fake
ties save
lives I wonder what her intuition her
first response would
be from ties to eyes which one was
better huh t or
F fi F it's just f it just turned into F
maybe we should have stayed with
t maybe we should have never tried oh
yeah yeah find out if she says
iron iron iron I I say normally I say
iron iron
iron that that would be interesting uh
comparisons I think she does she says it
the same way I
do she already had a chance to say
iron she says like me does she does
she of course she does of course of
course she
does so now maybe you guys understand
me why I say it like
[Music]
that pizza making collab when actually
you you know after that after that
debate it wasn't much of a debate uh we
went on to like continuing our
discussion and in Discord because it was
going to get too heated right um but
immediately immediately it turned into a
t conversation of her uh inviting me to
a pizza date in
Japan and then we talked a little bit
about Italy and this and that and told
her about the places I've been to and we
talked about some stuff regarding
that I I I'm really happy we can talk
about these things like somebody who you
know can relate
to that kind of
[Music]
stuff so we we were chatting for quite a
while just European
[Music]
things must be happy to have more
Europeans well the thing is with Raa
she's European yeah but she's really far
away from me so it doesn't
really you know I can't like just like
hang out with her I can't just go on an
airplane for one hour and meet her so
not really what I
expected cuz that's that's what I was
generally going for when asking for
European members
[Music]
but it's okay still fun to have her
around
mhm oh we're back in uh the studio SL
field the commentators
are are talking but I'm not listening to
them well Austria currently has six
points we're at the top of the group on
the top of the world we're higher than
friends
Yahoo so far so good
but what do you mean what about CC orb I
know I know they're closer
yeah at least the time zones fit a bit
better but so far they've kind of been
streaming pretty late though I wonder if
it will stay like
that so
far so
far pretty late still I'm guessing they
still want to get some of the na viewers
to get to know them and maybe then
they'll start a bit earlier
H I don't
know yeah the they had to debut at like
5 a.m. or so uh
so and the the get to know each other
meeting that we had was also like 4 or 5
a I think 5 5 a.m. as
well so they've been kind of forced to
be up at a shitty time for their time
zones uh so maybe they still have to
adjust to
that yeah their sleep schedule
was bad just like mine that's rough why
did management do that because our main
audience is na so
debuts you would want to try going for
an in a prime time
right
okay they're they're showing a repeat of
the self goal but I I don't know I feel
like even if Malin wouldn't have inter
accepted I feel like we may have still
gotten the goal we were definitely on a
roll in that
moment oh I love how I love how the the
captain I guess I don't know his name
what's his name AR anovich he was like
spreading his arms like hey I'm I'm
right here just so you see are you sure
you're seeing this I'm right
here making extra sure that he's visible
to his teammate for a
pass isn't your main audence na because
not enough people streamed in new time
yeah oh oh they're showing a view of the
of like an outdoor live stream in
Austria how cute no for me I mean I
don't know my main audience is na but
that's not because I'm going for that uh
I'm glad that there's so many na people
that can watch me but I stream during
European uh prime time
so evening late afternoon evening to
early
night uh Austria time so whoever can
watch me can watch
me whoever can watch me can watch
me think we're going back in a moment
restarting in a
moment actually no never mind they're
still showing
repeats kick off it really
no no not yet right oh no okay wait it
looks like they might go for it in a
moment now they're walking in has there
been any
switches Dyke he called him F
Dyke
again let's [\h__\h] go Austria you can
do
it yooo
wow wow wow wow okay
start it just started for me now I
started at the moment it was
kicked wait what the hell immediately
lost the ball focus focus
everybody in Germany there's no free
live stream of the game what what
what oh wait I should have I should have
started like from 45 not from zero
[\h__\h] oh
well go no no no what to early no one1
[\h__\h] right
away what so
[Music]
ha no I didn't see it yet so it didn't
happen it didn't I didn't see it yet so
it didn't happen it didn't happen it
didn't happen it didn't happen what the
[\h__\h] wait which side is we're going to
the okay okay left side is Neverland now
okay okay okay no no the other way
around ah ah ah no
GB GP I can I could totally use your
name to make a you know like
a like an uh like a I could swear at you
right now with your name just change it
a little bit but I'm not going to do it
I'm not that
[Music]
childish in German at least in German I
can do
that that was so fast what the
[\h__\h] they're coming in strong in the
second half right way in the
beginning
wow that was a fast ball our goalie
almost had it though
almost I'm watching the slow motion he
almost had
it okay the commentators are saying no
chance but I will say he almost had
it does Austra need to win no we don't
need to win but I want to win
I want to play against uh
turkey the other choice doesn't seem so
nice you need to win or France to lose
all right cuz France is still playing
huh oh we fell down hard from first to
third in our group
eat St
bu it will be my
pleasure if orange wins that means
that's also a kiata win I have no way to
lose today
nice camera work
man well I am orange and I'm
white in many ways I'm white because
they wear white and I'm Austrian but I'm
white also because I'm
white and I'm orange because orange
image
color I'm white because I'm white and
I'm white because I'm
[Laughter]
white
understand go white girl
go go white men
go Memphis there's this D with the name
Memphis on the field and I just feel
like that's a really interesting name
sounds like
um a brand of
cigarettes it sounds like a cool name
but I'm too straight edged to support
that I've definitely seen that player
before elsewhere though seems
famous oh it's a it's a city too huh but
it sounds like a cigarette
brand Marin on the ball trying to redeem
himself and loses the
ball
Marin is this going to be a VA yeah
there will be a vaud
okay come on Austria come
[Music]
on come on get the ball get the ball
yeah yeah yeah
yeah bring it home Austria
Austrian aric has
been pushed
aside
apparently his
ankle hurts a little bit it's okay we
have the adrenaline let's fight through
it come on
arnovic we need to keep on
pressing think of the ranking you know
you don't want to play against
Spain you know you want to play against
turkey H
sabit really ran hard for that ball but
the goalie got
[Music]
it yeah we can bring it back we can
bring it
back either way we are so
in we are so in
guys I did not I did not ever think that
we would be even able to proceed into
the
next what's is it called
uh finale in English
is an eighth of a
finale uh what pre pre
pre is round of 16 is what you call
Playoff round of 16 what the [\h__\h] is
that quarterfinals let's call it Dad
that sounds
better round of
16 is it because there's 16
groups remaining no way that there's
[Music]
16 16 teams oh really it is going to be
16 teams
remaining that many
ah oh
really
oo
funik with the
header and another corner kick or is
this a repeat what the [\h__\h]
to oh another one
okay
finale oh I feel like certain things
like uh sometimes this only happens
sometimes
like for example in German when we're
like like oh for real then we
say and
sometimes sometimes I feel like I say
that in English too and also uh like
stuff like or I say something something
I think it's like that or so like or so
I think CeCe
might say it that way way
too cuz apparently that's not really
[Laughter]
[Music]
English or
so good
Lo yeah good lo oh wait somebody hurt no
Tommy H no the
goalie is there there's all they have a
replacement for the goalie R in case
something happens
but you probably want to go with your
main goalie usually how did he hurt
himself I didn't really see
it bread
allergy strop waffin
energy allergy allergy energy did I say
energy I mean allergy
wait Pence Pence is ours right our
goalie was that our goalie that's our
goalie yeah okay okay okay I thought I'm
still thinking that's the neverland
side France got a
penalty for what what did they do they
getting penalty kick that's cool that's
always
exatic but that's good for them right if
they get the
kick isn't that kind of good cuz I feel
like those chances to get a goal are
pretty
high yeah hey so isn't it more like a
penalty for
their uh enemy
bad for Austria
[\h__\h] why why bad for me what I want
France to lose it's okay I'm in anyway
but
yeah France scored oh damn wait is it
what's the is it one zero there now
okay oh wait is France playing against
Poland
right I forgot what was the
opponent was it po oh they got no chance
there's no way that Poland is winning
that think about it for a
[Laughter]
moment I know right
oh Oh you mean if France wins this we're
we're not going to be first of our group
so we won't get to play to Turkey oh
well maybe there's someone else who's a
good good
option what was
that what was that the referee did not
care hi chunky wonky you want to watch
so uh
football uh watching replay of the
supposed foul I guess was that no that's
something
else goal what what go I'm not looking
I'm not looking I'm I'm scared I'm
scared oh I'm scared yeah it's probably
not not a good one not a good oh wait
it's going to the other side I'm not
looking at the chat chunky wonky chunky
wony comes and there's a goal can you
believe it wait wait wait Austra is
going Austra is going in no way no way
no way no way no way no way come on Sab
Sab
shoot the ball into the [\h__\h] goal
oh no way no [\h__\h] way no [\h__\h] way
no [\h__\h] way I was scared I thought it
was going to be Nevers
[Music]
oh that came in
hot good [\h__\h] job my man good oh I
think it's drinky p uh drinky drinky P
drinky
paw a real goal a real [\h__\h]
goal e what do you mean own goal
what oh it is it kind of
see slow motion wait who was it this
time not M right what's his name what's
that guy's name thanks for helping
out de de
or oh
there yeah doesn't matter I think it
would have gone in anyway I don't know
depends on the angle if that guy wasn't
there I wonder would it have gone
in the fre
the damn is that going to be counted
officially as a a a goal from from def
FR stop taking our goals Netherlands and
giving them to us we can do them on our
own you don't need to help us you don't
need to hold our hands
you don't need to assist us like that I
know orange is my color but I don't need
your
help now at least Malin is not so
embarrassed anymore maybe because he
knows he's not the only one who did
that today
yay yay
yay they're getting aggressive yeah
maybe there'll be more attacks on people
from now on desperation kicks in
oh Leo
CFI I think I saw bomb Gardner coming
in who played last time against Poland
and I think he got a goal that
time yeah BNA got one of the goals last
time he's in he's so
in let's take those trees down let's
chop them
up he's a tree
Gardener and
Lima the Lima is
minor Lima I think was in the Poland
match too wasn't he
switching with Wimmer
Wimmer Wimmer was not the winner
today
yum still
whimble man the audience is excited even
if nothing's
[Laughter]
happening oh they were switching someone
else
actually switched to wrong
person who the [\h__\h] do you want speak
clearly to me um I want this guy why are
you not listening I thought I told you
clearly and
loudly you're getting it wrong you
little [\h__\h] what do you mean I'm getting
it wrong I'm going to kick all your
players out if you say that
again a wait what
a I wonder if they're happy to be
switched out like ah finally I'm getting
a [\h__\h] break man I'm so
exhausted glit switch with qu
fi perfect lip breeding I know
hey do you think they want to play more
after an hour in playing in the
heat maybe they just you know want
to in such an important game obviously
they want to score goals and and get
the the fame and the
celebration but I think a part of them
is happy too that it's also not just the
exhaust but also the pressures off of
them from that moment I think mentally
that that's a big
relief like you're leaving at a point
where Austria is leading you're Le
you're leaving at a point where Austria
is leaving leaving [\h__\h] you're leaving
at a point when Austria is
leading so if that changes after you
leave then it's not your
fault you can do it K thanks
English oh another Switcheroo what who's
switching
Neverland oh yeah
Neverland
a Mickey
[Music]
fer I am the myth speaker
of yeah of English right wait
what uh they did put wait Schmid Schmid
they put Schmid down there was that uh
the Austrian player or was it the
Netherlands player I don't
know probably
Neverland the my speaker of
Ian the I don't know
Lima B
gner
Sab and so on
an EO
mukashi not here today
D that dude is
huge wait that dude when he was right
next to an Austrian guy he looked like
he's twice the size of width and height
of everybody
else he looks like he's he he could play
like quarterback in the American
Football
[\h__\h] Dutch people
huge is that van dy I didn't notice
until now that that dude's
huge orange person huge
huge damn why is he so huge what what
veggies did he eat when he was
small shees
he he's got
a Van
Dyke is huge I'm not going to say wrong
anymore he ate
horses I believe
it wait where is he what's his number I
want to see his size difference again
maybe it was my
imagination where is
he four
ah wait no wait that was 15 15 also
looks
big where is four turn your backs to me
come
on oh wait I think I found him I think I
found
him is he's massive
right
huge I is he the
captain is he
I wait 15 looks
big maybe it's not four maybe it's wa no
I didn't mean four guys I didn't mean
four four is Tiny 15 is
huge I mean
15 Van de van yeah he looks huge for is
Tiny he's a tiny man he's a short
King uh for is 195 it doesn't look like
it he must be cheating can't believe
it I they all is tall is it just all of
them 195 is actually
insane they don't look like 195
taller than
you that supposed to be a
roast if I was 195 I don't I I think
people would be terrified of
me as a lady oh people that's actually
unfortunately a size where it would
probably not be perceived as attractive
anymore by guys and more intimidating
and like man I'm I don't want look so
tiny next to her and so on it's just not
not good
anymore sadly I know there's there are
some women who
are that
tall but sadly the general perception is
not
good you love tall
girls oh you disagree you want to date a
195 mommy h
[Music]
hm good for you I'm glad that you feel
like you can climb that
tree Malin out oh did he get switched
out date a crony she's also not 195
though but honestly IRL a 195 person
probably will have legs like that V host
sounds like a Austrian German
[Music]
name jumping in in the middle of uh not
a corner cake what is this
what what do you call this kick free
kick
ah Freedom
Kick
USA
USA or stop the wrangling stop the
wrangling dou
who
whoa sorry the commentators just said
that we are leading two to one and that
just made me happy again
[Music]
K favorite Austria
player I mean I don't really care about
like a singular one but I guess sabita
has been standing
out of course the
man he's been uh leading a lot of
the in in into in what's the word
initiatives I thought of it my speaker
over
in h oh and the bald guy but is he here
today I don't think so I'm missing the
bald guy where's my
Baldi these people all have
hair the hair ratio is too high
T is h no not the tummy h
no
no man he was good he got one of the
goals excuse me I like bald men who can
kick balls with their heads in to a goal
okay that's a very specific kind of bald
man I almost almost oh he's
oh I like the
motivation yellow armpit guy
arnalich bro anovich why' you slap his
back like that though
no don't say that Chad shut up no no no
no no no no no no what's happen
no no no I'm I'm covering the chat with
my
hand who what what what what's
happening what's
[Music]
happening GOP not you
again I
uh
theight is it the night [\h__\h] yeah let's
[\h__\h]
go maybe
offside me did Memphis do
it are they check
denied okay I'm watching The Slow Mo not
slow motion just repeat right now okay
why why though I don't understand
uh still
checking Deni not yet denied
what I can't see the
issue it's a goal looks like a goal
doesn't look
offsite they're still checking they're
still checking
I don't want to know I don't want to
[Music]
know definitely a go looks like a go to
me I mean yeah the goal is there the
goal looks like a goal to me
too but please for the sake of
Austria oh
oh oh oh the oh did they
decide penalty for Poland oh it's
approved
[\h__\h] it's okay Austria can get another
one we'll just get another
one will one up you
oops one more one more
one more one more Australia shoot and
t
dinglish wait so they thought that maybe
he touched it with his
hand I don't even I honestly don't
really see where where yeah where that
would have
been happening he obviously kicked it
with uh his leg I agree with
that but I would have loved
to uh honestly at this point it might
stay 2 two it might stay like the
something the end also I forgot I never
ended the poll here let me end it now
26,000
votes
26,000 all these short uh
Zoomers who go through it vote and then
leave the stream
26,000 votes
Mama
Mia Poland missed oh man you had a
chance
Poland well they have nothing to lose so
whatever Austria needs to win to
advance no
no no
right we don't have we can do a a draw a
tie as far as I
know as far as I
know yeah we can advance third place
we just play against the best
team yeah they're wrong
right oh you mean
Poland are you talking Poland or what
whatever I I think I know what I
know go Poland
scored oh shees right after the the
failed penalty kick
wait go for wait go for Poland right go
for me or go who who is
going who's what where's go go no way no
wait wait wait I thought you were
talking about Poland wait
wait they catch up again sorry I can't
hide my [\h__\h]
[Music]
excitement sa you [\h__\h] goat
Chad you [\h__\h] goat Chad
what do you mean two
goals what do you
mean holy [\h__\h]
sabit I told you we're going to catch up
2 minutes later catching up bro oh
Poland too oh we're kind of
right now go goaling at the same
[Music]
time
bro wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my God I love to see austrians
happy what Australia what's with
Australia where the [\h__\h] is Australia
what do you mean they got a
goal Austria first place well you mean
uh uh in the loser group or in the
winner group I'm
confused s wants another one he wants
he's hungry he's
hungry what goal what do you mean goal
what do you mean goal what do you mean
go there's no [\h__\h] way there no
no
offside okay I my heart would burst
holy
[\h__\h] it's good that the chat is early I
would be too happy if there was another
goal I would be so happy and then I
would be so
disappointed
[\h__\h]
[Music]
she yeah he knows he knows immediately
after he shot that that it was
offside I saw it in this expression
but damn we're on fire we're on fire how
did we catch up and scale so
much damn that goalie did a fullon
split he was splitting like a stripper
hey
sheesh we're doing really
good it's my influence right
a Austria and
Fuego Amigos on
Fuego shees K buff I'm their angel their
um lucky
Angel so it was offside because uh one
of the like the defender there was no
orange
person closer to the goal right there
always has to be it doesn't always have
to be though right I've seen legitimate
goals where there was no defender or so
in front of him I think I think I've
seen
that only if you receive a pass oh
okay
okay hm
wait how much more do we have six
minutes and then
extension when he well
when when the when the austan received
the pass he was ahead of the Defenders
okay well I feel like that shouldn't be
a
rule I feel like what what's wrong with
that like I said that last time your
fault if you're not there we're not
going
to baby you I don't understand why
that's a
problem ah but it's it they showed the
graphic where they showed it when he was
further behind was it not the problem
where he was in the situation where he
kicked it it was a problem where where
he received
it I don't
know so close oh something close is
happening yeah that's the problem where
he receives
it yeah I mean what's he supposed to do
Let It Go oh oh oh Neverland got a close
one ah he's I feel bad for him he's
eating the grass out of
sadness you shouldn't eat the grass you
only touch the grass my
friend but it was really good damn I I
think it's really incredible skill to be
able to shoot headers so spe so
specifically into One Direction like I
don't think you can be super super super
super specific with the direction
right accurately precisely
yeah but obviously they practice a lot
so to a certain degree they can but
seems difficult very
difficult Come on
B I need a good angle he had a good
angle
too so I feel bad for him but I'm
relieved very
relieved guys we need 18 18 more
subscribers until 1. 5 free
18 18 just saying are there 18 people in
the chat who are not subscribed who want
to celebrate this beautiful day together
with
[Laughter]
me come
on not me yeah had sub count I don't
want to
no I I don't really like the looks of
that
thanks for the membership Yoshi and
pudding
Yoshi all attack us would just be
camping at the goalie on oh oh okay I
guess I understand
that if there was no offside there would
be campers
yeah I
suppose well Neverland has no reason to
be sad guys I said subscribers not
memberships I knew I I don't need the
members but thank
you thank you can you receive a
membership if you're not
subscribed no right you got to be
subscribed right
right fumbling that
kick you can happen to me once E I guess
when if there's no better options like a
subscribe person
face the
membership
nice did we do it let me let me
check y we did it actually that that was
like 200 subscribers I said 18 and you
gave me 200
1.53
baby I'm
winning oh my God we're just you don't
understand guys this is the first time
that I'm actually growing in like two
years it's it's actually uh like a dream
for
me I I'm I'm too happy okay I'm too
happy thank
you thank everybody let's watch more so
football football together the next
weeks you guys know like we were on 1.51
forever and then just recently we
reached 1.52 after like a year or
so six minutes added okay I'm scared I'm
scared six minutes Anything could happen
but at least we're in we're in
ah I always want to say so but I keep on
stopping
myself
okay I do want to I do want us to play
against
turkey because you guys said they're not
that
good the worst outcome of these six
minutes is a tie honestly they can't do
two goals so we shouldn't be scared if
you come first you will play turkey all
right let's [\h__\h] go but I don't
honestly I feel like even a team that
seems weak can be surprisingly strong
you know they can play better on some
days and worse on some days so I
wouldn't necessarily
say that it's a certain win or so but at
least I feel safer than playing against
a team like Spain right but never
underestimate like I underestimated
Austrian look where we at look where we
are
[Music]
at oh
man oh they they're making a switch
now in the last 5 minutes he just wanted
to be part of this
experience just have it on your
record are they buying
time but if if they buy too much time
they'll just add more time
no do you think they're stalling
oh
a Austria come
on no oh they they won't add
anymore they can just do it once okay
uhuh no no more at a time e wow
then that's certainly something I would
be pissed about as a Neverland fan oh
[\h__\h] sorry for wasting your time nland
I'm genuinely sorry about that but you
know you don't have to be as scared as
we
are I I'm scared of
Spain you're pretty good as a team you
don't have to be so terrified right
you're confident come on give us turkey
give us
turkey good job PS SC man SC
man it's a legit Strat yeah I'm sure it
happens a
lot when you really want to keep the
score the way it is at the end oh
someone are they acting injured now too
on
purpose is this also on
purpose but what what if what if they
just act injured for for 6
minutes they can't just let that stand
like that
[Laughter]
right no
way give him an Oscar hey as long as
he's not rolling around like
Neymar as long as he he's not flipping
times oh are they continuing even though
he's on the side they can't right I
don't think they
can oh I know oh I know I've been
watching a lot of football clips these
past days my recommendations
are uh very different from what it was a
week
ago oh man cord cord just stalling as
much as he
[Music]
can bro I feel bad there's no need to
stall that much Bros
it's okay no need to stall that
much what he got a yellow card because
his injury was treated on the field even
though he was supposed to be out of the
field could he not have swooped a little
bit to the
side then then that was on purpose
that was on purpose and if he could have
just been treated like 5 cm to the side
holy [\h__\h] but why did the doctors not
just push him like I mean are they not
allowed to like move him 5 cm oh my god
oh that's ridiculous that's ridiculous a
yellow for
stalling
Oh I thought he was like legit still
playing oh [\h__\h] that's funny that's so
oh they're team doctors so they're oh
they're in on it are they in on
it they're in on
it wow they're con artists these
football players are con
artists Oh I thought they were like um
neutral general doctors not just team
doctors but I
guess it's good to have your own doctors
cuz they know the players more Etc I
thought it was like a referee thing
referee neutral doctor's
neutral
a is is it over is it
over sorry
Nance sorry
Nance
ooh sliding hard on that cusa
oh man sorry Nevers I'm sorry I feel bad
they look
sad I'm
so
empathetic not empathetic I have empathy
is what I'm saying you know
right they didn't they didn't whistle
yet on my
side are the other the fans whistling
because they're like end the game
already
oh oh sabon took the ball away from Gull
so there can't be a last minute
goal it's still going hot over
here oh 30 seconds
over when is it
ending referee come on end the game end
the
game referee still w watching it go
around referee do you have a watch or do
I need to sponsor you a Rolex
huh keep the ball keep the ball keep the
ball keep the ball
[Music]
Austria
yeah [\h__\h]
[Music]
W oh fre titties fre the
[Applause]
titties we're leader we're lead of the
gr we're playing the worst one next
time if you want to win Austria just
always get get me to do the watch along
and it's a certain
win wow my stream is wearing behind mine
was also really far
behind yay yellow card for me why for
freeing the
titties excuse me it's [\h__\h] hot in
here I am from
Austria I am
indeed damn I really didn't think we
could win this because you guys were
hyping up Netherlands real hard and I'm
sure they're a great
team but you guys need to stop
underestimating Austria when are you
going to stop now right when are you
going to stop now now you've seen us win
two
times so
far it's time to stop underestimating
Austria I'm stopping too I I fully
believe in
it ah
damn I told you Austria was pretty good
lately yeah yeah yeah yeah I felt the
same way after Poland but I was like
okay they all say Neverland is that good
then they can't
possibly happen right a look at
Austria okay next next K I'm going to
sing the song
[Music]
I vaguely know
it did Austria play with France H I
don't think we did
yet I am from
Austria oh some of them switched into
turquoise shirts that's another one of
my
colors they know I'm
watching wow
I guess the the ones that didn't play
are in turquoise
shorts wait the goldie is wearing orange
oh look at them so cute t arm and
[Music]
arms a
sabita come on you late to the
party oh they're letting him in like
he's a car on the street we love
that oh sabit looks like he could play
in Lord of the Rings like he could be
playing
Aragon doesn't
he oh the second row of
austrians a what you
do Austria you're first in the group you
[\h__\h] did
[Music]
it Bros
bros
man giving me some teary eyes
man oh
oh we played against Neverland seven
times in the past 34 years and always
lost this is the first
time in 34 years that we won against
[Music]
never
whoa whoa w YouTuber buff anime
buff oh my
God I'm so happy for them for us
[Music]
I put this on the list of songs I want
to sing in Koka as well next time never
sang
this maybe we should do uh a football
songs K any song that would be played in
the
stadium I don't know the might not be
that much choice but Seven Nations Army
would be one of
them
a okay we had 49% ball possession five
attempts on the target total attempts
nine saves zero oh my God because they
don't need to be saved Corners two
offsides one
[Music]
team top five distances 11 kilomet from
cyad oh they're interviewing
sabita she's screaming into the
microphone
are you guys seeing an interview
too no
[Music]
yeah man of the match he got MVP sabita
cute
not on yes yeah I guess
so oh what's your
secret we switch through yeah especially
in the sixth last six last
minute whoa who won austri
Yo wait it's going to be Austra versus
Portugal no [\h__\h] that no way
no way no why would why
no we don't know yet okay when will we
know tomorrow I can't wait turkey or
chick uhhuh okay okay okay and do we
know do we at least know the day let me
mute them do we know the date at least
cuz if it's Monday then I have time if
it's Monday
Tuesday I already had something for
Tuesday I guess I can try cuz on Tuesday
I was going to do a longer stream I
guess we'll replace it cuz we got to
watch
this July 2nd damn
okay do we know the time is it 6: p.m.
again maybe maybe oh 900 p.m. oh okay
okay okay
h o I was going to do a long stream
originally
because uh I'll I'll I mean I'm not not
streaming the rest of that week I am
streaming but
after uh a few days will be a few days
of that week will be difficult too cuz
I'm traveling to Japan next
week this week I'm traveling next week
I'm traveling the week after that I'm
also somewhere I'm somewhere all the
time guys
I'm very very all over the
place maybe I'll do two short streams
then on Tuesday I don't know what the
other thing would be maybe a small
collab or so I don't
know I'll think about it because I I
would feel bad if it's only although I
could also use the time to finish
Polaroids and stuff cuz I didn't even
get to start on the Polaroids missed
worldwide yeah that's me
[Music]
ah time sure flies no but Tuesday is
good is there any other dates that I
could already
know oh in the same
week or is it just this one for
now where do you guys even get this
information yeah bad timing I know I'm
kind of on a roll right now I want to
grind
too it depends if I win that one okay so
if we don't win that one we're
completely
out if they win it would be the sixth
ooh
okay ah but the time that the things I
will be in Japan and the times where
these matches happen will be like early
morning like 4 5 6 a.m.
jst
oh I want to watch
no I want to watch no bueno no
bueno I can't stream at that time in the
studio but if it if it really comes to
that I'll try to find a way worst case
I'll do a Twitter space
but Suffering From Success
yeah uh yeah it depends if all the
matches are at 900 p.m. then it would
be 4 a.m. jst or so I
think I need to do it from Austria
yeah but I I don't know if I can stream
at 4 scream scream at 4:00 a.m. in the
night
damn they need the anime girl buff yeah
they're going to lose I can't abandon
them
[Music]
are my Japanese bro still
here you could scream into a
pillow the whole match the whole two
hours will be muffled screams
[Music]
didn't h on Camp at the studio I mean
it's not impossible like uh I've I've
I've seen others do that before too like
I think Bales or so uh like you can
enter the studio while it's still open
and then you can use it throughout the
night there's just no staff support but
yeah I could possibly do
that depending on how Tuesday goes I can
decide that yeah who's
bails but yeah that's that's interesting
CU that's my birthday weekend but uh
Saturday wait that oh but that wouldn't
that
be the seven that would be the seventh
[Music]
though I have a stream
planned no wait that would it it could
work it it could work it's just going to
be crazy because I have two streams
planned kind
of uh on the
seventh in
jst cuz
yeah I'm doing the Birthday Countdown
and Callin and I'm doing a k the
countdown is like during noon jst 7th
and the kok is like uh 7 p.m. jst I
think with merch announcement will be
there
too so I would have three
streams maybe I can I can still move the
the Birthday Countdown in cins
around uh to the previous day or so I
don't know everything will be decided on
Tuesday I
suppose
mhm wow the match is July 2nd at 1 hour
from this time yeah 900 P p.m.
this are are you this dedicated oh [\h__\h]
yeah I am if we get that far I have to
watch
it however far we get I'll be watching
these matches unless unless I'm on an
airplane that's the only thing that can
prevent
me if I'm on an airplane or if the match
is while I'm recording something so
that's already set in stone like 3D
recording stuff and then I can't I
really can't but thankfully that weekend
is my birthday weekend so I kept it open
for the birthday so I can do whatever
the hell I want I have the I actually
have the studio reserved already for the
whole day I Gemma to reserve the studio
for the whole day for me so I can use it
pretty
freely y y
[Music]
yooh as a duy I bow I bow thank you I
really didn't think I could do it but
thank you no not the 20 million no I'm
not using the 3D Studio I'm using the 2D
self streaming booth for
the birthday streams and
stuff for sixth and
sth
mhm it's my birthday I want to watch
football all my birthday streams
cancelled we watch football
[Music]
instead crazy can't believe that we
didn't only just get through and and
like win against Netherlands we didn't
just win against Netherlands we even
became first in our
group bro bro what
what what do you
[Music]
mean oh and I mean we have not just that
to celebrate I want to
celebrate one I'm free Free
[Music]
million
oh holy
[\h__\h] thank
you it's been going really fast these
days thanks for all the support thanks
for everybody who who's been joining kfp
these days it means a lot to me
yeah it's like it hasn't looked so good
in two years or
so oh thanks to the wers free the
wers no it's uh I think several factors
coming together but it's a good time
right now and one day support Day One
support thank you hopefully not just one
day day one day one is
good h
thanks for the membership gift clearly
it's the Austria
buff no it's just the fact that I'm
Austria not not this Austria football
match just me being Austria is the
buff I am Austria I am from
Austria are you going to watch Denmark
or are they starting after this I asked
and I didn't get an answer before but is
that what's playing in 50
minutes
H okay I want to but I was thinking of
this time just this time I'm ending it
like here cuz I have to prepare some
things I didn't get to today
yet
sadly sadly very very very sad actual
short stream holy macaroni I'm I'm
curious though what England and and uh
what was it sorry I already forgot
England and
who England and who England is me I've
heard I've heard Slovenia are they good
are any of them
good solid no mid we are solid you think
so England is good England's supposed to
be good England's good but it's not
playing
well a bad
manager
what what they should be managed by Ted
lasto and things would be different if
only that was a
reality Slovenia played well so far oh
you're following like everything
ah England has great players Dreadful
team play
WoW become the next head me I don't need
to be their manager to support them all
I need to do is do a watch
along and watch over them watch over
them win surely once again next Tuesday
against turkey
no turkey yeah right turkey was
Turkey some I thought it was turkey or
Czech it was Turkey right oh wait we
don't know yet we don't know yet right
turkey o okay okay okay I didn't forget
it was not sure yet
okay well either way I have a good
feeling against those I I don't know
those teams but my heart tells me it's
on it's so on thanks for the membership
gift not gift uh you entered yourself
thank you welcome
egg most likely
turkey
R Austria versus Raina
no
no oh it was a gift oh
oopsie oh thank
you PAB she so off over is so over who
do we cheer
for excuse me does it say chicken versus
Turkey no does it say Austria versus Pou
no
neither we're playing we're not
playing say turkey well we're not
playing against wa don't worry it's not
a
real yeah it's not an animal
one bunch of poultry versus
another no no whatever you want to call
me the Austrian players are not poultry
okay D thanks for the membership gift
D yeah we're not acting like chickens
either the way we've been playing on the
field dominating asserting our dominance
France a tury ah yeah cuz France has the
chicken on their chest the rooster yeah
there you could say it's pava Nashi
match
maybe the last 10 minutes the no not the
last 10 minutes the last six minutes
okay yeah they definitely stalled that
was
a bit of an embarrassing
display for yeah I think they really
wanted to be first of the group like
because first they do the switch and
then they do the injury on the field m m
Mama Mia how far can you go before I
lose my respect for you it's normal okay
I would be so
pissed then honestly there were those
other matches recently right where they
uh scored some goals in the extension
in that case the opposing team should
have totally
stalled faked some injuries and stuff
switched some people out all team does
it apparently they didn't do it
there do you know
your c s it's yeah yeah that's the thing
it actually seems to
be wait no not I think oh I don't know I
think I made mistake uh I don't know I
don't know I I'll ah [\h__\h] uh I'll have
to
check I have to
check
wait that's next week right that's next
week I can still change things uh should
be fine um
let me ask Gemma cuz I feel like I
already made a decision but I forgot
about it because it was confusing to me
as well 7th or sixth not
sure Italy scored in the seven minute
from the eight minutes overtime sheesh
they should have faked an injury on the
other side they should
have but no I I would prefer it doesn't
matter if it's a strat I would prefer
just like play it real don't do that
that's
lame that's kind of
lame that's why croaa didn't make it
apparently because they didn't do a
Switcheroo or Faked an
injury
damn but the injury you kind of need
something something to happen at least
some kind
of bouncing into each other needs to be
there in order to give it a starting
point w was stalling like the yeah maybe
maybe it has to do with my nationality
the way I like to stall and the
austrians and on the football field like
to
stall fball
[Music]
fball and fball them football
field that explains everything I know
[Music]
right fake it till you make it just like
right now I know I know I don't want to
go I want to run away from the things I
have to do but I I really
shouldn't oh what a FY but that's just
just a foosball
Fury but that's just a theory a foosball
Fury and uh a waa Fury and an Austria
Fury maybe from now on I'll just say it
in German because then I'm I'm not
hesitating to say soccer at least I
should just try my best to say it in
German I think you guys would like that
anyway
FB I think it's still recognizable it's
a very similar word anyway
fball
fball fball is
[Music]
fball fball no not football fball
fball fball the more I say it the cuter
it sounds fuzzy ball
fball
FB no FB with s with double s or the the
sharp
B I see ustra one we
did could you believe
it I can't believe it
either and I'm
sorry I'm sorry and I know uh
uh that all those self go people they
will go home and they'll take a shower
and they'll cry while they're in the
shower and they won't be able to tell
apart which ones their salty tears and
which ones the actual shower water they
won't
know it'll be all the
same yeah there's still still qualified
yeah
they helped us for a win and I said I
don't want your help stop helping us
Netherlands I know you love me maybe
they also know about this stream and
they were like oh waa is watching us
well she's cheering on Austria so maybe
we should help Austria because we love
Wawa
too Netherlands loves
understandable it's so respectable
Behavior they are or orange yeah maybe
that was a sign sorry I I noticed so
late you've been wearing orange all this
time and I know this now I've been
joking about it but I didn't believe
it I would if I was
them of course you would you're a
chicken
bucket Malin should be feeling
devastated
n let's let's stop dunking on maren I
feel bad
I'm H self goals are funny I don't think
we didn't have a single self goal when
we were playing against
Poland so even though there has been a
lot of self goals in this tournament so
far I didn't see one
so I didn't feel like it was a big thing
in these past matches I just didn't see
any
self goal against
France who you mean who po what Poland
against France you mean Austria wait
when when do oh is that that that's the
one match that I missed
right we played
France I forgot about
that mundock was cheering me on in uh me
and Austria on from a bar
Netherlands American guy walks into a
Netherlands bar to watch football cheers
on Austria because of an anime
girl I hope they were nice to you in
that bar I mean did you really
openly like that that takes some balls
to walk into a Nevin's bar support
Austria during all of this if you did
that and loudly cheered when Austria got
a
goal and besides
you is
this or more like
Boo that would be
funny it's like who the [\h__\h] are you why
are you here why are you not supporting
nland are you Austria Austrian and and
you'll be like no I'm American I'm like
and they're like what the [\h__\h] is wrong
with
you what connection do you have with
Austria is this the final score yes it
is we won it uh is over already it was a
good time Austria won every time like it
started with one nil for Austria and the
Netherlands caught up and then Austria
was like okay now we got to catch up and
the Netherlands caught up and then we
were like okay I'll throw in another one
if you really want it
yeah okay
uh yeah it seems like my birthday will
be moved to one day later pretty much
this this this year cu the merch is
already set to be uh yeah well the count
down will be
EST a
[Music]
PST six still but both streams will be
act I might I might still move the
countdown stream
maybe uh maybe not but the merch will be
evening time jst on the
7th
mhm will there be limited time uh I
think so yeah limited um signed yeah I
think so I think we had limited stuff
yeah I think we
had oh
I hope you will like the merch I'm like
kind of
organizing uh anniversary merch and
birthday merch at the same time so it's
kind of like all mixing up in my
mind what I'm creating u i kind of lose
sight of what I've been creating for
which event
uh yeah but I think yeah remember am I
remember thank you thank
you okay well I'll call it
uh a day tomorrow will be a longer
stream we'll be playing which spring R
for the first time in a while I I'll
give you some tangents during that too
don't worry I'll I'll provide you some
tangents thanks for the while watching
thank you for joining
me I'm so happy that we had a positive
outcome
dang damn
I can be so proud of Austria I can
proudly go to sleep today
[Music]
later y now the pressure is on yeah I
mean I think the next one we can still
win but the next next one will be
rough I
think might we might lose the next next
one
don't jinx it I jinxed it today too I
think but several times it's good we're
fine we're
fine yeah yeah yeah I'll watch all the
uh other Austria games I'm I'm streaming
all of them as far as I
can stay positive Austria all the way
right I got to believe got to be like
tanoshi Austria I can't doubt them do
all the football fans like always
believe that their team wins will win do
they always believe it no matter who how
strong the opponent is do they always
feel like oh I'm def our team's
definitely going to win no right are
they realistic okay okay they always
hope I thought I thought maybe they're
all pretty
delusional but okay it's good that
they're
pretty
realistic but they might get a little
bit delusional after these matches
seeing how well we've been
doing I always think my team will
lose I have mad cope but no we got a
hope and we got a
cope hoping coping
I will draw K an Austin Soca outfit
let's go thank
you which was it going to be the white
shirt or the the red outfit or the
turquoise
[Music]
one don't draw me in those orange shirts
I know orange is my color but that will
make me
Neverland you got to give me the right
color draw her was a bold player no no
no no no please no no please no God
please
[Music]
no yeah there's a to I saw the players
who were not on the field were playing
uh were wearing turquoise shirts they
were really pretty turquoise shirts with
white uh
pants looked
good m okay I'm obviously stalling
[\h__\h] I'm going to go thank you so much
for the support and thank you for
1.53 million we are running up that
hill with so much
motivation no I don't know I forgot what
did you say say
[Music]
baby and in German we
say byebye
bye-bye thanks for watching see you
tomorrow for uh 400 p.m. wa time RP p g
jrpg
stream which will be hopefully a longer
stream San
[Music]
Francisco
ah no
[Music]
poow
oh oh
[Music]
oh