[Applause]
[Music]
Drinking wide open is an addiction.Patients are wide open but it's
strange.I
hadn't decided what I was into.It's a wonderful exploration.I have a
good sense of perspective.Now there are 5 of us.I used to be able to pass here.3
people.  We're competing for the venue.
Something's wrong. Help me,
manipulate everyone. I want to care just because it's me. I do
n't care. If it's the worst regret I've ever had, [
Music]
Oh [Music]
I wish
[Music] I'm
begging
[Music]
Professor, please hurry up.
medium heat  I
feel like you're the only one who won't choose me anymore.I'm about to start looking for the most important thing in the world, and I
want to meet you.I can't go on a dream trip without you.If you do
n't think about me, I'm
starting to feel worried.I
definitely shouldn't be lost in a place like this.  [
Music] I wonder
if I love it.I'm so depressed.I'm the
only one who did it.The
cute thing was the
wide waves.The drunk was an addict.The sky was wide, but I had a strange
feeling.I
hadn't decided on the store manager.That's the wonderful feeling of being a detective.
Now all 3 people are on leave. It's a
monster. It's a monster. It's a
fight to steal it. I wonder if everyone can tell themselves how to run away. I
just
want to care. I don't care about anyone. It's the best.
[Music]
Oh
[Music] I'm
praying
[Music] A
wish.
[Music]
So we said yes, and
now we've started. I
'm sitting straight in my chair. It
's such a small area.
Yes, today, Chiara-chan is doing sleep.
Since you're here, I'd like to
introduce myself.It's Amarin.Here's
Wine.Hello, Hololive 3rd generation.Wait a
minute.I'm told that I have big shoulders.Ah,
this is it.What
do you mean by trying to look like a samurai?  I don't understand
what you mean.It doesn't really make any sense.It doesn't
matter.If you
say it with wide shoulders, you'll become more of a man.
Because you can see it, it's
gotten really narrow. I'm
starting to look like a girl.
[Music]
Today, I'd
like to do it with two members of Potion Marine. This is a live English performance.
1st term.
Chiara came from Austria during the Meiji period.  What's up? It's so bad at home,
there's nothing I can do about it, but I just came home and I'm
like, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, no, but my
eyes are busy from the moment I see all these cute things.
Well, seriously, the
captain was already in a panic as he was preparing for the broadcast, and
Kel-chan was
wandering around the room freely, taking a tour of the room by herself, just in case.  I
'm saying this for my seniors, but what do you mean? You're
always saying that you're 7 years old.
Everyone is laughing at that. They're
saying you're not 7 years old. They're
making fun of you.  It
hasn't been blown up, but
looking at the house, I can't help
but think that he's 17 years old and must be up to something. He's trying to make himself look younger by putting things in the house. He's stabbing me like he's doing it for Mari's sake,
though.  When I looked at these curtains, I
saw this bear.
Even when I chose it, the
person at the store told me that it
was designed for a children's room,
but Maria hasn't seen it yet.  I'm
a kid, so how much do you like the cute Rilakkuma in the nursery room?
Until now, it's
not Seven, but if it was just the cat's room, it would
probably be here.
There's also this one. There's about 30 cats there too
.  [Laughter] It's
okay, but I
can count. It's easier for me to count in German,
so it was applied to the overwhelming sense of speed.
What the heck? You
like walking. I like it too, but that walking...
There's a famous Dojin song, but
oh wait a minute, I'm too native to
understand anything, but ah, the Eiswine
Gutenburger is German from there, but I'm
so native that it
didn't sound like the same word.
Wow,
Marisa stole a lot of stuff,
right? I
like the singing character. I
installed that. This is it, Iosys-san.
Please get permission from me. Seriously,
dance.
I was really worried because
we hadn't decided what we were going to do at all.We've been
talking so much from the beginning, we're so
excited, it's so nice.We have
n't decided at all, so it's like, oh, it's so bad,
so
what else is there?
Cirno's Perfect Math Classroom
[Music]
[Laughs]
I'm too distracted. I wonder where it is.
Wait, if you
don't calm down, some information will come in.  My
head is confused, what did I do?
Wait a minute. I'm calm,
so I can just write it down.
Wait a minute, don't worry.
Wait, I
made a mistake. This isn't the
one. No, because the captain was more interested in
getting cut than preparing for the broadcast.
At the moment when the broadcast started,
I said "My tea," and she
said, "Hmm," and
echoed, "Oh, that's right, Chara-chan."  I
forgot about auntie Oh no, it's
machine gun talk.
Well, it's a
quick turn in this. I
thought I'd sing a song today. That's what I originally thought.
That was the plan. I'm
totally looking for where it is right now.  Well, you
know, even if I tried to search for it, it's
in Roman letters, so I can't read it at a glance, so I just
have to write Marisa.
Wait a minute, why are you going to use the difficult method?  The
lyrics are from Wait a minute, right now, it's
open at best, it's open here, it's open here,
and it's probably just open. It
's easier for me to do it if you look at it seriously, it's okay, it's American, it's
not in English, it
's in English.
Well, today's broadcast is a bit noisy. I
wrote Welcome to Underground in the title of today's broadcast, and it seems like people going overseas were confused. Why is there
such a grand, this, that thing?  You
know copy-paste, which is copy-copy-paste,
right? It's a famous joke. What's this kind of meme? It's a
tough Japanese meme.
By the way, what does Welcome to Underground
mean? It
seems like it's close, so I thought why not? It's like, well,
underground.
There's something like this on a tissue. There's something here to moisturize your lips. Maya, runny nose. Japan
is amazing. I got this from an actor.
Wait, this isn't in English, but I
was so happy that I got so many compliments on that one. I
guess I
shouldn't say it's amazing. I have to join the cast, but what the
heck? I'm about to
start streaming. I can't hear my voice very well.
Something just happened.  It
started off because the senior's voice was easy to do, but
that guy's voice was
still a bit low. [Applause] But, you know, the guy who wasn't on that program had a lot of cuts, and in reality he was wearing more.  I'm
really thinking about uploading the one that took all of that
to YouTube,
but seriously, the level that I can raise is really
similar.I
think it's called Generic Pekola.This is a
substitute for when Pekola doesn't pay attention to you.
Speaking of Pecola, I
was trying to memorize those lines,
but if I
tried to do it in freestyle, I don't
think they would be similar, but I guess I'll
start with a competition and
go with the flow from there.  Hey, okokok in the flow  I
love Marin-chan,
Pico
, it's amazing, it's so amazing, it's so exquisite,
Marin-chan, I don't say that, I wonder if it's
called Marin,
but Marin is better because it's a casual name.
Hmm, you can call me that.
That's fine. I won't be called away.
Akirara-chan. I
want to be called that
character. I'll
call you that. Yes, it's okay to call me that way.
That's really true,
because people don't use ``sachan'' or ``3'' overseas, so I
don't. Well, that's true in Japan,
and
I used to be used to adding that.
But recently, I've been living overseas again, so I've started
using it again.  It's so troublesome that I forgot. I was
n't careful enough to do it.
Now then, listen to me.
Yes, then, listen to me. From Chiara Takanashi
Marisa stole something terrible.
Yes, please come in for a moment. The
speaker is playing.
This is
how it
sounds. I'm
not trying to sound bad.
[Music]
[Music] I'm a
very native speaker, but let's
turn up the volume.
How about the volume? It's
coming.
[Music]
From here.
I don't know that kind of
magic.If I
tell you my feelings, it
'll break.I guess.I
guess.Even the
hearts of people who are different from you can be
easily
[Music]
The secret is always
screaming inside my heart
Because I'm different from you I
don't steal people's hearts so easily
So,
wait a minute, the first part
is a lie I love you so much The first part I'm
glad I sat down You know, the first part is sleeping like crazy  It
was interesting, but I was really busy at first, so please
sing that one more time. Hey
here, it
's not yet, it's not yet, it's not yet.
[Music]
[Laughter]
No, I thought it was a native, and I
thought it was cool. I
wanted to sing this at karaoke before, but
there was no Inchi Island, so thank you. I'll sing this,
get permission from the person who wants it, and send it to Chiara-chan,
too.
Thank you.
It was amazing. It's like this. If you
pronounce it like a native speaker, it's probably the same way. It's
pretty easy to hear the lyrics in English, but when Japanese people
sing them, the
way they speak English is so relaxing.
Let's sing it natively.
When I sang Tricolor Airline with Gura,
there was a part where Gura started off by saying, "Trichor are ain," but I
ended up saying things like that first.
But now, it's
a little weird. I don't understand the lyrics.
Well, wait, I
can't take you with me, but I'm a multi-senpai.
But I like this kind of thing. That one
from English-speaking countries.  There are as many
members as Manny-senpai,
and they don't talk, so I'm sorry
for the wait, but I feel like it's a bit one-sided. They
get so excited about the people that they're talking about China.
See, for example, this,
uh,
here, etc.
White, but I forgot about this and that.  Well, after I told you how to
sing, I
thought it would be difficult to apply it well.That's
what I mean.The other
day when I met Nekkoune-senpai, I was wondering if he was talking about
me or him.  I
was told that I looked like I just came out,
but I
was a little shocked by what my senior said to me.I
guess the final fans were happy.But
what did the captain say to me?He really praised me.  She
's so beautiful, her
eyes are so
beautiful. Wait, her eyes are so beautiful. She's the heroine of Resident Evil.
Resident Evil. What does the heroine of Resident Evil look like? Wait, what does the heroine of Resident Evil look like?
The face is scarier
than the world.The
eyes are like this.The
colors are like that.I
can't say it well, but
thank you.It's the
first time I've heard someone say something interesting.Resident Evil.No
, I'm praising it.Mirage
Jobi.That's a
great name.  That
's right. That
's not true. That's
wrong. Wait a minute, it's like that. Wait, I
'll have you look at Mirajob. It's correct.
Wait a minute, oh, look, it's like this.
Upper part of this character Well, I do
n't know how to pronounce it, but on the other hand, I don't know. I do
n't understand it. It's not
English. I guess this isn't English.
Eh, what is this? Then this one is,
uh, yeah, that's right, it's not English.  You're really
hot and
excited from a different place, and
if you pull out any more, your breasts will be on full display. You're probably thinking about
everything, but you're thinking about that.
Everyone's a group member.  I
don't have a captain. I don't have a
captain.
Well, I don't think it's karaoke or anything,
but
even if I don't have one, I have to make that request.
Everyone, please make this. Western music. Yeah,
it's different, but
it's my favorite. Even if I say I like it.  If you ask me what's your favorite Japanese song, I'll be in
trouble if you say this.
Well,
what's wrong? It's not that at all, but
with the flow of events right now, I'm reminded of it and the only thing we talk about is breasts,
Manny-senpai.  She was
trying to show off her breasts to me earlier, and
since we were talking about big breasts, Mario also said that she
has big breasts. Yeah, well, it's
heavy. I said, ``Hey, you
can hold it.'' I said, ``
No, no, I can hold back.'' Look, no, I don't
like women's breasts like this.  I've never touched it before, but it's a
paradoxical
feeling, it's so soft.
[Laughs] It's so
soft. What do you
want me to touch? It's
embarrassing. What's
next? I don't have any future plans yet.  I have
n't talked about
it. I haven't said that I'll be streaming it, but I think it's about time to say it, so I'm going to talk about it in episode 5. Well, I've got a lot of time to do it. I have a lot of off-collaborations planned, so let's do this tomorrow. Hey, Senpai, that's right, this is what happened before this cat.
When we met for the first time on the official program on the 30th, you suddenly fell in love with me.Maybe we
didn't touch
each other, but really, we've been looking at each other for
a long time.I'm in love with you, too.  I
think she's going to
say that she's cute and cute. I'm not saying that.
Yeah, Mari hasn't said that, but you
see, she's
a little jealous. That's okay. Emmalyn,
too, wants to be called cute. Because she's
holding both hands, No-chan, Uchia.  Tiara-chan,
Captain Edun, and Chara-chan
think she's cute.
Well, that's it. So
what are you going to do the next day? The next
day, you'll have to work on a case, but after that.  of
Yes, I haven't told anyone about this yet,
but
yes, I came up with a
couple collaboration that matches the Kami Kikashi Planning couples.If I
say "couple", my daughter will
get angry, but
Noefrey Takamori
's play, which is not a couple, is a couple.  Well, there
's no premonition that we're not a couple anymore, so I asked Takamori to say the same thing. Well then, we broke up because we were idiots. Let's rekindle the flame of that lost love.
That's the kind of episode that's gone. Yes, Japan is gone.
Yeah, that's right. So I
'm going to go see that Inu-senpai who wanted Marine Pire 2.
Well then, I'm going to compare Mari's breasts with a
degraded version
in hand. Let's compare. Well then, let's compare.  I don't know
what to say about the staff at every meal.
There aren't many people with big boobs in Marine Japan. It's not like that.
There are a lot of them, but if they're big in Japan, they
're big somewhere.  I mean, wait.
Where does it come from?
Well, it's
not more than an F. I
'm licking
it. I'm being licked. I'm
asking for a proper, proper licking. I
don't know what it means.
Well, leave it alone
. You're lucky. What's with your boobs?
And your ass.  There's a butt, and there's a butt.I
can't see this kind of shape.I can't see it in Japanese.So,
what is that?
In other countries, they say that sand clock.
In other countries, they call it sand
watching. Oh,
wait,
but the clock is black.
Oh yeah, yeah, what's that? Eh, hey
old man. Yes, I said something sad at my house today. What's the matter, Marine-
senpai?
When I was eating, and I
ate it, I realized that Tiara's Japanese
was
n't very good. She didn't say it clearly.
No, no,
no. I heard that the captain did a collaboration with her a long time ago.
When we were in Japan, we went out to eat together.When we were in Japan, we
went to a buffet together.We did some collaborations.But
then, at that time, things were already messed up.Wait, we were going to collaborate,
but we
didn't collaborate.  In Japan, we used
to talk about holotalk using the cat's token,
and we
talked when we went to the buffet together, but at that time, it was
kind of weird.  I
was talking to Smoothie about the
fare, but I was having holotalk for the first time in a while, and I was
watching Tiara-chan's chat, and when we
were chatting, things were a mess.My
Japanese suddenly became so bad that I realized that I had
returned to my country.  I'm forgetting Japanese. Oh,
Japan. I do
n't collaborate with the members as much anymore
, but I think I'm forgetting Japanese.
I'm like me.
Thank you for getting involved. I
don't think so,
Senpai. I suddenly have zero self-esteem. What's wrong with me?
Marin-senpai is a god, so it's
not trash. I guess she's a god to me.
But I like Pecola better, Kirara-
chan.
That's right. No, no, uh
, we have different allies.
Senpai, hmm,
Mari-senpai.
Kirara-chan is no longer fluent in Japanese, so that
's why she speaks in English.  I
can defeat you, I'll help you.That's
true.It's been like that for a long time.That
's right.It's not like this now, it's been like that for a long time.That's
right.On the contrary, you can't get involved, Pecola.I have so
much respect for you.You've said something like that before.  I
think I said the same thing during holotalk.
Hmm, you know, I
read this a while back, especially Bacon-senpai, and I
remember seeing that after that.
Yes, this
senior, I'm going to Japan, but
if you do
n't mind, I'll fit in. It's a long trip, so the hurdles
are high, but he said it's okay.
But he said that.
Honestly, since then, I haven't touched on the topic a bit.
Well, I'm a little sorry after all, but I
understand that even the captain can't just casually
say, ``Let's meet up.'' I
think it's too much for Pico's seniors.  Even though we've
been together for this long, I don't
want to go too far and make him feel bad.You know, that's how I feel, too.However, when Senpai gets angry,
why are we still together?4  It's
been 3 or 4 years now. I think it's
time to get rid of those feelings. I
think it's funny that I've been phoenixed. I
'm a bird,
after all. I'm sure you're a phoenix smoker.  I'm
happy when you give it to me, oh yeah.
Well, I guess I do
n't have any seniors, but that's
okay. This time, I'm
not going on a trip to Japan, but I've been in Japan for a
long time, and I'm pretty packed with plans and stuff.
Yeah,
but maybe Hey, you look
busy, you're busy in the Year of the Rabbit, you're really busy right now, you're
doing a lot of things, you know, you're
really busy, so the
captains are the same, the captains are the
captains, the captains are the same, so that's what they're doing right now.  There's
no Year of the Captain,
right? There's no Year of the Rooster, right?
There's a Year of the Rooster. There's a Year of the Rooster. Couldn't it
be? Look, if there's one, it's already there. There
's nothing written on it. It doesn't
matter what kind of bird it is.
Anything.  Isn't it okay? I can't
get it. It looks like 4. If you change the English, I won't understand. I'll
read it. Write it in English. It
said Easy English Easing Contemplation.
This, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, Prograstinian, Prograstina show, Prograsnation,
in the first place, this is
unfair, you know, it's crazy, you know, if you
put the letters together and put them sideways, you can
pretty much figure out how to read them, you know, the Japanese version.  I don't know how
many kanji there
are. I've never counted them. I wonder how many there are. If I
googled them, I'm sure they'd come up, but they're
all
in C. I do
n't know Japanese, so that's why you're asking me to do that.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I don't want to get angry like that. I'm sorry. Let's
make up. Let's make up. We'll make up.
Senpai will also want to hug me. You can
hug me, but I'll be shy with my hands.
If you hug me, you'll be in a nice mood. It might be
dangerous, but you'll be in an aromatic mood.
Romantic.  I'll take it, I'll
give you 70 of them. I'll
sing something. I
came on board. Hey,
Mr. Manager,
there's that English part of OnlyMyRailgun. So say that.  I do
n't know, but what does Chiara-chan
say? I'm curious. Let's
divide the parts. Eh,
but the captain is expensive and I can't sing. Eh, I'm singing
by myself. I was singing by myself, but it
's a collaboration. It's a collaboration. We're
together.  I'm
seriously in love with Reel, which is in the top 3 of my favorite anime.My
favorite is the Bakemonogatari series.I
really like Bakemonogatari.When's the new one coming out?  It's
coming out, but it's kind of a big ending,
isn't it? It's like an ending story, so
I'm still planning on doing what I read, and
he
actually said that he was planning to make all of those works into anime, so they'll
all be animated.  I want to see
it, that's what I'm saying.It's true,
Araragi-kun too.I
don't know everything, all I know is that
you're the one who loves Nadeshiko the most.I
love you so much.Not today,
though.I'm worried.
Kashinobu Hanekawa, I have two choices. I don't
have to choose Hanekawa. I just like boobs.
No, Haneko. That's amazing. I'm
going to fall in love with her, right? She's my girlfriend type. I
want to make her happy. I'm happy because I didn't choose her.  It's
like I'll make you happy.
Shinobu is a young man, a big man, and all in all,
both are good, both are good,
right?  I
also admire overwhelming strength,
so please listen to me.
What do you think? The microphone is red, but it's
okay, it's okay. Let go
of the dreams carved in your heart, even the future.
[Music]
[Applause]
Don't fight.
This meaningless power will
scatter the light.  Beyond that, I have a
distant feeling.
Oh wait, there's no earthquake.
If I can't look back on this road I've been walking, I can
destroy everything here and now. This cityscape falling into darkness.  I'm
changing the team I was born in. I'm
sure to protect someone from the accelerating pain. The
light also ran at the speed of a
certain premonition.
I'm shining brightly one by one as I grasp the spell. I
believe in my vow that day to this one person.
Light gel tears.  But there's
no winter break,
cool character-chan. I
can't lie that there's nothing wrong with the sadness I feel when I stop.
Besides, even if
I get
hurt without going around, even if I get hurt without going around, I
can aim to keep on running.
My eyes go crazy
As long as my heart cries out, no
one
will stab me yet
[Music] That's a
great dismissal. Well, I do
n't know, I don't know, I
don't know, I don't know, I don't know, but right now, I'm
holding it in both hands and it's starting to look like the darkness I'm cutting through.  It's a
heavy, deep,
painful memory, I don't understand. I do
n't want to cry. I'm still me right now. My heart is full
of emotion. [Music] I have a certain premonition that I'm going to scream at the speed of light.  The
dream that I carved into my heart with my nose is
even in the future This meaningless power that knows no limits
scatters light The
distant thoughts beyond that are
really cool
[Music]
Chiara-chan, the tree looks just right,
thank you.  Actually, I've
only heard the anime version of
this song, so it was completely unknown to me.  I
love everything, I sing it so much. What do I like most
? There's
something about it. There's something about it. It's the one from Owarimonogatari. I
haven't watched it too many times, so I remember
it. Oh yeah
[Applause]
Try singing it. I
forgot the donuts.  I
think it's my favorite, but I tend to forget it because of the pressure.But it's
all about innerwear.Alright, I
saw it, but I only watched it twice, so I
remember it a little vaguely.
But I scolded you so much that I forgot about it twice,
but
it's true, no, it was five years ago, or if I was a senior, I heard that you would have known about it, but I'm not
sure about it now, but it's true, I
like it, it's good, I love it.  I mean, the
players are just in their youth, too. That
opening scene is so cute!
Shineverse, here and there, they're talking in English
. I
didn't know that, but that's how they talk
.  It's
okay, I
know. I'll make it more flashy later. Do
you have any other favorites of my house? Everyone, look! It reminds me of the Minami family.
There's a song by him about curry curry. It's like
Hosaka.
Just remember it.  I don't
think so. [Music] You should just look at music. You've probably heard of it before, right? It's
popular after all.
If you look around, you'll
find it. Seashells are a little hard to look at. Ah, I see.
Eh, what kind of anime is popular overseas?
Eh, I
wonder what it is. Eh, it honestly feels good. I don't know what it is.
Eh, hey, hey, that one was popular.
Little My Pony is
different overseas, too. I'm
sure it's different here.  I also looked at a little bit
of the Pine Family, which has
cute skins,
and Little My Pony Powerpuff, and
Jojo, which is
for kids, but Little My Pony for kids, and
Nobody, which is for kids, but I really
like the old Pao.  The
community is kind of scary
Adult funk music
Stars Lab
Dex I
saw it on the network, but the real pronunciation is
yes,
but it's Dex
Lab.I
don't know.Also, there's a
cat
cooking something, like ketchup.The cat is also ladleping.
Where can I watch it? That's why Cartoon
Network is in Japan. That's right.
Let's go back to the SpongeBob Tom and Jerry anime.
Cowardly College Boy  I do
n't know, it's a bit late.
Wow, I didn't expect to see that. I've
lost a little respect for you. Um, why, why, why, what's wrong? I like it when you say something like that, rather than having a good sense.  If you
ask me, ``What's the anime?'' It'll
probably be something like Doraemon or Anpanman.I see, it's lower, it's different, it's something like
peek-a-boo.In Japan, we say it.
In the first place, I don't know what peek-a-
boo is. I've
never seen that one. Please wait. Peek-a-boo. I've
seen this before. Look, I've never seen it before.
That dog is scary. My
respect has increased, but on the other hand, I'm a
senior. Yes, please
eat.  Oh, hey, this is
what it is. Mana Manor. When I came to Japan, the
flavor I gave to those Wayfers that I gave out to everyone was lemon flavor.
Time as a Samurai.  It's
delicious, that famous Austrian one.
[Laughs] I
'll try it on this tissue, even though the real flavor is hazelnut.
[Music]
3 Ah, the
smell.
Hmm, you're spilling it all out. It's really crumbling right
now. Please
put this on a tissue.  I've
never eaten many foreign sweets,
but this is it. Hmm, I
don't want you to see me as a representative.
What is this? It's just this. It's
really famous. Hmm,
but there are even more delicious ones.
Why did I lower this? It's
just meh, it's a little meh,
but I thought it would appeal to everyone, so
this one certainly has
something for everyone. Even
my senpai and Kone-senpai really liked it. There's a
lot of things written about it, though.  It's
not English, it
's German.
Eh, you can tell me what your plans are for Senpai.
Eh, you
can say that. What are your plans for the 5th? What are your plans
for the 5th? What do you mean? Oh, maybe there's a
marine infestation.  I said I couldn't do it
What are you talking about? Listen, what are you talking about?
Hmm, thank you muta mute. Mute. Yes, I'll mute. [Music] [Music] Hey, I
think I probably said this on the stream.  It's
been two years since I said I was going to go, and I don't
want to turn into a fraud, but there have been a lot of things
going on, but I've become more serious.  It's
not a good idea to be serious in this day and age, but Japanese people always
say they want to go abroad, but they
don't get it out of their heads, and
no one really thinks that's the case.Well, the
captain was
really planning on going.  Hey,
please tell me a little bit. If you don't mind, I'll ask you to
come with me. But then I made a comment saying that the manager was busy, so I shouldn't take her with me, and
when she said that, I went alone.
Why did you say that? You
said it in the comments. I'm the
manager. I'm
telling you to come by yourself. Why am I the only one who brings
someone I don't know?
I don't like it, but the truth is, if I wasn't in Japan right now, I'd be
planning on going to Austria right now.The
store manager has
never been overseas before, which is scary.It's
time for me to go.I'm eternally 17 years old.
But at some point, life is going to be bad, so it's definitely better to
go to various places before it ends.If someone
tries to speak to you in English at the airport, you'll
have trouble understanding it.  I
can't call you.
No, it's okay when I leave. When I go to bed, the
first place
I go to is the Austrian airport. I'll
come pick you up. Of course, I'll also speak English at the exit.  It's
written all right, so it's okay. What should
I do? If someone speaks to me in very fast English as I'm leaving the airport, it's okay. I ca
n't speak to them in fast-paced English. Perhaps it's a mystery that I can't speak to them in fast-paced German.  I was
just
thinking about what to say when you're in trouble, but don't worry, you'll be with me from the beginning.
[Music]
Seventeen
Girl.
But to be honest, I've
been flying all over the place on that plane, but I
don't really need it. Especially when I
say something like "direct," if I go overseas, I'm
sure they'll say, "Okay, so
let's have some English conversation."  The
second part is like an airport story. I'm
still the captain at the airport and I don't know the exit.
Excuse Me
Seven Girl Excuse
Meets Where are the Parents? The Parents of Monster Parents? Um, uh, I'M not77 It's a passport. The one that makes a beeper. It's okay, thank you, thank you, thank you x902 Taxi Taxi Airport, Taxi Airport Taxi Cars.  So I'll call a taxi.
There's a normal sign of applause, so there
's no need to call Ok, Ok, Ok, because I'm here.
At that point, that's
all I need to show my passport, and once I get over it, I'm already there.
But what if someone says something to me?
What's your purpose?  If
you don't want to be told, you won't be told - well,
but even though you said that, it's
better to say meat friends, meat
friends, yay
meat friends, no,
to friends
[laughter]
Meat
friends, that's what you mean, right?
Well, the pronunciations are the same, so I guess that's the mistake I just made.
I forgive you, I say I'm really going.
Meet
OUT
meets. We're
just not the same.
When I say that, I
understand. Well, it's okay now. Be
strong. What should I do if a man is about to kidnap me? I'm about to be kidnapped.
What would you do if you were about to be kidnapped by a strong, strong, strong man who is three times bigger than Marin?
Well, that's not the case. It's not like that. We
're still in Austria, so we've done that
over and over again.  Do
n't forget,
even Chiara-chan
might be targeted by a strong man. She wo
n't be targeted, she won't. You know,
slow mountains.
Sexy girls might be targeted like that,
but
Marine is a sexy girl.  Well,
that communication is
true.
[Music]
But with this past, I'm afraid. Maybe I'll
go dressed like that. I'm a little Japanese. If I
show up dressed like this, I'm sure
a lot of
things will be said to me.  I
like having breasts that allow me to know what is being said
and what is being said to me. That makes me happy,
because I get compliments on it. It
's easy to go there, but I think it's easy. Lately, I've
been to Japan for the first time in two years.  I was surprised to see that so many things had changed.It
really had changed that much.But my
seniors wouldn't know, and I would
n't go to the airport even if they didn't know.Maybe the
airport had changed in those two years.
Compared to just a few years ago, it's
amazing. For example, what kind of things have evolved
? Before coming to Japan, we had to
go through the procedures online, although it wasn't every day. We also had
QR codes, which we didn't have before.
When I got to the code, I
couldn't show it to my computer or anything, and it was terrible.You
know, I was really nervous, and I was nervous when I arrived in Japan.
Oh, what, what, what, what, uh,
there's a person at the
immigration office,
like the immigration bureau, right.I gave that passport to that person,
but I've been to Japan many times,
so yeah, to be honest, I'm always nervous, so again.
I felt like this guy had come, and then I thought, ``
This guy is dangerous, he
keeps looking at my passport,'' and I
thought, ``I'm looking at my passport and checking something on my computer.'' And
then I started talking to other people.  I was
worried
that I was running out of time, like I was going to get caught, but I just wanted to
pretend like I wasn't nervous.
Something really happened.
After about 5 minutes,
Mr. Kihara
saw this paper in his pass pot and
took it out. He
gave it to me and I said goodbye.
When I lived in Japan before, I
still had some hair left in my hair, and I was just worried about it.I was just wondering
what the god was about that.If you
ask me, I
was really worried.
So,
what is the working holiday paper? It was the beautiful
woman from Barking Holiday who stayed
in Japan for a year. She felt like she
had great freedom and was given a visa that
allowed her to work only once in her life.
Well, it was just a one-time thing, so I took a picture of it.
But when I left, I had something on my hair,
but apparently I forgot to take it off. Yeah,
that's something I had to worry about for five minutes.
No, I was surprised. No, what kind of paper
was that?  I don't know, but I was so
excited. It was written in Japanese, so it
was written in Japanese,
so yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
but there's more to Japan.  I just
realized that something has changed. What, did you
go to Gusto school?
I love the original A.
When I hear the words Gas and Saizeriya, it's Gusto,
so I was like, "
I love Jonathan, I love you, I
love Saizeriya, I
love them all, but
what if I went to Gus?"  The store
clerk has turned into a robot.It's been a long time
since I've
seen a robot cat serve the food.I
was surprised.  Apparently there's a
robot cat that puts it in the rice,
so a
collaboration robot with food comes to that cable.I
know, I know, I've seen this before.But there's
this kid at my table, it's
normal,
but his face is
reflected on the screen.  The cat's
cute face, even if it's not Leah's face, it's a pixel.It's
become cute.The
captain is also cute.And not only that, but
what else has changed compared to two years ago?
At the convenience store.
At convenience stores and other places, there are
more cash registers where you pay by yourself.You
put your money in there, and there are already plastic bags.It's
that color now, but overseas it's always been
that way, so I
don't really care about those plastic bags.
Now that you have to pay for things, you've had to put them in plastic bags yourself in
many places.Even
though they don't often put things in your shopping bags, it's not the only thing
I've ever experienced on this
trip.  What I have experienced in  They
wouldn't let me in for quite a while, but I'm
fine with paying for it myself, but I'm not good at buying it myself,
so I get a little nervous.Well, it's
not a supermarket, it's a convenience store.They let me
in.A convenience store
is a convenience store.  That's right, but
other places won't let you in anymore. When it comes to
supermarkets, etc., you have to
put them away by yourself. It
was just a store where you could go for drinks or something.
But things like that have increased, things have changed, and I
thought, ``Japan has changed so much in two years.'' I do
n't think it's changed that much in a year and a half, but has it changed that much?
Marin also changed when I met her for the first time in a year and a half.  Well,
I
guess I should say I
forgot and forgot, but I
also forgot about Marin and Ei-chan.If that's the case, then it's been
too long since I've canceled it.It's because I
met my paralyzed senior.  About
half of us are feeling more anxious than dogs. It's
okay to play. Just once,
today.
I was standing in front of my water, and
before I knew it, Mayu-senpai
called me to say that something had come in.  But I'm
in front of the store right now, and
when I said I couldn't see you, I didn't see you. That's why I
got angry when you let me in. If you
say Tiara-chan, I'll understand right away.
I guess that's what you think.
I hid behind the wall That's right, I'm
sure that's what happened. I
wrote ``A dog that lives there'' and the center
came back to me. I
went back to the entrance and I was there.  I was looking at her face,
and I
was like, Wow, I
completely forgot about this.
She said something to me because she did something for me, right? I guess she said, 'I can't do that.' To be
honest, I'm a little confused.
In the light, in the light, that
red hair, that
poop, I
started to see how cute it was, and it was
completely different, as expected, but the
eyes were amazing, and I thought they were tiny, but they both
looked like slimes,
even though they were wearing masks.
With the vacuum cleaner, I
look in front of me. She
was cute before, but I feel like she's cuter this time. Maybe
that's why I didn't understand. It's appropriate. Say that and do that. It
's true. It's appropriate.
Thank you very much for keeping up with me. I want to eat with you this time. I want
to eat yakitori. I
want you to listen to me.
Yakitori, why, why, why,
all
the time.
Yakitori, this time. I
want to stay here.  It's been about 2 weeks. I've
been eating
ramen twice,
fillet cutlet once,
and a lot of other things I've
forgotten. I have a good
memory, like curry and kare, and things like that.
Yes, but I still didn't want to eat that yakitori.I wanted to eat
it.I wanted to eat something I hadn't eaten yet.I ate it.I ate it, but yeah.Neither of us
ate it at all.No, we don't eat much at all.Maybe the other
two do
n't like internal organs either.  I mean, I'm kind of excited,
but I don't think it's something to get excited about.When I go out to eat in Japan, the other person is always ok, and I feel like if I
say no, I don't have anything like that.
No, I don't want people to think I'm a foreigner.
After all,
internal organs aren't meant to be eaten. I have them too, but I always think so. They're not internal organs. Hey, hey, my
ex-senpai
almost died today.
Hey, Mainichi Senpai, I was
just sitting there when suddenly a glass came from next to me, and a glass hit my arm.  I
took it slow, but well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
Yes, it was okay. I guess I
got that for free instead. I had a lot of
drinks. I was already full.
On the contrary, I was even happy. I
didn't break it, but it
was like someone bumped into me and said something like that.
Something like that happened to me. That thing behind the
bridge was
all sorts of stylish, and I thought it looked like Japan. I
thought I'd go there to save myself.
Thank you! It was
delicious. It
was delicious. Well, that's it for today. Let's
take it easy.  Oh yeah, I
'm going to stay at Senpai's place too.Oh yeah, I'm
going to go with Kea-san today.I'll borrow those pajamas too.There are so
many things to swallow.There are so many.
There is such a thing as gelato pique.It's
hot and light, but it's summer gelapy.It
's got the image of being fluffy, so it's
fluffy, but when I go to sleep, the
300 or so Rilakkuma in my house
wake up and kill me.  It's
not like that, right?
Because it heals me, but
which of these do I like the most?
So this one, no,
actually this one.
There's only one alpaca, Altogai. You know, they're
stuffed here and there.
That's right. If
there's someone who collects them, they're there. I also have alpacas that
have real alpacas with that wool on them.
Alpacas
like that.  I like you,
don't I love you so much that I want to go there?
Nao-chan is the one who turned me down.
Don't you know that she likes Marine more than the devil? I
know, but there's something about that matching...  I was
thinking of something like that alpaca couple.My
older sister had the pink one, and she
gave it to Marin-chan.Among them,
there's also the Riraku that she received from the fans.It
used to be okay to receive it from the fans.
The one I use as a pillow is like that, so I thought,
``Stuffed animals'' are
basically a no-no for fans, so I don't like stuffed
animals.I don't really have stuffed animals, so I wonder what's going on.  I've
received quite a few small items, like pouches, but it's really different from all the other stuff. It's all pink, and it's cute, right? It's cute, but it's really scary, too. I was able to stream it as soon as I got here, but...
After all, I
thought I
had everything. It's a bit small, but I
have a stand for the camera, and the
cables are there, so when I prepared them, I found
something like that.
Plug in those two headphones and have them ready
so I can listen to them.I have two that allow me to hear my own voice properly, so I'm going to watch it.I
think it's amazing that there's so much out there.As
expected, we've collaborated many times at our house.  Hey, I
have plenty of time.
[Music]
Well, it's almost been an hour. I'm going to
sing one more song. What should I sing? I don't know what to
sing.
Anime songs are better, aren't
they?  You
know it,
right? It
feels like I'm suddenly in a soccer hall. I
don't know much about it, but
for example, what kind of
flower is that flower? That flower is that flower that surrounds you and summer.
Dreams for the future.
What should I do?
Yeah, everyone's
recommendations.
Winter.  The "Poi-bye-bye" song is like a
winter-like "Bye-bye" crowd with a lingering snow. I can
dance to it, but I can't sing it. I ca
n't sing it. It's
difficult. It's
difficult. It's difficult. I'm really busy with Mary-sama's song.
Idiots and idiots, of
course it's okay.Then let's talk about the idiots with Chiara-chan.It
's difficult.Okay, it's
a bit Japanese Army
Broadcasting
Pirates
There's a Roman alphabet, yes, yes, it's true.Okay, then I'm
going to let it flow from now on.It's
going well.
Okay, okay, let's show off a little bit,
tonton, tontontontontontontontontontontontontontontontontontontontontontontontontong With this, thighs
tonton
[Music] If you're a
pirate, dance 4 times and
scream.
Please change the principal.  I'm moving
forward with my career change, let's move forward,
the sun is going to the sun and thunder, it's a good day.To the song, I'm
feeling the best, riding on the sound of the waves, in the ocean,
girls,
derby money, my
big brother is happy, now, far away,
sparkling,
deep in the mountains, I'm dreaming in my dilapidated house.
[Applause] It
was so fast, it's the end! We
're pirates, we'll raise our flag with a compass in one hand, and we'll embrace this sea. Our
last days are
full of softness, and we'll
see them as we dance, yes, yes, yes, yes, no.
.  I
'm the type who lets it out far away, red and red, and enters from a fashionable perspective.Run
ahead, a real
love train.It's
easy to enjoy the sunset.
[Music]
But
let it out no matter what.That's the true nature.The
legendary ale that calms down the pirates.When I'm
sad, I'll sing.
[Music]The
scenery is
precious.
Friends, the
rabbit is coming to the party
.
Negotiating marine. The
radioactive style is the cutest in the world.
The heat is the princess, Sugaki is spicy.
What should we do first, young lady?
[Music]
[Applause] I do
n't remember raising you guys to be that cute. You
can really sit down. I agree
with the release.
Thanks to you guys, I
can be a good omen.
[Music]
[Music]  ]
Pirate
Well, let's
go. I'm heading home. Bye-bye
. No, don't get excited. I'll do this
later. Thank you. Thank
you. Well, Chiara-chan, see you tomorrow. I
heard from Corone that we'll be broadcasting together.
Well, that's okay. Chara-chan's
channel is also posted below, so
please subscribe. I
'll respond when Japanese comments come in.
Well, I'd like to
follow Chara-chan who is staying in Japan.
Please, please. I
'm the one who likes to have sex. That's just what I said. It's
too straightforward. It's
just like that.
Let's go see a movie. Let's go to the movies.
[Applause] [
Music]
This is it.
What should I say to you guys when I open it?
Forget what I was looking for, do
n't get too hung up on this treasure. Yell, I also found something fascinating. It's great,
but the
red on the internet
is the ultimate pirate's treasure [music].  I
[music]
have touched you,
don't understand the scent
[music]
Look,
travel around the world
[music]
Captain Peke, I do
n't want to catch you, I
want my sweetness
[music]