[Music]
do
wow
[Music]
my hands are really shaky i'm a terrible
cameraman
[Music]
the camera shakes a lot it's just my
hand okay
[Music]
don't worry about it so we're here and
we have a halloween special we have some
activities planned uh but for now as you
can see we have some new costumes so i
guess we'll start all the way at cali
wait where's challenge and we'll do an
introduction
man that's embarrassing
let me go go more
here have
i have some things to show you
hold on you guys what kind of drinks
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
oh sorry i'm in the way for halloween
you yeah that's how you say it
it's real now
yes that makes sense
it's so cute i think it's a lot of
people's fantasies seeing you in a
nursery
oh yeah i mean it is i can totally
understand that
there are some socks there are some
socks here
i'm looking at right now and some eye
area between my my socks and the the
drawers oh yeah yeah
kelly can you come closer to the edge
please for four sides
yes ma'am
oh yeah
oh yeah oh yeah
it's black
[Music]
[Applause]
no i'm embarrassed
okay cheeks i'm having a lot of fun i
always have fun when you do these
kiara
[Music]
i
chose i originally wanted to do so many
other things but i chose to be a vampire
today because today i released my
[Music]
vampire yeah it goes like that you're
welcome you have an earworm you warm now
by me yes
dress
do i look like a vampire i hope i do a
cute vampire
let me i clean it for you a little i
just
oh there you go
so i expect
[Music]
yeah that's what they know automatically
uh-huh
okay i'll think about it
i actually haven't had a chance to
listen to the cover yet but i will one
hundred percent after this
you're so busy that's yeah i've been
setting up some things but i will listen
to it i'm so excited you guys are
releasing so many covers cali uh also
announced a new song huh oh yeah
tomorrow
today
soon after the stream actually sweet
[Music]
it's not necessarily sweet but it works
and i was thinking dad costume it must
be an orange isn't it
um
[Music]
oh
um i chose this one because somebody had
drawn this but actually this is an
outfit i wore when i was a kid i
remember like uh there's like small i'll
make a picture small baby on my pictures
where i'm wearing this like pumpkin
outfit with like a little wood challenge
i really like this outfit
[Music]
i feel like pumpkin will also match you
because you have the hair to match oh
yeah
same
[Music]
i am
mad
scientist
[Music]
yeah that's it
yeah by daytime i'm just a normal
student
all right it's perfect for you yeah
yeah i'm a normal student by day
mad scientist by now
yeah
spiderman she's performing experiments
on me
yes
[Music]
yeah it's very comfortable i asked for
no pants it looks really cool i think i
have pants
the joke wait really i don't have one
more i asked for no pants but i think i
did that
i think
i think they're tight
okay
it's okay
[Laughter]
intellectuals
there we go
[Music]
uh
oh yeah wiggle that
[Music]
wiggle wiggle
oh
[Music]
i promise you good luck and good
halloween candy pictures oh yeah
you say that now i'm coming for you
after the stream
i'd love to see like a fight in that
costume like just
pissed
i just say mortal kombat like the the
the default
[Music]
i want to see like
um
yes
so as you guys know this is a costume
party so since it's a party we didn't
like some extra guests that are here i
think they should be around the elevator
at some point
i think let's go check on them they
might be here already all right let's go
[Music]
oh
i hear sound oh there's my cane
[Music]
oh there they are oh my goodness
what happened here
oh my goodness
oh no
come here
to destroy these monsters
[Applause]
oh my god
oh goodness
um
[Music]
thank you sorry i'm trying to get you on
camera wait a worm can do a back flip
oh there you are oh my god
you're beautiful
you look a lot like your cousin
backflips
your blue cousin
are you okay
[Music]
what is
oh the battle between chaos and death
who will win
oh no
kelly kelly callie what have you done
what have you done today no
i don't know what's wrong with her i'm
trying to figure out if i cut her open
then
come on
kill you
oh no
oh no oh oh no
oh my god
oh dear
she's dead what's wrong with her look
like this
wait you gotta cook it first girl no
eating raw rats
[Music]
oh dear
what happened to you
oh
[Music]
crony
hey that's my cane
that's my walking
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
in my natural habitat
pretty long neck
[Music]
a ghost
you know
oh wow okay okay time and space
telekinesis
very nice
[Applause]
[Music]
are you professor
i can put
[Music]
oh you're almost good
all right oh hello
hello
dinosaurs
[Music]
and the cutest dinosaurs both the cutest
things in the world and one screen
oh my god yes i don't know
twisting off oh no don't worry about it
don't worry about it
my my brain felt so massive
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
all right children listen to other
sunsets
[Music]
[Applause]
attendance checks
[Music]
over
the
and recently we did have a zombie
outbreak a zombie ahmed outbreak so we
had to close your mouth infection here
but uh i'm
and we also have a few different uh
reception desks here we do have a small
one like usually i would be here
i would help you guys uh you know if you
had like some issues
you guys
wanted to know what timeline to go to i
could help you with that uh today we
will be traveling to another timeline
and as you guys know council came from
another timeline which was in another
dimension and you guys got all my stuff
in the elevator somehow
i've been having some issues too
yeah the elevator
here we have concierge as well which is
currently closed as uh it is a holiday
um but we also have the elevator which
you guys have seen awesome awesome tunes
in there
um
we won't be using it today do not press
the second button we'll be using that
later and over here
[Music]
we have some candy
oh my god
[Music]
crying over here his fountain of tears
they are salt water we were thinking
about adding some fish but uh yeah some
salt water uh fountain here
sweet though
it's actually part of yeah
[Music]
um
this lobby uh has a lot of timelines
attached but we do have portals
specifically for all of the small myth
members here i'd love to add some more
in the future
[Music]
cardboard
oh there we go
it's a good camera angle
[Music]
uh
in one second
[Music]
there you go
i need candy to give to bed that's my
bargaining
steps
[Music]
the chaos
how about we go over to the next area
now let's go over to the next portal
okay
so cute
i'll get it back
i'll be there in one moment
this camera is so hard to use uh oh
they're leaving they're leaving
[Music]
that's right all right we're gonna go
into selfie mode for now all right let's
go let's go chat
[Music]
right they go
yeah
oh there they are
i'm running with the camera
so much candy
[Music]
oh
beautiful all right
a lot of messages about how a phoenix
vampire is very contradicting
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank
yes
[Music]
a little bit about this map i forgot to
do the last one but this is actually uh
australia yeah it's really pretty around
the side of yours you can see the trees
have been changed we have some pumpkins
for decoration and this is like the uh
main town plaza it's really nice kind of
reminds me of like animal crossing or
something is really cute
[Music]
oh yeah return to pumpkin
i am pumpkin
all right you guys take whatever you
like we're not going to be moving over
to the next portal
what's going on
yay
the ancient ones of
[Music]
let's look at it first
memories
is gonna hurt my
my
really pointy object from a different
dimension
i think not much
[Music]
oh no
not in the heart
[Music]
oh
of atlantis which we could go back in
time and bring atlantis back and it's
full glory if you guys would like to see
that at another time but today this is
the timeline that we are in and it's
quite beautiful here under the water
yeah under the sink under there
we are gonna how many uh like meters are
we down below the surface
[Music]
i don't know
oh
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
kelly just jamming
you can look out the window
[Music]
oh
you can sit on the window
uh
oh
[Music]
now i can join cali
i think all right
it's about this area i believe this is
inna's room
[Music]
also here nice relaxing tea area as well
as some nice open windows with a
bookshelf and of course some painting
equipment as you guys can see
these channels
painted are actually from her first yeah
mad scientist pasta
oh yeah right there oh yeah beautiful
[Music]
yeah yeah
and in his stuff she probably won't
don't worry about it don't worry about
it okay i need to oh okay
with the camera did i disappear
[Music]
yes
okay
that's right
[Music]
you gotta go find army
is
this camera is
not cooperating
oh there's a blue there's a blue oh this
is a pop down a little right here
i think kiara is the oh she's over there
she's trying to fix them oh yeah so uh
this is uh the desert
small almost
ends up here
after some time maybe some crimes
there we go yeah
brownie
it was iris i saw her do it
i saw her inject the concoction into
crony
connie i didn't know that this was a
deadly concoction it was an accident
injector what's the antidote
at least she's not happy
[Laughter]
concoction of life
she's
oh yeah
just to um you guys a little bit about
this area this is where some small
armies come to rest whether it's uh due
to
time or crime uh it's a bit of a prison
it's a bit of a resting place
[Music]
oh to everything we're going to go sit
down
[Music]
why
isn't it
huh
okay this time it wasn't me
attention everybody will now begin the
second portion of the field trip as
today is halloween so we have some
spooky activities planned
on to the spooky
[Music]
please press the second button here the
instant teleport button
[Music]
oh my goodness this area is
oh
no
crate
crate artists
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
it's been long dead
[Music]
they're adorable
we're gonna do a little tour of this
area let's start over here first
um i actually believe that this might be
what caused uh you guys's
um
[Music]
i think there's been some messing around
going on oh yeah
but as you can see there's this looks
like an evil ritual
remember there's nothing
this is for clones
is
[Music]
oh
like a
[Music]
that sounds funny
god
i need to show them this
[Music]
yeah okay
sure we're trying to switch the camera
here we go there you go
here we go um
hello
have
[Music]
oh
oh my oh and a luigi board
[Music]
has a huge grain and we also have this
the great yellow pumpkin
i never played this before and i know i
want to keep it that way
you're welcome to take a seat we do have
chairs scattered all around this area if
you'd like to take a look oh yeah does
anybody have the flying chest and we
also have this music
[Music]
maybe like nothing to do with this
spirits if you're already operating
how's this chat
how's this
who do you like then from the mario
franchise huh
who's your favorite this way
i'm gonna put you guys
hey okay
[Music]
is
trying to work the camera okay
it's a very hard job i'm gonna cover my
ears
[Music]
uh
is
[Music]
i think this one catches most people
somehow it's okay
so yeah
a lot of other kids
listen to me
for this
oh i just noticed
and
[Music]
anything um there's a magnifying glass
that we can use but it's in the other
map we're watching
he's watching yeah
[Music]
though oh there you go
all right if you guys could take a seat
please i like you too
[Music]
um
so what you're talking about
hold on i need to hold on babe
i need to
change cameras
[Applause]
[Music]
you can stand if you like especially
since chairs don't really work well for
you
um
she sounds like a girl
all right
yeah
[Music]
like that
this this this version of bae has seen
things
[Music]
she's seen things and she's uh
i'm being sliced into pieces right now
and i'm going to say cronus
okay all right
um okay everybody welcome to the spooky
spooky timeline as you can see we have a
big yago here and we could uh actually
this report is used to talk to the great
spirit of yago but unfortunately it
seems like we've misplaced the little
planchette i believe it's called uh so
it's not here but
i thought instead of talking to the
spirits we could tell some ghost stories
do you guys know any ghost stories
yes tell us
tell us your ghost story you ever seen a
ghost before
yeah
okay
once i was driving down a winding dark
road and i saw a lady and she had no
face
so i hit her and she turned into a ghost
no
she turned into a ghost
did you kill me
turned into a ghost
[Music]
i was also in the car i wasn't driving
enough because i can't reach the pedals
uh and uh i think it was with my mom we
were coming home from somewhere it was
really really dark and then all of a
sudden across the road there was this
like mist of some sort that had no
beginning and end it was just in the
center of the road and we drove right
through it and we try really hard
to we ever see something and it it takes
you by such surprise that it leaves you
speechless for a little while yes
yeah like that that's what happened it
was it was it was kind of genuine fear
for a second uh but we're trying to
think of what it could have been and
there's no way it could have been
smoke right because smoke
it you would have seen it fizzle or how
would it have traveled out into the road
like that without any
well how would it have lived that long
you know but it's really scary and i
don't know how to explain it or i don't
have any other ways to explain what it
could have been
oh that is scary that's scary
it's pretty spooky in the car so you
guys are in the safe here
yeah but ghosts can go through walls
i look
like us like a kind of spooky story but
it's like from a thing it's like a book
i'm not gonna read it but like i can
recount it to you
yeah yeah
like are we allowed to do that you get
in trouble
i think it's okay it should be okay
yeah okay gotcha
so basically here's how it goes
all right
here's how are you okay kiara
i looked at the chat for one second i
just had to laugh
oh that's a mistake
all right
so
there's this girl right
and she's at a gas station she's filling
up gas in her car it's just a normal day
getting off of work you know the usual
and then she decides it's time to go
home as any other sane human would you
go to work you go to home just a typical
day
right
she finishes getting the gas in her car
settles down in her little seat
gets ready to drive away yeah i hear it
too gets ready to drive away why is that
uh
i don't know
i i hear it coming from your area yeah i
think it's here she gets she takes a
little seat gets ready to drive away
and she heads off down
excuse me
i'm sorry
you're good you're fine you're fine
you get
takes a little seat in the car right oh
and musty and spooky road and she's on
like a countryside roads there's no one
around until she realizes that she's
being followed stop oh my god no way
someone is following her i know someone
is following her up yeah that's right
there's a car that's hot on her tail and
it's been following her in fact for a
while she realizes that i've been
following her okay
ever since the gas station
oh my god it was even weirder about this
car
yeah that's right if you remember the
gas station there was a dude and he
followed
there's a car you're envisioning your
head now there's another car there's one
car here there's a car here and they're
going down the road and it's dark
outside and then the car behind her this
innocent victim starts flashing his
lights flash flash flash over and over
again over and over again oh man body
motion surplus what what could it mean
what could it mean she doesn't look good
but she's starting to get real scared
because she's got
another 30 minutes left to drive all the
way home so she keeps driving and the
the dude just keeps flashing the lights
flash flash flash what does it mean we
don't know
she gets very scared and decides i need
to call the police i need to call them
so they'll be ready when i get to my
house this dude's going to kill me he's
going to jump out of his car and and
then and then hold on i got i got my
effect my special effect he's going to
come out of the car
and and stabbed
like that
no it's too scared of that happening
right you can stab with a chainsaw yeah
so so she decides
oh no she did she gets pretty mad at him
but he like doesn't care and so and so
she keeps going and he keeps flashing
eventually if she gets home she runs out
of her car the police are there they all
pull up and she runs out of her car and
the guy pulls up in his car
and he comes out and he's just a normal
dude
and he says ma'am are you okay she says
what are you talking about
my man says
there's a dude in the back seat of your
car
getting ready to stab you
every time he was about to stab you i
flashed the light
and then they caught the guy in the back
[Music]
yeah it's my story thank you callie
thanks kelly
[Music]
okay that i mean that counts
yeah
[Laughter]
hey
i mean they're scary
um you accidentally you accidentally
step step on the floor and you actually
step on the center feet
[Music]
a furry spider like a furry spider was
once in my eyes
[Music]
we were i was like walking past
my
bedroom
and then
i had i was doing something but i had
direct vision into my bedroom
um and then i was just staring at the
ground and then suddenly out of nowhere
a huge like black fighter just crawled
under my bed and then
i didn't do anything
did you find it
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah
yeah i'm only showing five percent does
anybody else have a scary story yeah
[Music]
did you see me
um
my my my chickens already know about
this
yeah
sorry sorry
oh okay i was um
i was living in japan until a while ago
and um
i
i moved after after joining whole life
uh uh i moved into a big big
house
but the house was
very very uh
old it was that when you walked on the
wood it would make sounds like
wait wait wait
right
oh
it was really really old that it had a
lot of
it had a lot of uh issues to it but well
it was a big two-story house all for
myself so i was like i'm just gonna try
my best to ignore that it's uh looking
really
old so
the first night
arrives and i'm i'm like yeah i got this
whole house to myself and i was trying
to chill but i was hearing noises
from the ceiling it was like
[Laughter]
[Music]
but i was i immediately contacted my my
landlord and he was like yeah there
there might be some history of ghosts in
this house but please don't worry about
it
some ghost exterminators
ghost extermin
a few days later
um the the ghostbusters came by and all
those days i i heard the ghosts like
continuously not only in the night but
also during the day and was kind of
freaking me out because i was also
trying to stream but it was i was
hearing it on the first floor and on the
second floor and on the in the side of
the walls and in the bottom and on the
top everyone
so
uh the ghost experience they came and
they looked into the ceiling and they
they saw the ghosts they saw the ghosts
really and they said that it's like
they saw like about
freako animals three ghosts three no no
no girls
and they actually have gold
ghost poison what's that you cast me
that's right girl this is salt
and they put that
they put the ghost poison in the ceiling
and then they closed it and they they
were like okay kiara you call us and
tell us call the ghostbusters and tell
us how the poison worked
and then a few days later i did start
hearing less
[Music]
so i called again and i was like yo
ghostbusters i'm calling you because who
else would i call
right girls ghostbusters they say all
right
again and they looked inside and they
found the ghost of two ghosts the bodies
are the ghosts of two ghosts
oh i see i see
ahahaha
apparently those two ghosts of the
ghosts where um the parent ghosts of the
ghosts that survived
it was weird because they added they
kept them trying to add poison for the
last surviving ghost but it seems like
that ghost has started to form some kind
of immunity
and uh we tried many times but it didn't
didn't work and then one time for
example i was sick i think
with the door open because i had it it
was like such a tiny idol meeting room
that it's like almost impossible to
close the door
oh
my god
didn't you say that the ghost like ate
your food once yes
yes
that's
terrific i don't know if you've heard of
it the ghosts are apparently um uh uh
not they don't like eating chocolate
because they will kill
in the end i started to accept the fact
that i'm living with a ghost and
actually we're best friends now and the
ghost name is casper
guest
[Music]
so yeah
she's collapsing in on herself
come on
[Applause]
[Music]
i know
she can't hear us
it might help um purge the ghost if you
want to play on desktop that's okay too
because i know you're feeling a little
sick so yeah if you want i will read
about you okay
if you're feeling too sick okay okay
all right
she'll be back
she'll be really easy just get comfy
yeah
[Music]
comfy get comfy sit down relax
you can hug
she'll be back maybe we should go to the
summoning circle to summon her a shark
maybe yeah
did you leave some of the the
the ghost poison around
i think they're pretending to be like an
owl
i think there's something wrong with
fish
many different animals
for a second
sounds like a whale
[Music]
yeah she can totally hear me
i'm assuming she's talking about me
uh
i'm concerned
ladies
and gentlemen hey callie
how are you
hi dude
what's up
i
for things like this but you know oh
yeah that's a fun time
what else
you know yeah i play dead you guys want
to hear another story oh yeah mine's
wrong
yeah i can tell you guys it's not a
spooky story but it's a it's terrifying
all right cool thank yous yeah um all
right so here's the story have you guys
heard the story of the crunch bird the
crunch bird what
the story of the french bird long ago
yeah i remember it was a crunchy bird
and father told me can't see it i know
it sounds like that's right
right exactly like you can imagine a big
scary phoenix
basically
crunch bird my grandfather told me this
story it's been passed down in reaper
legends for generations so basically
there's this couple and they decide that
they want to have a pet right they
decide it's finally time to get
themselves um a pet of their own because
you know they've been living alone can't
have kids that kind of thing so uh so
they've decided okay we're gonna go you
know off to the pet shop so the
husband's really busy he's working and
so he tells his wife go ahead and get us
a pet he doesn't care what it is he says
whatever is fine right so the wife goes
to the pet store and uh is kind of
talking with the pet clerk and she's
like i wonder what would be good you
know a dog a cat hamster all very cute
but
hear me out how about a bird and so the
the shop clerk because all right i got
some birds i'll show you some birds
takes her to the back starts showing her
the birds and she's like oh these are
all very fine birds but what's that one
in the back there's this big cage in the
back it's got this huge foul beast of a
creature inside of it he says oh that's
the crunch everything's way too
dangerous yeah crunch bird is what it's
called you can call it whatever you want
but i call it the crunch bird and she
says well why do you call it the crunch
bird he's like do you really want to
know she says
yeah i really want to know he's like do
you really want to know she's like yeah
i really want to know show me the bird
really
all right and and he says crunch bird
table
and
exactly that's why it's called crush
bird iris i can see your pantsuit all
right
he says
next he says crunch bird crushed bird
chair the crunch goes
and it destroys the chair
all right so now the chair is destroyed
and so the wife says you know what this
is a dangerous animal but i think it's
got i think it's got potential you know
it's got like
it's different you know it's not just
like your run-of-the-mill usual uh pet
and i think my husband might have
potential
exactly it's got that potential real
special pet potential try saying that
ten times fast real special pet
potential special pep it's probably not
that hard so so she says you know what
fine i'll take the crunch first and um
and he he they do the exchange she gives
them the money he gives the bird right
she takes the bird back home sets up the
cage gets it all nice for her husband to
come back home
now husband walks through the door and
he sees this foul beast in the corner
and he says what the f word is that
can't say the f word we have children
watching possibly so she has to show you
she opens the door and lets the crunch
bird out
and she and he says what can you tell me
what on earth is this thing she says
oh it's a crunch bird he says crunch
bird my ass
[Music]
welcome back
hi
[Music]
not that good beautiful this is
something that i experienced
oh no
so a family member and i were just you
know chilling out in our room and at
exactly 12 a.m
uh
the phone started ringing so i said oh
wow
why would friends call you at this hour
that's really disrespectful
and then
and then she looked at me
and said that
that's not my ringtone
and
the the song that was playing uh was
pretty much all about
uh like i've been everywhere searching
for you
where have you been
because i see you like
are you hiding somewhere in the crowd
and
and then we got kind of creeped out we
uh picked up the phone and and
it stopped playing
and then suddenly at every night
exactly at 12
that same ringtone was happening
and that was that was not the ringtone
that she said and
later on she decided to delete the song
from her phone
and it still kept playing
and
and then we had some
interesting events taking place such as
how when i was all alone in the house i
would hear
a piano key
a single
piano key just going ding ding
i would go and check it out nobody's
there or
i'd be all alone in my room and my dog
uh who's in the same room would
look at whatever's at the end of the
hallway
and i keep trying to call their call ty
mutt's name and
they won't
they won't turn their head it's fixated
at whatever is at the end of the hallway
everything was pitch black
uh yeah
um
that that phone kept ringing
and maybe something about that house was
weird um
[Laughter]
just the prank bro oh
[Music]
and that same family member had
some other experience where
they would have nightmares
about how they can't move but they would
be in a fire or they would get shot some
a lot of nightmares every single day
or sometimes a woman like crawling over
the ceiling really fast just to look at
your face
[Music]
everything that's on the ceiling is
haunted no
yeah like a ceiling fan
and then later on that was when she was
living alone and when she decided to
live
with her family again
this time she couldn't move again in the
dream but
uh at her bedside she saw
a woman with all her face covered
and she you know with the hair and
everything and she said oh you know what
i see that you're with your family now
and
because of then
i won't bother you again
i hope you haven't talked to you like
that oh yeah yeah and afterwards
that's kind of nice yeah after that she
never had those strains where she's
paralyzed in her sleep
oh she was lonely sleeping
[Music]
experience of being in sleep paralysis
take the chair
take the chair does anybody else have
another story they could sit in the
mirror but
i'm gonna tell you something
[Music]
so
we're going to just move into groups and
the senpai's will be scaring the koala
highs so
[Music]
group b so if group a is going to be
council you guys just step on over here
for a moment all the way over here to
the left or to your right
thank you and we have miss and iris over
here
[Music]
okay
the way this is gonna work is um i'm
gonna send you guys counsel don't go
into the maze yet but i want you guys to
go all the way over there to the other
side um where the summoning circle is
and if you guys could wait over there uh
that'd be great thank you guys
[Music]
you guys if you go to your avatars that
you can select you have a few different
options you have two different options
um and what you can be you guys are
gonna be monsters and you're gonna hide
in the maze
as they enter in and try to spook them
just don't go too far into the maze we
don't want you to complete it just pick
a corner once you get in there and then
uh you can surprise them there are some
little hidden alcoves in the maze as
well
you guys can i mean like this
yes
i like that oh my god oh dear
[Music]
between
oh yeah look at this oh t-posing
recalibrate
disturbing predator apex surprisingly
let me let me pose real quick if you
guys could just
hear uh momentarily do not
[Laughter]
don't follow me just uh stay here mom
and oh god
knocking here hold on
i can show the full extent of my rap
moves here
oh
[Music]
don't go too far just pick a corner pick
a chord
and uh try not to go too far into the
maze and we can get you out easily when
it's your guys it's time to switch okay
you guys are there to scare them so you
know use your scary balls
you can explore the maze but not too
deep okay
okay don't go past the uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh do we go through
okay guys don't don't go past the dark
part don't go past the black section
okay okay okay
okay i'm gonna give you guys if you guys
can hear me i'm gonna give you 30
seconds and then i'm going to release
them into the maze
this is the dark part
that's the dark part
this is the dark parco
i always sit here
okay okay
yo yo what's up dad
welcome to my crib
in english
are you whispering
in what i am whispering
coming through amen coming through
i may come in
[Music]
all right council uh you guys can go
ahead and enter the maze
[Music]
oh
scars
six packs
don't touch my abs don't touch my hands
listen to kids
[Music]
oh
uh
[Music]
my god
oh that's so scary
[Music]
you will never
hey no i'm a scary monster all right um
[Music]
i've been sitting here for 10 minutes
oh thank you welcome hello
hi
i can't see you come here
i am a little frog
come here
i think you should change
oh
what's up you guys want to take a selfie
again oh my goodness
right now
let's take a selfie come on come on come
here come here let's take a selfie
i was keep posing all right
oh yeah
i gotta recalibrate
what's up
in my book
[Music]
oh yeah look at have a
oh yeah
i just saw some shark bud what so cute
[Music]
oh my god
selfies
[Music]
join us
[Applause]
[Music]
do not go into the box
find the uh find the exit
oh that's not the exit we're going oh
are we going yeah i think so i don't
know where the exit is
[Music]
i think it's this way
we go through here
follow the voice
that's the guy
oh my god
tiara is
see i was i was chilling in the corner
for the longest time
[Music]
i was supposed to scare her
you're talking
oh yeah
so who's back hey guys
oh my god
the shark back
council there's still
more of them
all right let me take your chat
let's go cali okay let's go all right
kelly shark bro let's go let's go wait i
should do a selfie mode
all right let's go shark bro
welcome to the shark bro blog
halloween vlogs we're here
yeah
juniors yo shark bros
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
yeah i guess we gotta go guys yeah let's
go oh look at that taco
i don't know if you guys can see a taco
dachy this is what vlogging feels like
what the camera
must be you're getting really good at it
oh yeah look at this look at this
[Music]
i'm just following the giant giant white
ghost
all
right and cali follow me
you guys can exit movie go into there
you can go in there and where are you
guys
oh hello
[Music]
i am lost
yeah let's all take a selfie
let's take a selfie here no bros join me
shark family let's please yeah
yeah let's go
let's go
flex
[Music]
[Applause]
this looks like
[Laughter]
the frog the frontal part of the frog is
really kitty kitty like
oh i can't i can't show this
i can't show this
spare me
so much
oh what a beautiful sky here today
oh god
oh my god i can't
oh my god oh no that looks no
oh
god
what's happening she's
possessed oh she's back
oh they're back
hello
you guys missed the party
oh my god
you guys are back
everybody's back okay we're gonna
it was worth it
[Laughter]
work
[Music]
oh
over here guys
oh my god we're turning red over here
red tomorrow today
[Music]
you could go into your ui settings and
turn off name plates if you guys don't
if it's only for emails
okay now you guys switch back to your
normal avatars please all right
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh there she is
welcome back
[Music]
uh you guys stay here and face the crony
grave and i will come back and get you
all right
[Music]
selfie time
my favorite time
hey
join me come on there's a camera right
there
[Music]
sunglasses
yeah i don't know about you guys i
really liked those um i really like
those shark and like frog costumes
because they felt like they gave me the
expression to be myself oh yeah like you
can't see my full dance moves with the
small eno like right exactly i wonder
where the model is
[Music]
there's nothing random about that
destiny
this
[Music]
[Applause]
it all started
with sea creatures with a frog in the
shot let's see
creature
out of the frog and the shark came a
dinosaur now the dinosaur came to monkey
hold on it's silver
[Music]
oh
that's what i said
wasn't it oh really
yeah but is she original i feel like
that's a meme like a chap i don't know i
don't even know maybe i remember i
remember
seeing it yeah yeah she said that yeah
well i don't know where she has it from
maybe it's original
i'm like so dead is this a descent by
cursor we're just i don't know too old
for this
it might be i feel like i've descended
[Music]
and get all the way to the end okay
there's an end
all right let's go guys enjoy
the dark area too
yes oh my god
all the way to the end
[Music]
what's this
[Laughter]
oh my god kelly's just like babe just
walks
it's a mushroom
[Laughter]
oh thank you i got your heart
big red heart
i hear asmr though
all right
you found a big red heart there you go
you can have my heart
[Music]
oh no i'm just sitting check out his
yeah do you check out his blood path oh
i'm following the blood path
all right i'm still following the blood
i'm following the blood ooh there's a
candle okay bro there's a candle i got
you bro i got your backpack uh
oh my man nice okay cool yeah
oh all right this is actually kind of
spooky uh no i don't know man uh you're
good bro bro we got this bro we're
already there we're already here we're
here all right all right
oh man yo well man do you see those
footprints coming yeah yeah man
yeah man did you not know have you not
seen like opening no i thought it was
just uh just a myth bro
oh man no you gotta you gotta check oh
no
oh wow
um
oh wow bro
have you seen this bro
are you seeing this big what does that
you will give her
your big
red heart
oh she's got some uh um
she's got some nice she's got something
she certainly has a big red heart right
right here she has two big ones
do you know what i'm talking about bro
[Music]
yo yo yo let's take a selfie with her
yeah let me try yeah take a selfie man
where's the selfie button here yeah
first yeah we're explorers my dude
oh no that's not the selfie button uh
no
that's the return to the origin buzz
i almost got it all right that's the
selfie button bro bro
all right here we go
[Music]
[Laughter]
that was actually kind of creepy
just ran off
[Music]
yeah i mean
oh
[Music]
is she carrying like fruit
yeah melons
[Music]
big red hearts
i'll give her my bigger heart here you
go
[Music]
[Applause]
come in
who is this
[Music]
oh my god
pineapples
kelly
kelly is good
you okay
right up to my face
your face
[Music]
let's
go oh my god where's the exit what a
journey this has been
[Music]
there's something um us
oh my god oh it's right here oh okay
this left this way bro
gally bro you okay
this way i can kind of hear this here
you are my man okay i got you
[Laughter]
[Music]
i think we made it oh we're here
you guys look like your names are gary
me
me yeah yeah
what's up oh there's only one rat here
i don't know i'm uh i'm kind of getting
like a marv did i hear something
i heard something marv
marvel
you're too early marv
[Music]
hello
can you see this
can you see
candy
[Music]
oh yes yes we have a special premiere
that we are going to be watching in the
auditorium and we're going to go up
there
[Music]
return to lobby
oh there we go
okay so the auditorium
feel free to bring some light sticks
[Music]
uh set the camera
let's go let's go let's go
this is pretty good the second one
maybe i want a second round
i'll wait until everybody's here i'll
get up on the stage real quick to make a
quick announcement
all right oh i fell off the stage
okay no
sit oh you guys are welcome to take a
seat you can stand if you like um okay
so originally we're gonna have some
performances but uh it looks like it
didn't work out in time if anybody does
want to perform now's your chance you
could do show and tell you maybe you
want to show us you can juggle or maybe
you want to sing an acapella too does
anybody want to come up anybody any
volunteers
no i have stage fright i'm okay
okay well we do have uh for chat and for
you guys here in the crowd we have a
special music video premiere
music video
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
so if you guys want to get a good view a
good seat now's a good time i'm going to
turn
[Music]
[Applause]
seen this it's a well-kept secret oh
yeah
and pope
hasn't seen it
hasn't seen it either i don't think
yeah i haven't seen it you guys is the
screen let me pull up a chair
here we go looks great
hold on any second all right my light
stick is a sideways don't mind me
let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
[Music]
fairies
our faces
[Music]
[Applause]
hungry dinosaur just one tiny bite
[Music]
[Applause]
happy halloween
[Music]
um it will premiere on my channel so you
guys after the stream if you want to
re-watch it you can go there and
re-watch it as many times as you'd like
and
[Music]
definitely
callie wrote the lyrics
and also
the music video animator made such good
use of everybody's models made by sea
phone husks off and also twilight 3d
it's so awesome so many people worked on
it so thank you everybody that worked on
it thank you so much thank you guys for
watching
[Music]
oh
in the
[Music]
background in the closet tonight
[Applause]
[Music]
radiant
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
please
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
so good
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
you're telling me
oh
we're gonna jam out a little bit and
then we'll say goodbye to everybody you
guys
have some cool screenshots so dance
together waltz together hold each
other's hands hug each other whatever
you want to do dance on the table
[Music]
please how do i oh there's a
i don't know
oh
[Music]
um
thank you
[Music]
what's wrong with the cameras
here we go
oh
thank you guys for watching the
halloween stream i hope you guys
[Music]
thank you
okay give me one second
bye-bye
[Music]
give me a second
i want to play the credits
um
[Music]
okay
there we go
[Music]
chad thanks for watching have a good
night
[Music]
you