foreign
[Music]
assistant
foreign
[Music]
assistant
thank you
[Music]
answers
laughs
ah
yes
[Laughter]
okay I'm switching
wow hello hello
we're here we're ready
we will be as bad as we could be
as ready as possible hey look you know
what let it be said that we tried man I
grinded in this game we've been here two
we've been practicing yes yes I don't
know it's doing pretty good we weren't
doing well I don't think we lost yeah we
had some good battles we were too strong
together
well I found the BC buff
yeah true true movies
I will be taking over yeah MC for today
let me introduce you to the stream
today's stream if you're not aware is
the pre Pokemon World Championship
events
hey thank you for inviting us yeah yes
thank you huge thank you for including
thank you very much thank you thank you
exciting the first Pokemon unite World
Championship to be held in Asia we'll
start tomorrow from August 11th to 12th
in Yokohama and in the Pokemon unite
category teams from all around the world
will fight for their championship and we
will also be fighting for championship
against Indonesia and JP we're
presenting team hello Ian this is a
series
here for our team I am serious fauna
I'll be taking the Pokemon Wiggly tough
as full of support we also have Miss
Calliope Mori would you like to
introduce yourself hi everybody Mork
Clive here
um I will be playing as uh Garchomp
jungler
um I will be jungler or I uh I will feed
[Laughter]
I will be mid laner excuse me
all right Iris Would you like to
introduce yourself uh hiris is Iris I
will be uh using glacial and today
elevation's wearing very cute clothes
and I will be bottom today
all right next up we have takanashi
Kiara hi hello
um I am representing every European out
there who is currently awake at 4 5 or 6
a.m I've been staying awake but I'm very
awake still so I think I will be fine
let's come buddy muscle I'm doing alola
nine tails because yeah what else
but it'll be great it'll be great
we also have Amelia Watson please
introduce yourself hello Amelia Watson
number one detective today I'll be your
tank yes rely on me please
oh yes I'm going top with uh Kiara yes
vital yeah yeah so it's my bodyguard
yeah
well there it's only a little bit of
time left before the world championship
I'm sure everyone is very last
championship oh wait yeah well for today
there's only two a few minutes left
so how about we watch the PV together
okay I'll do a little countdown and we
can all share it on our streams okay
okay I hope I don't blast your guys's
ears it's the start to start one yeah
first one
three two one go our summer starts now
wow it's real it is amazing I love the
animation Yeah
I broke the budget for this one whoa
can you name all these Pokemons
candy
cronies it kind of looks like
did you see her I wish I looked this
cool when playing Pokemon I know right
we will we'll look this cool yeah we're
just holding our switch procons exactly
time
I did not recognize that fish Pokemon
was that something new
I know which one you mean there's so
many being shown right now
[Music]
[Applause]
it's fun to show anime on our screen
yeah with permission right I know
permission wow
uh let's move on over to the event
overview I believe we are ready
[Music]
but I'm not I'm not ready I'm ready oh
wait wait the slides uh the the the
slides right yes
wait a second wait a second
[Laughter]
these slides wait it says here we're
first this is wrong it says Ian first
one is what's the change
differently yeah we'll see a second and
we thought that that was a good idea
because you know
we gonna play right now stop son can you
find out for us if this is accurate
right now and we'll just talk over it
for now
hello I have a Pokemon unite World
Tournament is a promotional event for
the Pokemon u9 category of the world
championship 2023 oh I have a whole life
English and whole life Indonesia will
battle head to head to settle who will
shine on top hopefully it'll be us
the three matches will be JP versus id
id versus Ian and JP versus Ian and the
match will follow the WCS rules and
therefore Mewtwo will be banned oh wait
are you guys showing the slides sorry
yes yeah yes
it shows like it's like black wait wait
reopen this it's okay for me yeah reopen
and in a case of a three-way tie the
team who scores the most will be crowned
the winner
so okay tournaments go
the winner wins
wins and the losers I think there's
there should be like something right
consolation prizes
mm-hmm
next slide
oh please thank you okay I was picking
up prizes speaking of prizes
the MVPs each team will be awarded with
like real physical prizes the WCS
official uniforms which are not for sale
exclusive
wearing the Pokemon United
and other teams will be awarded with 2D
trophies according to their placements
I know which one we're getting
let's go yeah
difference in color that's all you know
yeah something different except for the
color if it's just on our screen no one
will know yeah they'll think we're the
winners
just because there's a bad shirt though
yeah me too I love sporting well
speaking of the shirt our characters in
game are also wearing this shirt which
you can also purchase yourself from the
shop the digital version in the in-game
store
we are going first seems like it yeah
apparently okay
by fire here we go we were doing good
just remember how we were playing okay
I don't know if I think it's just
because just because it's the JP okay
his JP team it's fine okay pretty darn
sweaty though no problem no problem it
can be sweaty too just gotta get the
mindset you know energy isn't
precipitation and here are the other
participants for the tournament from JP
we have okay
[Laughter]
later
oh yes
[Music]
[Applause]
um
be full but they're cuteness they're
scary
yes they are scary I mean we're supposed
to be Laura Wise you know like Gods and
Men oh my God we should be pretty right
right amen
including one one detective one British
girl
the most mythical of creatures
I know in Hollow yeah and I've really
been wanting I guess we have we got on
me we have British women
[Music]
yes I missed hearing your British accent
you don't bring it out very often you
know
I wish you would let your natural accent
shine sometimes
[Music]
it's okay I'll try it
next slide
first
[Music]
oh yeah
what well how do we get into the room
uh they will send a code and we will
input the code make sure not to show it
on stream I love how the order of the
matches it makes it seem like the whole
alive JP and ID are like the the finals
and I get to sleep early if yeah I mean
yeah I can sleep nah probably stay awake
anyway though let's be real let's be
honest
and call me if you need help please just
say Maury
were you losing your lane matchup you
know who to call
the code will be provided to us
the
should we do we wait until they are oh
it looks like they are they're going
okay okay we go there yeah wait are they
are we is there a Lobby already the all
regions Channel it looks like okay to
produce it for introductions yes
okay we go we go let's go do it really
is it really daijo boo really ID isn't
going
I just went
I'm nervous it's just you and me
do we go in I guess so let's check
what's going on if they kick us out
[Music]
um
foreign
[Laughter]
thank you Kiara yeah
come at me
[Laughter]
can you hear me
please check the volume okay it's okay
[Music]
she will
motivation
[Laughter]
um
team leader please share your feelings
now
I'm feeling motivated confident and we
need to go into this with optimism
we've been practicing believe in
yourself I'm proud of you hope your kids
have been climbing the ranks you can be
let's go JP and ID team yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
motivation gaps but it's okay
foreign
[Music]
already started right the gong the
gongling game
yeah there is
everyone here
oh
[Applause]
yes
oh
my tummy hurts
some food
it will be daijubu
yeah don't be nervous
so we're going first
yes
we're both the first met we're yeah
we're the first two matches and then
they do the finals amongst I will
crumble
is that the code okay
yeah I hope it's over quickly
[Music]
yeah there's your code
okay I gotta hide okay I hide yes hide
code Avi search
okay I searched the lobby
I'm in the lobby
oh I think it said something like we're
supposed to be
uh uh like at top
or at bottom like there's a specific
order they want us to be in
really yeah it was in the in the like
explanation thingy but now that the
order has changed I'm confused too
but maybe we're in the right spot
because I think it said Yen up for the
first one and Ian down for the second
one
[Music]
let's go with that yeah yeah
okay then now we can show it Go
panicking aloud okay no panicking play
it safe play cool
um for Cali as usual okay wait so are we
gonna go for top objective first or
bottom or we're not gonna decide we need
to be aggressive I think
should we decide on that beforehand yeah
yeah it might be situational depending
on where the others are okay
um I should be high enough level at a
certain point where I can kind of guard
the bottom and then also take out the
bottom objective by myself if I do the
jungle correctly
oh okay there is that but it will be
good
stay out of my jungle please
start to storm bus and then get our
first our first uh
goal down and then they also get an
objective we can try to go and steal
their Farm in the jungle okay in the
wilderness we'll wait your command
apparently um jpg struggles against
aggressive players so we really need to
play aggressive okay let's play
aggressive
not too early not too early okay we
could show the screen now right yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah aggressive but
safe
um
it'll be fine it'll be fun I wonder how
our team comp is I wonder if it's
supposed to be levels though for sure
yep
um and then oh my God can we try to be
not like screaming all the time because
it will freak me out yeah okay okay okay
yeah we'll be calm just like we're
playing against the bot so that we can
also hear fauna clearly when she wants
something from us right
on too okay so Dragon Claw is the meta
but I'm going with earthquake so that I
can take out the bigger Farms of swablu
and alteria so and also attack from a
bit more of a distance who's going who's
going Bottom with me I'm going Bottom
okay
just like I hope I hope my galicians
better than their glacier
we got this no problem here we go have
confidence
Let's go Team let's go just like
practice just like we practiced just
slap oh God my hands are so sweaty
already
I'm in pain
office really quick I'll use it again
later
for the middle go for the middle I mean
oh gosh darn it oh see they're here ah
they are here of course they're here why
are they here do you need help I think
I'm okay they stole one with me though
okay did they steal it I don't know what
do we do next do we attack them I am
useless until level five
poke a little bit okay
let's go again you're scared
[Music]
just don't let them steal it don't let
them steal it ah I think I still think
they did
going back to rest one second
okay
who needs more help bottom or top oh my
God we're doing okay we're doing fine
right now
I need to commit um
okay
nice nice skills
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay
this thing traps you damn yeah
um we should commit I'm gonna quickly
lifesteal okay
[Music]
nice Kelly
okay nice nice nice
and a little guard here let's take it
down here yeah yeah let's go
score
steal the farm hold on oh scissor
scissor dude they're higher level
okay I need to level up dude's almost
dead though oh damn it good job okay I'm
lagging pretty bad she on this bag oh no
oh shoot okay hold on no one's dead
right now right okay and I'm lagging I'm
gonna go grab Center Farm yeah go ahead
we can hold I should be able to get some
life steel as well yeah and pop this
really quickly the objectives are up in
40 seconds
um
should I join down there
[Music]
don't attack yet
I think they're gonna go for bottom yeah
they're going for bottom should we
should we interrupt I think we should
try to steal it
okay let's try steal it okay
you guys can okay good um
like distract them
don't die don't die um
let's go
okay let's not play too aggressive oh
man I'm back yeah play safe places hey
welcome back go back if you have to
I don't want to grab Center form again
hold on oh actually yeah
you think they're gonna steal it
they might but we could grab it we could
grab it we got it we got it you got it
nice we got it but we have to protect it
uh they're all here all right I'm coming
let's go I'm coming let's go top they're
there it's okay let's go over here okay
we're coming we're coming
it's okay no problem yummy
where's Umbreon
it's fine it's fine don't worry don't
worry
I can't really fight uh um
it's okay just uh be the bouncy person
okay just be bouncy
I'm gonna back up I see you yeah ideally
we don't want to fight on there there
yeah if we can I'm trying to get out but
I'm lagging oh no I'm sorry it's okay
we'll be fine
all right I'm coming I'm coming
oh they're scissors you're gonna pop an
oat real quick hold on can't do anything
hold on okay
nice I'm so sorry
oh did one die is someone die right
sorry
but I also died too we're good
they also died
one of them I got greedy I got really
good with my little teeth okay let's
let's be let's try to run
back run back my game is updating real
sorry about that guys I will be back
okay let me get over here and help
nice actually
hold on let me grab above the bottom
glaze down scoring bottom okay hold on
um I think it's about to go bottom
is pretty darn scary oh God okay
committed too much
I think I think we need to farm a little
I think we're focusing too yeah I'm
trying to fight them yeah uh he's bad
girl no they're they're trying to kill
me all right hold on yeah we can try to
get them
but I can hold it I can hold her you can
try to hold bottom yeah wait what level
are we is everyone higher than us no
they're Nine and Nine yeah nine nine
okay
and eleven oh shoot okay I got surprised
uh and then it's the voice snuggle
behind me
nice nice very good we gotta keep it up
I'm gonna go back to bottom
okay xion is good
I don't know who to who's what I know
who I know I can't pop a speed ah yeah I
really need to drop my scores though
yeah we shouldn't get greedy
right now okay let's go bottom they're
oh they just got they just got ready
guys okay let me uh okay hold on a
second nobody was coming to rescue
okay I should have known they were down
there I was not paying attention to the
map
thanks guys I will be there in a second
oh I need to be a higher level this is
not how I feel like this is crazy okay
[Music]
did you go that way
oh
right
right oh shoot [\h__\h] they're totally uh
I'm dead okay
hold on
I'm not high enough level yet yeah we
should be careful about team fights I
think I think we need to because there's
only two minutes left actually we should
oh God okay get ready we should defend I
think I'll go back okay should I go down
or up I'm just gonna get a buffalo are
going up yeah but we might need it we
probably need to take my breakfast
already oh my God the time the time this
is going so fast play safe okay so we
got the full attack we're all here we're
all here I think we should be here let's
go let's go it's almost dead
okay
we got it we gotta try to score
I have something to score oh we should
defend if we can too okay oh they're
they're totally yeah
[Music]
why am I scoring here I don't know
it works no it doesn't work
ah
um
where did they come from
there's like three of them oh God I'm
dead I'm dead I'm dead oh damn it
hey but we didn't do that bad
we're pretty good in the beginning it
was a good match for them makes mistakes
here and there we did we did I don't
know we just have to stop them from uh
depositing points and we can still put
in okay we might be even right now
um
I'll defend I'll stay and defend if you
guys go 31 seconds I have no point I
don't know if that's enough to go over I
was willing to risk it
the hell got me at least they hey I
distracted them
right now I think I'm out of this is the
bottom no they were all the way to the
right at their home bases so I probably
can't
[Music]
inside
next match
good job good job
I'm proud of you guys I thought that was
pretty good yeah if we got the records
yeah and it was closed it was close
because we were I think I need to farm
so
it's kind of rough but yeah anyway
um
maybe check chat for one second
yeah I I need to farm more I'm like
going inside my presence from the Ambush
um
I meant Discord not so we're leaving the
lobby right
are we playing again immediately yeah
immediately yeah we're warmed up it's
true but my hands are shaking I know
controllers I'm sorry Chad oh is there
already a room is there a room
another one what about now Chad
I thought it was just super quiet champ
[Music]
okay wait do we still have a chance
right yeah okay
yeah we do we do we're only behind 200
points as long as we'll see how ideas oh
they're adding like buddy
oh yeah
oh well yeah they know they know our
cards
it's true they watched that is true they
have that
okay
damn it I think I know and I thought
we'd be in that position or this next
one yeah
yeah I think in that one team fights
were our weakness because we weren't
arriving all at the same time yeah yeah
gotta make sure not to start and I was
doing this
before everyone arrived oh whoops I'm
sorry wait hold on is this the wrong
wait
oh they went to the wrong one
um yeah I will try and help if I can but
I really need to try to focus more on
farming yeah yeah you're a late game mom
so you can focus on farms and we can
just try in the
try to defend yourself I'll try to help
if I can though yeah yeah
since you're looking at the time a lot
um oh yeah we just need to remember so
seven minutes for subjective unlocks and
then in two minutes Rayquaza so around
like 30 seconds or a minute before that
we got to be prepared yeah like at at
three hours three Thirty don't use your
old I think
when there's yeah 3 30 left okay
how do I move my position wait
I'll be here are we supposed to be
bottom this time yeah I think so they
were all on top so
it seems like it but I don't know
it's fine
we missing fauna
oh yeah I okay
okay
um
yeah I I get so tunnel visioned and I
don't really get what was like after I
get to a certain level I'm just like
what should I do now yeah I think just
stay with the team or yeah
they also focus on leveling in the
beginning because Evie is weak as hell
in the beginning and yeah I have to wait
until I get to like at least level six
or seven to get ice shard
yeah
I think it too
we were focusing a lot on finding them
and we probably should have just been
staying back and farming yeah
yeah
we can try that too
okay okay okay
I'm pretty sure I did like I think Raina
was using it that bear thing um I forgot
there there's a bear yeah there's a bear
maybe she was only using it for that
stream I don't know but
they were going with like a pretty
pretty
meta-ish I think I forgot
I've got your back so just show the
screen I forgot about that okay okay I'm
glad you're back so cute I'm going to
focus on being the strongest
good buff
whoa
good work no
I gave up on Lapras
is doing really well with Glacier we
need more we needed more um Power
anyways I think Lapras is too too weak
for this
comp
and also also because Lapras did not
have much outfits yes
those are a really cute outfit yeah you
really don't like zorark
oh yeah
I think she's juggler yeah I think she
is oh God we're gonna have such a bad
time
words
confidence up
okay okay all right all right
I believe
all right I'm gonna be the strongest
right now
seven minutes and three minutes beware
all right yes
three minutes what happens in three
minutes keep your Healthy ready okay
yeah what 3 30. don't use your own how
long does it take for the ultimate it
depends on the character yeah it depends
you'll be safe if you wait 3 30.
it's all arranged
I think it's
I want to get that form
steal it
I think I stole it nice I'm scared oh
man
it'll be fine I'm going back to heal oh
okay
they're being very aggressive
[Music]
hey I'll come down to grab well you guys
what do we do
um
[Music]
she came out of nowhere she was ready
for those birds they're pushing top
they're scoring right now okay hold on
should we go should we go there's
scoring or we can we hold our I need to
grab some of these Farms I need to
actually get some Buffs go back oh my oh
my oh my God oh my God
oh
yeah
that's too strong
it's okay it's okay we still need to
live here we're doing okay in the middle
so
yeah just try to play safe don't die and
farm as much as you come in a pop
actually okay
I mean I'm gonna speed up I need to keep
farming actually I need to focus on
being the strongest I'm gonna go for
Middle Farm yeah
I think they're all going for a top is
it just me I think I feel like
Iris do you think you can hold your own
down here
I could I could I'll try I'll try you
can you can go up I'll I'll try
I don't know
I should oh wait they have theirs
zero zero scary
bot
run go down don't fight right now
oh that was close that was close yeah I
Uganda
I was gonna help them I was gonna help
them yeah
I'm lagging again oh no oh gosh
yeah
he's here try to hold him off top yeah
just try to hold them off and just try
not to die I
can solo this
okay I wonder if I should break it or
not
yeah and I'll try and farm at the same
time
points uh should I um
yeah we should try to defend
um but we'll have extra Farm after this
oh God I died
I shouldn't have sandwiches
yeah they're really coordinated
[Applause]
okay we can take it yeah make sure to
farm the Pokemon in this Lane in the Top
Lane there will be bonus mons of uh
spawn oh because they didn't give a good
Farm yeah okay
they're getting out up here
yeah they're all in Top Lane it's scary
oh I think I saw three of them on top we
can group up let's group up yeah okay uh
which where should we go I'm actually
just keep on top I guess we should we
should Farm probably I'm gonna farm so
they're gonna come in and try to kill
like anyone
okay
I'm fine fine there's no I don't see any
form at the top right now yeah I got the
one on the bottom farmed our jungle okay
oh no they're they're trying to kill me
they're oh they killed me
I love Carlos near me yeah
yeah it's scary
how are their levels doing right now
uh let me see uh I'm still a level above
we're in it I'm gonna go bottom
right now
let me know if you need me somewhere I'm
farming come down
I think it's fine though okay uh we
should probably go top
um
I'll wait for you oh wait they're all
down in the bottom Lane
okay we could just go top them Kyle is
bottom Lane wait did they leave they
left chicken solo everything
yeah okay I have successfully
top my score okay yeah okay do we want
to go aggressively for once
here they come
oh
no
oh gosh
I was a party
are you kidding me I love being useless
to my team wait Rayquaza Rayquaza yeah
okay that was because of the leg let it
be known let it be known that was
because of the [\h__\h] legs
cool all right well let's just aim for
Rayquaza and see if we can make it count
okay yeah
thank God I didn't die everyone should
be saving all their stuff so we can try
to win I'm saving us
help oh okay um
oh we're really struggling yay it's
really struggling actually hold on oh
here comes
oh
okay
yep
yep dang it
um right just get ready for Rayquaza
okay yeah yeah I still have my ALT
thankfully
we do have a lot of points we could put
in yeah we might need someone to stay
and defend I'm not sure
I don't know I feel like all of us can
just go quickly yeah I think they're all
gonna go I think they're all gonna go
Rayquaza oh they're probably getting the
bottom objective yeah you can't get that
in time
no no
no no no no no
I mean get get them get him get him all
right nice nice ah dang it they were not
there
okay don't lose all your HP to the
Rayquaza yeah because they're gonna show
up really soon
stop your Olds if you have them that was
a boss
your best try to score
I'm so sorry they're so strong lagging
so bad oh God they killed me
here I got I'm gonna pick up the points
yeah yeah
thank you I need to help Cali I'm coming
they're guarding the middle they're all
guarding the middle maybe you can go top
top the topper the one is
empty hello
come in
okay
you can interrupt their scoring oh Top
Hat has nobody on it we got a guard top
pad too okay I'll stay on bottom though
because there's so many
this one person on top is enough
leave there's no way there's no way oh
nice Cali let's go yeah oh okay
okay let's see let's see it is not
there's no way did we I don't believe it
because did we actually I wasn't able to
get it turned in
[Music]
one
that makes no sense
[Music]
I'm the baby
yay
[Applause]
I'm so happy
proud of you guys
I think we did really well in the first
one
yeah it was really close you guys know
if they sell this stuff
hey I got this shirt guys that was a big
yeah
so now we spectate I'm gonna be happy
I'm excited
I'm so sorry
if we maybe got in second place
hopefully we'll see after the next match
if they tally up all the points I don't
deserve it so like I don't deserve that
if
if ID loses somewhere first I don't get
away how do they have to get less than
like 300 points which is unlikely unless
JP is
we'll see
okay
okay follow the points oh
I want to spectate are we able to do
that yeah I'm gonna set up one spawn
that makes the room we just join as
Spectators first okie dokie
oh me
too much excitement
we did good nice job yeah we want a man
yeah I'm proud of I know we did so well
the practice paid off oh
I'm glad that we practiced a lot yeah
I'm glad I grinded like like 10 11 hours
yesterday
yeah it was worth it
you too fauna thanks for helping us
learn the game yeah
I wouldn't have been able to do it
without you
it's for playing
also thanks for the the tips uh chat as
well to improve my jungle game I feel
like that second that second game was
much better
yeah yeah good good and strong middling
game let's go Ian Strong Man uh Kyla was
scary yes yes she is scary she just
comes out of nowhere and then bam bam
bam bam
so scary nice can we get a run back with
JP now can we try it again no no
[Music]
uh I know cute well you you want to
sleep no it's not because of that I'm
not even tired even though I've been
awake since I don't know so it's
adrenaline forever I know I feel good
yeah
oh
[Music]
happy yeah now we get to sit back and
watch back and relax no matter what
happens we've already done so
I know we
did I'm really curious to see how these
aggressive teams play against each other
so wait for us to get first place if it
were to happen
um then
what wait wait so if JP wins then we def
then JP definitely gets first place
right I think so Heidi wins then there
might be a chance depending on point
difference but they could get like 800
points yeah I don't know yeah it could
be a close match with these two teams
yeah
[Music]
yeah I think because I don't know I
don't know if we'll amount to uh we'll
make a third place because of our points
it was pretty close third place oh maybe
yeah oh it is
we still we still
we fought we won one weekend
yeah and then the JP match was close it
was pretty close we just kind of slipped
up at the end and yeah I should have
been stronger
but the Ping was holding me back
it's the Ping
yeah hey the lag really got me the last
match okay we're starting
oh we're starting okay I'm starting okay
I wonder how spectator looks yeah
oh do we get to fly around oh wait I
need to show up soon that'll be kind of
cool I think that you I think I think we
get to just fly around the camera did
you guys know that like on the edges it
is of the what you may call it the the
map there's like this Magnemite holding
a camera yeah it was so cute this is
cute yesterday it was adorable
cameraman
yeah
who do you guys who are you betting on
um
[Laughter]
if he was not very aggressive so ID
might happen yeah ID was very aggressive
yeah
we will see though
because they're both pretty strong
it will be exciting I know I can't focus
though my adrenaline's too high yeah I
never mean to chill
chat who do you want me to to focus on I
can follow someone specific
or
I want to see how she jungles actually I
mean yeah Kyla
but if everybody looks like Kayla was
was Middle Lane right yeah seemed like
it yeah
because JP got a break between maybe
they've you know recovered
it back
oh man can I yeah you can't screw around
actually yeah I want to see what she
does is this okay oh no this is ID team
if you guys want to see Kayla you can
watch Kyla stream
yeah true so cute
the baby baby they're so cute
they feel like he's so efficient I think
the flower was like a starfish looking
thing in the beginning
it looks like a starfish you know the
red yeah right you're right starfish
with the flower or like a star fruit
yeah yeah
they seem so determined oh my God oh my
God
go for it
[Music]
right now
oh oh oh Kyla has arrived this will be
interesting
unbelievable
and they're gonna take that that bottom
Farm baby it was ready for that they
said yeah well JP is using the grass a
lot they're like hiding in the ground
yeah it did push pretty hard to get in
there okay
where'd she go there she is grinding
she's back in the rotation to get the
Buffs again
she's level six so it's Glaceon Who's
playing
um
no okay I think Japan
they're oh they're killing Kobo yeah
Japan oh JP winning right now scoring
right now okay
um
foreign
they're strong
Anya's chilling Anya no Anya yeah
[Music]
two versus three on the top what are
they gonna go for
okay I believe in yourself
okay they got one ah it's still kind of
the about to unlock all it comes out
yeah let's see what they do for her
they're getting resolved prioritizing oh
Kyla's Logan
they did push them back nice out of
there we can see the point difference
it's it's interesting yeah I don't show
the point difference when you're
actually playing yeah
glad they didn't honestly I think I
would have choked
even more baby going oh yeah if he's
going for regular for the top yeah
what is there retreats
oh oh Japan Retreats
they don't retreat I guess I already got
it yeah
I feel like yeah you put in most of the
work but let's go
how about the final hit that's what kind
of that's what matters yeah everyone's
on top right now everyone's ignoring me
about him I guess you lucky is much more
important he defended really well though
this is exciting I like spectating
I wish I could zoom out
I'm assuming let's go Cobo where's she
going where's she going it's dangerous
cool but there's free there's free
enemies coming
on here
oh they're aiming they're getting
they're going for the Regis okay ideas
I know right that's so weird it seems
like JP is winning but
um yeah yeah I just been picking them
off getting some kills yeah
I guess the others are joining
right
now
oh they're scoring a lot here oh oh that
was getting close yeah
okay with the late game is so they know
what they're doing
they're constantly farming they're
always picking up the forest mods yeah
[Music]
oh this will be I think it's so close
up top
yeah it is well Cooper's going for the
bottom they're going there yeah get rid
of it if uh ID has a plan for records
oh they got Ollie
[Music]
I feel like they would be very good
communicators the ID girl so they're
gonna discuss what's true if their
Minecraft server is anything
[Laughter]
everybody is
oh no
Last Hope is Rayquaza I would say so
we need you Kyla's not too big still
yeah yeah Rayquaza can still turn turn
it around but us being third place has
probably already set in stone yeah
that's okay
like 300. we might get second place she
already thank you is it by points or is
it by games one
okay okay I think I think yeah if I mean
if JP wins this then I think my points
we'd be okay but if they get Rayquaza
what is what I mean
Kyla is going forward
she's alone and they're also a good
choice
is
yeah she is
one minute
no no yeah we'll see how Rayquaza goes
Sophie that's the main fight we're all
cheering for ID for a lot of reasons
by seeing how coordinated JP is I'm
feeling like proud that we um
we all together pretty good against them
to be honest I feel like I died too much
it was close if only I didn't die that
much
dang it uh I should have aimed my old
better
um I'm proud of us I still think we did
well
yeah our last minute our grind was I
think we did pretty good yeah
if only in our practices our enemies
weren't so good so so you know
Reggie like you when Rayquaza's gonna
yeah they are respond really soon yeah
interesting yeah yeah I'm just gonna go
for it but yeah rainy is already
starting
you can win
so close
I think and everyone else is going
offensive
what is the right answer for this one
careful be careful I don't know
ID defend Maybe
well yeah they don't know what the
points are yeah they
have no idea
I'm so excited yeah
we'll keep running
oh my gosh
they got the points in nice oh gosh
fubiki's gonna try and score these
points
yeah let's go
that was awesome that was so clutch
wow Tyler right right I know it's a
really good match yeah great it's like
clothes for everyone that was amazing
wait so everybody won one match yeah
yeah now it's all according all the
points oh shoot
well guys we did our best yeah
I mean look at how scary and chaotic and
crazy that battle was like wow that was
pretty insane going up against these
girls is quite a challenge
huge was huge
MVP on the Japanese signs
and all peku and only were the MVPs just
now yeah olly was MVP
everybody did well
I am I'm proud of everyone I'm proud
yeah everyone knew what to do pretty
much yeah there was nobody that was like
fumbling around like I didn't practice
Yeah
I can confirm I did practice a lot
hmm that was fun that was really fun it
was fun that was really fun yeah I think
I might try to play more this season to
hopefully get to ultra well I'm playing
yeah actually this was I feel like we
all got closer you know yeah it's it's
really like it feels like sports like
team camaraderie yeah fun to play games
together too like yeah or something yeah
yeah fun collab game very fast I think
it's a good zatsu game too yeah yeah
once you know what to do you just yeah
if you're not too sweaty um
okay
[Music]
and we must capture the slides again
yes awesome excited for that it will go
well
it's fine I just need to
prepare
yeah the chat asking we don't know the
final tally yet we don't get the winner
did you know math then you may know it
by now it's probably no but don't tell
us don't tell us we don't want to know
we want to stay oblivious yeah
yeah if you can do math your band no
math allowed you can't be smarter than
the fifth grade first grader
I think we will at least be in the top
three
I think so
yeah
if you think about it like the Olympic
bronze medal is something very something
very proud an honor it's true it's like
that right yes it's as big of an honor
as that
I'm proud that we won a game I saw so
many people say today we were not gonna
win it destroyers
we're gonna walk all over us yeah
we've been training we've been working
but I was ready to be the most beautiful
carpets there to be existing no no wrong
orange carpets we're a rainbow carpeted
together a flying carpet
flying one where am I flying to
flying to Victory
we'll see about that other team's pad
the underdog prevailed
well chat did you guys enjoy watching
that did you know what was going on all
the time eh it was at least fun to watch
yeah I hope so I know this could be so
sweaty like these kinds yeah yeah yes
yes
like this like you know and I see like
tournaments going on and whatnot I look
at it and I always like oh they're just
spamming skills matches
it's just like an MMORPG I was like oh
it's fun but I don't why is this so
competitive now I get it yeah I think
I'll fall into it all of the end when we
like joined this in kikaku I don't think
we any of us expected it to be dead
serious yes I did yeah I thought it
would be more it would just be a fun
yeah it's a fun just a fun one
friendly a friendly competition
definitely
[Music]
it wasn't too one-sided in any of the
matches I mean yeah the thing is like a
lot of Japanese and ID members were
already like really well practiced in
this game from what I've seen a lot of
master
um ranks
so you know yeah
four days ago
but we put in the work it feels good I
was playing in my dreams
you're feeling pretty late last night
yeah did you win in your dream or did
you lose uh well I was just like
attacking stuff in my dream but then
when I was trying to fall asleep I was
like running around in the game and I
kept running into walls and I was really
frustrated
oh yeah
I get chased a lot in my nightmares just
like here in Pokemon unite Pokemon
so it was a nightmare no no not at all
while we're waiting
yeah yeah it'd be kind of fun free Match
rematch cheeky match I don't know I'm
kind of scared to rematch
I'm happy with the way we've broken yeah
true yeah I don't know if we could do it
again
it's so much more fun to like play with
like friends and like VCS and when yeah
it was so frustrating yesterday when I
was like yeah you know queuing by myself
oh and then like the random would like
you know leave me in the in in the area
alone and I'm just like yeah and
everyone's at the top in the beginning
I'm like what the Yeah I'm like I'm
Central yeah I'm Central I'm jungle and
then I wait like five seconds and then
right before the match starts somebody
else says I'm jungle and I'm like are
you kidding me I might as well not even
do it
yeah I also had troubles playing alone
soloing Reggie leki so many times why
why I was like why don't you girls wanna
go up there and get that objective why
not
they were just there to steal it after I
already got it man feels bad man
feels bad but this feels good man yeah
it's like playing with the five stack
yum
yeah I'm still I still don't know if the
held items I chose was the correct
answer though I didn't go with like the
most standard build I went with
I chose something else for the because I
wanted to make myself less squishy but
um
I was still really squishy so I'm just
saying maybe I should have gone all
offense oh they're going up now yeah
okay the final result
I'll mute the game be jam because it's
loud
[Music]
wait a sec
one moment gotta set up the slides fine
slime slime
[Music]
hold on hold on hold on guys excuse me I
got it I got it too
I got it size wise it looks a little
okay
sorry sorry this wasn't supposed to play
this I'm sorry I'm sorry how do I turn
it off
oh my gosh sorry
[Music]
oops God is almost done thank you for
your good bottles
[Music]
oh my God
are you ready for it yeah
[Music]
okay sorry
[Applause]
[Music]
there we go
I feel like I'm hallucinating ID team
and third place is
[Applause]
[Music]
really amazing
let me know you were sold
um as a leader in waiter are pleased
here you are sold
I'm really proud of everyone many people
doubted the ENT but I hope that we
showed we showed our our abilities today
I think we did I'm proud of everybody
thank you thank you for your team it was
really amazing amazing match yeah
as a leader only time please see
yourself hi
um we we all worked really hard like uh
all of us really strategized a lot do
you guys have anything that you guys
would like to say ID team ready ready
[Music]
[Laughter]
we can see a really good teamwork
communication thank you so much
is
thank you so much
I'm really glad you enjoyed this much
it is
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
and not only this so um
MVP is
thank you
all right
[Applause]
[Music]
in Ian region
MVP
oh my God
as expected
great leader you got an MVP in the first
match and you're really supportive
yes
[Music]
yeah you go to MVP and you contribute to
the uh comeback come back Victory bye
yeah
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
oh so we on the stream now or something
and we show the last video
just give me a second hold on yeah take
your time
when we left the slide thing you played
it
they played it didn't you play the video
one more slide we need to show one more
slide
okay
[Music]
let me pull up the slide
it's my time
it's not not the video
foreign
was so exciting imagine how exciting the
actual one will be tomorrow yeah you can
also do predictions right now it's true
you can do predictions in the in the
game if you get predictions right you
get prizes I heard personally that the
team uh Peru is absolutely cracked
really yes no no I don't know
you I predicted also on a ringing
oh you did let's go
wait is there European oh yeah there are
European teams I should I should
probably cheer for them
go Europe go Europe let's go let me let
me remind everybody and did the Pokemon
unite category of WCS will happen
tomorrow
and here is a slide of all the
participating team members whoa uh the
Pokemon category will be streamed on the
channel listed in the description
tomorrow 9 00 PM November 11th jst
um tomorrow
in of course you can predict in the game
when you get something for it right you
will win prizes if you guess correctly
so please check it out please watch the
stream and cheer for your favorite team
yeah and we'll see you all tomorrow
yeah oh yeah I think that wraps
everything up I'm really proud of you
guys I think we did really well yeah yay
considering considering like you know
how much we didn't really know yeah much
in the beginning
yeah that's right yeah
it makes a lot of sense
thank you I want everyone to get MVP
though
yes I think I'm really proud of us
genuinely we might have got third but
they were close matches they were
getting matched yeah yeah it was on a
huge Point Gap it was totally exactly it
was it was pretty close it's so true
about it with Matt shall we play the
ending PV and I guess we should okay
live streams yeah then jump away yeah
thank you everyone for watching thank
you thank you thank you thank you so
much for the support
we're not where are we are we muting
during the video they said we can talk
during it too okay okay but I mean
let's do three two wait you guys wait
wait wait I'm not ready
all right we're good okay
three two one go Pokemon unite recently
celebrated its second anniversary allow
us to congratulations yeah
this looks fun I didn't even try that
yet well I wonder if it'll be a just as
sweaty today
[Music]
I didn't know me too why Mewtwo was this
like tiny
[Music]
imagine imagine our teams participating
in this mixed into the real teams
in Pokemon Unite
popular halloware for Pokemon
stylish
I love the pirate outfit second
anniversary
kill it
[Music]
yeah thanks so much for everything you
guys that was fun yeah that was fun
thanks too I'm gonna be happy thanks for
inviting us for this thank you very much
a lot of fun thank you I'm really glad I
was able to take part in this and
experience this type of game yeah yeah
it's fun training with everyone I'm glad
we were able to train in the morning
rise and grind you know it was my first
first type of this genre game yes it was
fun danke schoon
I'm so tired
[Laughter]
well I believe that's all we have for
today we can let everybody get some rest
yeah we tried our hardest
thank you thank you thank you very much
thank you very much
okay okay
[Music]
have a great day
okay muted
okay I muted them uh
yeah I don't know how to say I'm too
tired um thank you um
uh yeah next we are practicing for our
Minecraft tournament
help help oh yeah
yeah cool uh bye bye
I am going to sleep now and then I'll go
to doctor's appointment
and then go back and rest more
bye-bye I love you
I love my God and thanks for all the
rest
already you're watching anymore but bee
boo and she only reigned it and nerissa
was in the chat
you cutie patooties my God
yeah don't forget to watch Hollow talk
on the weekend
foreign