[Music]
feel it R through
me
intoxicating DJ keep
[Music]
playing we dancing
so about it so emotion
[Music]
feel it R BR me
sh
feel feel it you feel me
[Music]
oh
honey night is
[Music]
feel it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
baby me
feel it rush through me
[Music]
feel it me
oh
[Music]
K
KY k okay
uh you guys are still not
[Music]
working I even went back to steal ena's
CSS
[Music]
again what the
hell why why why
why
what there it is
okay I made a sanity
meter
here I made a sanity
meter let's see how low it will go
[Music]
today I think we will be able to empty
it don't we all think so m
no it's currently full that's
full maybe the color will change too the
more we lose we'll
see are you sure it should start full
excuse
me hell yeah just even if even if we
assume like this is just the the current
state you know we can assume that maybe
my my mental state by default is not
completely sane but it's still at its
fullest right now whether or not that is
like
perfect saness or not is not it's not
depicted by this okay whatever um we can
only go lower from here is what I'm
saying you're lowering on it
already mechanic and outlas what I mean
sanity surely is a mechany in a lot of
games horror games especially m
that's my what you have a problem with
this what my you have a problem with my
Max you're like unimpressed or what it
doesn't get much Fuller than
this
anyway uh I guess I I did full screen
previously I can do it with this I I
can in the distance
meow smothie my
baby smoothie my sweet baby why are you
so
sweet I I came back from another trip
that maybe I'll tell you about if you
guys are nice and if I still remain my
sanity for a while you know it's it's
mostly you know on
that but today the intention is to
finish this game
[Music]
yes yes that's the
intention uh and then we'll read super
chats after a little bit uh I still I
have like a deadline for one song
recording
today
[Music]
um I I think I think I'm still like one
of the most obedient when it comes to
deadlines so probably I could be
forgiven if I do it tomorrow but let's
try let's attempt at least problem is I
don't even really know the song oh
well uh but yeah we're going to finish
this H you need the stream today we're
wonderful I'm here for you you need this
stream well this might not be
as
um I don't know it's not GTA but it's
freaking Luigi we're going to we're
going to uh you know take some freaking
ghosts down suck him in [\h__\h] ghost no
I'm I'm really mad at this game and I'm
projecting it onto Luigi but it's not so
much Luigi is it it's mostly
Toad
and what's the boss fight I mean that
wasn't really Luigi's
fault I it's not so much Luigi
it's lui's game I blame him yeah
true EAD yeah EAD is also at
fault it's always Luigi no I don't know
I'll have to confirm today if my anger
is correctly directed towards him or or
if it's
unfair it's but like I would say a lot
of the anger has to go towards
toad that little
[\h__\h] do you hear that oh that's probably
loud let's [\h__\h] go we're going to
finished this
today Lou just maned my second Lou just
mantioned game on this channel to be
finished WWA is going to do it I'm going
to do it wa look at the money
wa like everything is a bit big too big
let
[Music]
me am I too small now are you okay guys
should I put this
here if only you guys were not like
taking up so much space now that you're
just a box
[Music]
yes why why you got to take up so much
space go on a diet or
something to I don't freaking know I
just finished uh this world I suppose
H have I not or is this the next one huh
can I finish this
[Music]
world ah oh never mind whoa I switched
from
here that looks
huge that's going to
[Music]
be taking a while probably it looks like
a big one although who
knows the Moon
what it was from an arcade game final
dungeon yeah this massive Mansion is
filled with exotic exhibits created by
its late Globe trotting owner oh and it
is also it also contains the strongest
paranormal signals or ever recorded yay
yipp oh yeah so we should do a tangent
note
perhaps uh so Nissa
Italy uh free
live uh I don't think I talked about the
haunted uh house like in Taco to Tak it
sounds so good uh I didn't talk about
that the did I
Tak um
okay those three are enough for now
honestly I don't know if I'll get to
tangent properly about it
[Music]
not sure which one's
better also yesterday I looked at a
really old
archive uh and it was wait oh there's a
new chat leg episode let's go 38 minutes
ago I'm excited for that
[Music]
um it looked at really are old
uh
archive and uh oh you didn't hear that
and I noticed that like okay this is
like three years ago I noticed that the
chat uh it doesn't show the like chicken
icons why is it not loading now
hello I pop it out maybe because of you
guys goodbye I'm going to close
you it doesn't matter which one that's
not that's not the the important
part that's not
working a there we go now it's working
doesn't show the chicken like icons or
whatever the member icons but it shows
like stars now which I'm not sure why it
does that YouTube but the cool thing
that I noticed is that now it it shows
the members that are still only the ones
that are still members I think is what
it's showing
and even though this is three years ago
I'm surprised how many are apparently
still
members and it kind of gives me a
feeling for who's still watching me
after all these years not saying that
you know everybody has to be a member
but it gives me a good feeling because
if you're still a member like if you're
still paying for it that probably means
you're still
watching yeah some of you guys are here
right now I'm
[Music]
sure oh and I I think it shows oh
yeah oh it shows what what how long you
were there at that time like how long
your membership was at that time that's
cute oh na M was just a member for two
months here little
baby 570 was a member for 6
months El rabu was a member for 6
months cute little
baby let's see who else is here is Maybe
a one here two months Jeff B two
months shinger 6 months Dominic K 6
months oh you here froo two months Jimmy
Sullivan 6 months Franklin two months
these are all familiar names they're
still here Andrew Alasia 6 months sour
ke blade 6 months dun 6 months no Joel 2
months Renee 6 months okay I I think the
6 months is kind of rough roughly like
anywhere between 6 months and 10 months
uh 12 months maybe RJ 6 months J 6
months Joker 6 months rapy Theon 2
months Mist 6 months detective bigs new
member
oh I I I think this shows only the ones
who although maybe I'm wrong I don't
know cuz all these names they I still
see them
around I see him around wow and I look
at you now look at you now 7 7 two
months how you know two months ja sad
two months frero 6 months Anon casar 6
months yeah am I there well I mean this
is just like a like a
moment if I would play the
chat and and let it go do its thing that
it will probably show all of
you yeah
it got me excited to see like so many
names that are like there three month
three years ago and they're still here
now which makes
you no oh right I wanted to do this I
wanted to do this because I was like oh
once I'm four years in I want to do this
but ah yeah we can do this now wait wait
we can do the thing
again wait how do we do this again
uh how do we do this again do I have to
does this work of hyper chat probably
not here the
thing let's go wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait oops let's I'm making you bake
for that I haven't done it in a long
time but now now we are at um you
know 4
years so let's figure out how this works
again I'm doing a
thing I'm going to I'm going to I'm
going to get rid of all of
you I'm going to free myself of
you if I figure out how to do
it is this hyper enable hyper chat means
it's not on right now and then how do I
do the how do I do it but maybe it's not
in the studio chat here it's
probably you on to tell
you're so big you gr I literally forgot
how to do it
uh wait I'm so excited to do it is it in
the in here ah must be in
[Music]
here
okay okay okay okay okay now don't worry
I know that there's some people who
subscribed uh like who Des subscribed
unsubscribed by accident once or so for
example or who were unsubscribed by
YouTube or something or you know maybe
maybe you had to make a new account at
some point so don't worry about that
okay don't worry about it here let's
start with um
minimum one
[Music]
year hello
hello this is the test the test has
begun easy it's like we're playing that
game when you try to bend your back
backwards and go under the the the the
the pole what's it called again the
clans no that's not what it's called but
uh limbo you're in a
limbo I say ah you say B ah
[Music]
what's with the delay there we
go all right Chad come on it's too much
at once too many
bees I'm a bee I'm AB a maybe I I say I
you say B always stood for a b okay next
step two years
3 2 1
go subscribe is only mode only people of
two years
[Music]
minimum
discrimination let's
go
discrimination hey I say I you said b
l
[Music]
b you're here here of course you're here
you should
know yippe I shall win this game we'll
see about
it if I don't make it tell k I love her
a I remember before I sub what why would
you do
that oh but 24 months that's a that's a
close cut
off you don't know how early you
subscribe we'll find out now we'll find
out now cuz if you can make 3 years but
not four years that could also mean that
you subscribed like a few days after my
debut
right like maybe not first day but you
could have been like 10th day or so I
think but get wrecked wasn't early
enough all right three years are you
ready I still don't really see much
difference maybe now we'll see some
difference in people I said ah you said
B
PR years gang where you
at oh I don't know it doesn't really see
much been front
again a little bit maybe a little
bit little
[Music]
bit thank you for subscribing for free
years sign sign be
that's the sign yeah can here since day
one we we'll we'll see about that are
you lying why the [\h__\h] you lying why you
always
lying YouTube thinks I'm less than
22 2 years subscribe oh what the hell 44
months 2 years maybe maybe you this you
I think member subscriptions they will
never be like accidentally cancelled but
like Channel subscriptions maybe like
normal subscriptions perhaps so maybe
there were some YouTube Shenanigans
there but that's crazy YouTube that's
[Music]
crazy
okay okay okay okay are you ready for
the four years because it's been 4 years
and like I don't know 5 days since my
debut so if you make it now that means
you will subscribed like since pretty
much the very
beginning okay I'll be dead fairwell
well say your goodbyes guys say your
goodbyes oh no adios amigos oh no this
might be where I fall out oh no it's
okay I don't blame you I'm just glad any
of you found me it was nice knowing you
it was nice knowing you guys thank you
for finding me no matter if it was in
the four third second or first
year I'll miss you
goodbye
no I say I you say
[Music]
B oh my God there's still so many no
[\h__\h]
way
what the outsiders crying in the members
messages no
no stay away this is a fouryear people
Club
only go away go away you have no right
to talk here leave the
premises leave you're not welome here
anymore I make the rules get out of here
let my four years
talk shut them someone shut them
up wait to Let's I just want to talk to
my four years people oh so like do you
think you we like debut stream um
subscribe like first day or like even
before like tell me about it like
obviously you we like obviously it's
either like first day or like minus two
days or so or or like plus two three
days
obviously mhm before the
stream oh Debbie I've been watching you
since Debbie became a member later
that's cool
thank you I had to prove myself you know
I said when you said you like mon a
let's go and now we've been on the
endless grind i s before you debut but
didn't remember until that's fine now
shut up shut up everybody under four
years you're too young to understand old
Mike
kiaha I was there in the beginning thank
you I'm very much subbed at debut day
thank you maybe I did sub day one I
thought I sub one more Play No
apparently not let's go September 18
crazy he don't give them memberships
then they can
talk I want to come back no wait I'm
still talking to them I remember your
first game stream the chicken egg game
it wasn't it fall guys though and then
the chicken egg
game EG is broken heartest too why can
you see how long what's up well I I
think somewhere in your like subscribe
channels profile whatever I think
there's there somewhere where you can
see it yeah it was fall guys I I
remember the insanity of that my sanity
sanness sanity meter was very low
then yes yes that was like very
low K Taki aggressively doesn't like
sushi I guess that's okay ah
acdi I just the one who made the logo
thank you the logo for the thing I've
been here for a while I remember your
weird old M thank you for
staying yeah 24 hours something like
that uh I think you have to check for
how long you you subscribe for on an
outside e okay lame I think of
memberships you can look in the website
I remember how excited you were to play
Mario yeah I was and
then and then the happiness quickly
disappeared
deut times were abysmal for nor really
were they H are were they I guess they
[Music]
were oh my first
K ah that was September 15th ooh close
cut
off thank
you I was surprised you stre immedately
after debut I was motivated but honestly
I feel like uh
I feel like the girls would do it too
nowadays if if their debuts weren't like
split like to two days or so because uh
I think they're not meant to stream
until everybody has debuted otherwise
they would probably do that
too your streams are like 7:00 a.m. on
my time so I managed to stay up to watch
thank
you yeah I remember when hooka told me
to shoot myself at the sun I so sleep
deprived during the day I had to had to
have multiple alarmes me too no even
even when I'm sleep deprived I don't
really need multiple alarm clocks I'm
very
reliable I'm still young remember for 3
years 11 months 22 days thank you ah
also very tight asking to debut last so
you can stream right again after the
second yeah that would be
ideal oh no you guys you want you were
victim of the OD on ah lift the B on up
no I don't believe you I don't believe
you're threatening
I remember I missed some my debies
because Among Us was just getting Big B
then what what do you mean you played
Among Us rather than watching The Myth
debuts what's wrong with
you what can watch it while playing or
something like that where's gaze I just
got here Amry Luigi welcome you made it
you made it the test the
limbo you walked under the fouryear
pole with
ease fire emblem streams
yeah guys I'm not talking to you guys
stop sending super chats and members
messages I'm not talking to
[Music]
you I'm only talking to my four years
right
[Music]
now just don't turn it to 5 years what
whoa whoa who what will happen then
eh will I be alone
[Music]
yeah Fire Emblem oh remember remember my
uh my my first yis stream the sponsored
one where I I my PC was so
bad okay 5 years then 5 years I'm going
in 5 years
go huh H there you go
silence
silence M nobody loves me for more than
four years you just so
over what first Super Chat really what
first Super Chat space waterfall really
what oh well now the only way for you
guys to talk to me is with
money pay to win chat pay to
[Music]
win and then they were none let me in no
no I want to be alone I Think We're
Alone
[Music]
Now I'm just going to okay this is how
we're going to play Luigi today I can't
deal with like you guys and Luigi my
sity is going to not keep up with it
[Music]
thank you and so stopped the voices in
my head this is true you'll be the one
to read the Super Chat that is true most
expensive chat in the world no $2 I'm
sure there's like websites where you
have to pay more to
interact oh yeah yeah pay to talk pay to
talk pay to chat I can still use one of
them yeah but only one only one of them
for now
42 mons have come so fast thank you you
are the first R I've spent money on
thank
you o membership no no no no no no don't
do
that I'm like what happened I decided I
wanted to just not talk to you today and
yet you are talking to me how dare you
how dare you get out of
here you're so rude why don't you
respect my boundaries Mama Mia
I guess I have no
choice ah me me Garden Park you can't
talk with me
now please
respect let's keep those Sal points
yeah the power of money virtual mean and
GRE oh yeah yeah yeah this could be
virtual me and GRE
mhm a can't be San oh no okay okay okay
go I'll I'll bring it back
I'll bring it back guys do you want to
come
back it's hard you guys can't tell me
huh you can barely tell
me aw what you going to do now huh if
you don't tell me then you w back How
Will I
[Music]
Know Okay Okay most difficult
challenge subscribe for 1
minute taada
thank
you thank you but you didn't have to I
literally just switched it back scammed
you got scammed you got scammed you're
free
yippee I'm satisfied I wanted to do this
once we hit four
years I should have done this like in
the four years anniversary
stream or or in the maybe in the life to
D 2.0 reveal but I'm just doing it
randomly here why
not thank you only one week oh
no I'm sorry failed you before no don't
worry don't worry about it like you
really didn't I I'm so grateful for
everybody who subscribes like in in
these new newer
times in the New
Age no D don't worry don't worry it's a
joke it's joke be
[Music]
I stopped 10 minutes ago thank you see I
need people like you just as much so
everybody subscribe like And subscribe
and leave a comment turn your
notification Bell
on Yahoo now I'm sorry I'm sorry for
traumatizing you
chat I'm sure it was traumatizing for
some of you
but now you know if you don't want to
feel like this ever again stay
subscribed stay subscribed
[Music]
okay I've learned from my failure
good if we unsub does it count it yes so
don't do it don't touch it don't touch
the
button okay guys time to play Luigi the
man something something treacherous man
oh
no here we freaking go we can finish it
today right I heard it's what just one
mansion and one or two
bosses I'm not going to listen to
you you are manipul relative
gaslighting I do not like you wait what
did you just give
me what did
you by the way were you in any way able
to buy upgrades or does he just like
automatically give them to you when you
were be
there
freedom I could you s you were since the
beginning could be that YouTube Just
unsubscribed
you I am green pay
wall thank you thank you for the support
you hit the Subscribe button twice oh
oopsie you get the upgrades for money
like automatically right yeah yeah yeah
he just gives it okay thank you
H are you still able to like follow what
I'm up to on on the on the Blue app oh
oh oh God oh my
God holy [\h__\h] yeah
dangerous I I you know what I did last
night I was like just like I looked at
my phone screen I thought oh my God what
an eyesore and I um switched out I
downloaded an app to switch out the app
icon for Twitter from the stupid horny
website looking porn side looking x i
switch it back to the
bluebird you cannot stop
me I am loyal to the blue
bird
base one more balancing like a ballerina
Luigi oh are we going to do oh no no no
no
I'm literally holding it
straight I don't know why it's doing
that how do you jump over to the other
side again hey hey hey hey hey hey how
do you how do you how do you jump how
do wait what how do you how do you jump
again doesn't show any
button do I just I'm not sure
anymore yeah we're back
oh just the other stick ah okay thank
you for remembering
that no no no no no no no I okay oh calm
calm
Calm hey what a ballerina you are Luigi
you got a future in
that
okay nice
take home see once you start wobbling
it's hard to uhoh oh
no oh nice save nice save Luigi but this
means you can't go back
anymore yes yes oh sus these things do I
have to light them up by any chance I
forgot how to do
it wait not
I oh thank you oh no don't fall down I'm
going to fall with it cuz I'm so
greedy it's watching me that one no turn
around sanity meter
dangerous is the other one to watch me
too
no know that I'm for
turn the [\h__\h]
[Music]
around guys today my momy's birthday
which maybe she's watching this I mean I
I knew it was uh coming I brought to her
uh like yesterday hey I got some
presents for
you happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you ah she's watching
because she just turned
online happy my chat is wishing you a
happy birthday
Mommy see look at all these people look
at
them M chat ah she's watching okay
say hi to my mom happy birthday
Mama
F happy
[Music]
birthday thank you guys for the sweet
wishes for my mommy I'm sure she
appreciates
[Music]
it Mommy
mommy
birthday wait I was going to be like uh
either at her place or she was going to
be at my place but my brother is doing
something else uh he's somewhere else so
that's why it got moved for
now but originally I was going to be
away one more day
longer I kept it open but here I am
recover the front door key I'll let me
peek through do I want to see what's
going on there oh no the fell they can
very well stay in those pictures oh yeah
Capt put him into the picture put him in
there yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah put him
in put him
in do
it [\h__\h] oh King King bu yeah yeah yeah
yeah that serves him
right so that means two
Toads because one was already in the
picture
is was there any point in flashing the
lights I don't remember
no hope she's enjoying some M Minecraft
of Magic the gaing man I really wish I
would have gotten magic the gaing perms
I think I like requested it twice and
then you know they send an email to them
and then you wait and you wait and you
wait but they don't they just don't
reply the Publishers just don't reply so
mad what's going on here
oh that looks like
[Music]
[Laughter]
fun don't be mad what don't stab me oh
you were scared of me you scared of
me what do I look so
[Music]
frightening what actually that was a
really low chance of me finding that
because I almost didn't care enough to
look momy no no what the don't fly
away
okay we need that I love MTG
right right I know right man maybe I
just got to play the IRL game although I
don't know if like even for that some in
some way we kind of need uh perms for
that too oh oh
W come on oh is that like some extra
level that I don't oh what is this
should I be going here
[Music]
now should I really be here
now yeah I should is this the first
place you got to go
to honestly I I would have not found
this if I wasn't so sane today
fre San right now oh that money is
helping my sanity too what the hell is
that the
mushrooms have you guys heard uh in
Austria in these past days when I was in
Italy there were like
floodings there were a lot of floodings
it was like really bad and I just saw
like videos and pictures on social media
and I was like okay good that I'm not in
Austria right now I guess but uh I hope
I hope my Garden's fine and
everything and I don't know if my garden
got flooded ever but when I came back it
didn't look flooded I mean some of my
Planters were
like like overloaded with water I had to
pour it all out the plants were like
kind of
suffering but also just like everything
was a mess like it must have been really
stormy too because like my furniture was
like the the heavy Furniture was just
like scattered and fallen over and I
don't
know
chaos absolute
chaos I'm supposed to fro me
somewhere it's a
[Music]
sword are the Hooligans still giving you
trouble uh so far not not but they
probably I mean there's always like
different
ones wait how do you do this again oh
okay whatever I got come here how do you
do
this
what I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm just
a little bit
panick Yeah W look at the money
okay uh to do this actually
I you think that's funny you think
that's so
funny does it just mean I need
to get them to Red like if they have
that pattern I almost had it but I got
scared because he was punching
me okay sanity I I will fix it in a
moment wait let's do the green one
first uh-oh no please don't uhoh
I cannot like Dodge because they will
reset my [\h__\h]
[Music]
G
no this game shut up
you're ruining my
store you're ruin no give me my
heart mama
[Music]
mia sanity
update I'll keep it I'll keep it like
small for now because uh we've got a lot
of Sanity to
[Music]
lose it doesn't mean that I need that
color really because when I for the red
one when I tried to hit him before it
got red it seems like he took no
damage but maybe I'm
wrong any I was thinking of the
floodings because when I was like uh
seeing the mushrooms I thought oh yeah
there's probably mushroom growing again
because it was so wet and when I was
flying in with the airplane I saw like
like most of the floodings are gone now
but I still saw on the like Countryside
of Austria like on the fields and
everything like the the crops and
everything they were flooded as [\h__\h]
still even now that most of it is gone
they were still flooded and like some
some
concerning amounts of water here and
there felt felt bad I was like oh man
nature
sucks wait did I look for the for
here yeah it takes a way for it to seep
away but I wonder
oh does that completely ruin your crops
if you have a crop
field are they just gone then
say [\h__\h] it the whole year of crops like
are you just [\h__\h] over hey y
bone very bad usually yeah sadly oh man
depends on the crop
yeah like we know rice fields like to be
a little bit flooded with water but it
depends on the season and the I don't
know time of day or whatever right
[Music]
remember from sakuna playing
sakuna
I wait it's difficult to get in
right give me those gold bars Please hey
do I have to burn
them
um have to
burn hey I'm not going to I'm not going
to give up on you guys I'm going to get
you
eventually wait
oh
wait can I
[Music]
not wait was
this Yoo
spe at least my fly uh infestations
are seemingly mostly gone now when I
came back from Japan it was really
bad and then I tried my best to like get
like kill them all with my electronic F
water oh wait there's another one
ah and then I just kept the fly sweater
on over the
nights and now they're mostly gone thank
God that was so disgusting they were
like everywhere all over my kitchen now
what about the gold bars
though I can't do I get them later
maybe yeah they like to daap themselves
if that's the only source of light then
it's easier
ooh several carpets how many though do I
want to
know endless I
wonder H almost seems
endless burn the web I can't I don't
know there's the web H
here oh okay I guess I'll bring it to
the other
room all right here you go I think they
need fire here too
huh
wa all right that was
easy fire fire light the
fire
Oh Oh I thought I would have to shoot it
up cuz I can't reach but this is simple
enough ridle Sal D
uhoh hello he's sitting so
chill what are you doing here little
green man oh oh his leg's moving Luigi
Luigi Luigi
careful uh-oh oh he's insane his sanity
level is very low obviously uh how do we
fight
him I see the carpet I'm going to make
him y
wait we got to make it stumble I I
quickly understood that am I not so
smart let's go triple now your turn same
thing
Yi oh SP
us D I didn't even have enough time to
get back up they're here
too don't mess with me
[Music]
AO God Dam
it okay
oh do we want to press X on that one
uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh it's going to go down
yeah damn it but the other door what
about the other door no didn't the
door open
up oh I
see I like
it I like
it Pizza
bastard no don't to dare don't to
DARE what literally it didn't drop
anything rigged
oh wait are we looking for the dog right
now I'm really not sure what we're doing
right now I'm just like following
paths I guess if you follow the dog's uh
print then you'll figure out where to go
easily I
stupid I hear him isn't he in there then
I hear his panting I was watching some
some like YouTube shorts basically my
YouTube Tik Tok uh with like dog videos
these days ah man makes me want to get a
dog um like all kinds of stupid dogs
doing stupid things uh but then today
specifically I was watching husky videos
they're so funny and so stop one so cute
and so vocal and so
annoying oh oh
ow I can make that easily thank
you are we sure there's not something on
this door on this wall wait a
second just one
coin
what huskys are toddlers
[Music]
I don't know why I did that I didn't
look at the floor I was just curious and
there was a high chance we would go back
to the beginning with that
[Music]
movement oh no oh yeah oh God if I fail
I'm going to be so [\h__\h] mad
um wait wait where to go left or
right left or right did you see see can
you
tell
left
well oh oh no no what am I
doing no what did I
[Music]
do had to get rid of some of my sanity
for that one let me in again
why did I loop I don't
know I was cooking something oh do I go
[Music]
back yeah okay he went that way
[\h__\h] well I can do that
again I I I still have to come to this
world for several levels
so at least like last time when we
failed that was the last time
we would be in that world unless I
purposefully uh were to come again but I
didn't want
to isn't that SS
[Music]
no although I don't think we'll
necessarily come back to this
underground world tell me if I'm wrong
[Music]
well hello there what are you doing oh
is this is this the game that I
played Just Luigi's
Mansion the dead body Thing game we
don't come back okay maybe I will
anyway no not F oh he's making F he's
not making
F somehow I used that word uh around Nur
the other day and she was like it's
funny yeah what do you mean I'm saying
it in the like best
way German
[Music]
way I hate you I hate all of you so much
like genuinely why don't you take off
your stupid glasses huh why don't you do
that why will you surprised I
[Music]
I okay
get him get him get him get
[Music]
him whatever stuck it
uh-oh okay why are they not taking up
their
glasses why you not
taking I might have to suck him I forgot
the main mechanic of this game
because no I think there were the others
who uh were um like lifting them and
then putting them back
on that's why I was like waiting for
them get
me oopsie godam it
I
okay me he's toward me
[Music]
you put it back
on gave me too much time I
[Music]
suppose all right at least I got good
amount of money from those
ghosts welcome cronies oh we got raided
by quason quason my beloved ah Quon
I saw she was playing GTA and looking
really hot in game but also outg
game hello we're today finishing this
game and losing our sanity one by one oh
how do I get that Jewel Jewel Jewel
Jewel wait okay maybe we got to play
with this
first
oh what's it going to do electrocute the
Frankenstein in armor wao oh oh why get
so so shoot ah the
B thanks for the rain thank you thank
you better run from Bulldog was just
talking about dogs
cute okay I'm always uh very bad
oh what I am so bad
at sometimes I just really don't know
ah okay okay okay oh wait it's not it's
not get the
Tak me a
[Music]
moment okay
cute yeah let's just get him right away
so that he's still close to where he was
before smart
Str oh yeah and now I got to suck him
back in oh he's so cute though look at
him
I have big Bo plusy in my bedroom
now he's so cute
he silver this time or
what huh silver there there're yeah like
white silver diamonds wait are we
getting diamonds
now no hey it was literally showing the
cross no buet docky no thank you
I'd prefer a crony ducky if
anything
but
honestly I'm not a big fan of duy
makas is that all that had to be done in
this
[Music]
room let's
see probably
[Music]
right Mak okay honestly just give me a
big quo plushy there's quo plushies out
there just like any kind of plushy in
the shape of a c speaking of Amit gifted
me did I tell you did I tell you that
she gifted everybody like a couple of
things again last
time uh in the in New York
did I tell you that and then so she gave
me a candle a frog candle so cute and
she gave me like some snacks I think and
she gave me uh she gave me like
bread like Plushies that have a wire in
it small ones that have a wire in it and
you can kind of twist it it's like a
baguette and more bread sticks and
stuff I wonder why she gave that to me
maybe she feels like you know she can't
have bread so everybody else should have
bread at
least I appreciate
it yeah okay where did doggo go straight
oh over
there so if I go any other way I'll get
lost supposedly right but the one time I
did go another way I found a secret
[Music]
room
so I wonder if there's any more rooms I
would want to find
for the door for the
door there's a couple of
Secrets oh
no do they match your setup maybe a
little bit but I think they're supposed
to
be cat toys
maybe got to see if they like it
what is this place supposed to be anyway
like what's the
theme
tunel
Tel
T believe in the
[Music]
tles no no no oh [\h__\h]
damn
it t surely we have to suck this go open
up open up
ooh n
h so I don't know if uh narissa told you
guys yet but you know where we went in
Italy in ba Italia we went to Venice to
beautiful V P you know the city with all
the water
everywhere yeah I've been to a lot of
places in Italy before but I don't
recall ever going to Venice if if my mom
ever brought me I must have been really
small but I had no memory of it so I
don't I don't think I ever went my mom
surely went but I don't think I did
unless I just don't remember it oh
water um can I pick up a pot or
my dog went that way
okay where the locals hey tourists I
wonder if there even are that many
locals cuz I can imagine housing being
very expensive there and it's a pretty
small
island
so there's probably not that many locals
I feel like the locals to tourist ratio
must be ah wait must be pretty
low or like unbalanced I mean
but it's like that in a lot of touristic
places in it in it
BR uh you want more what no you want to
be light up lit up
taada oh thank you a good money worth it
now he went through
here can I go through there
no too small really okay wait can I
look
[Music]
no when is flat of the time yeah it's I
saw like um there's this big Square St
Mark
Square uh where there's like a big
Basilica and a big uh Museum listen that
there's so many things there it's like
the most popular place for the
tourists and it floods just like there's
like these um what do they call
[Music]
again man
man the thing on the ground is that the
was that the word for it is such a
canals but manhes really why the [\h__\h] is
it called that that's so
weird there's these manholes on the
ground in the big square and they will
just like spill water and flood like the
big squares and then like I saw people
um trying to cross it because they were
so big like it was hard to walk around
it uh and people would take off their
shoes and walk Barefoot through
it or but it's like it's relatively
shallow like really shallow honestly and
then I saw there was so many people with
dogs in Venice like so many tourists
with dogs and so cute and they would be
so excited about the water and jumping
around in it and then the owners are
like okay [\h__\h] it I guess I'm joining
you so
cute and then oh what the hell and then
people would
be like you know some people would walk
through with their shoes
on
uh and then they would be wet right so
they they so they take them off and then
they sit on those stairs somewhere
really low stairs though uh and wait for
their feet to dry and then and then
there's this Venice respect Venice
Police it's not real police but they're
like they word his vest and it says
respect Venice on it and they tell
everybody every once in a while like get
up get up you're not supposed to sit
anywhere here
ow where am I supposed to bring this
bomb maybe uh maybe
see just leave it
there there we go
yeah we were told once to because like
we we sat down to eat our ice cream and
just take in the
scenery
um but we didn't know that we weren't
supposed to I had a feeling cuz it
reminded me of a different place that I
visited where it was also not welcome
but yeah you know they the moment they
told us we were like
okay understand even though we're so
exhaust oh we're so exhausted from
I well maybe later although we can do it
from here we were so exhausted from
walking around we just wanted to sit
down and there's barely any places to
sit let's go I solved the riddle wild
Tangen things that's difficult you
[Music]
know
sus doggle you h
here
wait I will not let you escape that
easily come here little [\h__\h] oh I got
him and the key oh first mission
complete is there nothing with this
painting yellow D our gameplay B no no
it makes me take more time of everything
so we're going to get a really bad rank
especially with the HP that we lost to
thanks for the membership for
you speci
complete wo half an
[Music]
hour yeah I did not expect anything
better than bronze
obviously could have done it
better you're going to love the next
mission uh-oh are you you're joking
right you are but I wonder if we should
just redo the same level right the away
uh just to get the secret thing or no we
can do it within the next mission right
and just walk there do it and walk
out got it Kissa anniversary it was
Kissa anniversary
too how how
so how
so basic Thea wanted to go to benis and
she told me a long time ago and I was
like oh okay
well I'm honored that you want me to go
with you so I can't say no even though
the time frame you know was kind of
overlapping with some anniversary stuff
but I didn't want to I didn't want to
say
no you know was happy she asked
me was like okay let's
go but it was really a short time we
were only there for like 4 days or
[Music]
so
really
and Toad did I just read
toad it was I want to tell you one thing
now
it if you guys ever plan to go to
Venice uh uh you should
either look deep into how to get from
the airport to accommodation or organize
like a transport but don't get ripped
off because like okay so narissa invited
me so I just kind of thought okay she
she's got an idea of how to get to the
hotel and
everything uh she said there will be
we'll we'll get picked up there's a
transport and I'm like okay
cool um
I'll tell you this story on this screen
because I want to tell it without
getting so
[Music]
distracted spoiler she did not have a
plan well I
mean we thought we had a plan so I
arrived like a little bit before Nissa
so I waited at the airport for a while
and then she came and I was like reunion
with Nissa so happy just us
too uh we h again we catch up a little
bit and we sit down in the airport and
we're like waiting for our transport
because narissa says we'll get picked up
from the
airport for sure and we're like wait a
while and just nothing happens and we
looked around we looked at all the
people who were holding signs looking uh
looking for something that says our
names or so or the hotel name nope
nothing waited for a while and then I'm
like you know what let's let's call the
hotel maybe and see if they know
anything like cuz we didn't have a
number from the transport the supposed
transport so I I call the hotel but the
receptionist like uh connects me to the
uh to the um [\h__\h] I forgot the word I
just had it in my head a moment ago the
the the the the the the
the the non- receptionist the guy who
knows a lot of stuff
con yeah the
con I I explain the situation even
though I don't even really know much
about it cuz I'm not the one who planned
it but I'm like hey I think we're
supposed to get picked up and the con
wasn't really helpful he was like call
your transport person I'm like I don't
have a contact do you have it they're
like no of course not okay so it was not
organized by the hotel you know
obviously so I'm like no so sorry I
don't know man they don't want to like
help us and and then she looks through
her information that she has a little
bit more and then
realizes okay maybe it wasn't pick up
from the
airport there's this place here that
they uh named and I'm like okay let's
look it up on the map and it was like um
the airport is not too far from Venice
but it's like Venice is an island the
small Island and the airport is on the
on the main like big Italian land I
suppose if you know what I mean so it's
connected by one big bridge but mostly
all a lot of Transport just happens by
both um but we were still very
intimidated and confused by the prospect
of a boat taxi or so and thought it must
be more expensive it is more expensive
but you know uh so I look up the thing
on Uber and um it was
like a little bit expensive but at least
it was a car that would take us over
this big bridge and on to the main
island so I order the Uber we go to the
Uber everything's cool uber Uber is nice
Uber is
friendly uh we have a few like exchanges
about Italian language cuz I'm trying to
remember my
words I barely remember
anything um and then you know we're just
driving driving driving Tak takes a
while and you know I put in the name of
the place are you guys still
listening I put in the name of the place
in Uber and he drives us there like not
saying anything about it but he just
drives us you're still listening okay I
just make sure you know you got to be
listening don't zone
out and
then he drops us off at a place that
looks like it has a lot of like buses
arriving and leaving so it kind of makes
sense to us you know we're thinking oh
okay this is kind of like a parking lot
but also a station and stuff this looks
like where we could have our
transfer uh he drops us off really
friendly gives us a luggage and drives
off and then we sit down and we wait for
our
transfer uh but I think at this
point no at this point
um I guess there was still a little bit
of
time but I was kind of hungry so I go
off and get a snack a little bit of a
snack I come back to narissa she's like
taking care of the luggage I come back
and I'm like okay let's
wait uh yes you joined it right on time
for tangent
cast uh yeah we wait we wait we wait but
we're like thinking okay this place is
kind of big like if this is the place
then I wonder where exactly we're
supposed to wait and what what exactly
we were supposed to look out for
H and we still don't have a contact for
this transfer
either so we just got to believe and
wait but
then
um
I I don't I'm not I don't remember this
100% I think I like we got going walking
around looking for places where it would
be it would make sense for a transfer
transer person to be
and I I go to like a little like
stand that sells like drinks and like
simple stuff you know not not even a
store just a little stand and I asked a
lady in it who was really friendly and
trying to help us if she knows like this
this name of the place if this is like
right here or like 10 m in that
direction or if she you know and she's
like oh that's that's actually really
far away and I'm like what what
what that she's like that's not here and
I'm like are you sure like maybe this
place also has a little street called
that or so like sometimes these places
surely have names that repeat uh in
different areas she was like nope no
that's really far like there I'm like oh
okay let me double check here and I
realized that when I first picked picked
the uh put in the address on
Uber it showed the right place and then
I confirmed and you know but uh the guy
dropped us off 40 minutes walking
distance
away for from where we were supposed to
be dropped off I put in the right place
but he just dropped us off somewhere
else without telling us like if you were
not able to get there by car he should
have told us because we were just
literally waiting there for half an hour
thinking we were already there because I
I know from experience that normally if
an U is just not able to reach a certain
place he will just tell you and be like
hey so I'm going to drop you off here
because it doesn't go any further than
this right you would
tell your like
passengers and that's fine like if you
can't go any further that's
fine what you doing what are you doing
uh and he was so friendly and like
communicative in general so I was
wondering like why wouldn't you say
anything and then I realized when I
opened my Uber app again to check how
long it would take to get to the actual
place we wanted to go to um it said it
it has a it had a popup message uh from
like after the ride asking me are you
okay it seems like you got like dropped
off very far from your
destination uh make sure to call this
number number or so if you need help
which is like an emergency number or so
but Uber gives you popups if they
realize that you were very far from
where you were supposed to be dropped
off like very
far they knew something was
up I think I still got charged for like
not the full distance but surely I only
got charged for the distance he like it
would be when I put in the address where
he dropped us off no you know what I
mean I don't think he I was I don't
think I was charging the full
amount uh it was already pretty
expensive from the get-go but now we
were looking at some really expensive
prices and no more no the thing is like
I realized okay Uber is now showing me
only Water
Taxis which is a thing I never saw
before on Uber it was it was only
showing me water taxes and they were
extremely expensive on Uber like uh for
that 30 minute walk 140 bucks for
example buy water
taxis welcome to Venice yeah don't laugh
at me um so we were like there's no way
we already paid a lot for this tax
and this can't be and our our transfer
pickup time is now oh my God what are we
going to
do um but I realized oh okay the fact
that it's only showing me water taxis
now me means that and he dropped us off
here maybe it really means that it's
actually really difficult to get any
further by
car he could have just told
us he could have just told us cuz we
were unaware man we were just relying on
us to be dropped off
correctly
yeah so seemingly you couldn't go any
further and I was pretty frustrated at
this point because I was pretty burned
out for from previous travels and I I
just I thought you know that the
transport would go
smoothly but
no so yeah we walked around a little bit
and then we find you know that these
water taxes they're all around the
canals and they they constantly are
ready to pick up people at any time so
we asked one not really hoping for any
good price but this guy gave us a really
cheap price
think it was like I don't
know maybe 30 per
person which was like half of what Uber
was giving us so I think it was like 60
or so in
total but then you think like 40 minute
walk if we didn't have so many you know
luggage with us we would have probably
walked but at the same time it was kind
of a tour too because like in this taxi
now it was just us to and it it was like
a nice boat nice boat and we looked out
the windows and we got like really nice
views for the canals we went for like a
big Canal deeper deeper deeper into the
the popular touristy spots like
everything was a touristy spot I think
but like the architecture looked so cool
and that was we were just sitting in
this water taxi and feeling like oh my
God this is so surreal this is when I
tweeted out um I tweeted out something
like this is so unreal or something like
that right that's when I was in the
taxi I was like oh my God this is so
weird like the fact that all this
Transportation happens on boats and
there's like public transport boats
which are basically uh replacements for
like real buses or like a Subway they
have like these stations that look like
bus or subway stations but it's bigger
boats instead but not like huge boats
it's like you know little little small
fairy type of boat
yeah no I wasn't hitting anything with
capital letters they is just so weird
cuz I never saw something like that
before and then the architecture looked
very different from uh any other Italian
city that I saw so far too very
unique and I love being on boats and
being on water so I really liked this
way of transportation but it was just so
funny and
weird and then the guy drops us off and
we're still not completely where we need
needed to be uh but we walked like over
a little bit more like maybe 10 minutes
it was kind of rough with the all the
crowds all the tourists and you walk
like we were walking by the Water by the
very most outer uh part of the island uh
around St Mark Square towards our like
pickup point and there's like you know
there's canals going out into the big
water so there's like a lot of bridges
small small tiny Bridges so we go up and
down and walk a little and up and down
and there's so many people so crowded
and then we made it finally but we were
like 40 minutes or so late at this point
so we had no hopes that anybody would be
there but we also had no
contact long story short we finally
eventually were able to get contact and
then they were kind of like where were
you and we were like well I don't know
man it was confusing this is not like
like any other City this is very
confusing sorry we we thought we were
there but you know the Uber driver
didn't say
anything and and then they sent a new uh
taxi and then we were transported yeah
to a a very
special very special nice uh
Hotel yeah all all good in the end um
that was so frustrating but all of this
frustration was quickly resolved and we
realized okay we're switching to
different accommodation in a few days
and then we're going to do better
there's a free we were wondering we
noticed once we arrived in the hotel
they have a every like 30 minute free
transfer going
on I wonder like surely it also
transfers people back not just to the
Venice island like why couldn't we take
that I I was
wondering there is no word of that so
maybe it really only goes one way and
then takes no passengers
back
weird
weird are you going to go to class oh no
I'm sorry I'm I yapped so
much yeah that was like our arrival that
was pretty chaotic and then on our on
way back though like um we we went
separately but uh narissa and I we we
booked some like relatively direct Water
Taxis uh back to the airport and it was
it was cheap this time we looked up like
you know shared Water Taxis to the
airport and that was fine that went well
I mean I was really scared like somehow
it it was not clearly indic indicated
which dock was the transfer to the
airport for this company was there was
no indication of it except like a a
vague map that they sent as an image but
like the dock itself had no indication
of it it was just shared with other
taxis so that was confusing I asked the
taxes are you my tax and they're like no
no idea what you're talking about I
asked never taxi are you my taxi like no
no idea but then I wasn't alone
I wasn't the uh after a while like an
American couple joined me they were like
hey are you waiting for this like
transport thing and I'm like yeah and
then we chatted so much we were together
we were anxious and they were like an
relatively old but they didn't look look
old married couple they were like
probably like 50 or something really fit
people and they um they were from
America they told me they were from Long
Island so they told me that's close to
New York and I'm like oh I've just been
to New York I I can say this
proudly so cool Long Island that sounds
like where rich people live
probably yeah wow SC isn't that like
when rich people live
[Music]
Long Island represent really it can't be
it is that's where I am woo rich
people yeah we yapped so much and they
told me about the kids and they told me
about their trip for Italy and they told
me um that the lady she was so cute like
she uh she told me that she has been um
running since she was 18 um she's
currently training for Marathon again
and she's she's been running uh like
since she was 18 almost daily probably
rock slide oh oh that's how you call a
bio uh uh uh raid that's funny but I'm
in the middle of a quick Tang I met some
Americans and they were so sweet and and
yeah so she tells me that for the I
think it was the past 3 years she was uh
she hasn't missed a single day of
running her miles
amazing amazing even for the winter and
even for traveling and this and that wow
that inspired me a little bit and yeah
we talked so much and and thankfully
they you know they helped me get through
the anxiety of perhaps missing the
transport but in the end all went well
when I went back so that's it for now
with the Venice getting to Venice and
leaving Venice tangents we are in the
second
oh God my reaction time is always so
slow with the golden
ones oh you don't want to give me any
more money huh
welcome welcome welcome to the stream
feel free to help me if you remember how
to play this game I'm going to try to go
back to the place
where can
I can I not is this staying down now I
have to go back to the
first level and redo it oh M
Mia sanity
has left the chat once again a little
bit oh wait that's a big
[Music]
wall what is
this what is this oh hello hello die
please what do we have
here wa so hard to turn this
thing without
stopping People Press F in the
helicopter congratulations welcome to
the
club what is this there must be
something to this what what's the
point maybe this is important
later I don't understand this
part tell me if this is for
later is it just for the bird doll no
way that's lame oh yeah we got the key
for the entrance door I suppose is that
what that key was
for oh I heard people are dying to
visit Okie
doie TCH has been packed yes press F
press
F oh
all
right
no that's so scary thank God you didn't
see that
Luigi poor
Luigi what is this is that
snow what happened here oh teleportation
[Music]
okay wait there a there's so many of
these warping warpy warping
portals but they seem very inactive but
this one snow oh no do we have to go
back to each world for a little
bit your first mission if
you so Tru accepted is to activate all
what the [\h__\h] are youing talking about
are you just like making a joke a portal
joke Hello
whoa in their
Courtyard looks pretty
fancy Mission
Impossible well so far these portals are
useless I think
okay then let's check for the open
doors oh oh no wait wait
wait oh maybe that
one I swear to
[Music]
God no okay that's too much but that's
how I genuinely feel CU these piss me
off so
much they piss me off so
[Music]
much okay haret typical eh why is it
stopped there
[Music]
hey why does it stop
there okay I'll pull the other
side what that stupid stop that oh wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait this one
then we push one why don't not stop that
that's annoying there's a door here no
there's a window
here why stop doing
that I don't see a solution to this
this room is so mystery to me is there
something about this
light I don't
[Music]
know jungle
exhibit
okay do we really need that in our lives
I don't
know oo cash
money today I got it's 6:30 guys my oo
my sleep schedule has been really good
for a while now in Japan too and even
while I'm back here and then in Italy
and it it was because like we were all
sleepy me and Nissa a lot of time and
uh why why did you do
that need to get them stuck somewhere
huh but it's kind of difficult
here and we were talking a lot and
interacting a lot socializing a lot my
God I never ending
socialization I don't know where the
[\h__\h] do I get you
stuck I'm just get
ow I don't know if I can vacuum the
spairs
ow I hold the flashlight and Flash them
both yeah but they block
it never mind
don't walk into the don't walk into the
pl I hate myself so
much it's tough to fight
[Music]
here okay okay okay this way this way I
can pull ah
man
okay do I use the spare to take down the
plant by any chance
yeah oh thank God at least the light is
on rested while means 8 hours well no I
I wouldn't be rested if I didn't take a
nap so thank
God all right
so I don't know if I can shoot it at the
plant
because it it doesn't shoot itself
unless I let myself get swallowed with
the spare I don't know if that's really
what you would want to do
uh now you got to grow a
seed what what do you mean
[Music]
what
oh what
[Music]
okay oh that's not what I
wanted going back
down
clear my sanity is still pretty high
yeah relative it's all
relative my friends we got a lot of
source here we got blocks of wood
which it would be nice oh wait no way do
we don't have to like chop them up with
the spare
right to make a bucket out of so that
would be
weird that would be
unprecedented we need a bucket I don't
see a bucket up
[Music]
there oh a
portal we can actually activate this one
I don't know if I'm so happy about that
maybe there's a bucket in there let's
see oh okay we have a shortcut there now
I
suppose ah maybe there's a bucket here
and we bring it through the
portal O
Okay random bucket somewhere or am I
thinking too much about
buckets m
portal free looks weird free will never
be weird all right I'm just going to go
here for
[Music]
now I'm scared of the guy oh he's not
attacking why are you not attacking me
what's wrong with you don't you want to
isn't it in your in your
veins
[Music]
H you have a Golden Bone when your
lives I know I wish I had one right
now again this room is a mystery like
the other one 25 Hearts is really not
good Dark Age exhibit wo oh
[Music]
okay literally literally when I'm I'm I
just mentioned I don't have one would be
nice to have one indeed oh and some
hearts well thank you so
much
oh what what was that what I looked away
for a moment was that a
boo I didn't see
one why did he move that
why did he do
that spooky that's a bull that's a
bull why why is it Mo doing these
colorly things oh thank
you so far I like this
room you might almost think it might be
bringing my sanity back up so
far what they're all Bing b
okay I'll I'll open it okay yeah I mean
obviously there was something in there
oh a bucket you have a
[Music]
bucket
okay uh-oh uh-oh
Co
yeah
and okay that was bad because I guess I
pushed to early do I do I suck the
bucket no
you thought you had me you little
[Music]
[\h__\h]
okay okay that is so mean of you I was
obviously
occupied you little
[\h__\h] maybe maybe
is it worth it like yeah I don't know is
it worth doing like a small one first
and then a triple if it looks like he
after a triple would only have enough
for one more small bar left you know
what I
mean or is there no
difference is wait so we would probably
bring it for this
portal but I don't see a portal
yet on the map there's a
portal now I can open this and it closes
again
okay oh I this reminds me this this is
kind of locked the museum we went to
the uh Doge Palace and it thought it was
so funny that it's called that because I
had to think of doge coins and the Doge
the whole
time there there's why is there a spring
yeah the Doge however is like a Duke I
guess oh now I can open it at the
book and the doge is like a Duke and he
had this huge Palace I mean there were a
million does in
vanis so we got into this Palace and I I
got myself an audio guide Nissa Nissa
was just like looking at everything
without a
guide but the audio guy honestly they
were yapping so much there was so much
to look at and so much history my brain
was overflowing I was literally losing
my
sanity because it was just so much
information and it was so insanely
beautiful and there was so much detail
and the the architecture was so
different and oh my God and they had
like rooms with a lot of armor too and
million different weapons and stuff that
was interesting
[Music]
yeah I was so over stimulated but the
funniest thing so I was listening to the
audio guide and looking at all the
pictures very
like like trying to understand each
picture but there would sometimes be
like 10 pictures in a room
and it was hard for me to grasp which
one the lady in my ear is currently
yapping
about um but one thing I kept on seeing
see I want to actually show this
on on the screen I think there's surely
no copyright to
this I saw this in the Basilica and on
on the buildings like sculptured and I
saw this in like a a lot of
pictures
[Music]
um just but okay let me show you
there is
something that repeats itself all over
in
[Music]
Venice this
lion right with
wings and
then it comes up in a lot of paintings
sometimes with people sometimes not and
he's always in the same pose holding
this
book and I was
like why what's an explain more but she
probably was explaining more but I just
did not
understand cuz there was so much to take
in but I was curious about it and then
after everything we went into the um uh
into the wait wait for it guys we went
into the shop uh from the museum and and
Nissa was buying a few things and I was
I was looking at some stuff they had and
I realized something I saw a really
simplified version of this lion holding
the book and that's when I realized
it's the same as this
bank and then I looked at the bank and
I'm do you guys know this bank it's
common in Europe I
think and I realized the bank like it
takes this famous Venice historian
historic Venice lion as its logo because
it's an Italian bank and they just take
it as their their mascot icon hasn't
always been like that but uh yeah
I'm like oh that's why it looked kind of
familiar but not really it only looked
familiar once it was simplified in the
in the merchandise from
[Music]
the the museum yeah it's not a Chima
it's a griffin I
suppose yeah nice catch but did you guys
would you guys have noticed you guys
didn't know the bank did you maybe it's
only familiar to
Europeans then I looked up a bunch of
about it like this this is really
interesting St Mark's St Mark's
lion
basically the lion of St Mark
representing Mark the Evangelist
pictured in the form of a winged lion is
an aspect of the tetramorph on the
Pinnacle of St Mark's Cathedral he is
depicted as holding a Bible oh that was
a Bible and surmounting a Golden Lion
which is a symbol of the city vanice and
form
of the Venetian Republic and I heard so
much about the Venetian Republic they
had so many does that were not dogs they
were all people not
[Music]
dogs but all the information I learned
has barely been retained in my brain let
me tell you
that that was really cool though like
I've been to Roman places you
know but
Venice was something else again entirely
the palace was insane Insanity that's
one of the biggest palaces or the
biggest Palace that I've ever witnessed
honestly freaking cold
[Music]
why why must I meet you again you little
[\h__\h]
fin boy he's green
maybe he's nicer because he's my
color green toad must be special
right who ter chasing me all the and
that laugh the horrible laugh foring me
I can do the voice normally better but
I've already been screaming so my voice
kind of hurts
sorry I didn't tell you there were two
of us no I I noticed I don't know why
I'm surprised he always thinks we're the
same person I want to this color blind
lady let's go save
my color blindness is not not a joke
toad before I fainted I overheard the
boo saying their boss finished trapping
him inside of painting and then they
muttered something about the ice AG
exhibit I don't care I'm just going to
follow the paths you know I'm not
listening to you can I shoot you inside
of these
[Music]
things I mean I I can't really what are
these for
[Music]
then the to boys is really rough
so let's not overdo it where do we take
you huh buddy I'm guessing we want to go
for this door cuz I didn't go through it
yet let's go toad oh so far not bad you
actually went through it first try oh it
wait is it the other door cuz I know
this room come
on
it you take on his voice C no but I can
do it better though I can do a real toad
voice
wait is there a point in bring where's I
guess it's probably this way right
because I don't think I have seen the
machine yet that I that you use to
transport him
back so it's probably not in the
anywhere in the
beginning
uh-oh I was not surprised by that oh
you're holding to oh have fun you can
take him
away just taking what are you waiting
for oh you let him go
[Music]
now this it's too easy right
now yeah at least he Chained and he
stopped screaming when he was being held
didn't
he prer him to be quiet so please give
him the
uppies all right that went well didn't
it didn't even lose
any any HP but I I feel like I'm missing
out on a lot of gems
which I don't really care about but you
know maybe I should care about
it I don't know what to look
[Music]
for shut up shut up you're so noisy come
on but I need the second one two in one
go sque
is it not a separate
[Music]
Mission uh what the
hell this looks more like a boss fight
room I mean not really the room
but this
[Music]
thing did you just fall down okay
jump down on your own you little [\h__\h]
your plant needs water I don't know if I
need to bring the one from Far Far
Away wait what what was that just
[Music]
no oh there's
money do I want to go here or should I
have gone left
first apparently this creates a portal
though wait is this where is this the
room where I died before or
this is a new
room give me the
[Music]
heart throw him in the pit the fighting
pit oh yeah I'm going to leave him alone
here with these mommies sorry
Mommy oh no is this the same F them as
before or new surely it's a new fight
but no more than four mommies please
you that's enough that's going to be
enough uh how do we do this again we're
going to like have them fall down ow
it's not going to go it's not going to
go well can they run don't they run
normally don't they
run ah I flash them and then they run
and this one fell over
nice wait ah okay
oh that's a way to do okay oh okay
okay these are strong
oh
out
oh now we're
cooking big money
let's
[Music]
go they scammed me two gold
bars don't worry that's not my sanity
leaving me that's me just getting really
sad and
[Music]
angry get out
here can I send you through this toad do
we want to go through it toad there was
another door up there remember
toad H I guess we can always go
back oh now we're
here
um
H help was I supposed to already come
back
probably I don't know come mind I'm I'm
un
[Music]
sure Squeaky steppies use your black
like
here or in the
hall okay I'll keep
[Music]
exploring there's one more portal that I
need to oh okay within this same
wait um is that the easiest way to bring
the water here for the portals and then
walking up that's a long
way if that's how you got to do it and
there's no better way to bring the
water come on that would be a long way I
think it was for
here yeah it's close it's close enough
to make sense because the portals are
right next to each
other so you want to think that
that's was that
sound the cat's doing some weird [\h__\h]
come
on kitty cats I heard some something
fall I can go somewhat faster I didn't
realize
[Music]
this path is so long though it better be
rewarding me with a
jewel it has to
right look at all this
effort
[Music]
come now if I want the buget again will
it be respawned in that room or will it
be here forever ah there we go
what I missed so
[Music]
many they must be really hard to get
J I want to I don't want to miss so many
toad come here come here to come
on can we find some more before I move
on like in previous
places like what about here
oh but this is where I wanted to check
out the other path
[Music]
anyway maybe some gems maybe you were
supposed to go left and you were
supposed to find gems here I see a ghost
obviously now go flash
him I'm such a
prankster
o you angry now huh o
[Music]
he's a big
b
one
two and three oh man so is this did you
guys answer me before if
like perhaps I should end like do a
small one in between so I can end it
with a big
one to get big
money I I sometimes I just can't tell
like how like I got to do
math I don't want to do
math oh do I send you to
over
there again
toad don't come back to me oh what did
you where are you you're
like oh
[Music]
here oh go go into the
toilet is that not possible
[Music]
I don't understand
help like why is this
still not
[Music]
opening is it really bad because I can't
seem to get him
[Music]
in like why you do this to me Luigi this
is
bullying this is bullying
hey I feel like he just
automatically swoop swooshes to the side
sweeps
swoops yeah where is the other ghost
then I already checked the things oh oh
wait
no I thought that would maybe something
be on the
wall h
[Music]
I can
leave
[Music]
weird [\h__\h]
off must be connected with this room
then something about
[Music]
it
oo if I flush this room something will
happen something oh yeah let's go is
that before the one I
found it
is okay it looks a little bit better
[Music]
now I hate you why you do this to me
oh ow
hey wait
no why did you turn
aroundi why you such a pain in the ass
to
[Music]
control there we go so this did that
clear the other room too so don't you
want to stay in
there stay no toad stay in there m Mia
you're just no fun
toad you're just no
fun come
on yeah you can Flash him and then he'll
be like stunned
Luigi's job is a plumber are you saying
he's doing a bad job now at it I think
he's doing
[Music]
great
oo okay come on
cleared cleared the area all of that
seemed very
optional what's going on
[Music]
here in the quter ah where the Crowds
Are oh midf
[Music]
flight Piel Len must be somewhere above
you ah okay to bring the toone back you
don't need to figure out how to R above
me there okay we'll figure it out
hopefully it's not too complicated but
this makes me think I have to go up
through the uh these like
cages perhaps toad has to go up alone
who
knows hey hey hey hey where did the
money
[Music]
go let's get all of them maybe I'll get
a gem for that no no
hey I missed one
[Music]
okay first thoroughly inspecting the
situation nough the plants are very
generous here thank you FAA for the
Super
[Music]
Chat and there's one up here I don't
know if I can suck this from here
probably
not did he just say wow
W are you just crying huh to me this
means you're calling my
name my name
name okay now what is up with this let's
shoot you into one of the cages okay oh
yeah that's exactly what they
wanted oh they want me to bring the
second toad huh cuz I can't get up there
oh wait but there's a oh wait it op up a
FAL but I I would assume you need
[Music]
both but I'll try this
anyway yeah okay can we just close the
cage and I go
alone no
H oh wait second what about this window
is a fake window whatever okay come I'll
come back to
it thank you for the membership
gift
[Music]
hey do what is going
on um
[Music]
oh I should look
ow
[Music]
rude to where are you are you in the
fridge refrigerator
[Music]
did you guys listen to the Twitter space
me and Nissa did just asking in case you
missed it it's still recorded and up on
oh do you want me to bring a ball it's
up on Twitter on Thea's Twitter in case
you missed it we had fun yapping in
[Music]
bed caught up with it good good good
good oh fire
[Music]
chicken K to killed the
plant K killed PA oh no clip
bait can't believe K just killed
b k hates fa confirmed
I I literally want to see someone put
that in the title now purposefully cuz
it's a joke it's a
joke okay no more fire chicken fire is a
chicken why surely there's a gem in here
and I'm too stupid to find it I'm just
really bad at finding gems today more
than uh
ever guys can you look up a gem guide
and tell me before I walk out of a room
oh see before I walk out of the room
just in case like first let me look for
it and if I am about to leave the room
and I still didn't find it then let me
know we got another CH oh
God left
H I don't know left or right
[Music]
don't your fing it's okay maybe I could
have made a little stop oh no this works
this
works oh it's so icy no
no oh it's so
close I didn't even realize it was icy
until like way in the
end don't scam me give me all of that
thank you I thought I would get a gem do
you never get gems out of this
H yay clutch clutch it's always still
clutchy can't believe I almost made the
other one even though I went into a
completely different
direction for a moment at least did I
miss
something
hey are you giving me a hint probably
not
[Music]
why does he not shut up ever why do you
not shut
[Music]
up come on he really has some lungs yeah
he must be using some kind of cough
drops otherwise I don't think his throat
would would
survive okay we are able to walk over
here okay oh why is it
moving why is it
moving let me touch
it why can I not touch
[Music]
it why you making beep up beep up sounds
anyway
[Music]
okay easy
enough shut
up like why like why must he scream
constantly even when there's nothing
going on like during a fight I get it
but like what is wrong with
you like don't the the developers think
of the people who are trying to clear
the game with like 100% all gems and so
on then you got to go for everyone like
so
thoroughly and you're just like ply
searching meanwhile to is
like
M
Sal doco
[Music]
incredible incredible anyway I got the
gold ghost really
easily now I there must have been a gem
even in this room or in the previous one
come on guys please tell
me it would be nice if we could mute
this
toia maybe there
isn't maybe there isn't
so how do you feel today game fq game
[\h__\h] you yeah that's how I feel like
what's the what the game is telling
me game says [\h__\h]
[Music]
you what do the gems do it's just for
the high score I
think oh wait never mind to we're
supposed to go up follow me
I hate you so
much I get the second one from you but
just for the sake of making mushroom
stew with you too it's
more efficient if I have two of you oh
is that
tuna no tuna wouldn't swim in such cold
water would it
wow oh
fun thank you for
thatn my
pH that should not be a
thing
[Music]
uh-oh oh what the
huh Garo
roof Gara roof what
what am I supposed to finish that oh
that I did not I literally didn't know
where I was shooting that I just
randomly spit it out I did not think it
would complete the
star all right a star wait I need the
tip tip please
hello hello you were so happy to send
one before now I have to force
you well that's kind of fun I wish that
was possible IRL shooting stars back
into the universe oh I got a gem for it
where is it placed unbelievable before
that one too okay no wonder I didn't
have a bunch of these cuz they were all
to the left to the left now what is this
go back down
or guess that's probably all you can do
[Music]
here
nice hello to the left to the
left thank you for that big elepant oh
and oh my God he actually let me go
without toad so so
kind so kind how do I get the chest ah
told
you can you open the chest please make
yourself useful one one time only come
on is it too much to
ask apparently but I randomly got money
thank you
can I look for
it a
to the other toad is in there what are
we going to do about that toad we need a
bomb maybe if there's a portal to the
world with the
bomb a coincidence there's a portal
right
here if we get rid of these two Toads we
will never have to see them again
probably what a great motivation come on
surely the bomb was here then right
away come on come
on although no the bomb was like
underground kind of like where what
would I
bring has to be
something around here or to the right I
don't
know oh that's where we
are what what that brings me back to L
that's where I just came from okay these
portals are getting
confusing I'm not thinking with portals
anymore because they're
[Music]
confusing come on we need something to
set on fire oh yeah I guess we don't
need
a we don't need a bomb we just need fire
yeah why am I thinking bomb so
aggressive so
destructive I think
I think we could probably get fire
um in the kitchen again the fire
chicken fire chicken fire chicken
chicken Phoenix
[Music]
what but why did I need the portal I can
just walk through the door can I not
maybe not eh but I think I have to eh
is this what the chicken
[Music]
was uh oh it's
stuck
okay will it burn will the chicken
continue to burn no it seems
[Music]
not then my other
idea come mind because I I I can't seem
to take it through the door would be
because this was like continuously
following me do I set this chicken on
fire instead somehow and then move it
that seems weird
too
[Music]
um I had the logs in the plant room
where the hell was the plant
room
[Music]
um
plant the first where I also got the
bucket from huh
um
okay it was all there come on so I
go through
here very complicated
nowo you get the lock that was very
sus I guess we just bring the log sorry
now it's wet but it will surely still
burn
[Music]
go for the same portal and we'll run for
the now not for the ice portal yet
because we first have to set it on
fire would be even more amazing if they
sent you for all four portals like first
you have to put some oil on the log or
something I don't know in a different
room and then you have to set it on fire
in another
room okay
kitchen wait I guess I could have gone
for the never mind I can't go through
doors with this I have to go through the
portals
[Music]
so was there fire in the portal over
here on the left on the
right oh it
was now it just has to stay like this
never mind
good I love the way he's holding
it
so we went through three portals huh
not we should melt as many things as we
can is there more that we want to melt
maybe for a little gem fish no no is
that are we good what what if I lay it
on the
ground
no
okay I found a real treasure [\h__\h] you do
wo all right
baby oh what what did that do what does
that
do what does that
do what does it
mean fire
thereare
[Music]
why wait the thing is it goes back right
away
[Music]
whatever yeah let's just save the second
to purple to or blue I think might be
the lighting but I think it's purple
yeah welcome back to the real
world just just the Box just the
box it can't just be a
box
yellow
[Music]
M yeah yeah yeah I know what to do I
know I know what to do I know what to do
I already figured it all
out I don't that's so weird why is it so
weird leave me leave
me on this K it really bothers
me
[Music]
it's wait wait wait yeah wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait I want
both of you no no no no oh no no no no
no can I can I get how many are there oh
there's
[Music]
threee two come
on
whatever because if I only get one they
keep on interrupting
me all right all right all right right
right right right all right all right
all right all right okay oh
yeah sanity going back up
almost yeah the sanity of the Toads is
going down however they're absolutely
losing it hey oh now with two it's going
to be even harder to get through doors
can you
um who the [\h__\h] programmed this game who
programmed the the smartness of the toad
HH I want to I want to destroy you how
am I supposed to go through any kind of
door
[Music]
no how I how
I wait this one's calm how how how do I
how do I calm down my
children he's caling
like how do I how do I let him go
without shooting
him cuz then he panics doesn't
he wait no he's calm okay so being shot
once by
me come on calms them
[Music]
down thought that would make them
Panic look at my stupid
kids it's like I have
twins the only difference is the
color almost
[Music]
like all right toads um you may not know
except for the green one what I'm about
to do but don't don't worry it's not
going to be weird it's not going to be
freaky you will probably
survive you'll not be burned alive or
stabbed through the cage oh
full my troop are reporting for Duty H
okay wait wait wait wait wait what am I
supposed to do
first
be no wait wait what's going on no okay
you can actually that helps me oh wait
that's scary what's going on what do I
take care of first what do I take care
of
first [\h__\h] out there so much to
suck come on wait where did you go
where'd you go where'd you go where'd
you
go oh he dropped him he dropped off my
kids
ow boo boo I'm losing my sanity what
does this
mean why can I not find you ever even
though I go into the direction where ah
where I think you would
be oh no oh no
why are you not
there oh there we go finally why I
see I got the tongue I want the
suckong [\h__\h]
off that's it that's it I'm doing this
[Music]
one I don't
care I'm so tired of the
chaos there we go there we go there we
go oh there's still one of those but
he's busy with those
[Music]
okay are you fine now what what WR why
are you still not dead usually it only
takes two hit but I guess he in this big
room he doesn't get as many
bounces
oh
oh randomly randomly cing
places
oh
whatever no
I wait wait [\h__\h]
a so
busy where is he
[Music]
now once my hands are free I'm taking
down my
f I
do it's a big chunk I'm telling
you it went I would say relatively okay
though but not ideal why is it still
like this does it need a second turn
[Music]
or
what why is it
SE
come no it's
bug
Oh Come mind
oh
okay at least it came back okay once to
was
out
hello second
attempt no more surprises please
[Music]
sanity
check yeah I'm losing it I'm losing it
but we're getting there we're getting
there Che one more time here I wanted to
check this no
[Music]
wait there's another wait if I do this
again do I get a reward no it doesn't
show targets anymore but he went in the
delete
stay okay I think that's too difficult
to accomplish because you cannot really
see the other side but tell me if that
gives you another
gem oh now you stay in
there well then I'll
try come here come here come here
here come here where are you he's
playing hide and seek
[Music]
now okay I need to try this now but it's
hard because there's
no
[Music]
uh no there's
no signs
now like here
[Music]
CL
enough didn't make
it I mean the other one got in so this
has to be possible how are you just the
other one gets in pretty
easily go in
[Music]
oh oh oh I did it no nothing
nothing after all of that
oh come on nothing guys
not
really
oh come on he's so nice he's just like
come
on get your [\h__\h] together is what he's
thinking but he just says it so nicely
nicest way
ever before I send off my
children let me check out this
here the Terrace what is
this this reminds me in the museum um no
actually in the Basilica
specifically we saw like these kind of
pedestals pedestals for statues that
were like br broken um so the pedestals
weren't carrying anything but I was like
think I said to narissa and she found
that particularly funny I'm such she
said and I
said maybe our acrylic stands would sell
better if we if we sold them on nice
like Stone big pedestals like
these you is that funny right I I can't
say it well I'm I'm I'm not good at
saying things at all I'm bad at talking
using language but uh but no like for
real though like instead of those small
plastic uh
fin like uh things round standies how
about we put them on like actual pestles
not not out of
stone but
something cooler than just a round
plastic thing that says copyright cover
and whatever
huh here you go still lightweight it can
still be plastic so just something that
isn't
flat oh bronze bus those places where
you can put a set of acrylic are more T
yeah have you guys been been buying any
of the uh breaking Dimensions things
I've been asked to advertise
perhaps if I would like to advertise
once again so I guess I will uh
because there's
pictures and you can align if you would
so want to do
this have you guys gotten the breaking
Dimensions one because those poses are
really cool okay and just like with the
Hol talk one where I intended for people
to put on there whichever member they
want on you can do
this you can put H
Tony on
there right wow you can put any
combination you
[Music]
want so those are also I don't have a
link right now but those are also on
sale on the Hol live online shop or
perhaps GE Jack too probably sorry I
don't have a link just look it up
breaking Dimensions acrylic stands on
Google and it will probably come
up I really like these because we're in
fighting poses and all we're all uh we
all are using our weapons so that's
pretty sick that's pretty rare to be
honest wallet CL is crying I know I know
[Music]
yeah you can make your own units or
remake the units that sold out according
to gek tack okay it's already so oh May
oh they told me a few days ago when I
was in vanice so it must have like
finished
[Music]
selling in the meantime huh is it done
oh yeah literally
yesterday ah [\h__\h]
I'm no meaningless advertisement okay
the money you have now saved you must
use for my Anniversary merchandise that
is coming
soon well you saw there's some group
stuff too right that was uh shown off at
the 3D live that we did hello yeah
remember I know there's like so much
merch going on and I I really like feel
for you guys that's I don't even want to
advertise it
um but at least you know I'm just
mentioning it in case you want to get
something but I understand you
[Music]
know the color of the metal doesn't
matter
[Music]
told yeah I know there's like so much
merch and I'm I know like it's
overlapping too much it's crazy it's
really bad
like but um to
me it would be important I get a I get a
bigger share you know if it's my my own
m
so can't say how
much so uh my anniversary merch uhhuh
uhhuh it's coming up
soon you I love your Yan voice thank
you actually just today in the morning I
recorded the another voice pack the the
anniversary one which I wrote myself a
really ex extensive ex no that's not the
is that the word I'm looking for
it's a pretty long one I not not as long
as the The Voice drama with
myth but I wrote something an
imagination in my brain that I had while
I was on the airplane it's all in my
head guys but I want you to listen to
what I came up with so coming
[Music]
soon thank you I was like at least at
least like they didn't give me much yand
to go with but the last he's got to hit
strong
right am I right or am I right
[Music]
M fun H yeah let's
go well at least we got the boo in both
so far I'm going to go back to this one
but do I have to go do the whole thing
or can I leave the level after I did
the you're giving me something now what
oh you're just repeating what you gave
to me in the first try
huh thank you
unknown I'm just so salty about how that
went wish there was an extended full
cycle version I wish so too I
wish no I'm option what do you mean no
[Music]
and whatever voice
pack I'm sorry I don't think she does
voice packs much like she probably never
signs up for
them at least she was oh I think some
people were hoping for a solo am voice
pack when they saw the
myth voice pack at in the
beginning and then I'm sorry to
disappoint you but it was uh not a solo
voice
bag but I
mean you guys listen to it
right that was really worth
[Music]
it yeah
remember like the English language thing
that we did that was mostly aimed at
Japanese people but I said you know the
voice pack is kind of fun so you can
listen to that even if you already speak
English um like that
one I asked the the girls originally at
that time like hey do we maybe want to
like get together in Discord and just
record our
allines at the same time while hearing
each other because I think it will help
getting
things oh get no I always got this much
but that just kind of didn't work out no
I don't think people really answered my
my
call um that didn't really work out this
time this time we did
that we were all like hearing each other
so
I would say that definitely helped and
impacted with
how how in the sink or like how
everybody is just more on the same
wavelength you know what I
[Music]
mean I think the other ones weren't bad
either it wasn't like crazy noticeable
what did I do here again
it wasn't crazy noticeable I would say
but it's definitely better when
everybody's able to hear each other
although it's a little bit embarrassing
uh to the well the well but nothing's
accessible right now how did I make it
accessible
how door so the dog takes the key ah
okay uh I just saw on the map it's
closed so I didn't even want to
[Music]
try just using logic but I guess that
was flawed logic to the
game go Dog go go and I'll take that
money I'll take the extra money the ones
that's easily
accessible do it work again
[Music]
did I go for the well definitely
right uh how did I do that again
ah what time zone are you in I'm in
Austria I have the same time zone time
zones as like a lot of European cities
like Paris
Berlin oh it's
the just in c e
[Music]
s GMT plus two right now
yeah sometimes GMT plus
one did I have to watch over here
was there no
need maybe there was no need well okay
we
[Music]
got let's not talk about
that freaking golden
[Music]
animals rudest
behavor I thought he wouldn't hit me
two
[Music]
two oh oh okay this time this time I
manifested
it
uhoh going to work
[Music]
out don't leave me alone leave me alone
leave me alone leave me alone
no I am going to die can you believe it
I hate this
[Music]
game why did I even
bother why did I even
bother
CH stop your [\h__\h] chaa chaa chaa
let's just go
[Music]
no okay a train to catch yeah yeah yeah
we have a train to catch and that train
is called end of game train come
on Mario Mario
Mario all right he was captured too I
forgot about him again we not just
forget about him again and maybe take
the main role in everything in the
future just paint just put on some red
gloves and that's call Early the
day how did he get captured this that
but we didn't know yet did we not were
we not aware of
this you want to say that one has a a
crown is that what you're saying
oh okay how close do you want to [\h__\h]
go I see the
CP was that supposed to scare me it
actually didn't this pisses me
off just pisses me off man oopsy what
was
[Music]
that train
exhibit there's a train exhibit
fun for train
lovers all right let's go let's
go thanks for the membership
welcome we're back in here all right I
don't quite dislike this place I I don't
mind
it how come you guys don't react to my
flashbang
eh why don't you
[Music]
the courtyard it seems we have to go to
the
Courtyard once again Jam in this room
where how
[Music]
hey yo you don't have do you have no
only that one I asked how and that's
probably it right away I found it I
found
it thank you for the hint though yay we
backtracked a little
bit
[Music]
yippe have you always been so aggressive
sir I call you being this aggressive
what's wrong with you now who hurt
[Music]
you what am I looking for ah going to
the court yet
[Music]
right talk princess chicken Queen
Phoenix parttime waria
mhm
mhm I know I know rooms like spray out
again because there's something new to
find is that
it so I was wondering like why are they
gr out if I already went there
up that's sus
[Music]
I don't
know the to probably the tot's probably
made them aggressive just Yeah by
running around
here they're gone now they can't hurt
you
[Music]
anymore I guess we're going up
no
what
ah maybe I have to use
my how do
huh how do I
[Music]
this how do I get to places now what did
what was the where is the sign here when
there's
there must be a way to
proceed how about
how
can't figure it out
yet can you move the
gear
[Music]
this no
is there something to
[Music]
turn the
stairs from here probably not
huh do I do it from a different
[Music]
room did eat that give you something um
I mean not that I
[Music]
can I was going to say nothing that I
can activate with my buttons like
[Music]
that what what do you mean exactly I
wasn't inter acting with it I was like
glowing and blowing and
[Music]
everything I just didn't get close
enough to see the eggs
okay okay I'm
sorry do you see my sanity it's not very
high and therefore my intelligence wait
a
[Music]
second what about the other places I
could go to
I'm curious I will go there first
because I I like to play jrpg
[Music]
games there's a ghost in here I can s it
because it's
dark Sparkle Sparkle
[Music]
to see
kfp oh this place again a
Terrace those stars are crazy man that's
such a pretty night
[Music]
sky what
nothing why did you open your mouth then
what ghost
no okay but I heard him laugh y why is
this how is this a
ship he disappears and I get too
close oh you can W
tal
octopus I could go through that door
probably if I stand right by it
maybe I got to do that
[Applause]
first
okay should I not go into this room
first is there a different room to do
first like this
one o
books Ena might like this
place O train exhibit H cute but that
kind of reminded me of something that
looked like
something
balloons balloons
why
why ah okay
that we like to see that
[Music]
oh yeah is that a gem
or wait I skipped the scene what what
did I get from
it why are you calling me hello maybe he
will tell me what just happened last it
goes the page in the bookshelf won't
open without the book he took ah he took
the book
okay the Periscope doesn't work well in
that Mansion but I'll try to find him
give it a second come on you piece of
brilliantly designed JK bingo
the pain of skiper skiper yeah but we
got to go fast you know find the poter
guys what the the you
mean do you
mean do you mean the stop oh my
[Music]
God oh my God at least they're not
hitting me
now does he mean the the dog
[Music]
I already looked for here did I
yeah okay well then let's look at the
footsteps
[Music]
steppies
okay rude as
okay no
[Music]
um no what what's happening no what's
happening God oh God no no
no
[Music]
no this is so triggering
[Laughter]
[Music]
why you suddenly so easily easy to be
sucked it's just the tiny ones I guess
[Music]
it's okay each page has quite the
triggering moments but all in all I'm
actually still
fine now dog I can't this door is fake
how am I supposed to get to you
[Music]
cuz that room
is quite the mystery to me to be
honest seems as if this is not the right
time for it oh never mind maybe
that why why would I want to bring that
down
can't can't influence
that maybe getting the ghost have to
make the door not
fake no I don't believe it cuz it's
still not on the map no I'm not going to
even I'm not even going to test
it it's not the dog there's no principal
oh okay you can close the window oh [\h__\h]
there's a
window
that hey hey hey hey hey
hey I thought maybe you were going to
kiss me at least but that's just
mean she's like don't [\h__\h] touch me
don't you dare touch
me what window are we talking
about there is a door there I'm fast
no it's like I got to place something
there
take my
place I like the helmet but I can't take
the helmet
either on the
ceiling
[Music]
what I that one it's so hard to see
it's not really going away is there
another
[Music]
one I'm so pissed off can you guys
please give me
all I don't have PA
[Music]
I'm losing
it oh I should suck the steam okay I
thought it would go away on his on
although we had that before somewhere
but I should have remembered
[Music]
now
I don't really feel like it's filling up
but I'm I'm I'm um
manually um no what's the word what's
the word word for fake
um I'm I'm filling it up with
[Music]
chocolate artificially
yeah spawn camping ah is that what we
resort to now
no not like you needed that [\h__\h] you I'm
pulling in
[\h__\h]
[Music]
you stop making it so difficult
no
no leave me alone leave me alone leave
me
[Music]
alone give me the H give me H get give
me the
[Music]
heart
no
[Music]
no what this mean what this
mean I okay Smart Cookie Smart Cookie
Tak
[Music]
this's probably for
later wait
what wait what
oh
oh not
up not up
[Music]
and
now what
[Music]
now where side
can use the balloon seon the other rooms
are hopping for
portals
[Music]
okay give me
J
Maga expected
more back to the Turning stairs ah okay
okay okay okay I arrived because I went
into the room on the right
[Music]
I grab a play Super Mario 604 at this
point no I don't know that that's going
to be worse
maybe it's all just
torture freaking baby games all just
[Music]
torture
okay I think we should go to the left
now I don't know if you could oh could
have even gone to the
middle but it just makes more sense as a
JRP player to go to the side paths first
am I
[Music]
right let me
go where did my money
[Music]
go well thank you
this music is so
comical you're going to be the end of me
I I
[Music]
can't no no don't touch me don't touch
me no no no no no
[Music]
look no touch is it's so hard to
understand don't touch the Green Man mhm
h space he might be hiding there space
exib okay wait where is that did I go
there
[Music]
before what are you going to stay up
there ah
no hey hey hey I thought they would come
down I was waiting for
[Music]
them let me just me just get this
thing don't tangle money in front of me
and then take it away from me a
[Music]
ah no
that is what I
[Music]
need okay
okay don't hurt me don't hurt me okay
[Music]
H we cannot let the staty hit
zero we don't want to know what happens
[Music]
then oh hello there money go you want to
go to space I'll send you to space Oh I
don't know it won't let me hit it won't
let me it won't let me pull
hey what's wrong with
you e
how do I get him out I can't pull it it
doesn't say
a like this
one oh hey
[Music]
portal okay let's take a look into the
space need more chocolate
okay oh big brain
ghost of course you wanted a book
because you need your brain to become
bigger makes sense
[Music]
H what I didn't skip anything now what's
going
on what
why what Happ what why are we here now
[Music]
what what are we doing I I'm not
mentally prepared for a fight like this
right
now can I suck the
stars and shoot them
back
no uh maybe I okay like this like this
no oh that's funny that's funny that's
funny
[Music]
really okay I just
okay I'm thinking
complicated w
be be what is this fight oh bombs okay
do I need one and
like was I supposed to do something with
them uhoh
uhoh I'm going
to I'm going to lose
it no I'm just going to lose
it
what huh yeah
is there a sign to where he will be oh
is he just always on this platform with
me I thought he was be by the St
[Music]
no 40 HP is really not good
come on give me a good
one I couldn't I waited to long I don't
know what this with these bombs I just
run the way here but I'm assuming we I
just have to dodge and not use them to
explode something oh God oh God oh God
oh God oh God oh God okay explode and
then let me get the heart disappeared
okay cool oh [\h__\h] oh no okay wait do
they get parts please be so kind no no
no don't call
me there you
go he has not so much more
left
yes
[Music]
yes yeah why was that so Random though
like if they would have shown me a scene
where I got like sucked through it or so
that would make sense to
[Music]
me well I
didn't I didn't get sucked through it I
was suddenly
there first game has something similar
so did they purposefully just give it no
no
Segway the door is open guys
is
[Music]
yippe so we are at the train exhibit
let's
[Music]
go top tier Ghost Hunter nice Dodge
there shut up
[Music]
I hate you so much I hate you I I
can't this game needs so much more
sanity than the other Luigi games
oh my
[Music]
God sad he's
almost 15 minutes can do a lot in this
game honestly I I feel more like a
zero but I need to drag it out also I've
been trying to AR officially inas my
canity by eating chocolate
balls I do my tasas let's
go friend oh thank you Game for throwing
me a bone every once in a
while but this just feels like a really
abusive relationship that we
[Music]
have I just feel like we don't work
together
[Music]
we really
don't we really
[Music]
don't and this isn't much of a train
exhibition if there's no train passing
by never mind maybe there will if I
finish these
tracks oh my God I was right I was just
like making [\h__\h]
assumptions can I get in w
[Music]
CH
chaa sanity restored by
[Music]
train what's happening I'm refilling my
sanity what what just
happen I got a j even better I'm was
just happy being on the
train and it makes me really
happy I like train
follow
train
train is new best
[Music]
friend guys are so
small
what
Mario why is everything so small
[Music]
yellow Luigi is such a good guy he
should just leave Mario behind and get
all the
sponsorships instead of Mario
mhm ow you're bringing me back okay I
guess I did my job oh
yes I did it
under half an hour
28 bronze
[Music]
100%
what what I got hit so much so
stupidly
huh n
maybe because it was just under 30
minutes but I feel like I wasn't even
fast it was just my usual speed okay
whatever I'll take
it I need a massage guys a massage would
be
nice but I had
like a really good massage in Japan
before my
flight and they're more expensive
here I was thinking of getting a massage
in Venice but the hotel oh my God those
were like the most expensive massage
prices I've ever seen before I think
even in the mules it was cheaper and
that was a
resort
so there I didn't give you one um
no I didn't want to ask for it
because you know I don't want to bother
her she did M Massage me a little bit in
the moldiv when she saw me like
constantly trying to massage
[Music]
myself she actually also has noodle
arms very strong noodle arms no weak
noodle arms
should have known as a well I am like
24/7 in pain like there's literally no
time when I'm not in pain so I will
always appreciate a
massage and especially if it comes
randomly I'm like oh my God I love you
thank you I love you I love people
random
mes yeah
quy oh my God I really got to take her
to the
moldes but then I can get massages from
the professionals and then from quasi
and then from the professionals again
and then
from oh I'm already
getting
like wait we didn't get the bull I do
there was a [\h__\h]
bull why did I not get it well I don't
care I honestly could that's
careless mini camera rescue Mario I
barely read anything what you just
said but wait that level it looked like
it had a different coloring is at the
end of this level and then we get boss
fights
huh no
way no way I mini boss ah okay and then
maybe there's a couple more yeah surely
there are seem too
short training oh wa inside of it how
how did we do that
[Music]
balloons oh
CH honestly if I had someone to give me
a massage every day
that would
probably huh save my life
man I can't pay for someone to give me a
massage every day I would go gross don't
be an expensive
Endeavor oh oh oh oh w w w w what are
you planning to do you're going to
explode I may not be the king but I
should well I big enough to crush
you okay we see see about
[Music]
that cute so cute what do you mean
escape the Trap I have to kill the blue
right wait do I have to like get him
to go to the tree uh the tree the train
and try to make him I can't walk on it
though oh what are you doing you hurt
yourself are you okay oh I
see there we oh that is so no that's
just boo abuse AB
abuse no do I have to shoot them towards
the train again or does it not matter oh
N I should have been faster so I get as
many as
possible oh wait do I want to send them
into these oh should the small ones go
in those I didn't even realize the signs
there and the the
compartments oh no wait do we have to no
not this part I hate that part oh what
this going
on oh okay so I completely failed dads
did
I all right all
right okay get yourself hurt get
yourself a tummy
H Stu and then
what uh
ah come on [\h__\h]
is following oh no my eyes were
following that so I
I anyway it went in did it no only one
one
ah they so cute [\h__\h] I'm so distracted
find cute wait what can I still get some
[Music]
in oh okay I am happy with
that
Yi oh this is cute this is a cute fight
I like the idea of
it the boo is just so
lovable I love I just did a peekabo I
just couldn't really see it I wish I
could change the camera angle are you
hurt no boo no let me pull your tongue
it will make things better right ah [\h__\h]
I I somehow I thought it was okay to
just send him to the compartment but
that's the wrong stage hey what are you
doing you're so cute stop being so cute
[Music]
let's do it again boo let's spend some
more
time ever
[Music]
so now do something yeah yeah oh yeah
that's a good jump oh you're such a good
jumper oh ground pound
yeah I know someone who can teach you
the best ground pound
[Music]
wa what is this C come
on
what okay I get another chance on this
one thank God okay is two anyway to
maximum like
[Music]
realistically no
I thought it was already over there
maybe if I reacted that
to going to take a while oh what you
doing boo you're soy don't
[Music]
you not the boo
abuse the [\h__\h]
[Music]
no not [\h__\h] Fair
no it's going to be so hard to hit the
right compartment
now oh
[Music]
no no
okay I starting to feel like in the last
boss battle last
[Music]
time
no let's just focus on this
one a
[Music]
no take my life did I get in one at
least I don't remember shortterm
shortterm
memory you get as many tries at least
Can't Fail like that one true I guess
that's
good but again just the time frame is
too short oh
God
sorry like they disappear and
[Applause]
stuff I'm I know I I got impatient
because it's pissing me
[Music]
off oh oh okay that gets you a free pass
I see
[Music]
ow oh God I I
oh this time he got
[Music]
himself oh home
run let one let one it's going to be too
late too late
[Music]
I was trying to get the
angle there two more yeah but that space
somehow it's really hard to get
there get the angle right
[Music]
starting to get boring there's too many
compartments they should like end it
after I don't know four or five five
maybe okay five would be fine don't you
think it's like a little bit too
many and they could make the hit box
bigger like they make such a they make
such a big hit the box for so many
things and this is where you are leave
the she
[Music]
Le I get
Hearts
[Music]
go yeah we just have to go
again
oh it won't let me I'm I'm sure it w
go no but honestly
[Music]
like
hello
tiresome got rid of some sanity in case
you haven't
noticed yeah
yeah so where's
Mario choo choo fun and all but like
what about Mario Stop Dancing
[Music]
okay okay
brude we get it we get it we get it
[Applause]
pH I'm not okay do I look okay to
you does any of this seem okay to
you this is
not
not I made a Qui take to the p and set
them all down to the oh you
did King blue is still out there and
this won't end until we defeat him
true breaking the fourth wall there a
little bit should have so the garage
[Music]
what he sold the portrait where King Buu
was stuck after the previous
game in a [\h__\h] garage sale
[Music]
what an
idiot what an
idiot this is kind of looking bad
here where are my booze at where my
booze paranormal chaos how many more
guys give me something to work towards
please
the Paris
M final Dark Moon Final dark moon pie
it's hidden beyond that portal and
that's why we haven't found
it free
close I B my GL you'll find Mario's
painting this is the last regular stage
let's go
wa
okay okay inspect the ter okay I don't
think I ever been there I only looked at
it ah maybe it's the middle
path maybe all along I was never
supposed to go or allowed to go through
the middle path because it is in the
middle what because the Paris is
there that would be easy access
now it can't be that simple but he
did this is like oh PG I'm changed this
is like in the previous level previous
Mansion where right around the end they
put
me they ported me right uh close to
where I need to proceed to which was
quite the nice service but if you think
about the trouble I went through
afterwards none of that matters
anymore all
right this one is hard so is it a boss
fight huh
H think so seeing him
there ah he's moring he's using he's
thinking with PTO at least but he's
thinking evilish
devilish almost like a
Dev oh no you know I'm not good with so
many ghosted ones what are you
doing where they
go sh this will be one hell of a level
wait don't tell me I have to go for the
whole mansion and find them all or what
are they all here on the Terrace
Yello uh the Paranormal levels just shot
for the roof this really seriously you
know portal will have to wait if we
don't reduce the paranormality our
Dimension will collapse upon itself I'll
update your map with the ghost locations
look likely
answer okay pumpkins are exciting I'm
not a pumpkin ding dong or something
like that
that got my little figurines now I have
the normal ones and
the my or treat ones speaking of my or
treat October is coming
[Music]
up spooky
season once again as if this isn't
spooky
enough I'm guessing there's none of the
par they're literally like scattered all
over and I have to go go through the
whole mansion again just how I
thought
great I love
it I love
[Music]
it isn't it
lovely is it I want to go back to the
main the first room so I can go for the
portals cuz I'm
guessing that might be
helpful don't touch me don't even think
about
[Music]
it or do I have
to do I have to go over the stairs
again I mean they're everywhere right
[Music]
well I don't even know which portal we
wear
[Music]
anymore hey it's one of the rooms
everything is
okay
[Music]
bely [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm surprised that wasn't enough
guy you are pissing
[Music]
me okay okay okay
more wait a second wait oh okay
a ow
[Music]
what why so
many Dam
it so what's wrong with you these are
Sur the last one are you
T
[Music]
hello oh there's one thank you the game
can hear
[Music]
me yeah those are the last ones okay so
I have a feeling now for what we can
expect here
is this like I still don't really have a
solution for
this oh well I don't care enough
although actually can I still not get
this why
[Music]
not wait what if I pointed
it okay I don't know um
it's a gem so only that's a gem I would
kind of like to have it but if it's too
much
effort then whatever I
[Music]
guess oh by the way I think I had the
best French toast ever in uh Venice like
I've been to a lot of decent hotels
where or or restaurants or so or like
breakfast restaurants where they would
have french toast and most of the time I
would be like the one that I make is
kind of better so this is kind of
disappointing but they had a really good
one both me and Nissa ate it I think why
it was so good and I want to try this
out on my own is because they kind of
French Bret the top French Bret uh crane
Bret the
top there's a counter what do you mean
there's a counter
[Music]
I'm you [\h__\h] you tell me that
now he did say that Chad told me
too
H well anyway next time I want to try I
guess all you have to do is put some
sugar brown sugar whatever on top of the
French toast and then burn it and then
you have a cranber french toast I want
to try it blah blah
[Music]
blah but what about the
frogs what about the
frogs I don't know M this is stressing
me out
a this is stretching me out I'm going to
panic I'm rcking I'm
panicing
wait
wait wait someone just fall down here
that's probably
faster no there's no way I'm making it
there's actually no way this is not
realistic cuz
like with a pain in the ass
I'm not going to make
it I'm
fingy I should have done this from the
start I Hur
myself well these ones are easier so
maybe I H
myself I hate
this what color do you want
blue okay
[Music]
I hate this I hate
this
R I hate this I hate this it's not
fair because where is the timer why
don't you show it the whole time why
don't you show it prely
giving me a sense of security so
rude
green this is so over it's so maybe it
stops when you're in a room actively
already fighting against them oh M Mia
Mama
m i can you leave me alone
sh
[Music]
okay it went down once like this
but
[Music]
now I I used secret
cheat it didn't do it completely
but
catx
catex [\h__\h]
this
[\h__\h] okay no problem no problem if I
don't just run away into a completely
different place
should be very fine I mean still rage
and
deing
fine
fine fine
fine wait I still have to inspect the
Terrace
okay yeah whatever um hello hello at
least there's no timer running yet
hello hello
a here I come it's like I don't even get
a bone maybe maybe there's a way to get
a bone before you get into these
fights but I wouldn't know of
it
BL ya
yeah
okay it's a timer on the specific room
if you leave her room uncaptured too
long you will trigger the
countdown not an old
okay
H so it only maybe moves
on while I'm in one of the ghost rooms
[Music]
so what you
saying H it can oh what you mean it's
the other way
[Music]
around
whatever ideally I would like both of
you honestly because otherwise it's
going to be difficult as we have seen
before
oh my God oh my God oh why is it not
pulling
legitimately [\h__\h]
[Music]
yourself did you just touch
me yeah don't get so cocky just because
you have an emote dedicated to your ugly
ass face on YouTube doesn't mean
anything is this room finished or what I
think it's
[Music]
finished was that wait was that
it huh
what what it almost feels wrong
What Am I game
[Music]
suddenly
skills suddenly see
more suddenly I see
[Music]
more put these green ones
man there's
so so
chaotic okay okay okay how about we
just restart no actually can I can I
please just get all free no no
no why not why
not huh a boot a
boot I don't want to be in that corner I
don't want to be in that corner I don't
want to be in that corner I don't want
to be
[Music]
hey
BL bullies
[Music]
that's they giving me no
break why are you so
mean oh my God what am I supposed to
do it's not
[Music]
sucking I'm pulling away
what how what do you mean I didn't get
all
free I obviously did
[Music]
wow
sh I do
[Music]
I don't know which one it is I don't
know I don't
know it's not the E is
[Music]
it
I'm I thought
space what happened what happened what
happened why did you change
position
what no no no no I saw
you what why you chilling what are you
fixing your unexist hair for
HH is that what you guys are all mad
towards me about hair loss oh yeah
yeah are you happy here well I can't
just go to the next room and ignore this
a bone a bone why thank you so much
game but what I can I can't ignore this
can
I what does that
mean better than onion here what my hair
is so luses and
[Music]
beautiful people would kill for my hair
people would die from my hey
banana hey no not the kitchen
go you don't play with Bo did you learn
that from your mommy your ghost
[Music]
mommy rude
hey
[Music]
hey okay let's do a small one and then a
triple
[Music]
because it's too much for triple to kill
him this work yeah
I is this room done yes
the kitchen
shrink oh did the kitchen
sink let that
sinking let the
sink one of the best jokes
of
humanity
let no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no please stop it is a
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay
wait oh
yeah don't mess it up
[Music]
I still haven't seen like an EAD a
reminder for the timer so it's probably
going well what are we getting anywhere
if we take this
portal M
it
oh what where do I how do I huh
why is that room red
though I could get there I guess for
here and then maybe up and then where
where's your Red Room go to Red Room
first
[Music]
okay I means go to that one first
mhm is of the utmost
important oh
what what's what was the what was the
thing with you nothing really ah you
just really pissed me off with like your
[Music]
spit yeah okay okay okay okay okay okay
I won and take a step
[Music]
back another one and take a step
back [\h__\h] you you now hey I got too
close
okay and this and now we take a that
bag what are you doing you are you
healing or
something that's against the
[Music]
rules oh okay I went I went all in on
that one
did something else change in this room
then like some rooms have been changing
obviously wait
the I want the the
[Music]
M it's going down no
okay is there a poo in
[Music]
here I don't
care
no why was he laughing why did I hear
him laugh he's in my head he's in my
head he's in my head
no I hate these don't touch
me shut up I'm doing my best shut
[Music]
up if I'm not if this is not the last
one if I'm failing this I cannot promise
anything guys what is what what what
what what is this do I need to go
[Music]
down can I fall down no I don't have
enough time I don't have so much time oh
not the mummies okay if I burn them if I
get them to like go over here oh there's
one not non mommy already
[Music]
how does he not get affected by
that oh I got
BM we have a chance guys we have a
[Music]
chance or do we I don't really know what
what what's with this oh oh
another
[Music]
double is it over oh yeah is it over is
it over get back to the
Terrace is there still time like a timer
to get there for here by any chance oh
what's the shortest way to the Terrace
is there still timer I don't
know time are gone I wish I hope time
are gone okay scary [\h__\h]
[Music]
man um okay an upstairs portal okay
okay thank you there's just too many
portals it's very
confusing I want to pull
this there was a go gold golden ghost in
here before I don't think I ever ended
up getting
it that's messed up man what's this
oops someone forgot their shoes I needed
fire a
man I wait how do you guys what I
[Music]
forgot what's this room have I ever been
here how do you
[Music]
oh
how was my day fine thanks I woke up at
6:30 well slept then had a thing work
thing and recorded voice pag I'm
recording
made a
thumbnail my dream I I dreamed about me
having a math exam upcoming so I kind of
had to cancel my streams I was like
sorry guys what's with all the
cancellations in my dreams
man oh [\h__\h] oh
[Music]
bully wait if it's red does that also
pound I guess
let me get the
[Music]
money yeah I went grocery
shopping
[Music]
okay yeah I I haven't done that much I
don't know I just um had a nap in
between watch a little bit of Lord of
the no um R of
[Applause]
[Music]
power oh does that go automatically into
to my account it better I got to watch
the archive to see if that went
somewhere otherwise I'm calling the
Nintendo guest service customer service
hotline oh there's more and more coming
out of there someone stop him I'm not
going to If I Die Here do I have to redo
everything
I grab a [\h__\h]
die don't get hit don't get
hit tell the [\h__\h] do
[Music]
home
I hate
[Music]
heart
drops
perhaps
sh
[Music]
M I'm scared I'm scared I'm scared I'm
scared looking
on oh
[Music]
oh critical hit all my
sanity what to
die
no oh no no I can't
no
no no
way where's my
hat
cute
[Music]
no no no no don't whole thing the whole
thing I'm in
disbelief oh my God this
game oh my God
um if I wasn't a streamer I would
immediately end this and never touch
this game again I
[Music]
think I would already be probably gone
at the end of last like before the end
of last
[Music]
stream
I no I I'm like trying to tell myself I
can't like stop now when I'm so close to
end of the game but at the same time I'm
I I'm baffled that I have to do this
whole thing
again what a pain in the
anus I I I can't believe it I can't
believe
it this is unbelievable
[Music]
unbelievable can't be
real cannot be real shut
up
Hello thank you dog
Hood
[Music]
but I'm sorry but there's like best
games of the year titles that I give
away and I'm not going to say it but you
know where I'm going with
[Music]
this and that's
like
[Music]
crazy it to's punishment mhm
I I I just I
I
I I I I know I'm not the best at this
game but
like I mean look at these conditions
like this like normal does look normal
to you
[Music]
I
BR bro
[Music]
bro bro
what's going
on is going on what
[Music]
the need to remember where I got the
bone cuz the bone is vital
I do
it where was the B can you guys remind
me ice H okay I all right is there any
way to get two
bones would there even be two bones
[Music]
somewhere no golden ghost wouldn't give
me a bone but
[Music]
don't think so okay what goes on in the
mind of people who designed this for
real
what aren't these Games supposed to be
played by
kids and I play games for a
living um
could be like at least on the level of
the
kit right like and so it should be
playable for
me he not some kind of
rodal or is it what are we doing why are
we going to circle
okay this one became easy oh wait
there's more one more two
[Music]
more I
mean s dancing
yeeha oh stop stoping and creeping
need a bit more Hearts than
that is there actually like the pumpkins
is it just like sometimes maybe there's
a heart in it is there always money in
them because like how can they not put
Hearts somewhere there is it Hearts
hidden somewhere in that last part just
so for next time just so that I know uh
where am I supposed to
go where should I go for that one I
don't know
thank you for the pink Super
Chat only the ghosts oh my God catching
them at low Health oh God should we go
ice AG I don't know what's the next one
but I'm just going to go there seems
good seems
[Music]
good okay I'm scared
these are at least not like interrupting
me as
[Music]
much the room with the green ones is one
of the worst if they don't they just
interrupting me they don't hurt
me so you're going up in my a list of no
give me money
no going up but like this is just a
cult I hate you all
okay well now the thing that I
appreciated about you isn't so fun
anymore
either was there more no it was just two
in
[Music]
here
bone okay
[Music]
yeah where where should I go uh should I
go for the portal again
should I go to the Garden again is it
time for the big fat
one it's not red this
[Music]
time huh oh
well why is it not red did I did I
forget
one how did I stand
[Music]
you're so rude okay but last time it
took me a while to get into the group
with this one oh how am I
still saying maybe this time it won't
take me as
[Music]
long let's go away let's go
away oh oh
God I'm sorry you guys have to sit
through this with
[Music]
me
sorry but we'll come out of this
[Music]
stronger for sure we
next still up there okay but also here
oopsie oh well I'll do these now cuz I'm
closer to them having a nice time with
your
screams the Journey of building a strong
B
yay green ones and yellow ones red
one not
sure why
okay hello guys I hate you what before
there was only one
[Music]
mommy you're not falling down
really why not
[Music]
thank you D
monkey okay let's let's let's let's get
into come on Bonk yourself against
something please green go be so kind to
me have some mercy on me
[Music]
taking me for a damn ride but I got you
I got you it's the waa grip he the
[Music]
W it seems
qu One Stop spinning wobble wobble
wobble
wobble wait I should don't know this is
the
best P to take
[\h__\h] now they're all
red okay go this way well there's a
portal there I wonder know which one it
is I don't have time to ask you and
think about it so I'm just going to
run wouldn't mind another cat watch
H don't worry I'm not really interested
in watching it
[Music]
again why are you why are you like this
sh get out of there get out of there
they're not your
friends
no
okay can't believe I'm still playing
this can't believe
it does not deserve my time of day at
all which musical are we talking about
actually um you know how Nara likes to
always talk about musicals she did tell
me about one ah Phantom of the Opera cuz
she like was randomly singing about it
singing it and I kind of I don't know
I'm interested in that one I wouldn't
mind watching
it the moment I show some interest she
she pulls it up on YouTube she's
like this and that this she's always so
excited so
[Music]
eager I don't know how
to okay I'll get there
so cute she's so excited about it such a
passion for it shut up last time he said
that I only had one more room left shut
up shut up go away is [\h__\h]
distracting
me somehow I can't push the button to
get his dialogue away like usual so I'm
instead of flashing my my
[Music]
[\h__\h] what I don't understand I don't
understand I don't understand how do I
get there apparently I'm on the wrong
floor I thought I misunderstood the
[Music]
M I don't know what
[\h__\h] why am I not there why am I
here oh the colors my time okay but like
previously there were green and yellow
ones okay
from the ice
bortle okay but then does that mean I
have to walk back
here was that really the best
way getting back now how am I supposed
to do this this the time the time stops
taking right when I when I'm in the
ghost
room right right that thing right
don't not that door that's an evil
[Music]
door I
capture do I look like I have time for
playing these games
now I'm going to R
this game sucks this game
sucks wow I'm about
to I'm about to I'm about to bre quit
and never go back to this game ever
again I don't think I can make it
anymore I don't think one 1 minute 40 I
don't think I can make it
[Music]
anymore not [\h__\h] heads
[\h__\h] yourself [\h__\h]
[Music]
yourself the [\h__\h] banana
my
[Music]
God
fu
stop I CED one but
supp means capture
[Music]
all oh I'm losing I've lost it I don't
own anything anymore my pockets are
empty I am lost forever I'm lost
Callie come to collect me it's all
[Music]
over oh
yeah what
now this room not down is there one
ghost left a
[Music]
whoa pH
I
can't I
[Music]
can't no no
no huh hm
[Music]
helloe
okay okay okay oh I'm
crying okay no not you guys why do I
choose you first oh God
no get
[Music]
her my ear my eyes are so wet
M
[Music]
baby my eyes okay
okay
what this is is is is there anywhere
where I can go through this that would
be nice to go through
now yeah okay
okay wait which
one
uh
wait top top to to to to
[Music]
they're all connected guys they're all
connected sound insane but they're
connected they
[Music]
are get out of there
no no no no
[Music]
what what did I do to you what did I
what am I doing
wrong why do you hate me so much
no I'm not going to stop because I'm so
close to
it I know you might be thinking oh
no wa is
doing is repeating
history but me absolutely losing my sity
it just kind of give me a different
point of view now you know I'm thinking
differently now I have reached a level
of just like
whatever like
whatever I've I've come I think I in the
past 2 minutes or five or six I have
come
to you know I have forgot the work but I
have come to you know whatever you say
whatever the phrase is I feel feel
perhaps better now than the acceptance I
mean I've I've been for some [\h__\h] you
know in a short amount of
time I may have laughed I may have
screamed I may have cried I accept that
this is [\h__\h] that this is pure [\h__\h] but
it's not my fault it's not my fault it's
not my
[Music]
fault and I'm not going to let this game
get the best of me
then I'm going to be feeling just
incomplete we
don't I will however try
to I know you can charge it but like I
usually don't have enough time oh never
mind actually I thought that was m
logging in
[Music]
him oh
[\h__\h] huh last as many as I can yeah I
know I know ideally I always want to go
with more than
[Music]
one [\h__\h]
hell oh yeah
[Music]
okay the whole portal
maze I'm starting to understand it I'm
thinking with portals not the green one
not the Green Oh green I
[Music]
didn't okay well
okay see they were not visible I
guess okay how did that boot protect you
are there some ug boots or
[Music]
what I always think he's trying to hit
me but he's just live now he does try to
hit
[Music]
me see am I not doing better now
I'm I mean mentally don't I sound
of sound
[Music]
mind huh
what
[Music]
yeah no I'm fine
oh this went better than before maybe
maybe that was my best run now what is
the best course of actually
shut
up sorry I hate him ch's in the
way what's the how do I get
I'm icing
[Music]
hi hi hi
hi
[Music]
no
no whatever these are kind of
okay oh that was a time baby now or
never woo
I want the money I don't want your
ass you went
[Music]
there let's
go [\h__\h] hell where are you taking me
it's abducting me can you shut up can
you shut up can you please shut up can
you please shut up can you please to
shut
up okay where's the best way to
go back for the portal or no down I can
go down straight
down I don't know probably same amount
of
[Music]
time can't believe that
like I ran out of time in that previous
turn
when I should be faster than anything I
was
trying I was even trying to go more with
the system than
before what do you want I don't I I get
punished for trying to do
better as understanding this whole
[\h__\h]
maze I get punish for thinking
[Music]
do
it I hate
you my whole life I will dedicate to
ghost hating sorry maid mint our
friendship is no more because like what
like what what why don't we you do
something about
this it's not
acceptable
okay what's the best
way if I walk out there do I actually
get there because previously it felt
like I was on a different
floor am I actually going to get there
wait why would it even change to to a
different form okay we're fine we're
fine we're fine we're
fine I hate this I hate this room I hate
this this [\h__\h] me up last
[Music]
time I'm not going to let you play with
me this time I'm not going to let you
throw banana peels at me it's a waste of
[Music]
food you have to eat the peel too okay
eat the
peel yeah okay we saw that coming is
rude it's just rude but there was
nothing I could do shoot your shots
Luigi we're relatively
undisturbed now is the
time okay see I'm fine I'm fine I feel
relaxed I'm locked in all I have to do
was lock in
now uh let me think do I go into the
courtyard no how do I best go
[Music]
there oh the plant room [\h__\h] hell I
didn't even see why does it matter why
why why why but how do I get there b
like
fastest cuz if I go in here get to the
Courtyard uh I don't remember how to get
there
[Music]
anymore I can't I don't want to think
anymore for the portal in the night room
was this the night room no was this the
night room
no which one is the night room I don't
know the night
[Music]
is I just I don't know
if this is the end of me I will [\h__\h]
die oh wait this works this works I can
go for the
[Music]
courtyard hate this
game really not
nice but I'm
fine come to terms with it
[Music]
I'm trying to do something
here people are supposed to be like oh
[\h__\h] she's locked in don't ruin this for
me
[Music]
get away here dirty little
[\h__\h] yeah was lock
locked in my whole life
man always been locked in hey don't take
my
money was there something in this chest
I don't remember have I been to the I sa
yet and I I forgot the bone no I have
the bone I have the bone I have the bone
I have the bone are we going
up two red
rops which one did I prefer I do not
recall I will go left first
first please be nice please be kind oh
this
room
wait okay okay this room's not so bad
uh if you recall how to find shut
up
[Music]
I is that the last one
the mommies
the I guess I could have just jumped
there but like you can only jump at
certain points so it's was like I'm not
sure I'm not going to oh now we only
have one
[Music]
huh supposedly makes me
easier Maybe
[Music]
is the timer gone because uh it's
actually gone
or because previously when I was in the
room it was still running and then I
died
oh we G
hallelu
fall okay okay okay okay she's so locked
in guys she's so locked
[Music]
in after Insanity Ark comes locked in
Ark get back to the Terrace he says get
back to the Terrace he says if you want
to [\h__\h] kill yourself yeah because
that's that's that's basically what
happens
there it's not recommended if you want
to just live a nice life just don't go
there but what does Luigi do Luigi goes
there cuz Luigi is a masochist and Luigi
loves
[Music]
suffering let me just
recollect one of the upper portals will
do right
[Music]
and then H wait wa we don't have a timer
now right we're
[Music]
good I
forgot is want to save his brother okay
that's really
sweet that's really sweet I suppose okay
we still have the bone we have
HP I mean full would be
better but I don't know that's just 1018
no big difference I'm going to be
okay okay if I don't make it this time
I'm never going to play this game
again which is so
sad I'm going to lock in now goodbye
[Music]
I wanted to charge that more but have to
[\h__\h] it up so I felt like now or never
how how do we make
you do it do
it did he fall down no did he fall down
no
I'm focused I need to I need to get a
[Music]
man a h a
h oh
really now I am worthy of your hearts
a
[Music]
give me heart I promised Hearts when I
suck you ghost
[Music]
in no [\h__\h] gratitude for sending you
to the afterlife
[Music]
finally after that meaningless shitty
life you led and the meaningless ghost
pting that you have been doing
here oh thank you now huh
[Music]
let me
go
no that [\h__\h] zombie mummy will be the
last thing I will ever capture it
seems yo really
yo you want a part of this
[Music]
huh what even are you okay it a red one
one he's running
up oh God one
is okay we have a bone it's all good
it's all good it's all good it's all
good where where where the [\h__\h] did he
go
that's
fine that's
fine
fine he fell down
[Music]
on your
ass how unbelievable is actually
unbelievable lift lift lift the [\h__\h]
lift the [\h__\h] lift
it okay I can't only get
[Music]
go
go not worth the
[Music]
trouble we have all the time in the
world run run okay after this hopefully
only the yellow one I can handle it
that will be the thir time that I'll be
taking that one
[Music]
down bring it bring it bring it bring it
bring it bring it I
say take down
sword almost ran into the yellow
[\h__\h] thank you blood goler
this is it everybody 60 HP should should
be enough am I right
okay but I'll do it step by step again
because otherwise it seems pretty
[\h__\h] impossible with this
guy like one at a time cuz I don't know
how else you could do
it she will always spit at
you and that's just disgusting I'm not
going to let you do that to me
how will I ever get that spit it like
stinkier than getting like sh on by a
bird I do want to try maybe not now
because that's the way but okay here we
can try this what if I keep on
moving okay I slipped I think you can do
it if you're
good I suppose if you move around
[Music]
ho I will not celebrate there's nothing
to celebrate
[Music]
Yello
cow but thank
you hey did it it's not over is is is
there one more uh boss or uh two more
[Music]
well hopefully this was the worst part
and the bosses are
easier
right I'm never ever ever doing that
again
[Applause]
yipp they Lord when to get hit by
rainbow light
oh
well may have been your toughest
challenge so far yeah
yeah
yeah I'm glad you are aware of
this absolute
monstrosity of a challenge that you have
creative wow upgrad what do I get oh wow
P
upgrade C your cats no I'm
okay I'll P them when this is all
over
I I'm fine I'm not hurt at
all King Boo wherever you are you the
number
oh we dance cha for the last
[Music]
time stop the nightmare
ha portal on the Terrace is still open
but we've got to hurry button up those
overalls my boy it's time to battle King
Boo send me just let me go don't cry
don't C cry for the crimes you
have
done who's cute so it's going to be okay
yeah his
cuteness will lead me to Victory
[Music]
wow well obviously I can't just walk up
there and get the [\h__\h] dark moon
[Music]
piece this room reminds me of
the uh Lui menion fre boss that we
fought oh it's not
bll it's not the B what the
[Music]
heck I see why it's called
nightmare ah but hey they got I know how
to do this this is wait what uh oh we
pull
oy can I do it
still oh and
now and now uh what what what happened
what was the point uh
what I like the way they
run oh do I need to get both at the same
time oh no what does it mean
this is like
oo okay I got him he was so far but I
got him H once again he only lets me do
it once like and then he recovers or
what
[Music]
mm oh he takes a new form all right easy
so far easy easy easy easy easy oh hey
ah hey hey and you want me to get all of
them oh I was a able to do it
amazing wait let's wait for
him and I'm close and I'm hitting him
right where he likes it the
most don't you and I still didn't lose
HP I think incredible but thanks for the
hearts when I don't need
them where are we going
bro a pro Carpenter exactly that's what
a carpenter does
Luigi agrees
[Music]
uhoh uhoh uhoh oh
oh I think we're changing the gimmick
now don't think I can swoop the carpet
under his
[Music]
feet Dark Souls let's
go already feels has been feeling worse
than Dark Souls GES so far oh
papa what what is we finding his
feet roll w w
roll okay well maybe it is still the
same gimick what are these books for a
what
w oh okay it was taking a moment to
understand what they want from me
probably oh he's on the
carpet what I'm still doing the same
gimmick wait what now what now wait what
what now
what what what
[Music]
what well now is the time where I might
need
Hearts could I not have saved them
okay what
now Tri both but he only uses
one what I don't understand
[Music]
see how does how do I make him stay
there does he just stay
because oh
oh well now
he's wait for both to be on the carpet
okay
[Music]
wait wait which one are you
moving here please
thank I must stay would you mind staying
no or what rude then
[Music]
what
stay and then but he what like this one
I guess this one won't reset
on it seems like it wants a
[Music]
Shader ah I'm going to die
I hate
[Music]
this
huh he's on the carpet please me move
this one thank
you Now's the
Time
right oh
[Music]
hopefully that was the only time we had
to do that
hopefully just fight with yourself with
your true
self oh
God no no no it's too far
[Music]
no so
far it's too far
bro that's the carpet
[Music]
oh thank God that's
it that was
manageable
oh H yeah oh pretty simple easy thank
God that that gohost never really was
that difficult like in the other stages
where he was the boss
too okay yeah King Boo's last we F we
had
the boss in front of us but no alas you
done it my boy you've actually done it
the final dark moon piece it's not going
to be easy but I'll try to bring you out
of that horrible illusion come on PX
later
M nothing compared to the ice ball I
don't know that monster uh ghost
Rush was worse I
think hey
silver say that might even worse than
the ice boss which I don't think I
didn't think that could be
top I need to I've been waiting on
watching the full playthrough from D
tendle but yeah after today I need to
watch this like there's no way like I'll
be so salty though when I
see how he'll just easily sweep through
it be like why why why does it look so
easy when he does
it oh okay I I maybe shouldn't skip that
oopsy because I'm sure that was a nice
cut
scene was there I I forgot can I jump I
don't think so what are we doing should
I try to make this land on
him ow I think that's possible
this is
fight H come here come here come here
come
here okay wait do I
okay they look like
um uh
jotto the chocolate that I really like
[Music]
at least I figured out the
gimmick I I he here a frog a [\h__\h]
frog who can't frogs betray me when I
look like
this
[Music]
unbelievable this is a frog how did you
dodge it m
[Music]
what we need to keep looking
am so he doesn't see it coming huh makes
sense but I feel like I did that and
then he dodged it
anyway oh
stair stair stair St see he dodged
it didn't have to be so perfectly on it
[\h__\h] okay here we go
[Music]
again go here go here go here ah
[\h__\h] he was so fat that see the job
[Music]
does I I will get hit too
wait I'm
scared okay uh uh can you take a step
back oh it hit him actually see the hit
box this like only friendly
when it does you have to be where it's
not
reasonable that's not it stage two here
we
go my sanity long
[Music]
lost even though my tears are
dry I feel
fine well this loss cannot be recovered
are we just going to run if I stay
here
um okay I just run okay I thought maybe
I stay somewhere but no okay I
see I like this this it's uh very fun
some money on the
way oh oh oh oh
okay no more mistakes oh God this so
close though
oh oh back up what the
f b
SP what is this what is this what is
this what is this what is
[Music]
this go back go
back he bounced the back oh wrong wrong
wrong wrong
wrong
help B back bounce
back I didn't see this death perception
is
zero wow so so nice with the
heart he's just having fun he's cute
he's got eye bags of Doom not quite like
the other Dooms but he's cute are we
doing the same thing again but with
these feels obstructing is that what
we're doing
bro I think that's what we're doing so
that I can't see these things very
well wait there we go
okay oh there's a big one
[Music]
though oh we can do
more come
on just got the ball tring go with me oh
I suck the
[Applause]
B oh
oh what what what what stage free face
free
[Music]
free he made it
smaller the rule of
free
okay okay 100
HP oh it's dark
oh so far so good good oh jumpy
pads jumpy pad is it the same no it's
100% not the same course run run run
missed the heart but there was no need
for it oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay okay okay I
oh no no no no no no
no I got stuck with for a
moment okay well done well
done oh wait the stage I thought it
would stay small but now he has
something what's new oh
okay I like it I like it oh
oh okay made
it I stay in the
middle oh
there's I thought there would be more
but of course there's only
one really
[Music]
spikes uh oh why are we so zoomed out in
oh can we break
that come here
[Music]
he is so funny oh the frog is
[Applause]
huge um oh oh okay we don't have to do
the same whole thing again uh where the
balls where the balls oh no
balls why did I
run this fight is pretty long too so
honestly I good where's the
ghost bro he was he he was out of the
Zone ridiculous come here
yeah
nice oh wait what am I
[Music]
doing
cheating King buo is
[Music]
cheating I have it on 4K now everybody
will know you're just a
[Music]
cheater y we clear the game it just
doesn't feel very good at
all because of the freaking ghost Rush
that we
had it doesn't feel good at all I'm not
happy about clearing the game because
the accomplishment the feeling of
accomplishment I'm just like numb uh
I've become so numb Mario oh he's still
in the picture well we cleared the game
they say in chat
so perhaps we can just leave him
there he's probably going to get stuck
again in the next game so let's just
leave him
there seems like he's destined to be in
the
picture I got
it
yes yeah like Luigi's Mansion free was
amazing
like this is I don't know man what
happened what happened at least I guess
they heard a lot of the criticism for
the second one and then made fre better
like more
bearable number oh really thank
[Music]
you get out get them out of here they're
traumatic they're traumatic to me
oh
sh okay look at them look at them
they're going to start screaming any
moment now I hope we shoot them to the
Moon never to be seen
again yeah it's prettyy
[Music]
nice it makes you proud of your country
I'm glad cuz I I I really just you know
I like Italy a
lot just came back from
[Music]
meia wait what look at their
eyes oh they look friendly now they got
googly eyes
now I don't trust you guys one
bit nah
nah nah you guys the emotes are just so
[\h__\h]
perfect what what
don't are you letting him
[Applause]
out are you letting all my heart work
out doesn't [\h__\h] matter that they're
good
now they're going to go evil again
bro what we should keep it
contained M
[Music]
Mia Luigi it time to break the fourth
wall okay okay never mind never mind
never mind never mind okay you got me
come on doggy eyes n get out of here
thanks Mario
fing look at him he looks so dumb wait I
don't think I've ever seen him with
those eyes before
okay shut
up no no no just no
[Music]
RGB was it really worth it
Lui maybe for the sake of adopting a
dog so dumb
can't believe it I can't believe I
invested so much time into that [\h__\h]
ghost
rush but
I I mean you
know I finished it and and everything
after that was very
bearable just had to get past that
[Music]
point is this is already it's going to
have
apologies otherwise I don't want to see
it like would I get a a voucher a coupon
for therapy after this okay that's
cute but it's not going to heal the
PTSD best we can do is a
slid this will not redeem the
ghosts this will not redeem the
suffering they have caused all of
[Music]
us this will go down in kfb history
books as a negative memory
[Music]
okay that's so
unfortunate corn CBS okay corn corn CBS
corn clubs are nice I bought a lot of
them today
cuz I I saw them and they look so
delicious the grillin with butter and
salt and that's all it
needs that on your birthday no happy
birthday we can't have your birthday
ruined can we salt emote what what what
do you want you want a salt emote what
would be a salt
emote honestly just use the angry emote
or the o one or any of those or the no
just no no just
[Music]
no
no I don't
know what was my favorite boss fight I
don't remember most of
them cuz I I traveled I started this
while I was in Japan I mean the time
frame itself it wasn't that far apart
and Scattered
but there's
so many rough memories at the end there
that I don't
really remember anything before that it
was overwritten my memories were
overwritten there wasn't a nice one in
the
beginning
[Music]
really I really like the ice bossom
until I hated it
[Music]
eight out of 10 had a little something
for
every you're
[Music]
funny I have to rate
this and then might be my worst rating
of all time which is
so unexpected when I went into this
[Music]
game I'm still glad we played it because
we added onto our Luigi's Mansion
collection I want to give it a free out
of 10 but I'll be kind and try to look
over uh some of the bad things and give
it a benefit of the doubt that there
were more good things than I remember
and give it a four out of
10 I I'll be nice four out of
10 got to see it a little bit
objectively I don't remember what I gave
the third
one you guys remember by any
chance surely I gave it a really good
ranking
[Music]
CH was like eight out of 10 or so eight
or nine yeah for
sure I didn't care much about the early
level student
really yeah let's just let's just give
it a four out of 10 anything below four
is yeah
rough I mean you know it I think the the
the concerning thing is induced more
rage than any other rage game could have
induced out of me I think like climbing
game I don't play many rage games but I
I think this is
like has made me more mad than any other
game
[Music]
before sadly
yeah they were long they were
unforgiving the enemies did not annoy me
that much in uh
free like I I did not get interrupted as
much or had struggle as much I think in
I I would remember that I think roughly
Metroid yeah I struggled and raged a bit
in Metroid for sure my 4 is more
like comedic I would
say like it's just that's yeah this is a
bit
different the boss fights were
unforgiving I don't know this is Skyward
Sword I didn't I don't know if I raged I
was just like
crying I was just
crying I I don't know if I was really
that enraged
enraged I was just feeling pressured the
game
was better than this like I mean the
emotion controls
were quite something
but I mean it has a lot of other things
going for it like I liked the story and
the like General gameplay and
everything so I would never rated a fre
or
four yeah that was just the
end that was
yeah a little bit difficult did I miss
any German coming out it felt like Prime
set the bar of that no I don't think I
really I usually can't contain my German
like it's kind of on purpose when I
speak German randomly I I usually
contain
it it's not really natural when it comes
out of out of
nowhere can you play Kingdom Hearts no
um I think
uh I'm not really I don't really have a
connection with the game
[Music]
so even if I don't know what you're
saying thank
you no I'm not participating in GTA
there's no there's no like Midway
participation as far as I know uh it's
not possible as far as I know and I I'm
fine like I have other things to do this
[Music]
week I think tomorrow I haven't 100%
decided yet I have an idea but I might
just I might just decide when I wake up
I'm not sure if I want to do like I was
faking Fallout but I'm not sure if
that's the
best idea like another longish stream
but I mean I said long this has been 5
and 1 half hours I'm probably going to
read some super chats now
um then maybe get 6 and 1/2 hours or so
is that long I don't know anymore that's
supposedly long now Fallout I could make
it shorter but I feel like I want to
take some like time of Fallout but I
wouldn't know what kind of shortage game
I would
play so I'll think about it if you have
suggestions let me know like look at
something the girls the other girls have
been playing recently
[Music]
oh thank
you for Super
Chat oh potion C I don't
know
maybe
EF always ah I feel like slay as fire or
something like that would be fun again
[Music]
b
b yeah why not
maybe maybe maybe
maybe every once in a while I get like
an it for slight
fire ah what was that game in the what
was that game that I was interested in
in uh in the direct
direct that I said was kind of slight as
spish and something
[Music]
else uh not of
mama uh the most recent
one I think it was it had like a short
name a short title just a few letters
the Plucky Spire I saw a little bit of
dendo playing it yesterday and it's so
cute so Charming uh it's not what I'm
talking about but I did uh request per
perms let's see if we'll get them I
think I think we will the Volvo digital
we usually have perms for
it no not batro no something else that
looked nice that I mentioned to you
[Music]
guys I want to get perms for whatever I
was thinking
of no not no no no the G sequel
[Music]
sequel yeah I think that's what I mean
but is
it well what was it
called is it just Griz is it just called
GIS a was it really that I don't know
whatever
I don't want to hear this music
anymore turn it
[Music]
off okay
um get get get me somewhere
[Music]
else ah here I
am back in the pond so peaceful and nice
Peace at Last yes my swamp the stank
imagine this
smell gummy worms yum y y y y yum you
know when I flew back from
Japan um I didn't even tell you like I
was struggling to get an upgrade uh like
online like I did it before over the app
right doing like a bed a a bid um but
somehow it didn't work this time at
all um and I really felt like I needed
it this time I didn't pay for the ticket
itself so you know just paying for the
upgrade wouldn't be such a big
deal but I just couldn't like get an
upgrade like it no matter what I did in
the app uh online just didn't work and
when I called them they were also like M
no try again tomorrow and then I try
again the next day and it still didn't
work m and then they were like okay uh
go to the counter when you are like you
know leaving and try there and I'm like
well I mean that's there's no
guarantee right that I can get an
upgrade there so that kind of sucks but
okay guess I have no
choice so I did
that um did you hear the bgm by the
way probably
yeah
okay I did that I went to the counter I
was like I want to buy upgrade how much
it it was only like maybe 100 200 bucks
more than it would have been in the app
so I was like okay well I'll take it
then my card didn't work cuz I only have
a debit card and I really need a credit
card it seems so then I I was like okay
I'll be right back I got so much
cash but everything took so much time oh
they were pissing me off I'm a frequent
traveler now okay and a frequent
traveler I get an extra piece of luggage
to check in okay so I was going to have
three pieces of
luggage originally two but fre frequent
travel I get an extra piece of luggage
so free so I thought okay I'm going to
um cuz I have so much stuff I'm going to
go home with free luggages I I borrowed
one from
JMA V IP perks let's go so the one that
I B for Gemma it was a small one cuz I
thought okay I a small one will do yeah
so I I I went there and I was like okay
I have threee pieces of luggage and
she's like okay you will have to pay
extra for that one and I'm like no
because I'm a frequent traveler and I
show her literally the writing on my
ticket that says one uh like uh cabin
luggage or whatever and free checkin
luggage for me and I show her and she's
like and she tip type tpe type you know
Japanese polite and trying to figure it
out and then like she just reverts to
like 5 to 10 minutes later she just
reverts to um yeah no you have to pay
for that one I'm like are you sure like
this literally says I'm sorry but this
literally says I have free pieces I
should not have to pay for
this and then she's like no no and
then um you know they also sent an email
uh where it says uh today you know we're
fully so you can put one of the luggages
the hand luggage that you would like if
you have a little suitcase to bring into
the cabin you're welcome to check it in
for free extra and I was showing her
that email I was like okay but you're
doing this right now so let's let's
let's ignore even though we shouldn't
ignore it Let's ignore that I have the
right for free
luggages uh what about this then like
this this little luggage is the size of
a cabin luggage what about that and is
like no because it's free kilos too
heavy like even and I'm like What's the
logic like if you check it in
then it's not cabin luggage anymore so
the the free [\h__\h] kilos that's really
not much it shouldn't matter she's like
no no no no it's too heavy you have to
pay for it and I'm like okay but my
other luggages are not too
heavy so in total
you know it evens out she's like no so
and she I went back to okay but like I
should have free luggages Anyway full
luggages because of this and I show it
to her again and I'm like do you have my
frequent traveler number in there in the
system she's like
yeah it was just like impossible like
she UND she saw it and she asked her
colleagues too but something about like
I know they have to go by whatever is in
their system and they they seemingly
can't do
anything that is that goes against their
system like like like that whatever
whatever is in the
computer but then like something was
wrong with it because I really should
have had threee pieces and it just
didn't
work I guess I just couldn't register a
third luggage without receiving
payment so then the system wasn't really
100% understanding that I deserve free
luggages yeah and I'm like okay
whatever you're lucky I didn't say this
but I was thinking you're lucky I have
like my third piece of luggage is a
cabin size so that I can just yeah move
the free kilo into some other suitcase
that I have then weigh it again and then
check it in like through the option of
checking checking in the cabin uh
luggage
uh you know what I mean like I would
only
ah I would only be
able to do that thank
you thanks to the FL being fully
booked but that was my last resort
because somehow they just did not accept
my fav language without me paying extra
and then I was wondering like okay but
I'm upgrading to business though should
I not be getting another piece of lugage
just through
that uh but
apparently no I don't no usually you get
another one
then I
know yeah um no I didn't I didn't pay
for any extra uh luggage um I ended up
just you know moving the free kilos of
the small luggage into the bigger one
which was still under the uh weight
limit and then checked it in as a cabin
bag to be checked in through the the
offer you know what I mean
yeah 6.5
[Music]
lb yeah thank God I still had space to
move in around but everything took so
much time like I wasn't I was at the
counter there
where you give up your luggage for 1
hour if not even a little bit more than
an
hour just because the upgrade took so
much time me doing it in cash and
everything and first trying with card
and me doing a cash then in the end and
then the freaking luggage problem just
everything took so much time so I came
pretty late to the gate but they said
they said uh uh you will get your change
which was like two [\h__\h]
Euro something like that you will get
your change at the gate because there's
not enough time is that okay I'm like
yeah sure okay I go to the gate make it
for all of the security check and
immigration I go to the gate I stand at
the gate
um they're like okay please wait um we
don't have your cash yet please wait and
um I sit down they're not boarding yet
at this point
but they're starting very soon after and
then the whole boarding process because
it's a big flight takes like 30 minutes
or
something so I I in total waited like 40
minutes or so for them to get me my two
[\h__\h]
Euro the lady finally comes with my
money and she's like okay here is your
money and I'm like oh is this like that
took a while and she's like yeah it's um
it's rare for people to pay in cash so
I'm like oh
man what everything took quite a
[Music]
while but I got my seat and it was
coffee and I could sleep
decently I
mean I didn't sleep that much in the end
but at least it was comfortable and I
didn't have a lot of pain in my body
like I normally would
yeah why I need that credit card just
get a credit I really want to because
then I will get miles for it
too um and I actually I tried signing up
for one like a while
ago but then I don't know it got too
complicated I was like I'm going to do
this
later I don't really know how it
[Music]
works no I don't have a credit card I
only have two debit
cards which usually works for most
things I'm surprised it didn't work in
this case because
everywhere like I don't know normally
works for
everything H but in Japan
yeah I can see how how it might make
some trouble in Japan because I think
they don't really have debit cards in
Japan so certain
services are just limited to credit card
cards I
suppose yeah I don't think we have
credit score in
Europe doesn't your current back just
automa off yeah but if I I was like oh
my God depending on where you get your
credit card you get so many different
like benefits so if anything I would
want to get one from probably my
miles uh thing program cuz that will
give me extra
miles so I I want to get that
one I believe she only talked about n
Italy tangent so far H yeah I guess
so I mean we don't have to talk about
all of this right away but uh I don't
know I I don't know it's been a while uh
3D Live uh you know recorded that a
while ago so was hard to
remember but me and Callie we
really got dud uh for uh reflect I'm so
happy you guys liked the the show was
very dramatic
[Music]
right you know I really got to give
respect to cie um she was like gone
for a like a long time uh before the
recording and had to practice it all on
on her
own and I I wasn't sure how well she was
going to get down the Coro when she was
just practicing it on her own in between
her work stuff um
yeah um like not just reflect but like
all the other things
too and and then the first time that we
would dance together was on the
recording
day so I was really worried but then I
saw her like we were like practicing it
a little bit before the take and then
she actually like was was was really
remembering it well and even the
positions because that's a thing that's
like you can maybe learn the Coro quite
well for a video I usually learn coros
for videos a lot of the time um so you
know uh I don't mind it at all but
having to learn the positions too o that
adds a little bit of extra to it and
then you do have to do it in person to
really get a feeling for you know the
distance and everything but she did so
well so I wanted to praise her a lot
because um I'm really
grateful that she even though she was so
busy she tried so hard and the result
was really good
how is the whole package hell
yeah
yeah yeah what else like Ena Ena also
was working hard and like practice uh no
prti she was like drawing on her tablet
in the free time like she was so busy we
were all really
busy um and then oh my God they would
break out in in a few future Island all
the time all the time they would break
out randomly cuz it was in ena's head
and she would suddenly start singing it
and then Kelly Jones was
like and I'm just standing there
like it is catchy it is fun her
performance was so cute and then am's
performance I mean I'm talking about
solos now am Miss am Miss was h M oh my
God I love that scene where the camera
was like kind of looking down on her
from above and then I think she lifted
her arm towards it and then it zooms
away like it it roues away you know
which scene I
mean that was cute I got my
heart and I think Violet is probably one
of the songs she practiced the most over
the years and one could really tell she
did so
well
yeah and Thena ah so when we first chose
songs like I I immediately called dibs
on you know
Amazon and I think Ena Ena pretty
quickly wanted said she wanted to do a
cie song particularly this one
um I think yeah it all kind of came into
place like little puzzle pieces and and
goodle
I hope that she didn't feel like a man I
got the short end of a stick or anything
I hope she was happy with getting you
know to sing one of my songs um but she
like when I was like okay which one do
you want to sing I have a big repertoire
now I'm surprised you chose
K but yeah it was the newest song So
makes sense makes sense she really liked
it I think
so I'm happy that she performed my song
yay it was really cute like I think very
different type of Kima but very cute she
sang it quite differently from me I
think different
[Music]
spice yeah and then Callie uh ky ky sang
GAA song full color
which is such a good song and the Coro
is fun Cy had so much fun dancing it and
she was so she was so motivated and so
proud and I'm proud of her
too and it's still unreleased
unfortunately too bad it's a really good
[Music]
song y first time was Sayang public oh I
guess so so like I think surely there
were some people in the chat who like
were like oh what is this is this a new
Cali original or is it a cover of
something there's surely some people who
didn't know it was good a
song Just because yeah that's the only
time where it got performed
publicly for
free you're a bit confused oh but then
when I did Chu tuu I'm sure that's when
it kind of became clear what the theme
was it was a Swit Choo yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah I really love like reflect the last
moment the scene oh my God I was on my
knees so much in that Coro my knees were
kind of hurting to be
honest um and it was like really
dramatic and I I my neck was being weird
again like the other day when I had my
own Freddy live recording they told me
that there's just something weird I
guess with my model in the neck part and
they have to like manually hold my neck
back now otherwise it looks weird so
weird I never had that issue before just
like started this
year but I I don't know you probably
can't tell because there's so many angle
changes um but I definitely was able to
tell that on that day it was kind of
weird
again h i going to fix it no no no not
not unless I use a 1 million wish or so
and you know I'm going to I'm going to
keep that for something else if I get
another one you guys don't have to
donate anything for that because uh it's
a 1 million wish but I do want m s had a
a model upgrade and I don't know like
was that a 1 million wish or so it could
have been
[Music]
hm it looks so
cute yeah it looks so cute she looks
like so fresh it's wow did you see if
you didn't see like it's it's the same
like uh outfit and design but the
proportions are kind of different and
like I don't know this like it's hard to
explain it's just um
different h
[Music]
I mean I don't understand uh if it's for
her 3D life okay but like normally what
you get for 3D life is a new outfit like
concert outfit kind of thing you don't
get a redo on your model that's normally
like you have to use a wish for it but
maybe she did like she totally couldn't
H it looks so cute
it looks so cute and did you see though
her butt is
jiggling her F in her butt is jiggling I
did not think cover would do that I I I
did not expect
that maybe it was like a personal wish
from M and Senai but I did not expect
[Music]
that it was jiggling quite a bit though
oh yeah I'm sure she
[Music]
was oh that was one of one of her wishes
perhaps when when remaking it the future
is
now yeah there's a stream on uh it was
on the official Channel not on her
Channel I think on the official Whole
Life channel I
[Music]
think yeah anyway um Frey did I write
down any tangents regarding that it's
hard to find my tangents these
days ah my mom wrote to me generali it's
not a bank it's a insurance company
there we go the the lion the lion
[Music]
thing tangent from ages
ago
um let's see this is breaking
Dimensions
tangent where oh this is the T
M yeah I was just writing down my my
thing for the
D
[Music]
thing did I even write down anything
maybe I
[Music]
didn't these tensions are
old that's so old
[Music]
uh what what does it mean what does this
mean what does this
mean
um
[Music]
wait first of all okay
uh is Tanaka in the
chat probably not
[Music]
right have I even seen T like
recently Tanaka is the one who I
recently
randomly saw in the most random non
vtuber stream
ever and you know it says like Tanaka
kfp in the name you know and I'm
[Music]
like
so funny I just wanted to let you know
that that was
you and then yeah recording I only don't
I don't really have many tangents I have
a tangent where um two of like we have
some uh Ian uh directors who like take
care of uh each like you know one
director will take care of one
generation and so on um but they still
like like sometimes they'll still like
show up anyway for things that aren't
have don't have anything to do with
their generation so um also because one
of them kind of handles
honi so okay okay the other
[Music]
day I met two of these
directors and uh I think this was
actually during the the myth
recording um they were like wearing the
same
clothes the same kind of like cocky
pants and the same kind of like green
shirt or so and they're both wearing
were're wearing a hat I think too
they're just wearing the exact same
clothes and I pointed it out and every
everybody all the staff all the managers
in the room laugh and we all kept on
teasing them the whole day and the
following days about it like the whole
day we were just like calling them the
wrong names like one director we would
call him the name of the
other I just making fun of them it was
funny
lighthearted and then the the other days
I'm like oh are you we see one of them
and we all the staff all the
Ian managers and every were like oh I
wonder if they're wearing the same
clothes again today and we were waiting
waiting waiting to see the other
director but I think we just didn't see
him on that day but yeah then we kept on
making fun of
them it was just too
funny
[Music]
yeah hello smoothie welcome welcome to
the Stream
[Music]
what are you doing do you worry about me
at all when I
screamed oh yeah for for by the way for
the video that I uploaded my like my own
little Vlog did you like it I wanted to
make it kind of more intricate and comp
complicated and everything but I wasn't
even sure if I was going to do it for
the longest time time cuz I wasn't sure
if I had a right like camera a good one
for it in the end I just ended up
filming everything with my
phone uh like same with previous Vlogs I
wanted to mount a camera on my body um
and I even bought a special mount for
the camera like I got I borrow a camera
from the
staff uh like one that they just owned
privately
and then
like there was no
um it was the camera was like somewhat
old so they had no mounts that were made
for the camera anymore and we had to
like
combine all kinds of mounts like three
different products mounting together
into one thing that would work for a
chest
Mount and
then you know I had to wear gloves too
right I had to wear gloves
in in the heat it was hot it was public
I felt weird about it it may not feel so
much like that in the video but IRL it
felt so weird like I thought if anything
I I like look weirder if I wear these
long black gloves outside than if I
wasn't wearing them more attention
grabbing you know what I mean so I took
him off as much as I could uh in between
scenes and when I was walking around and
then I had to put them on each [\h__\h]
time but in the beginning we tried me
and um PMA we tried mounting the thing
uh the whole camera thing on my chest
and then we realized first of all this
looks
ridiculous I feel like embarrassed
walking around like this people are
going to look more at me than if I just
carried the phone in my hand and filmed
with my phone cuz it was standing off of
like the it wasn't like like like L
lying directly on my chest no it was
like like a few inches away because the
mounts you know there were several
mounts connected to each other so it was
like this whole distance away from me
like uh uh uh index finger distance away
or even more from my chest and it was
this whole construction it just looked
weird and then I realized well this
camera doesn't even give me a preview of
what I'm filming and it doesn't show me
what I filmed even afterwards like
there's no way of watching any scenes
that you filmed and checking if the
audio was captured or anything like
nothing so I was like
PMA let's just use my
phone let's just use my phone it will
mean that I can't use both of my hands
at the same time unless you hold the
phone sometimes so we just did a mix of
me holding the phone and they're holding
the
phone and yeah at least I didn't have to
wear the whole chest mount and look
stupid with
it now if I knew that I was going to
take a video like that I would have
brought my own little camera that is way
more
like not stand etish you know my own
little camera it has this like magnetic
necklace for example it has a lot of
different tools to do it but like
mounted on your cap or whatever but if
you want to wear it as on your chest for
example you get you put on this um
magnetic necklace hide the necklace is
on your shirt and then Mount the tiny
tiny tiny camera on top of that spot
over the
shirt and so you only see like the
camera but there's there's no huge Mount
and straps and stuff going around you I
just didn't I didn't bring it because
you know the trip was so long and at the
beginning of it I didn't think I would
need it was a good video so thank
you thank you very much I'm glad you
liked it I think it came together nicely
if I do this again I want to think like
plan everything out way ahead of time
and make it a bit more
intricate yeah I had the idea while I
was in Japan and and even then you know
I wasn't sure if I was going to do it
until last minute because I wasn't sure
what I was going to do for the reward
and in the end I mean I know it's
ridiculous you guys would have gotten
the 2.0
anyway but it kind of made sense to like
announce it like that I needed a way to
announce anyway so I was like well this
is fine in the end it's it's it's it's
about the fun things we did along the
way
yeah two birs one stone exactly now it
feels like you earned it
[Music]
exactly I'm not sure by the way what to
do during the stream besides showing you
I I feel like there's not as
much like I feel like good as 2.0 had
more to show in terms of
[Music]
like I think I think her Trident and and
uh bloop or whatever his name was at
this point I don't
remember feel like they had more
functions or changes
now I don't have a GoPro by the way I
just have the other thing that's similar
to
it yeah bloop has jiggle physics yeah
yeah yeah
so I don't know what to do besides
showing it off and then I don't know I
don't I feel like I don't know how to
fail the
time oh it's going to be a short stream
um K well I just did a k i don't want to
do another
[Music]
one it's um
and the Sunday stream is a different
special
stream youn I was thinking yeah but then
it's on I I was thinking I should just
do like 1 hour of
singing Do you
remember that's one way to Showcase my
2.0 right but then it's unarchived but I
I kind of don't care like why not
unarchive it huh
you'll see it again in the future
streams it's just as a joke should I do
it do you
remember the 21st night of September
it's a good
[Music]
song you can do the subscribers only
thing against I was I was thinking that
too while I was doing it why am I doing
this now I should do it on the 2.0
reveal because I don't know what else to
do then
[Music]
yeah an archive model Ral yeah kind of
rare no it doesn't matter like you'll
see it again it's not such a big deal in
the end I don't think it's such a big
deal it's better than what I thought it
was going to be in the end like in terms
in terms of uh how different it is um
but it's not crazy
look
crazy yeah it's okay I will not do the
thing again okay I won't do it again but
maybe we'll actually do the unarchived
thing I mean the fact that it's
unarchived and a reveal will maybe get
more people to watch it live too right
like it's like oh on archiv I have to
watch this mental
manipulation I might even make it a
short uh stream sorry if you don't like
it I might do it
anyway combining all the things that hit
hard
unarchived somewhat Marathon because
singing one song uh reveal shorts
stream it's a power
move and I can a r yeah because it's not
it's you see it again and I'm I don't to
me it's not that
port and like it's just a 2.0 it's not
that different in the end like I don't
know I don't have that much to show
and uh it's not like it's an
outfit you hardly ever use your default
though yeah I
[Music]
know she keeps on rubbing herself
against my legs
well if I don't have any better idea
that's what I'll do out a hat every 20
minutes oh that's
cute oh baby
[Music]
stopy no short archive reveal part that
will be bad because if it's so short
then it will just
have no no no no no no has to be one
thing
y remove 2.0 hats add naked to the title
[Music]
what St thank you
GD thank you I am being haunted oh no we
have to read oh it's not Luigi's I
thought I thought that was Luigi's
Mansion super chats okay no it's the
mint well it's kind of same
thing okay I'll read those
oh
B stop being so
cute she keeps on robbing her whole body
against me it's so
[Music]
cute
man was a much less stressful ghost
stream though it was a little bit
stressful like the prep for it um
I I
I didn't get um like the headphone
splitter that I needed because it was a
k until like 10 minutes before the
stream or
so um jenma brought it over like I kind
[Music]
of
uh like the day before so I remember oh
[\h__\h] I think I need a converter thing or
whatever
and then I don't know somehow it took
until right before the stream to get it
but at least we got it last minute yay
thank you
Jen Taco Mor Vlog trip oh oh oh oh oh oh
Taco World Vlog yes yes yes that was fun
too like we did so much together Taco
Taco Mor ton did so much stuff together
during this these past I don't know one
or two months M I feel like we bonded a
lot and like you guys don't even know
this thing was like cancelled once and
then brought back to life the next in
the next two days or
so um thank God yeah I'm glad we did it
in the
end it's all it was all kind of hectic I
feel like because it was canceled once
and then planning it was probably really
difficult for the team because there was
not much
[Music]
time
yeah you got yeah and I
[Music]
mean I don't know
like I wish I wish like you know I wish
we could have done this with all five of
us because like I see like Advent and
everybody you know they're doing fun
stuff with the whole generation I wish I
wish you know but you know things just
don't work out sometimes and that's fine
we had a lot of fun with Taco Mor
Tony and honestly that haunted house it
would have almost been impossible to do
that with five people I think it was
already so crowded with us free and like
you know camera people manager s and so
on audio people like all kinds of people
were all squeezed into that already tiny
house it was so
small oh by the way I think uh qu
[Music]
s it's been a while Cory wrote to me
she's like I want to feature this in my
morning stream I guess she already did
by now um and she told me she already
did the same thing the same experience
a long time
[Music]
ago and I thought they wouldn't
have like I thought it would be a new
thing because they were still doing this
thing like what they were asking us to
keep the
spoilers
away but I want to tell you okay so
there was you saw there was these like
hiding spots right and I just I just
went into the same hiding spot each time
the first time like it took him so much
time to finally open a door I thought he
was gone as you could have seen as you
saw and then he opened it and I scream
my heart out and he's like kind of
giving me a sign to follow him and I
wasn't sure if I should follow him I
thought like is this like mental games
am I supposed to follow him or if I
follow him will I just die like you know
what I mean like should I really follow
him does do they really want me to
follow him I'm not sure so I hesitated a
little bit but I yeah I was I was scared
and he he then like trapped me in a room
I was so tiny it was even tinier than
every other room and why is smie just
sitting down there now awaiting me it
was so tiny and there was no air
conditioning in there so me me and cute
nice director Chan we were stuck in the
room and there was no air conditioning I
was sweating I was like because I just
screamed so much and got scared like
that's that makes you sweat too right I
was trying to figure out the riddle and
I just couldn't because we were also
under a big time pressure we had maximum
an hour and it's so funny because we
literally like kind of finished it with
1 minute to spare or
so it was a
miracle it was an absolute
Miracle um like the whole thing that
that Riddle That was pretty much in the
beginning still and and uh yeah yeah
yeah I don't even know how they solved
the riddle in the end because it was
mostly on their
side and then so I was in that room
right and was it in was it
them was that in a different no it was
in a different room I
guess
uh okay so we go into a different room
and and uh I think cie was in a
different room and me and Ena were in
one room
uh and then I have to explain this a
little bit better
okay wait I can show you wait let's go
to let me copy paste the
source this is just Photoshop green
screen a movie star
stop how big is
this there we go okay
so there we
[Music]
go it's kind of hard to remember but
there was this uh let's just say this is
probably not the perfect shape but let's
just say there's this
[Music]
room there's it was pretty small again
there's a phone here I think and like
something
here and me and Ena were standing here
actually this was Ena this was me we
were standing like this okay and we were
on the phone talking to cie right she
was on in a different room we were
communicating because a yeah there was
the sign here uh with
like all kinds of words and in random
orders and she also had a sign there and
we had to like kind of combine it and
make sense of it I never understood it
in the end I don't think
so um well we were communicating through
the phone while looking at that and then
we clear it I
guess I guess we did because then
suddenly out of this sign like the sign
drops or falls back or something or the
the the only the only the demon like
just jumps through and jump scares the
[\h__\h] out of
me so I immediately make a run for it
Ena just kind of doesn't scream and just
stand still which is what makes the only
think oh she must be staff because we
had a bunch of Staff around you
know uh and and so he just follows me
I'm screaming I'm screaming I'm
screaming um Ena just stays there so
gets completely ignored by the Onie I
run into a different room I hide into in
the same cupboard again because uh it
starts the The Haunting music and when
the haunting music starts they say that
you have to hide and once you're Pur
like properly hidden you have to say
more EO like it's okay
now so I run in a hide and I wonder like
where's Callie where's
Ena what's
happening uh yeah and so uh app the the
on eventually then just went back or so
and passed by Ena while Ena at some
point I guess she thought oh I should
probably hide too so she walks you know
just chill and they pass each other you
[Music]
know they're like ah excuse me excuse me
what the [\h__\h] so the keys just to not
scream are you kidding
[Music]
me and so like each time I would be like
kind of the Haunted one and I don't know
I somehow my memor is blurry here I
don't know if this was the same
situation but in the end when we finally
had the solution that's why I didn't
move hello he I say I you say
B
hello hello was it the
on I said I you say B hello
[Music]
hello are we back I said okay there you
go sorry that was weird I think my
internet went down or so what was I
saying ah so I don't know my memory is
blurry I'm not sure if this was like the
same occasion of after I hid in the
cupboard I think it was different
occasion
[Music]
um but we finally solved the
riddle and so it was something we had to
give we had to hand it to the
Onie
and how the [\h__\h] did I even do that
somehow I don't know why but they
decided I should be the one handing it
to the Onie why
me why mean it was a bunch of items
so um it would start haunting again but
this time like uh I I think it was like
switched around instead of the most
deciding it's time uh it was us you know
and so I'm in I'm in the I'm in there
and and and It's haunting and he goes
around he goes around and I was supposed
to do
something what was I supposed to do
because we failed and he just left again
hey stop eating the plastic why is there
plastic down there
anyway and they're like what did I do
wrong why he something something went
wrong and we had to repeat
it and then finally he opens the door
and I'm still
scared and I give him the things and
he's just smiling so happy but still
very
terrifying I give him the things and
he's just like okay you're done but we
literally had to redo that because I I
don't know I don't even remember what
went
wrong but somehow I was always the one
who interacted with the freaking
I was such a mental wreck after
that stop being so
cute
man enina was chilling cie was chilling
she was
vibing why why why they didn't protect
me I was just scape goat for
everything yeah we're proud that you did
so well B
you they can smell fear yeah I don't
think that it's that specific cuper that
always gets hit I think the first one
was
random
and I don't was there even I I don't
remember I don't think it was the same
cupo I I hid in the same cupboard but I
feel
like maybe maybe staff just not our
staff but like the haunted house staff
maybe they just told him where I
was and I was just the most entertaining
to haunt I don't know hi
waisa
hello
lisais I need to it's it's it's half 11:
p.m. and I had I woke up really early
today at 6:30 but I had a nap
so I'm good I'm good but I screamed so
much I
honestly I
can't I don't want to read super
I don't want
to can I get away with it one more time
chat we need to play something where I
don't scream
[Music]
tomorrow I screamed so mucha I lost my
absolute [\h__\h] mind I don't think in
my four years of streaming I don't think
I ever lost my mind as much as today I
literally had a [\h__\h] Joker Arc I was
so angry and so raged and then I just
couldn't help but start laugh I had this
laughing fit and I started crying so
much while like because I was laughing
so hard I just had to cry it wasn't like
crying out of sadness even though it was
very much a thing to be sad about I was
just
really losing my marbles today and there
is uh I lost my
[Music]
marbles Joker to mind break speedrun
because of the game yes I I would not
recommend this game for you to play I
don't I think you would Rage Quit
probably before me cuz like there's
there's a bunch of parts that are rage
quitable yeah Lou just mentioned free
very very nice Lu just Mansion
two no
comment and I think Lu just Mansion one
is probably also good I I didn't hear
bad things about it um yeah
but free is really fine free is actually
fun free was really good and you know
could be an October game you know just
because ghost
woo yeah um I suffered so that you don't
have to suffer
basically
noisa noisa Nisa noisa I I missed you I
missed you I'm so happy that we were
together even if it was just for for a
few days I love you it's so nice that we
could do it together thank you for
having like inviting me kind of and and
yeah my sleepy
sleepy
bird no I wish I could have been more
helpful but Venice was quite a challenge
even for me the whole water situation
was very difficult
I told them the story of us being
lost uh upon our
arrival having to yeah having taken the
Uber and then being dropped off
somewhere didn't realize until way later
that we were dropped off wrongly and
then having to find a water taxi and
this and that like
yeah yeah we were so frustrated but
afterwards it was all
forgotten V this is quite the maaz
honestly I really liked how walkable it
was and our um second accommodation was
like really Central and well situated
that uh we were like really fast at s St
Mark uh square and at all the main
attractions and I mean in the end I feel
kind of bad we didn't um check out that
much we just didn't have that much time
anyway um and we were also tired
um didn't have too much uh uh didn't
didn't see as much as we could have like
there was there was we probably missed
so much cool
stuff we only saw like the most obvious
ones but it was still beautiful and at
least that gives us a good reason to go
again
someday yeah we could go everywhere so
easily oh oh I need to tell you like
when we check in it was you know kind of
like an Airbnb and so a lady came by and
she opened the door for us and we had
like this whole floor to us and the the
elevator literally goes to our floor and
then you know you have to use the key uh
to get up there and and then the moment
the elevator opens it's just our whole
Airbnb and we had like a you know
Terrace rooftop everything so cool we
had way too much space actually but you
know we go we go in the elevator with
the luggage and I was the first to step
in and the moment I stepped in something
broke I didn't even step in so harshly
but it dropped by like maybe okay I you
know I can only really say centimeters
but it dropped like by 10 C CM or
so and made this loud like donk sound
boom and I was like oh [\h__\h] that felt
wrong but everybody you know went in
um and then uh first of all Airbnb lady
doesn't really remember how to get up to
our floor takes her a while to figure
out she need needs a special key to get
up there she brings the key she finally
turns the the key thing and pushes the
button and then it just takes an earing
long time to get up there I swear to God
like it was just a couple of floors but
it took
like it it C CED up there so slowly I
was like oh yeah oh yeah something's
broken the moment I stepped in there
something's broken I asked the lady like
is this normal and she's like no
no and it stayed like that for a whole
trip and I'm guessing no one's going to
fix that for a
while
yeah h no we use the stairs when going
down but when going up you know sagani
we weuse them the
elevator I just enjoyed a long elevator
ride very long if only it had elevator
music things would have been
better and the elevator fun you were so
cute and wanted to spend as much time of
you as I could honestly I thought it was
funny man I I just feel bad for the
future people who check out that Airbnb
and who have to always deal with that uh
elevator now and they're probably never
going to get it
fixed let's be honest they're not going
to get that fixed if they didn't
immediately try to fix it after it
happened it's just one of those
things you to got to go on vacation
again really soon yeah this one was
really short and you know it's like one
of those kind of City vacations where
you walk around you should be walking
around a lot um I kept on wanting to
jump into the freaking canals they were
so beautiful everything was so beautiful
so unreal like first of all like the
first taxi ride I already told them
there Isa that was so unreal like it
felt so like w never been in a place
like this before this is so weird like
no other place no other airport that
I've ever seen like has [\h__\h] water
taxi stands the
[\h__\h] but like we would just walk through
the like City like even like away a
little bit away from the like you know
popular uh place just any kind
of
alley has just
this like how to say like every view is
gorgeous cute with the canals going
through and the the houses like
everything being so narrow and
overlapping it and then all these tiny
Bridges everything was so ecstatic
and then everywhere there's these little
uh canoes going
through I mean those are obviously a
huge uh money bait for the tourists I
those Americans that I met they told me
how much those are the gondolas those
are too expensive crazy we just looked
at them we we were at least we weren't
so stupid to book one although I felt
like you know even if it's expensive
like just for the experience we should
do it but we looked at people
doing it and that was nice enough it was
you know really pretty and sometimes I
thought it was so funny how the
gondola guys they would like interact
they would like scream to people who are
like just other Italian locals
restaurant owners and so on or like
police people who are just standing
around on the side while they're on the
water they're just like they're
like
M Pizza Pasta
and they scream back
[Music]
like I just love the those
Communications between
them Loki wanted to write one for the
experience yeah but they looked the
gondolas the the boats the taxis I liked
those but the
Galas they looked kind of tacky to me
like as if they made them extra tacky
for the tourists I I feel like they
should have kept them old school like
they had this like tacky Furniture in it
I I'm like is this I'm sorry like I mean
that just looked like a tourist
attraction to me but okay to each their
own it was so much fun I love I love all
the gelato we had so much
gelato
yes good gelato
[Music]
because they're KY by Design are they
though like I'm sure like like I don't
know 300 years
ago okay why I mean
surely 300 years ago there were surely
already gondolas in Venice like Venice
existed Venice had canals surely they
had gas uh but I don't think they would
look like that why did they make them
look like this I I feel like it looks so
tacky but still cute super cute m
you already had two honeymoons may as
well go for a
third uh yeah I wonder where we would go
I'm glad we had this alone time like in
Japan we this last trip we really didn't
hang at all like we barely did we even
meet in this last trip where I was there
did we even meet I think we didn't have
time and Anda I think left soon after I
arrived and
we were like ah it's fine we'll meet in
Venice anyway I'll have you all to
myself
anyway yeah my thirsty
sleepy singing bird
woman she was really homesick oh yeah I
totally get you like I was super
homesick too
weisa yeah yeah yeah yeah oh she's so
you know she kind of has some some am
Vibes to her because like we were eating
pizza on the last day and uh like we
both left over all the crusts I'm so
sorry um because it was it would have
just been too much um I I don't hate
crusts it's just like if it's a whole
pizza usually the crusts are too much
for me and so narissa also kept all the
crusts um and then she she put like five
of the crusts pieces like of each piece
put like so many of them in her pocket
one after another cuz she was like I'm
going to feed the pigeons with
this I was like oh that's genius and
that's kind of like what Amy would
do oh she put it on the pocket yeah and
then on her way back walking to our
Airbnb because everything's so walkable
thank God she would find she would look
out for pigeons and suddenly there were
no pigeons when you needed them but then
we found some pigeons and she started
feeding them and more and more gathered
together first there was one then there
were two then there were three and then
there were four and they were when we
finally wanted to leave them I like it's
it felt so bad like oh man they still
want
more but we have to stop
somewhere they don't wanted to feed
pigeons in Venice and now I want to die
oh really well I mean they don't want
want people to feed pigeons anywhere
really do they M but people still do it
and I
mean at this point it's not like you can
like save him by not feeding someone's
always going to feed him and I mean I
mean I don't
know ah yeah feeding bread I guess yeah
right right right right that's not the
best thing to feed them well you know
they just had a few
crumbs and I feel like that's still like
better than some of the other [\h__\h] they
will pick up from the
streets rest turn in
GTA but yeah I forgot about that I
forgot about that why did I
memory why did I forgot that when I
literally watched it in jet lag I
watched the episode in jet lag where uh
they were like the challenge was like
getting a bird to eat something and they
like purposefully fed them something
that is okay for birds not
bread pigeon tummy H I'm sorry I'm sure
they're
okay it's the F that that counts you
know birds feeding other birds is
cute
yeah no they didn't die don't say that
pigeons are so cute all birds are so
cute I loved all the seagulls they were
so many seagulls like sitting on things
I love seeing them they're cute even
though they're terrifying at the same
time throwing them the ice cream cones
who the [\h__\h] throws them ice cream cones
why would you do that well you know next
time we'll prepare some I don't know
what do they eat what what should they
eat
seeds fruit we'll throw them something
nicer next
time turquoise
raid what does that
mean
I'm
wait wait wait wait
wait wa was is that the color we we we
decided she had in the end oh I'm I
don't I'm sorry guys I'm
really not in the mood for more ghosts
now
I me and
ghosts it's over I don't know if mint is
like now watching too or if she just
sent her
people and oh
I said this one before but let me just
say again um I had the worst gaming
experience of my four years ever I think
today two wives in chat let's
go
yeah I don't know if anybody of you
Raiders played Lu just mention too if
you did then maybe you understand cuz I
finished the game today and the ghost
Rush
absolutely made me lose my
marbles it was painful to watch I'm sure
for everyone here it was so painful for
me too oh my
[Music]
God yeah Joker Arc is real but thank you
for the raid I hate ghosts and I will
suck all of you up unless you have goly
eyes because apparently ghosts with go
eyes are okay
now says Luigi's Mansion
too yeah you'll have to I don't know do
you want to watch the I don't know if
you can take it it might be too painful
to
watch was it worse than Mario Sunshine
Mario Sunshine for Mario Sunshine I have
too much love for Mario
Sunshine to be really mad at it I guess
I rage quitted that game too
it just kind of I don't know that became
too difficult for me but I still love it
I and I think it's a great game I
wouldn't rate it low I think that that
that's
H it no it's different it's
different you should UNR quit
it I don't
know maybe one day but for now I don't
want to see the Mario family again for a
while and I I just came back from Italy
now I finished this Italian guy game I
just I'm I need an Italian detox I won't
be talking to L either just
kidding oh I'll talk to
L I'll talk I I'll write to her but the
moment I hear her accent it's over just
kidding just kidding I love Italian
accent like like people English language
spoken with a strong Italian accent is
way easier for me to understand than
spoken with a strong ass French accent
I've I've noticed this
now like some accents are uh easier for
me to understand than
others I don't know why the Italian one
is easier they speak clearer I
think chatino chat packs what
[Music]
laughter is so
funny man we we should n next time we
just going to bring the along next time
so that we don't get in trouble with you
know transport
stuff would be
fun like if it's Italy you know we got
to meet up with Lou L
loud she can talk to all the people and
get us the good uh good
[Music]
stuff so about those jetpacks what's it
the
jetpacks wait wait jetpacks wait that's
ringing a bell
[Music]
somehow right I saw them uh something on
Twitter I saw something about
[Music]
it I remember now I saw it on Twitter
I I was like what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] why the [\h__\h] you guys don't need
jetpacks you can
fly you can fly don't
worry oh man so many people here so much
I'm I'm so I wish I could like entertain
you guys longer but I'm like mentally so
drained from this
game and I literally I was about to rate
it a three out of 10 but I was I'm kind
enough I have the mercy to rate it a
four out of 10 and this is my lowest
ranking of any game ever holy
[\h__\h] but I like Luigi and I like Luigi's
Mansion free
okay too much
[Music]
ghost so uh I said that this week will
be no schedule but keep in mind uh
Saturday will be my
2.0 life to De Rine meal of my default
outfit uh upon which all future outfits
will be based on you know uh and Sunday
is a special stream that I can't reveal
yet but soon and uh once a few things
are set in
stone and uh yeah the Sunday stream will
be special so both Saturday and Sunday
is special Friday will probably be
members but I I'm I think we're not
going to do watch long we're going to do
something else but don't worry about it
don't worry about it we'll do it next
week hopefully on the weekend I know you
guys prefer the weekend for watchong for
those Long Wongs yeah yeah yeah I'm
scrolling I'm scrolling what is it um
dear ghost girl Lu should have just
stuck his nose out of business for real
like it's not so much Luigi's fault it's
more like egad's fault
the the guy you know who who gets us all
in trouble in Luigi's Mansion and the
Toads the toads are a
[Music]
curse they named the board after him
didn't they though did
they think about it chicken
think which came first Luigi or the
Luigi
board double toad was harsh
two toads really two Toads one Phoenix
really I don't have the energy for
that I'll make sure my pizza has lots of
mushrooms okay thanks cuz I'm not going
to I'm not going to eat
mushrooms not going to be eating
mushrooms the to with clock phobia
[Music]
I did tell you to just leave the toad
alone until he found the other one e
what do you mean like he's got to follow
me like what do you mean what do you
mean I don't
understand whatever it's almost me
tonight I'm going to go eat the food now
I still have left over um Indian food
from yesterday I really like to order
this like lentil stuff I forgot what it
was called
cuz I don't care so much for like
ordering meat Foods often they just put
so much meat in there and too much yeah
D I guess I guess but this one I think
it had a different name and it was like
uh it said like something something
lentil something something butter sauce
and it did taste kind of buttery but it
was it was dark sauce and um I chose
mild and I'm I realized while I was
eating it I should have chosen medium
actually because it was so mild that
even for me I felt like this feels wrong
so I'm going to spice it up a little bit
cuz I have left
over going to spice it up with some
spices d m wait I can tell you what it
was in FY it's good I should have just
not done so low I shouldn't have gone so
low on the
[Music]
spot let me tell you what it
is it was Dal
Mak is that the same thing that's what
you guys were
saying first time to see the live
[Music]
streaming oh yeah I like I like food but
I probably always I always order the
same things cuz I'm like oh I don't know
if this is going to be spicy I don't
know if this is going to be spicy let's
just order the thing that I know that
should probably not be spicy but last
time I ordered this like lentil thing
from a different restaurant it was spicy
as [\h__\h] and I was
dying wish there was an in
between madas is the spicy version of it
oh okay
yeah butter chicken always got to order
butter chicken but I feel like such a
basic white girl if I order butter
chicken one more time I'm I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm going to be so white that I
could become a wall in my
[Music]
room it's so basic man it's just so
[\h__\h] basic like they have so much
good food
like why why why always order butter
chicken
man but the thing is yeah I I really
like worry if I order something it's too
spicy and then I can't eat
it I need like a Indian food buffet
where I can just take one spoon of
everything and just taste test
[Music]
everything so uh so much for
Super Chat
reading but you guys like hearing me
talk so much right because it's been a
while since we talked so I'm sure you
guys appreciate that
right no complaints
[Music]
rhm yeah that's what I
thought that's what I
thought okay
[Music]
okay good well well well uh make sure to
be there on the weekend for my streams I
appreciate it very much um yeah
[Music]
uh let's do our best guys G and I will
now regain my sanity and decide tomorrow
what to play
something that sooes my
mind I really really am tempted to play
later
Spire thank you for the raids today got
so many sweet raids and so many nice
visitors thank you appreciate it very
much thanks for watching good night
everybody and ger say I'm going to go
pet my cats now and be happy and forget
everything that happened today but don't
worry about me guys don't worry don't
put it into the kfp history books is
such a Negative moment thank you
weisa it it it was fine you know I I
recovered I recovered from it and you
know the last boss fights are so easy
it's all good I'm I'm not that I'm okay
I'm
[Music]
okay let's just laugh about
it but not in the Joker way not
[Music]
anymore okay
tomorrow I see you again byebye probably
around the same time or a little bit
later maybe one or two hours later I
don't know byebye byebye Hope in Hope in
Hope
in frog
[Music]
chunky wonky hi