[Music]
now hello hello welcome to to Minecraft
Monday snail is here and as soon as I
open my
mouth he's preparing his exit he was
sitting on well he's still sitting on my
lab for now hurrying
peacefully and now he's he's
mad he doesn't like the
yaps he doesn't like when my attention
is on anything but him which I guess
that's that's
understandable snail don't
go okay today is Minecraft Monday and I
forgot that my alantra broke last time
so I need to walk all the way to the the
place so hold on I feel like this is
not
correct adjust it ever so slightly okay
that's that's better
I need to walk to the guardian Farm FF
FF sounds like I'm about to
swear f f
f B's funny fish farm it's too many FS
remove one of
those Fest funny farm no nope not that
either let me get into VC cuz we are
open VC
today I forgot how to want to
play
[Music]
Minecraft
okay I've got I've got too much to
juggle right now I've got a
snail who still
purring but is still preparing his exit
probably even if I Endeavor not to move
I was about to fly already okay I guess
we're walking
I guess we can walk this
way it doesn't feel good to have to
walk after all my time in
Minecraft I forgotten how to
walk
hello walking's
hard B boo good morning good morning I'm
coming I'm cling into Kier and Co oh
thank you yes Kier and Co appreciates
your support thank you I mean you're
welcome I broke my elytra last time so
now I have to walk all the way oh no to
the to the
server that's why I walk one do you need
one oh I appreciate it but it's okay
I'll just walk okay and I better fix it
I'm
[Music]
coming how are you doing I just woke up
for work but it's like normal cuz it's
like you know you wake up and you get
some coffee and then you go to work
you're 9 five yeah it's just like I have
an actual
job make sure you clock in cuz we're not
paying you if you're not clogged
in okay I'm clogged in
[Music]
oh who is
this says I'm eating a Sal right now I
forgot
I I'm eating s right
now fun Acer says
good Giga jimin says M yers Koski beu
says what's a
s the narrator is so so loud Giga jimy
says
[Music]
saled how do you turn that on again I
think it's what is it it's like shift b
or
something hi shift B did it work no okay
maybe it's not shift B I was oh wa
control b control B I always
accidentally turn it on when I'm trying
to turn on hit boxes
was it always a girl wait yours is a
girl mine's a girl mine is a
man how did you get the lady narrator I
don't
know is it is it based on your like
computer settings or something yeah I
don't know but it's a it's a
lady Microsoft I forget what her name is
it's Microsoft Sam is the man
Microsoft
Sam
Microsoft not
Cortana
Microsoft
samella hold on I can't think she's so
loud they are
loud is she is she narrating everything
she narrating everything if you do it
again you can toggle what she narrates
to be not
everything
chy
oh hello hello I'm my
f my f yummy what kind of
s very very basic s um it was actually
an extra when I got Sushi yesterday and
I saved it for a little snack the day
old Sal my day old
Sal did you at least put it in the
fridge so it didn't yeah it was in the
fridge it's salad right are we talking
about salad yeah
salad you're like is this a kind of food
that I've never heard of
before is it the the Japanese salad that
you get sushi restaurants I love the
dressing yeah the dressing is good is it
like the SES one yeah oh I love the
Sesame
[Music]
one so yummer wait what did you order a
sushi let me I got salmon just salmon
just salmon like well it was like um
like a Bento deal thing so I just got a
bunch of Salmons
a okay
Sage hold on I'm trying to conceptualize
this wait not even a roll just no just a
bunch of Sandwich did it have rice yeah
it had rice
okay my salmon and
rice well that sounds healthy yeah so
yum R I'm just like a a
bear yeah with some honey too M put my
my Paws in
honey oh gosh how do I how do I assist
in building this tree um so I was
thinking about it I
think one thing you could do is get wool
blocks from the wool Farms inside the
tree at the bottom and you can build
like a
scaffolding uh like Under The
Canopy uhhuh because we need to place
blocks underneath the tree and it's
easier to do so if there's like a
somewhere to stand do you mean
like never mind what's a
scaffolding like not actual Minecraft
scaffolding but like so I built some
already under the tree under the orange
and green
sections if you like continue that so
that we can place blocks beneath the
canopy okay I'll let that get out I'm
looking my gosh so many green wools in
here yeah I have a lot of extra wools so
I figure we can use that to build the
cannon they're the scaffolding these
poor Sheep No they're
fine they're they're
living they're screaming no no no no no
that's all they they know that's all
that they were bored that's all they
know so they're happy with their life
cuz that's all they'll ever know exactly
yeah they have their families there
yeah they can talk to each other all day
long they love to
Y it's collecting all this wool really
quickly
yeah it must feel good right for them to
have their wool shaved it must feel good
for the sh yeah
you must I know it feels so good for
that sheep getting shaved right now I
wish I was in that
box well you could be I'm going there's
a there's
two two there's
another there might be more than two
even oh there there is more than
two it must feel good as hell for these
sheep
does I can assure you it
does the pink Sher boxes that has just
full of
wool yeah you can you can take some of
those there's so much wool here okay I'm
going up oh I see what you're talking
about now yeah do you want leaves for
this Cavalry or do you want wool well if
you have leaves I mean it can be
anything okay the thing is I have a lot
of wool like leaves are easier cuz I
need to remove them eventually but now
that I
have free free
labor it'll be easier to remove anyway
so we can probably use wool you don't
even give us a company man a lunch break
you can have lunch I had Sal I just ate
a
Sal yeah if you eat before you come into
work you don't really need to eat at
work right yeah exactly what if I forgot
to eat because I woke up right before I
had to clock in well you can you can eat
while you're placing blocks
okay I have to turn these sheep down
I've got
bread what are you doing to the Sheep
got to turn them down they're so loud oh
I thought I thought you meant like
they're asking you on a
date I need to turn these sheep down
they keep they're all trying to rise me
up oh my gosh
what you don't like their their screams
of um love yes it's very
loving see they must be happy if they're
thinking about about love right yeah you
can only think about love if you're
happy otherwise you you would want to
escape instead of finding love it's like
it's like maso's hierarchy of needs
right yes yes
love is famously not necessary that
so so they must be
content do you need help are you getting
killed There's a Zombie trying to get in
the way of me and the Sheep oh it's
going to kill me don't look at me wait
where are you where are you I'll see
don't worry don't worry I'm eating he
can't kill me if I eat ah ah he can't
kill me if I'm
eating I don't I know where you are
which Farm are you at I'm with the white
and pink sheep
okay get away from
me
my all of my wall do you do you perhaps
need some equipment provided by your
employer my employer provides equipment
that's right I would gladly take some
okay I I'll be right
over
equipment I'm running back to the
tree I think I've got just the thing for
you
yippe fauna FAA Tree World building is
the best employer of all kinds K Cole
it's called K Cole Kier and Cole will
she beat me if I say it wrong looks at
her
no no no no in fact we're considering
rebranding Under the faart Umbrella so F
oh are we being bought out by big cor we
are
yeah I'm broke but a fmart has a lot of
money I
see actually it's like Kier and Co might
have gotten in trouble with the law so
now we're we're declaring bankruptcy and
we're going to transfer over to to fart
that way we can
avoid what kind of trouble
repercussion oh you know just like um
negligence in workplace
endangerment wait are you telling me you
want to sleep Gigi I'll turn it into day
oh no it's okay I was just setting my
spawn point by the
tree My Wo my w
did you find it I got all my wool
[Applause]
back an
Enderman don't look at him don't make
eye I'm looking away look away he won't
know what hit him look away like he's
a I don't know a hot
girl I would I would make eye contact oh
you're one of those people I see I would
be
staring ow oh my God that reminds me
when I was in the Far East on my last
day there I just remember cuz looking at
my photos I went to an arcade and
then I maybe this is strange to be
admitting on the
street go
on there was a very beautiful woman that
I
saw who was posed up next to the the
gacha claw machines and she was wearing
like tiny shorty shorts and no bra and
like the tightest shirt ever and she was
like taking photos and I was staring at
her is that
like like what is it at like race events
they have like the just the like hot
girls that are paid to just like stand
around and be hot I think she was taking
photos for personal purposes oh she
wasn't like P
is she was she an influencer was she I
think she was an
influencer yeah she on the ground taking
aesthetic photos of the arcade yeah she
was like leg up leaning against the claw
machine handing her hair like looking
away and then she had like the
photographer with her and I was
just no no she was
beautiful and I was staring
was it the Hol live machine no it was
just a random machine anyways um I guess
the awkward thing to admit on stream is
I snuck a photo of her wait I thought I
thought the a I thought that whole
preview was the awkward
part we haven't even got there yet I was
just so like oh my God what is she up to
this beautiful woman and her
photographer I'll I'll find the photo
I'll send it oh my
gosh let's see what I
say I have got to see a criminal the GG
camera roll I have got to see what You'
got in there besides reminds me of the
time where aan and I went to a cafe and
then one of us was like wo don't look
Nast
but like there's a really beautiful girl
behind us at a
cafe and then we all looked at the same
time we all scar of that girl like at
the same she was very pretty she had
like she had a really nice dress on her
hair was all done and she has like
accessories and stuff but yeah we all
collectively looked together and then
just started judging her appearance like
I also swivel my head when I see a
beautiful woman me too me too
but I feel like we get a pass because I
don't
know when other ladies are like
complimenting me or staring at me I'm
like wow thank you yeah wow because they
they know they know what's good you know
they know like a goodlook
lady lady so if if a lady thought I was
goodlook then you know it's got to be
true cuz it's
lady right yeah
just people they their hair is just so
perfect I don't understand I don't get
it why is hair so beautiful yes why and
they're like perfect bangs that's hard
because it's humid in Japan and humidity
is like the enemy of good
hair I think I think they go and listen
to this they get their hair done I agree
I agree oh my
God humidity in Japan is so bad messes
up my hair all the time I agree also I
think
you're what oh sorry oh my God so I fix
it oh no come back come back come back
beautiful lady come
back please are you done with your S I
apologize I'm looking for this beautiful
photo is it better
yes the humanity is bad in Jaan right
it's so bad my hair get so puffy in
Japan when you in summer when you step
outside yeah like from wherever you
staying hotel or so you step outside the
moment you step outside you're drenched
and sweat it's no joke it felt like I
was being splashed in the face with like
hot water yeah yeah like when you step
out of the plane and it instantly hits
you the
humidity the air feels like you can just
touch yeah you can drink it eat
itum make ice cream out of it e e I feel
like that wouldn't be so
good I wanted to say hi because this is
the Clementine family right now hello
you're right it
is
yay together we're together
again yay yeah I can't join Minecraft
but it's late for you right yeah and I
just streamed for 5 and a half hours P
the Exile where you at uh where am I at
I'm at the Caravan I already freed the
Gin do you know what I mean I you want
act two uh yeah oh okay you're ahead of
me then I
just no
way f are you going to play I want to
play it I don't know anything about y I
didn't know anything about it either but
it's like really fun do you know
Diablo Diablo I have not played Diablo
but I played Torch Light which I think
is a Diablo
game oh okay let's play yeah I wonder if
that's comparable we're trying to like
Loop everybody in how many people can
you play with like
infinite I mean technically infinite I
don't know how much is a party though I
think it was six yeah six that's
good is it a game that you have to play
a lot you have to syn like hundreds of
hours in no not hundreds no no no not
hundreds because you can't even syn
hundreds of hours in there because it's
just Early Access you can't play the
full game yet
anyway so oh yeah it is early access
isn't it yeah I mean you could still
throw in hundreds of hours but there's
no point still skill tree Okay g this
way okay I'm so lost this way this way I
will show you what about the skill tree
don't look at it I think I've I've seen
it don't stare at it it's a skill
ecosyst it is it can't hurt you if you
don't look at it I don't know I like it
you can have like summons and stuff
right
lasses why there so many monsters
underneath this tree we run run toward
the water water the water will save you
okay okay it's the Dark Forest go up I'm
going I'm going up go up they can't hurt
you
here how's the tree going it's actually
it's it's within completion range I
think
oh today I mean I mean it's obvously at
the point where you could call it done
at any at any
moment but it you want you want like you
know
the finished you know like it feels
finished you know right yeah yeah
yeah there's still hold a ceremony I
should hold a ceremony with with with
red tape what was it red tape uh red
ribon don't fall yeah yeah cut the
ribbon yeah yeah throw a bottle of wine
at it oh just throw it at your computer
how do I get g under safely without her
Dy um
where is she where are you oh they up
there on top of we're on top of the
orange hold on let me deliver some
stuff for
you the answer is probably you can't do
anything safe don't worry I saved my
spawn point underneath this tree so I am
free to die
freely here let me give you some stuff
[Music]
GG I don't know if this is like cheating
though cuz you just joined just make
sure to give this back you know if you
don't want it's okay the first the first
day they joined they like raided kle
took equipment
anyway is it oops G jimy says
a Koski beu says
T actually press T first instead of E
[Music]
she's dressing me she told me to cover
up have some cookies yay
cookies and then here hold on to this in
your
offand keepy says t t t
t yay do you know much about Minecraft
Gigi not really I feel what I don't play
that much Minecraft you're such a gamer
it's you you have to
start but we're in our po Ark you have
to continue fauna's Legacy yeah I'm
going to build a tree right next to
you build a tree on top of her tree the
same exact
tree that would be good really would you
welcome that FAA of course I would be
happy if somebody took up Minecraft
Monday please someone bear the curse so
that I may be free M A Fine craft Monday
but don't you feel like if she would
build a tree on top of your tree would
be like undermining your
tree I
mean with the way be smaller yeah like
World height will not allow it to be be
larer
so I'm not
worried maybe how about we you do like a
you dig down you build like an
underground tree that mirrors the tree
that's above
exactly a dark evil tree yeah it's a
shadow I feel like we should have Gigi
build
something uh related to her instead of a
tree like a tree a giant fist wait she
lovese wait what remember when gy used
to chop chop so many
trees yeah yes the beaver make a giant
beaver eating the tree I'm going to make
a giant beaver in the sky or giant axe
but yeah beaver's nice too a beaver with
an axe kind of threatening
honestly the beaver guides the man tree
it's
romantic is it romantic it is I'm trying
to find a way to get you down safely
hold on okay I'm just
following you need a water bucket what
about down
here oh yeah come down there did you see
the water
[Music]
yet okay and
then I can probably is that a creeper
that's a creeper yes walk towards it
careful
there may be many
mobs this is a very dangerous tree tree
yeah it's okay we do it for fom Mar we
signed up for these working
conditions it was in the contract yes
I'm sure you read it right you didn't
man
cave it doubles as a mob spawner you
know nature giveth
and nature will not take
away okay I'm hold on I'm going to fly
down to see what's under this and maybe
we we can find out
[Music]
okay um do would you like a water bucket
would that assist you I'll take a water
bucket I watched parkour civilization
figure it out can you do the one block
challenge yes would you be jumping for
the beef I would jump for the
beef don't you think the beef jump looks
really easy though yeah it does right we
should try it we should set it up right
now okay where are you guys okay yeah uh
I we can use the wool we have to get
three hunger because we have to be
hungry
oh start jumping I'm jumping jumping
jack workout time where are you guys
getting hungry oh we're we're we're
inside the tree at the bottom or the top
inside inside where inside the uh
UFO the UFO the we're inside you I agree
oh inside the the top like the canopy
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah at the orange part yeah orange yes
okay I'm almost hungry I'm hungry I'm
ready to do this challenge I'm three
hungry good luck you hungry don't die be
hungry um what was it it was like this
and then it was wait wait don't do it
yet I have to see
this how many spaces away was it just
one right was it like this yeah I think
so that looks easy
right jump for the pumpkin pie that was
too easy see maybe maybe it's like the
oh it's diagonal it's
diagonal like
that that was easy too maybe you're just
not a parkour Noob me it it's the the
thread of it all you know so it makes
them scared
okay now do 360 j 360 yeah do a 360 oh
okay my mouse is wired right now so I'm
[Laughter]
scared I I got this i got this you do it
you do it what did I make it that what
was that a 360 that wasn't a 360 I
didn't see you sp that was a 180 at most
hold on hold booo
[Music]
oh you just tossing cookies for everyone
up
there got to have something to jump for
right okay that was that was totally a
three hello
[Music]
hello I hear the gamer keyboard
noises yeah are you still on Pole
uh no I'm I'm making thumbnail I'm
putting up stream for tomorrow you do
that so diligent it is so early got to I
I do it like 5 minutes before I go to
bed day I do it like 1 hour before the
stream most
days I did it before I logged on voice
CH yeah that's kind of crazy I was it
like the like the day the night before
like usually after one stream ends I
make the fun before the next day and
then I go to sleep that's good but don't
you wonder like if it'll get pushed to
the bottom no I wonder that for the new
uh uh Trend that some girls are doing
where they put up the whole schedule
like the full week of streams onto it
that that's like I feel like it gets
pushed down too
much but like just like it's not even 24
hours sometimes or sometimes I just do
10 hours before I feel like that's good
enough to notify my subscribers that
it's happening but not early enough for
it to get pushed down too much I mean
they should only be subscribed to you
and no one else anyway shouldn't be a
problem right no no no they should be
subscrib to the full Clementine family
that's right family
time yeah my nice keyboard from way it
does sound very are those cream give me
Keys yeah like the some more oh okay
wait wait wait wait here how about uh uh
oopsie
uh such a yummy sound those sound good I
want to eat them and then choke on the
small pieces yeah yeah yeah
yeah I have lots of pieces left over
should I send them to you
yeah one ke challenge I will
sufficiently choke on
that oh no see who can eat the most
pieces without dying yeah whoever dies
first loses I feel like I could eat a
whole keyboard's
worth I have a rock stomach so I'll be
fine well what are these intrusive FS
stop
stop not edible why look yummy yeah why
sound yummy yeah
mysterious where should I start placing
BLS follow
you can follow me
okay up
the I love climbing I love Minecraft I
love Minecraft Minecraft Minecraft
Minecraft Minecraft Minecraft I love
Minecraft that is how I feel every time
I play Minecraft Minecraft Minecraft I
love Minecraft I'm playing Minecraft yay
Minecraft let's go toys toys I'm 8 years
old
play and I love
Minecraft you're so
enthusiastic wow
um oh what's happening she's hitting me
why what I'm getting smacked good thing
I have armor sorry the intrusive
thoughts would take me over okay I will
rain it in
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't have many blocks right now
um I think we
should um hold on hold on I know what to
every
go stay stay in the water
fountain oh God okay
didn't wasn't I going to make like a
landing platform oh I did
okay land on this
okay let me build
over and then you will be
connected to the network of
[Music]
scaffolds I'm I'm connecting to the main
frame uh-oh
do you see the bridge I see it I see it
I'm
entering why no almost
died you have your totem right yeah yes
and you have food oh I I made it I made
it ah she H
me don't worry don't worry I'll make it
I'm going to I'm going to take my sword
out off of my hot bar there we go there
we go no more intrusive thoughts
need needs to hire an HR I HR is always
the worst Department in any workplace we
don't need one no that's not true HR and
kfp is very
fair is it yeah if I ask kfp will they
think it's fair
totally
that right here no I no they're no they
love HR HR is very trustworthy place to
go
to are are you the HR department by any
chance is it just you I am uh I uh I
have things under
control I there the HR is an extension
of
me but it's still its own thing totally
yeah it's not not corrupted or so I
believe you I believe you too thank you
that is a good choice I saw your
restaurant full of chickens in there ah
I heard you criticized it I did not it
was the others
M I must look at the evidence I would
never I said they looked really really
happy of course that is just stating the
truth
yeah I was just stating the obvious the
facts
MH I'm so glad you are watching Breaking
Bad now and you understand I'm done
you're done you finished done I finished
I binge watched it within two weeks or
so good that's the way I'm glad you
understand the the
Gus you know when I named my uh Poe
character path of Exel character what
cuz I started playing path of Exel two
days ago immediately after or like in
the middle of me watching the finale so
I named it heisen BB a
perfect who's your favorite
character
H Hank question mark oh
Han h no h now you understand where the
Hank meme comes from yeah at the C the
SC stop I didn't know anything about it
beforeand oh so everybody here right now
in the Clementine family watched all of
Breaking Bad yes yes oh nice all right
okay yeah it's nice to finally know in
what kind of situation Walter was when
he was screaming in that
car it's
nice and Mike Mike of course Mike's also
great I love Mike I like Jesse too I do
like yeah Jess's
awesome have you girls watched El
Camino yes
watch what I haven't yet it's the the
Jessie sequel yeah if you like Jessie
you must watch elino I do like Jessie I
also need to watch the sa one I know so
good yeah I haven't finished it I
started it
today it's really good so far yeah I
like that Mike is in it more yeah yeah
Mike so nice to see Mike
[Music]
again cute don't don't listen don't
listen too late I listened don't don't
close your ears don't hear that what are
you going to do about it what are you
going to do about it close close your
eyes it's not
real
what I almost died I'm
okay stream couldn't not be
created
Why
YouTube YouTube you just YouTube things
just Indie
company small Indie Company please
understand I will
understand
so we're trying to build a
scaffold yes like
under I keep falling off oh
no underneath the Le leaves um Not
underneath the leaves you see this like
wool up here uh-huh this is like the
canopy but it's the underside but I want
to place blocks like these these lights
mm so we need to build somewhere to
stand so it just needs to go under okay
yeah so if you can like build it out
like over here you know just like
this and it these will get deleted later
so it can be
anything okay okay I will begin building
a pathway for you to place light thank
you and then I will delete the pathways
after you've placed the lights well
don't don't delete them just
yet we've got a while to go
still okay I will work on orange side
then since you started over
here stream could not be created
again you to
why did it did it log you out it always
does that to me no it didn't maybe
there's some weird word word in like a
band word in my description or
[Music]
so what was stream are you
making like um you know how uh Rica and
ren were visiting me in Austria these
past days MH we're just like it's a
collapse room where we talk about what
we did oh
so I don't really see what's wrong with
the
stream YouTube is gatekeeping me damn
you you how dare
you
unbelievable when you're being so
diligent and making it early
exactly this is how YouTube repays you
this is why I
procrastinate
yeah all right one more try
what
[Music]
no maybe it's me maybe no it's not you
it's never you always blame something
else yeah it's not your fault never your
fault
never okay
[Music]
try
again do we need to put uh torches are
enemies going to spawn on here yeah they
will oh okay it's just like
a I mean if you have a bed we can sleep
before they spawn although I don't know
I mean we're going to be placing lights
you know
so they won't spawn if there's lights
right that's
true just need to put all the night
lights up in the yeah the
leaves oh I already see a creeper
climbing up oh
man not the Minecraft brain rot
intrusive
thoughts me back in the mind pickax side
side side side side side side to side
side side to
side this t a grueling one M some
Diamond
tun you actually know all the
lyrics diamonds tonight I was trying to
remember the song you sent me it was
like a a little kid yeah in Minecraft
live yeah wait what was it it's called
Minecraft life Minecraft Minecraft life
I'll send it to you too bi boo I love
that
song I was trying to remember oh it
worked good yippe
yippe I was trying to remember it but I
couldn't and I was very sad this kid
deserves more Stu I know it's
underrated it should be up there with
all the Captain Sparkles classic yeah
it's so good Minecraft life the
Minecraft
life I don't know what you're talking
about but it sounds cute when you're
recreating it send it to you too you can
look at
this please do please share Minecraft
creeper not
invited mining I just love his mic
quality it's so
good when was it released
um it says seven years
ago wait oh he's got talent do you know
the same brain Rod song from this tune I
got no guns no girls girls got to die
wake
[Music]
up I can I can't baby beans who your
peep and SP is jump jump in the C you
know that one yes
yes what are we jumping into okay I'll
send it to you hold on I'll send it to
you which scaring me I know the original
I learned 3D modeling for jump in the
cat there's a Minecraft
version with the Ender
Dragon okay so this is the original G
and then it
spawned variations of it but here you
need to know the
with okay watching meme college right
here meme
education I got to die no girls girls
got to die b
[Laughter]
b that's so
sad when you're happy you enjoy the
music and when you're sad you understand
the lyrics
[Music]
yeah is it Skyrim the original I think
it is a Skyrim dragon
here here your chat I will send it to
you guys too so you guys can know and
then I'll get in trouble for it I don't
[Music]
care everybody deserves to know jump in
the cat they do
[Music]
yes pin that
yeah who's that my baby smothie smothie
oh she's wondering if I'm done streaming
a yes I yeah girl you're so
smart your cats are so vocal they're so
cute yeah no they can be vocal when it's
time to be vocal but then most of the
other time they're just quiet oh yeah
well behaved very well behaved well
behaved my cat is silent he almost never
meows I love that that's so mysterious
yes
yeah what is he thinking he had a vow of
silence a mon he has a can't break it
trouble
pass what is I need to know more about
what's yeah what's in there what's in
his head I think he mostly thinks about
snuggles he doesn't really care about
food either like he eats but he doesn't
eat that much much and he doesn't really
get excited about food is he very
affectionate he
is he's a lap cat
no gos a lap cat # go I'm think about
getting a cat like really soon cuz
everybody has a cat I'm like I want a
cat yes I want to I want an affectionate
La cat cats are like really expensive in
Japan yeah but it'll be worth it and you
only will be able to buy it from the
like shop place the breeder place
because yeah they don't let you take
them from a shelter no only if you're
like Japanese citizen or
[Music]
so so that's unfortunate
bad yeah when I got my cat's nail I went
to the shelter and I was like I'm like
looking for a lap cat do you have any
lap cats and they were like we have the
perfect cat for you he was 10 when I got
him he's 14 now that makes sense cuz
like then you already know oh he's a la
if you get a kitten you don't know yeah
kitten could be anything
M but the shelter workers were like this
one this isad you're like you're an
angel you know like we need more people
to adopt older or the older cats yeah
and they have their own charms they do I
feel lucky to have to have stale he's
the best cat ever
a there's a lot of Pros to adopting an
older cat like you already know what
their personality is going to be so you
can get a cat that resonates with
you there
more mhm maybe I'll just wait for the
cat distribution system to yeah s me one
that's how my family got both of our
cats just through the cat distribution
they just randomly came to us one day so
maybe maybe if I just hold off a little
bit it will could be yeah you could find
a stray cat yeah got to make sure it's a
straight cat
though take home someone's cat yeah
conveniently remove their collar
accidentally accidentally take home
Callie's
cat she has trouble with them anyway
right now one of our cats she's an
outdoor cat so we let her like go
outside as much as she wanted to um she
came to us without claws so we think she
had a previous owner cuz she didn't have
claws um but we let her out every day
and she just always came back so I don't
think she liked it there or ran away or
something but she always had a chance to
go back
home nice you're home now yeah
doesn't it feel good to be chosen by a
cat it does very much
so I'm waiting for the cat distribution
system to choose me yeah I'd be ready to
I'll take
it don't don't declaw cats by the way
that's B don't do evil
yeah I just let my cat scratch on my
couch
instead say
I don't know how you get them to not
scratch up the furniture I just accept
it but it's part of the charm of your
Decor you just need Furniture where it
doesn't stand out I have a couch that uh
the fabric you would never see somehow
it just doesn't become visible when they
scratch
it it's great the trick
yeah or just don't have a
oh yeah just don't have a couch I mean
don't have furniture my couch is my
cat's couch you know a
yeah they St as much as you do yeah
yeah and then when they sit on your lap
too bad you're not getting up they
decide when you get up
mhm for me this like all the constant
Str
struggle he's always on my
[Music]
lap yeah when I got him he was like oh
should we sleep
maybe oh okay okay let me find the bed I
falling oh check your I'm going to
bed okay I'm going bed ow hold on sorry
I'm need to find a bed
there's a lot of
skeletons Koski beu says
t
t Giga Jimmy Ren says
T I love seeing how they pronounce the
does this the tax to speech do like the
thing where you can use it to like make
funny sounds oh like the twitch
donations like the like the vibrating
phone
I don't know does it try it hold on I'm
try I'm trying
it
anticipation hold on I found it I found
it will they read this
Koski beu
says it didn't read it at all
no it doesn't know how to read you can't
judge will it say swash swash swash SW
fun Acer says so I so I so I SW
no Minecraft narrator won't have K
says it won't read it at
all not at all kosu says are those real
real ends why are they like Min I don't
know they're tiny but they when you when
you put it in textas speech it vibrates
the the the guy the guy goes
it vibrates the guy yeah it vibrates the
guy that's crazy well hearing the B boo
version is just as good maybe better
I'll
do oh hold on I'm getting a phone
call you actually weren't it was me did
you know it was actually me oh why oh my
goodness I never would have known I was
just that good you got me
that is good for a ringtone you should
do that as a voice pack so it can be
like you have your phone on vibrate but
really it's it's not on vibrate
idea I'll vibrate your phones I want
that I'll record it just for you yes
please
a lot of enemies down
here on
the where are you it's okay it's okay I
keep falling
off it's fine though I'm back I'm back
let me know if you need Rockets I made a
bunch oh I I will run out soon actually
okay let me rocket
delivery okay rocket delivery
[Music]
oh gosh oh
gosh
ouch it's dangerous work building these
scaffolds oh you're right there monsters
okay so many of
them okay girls I'm going to scaddle now
to eat dinner have a good dinner have a
good dinner
what are you eat for dinner I made a
bologa with red wine yeah that sounds
good well let's see how it tastes first
time I'm making it with red wine hope
you guys girls have a lovely uh evening
and much success with your tree thank
you don't die good dinner good night
bye-bye byebye
I always feel like I'm fighting for my
life when I'm on the
[Music]
scaffolding okay nice don't worry if you
fall as long as you're holding the totem
you you will live he'll protect oh gosh
there's creepers uhoh
now maybe I'll go get some frog lights
and light the place up a little start
start decorating yeah that might be
good you guys cook
much not really oh ow
skeleton I like cooking just I I don't
like doing dishes yeah me
too cooking is fun doing the dishes yeah
not fun not
fun what about like a one pot sort of
situation then I always try to do it one
yeah I try to cook in like the least
amount of dishes possible
[Music]
yeah I mean especially like in Japan the
kitchens are usually tiny you know what
okay I went you know how I just moved
here right I went to the Nintendo store
and went to the animal crossing section
and the Animal Crossing section has an
entire enre section full of like cookwar
so I have an animal crossing pot an
animal crossing water heater an animal
crossing apron an
animaling my entire and then like I have
jars from that animalic thing have
animal classic cups I have teacups I
have bowls yeah it's
animal themed Kitchen yes that makes up
for any like small kitchen issues yeah
completely did you see Animal Crossing
release the
offline app I bought it me too we all
got I wish we could play it together I
we can send each other our our camp card
so we pop up in that area can you still
do that yes yeah we can trade our QR
codes we can send each other screenshots
of
[Music]
our my ugly ass C me too I miss Animal
Crossing era it's okay I I have hope
that when the next generation of switch
comes out that it's it's
animal it's got to be right it's got to
be please
please and please be good please be good
please please update it for more than 2
years please please oh my God or give us
a complete game at launch oh yes that's
absurd
though still people do that yeah when
was the last time that actually
happened I don't know they do that with
Mario
right Mario is usually
complete Animal Crossing needs
DLC their staggered releases we need
something else to happen that you know
Society goes crazy I was literally just
thinking that we should just shut
Society down again yeah so we can have
Animal Crossing and also because I want
the same exact thing to happen when
everyone was shut in and crazy and then
they're going crazy over Rond oh my gosh
yeah and then like he would people were
paying thousands and thousands of
millions of bells for and dollars real
dollars dollars people were putting
Raymond on Etsy and being like selling
Raven for
[Music]
$5 inboxes moving ready moving ready
Raymond and then people making the
really sad comics where he's like I
didn't want to move out you guys are
treating me like like like trade and
then the the crazy um person that's
like Comfort character give him to me
you're not treating him right
seeing him on your Island where he is
not appreciated causes me distress it
makes me
sick I miss those days I want them back
me too did you ever do like turn-ups and
did you ever like oh STS yes yeah did
you ever go to someone's Island because
they were selling them for like 600 a
piece you have to wait in line for like
8 hours to go on their Island oh my gosh
the multiplayer was so bad like how that
worked and how you had to like wait for
someone to announce they came in
yeah those were the days I was in the
discords I was in nukon
yes we could have we could have been to
each other's Islands without even
knowing on the search for a pink
refrigerator yeah the DIY trades yeah
come over they're building there's a
meteor shower every everyone let's
letes Okay can I admit
something I what are you admitting I
subbed to Twitch channels who had like
the Treasure Islands so I could just go
to their Island get whatever they want
and I had a subscription so I could do
the subscriber only Island so I wouldn't
have to wait in the queue for someone to
leave so I yeah I went to the subscriber
Islands so that way I could just get
whatever I was a big decorator though to
be fair but understandable you needed to
make the perfect Island
valon we've all been
there I used to do that in City Folk it
was very sketchy like looking back on it
because I was a child and I would go on
internet forums with my best friend and
we would find people giving away stuff
for free in animal crossing city F and
we would go to their islands and they
would be like adult
men oh we just took their money you know
and then left and never spoke again yeah
all you're doing is trading your your
code yeah yeah just to get on their in
their town for their
[Music]
stuff I always
wonder why why were people on those
forums oh my God green DC
Green Green I'm green
one I'm green
two wait aren't you green I'm green
three I don't know about that I don't
think you've got green anywhere on you
I'm green you just have to look a little
harder I'm green am I green anywhere no
no maybe in your like
iridescence you can reflect green
sometimes oh no I have green in My Hair
Shine probably somewhere yeah like a
whole rainbow probably yeah yeah
yeah I'm green five four when did we get
to
five
hello hello hello hello hello
hello how you
doing Minecraft it's time for you to
clock in thank you it's time for oh it's
time to work it's time to work it's time
time for go to bed I don't know where I
am it's time to go to bed I think you
log off you know when we ended I jumped
into that well I think I'm back in the
old JP server I can come pick you up
hold on thank you oh my God the end is
loud yeah you guys just joined the
server right yeah yeah what were you you
up to what have you
accomplished they did not yeah we're
stary that's it we got a tour okay it
was very nice we saw we went up all the
way on a tower and then everyone kept
dying because they fell
down classic also B killed us all which
was it seems like she hasn't quite
gotten that out of her system still did
she try killing you
yes
no people I'm trying to work and someone
is killing me this is why we need
HR we don't need HR HR is a scam if I
put on glasses can I
bhr yes okay we're now hiring okay what
is I hope I get good pay what is your um
complaint to to who killed who bi I'm
trying to build this beautiful tree and
then someone tried pushing me off the
elevator on my way to work was it skill
issue I was just in an
elevator skill issue sounds Justified y
Justified I'm just trying to get work
done for this company that I love very
much CeCe where are you I'm in the Ian
server uh no I'm in the old
JP no the old Global server oh okay oh
you made
it no she jumped into the well I jumped
into well a well the server jumped in
right the well the
well I didn't I didn't know it was a
portal I just jumped
into I spawned somewhere else okay I'm
here where did you go from
here oh okay I'll go back to the portal
I got lost
um I'll be there soon and I'll be such a
good worker in the tree
sorry um there were cats I saw
cats there are always lots of cats yeah
get all of these
servers everyone's just hoarding them
yeah maybe I'll kill oh there's a yes
you should no no no finish that sentence
no no do it you can't kill yourself
because I'm here now and I don't know
how to get
out oh you don't know how to get out
either yeah wa I don't know where this
is wait is it the lava room is it is it
the lava
[Music]
room do you need an
escort I think my escort might need an
escort H I might need an
escort she killed herself this is the
only way okay okay I spawned in a house
wait wait where where am I wait I'm back
at the I'm back at the back I'm back on
I'm back on the right server are you on
pantu Express house what house are you
in yes yes yes yes I'm in the in the in
the bunker okay I think I know how to
get
out I'm coming okay I'm coming out oh
you're buoni mhm okay I can maoni I
think this is why I saved last
time oh connection oh now you Rage Quit
okay I got
kicked are you
[Music]
cheating do
like cheat at Minecraft oh just tack
real quick she's using invincibility
mods oh no okay let me try getting back
in spawn rate on those ender
pearls that's that's what I
do that's me it's always like you know
cheating is one thing but I think it's
always hilarious when people cheat at
like really silly games like like
Minecraft Minecraft serious yeah it's
not silly
no I mean the oh my God you know the the
one where the all the kind of like the
the
beans no no no they jump Fall Guys Fall
Guys Fall Guys Fall Guys is also
serious you shouldn't cheat at it okay
I'm at the entrance exit to the bun of
hello I see you I see
[Music]
you it's time to go to work you my hair
roll it is
[Music]
I want to make a short of that dance
it's such a good dance dance it's so fun
to dance Too can you do the dance I can
do the dance do it do it oh where are
you going I'm watching I'm watching I'm
watching you okay
uh it's time to go to bed insert random
Korean that I forgot how to say
but y yada yada y
[Music]
H clap clap and then you do the sweep on
the
[Music]
hips and then you go p p and then you
swipe on your phone and stop swiping on
your phone no that's hard of the dance
it's swiping the swiping no but he's
saying stop swiping on your phone okay
and then p p p p did you see did you see
did you see my dance I saw it in my
inner eye I see it I see it it was
beautiful I Envision it yes it's time to
go to bed perfect time to go to bed oh s
y y wait it is time to go to bed oh okay
let me put my bed down oh oh oh oh okay
sorry wait I don't have a bed it's okay
you're on the other we're in the server
so it won't affect them
oh Minecraft is amazing confused they
really thought of it all when making
servers they did
I should make Minecraft too yeah yeah
but it's all circles inad of blocks it's
not squares it's yeah circles now it's
balls
spheres um orbs balls orbs spheres SPS
balls no 3D
circles
cets oh like a princess here we go yeah
it's all it's all Tiaras eny of
Minecraft I would play
that we're here okay and then follow me
we'll go to the tree I hope someone
makes a Minecraft mod where instead of
Cubes it's all no no no it there's a was
it there's a Tik Tok channel uh that's
like what if I added um I added blank to
Minecraft it's the best Channel and
there's one that's like I added
socks to Minecraft and it's like super
elaborate where if you can you can put
on the socks and then if you put on the
socks in water they'll get soggy oh and
if you if you uh run too much in the
socks you'll get sweaty and then you can
collect the sweat yeah people Bo I faced
out and I lost you
oh it was all the the Soggy socks talk
so the Soggy socks made me so
uncomfortable that my body recoiled from
following you okay I'll find I'll find
the channel hold on you need to see this
guy's Channel cuz he adds like the most
ridiculous things socks is just one of
the normal things he added to Minecraft
wet socks is not normal and you should
be you should that's the worst thing in
the world that's true like dying murder
you know that's okay but wet sock say
okay I said bad but wet sock worst up up
go up up okay
y oh no no okay I think we should ask
the people to add the wet sock mod to to
This
Server I'm never going to play again and
you should play with a real life mod
that every time you use that mod you
have a bucket of water underneath your
your table Bing socks and if you get
your socks wet you have to dip your feet
into the so into the water it's like
more immersive than
VR yeah it's like you know those 3D
theaters at at um amusement parks where
they like Spritz you with water and the
yeah it's that they should do that for
Minecraft that's what Minecraft 2 should
be there's circles there's a lady who
plays Skyrim with like a haptic vest so
like when she gets attacked it actually
hurts cuz she gets shocked all over her
body no oh that sounds
dangerous yeah that sounds espe the
electronics
but it's a Merc where are you I I'm
coming up I fell down again oh okay I'll
take your time it's
okay I feel like I like Skyrim because
it can never hurt
me get that vest on you
no Skyrim is my safe
place you want to do the hurting
exactly what you go C
see I'm I'm ah oh God I'm going to die
I'm right behind
[Music]
you you
are turn left Left Behind turn more left
closer more
ah okay take this wall
[Music]
thank you okay now
all we're making scaffolding oh yes yes
food uh oh I have food bomart can
provide food for all employees even if I
don't have any money best company in the
world you're working for me no she wants
my she wants my Crack Pie here have my
Crack Pie what oh Crack Pie Oh you
picked it up yourself you're an addict
here you
go where is Crack Pie she put put crack
in the pie yeah it's literally what is
that crack you
smoke yeah yeah yeah yeah it's um they
get people addicted so they want more
yeah it's a perfect business model if
you think of about it that's
smart right I'm upset I didn't think of
that okay so we're just putting
scaffolding like this all over the
bottom of the area so fa can put lights
on the tree
scaffolding like like you see just put
random lines of wool everywhere so that
way we can walk along this bottom part
do you want to get it okay so I start
here and then I go yeah this here and
see am I doing a good job boss you are
hold this in your put that in your off
hand oh
what's some more pie it's unfortunately
crack yeah
oh this is the healthy
option I'm trying to quit I'm I'm trying
to
quit if I mix some of the Crack Pie with
the normal pie then maybe it's like a
slower addiction you know like a slower
you'll
never we off of it you'll get too many
withdrawal symptoms wait wait was it you
who were like really confused about the
word wean for a while wean we you talk
about the word like a pacifier and I
went like isn't that like a pacifier and
then you said no and then you said yes
happened like two days ago
Queen like the the band Queen Don't Stop
Me Now having such a good time like that
yeah yeah that's that's exactly the
conversation we had you mean like the
rap
gas that one yes exactly what I was
thinking
of why gas
you you really have to ask you really
have to ask I don't even know what
gaslighting is high selling girl is
trying to gas can I destroy
the the what is this the the grass
thingy Vines The Vines no no okay I why
do you want destroy because it's in my
way okay I'll build the around it yeah
build around and go a different way okay
okay I'm going a different way actually
I might change my I'll be right back
okay this I'm not very good at staying
up
there do you do you keep falling down
yeah hey you know what that's okay we
ask a little bit the mon so did you
mistaken me for someone else cuz I'm
really sure I didn't okay I'm going to
go into our DMS and we're going to send
it show you it's we've had this
conversation like we
have how do you write the ween
we we ween we
pacifier w e a
n we we I don't think we've had this
conversation
I'm so confused she's gaslighting you
yeah I don't know who I mean I mean I'm
not gaslighting you I'm very confused
Cece's gaslighting you oh yeah okay I'm
being gas yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
did I dream you you dream of me and
wean she dreams of you weaning just for
context it was about a pass it was about
the word wean off and then that it's
like you can use a pacifier and then you
dream about me using a
pacifier oh my gosh yeah you're
confessing I dream with few people but
not of a
pacifier it was a beautiful dream but
there was no pacifier involv why not
that's okay that's a little insulting to
me there absolutely was no paire I
believe you there
was there was no pacifier everything
else is true I stand by it no
pacifier okay um anyways I might be
going crazy because I can legitimately
not
tell what it was um maybe you had it
with another person no no there's no way
I check like all the last GS like I I
put wean into the Discord of literally
every single person I've talked to you
made up
this it's like it's like when you she
made a conversation
[Music]
ni and then you're mad at them and then
and then they're like why are you mad at
me and then I'm like oh you were mean to
be in my do you I said that to my
brother once I woke up and then what and
then I ignored my brother for like the
entire day and yeah cuz my brother
bullied me in my
do oh so you're the type to like hold
cres from your
dream well I know I thought it was
real fa Fair fa you know what in my
dream you gas like me people I can't
believe you did that oh I'm
sorry apology accepted we can move on
from this topic
now I feel like I missed
something she's a liar and a cheat and
we should get her fired from this
company our HR is a liar and a cheat no
stop I just got
here okay
first day on the job and already lying
she's going to embezzle the funds
next someone's taking the
books exactly cuz they're already taken
it's okay is it okay if I say
afterwards I don't know HR what do you
think HR is I think that's okay yeah
that sounds reasonable I guess it's okay
HR said it was we got the clear yeah HR
I was being gaslighted by HR
yes yeah can we fix that no
oh well you heard it sorry
[Laughter]
guys okay you just can't be mad at those
Giggles you
know no
stop but I mean I was going to like this
is this is huge F like it's one thing to
see it on stream and it's another one to
like be here this is huge it's
crazy it is it is huge right for a while
my chat was trying to tell me that it
was only a medium tree it's a
big big tree GI it has its own ecosystem
and everything gravit pull like I keep
falling the reason people keeps falling
down is because the gra
again yes that's why Shadow
the plan a
tree there is a shadow look down look at
the Giant Shadow on the floor the Dark
Forest I feel
DLC I feel bad for everyone who buildt
underneath my
tree it's okay they can use I cast a
shadow upon the land what if we kissed
under the FAA tree you wouldn't be able
to kiss for
long you're going to be interrupted by
the hundreds of
monsters and the cries of the
sheep yeah the Sheep asking if they can
get kiss sheep sheep sounds make it more
romantic the Sheep want
in they do I don't I don't know how HR
wait that's me I don't know how I feel
about that
you should make like a bunch of ttin I
fell
down wait what happened to your totem
holding the
totem I had in my hand which
hand oh do I have to like equip equip it
yeah well put it in your inventory
there's a spot next to the green book oh
put it in there that's the off hand spot
sorry hold on let me let me fly around
and look for your stuff where did you
fall wa I can show you exactly where I
fall fell and then you can fall from
there yourself oh okay okay okay so I
was what's the what's the button to
enable hit boxes
again stuff it's not it's not control
B cuz that's the Nary that's
specific what you might think be for box
agree okay I fell exactly people where
are you oh it was B for box but not
control B yeah I fell here oh where's
here right here are you back up yeah I I
spawned up because I slept in the bed oh
okay hold on there's a lot of Enderman
around hold
on the tree has its own ecosystem it's
beautiful
CU I don't know what the context is but
I the video that people or whoever um
pinned is one of my favorite videos and
I'm really happy really in the cat jump
in the cat I love it so much I love it
so much it's so
good honestly the any post that
takes you like a lot of
effort you know way too much effort yeah
I really
appreciate I think my favorite type more
people yeah we we need me you guys have
you guys seen the cat that you sent to
your group chat without any context one
it's my favorite video of all
time to us you have to send us with no
context now there is
context for for some reason my oh my
elyra broke that's
why okay hold on
I have the stupid the stupid uh song
stuck in my
head I'll get a new song stuck in your
head don't worry hold on I just got to
find a safe
place I have strategy stuck in my head
still oh hey boy I'mma get you I'mma get
your real
you oh I have a
a no no more
[Music]
uhuh uhh
uhuh kissy face kissy face I feel like
I'm aging 8,000 years in one second no
the second song that they were singing
was like a normal song but it has this
like tick Tok Tu bait sound bite and she
goes
like I'm not it's
it's apartment it's with the with um um
what's his name uh Brun Mar and Ros from
black pink yeah and it's everywhere it's
driving me
insane okay I found the song I found I
found my favorite video I'm sending it
to all of you it send this to your group
chat without any contact I'm sending it
without any contact
okay maybe you should like leave the
voice chat and then send it to us and
then come back in so that in with less
context oh I do love this
video hold on I have to mute my desktop
audio on
stream it looks good you I'm just going
to add everyone in the in the server and
just send it hold
on I'm undertale music
yes at
[Music]
everyone okay this is pretty good yeah
yeah at
everyone boom okay there's a lot of good
memes with undertale music I always
think about the fingers in his ass video
all the time that's a good one that's a
classic
it's a really good
one you know have you seen it B boo
that's a that's a challenged cat it's
playing the really not seen
it that's pretty
impressive do you know they're all like
uh um Kida from dong and
roma MMD dancing to
it you know it's really good at dancing
so talented
and the song's really catchy too I
always sing it when I hear
it fingers
[Laughter]
in fingers in his ass fingers in his
ass
name fingers in his wow fingers wow
isn't it
catchy Thank You Toby Fox fingers in his
W I don't think I know that one oh you
don't know the meme I'll send I don't
[Music]
think people where are you people I I
haven't I haven't been able to work
because I don't because my stuff I I my
elij is broke oh no can you give me here
I have some stuff for you oh yay put put
this on you think I'm going to make the
fall with these wait actually I don't
want these fun I'm just going to die
again and then I'm going to lose all
your stuff no no no you're not going to
die you're not going to die on me
nobody's dying on my watch okay okay
take this and put it in in the slot in
your inventory and then have this one
too in case you die and then this one
just make sure
you fingers is beep fingers is beep
fingers is can
have please it's so good it's so catchy
fingers in his beep fingers in his beep
fingers how does she burn to death
immediately upon joining the
server gig Jimmy
[Music]
say hold on I can get you
both fingers in his
hole that sounds worse somehow way
worse that that is make it worse that is
worse he said that
he he said it I'm just repeating it so
you w say the for the first you'll say
fingers in his
yeah well that worked I did get replaced
now I have undertale music stuck in my
head instead beautiful undertale music
so good it is it is actually yeah have
you SE heard his um the Toho collab that
Toby Fox
yes good so good thank you wait oh it's
a link
[Music]
it thank you now you can work beautiful
tirelessly oh oh my God I thought it
fell down no no no I have I found R
where's R R's at the bottom of the tree
oh wait I have one more thing for you
CeCe ooh
a present I mean do you call it a
present if your boss is like giving you
stuff you need to work a Christmas gift
for me it's a your bonus your Christmas
bonus here you
go you you you give you give me a bed oh
wait it's not even green pH I want is
this sorry it's the wrong color can I
just put it here just carry it with you
and then when it's time to sleep you can
put it down down okay although You'll
Lose Your Spawn I guess so you could
leave in my head I just hear fingers in
his
beep it's really catchy it's really
catchy it has no right to be so
good but the beat goes hard too
yeah okay I'm back at where I was and I
can go back to work beautiful okay I'm
trying to escort R to the the tree but
there's a lot of enemies around us is it
daytime yeah oh there's even enemies
during the day but but shadow of the the
FAA tree you know
yeah I placed a few torches down but it
was nothing compared to
the
darkness oh boss I have a I have a
business proposal what about what if we
turn this into a very overpriced tourist
attraction ooh I like the way you think
M we can have collection boxes at the
bottom of the tree so if people die we
just collect their Loot and like oh
sorry that's now that's good we should
build like a pit of lava but then
underneath the pit of lava it's like
Hollow so that people think there's
stuff burned up in the lava but really
it just went to the bottom and we can
collect it we fool them into thinking
that their stuff bln up
genius genius and then we have all those
collectors into to like the whole
storage like a huge storage system
underneath the
tree yeah oh and then and then we can be
like Amazon and like ship things with
the thing on our tree and then we're
going to make that also of a price we
can sell it back to people like oh your
your stack of diamonds burnt up that's
such a shame well we have a stack of
diamonds right here that we can sell
actly what you need they're going to
think we're like Clairvoyant or
something we really understand the
market you know this fast moving
Market
perfect I like the way you think CeCe
you might be up for promotion end of
year wait a minute the end of you is
very soon
yeah perfect see this is why I knew I
wasn't good hands okay I have delivered
R to the uh scaffold
if you have equipment for her for you
know company mandated stuff company
equipment
[Music]
as have you guys played undertale SL
Delta rune
yes yeah I haven't played prop R is
pretty good it is good yeah the next
chapters are supposed to come out it's
not done yet so excited wait until it's
done done that might be a
while it's okay I'm patient it's okay
I'm so impatient I have to play it when
it releases I was going to wait and then
I did wait I waited like 3 years I was
like
well play like one chapter I think cuz I
do remember some of it I I've played it
all so now I'm in
the
when okay any minutes now don't
worry I think it's better this way than
you know rushing and then it's true
yeah what do they say what's worse when
they wait and then and then you wait and
you wait and you wait and then it gets
announced and then it gets delayed and
then it comes out and then it's so bad
so yeah but I have trust it'll be nice
me too me
too it's so
dark well Delta run can't be bad I don't
think that's
possible right yeah I don't think
anything Toby fox has put out has been
bad exactly lot of music is really nice
too like the homestuck music yes
the homestuck
music unironically good he's just really
I've never got into home I know it's
like super popular what can can someone
do a quick brief summary of Homestuck
culture um home it's like it's like a
multimedia comic
series that it became Infamous ah why
why Infamous I think because of the
fandom mostly
it was really popular with like you know
teenagers morning good morning morning
and Tumblr and Tumblr and Tumblr
teenagers on Tumblr yeah I have a
question do you want me to you know
there's places that are higher than the
others cuz it's a tree should I build up
so you can reach those okay okay oh you
may have back down then it's okay I can
make stairs Raa where are you I am on
the top of the tree I
think okay let me let me give you some
stuff really thank you you don't have to
thank me it's just it's just your your
stuff you need to work company mandated
equipment yeah the company mandated
equipment I'm this is is this are we
good on safety and health regulations
here by the way um isn't that your job
to figure
let me see I did I did die once but must
be a me that that waslo error I think
yeah yeah yeah bomart gave all necessary
equipment to prevent that okay but you
should have given me a 30 page text
document that I didn't read and then it
would have have been your fault oh thank
you do we have workers come
no we have emeralds
oh oh okay do the pink pot
um so what we're working on right now is
the scaffolding below the tree oh wait
do you hold on let me give
you
this okay take these you know how to put
them in your off
hand yes I wonder why that tutorial was
[Laughter]
added okay and then you can come down
here okay wait actually here take this
bed
[Music]
too thank
you and
then come down
[Music]
here there you
go and then you can carefully
walk
[Music]
yes uh actually let's go this
way okay
[Music]
so you see how it's like um these
Pathways below the tree mhm so we can
place blocks on the underside of the
tree so it'll be visible from below okay
that's basically what we're working
on it doesn't matter what color right no
it doesn't cuz we're going to remove
them eventually
[Music]
so don't wor very dangerous it is is
very
dangerous which is why it's very
important to always hold the
totem someone has to do it I think I've
fallen more than I put blocks down oh no
but it's okay I'm back up back to
work should I place my bed somewhere
here yeah you can if you would like okay
can I place here yeah
yeah good night
[Music]
okay I wake up and I do work this is my
life now
yes so you can continue in this
direction okay just placing blocks the
only thing is um just saw oh my God you
need to build down over here you see
where it goes down I can build you a
staircase
yeah thank
you so you can build I have so much to
learn I know this is this is the
annoying part I'm making you guys do the
annoying work that's fine oh we'll do it
thank shift shift is your best friend
you won't fall if you press shift that's
right
yeah plus there are there are mobs here
and I do not have anything to do
myself we can go to
[Music]
sleep it's just too dark under the
tree what are you what are you saying
about the train are you saying bad
things about the she's reconsidering
your
promotion no no no no this will go on
your yearly
evaluation okay I can sleep too
everybody sleep
okay sleep okay
this bed
down I go I go to my bed okay I if you
don't have a bed you can let your
employer know and she will get you
one okay we I'm eeping sleeping through
this night sleeping through this be
careful when you wake up that you don't
fall
off the zombie still here you so
dedicated zom still here no my bed fell
down
okay so I go to the stairs and then I
build Street um so basically you'll just
follow like the path of the roof you
know okay like so you just want to build
it so that you can reach the roof and
place blocks
so um she wants to build Place lanterns
at on the roof of the yes on the bottom
of like the down part of the tree so
we're building a little grid so we she
can walk on the grid and easily reach
the ceiling
okay so let me get some blocks
o yeah so over here like this part will
need to be up but then you see the lower
part mhm that's where it will need to go
down like over
here okay so I'm going to build pink
blocks from this place
to straight
on um build it over you see this part it
comes down uh-huh build it over there oh
okay okay okay oh I see so then we can
reach the underside of that piece so
this direction okay yes thank you I'll
try sorry if I'm going to do it wrong no
problem
no
problem CS do you need
something a bed a new
bed yes please she needs a promotion
what no I don't need a promotion right
now I need a bed she's costing the
company valuable
resources wait wait I thought the other
one was my Christmas
present that was a trick you fa with a
test to see if you you are chuly
worthy here this one will be will be
better ooh can't wait for my second
Christmas present this is my New Year's
present guys Happy New Year happy New
[Music]
Year
Christmas
away yeah it is almost
Christmas can you believe it guys
what do you guys want for
Christmas
um a kiss you kiss yes yeah kiss all
us wait this is like inappropriate your
boss shouldn't be kissing you I
think it's it's
kiss it's okay
[Music]
hello okay it's fine
hello hello I'm late but I'm here
welcome welcome hello I'm I'm
lost oh okay let me find you you fauna
I'm where you had me idling the last
time we worked on your tree
oh helpful I could stay here um it would
be helpful but if you would would rather
build no that's actually perfect because
I I've been out all day and my cat
missed me and uh he is now sitting on my
desk so I can't access my keyboard B oh
my goodness my baby so I'll I'll idle
here he is clingy
oh I love
him I saw him on Twitter
yeah did you did you like him was he
cute do you want to meet him course yes
want to meet him yes I want to hold him
in my hand he does he smell good did you
see him yet Hees I smell him all the
time every time I see him he smells so
good that smells so good I love cat
smell you guys making good
progress yeah yeah we're totally not
falling more times than we're working
what no we great CeCe where is CeCe I
am um pretty close to the wooden parts
of the tree oh my gosh there's a lot of
creepers over here I'm getting attacked
oh my God okay um I started with the
orange and then I build pink because you
give me pink uh what color is above you
uh orange orange oh she around here can
ask if someone has
torches I'm torch um I do I fell oh I
saw that can I have Tores yeah you
live that's
cool I will deliver
torches thank
you okay well maybe you can ask to
supervise
myself I can yes wow somebody has made a
lot of progress over here I'm working
hard
are you guys are doing
great things go so much faster with
employees is this why people have
employees oh my gosh must wow so I'm
going to build from here to the top to
the roof
perfect and I'm going to continue those
lines
until over there yes okay that's perfect
got it thank you thank
you I'm going to put some back in the
water I'm scared of
[Music]
creepers torches are good it's
true I avoid them for no good
reason because you have to make an extra
thing and
that's we don't do that my inventory is
full enough already yeah that was
gorgeous was it's okay just increase the
brightness of your screen yeah right you
said this once you said my inventory is
sick and now I think about it every time
I open my inventory like my inventory
does look sick today yeah my inventory
is very sick please
help she has every disease we must fix
her She's suffering
okay I'm back on the tree I am on top of
the tree now okay how do I oh no uh
there should be if you're on top there
should be water that goes down a little
bit yeah but I I took a different
elevator oh than the one that you're
talking about okay are you at the tippy
top yeah which part pink pink okay I'm
coming me too oh now I'm between pink
and green I have a bed for
you and I have a feeling you're going to
like this one o i wonder green bed don't
spoil the present sorry I'm just
guessing spoil I'm a
psychic are they are you know everyone
who works here is Clairvoyant remember
it's part of our
branding oo is it yeah we know exactly
what everyone's missing at all times
what this bed what am I missing not drop
it okay where I to where I you don't
want me to
say I
see all there is a skeleton oh it fell
never
mind there was a
skeleton that's the best defense
against here
oh okay now I recognize it okay and then
right here is the water yeah yeah
yeah back to work no lunch breaks no
lunch Breaks Allowed eat on the job he
got a tree to finish yeah yeah
okay um where was I BL orange orange red
oh no fall again I'm so I need some Big
M there's so many there's so many so
many there I I currently see about 15 15
monsters
well handle it don't
[Music]
worry did you remember to replace
your your thing oh my gosh why does
everyone sound like they're dying it's f
we have to hire a monster hunter I'll
I'll hun Monster Hunter I'll slay them
okay I can show you where it is you're
right there are about about 15 monsters
that was a good guest
right
okay okay at least this time I'm
spawning I I I fell close to the
waterfall oh my goodness there really a
lot of
them thank you boss thank you for taking
care of
them okay I'm going to I'm going to uh
do some monster prevention strategies as
well thank you
wow so kind are you placing
torches no I would never play okay okay
I was like that's crazy that's what our
boss that's not me it's not what I stand
for down with
torches I mean really like don't you
feel like torches are the worst light
source in Minecraft
not
yeah like you only use them if you have
no better option you know yeah you only
use them to like you know plan out where
you're building but it's not aesthetic
yeah it's true yeah it's
true not aesthetic at all okay I
am back maybe oh gosh there's even
monsters up there
oh oh
oh
ouch
okay
back watch out behind you so there
building oh no it's why so this is why I
was building here and then
higher and then
yeah a
oh wow it's really very
dark oh I maybe we should
eat yeah that might help a little bit
okay
okay I'm tucking
in I'm going to eat Prett fart one
second yeah me too one
second don't let the zombies bite you no
don't bite me
okay I'm sleeping
too I'm in the nether I don't have to
sleep do I no you don't need don't do
not sleep in the nether do not try to
sleep in the nether it's
okay you do and something fun will
happen no no yeah it'll blow up I don't
want to blow up this tunnel though I
feel like someone built this with very
much
care I believe they did it was probably
Kyla it's okay she'll build it
again maybe we can summon her that way
Kyla your tunnel's broken we need to get
back
on Kyla you have to come fix this tunnel
Kyla
[Music]
help oh I'm out
of this how it's dark in here I didn't
put any lights did
I okay it's okay we you you haven't
reached that point yet it's
fine these are our first steps I
building no the monsters they keep us
alert you see you know so we're not like
checking our phones constantly like
that's a good point yeah stay in the
moment business you allow your employees
to be on their phones yes okay what okay
M experiments you have a startup
business you let your workers on your on
the phone you read the Google reviews
they're all complaining about the rude
servers and
rude workers that are always on their
phones no we're not customer service are
we no we could be
mayom if you take their phones away
they're going to like find a way to
sneak on their phones anyway right yeah
that's what I think and then people will
complain about it anyway
what if you'd give them like phone time
it's not like always phone it's not
always phone time what kind of business
owner are you I'm I'm mind experimenting
here okay I'm not a boss I'm an HR
person okay oh okay thinking I'm I'm
thinking I'm
thinking understand understand okay
thank you I felt a little bit of you
know I was attacking you yes yeah
yeah I'll write that down in your book
more that is what I was doing oh my God
pretty Northern
Lights yes oh are you watching yeah
since since I'm idling I'm just watching
your stream see what everyone else is up
to you did you see me go through the
wrong portal like three times yeah yeah
but it's okay we everybody makes
mistakes everybody has those days Days
yeah everybody knows what what I'm
talking about yeah everybody gets that
way oh you guys understand
[Music]
stand you get
it we all get each other that's why
we're here building the Treet together
oh oh I thought we were doing it for the
pay I mean that's
too I I'll pay you if if fart has
anything it's emeralds
so I'll take emeralds yeah how did this
happen I was pressing
shift okay I no longer have any totems
was she pressing shift sh I was pressing
Shift
review i w i was we need to talk about
your
performance this no that's me session
you might be off the team we not going
to make it to world like this work what
what right and Authority do you have huh
V you be
surprised you should have said seniority
1 hour
senority I don't even have that wait you
start noia this is an equal we're all
equals
here
well us is boss yes oh my god there
creepers oh God only answer to one boss
okay
okay did you R
theing fingers fingers in his
beeping are you okay yeah say the say
the other version
yeah yeah fingers in his hole bring it
back oh fingers in his hole fingers in
hisle fingers in his hole fingers in
hisle fingers in his
hole it's still it's still I need a
different song I know catch someone help
me it stuck in my
head I still have
[Music]
okay um I don't have do you happen to
have one more totem for chance boss um
yes your delivery may be delayed we're
experiencing delays in our delivery
system right now she's cooking let her
cook okay really it really is like
Amazon it's
fine please hold okay I'll I'll I'll
hold shift even stronger than last time
yes
hold shift and all will be okay okay
probably I'm holding
[Music]
it I remember still from your debut yes
you talked about video game music
yes and I think you have very good taste
in thank video game
music I love those
playlists yes I don't listen to Spotify
I just listen to like YouTube playlist
and just let it take me wherever it
takes me that's the best way to do it
yeah it
is it's so annoying that YouTube changed
their like recommend Foundation feature
and now you kind of get looped in what
you already listening to I hate it
frustrating give me new stuff YouTube
please
please also really nice when they do
like Jazzy video game music and then
it's like yeah oh you guys should listen
my suggestion is low five mixes of video
game music Kingdom Hearts one is very
Peak Zelda one is also very Peak yesi
video game
mixing are you
okay
okay no I got I got hit by a skeleton so
we can blame the skeleton we can blame
the SK and we should sue him and then
with that money we can get no more
totems yes yes yes mhm we will sue oh no
are you going to be able to recover your
items no respawned at the will you show
me where you fell maybe I can help you
this time yeah um if you go to the
scaffolding that I built it's like pink
it's under the orange parts and then
it's like there's like some orange
scaffolding a little bit of green yeah
yeah a little bit and then between the
Green the pink and the orange kind of
like around there is when where I fell
was an orange piece of wool on the floor
pretty close to next where I fell
M okay I'm just going to fall and
see did you fall
[Music]
by my place did you fall on a branch or
did you fall all the way to the
[Music]
ground I
think good question
well productive productive
conversation I'm not
sure don't
remember this you can remember I should
have I should like this is the only
reason we should all be streaming at the
same time so that chat can tell us CH
it's true do you have hit boxes
[Music]
Ono yeah I have hit boxes on I'm just
flying around helps a little bit
but there's so many enemies that enemy
hit boxes I found my stuff I found my
stuff y
yay it was on the floor we were going to
go bankrupt replacing all that
all oh God
cookies okay okay
[Music]
um oh there's a bed here too
she beds
everywhere she really provides for us
yeah it's like are views Comon post
those to glast Door Duro is a really
good company they take such good care of
us and by they I mean need diamond armor
and food we got health insurance like
literally we do we have yes you do we do
our totem the totems the totems are help
yeah I'm going to die she gives it to us
for
free for free so generous so kind it's
okay it's okay it's it's SP right there
there's like a lot of lot of enemies the
lanterns not the lanterns sorry the
Glo okay I'm helping I'm
helping I'm not sure how ow ow ow ow ow
ow ow oh
uhoh it's okay I got your stuff
where are you CeCe I'm like oh my God no
wait you didn't get my stuff uh I'm at
the the bottom stuff I have your pants
oh nice okay I'm at the bottom of the
waterfall can you baak them out of that
of there okay okay okay and there's a
lot of
enemies come over here I think they're
stuck in the water people okay here's
your
pants are you at the bottom cookies yeah
we're at the bottom of the water right
under the
waterfall okay your delivery has arrived
woo oh hello nice bone you've got there
thank you I just picked it up from my
enemy's bones I'll take so many of them
thank you my
shoes oh I'm going to put on clothes
again company company clothes your
uniform my uniform
okay perfect I'm
ready boss can you put some lights
around the around the waterfall that
those that we use elevator yeah yeah I
think should be the next plan of action
after we finish the tree is lighting up
the The Forbidden Forest oh gosh the
forest is really forbidden it's kind of
dangerous even to light stuff up yeah
okay okay I'm going back up I'm going
I'm not cut out for this it's not in my
job description yeah just just run
okay but now I have a totem so
everything is fine yeah don't forget to
put it on your hand did you put on your
hand yes
thank I feel like no matter how many
torches I place the the darkness remains
oppressive as
always eventually it'll have to go away
of Darkness for all the lights there
must be equal Shadow okay chipio let's
go
it's okay at some point you will reach
the light there's so many
craters of past explosions
here okay it adds to our tourist
attraction this is where someone died
this is where someone died flowers on
top of it it'll be fine yeah make it
beautiful I mean everybody loves like a
dark forest level in a video game right
yeah poison put poison in it poison yeah
poison swamp yeah poison
po everyone loves poison our
forest we we should make a poison swamp
at the
[Music]
bottom the
bog welcome to the B have a
witch in the
Bog with her own little house yeah which
Cottage a house with chicken
feet what
yummy the Baba Yaga you know Baba Yaga
oh right right okay John
Wick wait I think that's a different one
is it wait no yeah he's Baba Yaga wait
what John Wick is Baba Yaga yeah John
Wick is Baba Yaga he's a witch in a
swamp with a a house with chicken feed I
thought he's the guy with all the guns
but yeah but he's also bab modern Baba
Yaga why I see Baba Yaga when did that
happen that's his that's his
nickname valid
yeah it's he can be anything he wants to
be
okay he he wanted to be Baba yag Yaga so
therefore he is
[Music]
okay that's actually what the the movie
is about a tale of Discovery is it
I just so SP have you guys not watched
John Wick no except the one I watch
scary for me what do mean scary what do
you mean it's scary scary what do you
mean that's too much Gore what do you
mean
scary it's not even that gory it's more
action the one is really good you should
action scares
me it does yeah I don't like watching
people do I feel it you're an empath uh
that's
I it's not real g g it's not real scary
it's not real it's it's a
movie it's really cool action mov
there's a creeper no no no no no no
scared me too should we sleep oh okay
I'll put my bed I lost my bed I can't
sleep where'
[Music]
my cosing the company I lost my bed
everyone sleeping wait where's G um I
can give you a bed up
orange orange side up oh gosh up let me
let me walk
down I saw you nope I don't think
so there is a bed can sleep I don't know
maybe is it orange is it my bed there is
an orange bed I might have left
it hold on I can't believe she abandoned
her bed I'm walking back back I would
never abandon my bed I love my bed I
thought I brought
it did did fauna give you the bed Gigi
yes that's messed up of you I don't know
where it is the bed that is messed up do
you see me I'm lost where are you I'm on
the orange side I see a name top oh
there you
are okay
here oh wait do I have beds I
do okay I can sleep thank you sleeps
right in front of
[Music]
you are Minecraft beds right next to
each other on the scaffolding perilous
scaffolding I'm building
up um I fell down
and maybe I need a little H to go back
to where I was where did you fall down
too yeah know because the creeper was
like in front of me so I had two
options like one was dying and the other
one was just going into the
water no if you're in the water you
should see like a waterfall that goes up
yeah yeah I'm following it right now
yeah look just look for any uh waterfall
that goes up it'll take you to up to the
tree and then you can find the one that
brings you to the but it's safer up
there get get out from the bottom of the
dark yeah the Dark Forest is not is not
safe uhoh okay it's a work in
progress it is I'm placing torches down
as we speak
actually beautiful it'll be saved in no
time and then we can also have a tourist
dist attraction down there yeah tourist
distraction yeah it's because the line
to the fun Tre is going to be so long
like a less exciting but still exciting
secondary attraction to redirect the
traffic yes yes like
like they put like the line yeah plazoo
when you put all the like animatronics
next to the line mhm and they have it
winding so it makes you feel like you're
games so then we can have even more
money yeah big games you people people
are going to like get distracted on the
games and then the line's going to get
blocked off M you can have like little
little shoots that go off you know the
forest is Big we have
space and then we have that and then and
then we put food stalls with like really
overpriced
food and then they get bored from
waiting and then they eat the food and
then they have to stand in line for the
food M and then we should put like like
hotels in the line so they can like go
to sleep and wake up this so many down
there they can use those for free oh oh
oh we need free B bees but some
something that is like really like snow
something that's really temporary snow
like like water yeah yeah yeah free
water free free water free water's a
little too add bathrooms paid bathrooms
free water but paid
bathro and put like some flavor in the
water you know like Gatorade or
something so that it's more addicting
and they drink more of it and then they
have to go to the
P $5 per bathroom
usage yes that is my favorite strategy
in in Planet zoo is to make the zoo free
and make the bathrooms cost
$10 it works it does work cuz people are
so excited about the free zoo that they
forget about the yeah yeah and make it's
really cheap yeah when you have to go to
the bathroom you have to go yeah true
got it so a video about like H why you
get more annoyed at you know when you go
to a cheap airplane line or what it's
called and then you know they but
everything costs extra like o extra
luggage oh you want luggage cost extra
oh you want water cost extra and how
that like how the psychology works why
that's way more frustrating than if you
just paid way more to begin with mhm so
we should we should think about that as
well make it a little bit more expensive
but make everything team free you know
they paid way more in premium experience
yeah yeah yeah yeah but the value that
they pay more is not actually worth what
they getting right but it's like oh it's
free really bad peanuts o but it's free
that's
nice
yes and then some more merchandise maybe
like a towel with a logo on it or
something on it
mhm yeah I don't do I want my face on it
if they're going to be like washing
their dirty hands I want to wash my face
with your face yeah wait that's too
intimate oh no please okay it can be
like an employee
towel put your face on
it can you put like a hand print like
your hand on it like a hand print so
that way it's like you're washing our
face with your hand like you're actually
was your hand oh my God that's so
how would you know what whose hand it is
an arrow the nail polish obviously you
can't tell F's hands well I can but
maybe our customers from our wonderful
tourist attraction they will know we'll
we'll write F his hand in big letters we
we'll we'll puten nail polish and then
we'll get a friendship bracelet that
looks fauna s so then when people see
the hand they'll be like that has to be
faa's hand and then we can sell the
friendship bracelet exactly two pieces
of merge lied we can also sell the nail
polish too
yeah I'm going to get F's name tattooed
on my
Knuckles punch someone it's the last
thing they see yeah I like that wait how
many letters f a fun you well you can
put the A on your thumb right yeah thumb
thumb yeah
song The my song it just end up saying
fa instead and everyone's
confused
huh I put the fa on one one finger oh
the thumb the thumb knuckle
Works hello hello I'm here to do some uh
lighting thank you some monster
prevention oh yeah uh I also need some
extra torches if you guys happen to have
some okay I will
be right there I'm doing a good
job you are I deserve
torches you deserve demands now things
to do your job
[Music]
yes oh gosh
it's like a NeverEnding battle against
the
darkness we must light it up but it will
sounds like my
life your life is so hard hello yes it
is I wake up and that's it that's
already too hard I wake up yeah that's
too hard I wake up period that's it I
wake up that's too hard these on the
pink part on the top on the roof you
know I just got an upgrade let's go you
have some torches
[Music]
too thank you thank
you employe of the a right
here we've got we've got some
competition now
I can start the competition be careful
be careful I'm not scared of the
competition you know I'm going to push
you off I'm so sure about myself
survival is the
finished you have a totem of surviv
survivability thingy I'm
dying did you just fall in front of
me who just fell nobody was it you be no
I was out of wool I was I had to get
more wool it's a shortcut yeah shortcut
do you want uh it here further closer to
the tree truck as well um I think it's I
guess I should connect the wool
eventually but you know just who's going
to even see this part anyway okay so you
don't so I shouldn't keep going I go
back yeah you can go back
okay okay
Okay g is a player she tried pushing me
down I did not I was just standing
there do I just place them randomly or
do they have a pattern just place them
randomly
okay I will
uhoh ah ah so many
torches think we should be allowed to at
this job to listen to oddly
specific podcasts or video essays boss
yes of course narrated by
FAA you may check the list of
preapproved fa approved podcasts is is
the six hour summary of Kingdom Hearts
lore on it
um yes it is
now how many times have you listened to
that one more than no uh the guy tat
namora the the director of Kingdom
Hearts has specifically said in order to
like refresh himself on the plot that he
made he has to watch his own lore
videos funny yeah you know that's valid
yeah honestly I mean when did the first
one come out it's been forever
especially because they probably do a
lot of brainstorming and a lot of stuff
that they're thinking about doesn't
actually get they they do a lot of
redning like just
stuff yeah I I've been wanting to play
King for a really long time and the main
reason is there's this one video on
YouTube and it's called why I can't I
think it's called why I can't introduce
Kingdom Hearts to my friends or
something and it's it's just like a
bunch of scenes out of context my
favorite part is there Mickey Mickey and
he he has like a coat cloak on and he
goes he has like a cloak and it's
covering his ears so like you can very
obviously tell that it's him right
because this is still there and then he
goes like it's me I'm the blah blah blah
of darkness and then he takes off his
Cod and everyone goes
like Oh my God wait Mickey Mouse was
evil the whole time no no it's like
Darkness light one must exist Darkness
light light darkness dark he's good he's
good yeah emo and then
someone spoil us something happens to
someone and then another person goes no
who will I eat ice cream
with no that's the saddest scene in the
game what are you talking about that's
the saddest scene why are they just ice
cream symbolism it's symbolism of their
friendship iceam
I can say is that that video want to
play friend okay okay okay I'm sorry
people I'm sorry I take it back yeah
take it back the video the the the scene
is very heartfelt and the reason I
wanted to play it is because I felt a
lot of emotions POS negative in that
moment sadness sad you should feel sad
it's really sad okay I believe you they
just wanted to eat ice cream
together and the music's really nice so
that's also reason number two
the music's always really good in
Kingdom Hearts
[Music]
mhm oh yeah they have like the the songs
like the what's the one that everybody
knows
when music please I never played Kingdom
Hearts before but I know all the music
yeah same
true is the
goat you no that is not beautiful that's
better than fingers in
his
right don't remind her I just got that
out of my head how why would you put it
back when you walk away here take it
take it people take it
please baby please don't go don't go
okay do you need it oh no there's
already lanterns on the white part right
that one's kind of dangerous cuz I think
we're allowed to
sing oops okay we were out of
tune they what what are they going to do
it's
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry okay we all have stuff to do here
where do I where do we go next um you
can still build underneath
the the white part cuz I'm going to add
more stuff oh okay some stained
glass okay okay so I I am at a white
part where there is already stained
glass but you want to do more so I keep
building here okay okay you can keep
going I keep going my method was very
halfhazard
it's okay it was only you now you have
an entire team we
do that's why I've abandoned my
halfhazard method for this method it
works a lot better but it's more time
consuming mhm okay why aren't these
sheep producing more
wool are you out of wool I'm not I'm
just wondering why the green box isn't
refilling yeah it might be broken it's
okay fine there's another sheep or
there's another wool Farm that's kind of
nearby it's a little bit of walking but
I'm afraid of stealing from the green
now if they're not refilling I also saw
um I'll steal something eles hi oh hello
yeah there's can I go this way okay of
pink wool I stealing the pink wool yeah
there's a lot I found random boxes
everywhere as well that had ton of it um
H I have a problem yes I was getting
some extra wool for myself then I
destroyed the box and the Box fell off
and now it's gone that's
okay I need to find it again you don't
oh no you don't need to find it what on
my wool you can get more I can bring you
more
okay did it fall in the water I think so
it's really next it's next to the
Taco I think I found
it let's
go thank
you that was really
sad don't worry pink wool is is
infinite the tree is looking really good
it's almost all lit up amazing I'm doing
a good job we are doing a good job
than no just just just no no no she
correct just woke up girl I'm sorry if
I'm very quiet by the way good morning
thank you for waking up early to join no
of course I'm
happy okay here's your your suar box
thank you
[Music]
so don't go don't
go
[Music]
okay okay the snow looks pretty nice I
don't know there like right under it's
like a snow biome I think snow is
actually the prettiest maybe Sakura Tre
is prettiest biome in Minecraft I don't
know I love Sakura biome yeah they knew
what they were doing
nice
to I'm excited to break all this
wool yeah going be so
fun will it be will it be chear no it'll
be fun okay it'll be fun are there shars
that are like better at breaking it I
think can we they are slightly can we
burn the
wool that's scary that's scary wait wait
that's such a good idea
but the tree is that's how dangerous the
the the the tree well well it should
well it's not
connected
up as long as we make sure nothing is
well think about it boss think about it
I'll think about
it but I think shears I I'm not sure but
I think shears are pretty better than
they are faster yeah yeah
that are they are there like diamond
shears or is it just shears just
she maybe we can like use some
enchanting or something I don't
know to make it faster can you do that
youant I don't I don't know I don't know
I don't know I don't know enchant I
don't know
either oh you can that's cool you can
okay you know what you have to prepare
for us next time Enchanted shears
efficiency five Unbreaking three
shears perf would that be
fast yes with
mening
um um do you have more Frog Light
by I can get
[Music]
some I think what what am I idling for
again frog lights yay
yes thanks Che
Nissa I'm an important part of the team
here at K you give us a cheer cheering
for us give us a cheer but like have a
cheer from me every day if I could just
have you here every time I just
something oh you clean the dishes good
job it is so good that's the dream you
prepared the meal oh my God it's so good
look at that look at you go can you
praise me for waking up
today me anybody good good morning
you're a I'm so proud of
you I I put I put a meal in a microwave
and then I ate it
yay wait wait what kind of meal I made
it yesterday and it was leftovers it was
the leftover microwave meal it was sweet
potato Poes with with like um beans and
P Deo and and sour cream and you all
that by
yourself um well the only thing that I
had to make really was the p and that's
just a salad I guess
it's it's yummy it's like tomato so it
wasn't it wasn't a a microwave
meal no mic it wasn't the leftover
microwave meal it was the leftover
homemade meal
yeah it was in the microwave but I but I
made it the day
before sweet potatoes from you did such
a good job yeah that sounds
good I'll send you the recipe it's
[Music]
yummy okay I'm done with my frog light
Bak potatoes are great any
type okay I'll wait for R and in the
meantime I build
more thank you
I never really understood how to build
down like the stairs yeah you need like
a water bucket to build
[Music]
down okay just buildt
up
fire you put like 500 sand right under
you it would be worth it that's true
you can you can do
that I'm going to go get more frog
lights thank you
[Music]
Whit Ribbit it's froggy
time why are they called Frog
Light I think I don't know frogs are
involved somehow
right it would make sense that they were
for these I don't think we're killing
them what what what else would you take
from a frog say
what I wouldn't I wouldn't hurt a
frog no not one multiple apparently I
wouldn't hurt
frogs okay I believe you they're just
it's like a byproduct it's like frog poo
you know oh oh huh yeah so no frogs were
harmed we're covering the tree and frog
it's it's
natural it's eco-friendly is beautiful
yeah wow
beautiful it is beautiful
[Music]
yeah am I doing a good job it's really
cute are
okay I have no idea what's happening you
are creating frog lights beautiful frog
lights I'm so
[Music]
happy I'm here
behind
you over there oh I see you I'm like
actively telling like when when I came
up here I was like oh I'm going to make
the perfect grid and it's so
bad thank you so
cha okay well don't worry cuz it will be
it'll be
destroyed too much trying not to be not
not with fire with safety perhaps with
fire we're still we're still thinking
about it right uh no no we're not we
vetoed it bu but bus you said no no
that's v no I've thought about it oh the
answer is is
[Laughter]
no after careful
consideration at least you thought about
it she thought about it for at least two
second no I I trust it was at least 10
multiple
seconds okay
[Music]
oops okay when the scaffold is done we
can also Place Glass Blocks
around or added
depth okay wow the scaffolding looks
really cool from under the Tre it does
look kind of cool yeah do we have to
remove the scarf holding yeah yeah
eventually okay so we just keep the
lights
mhm yes and the
glass glass does not exist yet glass
glass glass
glass that's a
bug free so-called free thinkers wi
Apollo the parrot is mentioned GLK flask
GLK it's a b it's a
b
botle you're good at
that okay
um
uhoh my God there's a giant hole oh
yeah no I saw I saw nothing I saw
nothing we can we can worry about that
also at some point you
know okay but not all I see is
scaffolding
scaffolding I'm excited when I have to
cut all of it yeah it's going to be fine
it's going actually be really satisfying
especially the end yeah I feel like
that's the most tedious part no no the
destruction is it be fine yeah yeah yeah
I don't know just remember it takes like
10 times longer to break it than it does
to place it no not this super cool C was
simulator you know yeah that's true
we're tearing down I think it's more
Mindless too you know exactly what you
have to do yeah
yeah even though you're not really
supposed to think about the I'm still
thinking about placing where I'm placing
the blocks even though I know it's going
to get
destroyed
yeah it's hard to turn your brain off
completely with
[Music]
it I feel like I'm placing glass blocks
and I feel like you can't even see them
no it's like one of those things where
you need to see the bigger picture yeah
you know like right now it might seem
but then when they're all there I can
see
them can you see it yeah I can see I can
the the white one especially I can see
hold on let me go to the green I don't
know about the green ones I feel like
they're invisible the green ones the
most the best especially the dark green
glass no
[Music]
I can see it if I look really hard yeah
yeah if you pretend if you envision it
with your mind's eye of
course can see
it are you all are you all using the
pretty fire
mods for the game the shaders
mhm I am but I had to turn mine down
lagging my
computer the number one thing we noticed
when we joined the server was like holy
see I don't think it's my computer's
fault I think it's too much on the
server a lot going on
yeah okay boss wait don't you have a
4090 I do yeah then it comes yeah then
it's not it's not your PC oh yes I hope
it's not well you know the 59s are
coming out that that's true you should
get them from Minecraft yeah yeah yeah
590 to play Minecraft I mean Minecraft
is the The Benchmark right mhm is it is
it not still
crisis 20 years L you mean that super
old
[Laughter]
game when did it come out 2007 oh my
God hey that's not even 20 years okay
it's not even legal of 18 age yes it
cannot legally drink in so it's okay I
mean Minecraft is also super old right
how old Minecraft come out Minecraft is
like what 12 years old that's was an old
game9 she's getting
old the beta was in 2009 and then the
official
2011 so it's even
older e oh then what you thought yeah
yeah it's really old oh it's
raining the tree will protect us it
can't is it raining or is it
wondering Minecraft is entering angsty
teen
phase you're right is it oh that's why
it's so's about to go through emo phase
like right
now oh no what will they add wet socks
yeah new hairstyles ooh that would be
great hairstyles that come the the the
one the bang one eye yeah it it adds
like random t-shirts with like bands
logos on it and then when someone speaks
to Minecraft about it and it's like oh
you like that band they go like yeah do
you well name every song every time I
think they should do that and the wet
socks um boss boss yes ding ding ding
ding I I would I would like to I my I
think I can I go to bed ding ding ding
ding let's go to sleep
everybody my cat is here he's on my lap
and C are falling
asleep what me and you are both keepers
of cats right
now very distracting uhoh I moved and
now he's he's leaving he's had
enough I'm back
no he heard you complaining his
delicious
compliance no I'm sorry it's my Feet's
fault that they're falling asleep it's
not your fault please please don't go is
your cat
clingy is yes he is a he's very you
would lose all blood circulation for
your
cat I would I would I promise I would
but ow my feet hurt
OU is everybody
sleeping I'm sleeping I'm not s sleeping
I'm not but I'm in the
nether what are you doing you are not
allowed to sleep no sleep allowed for n
Raven
cross one second I'm
going Minecraft got the creepy biome
update wait did it I'm not up I am not
up to date with the new Minecraft creepy
biome me NE but I want to see a creepy
biome what is the creepy biome yeah what
is
that never heard of that okay I'm going
to I when I said the sleeping thing I
meant like in real life so I'm going to
go
s
oh okay thank go to sleep thank you for
joining I hope the scaffolding goes
smoothly from here on
okayy than you good
night good
[Music]
night you mean Minecraft isn't real life
I can't wait for her to wake up and the
scaffolding is gone and she just Falls
to her
death when she logs back in oh my gosh
she might right yeah we better finish so
we can get rid of
go so
evil feeling AR GG I mean you guys it
seems like you're pretty close like how
how much estimated work is there left at
this point it looks it looks pretty much
done it does well we could we could add
stained glass which might take a while
we should add cherry blossom leaves to
the pink oh yeah that too they'll fall
then right yeah it'll be so pretty yeah
yeah we should do that feel free if you
need to farm them I don't know if you
have a way to but you can go to the
little uh artificial Forest I made to by
beo thing is it the resource server if
you just go into the server it's
directly in a cherry blossom Forest I
think so oh nice yeah where is the
resource server
portal it's in a house it's in a house
yeah saplings guide me is it this
house uh hold on let me it's in the
shared house let me look
too not this
house the other
way come to the the portals it's by the
portals was this
house you know the portal to the other
servers yeah yeah and then it's this
house
go up here wait I need I need to
get I forgot the shears the most
important part oh in
here no it's a different a man oh is it
not cherry blossoms they updated it it's
not cherry blossom anymore that's okay I
can find some look I'm just saying by my
house there's a ton of cherry blossom
trees but it's going to be ugly if clean
it don't grow back won't they well if I
plant it
yes
yeah I I'm sure I have a t of saplings
anyway for the cherry blossom trees so
it's no big deal well maybe I'll take
some
saplings into the resource server yeah
it's so satisfying to see progress
though mhm it is I actually might have
quite a bit in
myai let's
see or I'll just raid Kyla's house
probably has
some thank you in advance
Kyla I've been stealing her dye and
everything Kyla is everything
let me
see I'm pretty sure I
have I thought I
had cherry blossom
saplings is this my glass oh it is
[Music]
um am I need to borrow some from you
Nissa okay I'm pretty sure I in my house
where's your house where bi's moai
statue is if you go that way um my house
is literally like to the left of her
you'll see a ton of cherry blossom trees
I do I see follow the cherry blossom
trees yeah there will be a little hobbit
hole
and inside I'm pretty
sure I should
have some oh cute H hole yeah oh it even
has the round door yeah just straight in
uh there's some chests to the left by my
bed that I I'm pretty sure will should
should have cherry blossom
stuff
yes yeah help help yourself I will take
a
few yeah this is my artificial
biome it's beautiful thank you I worked
very hard on it how you found cherry
blossoms um in the Ian server there's a
place K I think found them someone found
them and they made a way to get to them
so I went painstakingly back and forth
and got a ton of stuff from there
nice
yes oh and
then in here I'll just make my own
cherry blossom biome at the spawn in the
resource resource server do it so
everybody else can also get cherry
blossoms hell yeah
my finger is dying from holding down
Crouch Oh
no just live on the edge don't hold it
down your finger is going to be so
muscular mhm
so no be
ripped any saplings
I just need one to make sure I don't run
out one sapling now
one you can forge in saplings wait
really wait what was that
sticks getting
sticks it's better be real and not just
a trick to make me use up my pickaxe
durability
[Music]
uhoh uhoh I'm
getting uhoh are you holding the
totem
water water's good
too yeah I was still holding the totem
I
live y y
yipp never die work back to
[Music]
work oh my
gosh someone tell Kyla that her island
is overfilled with Pigmen is it oh
because of her portal
yeah they're just coming
through I couldn't get out of the portal
cuz there was a wall of
[Laughter]
Pigmen I know you're saying Pigmen but I
misheard you and I thought you said
Pikman Pikman and I so I had a very cute
image in my head Pikman Pikmin Pik
Pikmin
[Music]
Pikmin that would have been very welcome
mhm it would have been are they the
regular piglins or the zombie piglins
the zombie ones from the nether I love
the zombie
[Music]
piglins I just think they're
cute did you need
saplings um
no okay I mean always but
[Music]
no what we going to do after uh the
lights after the lights we can add
stained glass and other blocks for
texture
texture texture
yes so I'm collecting some uh cherry
blossom
leaves right now we can use for the pink
part can't wait for it it's going to be
so pretty yeah I think so I hope I don't
actually know how far like the
how far the leaves yeah how far the
pedals will go will they actually reach
the
ground stop it's fine
yeah I'm also bringing the the actual
petals themselves oh yeah those are good
too can you can you grow those with bone
meal no you can grow them but you can't
like make more of them grow I found
don't worry I found a whole show box
full of them thanks
found I found CL found soer box full of
petals W
[Music]
uhoh oh my game is
lagging I feel like I'm about to die
[Music]
resources while I'm here do you need
anything else by the way
[Music]
um
no maybe maybe like perhaps what I don't
know like plays terracotta but that's
optional terracotta really L is
terracotta in in various colors you
know that's optional
only to make things like really
fancy this will be the fanciest
tree it is pretty fancy already it is so
fancy I've been working on this thing
for over a year yeah and it's finally
going to get done it is no I remember
before I joined I watched you work on
the tree and then I started helping you
I was like
wow that was my goal with the tree to
make you like a like a piece of history
on the
server it is at this point something
really recognizable you succeeded thank
you I better finish it with your guys's
help we will get it we will finish it
finish it we will it's pretty close
already I think ouch
ouch what does terra cotta look
this terra
cotta I think it's okay don't worry
about it I know it looks like I okay she
does have it I see
it that's just
optional it's not
optional
mandatory not
mandatory
[Music]
mandatory I think it will will be able
to make it look good without it cuz it's
like it's hard to
[Music]
get no she Kyle's always take what you
need La just take it just take it La
that's what she says so don't
wor that's true
[Music]
I think she's always looking for an
excuse to get online and farm stuff
grind I feel like I'm going to tank the
frame rate with these
leaves I can't wait in their I am
bringing a white
glazed or pink glazed Terra cot and
white glazed thank you I think that'll
be good for them pink no white
[Music]
sections it's just so easy to use a
stack of
material on the tree cuz it's
so it takes like 2 minutes
I'm actually running out of Frog Light
already and
full
okay but take your time I still have
64 oh I see
you hello I don't see you oh wait is
that you no oh that's Gigi I'm
scaffolding you are
scaffolding made it all the way around
I'll make sure you can make
it
everywhere and then I don't worry even
if there's too many blocks I'll
deconstruct them
too thank
you there's not going to be too many
it's
perfect more fun to Shear
yeah I'll try to get special shears
I think even with the normal ones though
usually it's pretty fast to
remove they'll probably die really quick
though oh yeah
true I've been fisting a few and having
fun getting rid of them really yeah I
need to they're they're oh oh my God a
zombie just spawn right in front of me I
bet it feels really really good to punch
like if you think about it
yeah I feel like it would hurt I feel
like my arm would be so tired after one
[Music]
block there's some some Pathways I had
to rebuild and I just punched them
all didn't it take forever so much fun
I'm having a good time okay if you say
[Music]
so the nether is dangerous
yeah it
is okay we might be out
of of the pink frog lights is there
anything I can do to make them spawn
properly no I think it just takes a
while unless something broke when a gas
uh thre a fireball at me but hopefully
not hopefully not
there there is a farm of frog
light or you just craft them there's a
farm in the nether
[Music]
M okay wait where are you
Raa I am on the pink side um on the dark
side right now I'm like oh there you go
there you are hold
on uhoh
[Music]
oh there's water
here uhoh I'll make my way over to you
don't
worry through the
maze
scaffolding sorry no it's good thank you
okay I
have Sher box this was all the lights
perfect I think that should be enough
can we put pink petals upside
down
yes wait what do you mean oh wait no no
no the ones on the ground no I don't
think so you can't a
okay
[Music]
yeah that would be cool
though that would be cool
I want to see from the bottom I can't
wait to see it yeah I took a screenshot
actually did I or did I forget what the
screenshot button
is I'm just going to put some random
pink glaz terra cotta is that okay yes
okay oh it looks
nice yeah it does it's all lit up it
reminds me of
Christmas Christmas time is
near Christmas
time
cheer do you like Christmas time I love
Christmas
Christmas it's my favorite time of the
year yeah I'm so
excited I get to Ste cat
again a
you could say It's the Most Wonderful
Time of the Year I would not fault
anyone for saying
that I would say that's pretty
[Music]
accurate I think I'm going to wrap
things up here for today okay okay I
think work today yeah this was great
progress good job thank you guys for
joining
me thank you for letting us help you FAA
yes I'll finish this scaffolding before
the next Minecraft Monday thank you I
appreciate it yeah feel free to work on
it don't need to ask me or
anything but thank you guys and I will
be here next
Monday doing okay I'll be seated we'll
be
here we're going to be finish this tree
thank you we are yeah we I appreciate
you guys thank you proud
employe thank you thank you to work at
fart yeah I need you co is the best
company oh thank
you all right thank you guys you I will
see you guys later byebye bye
[Music]
and thank you guys for watching this is
very productive Minecraft Monday we've
got wait how many it say three more cuz
it was supposed to be five total but I
missed last
week three
more I think we finished this
easy
[Music]
easy all right thank you guys for
watching I appreciate you guys for
watching and being
here completion is inside and I'm not
going to worry about the bottom
part this it's a fine
already just as long as you know the
lights are filled in maybe some texture
and then remove all the scaffolding
that's good
enough I'll try to remember to AFK at
the at the Frog Light
Farm all right thank you guys for
hanging out I I will not be streaming
tomorrow it's my break day but I will be
back on
Wednesday so thank you very much for
hanging out and I will see you guys next
time bye-bye F well bye
[Music]