[Music]
do
so
[Music]
my
welcome
ina to my channel
no hello thanks for having me
no thank you visit australia thank you
for coming because uh this collaboration
wouldn't have happened unless you would
have us uh uh if you would have not seen
my cry for a collaboration
on the google calendar
oh yeah i was like
club maybe i was like it was like
exactly at the time i was gonna stream i
was like oh
hello no
it's like uh
i don't know like uh we like
communicating for the google calendar
don't we yeah it wasn't the first time
we did that
okay and so today we're gonna play
animal crossing ina hasn't touched the
game since her last animal crossing
stream right
yes it's been uh how long
i don't know it's probably been like at
least a year too long there's
cockroaches in my house oh my god my uh
residents of my island didn't want to
even enter my house but the update is so
cool you need to come back it's so much
fun i've been acting really
as well
i want to do the um what's it the uh the
cafe and oh the happy home yeah yeah
yeah yeah
the happy home of today i i had to renew
my uh nintendo online membership and uh
i i chose the one that comes with the
like experience updated one right yeah
yeah so maybe i recommend that to you
too so that you don't have to buy it
separately um
would you
like to come over to my island first and
then i show you my island and afterwards
you show me your island
yeah that's what we're going i don't
remember my island but i'll i'll do my
best
you have
[Music]
who is gonna come to my island
that's pretty loud sorry guys
oh
from the island's jago
why did you name it juggle
i don't know i don't remember
this was even i actually made the the
island and stuff like before we think
it was smart of you to already call it
something related to whole life
i was like i don't know what to call it
i'll just call it
everyone knows
but why i don't because like for example
my island is called
the island
yup what yago yago is the island
yeah go to the island oh yeah go yeah go
to the out was that the joke
i just came up with that but yes it is
well
let's take a look at you nino mai inanis
we're making a waterline
why are you in the bathroom
where's the effort what's where's the
effort
where's the gloves not available
[Applause]
[Laughter]
anyway wait i i guess you're standing
outside right now come uh wait you can
wait we can wait for a moment i just
want to show everyone look at this cute
outfit
anyways okay
look at my cute it's so cute
yeah
that's the apron yeah it's like a kotori
apron because i've been working so hard
today i i need something that i can get
dirty and i have a kfp
yeah
and actually i got my cheeks uh tattooed
with kotori as well
oh and in the back it says kfp too
yes okay um since my last stream i have
been working hard to give my island some
kind of layout and organization
and make it look
start to look pretty and this is the
first time i've ever really put that
much work into animal crossing so i hope
you guys are gonna like it
looking forward to it let's go oh oh
guys by the way right now uh this was on
purpose but it's it's um it's
thanksgiving right now in my island
uh i somehow
eaten thanksgiving
what
what did she say
you know what we eat in thanksgiving
not me that's for sure
well
for the for the people who can't eat a
whole turkey there's an alternative
let's go
you gotta be nice to me we just started
okay so i made a lot of paths so we
started out here and it's still a little
bit messy here but let's let's go to the
center i guess already because you can
get to know my my villagers they're all
here right now look at this big package
work everyone's holding drinks yeah
what's thanksgiving like here in animal
crossing kind of talk to my cute
villagers like cook it's been a while
shut up i've been around let me talk
oh apparently you can cook in the game
now i haven't tried it yet though yeah
you have to like get the vegetables and
stuff
for a good meal
because on turkey day we celebrate
nature's bounty in food
i
i got this new ugly villager um i i
don't want him i'm planning to get rid
of him again at some point but um
my favorite my favorite one is this
bunny here
she's called mira
yeah she actually
uh
when i played animal crossing before her
life for a little bit privately and she
was my first villager and then i had to
restart the village but someone uh
helped me get mira again so oh she's so
cute
[Music]
she looks like a superhero yeah that's
her thing
oh wait isn't there another superhero
filter
oh because that
is there
so i haven't talked to this so retain
oh franklin are you one of the locals
here
i'm franklin professional chef orc
extraordinaire
nook encouraged me to come and cook for
everyone
see turkey day is about celebrating this
harvest by preparing a feast with all
those fresh ingredients
and no one knows feasting like turkey
which is why we called it a professional
gobblegum
well i say that but right now it's what
those of us in my line of work would
call a conceptual feast
make no mistake i brought with me
everything i need to whip up and
positively goblicious clowns
i don't like clam chowder oh i like clam
chowder i'll eat it for you okay but
today is about nature's bounty not my
personal excellence i want to use local
ingredients where possible
just free manila
manila manila clams would be all i'd
need to adapt my award-winning classical
recipe oh
do you need to go fishing or no yeah i
need to die for them but i don't think
i've ever found those before
i typically have people to do my clam
dig digging where am i going to find the
digger on short notice oh there she is
me too
no no no no no no no i'm not gonna
happen right now also look at look at
this super scuffed black if someone can
make a proper flag of my logo please do
um i will use it no you still have like
the
i was making it and i thought that that
disappears after you save it but i was
wrong
oh
the basic clams on the beach
i haven't dug those in a while
anyway so my beautiful layout here big
path ah wait no no now we go down here
here's my house
oh
oh this is your house yes
right yes they did this is really a nice
exterior
let's go inside yeah i gotta be wearing
a proper clothing for
you mean your bathroom
yeah how do i remove my
clothes
should i
[Music]
so this main
living room is still a little bit um
messy but
it's kind of japanese themed
yes yes i love this moon chair and we
have a kotatsu yes yes
and let's go into this room
i love that music
yeah so addicting
one of my favorite this is my beautiful
bathroom for now oh gotta get rid of the
washers it's raining it's raining man
hallelujah yes it is
it's we didn't really enter the uh the
hot tub that would be so cool golden
toilet
oh
are you not
embarrassed that i'm here
it's just a chair
are you sure
try to get off of the chair then
there you go what did you do what what
what what does that mean huh
what's the idol meaning it's kind of
stinky in here let's get out of here
excuse me about you
i heard that silent
never right
what that was i've been drinking dr
pepper maybe that was that
doctor
intellectuals
i should have i should have wore like a
lab coat or something do you also buy
like
soft drinks in like
um like do do you order them online in
like big big big palettes like 24 pieces
or like 48 or so
because that's what i do
so i always have that if i don't have
family members
oh
all right let's just order like big
bottles yeah um
oh i can't i can't uh carry those so oh
here i'm trying to uh
recreate kfc but we're far from
finishing or i haven't worked on this
for a long time but i want it to look
like a fast food restaurant
but then i can give you this oh i can't
use that i think you have a team
outside yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
um but i like i like the sign we are
open that's perfect yes but i need more
inside
no one can say if you're open
don't take it so seriously
but i need more of those chairs if
anyone has them please give me give me
oh those i have a different color i
think yeah probably a lot of people have
in different colors i just need more i
don't care about the color as long as
it's more than one piece
that would be
nice anyway that was my i remember i had
like a teal one but i'm not gonna have a
yellow one
okay now let's actually kind of make
sense too yeah
i think so teal would be nice
now here's my bedroom
recently renovated
oh you can customize them now oh
oh that's uh you can order from the
kettle oh wait isn't this
it's like cinnamon roll and and
[Music]
this bed looks so comfy too oh that
actually looks so comfy yeah i can sleep
while someone's here
no okay
safe sleeping for later
okay
oh look at us we don't want to take a
photo can i do it while i'm sleeping
wait wait wait stay stay there stay
there no watch the angle please yes yes
of course
you'll be wearing a bathrobe oh it's so
cute i'm so cute
which filter
black and white
oh yeah perfect
are you watching the street
yeah i am i don't know oh okay if you if
you did that that um
surveillance camera one that's kind of
scary
yes
[Laughter]
freaking stalkers man
they're sleeping now okay i'm gonna take
this and then
uh wait i think uh
[Music]
oh cute and then
uh wait more from above
and then
wait
isn't there like a pro camera on this
one yeah but i think you have to stand
for that oh
okay let's stand up
and i'm sleeping
okay
i was ready with the bathrobe and
everything so that was a oh that was a
very girly room uh now let's go upstairs
ready
oh you already have it upstairs i guess
you had you don't have it upstairs no i
do i do okay
a surprise because you just started with
like the update right no no no it's not
before but i only streamed it like two
times i think okay upstairs is nothing
really i
i don't know what to do with this place
yes
started playing animal crossing oh yeah
she definitely then i need to give her
this thing here
yeah if she's just like fill her eyes
with these moons
yeah it's probably one of those star
items is it
i think so
the one that you get with with the uh
shooting stars
if you yeah yeah yeah you build it can
can you build it
uh you got a recipe from uh celeste
did you see my froggy chair
no
but did you sit in the froggy square
have you ever sat in the froggy chair
before
yeah
oh
it's numb love you oh no
you have to sit on the froggy chair
appreciate the froggy jab no i will
never let you call your mind now
you know the rules
so do i
what yes what's
you're never gonna let her
okay i need to show you a different room
i have one more roomy now
come with me
let me out let's leave heaven and go to
hell
oh
is this the usual room are you taking me
to the usual room perhaps
oh downstairs downstairs on the way down
the way now
i love if you just put like a single
chair
oh okay
well wow you even put a po yeah
there's entertainment guys well
it's it's supposed to be entertainment
until you realize that only one piece is
missing and that will trigger you so
hard
well i feel like there's more than one
piece missing isn't there oh maybe one
two three four five oh my god one two
two three four five yeah there's
more wait so animal crossing is saddest
as well
interesting we're on the same
vibe yeah
[Laughter]
they get me is a hurricane
all right that was my house uh i'm
currently more focused on the outside of
my island not on my house so it's not so
special but yes
[Music]
and please chat take a look at my
beautiful paths i've been working so
hard on these paths
oh i remember i tried to lay down all
these paths like on my island
i kept like erasing
yeah yeah
it's pretty difficult
i really like how um
if you put down the pads from like
animal crossing it like changes the
sound when you walk on them like the
crowd ah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah these are
really cute yeah these ones they have
like so many different tiles so um it's
it's a difficult to like figure out
where to put which tile yeah i'd be so
confused
so over here is my campsite currently no
one's staying here
and then
this one this path is connected to
are you here
yeah this path is connected to the to
the middle
to the center but if you would go up
here you can get to my nook's granny
also
you planted a [\h__\h] ton of holly today uh
oh
so it hasn't grown yet my sister
vegetable oh you got a tomato yeah one
tomato
[Music]
she took my tomato
she sees i have one single tomato and
she takes it all right all right all
right ina
wanna take a look at what my nook's
cranny has right now maybe something
interests you today perhaps
i already took a look inside i decided
to buy nothing
ah
the food looks good though and uh these
their food oh yeah is that cha huh
yeah yeah
fried rice
i love johan
this chair
it's like school chair yeah
just a normal school chair that thing is
cool too but it doesn't quite suit my
style
okay you make like a restaurant like a
themed restaurant
yeah
oh you bought the chair oh
yeah you like the sculpture
okay i'll buy two
good choice
making profits on my island already
what's the one on the right
that's uh you know those sticks that you
burn and then it incense insists oh it
is
yeah yeah yeah you can put them in your
bathroom or so cause that was stinky
just kidding
excuse me
all right all right all right all right
so continuing if you bought everything
that you wanted to buy are you happy
yes okay
my oh what about your clothings wait do
you wanna you don't have to
convey it come with me come with me
hey i worked so hard
okay i need to tell you we when the
update came out i i immediately streamed
and um i thought that i could get the
cafe right away but i realized i need a
free star island and i only had a
two-star island and it was like really a
mess and also i brought people over to
clean my island and then and then
yeah we had to work hard in order to get
that stupid update it took me quite a
while because just cleaning it was not
enough i had to do some other stuff too
i had to uh do some stuff in the museum
too so then it was not that easy but
here it is here it is
my favorite part about animal crush
now we can sit here together right i
couldn't sit here when i was alone
he always said it's reserved i could
only sit on the bar
coffee please
right there's two cups of coffee so 400
total he's only talking to you what the
hell i'm i'm the i'm the i'm the reason
this place exists in the first place
should i treat you do some coffee or
separate tricks
or is he asking about my tab yeah
why am i not being asked hello
um
but i'll show you some coffee all right
thank you
oh understood in onions you'll be paying
for everyone
i'll have those out in a moment thank
you
i don't like coffee but if if it's with
you i will force myself to drink it
oh you won't be sleeping tonight
oh with the coffee
oh taking screenshots
now this is living your best island live
yeah
cool thank you very much you you're
welcome no thank you
and i have empty cups now
did you know that like when you drink
coffee alone in in this
cat cafe uh you can like
you can you can blow on it to make it
colder and then he's like what the hell
are you doing and then you can continue
continue continue continuing he's like
are you sure you want to keep on doing
this it's gonna get cold and then you
can continue and can continue and
continue to continue until it's even at
room temperature and apparently you can
if you really do it much much longer
then you can even even get it down to a
cold temperature like i think like iced
coffee style yeah i didn't get it that
far yet because it takes quite a while
oh wow
but he go he calls you out he's like
what are you doing you should drink it
hot
but i see to him iced coffee is not yeah
coffee apparently he wants it really
piping hot but i'm nekojita i'm i'm
cat's tongue
what about you
oh i can drink it relatively hot not
like super scalding hot but like not
really hot oh
well thank you brewster
that's your name right
i think that was his name can i talk to
him no he ignores me now hello it's like
i'm not getting home here
i thought he like completely ignores me
like what did i do to you what did i do
you can only talk to him from like where
i'm standing okay
i will try he's making coffee
third cup of coffee i'm having today and
i woke up like an hour ago
thank you very much ena with her coffee
you can't live without it wait what
about me okay finally
welcome
like hold it
he i can hold it you know he doesn't
offer me
how did you buy
the coffee
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] he doesn't sell it to me
he tells me to sit at the counter what's
your brother what
is this normal is this a black white
[Music]
wait how do you open the favorites again
favorites oh oh i guess we can't do it
here right maybe maybe he doesn't offer
it to me because he already knows that i
hate coffee
wait i can buy another cup what the [\h__\h]
okay i'll get you a cup i'll get you a
cup
give me some hot chocolate please
yeah i'll give you only half hot
chocolate huh
no coffee please
he doesn't sell non coffee here
that's boring he should have a bit more
choice he needs to learn from kfp this
is not how you run a restaurant or a
coffee place all right i could sit here
forever yeah i cannot because he will
not serve me
but at the country
wait will he give me something
oh wait is that to go
oh it's not to go
this is just for you or are you ordering
together just me i guess for now
oh you're not gonna give me my fifth cup
of coffee for today
oh no
you need to calm down
it's an addiction
[Music]
it's too hot bristol it's too hot for
stuff
it's too hot he says coffee is gonna get
crazy dot dot dot
register give it to me instead i can
drink
oh wow the depth of a flavor expands at
this cooler temperature yes yes
does it i don't know let me let me taste
it it does but i kind of wanted one to
go
i have two cups of to go okay thank you
they're going to give it to you like
now he tells me i can order to go as
well
oh he wants you to drink an order a
normal one by yourself even if like you
ordered for me i need to order it for
myself to drink it here and then i can
order one
that's uh weird
have a secret sauce no wait never mind
he says have a seat at the camera
this is
a stupid bird
literally every bird of this world
except for me mummy and dana are useless
oh wait and uh uh i guess subaru senpai
is
a bird as well
not officially but
totally a duck
yes she's a duck she's a real duck
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah you can drop it probably
yeah drop by now
there you guys
we can hold it while we walk around oh
it's so cute
we're one of those starbucks girls
girl
yeah i got it he wrote my name wrong but
he looked at me like he is really
interested in me
oh my god yeah
girl
all right look over here
this is a residential area for uh the
people who have lots of money
oh this is so pretty yeah i don't know
what it is but it's pretty nice
yeah it goes ding dong ding dong
[Music]
drink
all right
[Music]
okay so
we have someone who lives here
and then oh yeah character i still need
to make this path yes yes yes yes
you can drink your coffee
oh my god
oh you can't you get a an apple thingy
from that okay yeah you get powerful
caffeine that's nice
i don't know how many times you can
drink and then over here is still a
residential area
can i play this one with the coffee
don't drink it again
you're done
did that make a sound yeah yeah it did
i think
it definitely looked like it was making
a sound
try running fast yeah i know you can
spill it i know that's possible
no i don't want to steal my coffee
i need my coffee
[Music]
anyway i'm gonna run
so uh actually what i've also been
trying to do is do some of these fancy
waterfall things here and there
and so things that look like more
natural and fancy
one of my tries is up here this is uh
where the japanese uh villager lives so
i made it look kind of like asian
uh-huh
and so over here is my
experimental area
[Music]
i'm making in real life i'm making a
potato uh
broccoli grater
look today this what do you think of
this does that look fancy
i tried
whoa
i'm trying it'd be nice that we could
add like like koi
oh like in dupont oh yeah yeah
and then down here as well i'm trying to
also i built so many bridges and
inclines since last time kfb so yeah we
only spent a lot of your money too
we got this little part over there it's
also a little fountain so yeah yeah yeah
let's play the thing ina and chat what
do you mean
yeah
yeah it's super difficult to do this
kind of landscaping stuff
it takes so long yeah
and then like when i want to get rid of
something i'm like to even too close or
too far away and then i make more water
instead of getting rid of the water or
the other way around
wow
anyway
okay so we checked out the the
top right area
now
let's go down here
okay okay
i have another residential area
oh here's the two residents currently
there's some really cute school uniform
blazers in my uh clothing shop you
should buy it yeah yeah it's really cute
i love i love uniforms uniforms are for
life
they got the white color and they got a
blue color and they got a pink color i
bought uh i think i bought the light
blue one
yes
pretty cool stuff
there's nothing like a artist or not
really an artist but like a tool
oh
cherry tart mmm yummy i got a recipe for
cherry tart oh
it sounds so good i love cherry tomatoes
oh you have to get recipes for food too
yeah i never tried cooking before but
you can get recipes now
yes yes yes yes
look at that pretty holly
so pretty
christmas season
thanksgiving music and this game is so
nice
music's so good it doesn't sound like
thanksgiving but i like it
what does it what what are you
what do you think thanksgiving sounds
like i don't know we don't celebrate
thanksgiving in my
country
[Music]
yeah next week is
thanksgiving at least in
the american
country
yes and yes that means also that is the
one year anniversary of my first
original song hinotori
oh and i have something really really
really really really really special
plants in order to celebrate the
one-year anniversary
[Music]
oh i did not tell any of the
other halloween members what exactly it
is so it'll be a surprise for you too
i'm surprised yeah but i've been i've
been working
hard to make this happen
and it's a really really big surprise
it's actually more than just one
surprise
what is it
can i guess
but i will i will not say
what it is but uh i i i i hope everyone
will be happy about it i think i think
it will be i'm sure you'll love it yes
oh
you did it
you look cute you look like a school
girl from some private expensive school
yes
cute
looks good on you
oh thank you oh my god i'm falling in
love
[Music]
god all right come with me here we have
some more
residential area
well this house is cute there's someone
in here right now who lives here again i
think so
oh
hello
you want to come into inyoung yeah
say hello
i have some really cool videos oh yeah
this one this one
all three or something oh she's cool
[Music]
of course macaroni wait wasn't audi
named after the the um
i'm a crossing grandma yes yes oh my god
wait it's just realized did i realize
that before in a different stream oh
[\h__\h] what i got the
holy [\h__\h]
oh my god
oh my god yeah
oh my gosh
yeah
she's so cute she just taught me a
recipe
how did she
i feel like she did
oh
is she gonna teach you
no i think she's just cooking for
thanksgiving oh okay okay
yeah i remember her oh she told me a lot
of people like wanted her she wants
horse macarons is that all crossing
between a horse and a fish
horse fish fish
i like like nebula
oh
nebula is a
long-lost cousin
like where where there's like a horse
like the top half of the fish is the
horse and like the bottom half is like
the fish or am i imagining things
i
i hope that does not exist enough
i feel like it exists in some kind of
like ancient art
it might
anyway
checklist
[Music]
these two are not home right now i think
look at what i did here i think this is
interesting this is a ketokidoke
bridge
but i thought
it it's kind of uh maybe interesting to
have like a really thin uh
river going through here
because this bridge it comes with some
water
oh
bridge also
sanio as well
oh yeah
i see it it's cute right
it's a cute frog frog character
okay so up here um basically there's
not much
left i'm just trying to do some
landscaping here
and and decorating here i'm doing some
more uh landscaping with water trying to
make it look like something
also been building again
many bridges here's another new uh uh
incline
yes and look look at this what do you
think about all these this water
thank you thank you
okay i'm looking forward to seeing more
decorate something here too
i want more more i've seen like really
really impressive islands that work with
so much water with so many waterfalls
oh yeah have you visited any like dream
island
people share their dream called i i
visited um
where are you uh
[Music]
island
i visited my viewers islands and there
were some amazing islands there i gotta
tell you
yeah they're crazy with their
decorations like how do you
how do you even think of this
now this place is kind of cute too oh
this is so cute yeah i love this item
it's so pretty and i thought this would
be a nice picnic date spot
so super senpai is waiting for me here
wait let me take a picture
can you do you have the emote of uh
sitting down
um
[Music]
oh no [\h__\h] i forgot no
no
yoga
i do
i forgot how to do emotions
um i think the right trigger
oh there it is
okay sit down no no wait i will sit down
after i do this
and wait uh handheld
camera
uh
tripod camera wait a second ah no wait
it took them out there
gotta go here first
but i can't turn it that way can i
[Music]
oh wait no no no no no wait uh
uh think
photo
handheld camera
yeah uh it's only like that damn it
and um
oh but that's cute wait can you get
closer to subaru senpai
oh okay
and then sit down um
[Music]
oh yes
yeah get that instagram filter on
[Applause]
beautiful you look so thin did you lose
weight or something
oh yeah damn girl
damn
wow
you're booty though your booty's still
popping no matter how much weight you
lose girl
absolutely amazing you have to tell me
how you did that
and dad oh nothing as massive as my one
brain cell
okay one one more
wow so picturesque
is that a word
oh wow
okay i took a nice picture
[Laughter]
i'll send those pictures to you later
oh thank you
i think that's pretty much all
i can show of my island right now
i think that's pretty much it oh my god
my music is so loud
should we go to your island now
oh okay i don't have an island but you
can come visit here
it's really not reassuring because
that's the third time you said that
i really don't remember milo
it's been a year a whole year
a whole year since i
played basically uh where's the layout
yeah the problem with these hedges is
that you just can't pass through
but it looks like oh these are really
cute oh wait before we go before we go
presents
do you believe in santa
oh i used to
you have to believe in him again because
i saw him in in disneyland paris
oh he was there
you know love so hard when you sent me
the pleasure
collab he sent me pictures from
disneyland and she was like
and then she was like
you know you gotta savor it i was like
balloons of minnie like stuck on the
ceiling or like floating away
i was like ready oh no
my queen
yeah i was actually that was while i was
standing in line for an attraction and i
was um i found all these mini balloons
stuck in the ceilings or in trees and i
was starting to collect the pictures and
i i just because you just messaged me
about the about the collab and i was
like i'm gonna send her those pictures
and i was like aina please help those
balloons help those minions come down
her milky mouse please help her
actually
they know what you're talking about i
showed the pictures on my uh stream on
monday
[Laughter]
actually i actually tuned in when you
have a picture of the uh
castle oh up on the screen i was like i
know that cass
as if we've seen it before in a
different street oh yeah but but don't
worry i actually i asked if it's okay to
show and uh it's it's fine apparently
okay i was like
a different adventure
but it was so pretty it was christmas
decoration oh
they just put it up like two three days
before i came
and yeah it was so nice honestly
christmas has like the best time for
lights for a lot of
instructions
okay so i will close my uh
dodo
and session let me go home first oh wait
wait does ending session mean oh [\h__\h] am
i closing the game oh
i think i am oh no you just kicked me
out oh okay you kicked me out
sorry no i'm gonna come to your place
now let's go
okay i'll get the door closed ready
actually you and i will be seeing our
island for the first time i should bring
you uh a present too wait one second
okay okay take your time because i need
time to open up the
island too okay and i will show you guys
one more outfit that i have that i
didn't show last time on stream either
[Music]
see i got this one
this is my casual outfit looks so cute
okay get something out what could ena
need all food
[Music]
i reckon you already have a lot of
things did you have like people over to
give you presents or did you never oh
i've been buying this i was just showing
my island okay so you probably don't
have
do you have a pc
oh
probably do okay um
let's see everything is fine ah you you
don't have anything from the sun video
collab right
yeah oh i'll give you some stuff sorry
sorry guys who who gave this to me but
it's
going to a new owner now
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's such a cute rug
it's so adorable
i've been buying so many clothes wait
since you're wearing that outfit i
should i could go partner look um but i
want to show my casual one
okay
okay okay
i'm gonna give you
i'll give you
i'll give you this
and oh wait
wait did you buy that already maybe
because it was in the shop today
did you buy the sushi costume did you
see it
oh yeah the the egg one right yeah yeah
uh
i wanna take this
okay are you ready
i got the photo code but you'll have to
hide the screen okie dokie
one second
hold
[Music]
such a childish umbrella
it's so cute though
and frog
[Music]
oh yeah i'm coming for you
so you're telling me yeah
is that is that just something people
are allowed to know that uh uh no no no
remember this one isn't like uh
friends with you or
no no i don't mean the code i don't mean
the code i don't know i mean
your islander
that you're your mom
oh no no there you know
mama they already know my money
took both of my switches and played
animals
i think that's so cute that your mom was
playing at animal crossing with like
you're pretty upset
okay so at first she didn't even know
how to like walk properly um and they're
like next thing i know she's already
like time like switching the time of my
switch and like she didn't know how to
walk properly in the game right yeah in
the game like how do you how do you walk
how do you like select how do you like
pick up stuff and then like like a week
later she's already like time traveling
and
decorating like crazy wow so if how much
uh
how much percent of the island is
actually made by you
um i say
probably 50 50. oh okay okay you gotta
tell me what's made by your mom and
what's made by you then
when we see it oh sh
okay cold is this
oh yeah
go ahead go ahead
animal crossing is basically like mama
tori's minecraft
yeah
now i'm trying to get mom mama needs to
uh
to play
play minecraft really yeah
she wasn't interested why no she doesn't
she's not really a pc person i guess oh
well yeah yeah but you can play
minecraft on the phone too right
as far as i know
i could probably get it on her ipad
maybe i don't know oh
oh it looks like someone's on their way
here i'm on my way yes
i'm cooking someone's on their way here
and one thing i want to say is uh on uh
since my last stream i've also been
working on and harvest island and i am
only missing one shop now
royal empress
which one are you missing uh the one
where you can store things like did you
know that now in harvey's island you can
do much more than just take photos yeah
you get like the the furniture diy and
a bunch of other yeah you can get the
the garden shop you can get the shoe
shop yeah you can get uh the the fortune
telling lady but i haven't tried yet i
wanted to get my first reaction on
stream
yeah and i'm almost done with it i spent
a lot of my kfp viewers money
oh
i saw a cute villager there
oh penguin
[Music]
yeah we got the fashion oh you got a lot
of holy down here too
oh my god
wow
okay
show me around please i would like a a
private tour
okay i'll i'll do my best
i honestly don't remember i really
oh all right
all right come on game the loading
screens in this game are the one thing
that really triggered me
oh yeah
oh
hello
that's cute is it from
is your mom the one who's using custom
patterns or was that oh yeah she
i don't use custom patterns too much oh
yeah so let's see
[Applause]
andrew here okay
her little cafe
yeah these kind of like outside shops
that people build are really fast
[Music]
i think this one is like half half me
and half mom
but she got all the all the patterns
here
that's so cute
i like it reminds me of santa's bread
shop in minecraft oh yeah
fine though nice
and then well there's the beach yeah i
see that you haven't decorated your
beach maybe i should yeah not much yeah
i had some stuff lying around but i
didn't show you because it's not really
i don't know what to do with it yet oh
that's cute
yeah this is a custom pattern one you
can like lay here oh
wait chill the waterfall take a picture
wait i'm like lying down the wrong way
that's okay that's okay
but yeah i think normally you would
always oh well
look at the ocean i have no other choice
wait okay so
[Music]
keep on missing the one that i want
this one and then um
wait what if i can i uh
because i can't change the the mode when
i'm lying down but i i think i can
change it when i'm here and then lie
down
maybe
[Music]
do this and then
oh you can oh
wait wait i guess you can't lie down
while you're doing that huh
and you really need to figure out
ah
i guess that works i'll just i'll just
do a
tripod camera and then i'll i'll come
over here from the side and hopefully
lie down yeah oh yeah
i wish i could
[Music]
chilling at the beach does that look
good
okay that doesn't work oh wait that was
the wrong filter
what was it yeah okay
done
thank you nice okay
ah
yeah this is the left side beach that's
so cute i
[Music]
i will not pay
it's okay you have it on the house
and i think this was for the uh
well the festival oh yeah yeah yeah i
missed that festival as well i don't
know what uh that was even about we got
together rather than like oh
okay
i left one over there
i think i don't i don't even know if we
can get there anymore whoa you take it
wow
the feathers oh that's so cool
i didn't know that yeah this this this
part changes depending on the season i
should probably change it to like
thanksgiving or something oh
yeah
i see that
seasonal park
wow now we got
well i guess there's not much here you
know how i look
there
okay
do you not have a
[Music]
she's the one that judges your clothes
oh and gives you a ticket
oh know how i lost on your flag look at
mine oh yes
yeah
why is why is the flag so low effort
what happened
what happened there
i don't know
i'm pretty sure i had a proper flag but
like when i checked today i was like
eh we gotta get a proper flag again yeah
i'll i'll work on that okay yeah down
here
is our
ah i want to see
oh yeah i didn't even see what was on
sale today what's what's on sale what do
you have let me have little tanookies
yeah
show me
oh nice bathtub
oh
it's like a really weird mannequin if
you think about it because there's
nothing like
human sized yeah
that's not how our characters look like
in the game basically basically that's
like the anime figure of animal crossing
ah
this drink is really cute though look it
even bubbles it's really cute
nice cocktail
yeah that bathtub is really cool but i
already have uh some oh yeah
so
i don't know if you want like an outdoor
pet
[Music]
oh i mean you can always just i don't
want it catalog
well good that i took some money from
your money tree
i'm buying it
i'm gonna buy it
huh what are you doing all right i was
just getting my miles
oh dr peppa
[Music]
you do you feel your intelligence going
up
ah
it's already at maximum can't go even
higher than that where'd you go you're
so fast
oh yeah it's not here
right here come back i'm
did you just move down
you're the famous frog that made the
video and frog which was so authentic
even my own frog noises are not as
marvelous as yours
i need to learn from you
what language are you speaking because
the subtitles are a little different
speaking
oh you have english
of those girls oh yeah oh you should
totally put this in your in your yeah
bird themed i should
i i don't have someone gave me one of
those actually oh yeah you should make
like a whole like yeah shine oh look at
that in the center do you see a bunny
there oh no that was just chairs
yeah
chad look at look at this angle and look
at the chairs that looks like bunny ears
doesn't it
oh it does oh my god
okay okay
okay using the same bridges
oops yeah oh i love those whatever this
is my flower uh crossbreeding brown i
like the orange ones pretty cool oh yeah
this is my farm
when we only had pumpkins oh
yeah i need to make a place like this a
fancy one
the wings look so nice too yeah it's
like the weeds actually like match i
don't want to clean up yeah yeah yeah
i get that yeah understandable have a
nice day that's my little little farm
okay okay um i don't think there's there
was anything here no nothing yet
um
after the farm you want some do you have
pumpkins i have them i have them okay
okay
thank you then
up here
oh
what's up here oh yeah this is the
weight of the um museum
nice there's like a little
courtyard of the museum
we can sit and uh
eat stuff nice
and you walk up here to the museum
oh that looks really big
yeah there's there's like an outside
portion with some some fossils and stuff
but
i like it
i love the cafe yet though unfortunately
yeah you gotta get it
yeah
finally there's little things to do so
go go get to work inha and yeah
mama nice yeah and then if you come over
here that's the outside portfolio
outside outside oh you actually made an
effort to like
uh extend your museum to outside as well
wow yeah cause i got so many fossils
right i'm selling them always
it does
yeah i see a lot of people doing that
but i i i decided to just sell
everything instead
yeah
that's a pretty high price
yeah i need the money you know
uh-huh yeah
nice piano skeleton excuse me that was
not a chiada skeleton yeah
enot would never do such a thing yeah i
would never do that i think this was
kind of like a again
incredible don't you
i think i think this is my monies
but this is
a fan of birds or what's going on oh i
just i think she just likes like fancy
pretty things
oh
i'm just saying she was working on this
last time yeah yeah and
uh what's up
oh this is the campground huh
so what's inside
oh no oh
stop wait someone is inside because
otherwise the tent wouldn't be there
hello i need a new villager on my island
because i don't like the current one
that i got
the blue one
who are you
i already have you
[Laughter]
i really like wait are you thinking
about leaving me benedict
is that what you're trying to tell me
seems like we got a familiar
australia
this is the weird thing about animal
crossing when you find your own villages
with the same names and like different
places and they act as if like they're
not the same person yeah
actually like right here in the sand i
used to have a um like a fire fireplace
oh
it's like a it's like a campfire how's
it going i think mom is worth working on
something different
and this has access to the back
okay
i want to look at your fountain okay
oh
that's much easier access i need to do
something like that because i have to go
down with my ladder in order to access
oh
yeah
i terraformed everything okay okay okay
now this is the residential area i think
oh
do we have them all in one place right i
wanted to look um
oh you do have them in one place yeah
yeah it's nice to have like like little
uh
pathways in the fences but they had
their own like front yard oh my god
i want the frog and i want the
the penguin those are so cute a sprinkle
all right all right
yeah let's take a look at your
residential area oh nice gardens nice
nice uh-huh
everyone got oh this person has a lot of
weeds
don't worry about it
yeah there's like a little
upstairs library here
whoa wow i like the style of it like the
dark brown leather
sofas nice uh-huh oh are those uh
an actual item right not a wallpaper
you can return your books here after you
read them i should do stuff like this
like things that should be inside i
should just build them outside anyway
yeah
i didn't really
think about doing that until now
[Music]
yeah we have some uh exercise machines
are you even using them
it's not mine it's in front of someone
else's house oh okay okay okay
we have a little waterfall
here
or
who lives here
julian uh-huh
yeah
making up here
oh
we're a little park and this is like a
premium area wow
oh
yeah you got a nice view into the ocean
and the lighthouse
hmm and where's your house
oh my house is uh this way
it's at the very top because premium
don't you know the sound they were like
running
yeah i like the sound
yeah okay house is a little outdated
there's some cockroaches placed online
can you please step on them
i will try
oh i'm coming in
i'll try kill as many as possible but
knock knock
knock knock knock knock knock on my door
oh it's kind of christmassy in here
yeah i think last time melanie's
decorated it she was like it was around
christmas time oh
like the
the blue chair of the piano
she's like
fitting so well with the red uh color of
hair
she has some good decorating scents damn
girl
okay and then if you come here
i think this is the kitchen oh
i have a house i also have it on the
right side on the first floor
[Music]
oh cockroach eel
i'm not gonna eat any of the food here
no matter how delicious it looks like
well i like the kitchen oh yeah this is
the kitchen
did your mom make this one too
oh i think i did most of this one oh
yeah yeah yeah those those uh those
this this
thing here that's called the craft from
in german
yeah crabs crabs
we eat that uh for uh there's this
carnival thingy in spring where
um
get really really
popular
um yes yes and then in germany
uh they call them berliner i think
isn't it like a jelly filled donut yes
yes yes i'm not sure where it's
originally from but i feel like it's
from a german-speaking country but maybe
i'm wrong
and but yeah both australia and
in australia we eat them mostly with uh
uh apricot jam mostly
mmm paprika
yeah
okay
nice kitchen show me more
i think some of the rooms are uh
in progress but oh
still
okay what's next the left okay
okay what do we have here
jim yeah a jab did you say jelly
it should be silly marmalade like jam
inside wow okay your bathroom is very
um
not so looks luxurious looks she looks
sure yet it's it's a normal house okay
what's with that trash can
it's my uh oh wait you can actually
throw things away in trash cans with him
no yeah i've never tried using one so
that you can all smell like idol meeting
away your fruits power
oh wait going to the toilet yes does it
right which
amazing thing since you left a little
present in my bathroom i'm going to
leave a little present in your bathroom
just give me a moment
okay
[Music]
oh
so much better
what do you mean it smells like peaches
and roses excuse me yeah that's the
febreze
i am febreze i went up to the
middle room
oh okay you like teleport on my screen
because you ran so fast oh my god this
is
so many
cockroaches sorry this is let me kill
two
oh
okay good i don't know
yeah this is my music room
whoa funky yeah
oh
you know like people like record the
notes and they play like the actual like
songs like editing the video yeah
so cool
animal crossing players trying to do
something valuable with their animal
crossing play time
yeah this is my music room still still
work in progress i should add like
uh what should i say i should add um
more instruments or like carpets and
ring out
yes it's got a sound proof it right yeah
soundproof the walls are kind of already
there but twerkable song
that was not workable
you know if you want something truckable
listen to spikes
[Music]
kind of a mixture of like
cute because of the wallpaper but then
also i don't know how to call this a
style
um what what would you call this
comfy comfy no i mean more like
sophisticated uh
uh
old-fashioned
yes yeah
victorian area um
yes yes the bed and the and the
the
wardrobes
are kind of like
kind of like that okay okay let's see
what you got downstairs okay basement
rustic oh yeah rustic
oh oh a little bit empty here
it's my work basement what what the hell
just happened
oh i just killed the oh my god all the
pesky cookers yeah i feel so much better
now
[Music]
this is my where where i lock myself
into oh you have one of those famous
paintings up there
well yeah i think that's a fake one oh
it still looks beautiful
yeah you can barely tell the difference
you have like different types of coffee
machines oh
yeah the good old one music
i think i think i remember from my
childhood like
having
had one of those before like at least
seen one of those before on the right
side
oh it's a coffee grinder yeah old one a
really old one yeah yeah yeah very
rectangular oh you can move it oh
[Music]
maybe we should bring this coffee to
brewster and see what he's gonna say
about that one
it's gonna probably be like this one
to brew his coffee
okay okay i've seen your place
did we miss something in your island
i think hold on let's see my map for a
second can we see everything already now
that would have been fast yeah
that seems to
too short let me see the map i didn't go
to your clothing shop yet
oh okay
oh it's like right behind um
the
i should really add the mario tubes ah
yeah i didn't use them either oh we
destroyed the
your orange dress i'll grow back it'll
grow back
i think you can leave through here
i think all of my roads are pretty much
connected so oh this is campbell
he has a
funny face
wait that face reminds me of that recent
fan art or so that i've been seeing of
like good at for example you know that
mouth you guys know what i mean oh yeah
the the grin
yeah what the hell is that is that some
kind of meal i don't know maybe it is
how do i get to the clothing store i
want to say hello to your penguin and
too yeah no to the frog i already said
hello i want to say hi to your penguin
okay
gotta go down i don't know where they
are maybe they're at their house
sprinkles
[Music]
sprinkles uh oh your clothing store is
upstairs ah oh what this way we didn't
go up there yet uh oh there's the bear
oh
what
big bear
she looks weird
look here now bears her
[Music]
bears are quite
interesting i think she was my first uh
villager i i think that's the first time
i've ever seen a bear in animal crossing
yeah what the hell are they rare or what
wait they have the track suits of the oh
i love that dress i love that dress oh
the dress one i think the dress i just
left it as a decoration yeah
cute i wanted am i salad
slap me and
they're selling uh they're selling a
pajama set with the
oh
with the cucumbers on the face oh
halloween dress cute i already have uh
all of that actually oh nice the
cucumbers
of course you would have
i'm gonna look inside anyway what do we
have
[Music]
they have cat whiskers do you have a cat
whisker oh i do i do
that is cute
you got the baby hat
i'm gonna take the mermaids oh baby
i don't have the baby hat yet rumble
but i still prefer
uh this one
and going to take
these glasses
and
not that i want to combine these things
but just later i was about to say i was
like that's some
interesting fashion choice yeah but the
dress i think it's it's supposed to be a
costume but even if i wouldn't wear it
as a costume it would look cute i think
yeah
already
nice okay
yeah that's that's about everything i
think my island seems a little small
because uh everything is just like
constituted into different places
[Music]
but it's so nice here i wanted i want my
island to look this advanced too
oh yeah yeah i'm sure if you play
boy
he's so cute
i want you
if if he ever wants to oh there's a
penguin whoever wants to leave
uh i'll let you know
the airport airport
i love the penguins
oh sprinkles where's your house at in
australia you can't come by anywhere
i'm the only funny trained and licensed
trendsetter in all of yahoo oh
you don't
exactly look like a trendsetter but okay
yeah basically your friend is in okay
i love being with the little swirl on
his head looks like he's some kind of
like um milkshake it's a cupcake
oh wrinkles
oh oh really is that the the joke
i think so maybe because they're usually
kind of related to their
names somewhat right maybe
cute i think i already have a frog but i
want the green frog too and i want i
want the penguin they're cute
penguins are so cute i was thinking of
doing a stream where i hunt for villages
but first i need to get rid of my most
recent villager again
oh and also i wanted to visit some more
um villa uh viewers islands because oh
my god last time i did that i was
absolutely astonished by what these
people have been making even among oh
yeah our viewers there's so many crazy
animal crossing players mm-hmm
wow wow yeah
crazy
so was was that uh i guess all of your
island
i think so did i did i missed something
what was on the bottom right
did we see the bottom right i suppose we
did i'm pretty sure we saw the bottom
right yeah that was the flower
ah
flower breeding grounds
for a different color
pretty sure
oh bear is here now
it's all the way over here
yeah i will give your island
the following
[Music]
ratings ten out of ten
yay
go chat go chat use the emotes yeah
okay i have some uh i have a i have
presents for you too presents
are you my friend
this is for you
i work well you like it more now right
because i wore it first oh yeah
you are my present
let me catch
[Music]
and you
this
and
this is what you gave me
[Music]
and
that's what i just bought okay the last
thing
is this
is
is what i think it is
[Music]
would you like to
continue being an amazing gen mate to me
and a
lovely
super cute beloved friend to me
yeah they just get friendzoned
and i just can't
really do it i i didn't know that there
was a possibility of more than just the
friend zone
i i was just thinking because you know
maybe you want to wait until
oh don't run
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'm looking forward to the day when we
meet in in real life hopefully so sad
that that's good
i didn't think my
[Music]
[Laughter]
we should wait until they sell flight
again don't go by ocean we're not ready
to go to japan yet wait
[Music]
wait okay go back yes yes
yes yes
[Laughter]
oh you're flexing on me huh
oh no
doesn't it look super cute
this is so cute you don't wanna eat me
i can be your breakfast
sushi for breakfast i
you complain about me friend zoning you
you don't even want to eat me for
breakfast okay i'm out of here
i can't come here but but nonetheless
i love you yeah
[Applause]
as friends of course as friends oh you
know what it feels so nice to have
someone say that to me thank you
[Music]
i think you also got the pretty um
surprised by that twitter announcement
didn't joke
i booked but i was like
yeah
i was i was doing a stream and then
someone in the chat was like uh
mentioning something about the tweet and
i was like yeah is that person trying to
like um make me
like is that person making something up
and then trying to make me say something
yeah make me leak something that i
shouldn't be leaking
like purposefully making something up
like that
and so i wasn't sure what to say i was
like what the hell are you talking about
and i looked on twitter
because i haven't even seen the tweet
yet at that point but yeah it's quite
surprising i think i was like half a
week and i saw the tweet i was like at
first i thought they were seeing that
the tweet for like id because yeah yeah
it looks like announcement
and then i checked again when i woke up
i was like wait it says it
yeah i had no idea they were gonna do a
tweet like that
well please look forward to it everyone
yeah
um one day um yes please please uh we're
we we will uh
show our beautiful 3d three-dimensional
bodies to you guys
hopefully asap
what's one thing that you want to do
when you become 3d enough i always say
that i want to hatch an egg on stream oh
i want to lie on the floor wow
oh
can i step on you when you lie on the
floor i can give i can try to give you
some kind of massage
uh
you don't want to try that
you can you can
mirror me yeah
[Music]
you probably don't even have to i don't
yeah you don't even have to lie down in
order to see
inside
okay
just kind of look a little bit like this
oh oh yeah
[Laughter]
yeah
but you're the one talking you're like
uh your whole chest is like out there in
your normal outfit
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you ina for showing me your island
are you gonna play more animal crossing
now or
what's up
probably
i'll stream a little bit maybe i'll
stream it again oh
there's so much to do now you gotta
finish harvey's island and in the until
the
capitol
yeah
all right
and i got to show my and my online
viewers how i uh how i've been trying to
improve my island i will continue to
make it look prettier so that i can
er
have such a cool island as inya does
yeah um oh i still got a long way to go
but i look forward to seeing
how how you develop your eyelid
invite me again when you decorate lots
okay i will do that
thank you inya for having me
that's actually it for today guys yeah
no no more
and this is just no wait but wait i
don't want to do one thing maybe uh no
you can stay with me actually yeah
because apparently
or is
i'm assuming that you can't go to
harvey's island with uh
other people right
yeah yeah yeah i want to see your
fortune telling yes i want to try that
out on the stream right now cause i've
been waiting to show it on stream let's
see what my fortune will be
okay give me a moment guys i'm gonna go
to harvey's island
waiting waiting right there i really
wanna make putting
pudding
cleaning
you have pudding oh you mean the items i
gave you
no like actual pudding you have actual
pudding
i want to make it i don't know how to
make it oh i think yeah pudding is
pretty easy
caramel flan some people call it
what what do they call it
caramel flan camel flan
caramel like oh caramel flan
yeah
isn't that what some people call it
never heard anyone call it dad before no
caramel flan
have you ever eaten creme brulee
yes i love creme brulee me too
i had two while i was in paris
it was so yummy have you been oh yeah
you saw pictures of the food yeah
did you send all the pictures of the
food you ate because i only said i've
seen
and i do post uh what i eat there every
once in a while
yeah
you don't do it often enough do you not
eat the things that are worthy of being
i'm gonna post like cup noodles every
day
you gotta eat more instagramable food
no just show me your cup noodles very
[Laughter]
oh yeah it does that uh channel really
only consists of
people eating out and showing us the
pictures of dad and but no one really
shows like self-cooked pictures except
for me i feel like
i don't think a lot of people stuff yeah
no no cooks in all live ian and
management as well i mean i've cooked
some stuff i've shared some stuff with
the members before but i don't think
that often oh
all right so look guys this is
my harvey island this girl i love her
she gave me this new hairstyle
i don't know how many yeah she's the
hairdresser right she's not there every
day but she gives you like one hairstyle
each time she's available on the day
yeah i want i want to see short hair
cure
like like like like this pop cut here
yeah bobcat
well uh in my one year anniversary
stream i did show something like that uh
i don't know if you watched it but uh
hookah papa uh showed me these pictures
um
of like concepts before
my current looks
came to me and i showed it in my one
year anniversary stream uh it was uh
even shorter than bobcat though
oh
it was pretty damn short yeah okay let's
see
who are you katrina
please come to the front if you are
looking for your fortune i am in front
of you girl
okay that's like you're kind of
diagnosed
[Music]
[Laughter]
something about you
i can see it
yeah do you see i can't see it
only i katrina
can see your truth
i will reveal it to you for wondering
no problem i got millions
i can tell you about your luck today
or perhaps you wish to know about your
friendship with another oh
how fitting
oh yeah oh what shall it be then
let's talk about a certain friendship
with the girl behind me
[Laughter]
that'll be good
in my crystal
oh wait is this
with home should i divine your
friendship oh
okay
darn it ah
if one of these would be you who would
would that be
betsy
bitsy really okay okay okay let's say
this is you let's project this
very well
let me consult my crystal about your
friendship with mitzi slash inna mitsina
retina no please close your eyes hi
i can't close my eyes
oh oh
i will not close my eyes assistant
because this is fascinating
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh i see something do you see the
results
as someone who lives with you on the
same island your acquaintance mitzi
knows you well
if you want to be closer with ina
continue speaking to her in the kind way
for which australia is known
okay
[Music]
that was lame
okay but i i guess they tell you like
how
well your yeah how how much how close
you are to each villager
okay well then let me ask you one one
for one more person
what
shall i bless you for ten thousand bells
it's a scam that will probably do
nothing right
please do it please
oh no chiara
oh she will oh wait do you actually get
maybe like a bonus like if you talk to
her once to mitzy once then it counts as
like talking to her twice or so
maybe maybe that at least does something
yeah
yeah okay close my eyes
okay okay
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
your eyes aren't closed no they are
they're totally closed i
[Music]
wow
i've i've seen it all i've seen
everything
that is all i hope that my crystal will
guide you as you strengthen your
friendship with inna
goodbye
and i'll feed us in
thank you
[Music]
that was a lot of fun yeah
there's not much you can do in a cool
lab in animal crossing i feel like but
actually seeing your island and using my
island took uh
up quite enough time so huh i hope you
guys enjoyed it too chad
yes yes thank you for watching
and in german
we say
you remember
it did
did you more read that in the chat so
quickly or
oh of course i know all people said it's
like english it's like i'll feed us in
oh listen
that's why i'm on it dad you remember it
thank you you'll feed us in
all right i will not be making sure
potato broccoli uh
ham
grant grote gratin do you want one too
should i cook for you please all right
please all right i'll see you in my
kitchen then
wear the ring i gave you
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
i'll put the ring on the drumstick okay
what
i'll see you guys
[Music]
do
you