[Music]
oh
come
hi hello
everyone is everything's normal now I
think this the stream is kind of a
little bit have a lagging problem I
didn't know
from let's hope it's better now yeah
okay so this is the first time that I am
uh asking uh some Ian member care Ronnie
Kiara and FAA to join the uh Age of
Empire 2 uh but we also have Ana and
rainy to play again in this
game
y so uh this time this time um we put it
into a team um since me Ana and rainy
already playing this game before so we
put I think it's wisely to put uh two
versus two versus two kind of thing like
like three teams um every team have Ian
and
ID yes International Teams let's go yeah
yeah yeah uh this time I put I put like
a like a game setting with a random map
a normal six player and the location
actually right now is randomly choose
Coastal but I actually have no idea
about it super thank I don't have any
idea about the maps yeah I don't have
any idea about the map
but are you sure it's random Mrs Mauna
who's playing Vikings are you sure that
was not on purpose you playing
Vikings I I put like game modes and
random M and this they put the location
on
Coastal
okay should I should I I should I put
like is fine right it doesn't really
mean that the whole map is covered with
ocean right it's just that there is a
coast
right
random the custom map pool it's like
custom yeah there there you can just
choose like 10 or 15 maps that you want
to be in the pool
oh so you can choose everything that
looks good to you for a big match
okay mostly oh maybe I just choose the
one that have like maybe six with mostly
they choose Arena too Arena and black
forest and the uh in the top uh two top
top two row Black Forest yummy black
forest in yummy Black
Forest oh yummy chries which one again
chocolate uh in the top row there should
be black forest and Arena it's
alphabetic anyway Black
Forest yeah I heard that I never played
it but it's very popular I think for big
matches and then what do you want to
request uh I turn Arena I don't know I
we put
hamburger it
you's
fine it'll be fine oh you so many fine
how bad can it be yeah
it's you
chose no no no no the one that is on
aren and black
forest um which one again Forest but
they're
so o look at that BR mait
Empire oh my God can I sh C map Pool oh
I can oh I Cans are there there's so
many oh wait is it like standard there
where's the big
[Music]
mapish they have like a spe how many
Maps there's a map called Mega random
like is it is there really like a
question mark shaved water on
it Mega random is just super random
interesting
everything going be heavily stylist like
everything is going to be random it's
not always going to be the same M I'm
looking at four people yeah but like the
thing is I can't select see like I I
can't see the six people maps how do I
see the six people I don't know how
mostly there are
four how
mostly how old I mean it's just a map
size
map and these are just map Styles right
there 83 maps in the
game automatically adjusted
look at
this adust
it you went to real world Indonesia oh
my God so much water in Indonesia not
real world not real world much water in
real world so much water in the real
world go back to random too wait random
Black
Forest it's
fine black forest um no no I put it on
random Black Forest Black Forest Arena
and be Empire that's the three random
that I choose oh it t Black Forest here
but I guess when you get to the game
it's going to be randomized yeah I
guess not bad if we go eat cake
right cake is good cake is let them have
cake yum let them have
cake okay um well I think it's time to
start okay guys guys ready boy going to
kick us out good luck good luck everyone
good
luck kill us all have mercy
MAA okay
byebye let's go let's
go
ah kind of excited it's good to have you
honestly got which which we got the
arena we got the
arena okay okay okay
okay
okay H I'm going to
see I'm going to build meal first I
guess here build a
[Music]
house
good I forgot to
build I seriously forgot the hot
Keys it's okay we can just relax
yeah I kind of don't want to talk much
cuz you know I want to focus but you
know that's not how it should work
unfortunately oh don't worry about
that
so
like do you like playing this game well
it yes I kind of like this game it's
like my childhood game
M oh where are you oh you're down there
okay okay okay okay oh so we already we
already got um what is it
called
what is it called oh cool yeah we
already have the the little Gates which
is convenient
[Music]
ahuh okay nice very
nice very very
nice 500 we need
that well since we have the walls it's
already kind of yeah we already have
walls it's it's
nice
[Music]
uhhuh oh you already
walking H all the scouts yeah you
already all the scouts
nice and
then
have okay and then do this have here and
not
yet they got to chop down trees where
are the
trees oh this is wood
okay we'll cut this
down come
on I think if I put in
here house house house house house house
house
house is your YouTube all
right yeah I think so oh dang it my
YouTube is not all
right H oh you already found you already
found where's FAA and
Ana Ana is really close to
mine okay uh right I can probably have
one I
can't more
wood I love how they
talking yeah just
jiberish then
okay uh probably the one that nearest
you probably
um probably rainy or or
k the clus of mine is
Ana okay sweet this come on I need
more put a put it
here I
need
more
at least we still have like some time to
grow and everything
yeah and we only have like 15 minutes to
stay calm after that we need
to oh we only have 7 minutes actually
that's not good at all oh my oh
my oh
my
okay well then don't complain if in the
middle we just like already
dead okay okay nice one's
already build build I'm just going to
put it in
here I have it
here why is so hard to get
a I'm
out why it's so hard to
get I need I need
more need
more go over there and over
there still on the
do it takes
time what you want to do actually
[Music]
no
we should put it in here right
great great
[Music]
great
cour I think I do need
one
for at least for
gold how many resource do you have uh
resources I have like
400 yeah I have't upgraded to the second
the the feudal age what are you guys
doing
kill I'm still struggling with uh
the yeah I'm still struggling with the
food yeah me
too food and
woods okay they're all working
good I need
more
kill kill hurry up
kill what
is this
meil
this do not be
idle I'm just going to put a lot of this
this one is
building keep doing
[Music]
it here actually
don't why I don't know why I put it far
away oh we have 2 minutes two minutes
dang it have you have you even make
a
okay 200 still 500 needed I'm going to
build a bar maybe around
here proba don't need
that
not enough food my
Lord my Lord not enough food never
enough
food uh that was actually a different
game ah I don't know I'm
just you know what kill
him no actually we need everyone
but don't worry we still have uh a wall
a big
wall Ah that's true yeah we still have a
big wall at
least okay
good we can probably build hous
make
another
right
here oh my God what are you guys
doing
what okay now you guys should build
this oh is that
become oh okay
oh that's
why I disclaim my
sheep that is not
good okay my Scout still
exploring what the heck is this
doing oh it's you okay never
mind to close that
oh you already on food oh
nice yay
nice see only uh Oro cron is number one
right
now all right very good I'm
still trying my
best trying okay we're going to we're
going to do great man we're going to do
great
things
Cosell uh let's build a
Barrack hey what are you doing
here what are you doing here
Ana here Scout oh Anya came to inspect
oh I think my Scout is already dead oh
oh my mine's not dead yet no no it's not
dead
yet
yeah
yeah I need I need
faster okay time to build another
houses time to build another
houses right you go build a
stone I mean mining camp wait wa
wait maybe give it a little
let's make a
civilizations okay that's
better getting
better cannot
forget okay go
work
and need more which is
good don't go go build a
house everyone's doing
[Laughter]
good
right I think that's good that's good
enough can build more stuff for
food come on I need a lot of
[Music]
food give me a lot of
food and then may just give me one and
then some of you just doing
that yeah my bed nobody is building CL
cling cling cling cling cling cling cl
cl I need it I need a
l i need a I need need oh we don't have
we don't have a water in here
like I don't know if that's a good idea
or
not
water okay 800
200 oh
sh
[Music]
still mining don't need that
yet make that
faster 300 200 not yet and then finish
that freaking house and then
do that's okay okay good now I can make
wow more
stuff Karan is so
fast it's all good it's all
good good put
defensive someone probably forgot that
they leave these things alone in here
and he
stuck or is he where are he going but
he's going to
die
than that that was so dramatic
[Laughter]
MAA is it life or
death I
mean all right this is good and then
okay the closest one from your
GES
Kiara
I'm still build another
one okay
yeah yeah almost
almost give me more stuff
bro
yeah yeah
y y
y know we're at a pretty good
Pace pretty pretty nice pretty nice
pretty
nice actually actually Cara is pretty
good look at that and look at the FAA
look at
FAA
h i mean you're doing really well what
are you talking about no no no look at
look at FAA
1,600 oh oh the economy yep uh diplomacy
was it
yep I'm literally so chilling right
now literally I think two fuers wait I
thought I
built did I not God damn it okay oh I
didn't buil blacksmith no wonder
[Music]
okay okay two buildings that I have no
choice build
more over
there actually you go over
there she just clean mass
okay 125
what else what else what else what else
what
else all right now that that's done
right 500 bu more
houses do this
matter okay
Castle age good
[Music]
good wow that's
crazy everyone's playing so good
I know right they're all advancing so
quickly yeah yeah so
good you we un
founder just damn
good all right almost done can't keep
zoning out keep pump okay it's FID
H
what
okay
good I don't know why I can I cannot
upgrade this
one H upgrade what it doesn't allow me
to upgrade for some
reason
sweet that
means I have
enough
nice
[Music]
nice they're
all
defensive I have to wait
finally
okay and then
sell very
nice
650 okay
yeah put more people
[Music]
here I'm going to build
Market Nice
okay okay good progress good progress so
far
mon
okay keep building not keep building
keep making
[Music]
soldiers wait no don't do
that y maybe that la
la la la la
[Music]
Rose H Color trade coost
a need more oh my God you
guys
build need
more
stop zoning out my dudes
okay yeah no they're just zoning
out I think I need to make another one I
need that
land all right
okay it to Castle stu okay good got
it and these
ones
there
Castle I build a castle maybe here I'll
build a castle right around
here sure why
not
we need more boots I need more
wots ran out of boots what's this
Monastery univers he Monastery might be
a good idea build
one around
here maybe
here uh to Castle a buildings okay good
good
good who's going to build
this I need more wood I need more
wood w w w
w I need have you made the trade have
you made the
market uh yeah I did nice nice nice nice
nice nice nice nice very good
nice uh maybe
archers
archers is it always been
[Music]
closed monster buil very nice
okay just have two just in case is my
Scout dead my Scout is dead isn't it
nope what are you
[Music]
doing two Castle
age okay okay okay
okay Castle I did build a castle did I
build a castle I didn't build a
castle you want to build a
castle okay come back I do
they're
struggling
nice okay
great oh
boy and then start printing
these
uh
yeah
this
and then they are running out of
resources suddenly forgot
how you forgot what I forgot how to find
the idol it'll
it'll it'll it'll where
it oh God you
guys you guys are jobless can't do that
I Target ital units see
plus I don't
know I don't know if I have
one
faster
faster you can be on
defensive don't know where the relics
are is a
thing
o where is The Relic oh God are you
searching a relic right now yeah I found
one Relic uh was
uh right there go pick that up
light all right okay
sick keep pumping it out
[Music]
buddy and then
you should I start building a Wonder or
no
why you're so
fast you're so fast when I should I
start building a Wonder or should I yeah
yeah yeah you can start building Wonder
because it can help you win yeah okay uh
let's put this
inside I'm still I think I need to build
something who
me all right start building stuff again
800 we need more
gold there you go over
there over
there great okay dude now go
back if you want to start a war tell
me a war y definitely not
[Music]
yet okay and then I think it's about
time I build a a
Siege archery definitely
so intense
bro Cavalry
Cavalry okay I think they shall
move this one instead
uh start selling sell sell sell sell
sell that way we can
upgrade oh yeah should start making
this maybe I should have more people
building The
Wonder go over there
still
chill it is still pretty
chill pretty
chill where the hell is where the hell
is my
monk nobody have any
idea I'm still
searching I don't have any
others go pick that up it's it's like
right in front of you grny so
fast oh over
there wait I forgot I
thought and then Cavalry we need more
food
definitely
food thank
you
you you should build trade cart crony hm
build trade cart and and click on my my
markets it will help you to add gold
kind of thing oh okay uh research trade
card or Caravan buil trade Card wait no
never mind trade card okay and that one
should go to your
Market which is uh which one is the
market
again this
one
okay I need to build more
houses
this yep yep yep oh okay oh okay
probably good
idea
let me know when you want to try doing
War I'll get it ready if I can okay me
too I'm still upgrading
though um maybe I put some
night uh
this wait where did my mon go
again yeah there you are go back
where waiting waiting
waiting why did she build a castle
here what who oh Kiara uh because it
will it will you can you can actually
kill it by with uh
uh you can actually take it down the
castle because the castle can attack
you so be careful oh that's very that's
why she put it
nearby sometime sometime I kill people
with
Castle really you need some seed
weapons
[Music]
oh just just be there Siege
weapons Siege weapon Siege weapon
where's The Siege weapon
again SI
Siege oh that's not
cool
what Siege weapon Siege weapon did I I
thought I built a Siege weapon somewhere
around also need to build one
what Siege Siege Siege did I not build a
Siege I must have not built a Siege okay
up
Siege
I didn't build it never mind
okay
M oh my God are you kidding
me
what oh yeah that's what what it will
do you can just
actually kill it
now
probably oh boy I forgot I'm going to
make make
some I'm so
angry by here
wait oh wait never mind never
[Music]
mind bro oh why did you do
that okay triple sh that's great can uh
you can make
magnol uh yeah make
magnol I'm trying my best
to really bro Cara's
here oh my goodness are you kidding
me what is
it oh okay I'm going to send
my I'm going to send
mine oh God the villagers are mixed up
too that's just
[Music]
great oh
great oh great oh great oh it's
already oh that's just
great
oh that's a lot of
[Music]
damage oh
boy
oh joy that's so
fun oh mine is already
dead sorry I not help much oh my God
why is she like
this oh my God she keeps
coming that's War
[Music]
baby but I miss
something oh
dear my freaking
Wonder oh no
coroni I don't have
enough didn't make enough oh
man
uh actually I can send them
in I should have done that
sooner uh can you close the gate oh how
do I close the gate PHA comes to
[Music]
you no PHA comes to you oh my
goodness
uh stop
working okay let's get them all to your
place
maybe oh boy oh boy they're like
destroying not
[Music]
enough okay I'm going to make this much
as possible and send them over
there
[Music]
okay you guys go over
there you go over
there damn
it damn they're attacking me personally
what I
do
oh it must have been because I was
building the
Wonder um did you know that you can make
a lot of barracks and a lot of actually
Rin uh so they can
actually
what they can build a lot of a lot of um
Barracks seed work so you can actually
um what is
called maybe
oh oh yeah maybe because you build
Wonder yeah this is probably why
whoopsie I think they're destroying the
hell out of my
[Music]
town all right let's see what can I do
what can I do let's
see
yeah close the
gate close the gate yeah it's better
close the gate it's better to close the
gate and rebuild
Y close the
[Music]
gate but like what's the point of
closing the gate if it's like opened up
dang
it
[Music]
make sure it's not
open for now yeah it's
[Music]
open
man I can't really fix the wall because
like she has the castle so like it's
kind of breaking down the wall
regardless why are you going over there
that's going to kill you
buddy oh are you like sending your units
over there yeah I'm trying
okay okay I'll try to send my units
there too
then uh not you oh can you help me with
these war 11 like so
weak oh dear okay you guys go over
there
okay oh man that's
stressful it
is okay and
then
no kill them
first what am I doing
here oh
shoot oh my
God guys keep at it
[Music]
mhm oh my
goodness
oh I am searching my
little
okay Retreat
[Music]
guys I should not have built the
Wonder actually you
should hm actually you should because it
will help you
win I know it's just that it makes you a
Target
yeah which one should I
[Music]
um
uh all right guys build a new
[Music]
life
mind if I
join
okay maybe like build over
[Music]
there I think my base is pretty much
screwed
oh cuz of the castle I can't
really redo
it yeah you cannot redo it yeah I cannot
uh I cannot I can't redeem it I don't
think so I'm going to build a town
center I'm sending some Army to stand by
in your village actually maybe you
should make some
too uh why are your villagers s didn't
do
anything huh you put all your villager
in my place and didn't do anything oh my
God
yeah you know I'll just like re redo it
at your base you don't need to try and
save it I think they're too overpowered
at the moment really yeah I feel like
it and that's one we can just put it you
can you can make uh some some Army in
your
base we can stand by in there so we can
just you know we aiming for Kiara right
now let's let's aing for
K's yeah K is like waiting there
oh I'm searching maybe I can have like
several can I have a few villagers going
over there and try to fix the
wall yeah fix the wall fix the
wall but I think that Knight over there
is going to like kill the villagers is
the
thing
so uh don't forget to research
everything
yeah even though everything's
burning
[Music]
oh
boy I know this is going to work
but oh don't attack
first yeah I'm not going to attack I'm
just going to see if I can rebuild
it
nope they just freaking
died oh can you build a lot of um magnol
with me magnol yeah if I can um
magnel Castle destroyed actually um let
me just build
one uh where should I build oh I need
enough
food
maybe like right around
here wait Town
Center oh my God that's Kiara K's
building over
here oh she's also building over there
oh yeah
oh no wait I don't have any
armies I think I'm going to
build
uh wait I don't even have should I
attack should I I should destroy this
building which one you want to oh my God
she built a freaking
Castle she built a
castle no
no
you know
what um I think I'm going
to maybe I should what the heck is this
okay you know what screw
this so she built a castle between like
uh ours our
castles okay
down Center
here it's a little more peaceful here
who's the red one by the
way help
me I wish I can don't you know what
don't don't put your units there I think
it's kind of pointless cuz I don't think
I can save my castle don't do
it so
what uh I'm going to rebuild my base
you you want to
rebuild
where uh between Ana and your your base
okay cuz uh Ana hasn't really done much
it
seems
okay then I'm going
to
build a
fortif be like
that oh don't be too greedy maybe yeah
don't be too
greedy
oh bro that is so
stressful okay
this fory
wall are you
guys
help just for you
guys no
[Music]
that's okay and send back
here what are you
doing
o
G is really going all out isn't she yeah
she is she really
is
okay
food
okay I need to have more food did
someone we should we should make sure
that there is someone already make
a okay IEM no no no no no no no
no okay and then build a
farm which one should I built theill
need if you have lots of money just
build a
castle Yeah I I'll try
that build a castle castle castle yep I
do I can have
Castle all right and then uh Builder
Builder
gate just just just what again right
here
okay what is the best one
for right guys go over
there
it's up everything
what oh it's okay dude what are you guys
doing
[Music]
run yeah
okay
all right
nice what
where in a back
[Music]
oh why is nobody
building
okay so so so so so so by bye bye
bye hurry hurry
hurry don't have enough woods and gold
again I don't think that I have enough
resources now
Timber
okay let's go over
there
Cavaliers okay and then go over
here oh
okay
okay okay what are you guys
doing
over here and then build a
truchet how many triple shetes do you
need a lot okay a lot I got
you
just I'll build maybe three or how many
do you need uh lot as you
can
as many as you
can and then oh they start to killing
me what I think I think we're going to
be the one who going to
died oh God I'm
sorry no we going to be the one going to
die I cannot even make a cross Bowman
like I'm red out of gold right
now God uh what do you need uh I have
like trle
sh I ran out
of That's So Many
gold I have 307 I can use the
[Music]
treuchet
no
no no
apparently everyone's going after us cuz
thought we were too
good yeah like like I think Ana and FAA
they don't even attack them I don't
know oh man I'm dead that
now can't do
anything okay I'll go over
there if you don't have any
can
just
ouchie ouchie ouchie
ouchie uh let me see
archers
OU yeah I cannot do
[Music]
anything man Auto Easy
lose oh no of
[Music]
true don't go there it's crazy
there are they
attacking I don't know if it's possible
to
run run for your life
apparently it's four against two right
now oh
boy nice
try oh oh no nice
try on like every s
oh my
[Music]
goodness no run run run run run run run
run
ah okay they're
everywhere we just running oh my God we
just running right
now I'm searching I'm
searching she put it
everywhere she put it
everywhere oh she destroyed everything
so l k put castle like in every
place
yeah she really
great yeah she's really
[Music]
good I wonder what happened with fer
Kingdom
though I cannot do
anything
I have a
tret maybe now that they're distracted I
can maybe send someone to
repair I just see
my my town
gone me and
Karan our T
gone
H can I do anything I cannot I cannot I
don't have enough
stuns didn't have enough
St
uh I'm sorry maybe I shouldn't have
built the
Wonder then no no no
no we're we're not we're not having a
really good strer gee I I even like uh
really
really I should have make a villager at
the beginning like lots of
villagers
ah we need to do a redo of this one day
one day we got to do a
redo
no don't don't go there that's
crazy
GG look at Ana she's so chill Anya was
like so
chilly fauna is pretty chill too I think
this is fauna no no dude ana ana and
rain is pretty chill f is Chill yeah oh
I didn't see H there you go there you go
there you go f now you found me
I'm dead
dead oh
no go go attack this maybe no
mercy no mercy in no Merc
see oh
no Castle's
gone everything's
gone wa don't don't don't
don't
stay
here I
do
oh oh who cares about the wood now
[Music]
60 I can't oh
man this team yeah we've been attacked
with by two team
literally oh no that's they've been
attacked by two team
literally oh dear oh
hi
okay I don't know what to do with this
but
[Music]
oh my villagers are dead it
seems
well that's
that
[Music]
well you know I think we did pretty good
yeah we did team yeah we did pretty
great
yeah okay we just I'm just doing a farm
lab going to become a wood
maker
oh
[Music]
well you know
what I'm going to go out with the
bang do you have any other villager left
no I don't that's it
why yeah no it's over I only have like
um a handful of armies and that's about
[Music]
it
okay I don't know where to attack
really so with the monk can I convert a
castle Yeah e no no no you
cannot
maybe I can convert a
villager there's nothing I have nothing
to lose anymore I'm going to go out with
a bang
[Music]
villager
villager can I actually convert one of
your
villagers
what can I actually convert one of your
villagers yes you can you can you can
you can oh
oh I believe again can you come to my
place maybe I should just like spend it
all on a monk
Maybe
maybe they can help me where's
your oh oh oh okay okay hold on I'm
going to open the gate for
now I'm going I'm going here I'm going
here there confir me confir me can you
confir me you going
inside oh no oh yeah yeah okay here
here come
here convert Hey convert me
this convert unlock the
get convert can you convert can you
convert me I did did I did I which one
is the monk there's like too many
people where's the
monks where's the monks oh oh there it
is oh okay
okay can you convert
me oh I can't you
can't
H then how to make it possible though
oh no he's going to die never mind okay
monk don't don't don't
bro you're so smart
bro oh oh I Chang I changed my diplomacy
to normal try to convert me again
oh where are
you uh convert
convert oh sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
oh sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry
stop convert convert
convert convert I can't
convert why keep moving
it so I still can't you still can't
yeah diplomacy change it change it
diplomacy to neutral neutral
okay you can you can you can you
can where you going bro I don't know
it's
just oh okay okay okay okay no we become
a light again we become a light again
okay now now what what should we do uh
you can you can make your your
um rebuild rebuild rebuild the the the
entire
team oh my God no no no wait wait wait
you don't want to do that
diplomacy uh Ally okay okay okay let's
go let's go let's go uh do I go back to
my place oh you can you can just stay
here you can just stay here don't go too
far stay here um make sure make sure
it's still uh far from the this is rain
is still Tre but rain is still there so
you can just make in here literally just
make in here that's fine make make here
yes yes okay what should I make what
should I make um you can try to make uh
maybe first at least the wall first and
then the Town
Center okay Town Center
yeah Town Center Town Center H 275 can I
do
it
275 need to build more
he
inside the castle gate right yeah okay
this this Castle make make another one
make another gate because this is too
small make another gate it's too
small what the heck are you doing go in
there oh you locked the gate can you
open it oh oh
wait wait okay okay okay open it should
be open now
it should be open
now okay
okay
okay okay you make a Town Center there
we so
close
okay it's better we we lean this one I
want to make
another okay we should wall up again yes
yes yes yes
yes uh we shouldn't expand to like where
we were before
probably town center and then just build
uh make a lot of villagers right yes yes
yes yes
okay man
[Music]
uh and also I think better we put we put
our um
anim I know how
kill let's put it in
here I
think I think I'm going to make another
another
wall
round
[Music]
okay maybe I can cooperate with you and
then build a wall together yeah yeah
yeah okay and then have more
villagers donations
than okay and then build build the
wall can you actually build the wall I
don't we can we can we can build it
together maybe maybe like this yeah
okay I'm trying
to make it big by we expand
it like a
SP
oh
man oh I cannot make another
one
H
cell
why how big should we make
it not not that big just close it off
now yeah just close it
off okay okay I I make I make it close
now I make it close
now I I can I can have it cuz I'm still
collecting gold yeah okay that's fine
okay uh okay you're making it close it
now okay I can close out the rest of
it really
yeah oh it's okay I'm I can I can you
can you can try to make a
castle okay can you make a castle nearby
yeah yeah yeah okay oh your villager can
uh your villager can like stand up in
the middle I cannot make a castle in
there you can make a castle in there
please I can delete them yeah you
can
okay okay it's
gone uh I just need uh Stones I need
more
Stones bye
okay see sh in
here
oh oh yeah yeah you're right okay yeah I
moved out of the way okay thank
you 650 I need
okay what oh
okay and then you guys
be is somehow rainy still staying
here she still stay in
there okay oh I got to build a mill uh
build a
mill
uh I don't know if I can build a mill uh
maybe
here can I build it here
oh actually I think you can expand back
to your place I didn't
know no no no no no it's better not uh
maybe it's better
not and I'm going to close that other
one
off oh can you can you close the gap oh
yeah I
am okay I
going thank you thank you uh this one
too I think this one need needs to close
the gap in the back there
and okay oh dang
him right now let's let's focusing on GA
all the
woods because uh and and don't forget to
make a market marketpl a market yeah
yeah yeah so you can sell the woods into
a gold or something to buy things oh I
still have the Marketplace Marketplace
is still intact that's good that's good
that's good where where's your
Marketplace uh it's like far away like
in my
castle oh oh yeah yeah yeah hey ah okay
okay okay
nice
yeah I'm trying to
L build it
bro
[Music]
yeah okay and
then seery
ra I think we also need Why Can't This
thing
move oh my God it's
stuck can you can you help me like I
think my char character stuck next to
like in the
windmill wait
where uh like the windmill that I built
it's uh it's blocked oh sorry sorry
sorry no no no no it was my fault okay
[Music]
uh uh if you have another
um another Stone it would be nice to
double the
wall double the wall okay
I can buy
more yeah I'm still I'm selling
things
why okay
bye uh you have your F
there
yeah okay thank
you two and one in a windmill too as
well
okay build a fortified wall and and this
two
[Laughter]
also okay
okay uh where man a scrim
[Music]
hereare I think um how about this I'm
focusing on economy you're focusing on
the
military okay
oh but you also you also need on economy
it's kind of
hard if you need something oh it's
blocked off I need to build a gate ah I
forgot
ah oh uh it's better to give it all that
that's also F
actually you didn't have G yet you
didn't have you cannot make
it uh can you build a gate I don't have
any I I sent
you I send you Stones uh I'm focusing
economy right now than if you need
something just tell
me thank
you I'm going to donate everything for
you thank
you I I'll also going to see if I
can also send this don't this
W oh thank
you Super Chat thank
you just SP wall on
forward okay I'm building
trebuchets how many just
need
[Music]
we need another what else what else do
you want me to
build I think lots of houses for the
military oh no I don't need that cuz
like I have a lot oh you still have a
lot okay
yeah yeah then makes a lot of military
then uh especially from the
castle where's the other
one are you lyer ing around
bro okay uh
build if you need something just tell me
yeah thank you this s another
wood
um
okay I'm going to research everything
right
now another chapet I have two right
now yeah oh I also think you need to
build
uh this Workshop bars kind of thing for
the armor H for
the
military
uhhuh uh do you have
food oh no if I if I make an army there
she's going to get notified never
mind that's
fine that's
fine you can you can kill this th p uh
rainy t
p well before before you kill the Rainy
St position you can just
um close the gate uh close the the wall
you know the wall that you've uh on your
old village uh-huh yeah close the wall I
I I can't do that because there uh she
has like uh kns
around
where uh like around the castle like she
has like Knights situated there so if I
go build like she's going to kill it and
it's going to get
notified oh I think it's better if you
close this way
like
so
okay and then you build a
gate yeah I was thinking about 30 do you
have more stone or
no let me
see it's okay I can just buy it I bought
it
and there I send wood so you
can oh bless
okay and
then what I need to
make the
houses okay and
then uh where are the others
okay and I'm going to focus on rain just
out r r just going somewhere I'm going
to build a watchtower do you think
that's a good idea or should I just
build a castle uh castle spawn Castle is
better okay uh 650 I need 650
Stone uh and I can't buy it
[\h__\h] okay there you
go give it to
you I can't buy
[Music]
it uh
sell
B okay about you go inside
there and we need this SP
house oh can you um close this Gap
off I'm trying thank you oh she's new
she's new rainy now we
here oh great
get
building
okay I don't know if we can do
it uh which which Rel uh which military
that can
actually I think this
one I no
I don't
know so so so so bye bye
bye the one that can um destroy the the
trees do you know the trees yeah do you
know the the military that can destroy
the trees there's a military that can
destroy the trees but I forgot what it
is
oh
okay um I wonder what else I can build
uh I'm sorry can you can you destroy
this uh this wall so we can actually
this wall this this
gate which wall uh in the middle so you
can you you see that I right now I'm
closing the gate at the wall and there
is a in the middle that have a
Gates like an open
space I don't know where where where
should
is this the one that you you can see
that uh you were right now uh farming
the
berries wall the berries uh yeah what
about it you can you can destroy that um
so we can build a castle in
there oh
okay uh destroy this thing Al together
yeah
okay I'm going to okay destroy these I
think right like that right is someone
coming oh yeah yeah yeah no no no yeah
yeah yeah that's it that's it that's it
that's it that's
it
uh okay
trust
me
and so
done K's done yeah ki's done Kara dead
been killed by fa I
guess wait if that's the case I can
restore my castle yes you
can but I guess be careful because uh
her villager is still there um f is
still around K us
please my Ry is
lurking never
mind
okay uh can you build it never mind I
can probably get build a
gate uh build a
gate
oh I canot make a castle can you make
castle around here yeah yeah yeah yeah
uh I'll S I will send you
these I will send you this okay thank
you and uh where's my
by the
berries theyby the
berries not the
time B man bik
man uh Castle 650 I need 650 of
it
okay well that's gone God damn
it Castle 650 oh do you have 650 wood I
mean uh Stone uh I just need 100 more uh
or well
200 oh I don't have it uh I can just
send you
this
just just sell it oh God I can't sell it
oh you cannot sell it cuz yeah cuz she
destroyed my okay then send it to me and
I will I will buy
it uh send send what again sorry I'm go
toy and send Stone uh send uh the woods
to me and I will buy
the
stone or you can also build Market uh in
the empty place in the back okay
uh how do I like send the the thing to
you
diplomacy diplomacy okay uh diplomacy
and then how do I send it you need a
market to pay tribute oh no I don't have
a
market yeah just send it shoot
oh okay then then make then make uh the
the market then yeah okay Mark
it there's subject is making more
K oh no they're coming they're coming
they're coming they're coming they're
coming they're coming they're coming
they're coming they're
coming defensive be on the defensive
don't get out can you can you I can lock
the gate no what are you doing it's okay
we just we just kill it we just kill it
okay
uh you're I am your T
butet oh no no no no no no don't close
the gate it's
fine it's no use to close the gate it's
no use to close the gate just kill it
[Music]
okay no not you guys it's elephant's
palom uh you're your your Castle fixing
your Castle fix your Castle yeah I don't
know why they're not
building oh my
God we're trying our best that's fine
that's fine that's
fine why are they okay oh no no no no no
no no no no
no wood wood wood wood wood wood
wood
oh oh God it's over oh
god oh gods
okay it's so over it's over I don't have
anymore
yeah no Archer no
catapult
nothing we
just well at least at least we're
just at least we're
standing yeah at least we survived this
far that's pretty impressive we
surv hey at least we weren't last yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah oh
God you know what this was
good we should probably
resign yeah that's fine it's
fine you don't want to resign
huh you don't want to
resign how oh you can just like go to
the main menu and
resign what
where just go to the main menu it's on
the upper
right oh yeah yeah
yeah but we will lose the score just let
them be just let him kill us okay okay
we will lose the
score
damn this this water elephant is
crazy oh my
God
man
just do what we can I didn't know I
don't know what we
can bro
yeah apparently we don't lose the score
yeah we should reside the Great Wall is
gone we did good
yeah
[Applause]
ah H how come you're not you're not
going strike out already crony I oh you
said don't
resign
oh can I resign I don't know can
we okay let's let's let's resign let's
resign
wait oh yeah this
one
resign
where oh
wait
[Laughter]
okay oh man that was cool that was cool
that was cool that was
cool that was
nice DN
gg gg damn your military economy oh my
God PHA is really
great yeah she was building she was
building building yeah building fona is
too strong the mother of
n too strong that was really
nice nice I enjoy that yeah that was fun
scared with at first like k put Castle
everywhere I forgot Castle yo I was
minding my own business and was like yo
yo yo yo Raina can you send some help
I'm going to attack Cronin I'm like what
dude I was minding my own business and
then I was minding my own business too
like everyone was minding their own
business damn Kiara was out for blind
yeah I mean I was just trying to get the
game the all
rolling I guess so yeah before someone
rolls it on me yeah I guess otherwise
you know people would be just like back
build like me like
me well me and Ana I feel like we're
playing like a farming
simulator me that was me that was me
before Kiara was like yo help me out I'm
like huh what oh yeah actually the
reason I attacked crony was because she
was building the wand and I you know
when you build a wonder you're a target
for
everybody well she building the wonder
she was building a Wonder yeah and that
gives you automatic win if you keep it
for a very long time and as we see this
game was going to go on for a long time
so the Wonder could have won yeah that
would have been a good Strat F was about
to attack but then I was like if they're
fighting each other then let them
be I just did elephant strategy just
build a million elephants and hope for
the
best wait can we see the I think MAA has
to maybe somebody has to press something
so we can see the the the stats or
something oh yeah the stats already here
um oh sorry I don't understand is it
quit current game yeah the one do you
click turn to map there we go nice nice
nice nice nice wait where do you see it
oh my Society hi
Society are living in this iety I
clicked return to kills a
lot but
Ki a
[Music]
lot yeah my
God interesting cool cool cool a very
nice oh when it's it's come back to
economy I sent a lot to
crony oh you were
trading
trading I had 11 castles it was good it
was
good bra yay nice oh
no very cool o our numbers are actually
not bad yeah nice food collected
yummy wood collected nice very cool it's
very nice very nice if you look at
timeline you see like the graph of how
things are changing
ooh look at
that oh my god wow F just like going up
and the tables are turning elant all
about the
elephants
yeah let me see I want to see not
attacking first was a good strategy
though cuz like we could
Focus yeah we just chilling at the
start I was like if if they're fighting
each other than let them
be yeah I mean why not that's probably
what you should do yeah but sometimes
the intrusive thoughts is true them
true the intrusive thoughts yeah I
understand my chat people say like
nobody stands in that
way what whatever we do n Alis
win oh well normally I would have liked
to play defensive too but I don't know I
had to kill the Wonder and then from the
Wonder everything was just like rolling
and I it just happened I feel like
aggression is good it adds the spice you
know I think I underestimated you guys
honestly I thought maybe
you guys didn't practice enough so maybe
you guys wouldn't know what is Wonder
out
yo well IED a couple guys how do I build
the
Barrack when it was constantly asking
yeah I don't remember almost a single
how do I do this how do I do that why
are people
unemployed if if I want to ask for
rematch again would you want want to do
it but not now
yeah but rematch another time will be
nice yeah maybe this time it's uh we we
make it pretty pretty easy because we
have a cheating seat in in our live chat
but the next time how about no cheating
[\h__\h] on the live
chat no
yeah sure if you can really control that
we could we could randomize the sifts so
that everybody gets something unexpected
from it's not months from now cuz by
then I'll I forget about the
game was it just the date immediately
before we forgot how to play again yeah
what I'm saying what I'm saying
mhm maybe after this I will put another
date so but this this seems fun like
like I I'm pretty pretty I think I
underestimate a lot of you guys yeah oh
my God that is crazy to play again I was
scared of you MAA I was so scared of you
I I told you I'm not really good at this
game you didn't believe me just because
I played this game doesn't mean that I'm
good at it even the said is good you
good it's just that you trying to save
me and I'm
sorry I think everyone need a practice
them after
all
no but yeah thank you so much everyone
for playing this game with me uh it's
been fth it's been like organizing thank
you I'm glad it happened
finally it was super fun thank you thank
you it's been we almost doing this like
for like 2 hours actually yeah wow I
know it flew by just like as I expected
the game is going to be 2
hours perfect perfect timing yeah well
um for this one actually I have a lot of
uh strategy game
um uh Age of Empire is like one of them
while the others uh there is another
game called Starcraft if you guys
interested on Starcraft it's another
building game another starting game if
you guys interested I would love to make
another one I'll try it yeah I'd love to
but I need to learn about the game yeah
I need to learn to yeah yeah yeah more
more learning more learning let's
go my brain is going to
explode but it is what it is than you so
much um I think we need to end theam if
you guys have any uh maybe information
for the
viewers I don't know I'm good oh no no I
just want to say thank you thank you way
for being a great
teammate thank you k for bringing out
the aggressor in
me for being a really good to like we
actually working good together yeah next
time I won't build the
Wonder I should not have underestimated
you need to build a wonder you just have
to figure out when you're building the
Wonder is your military already
finished also W you building it like at
least when I arrived you only had one
person working on the Wonder but the
Wonder takes like so much more time than
other buildings you need to build with
like 20 people at once yeah you need you
need a lot of people
and make sure that uh your military is
ready to you
know take
War the Wonder I wanted to build one too
someday someday someday
somay well that's all everyone thank you
so much I'm going to end sh there thank
[Music]
you thank you so much for playing this
game Let's Play Again h hopefully byebye
really thank you awesome bye bye
membership
later
[Music]
bye-bye