​​​ ​Usada​ ​​
​​ ​Constructions​ ​​
​​​ ​Usada Constructions' growth​ ​​
​​ ​has been spektacular.​ ​​
​​​ ​The other companies​ ​​
​​ ​feel so tiny now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Pek, pek, pek.​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​CEO, we're under attack!​ ​​
​​​ ​Randos from some rando nation​ ​​
​​ ​are attacking us!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on!​ ​​
​​​ ​Stop these slap attacks,​ ​​
​​ ​or your country will be gone in no time!​ ​​
​​​ ​Crap!​ ​​
​​​ ​So this earthquake is their doing!​ ​​
​​​ ​Capture them and​ ​​
​​ ​throw them in prison!​ ​​
​​​ ​Roger Rabbit that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Donezo!​ ​​
​​​ ​That pose is peking me off.​ ​​
​​​ ​Eek!​ ​​
​​​ ​What is it?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't contain the Ment*s C*ke!​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't do that indoors!​ ​​
​​​ ​Help, CEO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Graaargh!​ ​​
​​​ ​It stopped...​ ​​
​​​ ​Donezo!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're changing jobs?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't take this anymore!​ ​​
​​ ​I'm out!​ ​​
​​​ ​She fled!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not letting an employee leave.​ ​​
​​​ ​Never!​ ​​
​​​ ​I captured her.​ ​​
​​​ ​Eek...​ ​​
​​​ ​Pek, pek, pek!​ ​​
​​​ ​You shall see how grave a sin​ ​​
​​ ​it is to turn on Usada Constructions.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do it!​ ​​
​​​ ​OK!​ ​​
​​​ ​There!​ ​​
​​​ ​Not to me!​ ​​
​​​ ​...?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Eek!​ ​​
​​​ ​...​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara turned traitor!​ ​​
​​​ ​That much is obvious!​ ​​
​​​ ​The role of CEO is mine!​ ​​
​​​ ​CEO! Make a run for it​ ​​
​​ ​while I keep her occupied!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please do!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, she got past me.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're useless!​ ​​
​​​ ​*pant* *pant*​ ​​
​​​ ​Hah hah hah, you can run,​ ​​
​​ ​but you can't hide.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ugh...​ ​​
​​​ ​I got you now, former CEO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Die!​ ​​
​​​ ​I got her, former CEO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Take this! This is the strength​ ​​
​​ ​of Usada Constructions' bonds!​ ​​
​​​ ​HAHAHAHAHA!​ ​​
​​​ ​AHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!​ ​​
​​​ ​Got to love a fun working environment!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!​ ​​