[Music]
spe
[Applause]
[Music]
for
[Laughter]
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
to
for
[Music]
[Applause]
ch
[Music]
to
[Applause]
[Music]
for
spe
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
for
be
[Music]
King oh this is so
weird this is so weird and Belle oh yeah
right I didn't do an AM video on my
break I kind of wanted
to and then I couldn't think of anything
before I went on my break and I didn't
do
it Kitty Sashi boy this is so weird this
is so weird isn't it so weird I don't
know maybe it's weirder for me than it
is for you because it was quite
the quite the how to say
extreme change of Lifestyle yeah so
first of all disclaimer you may have
noticed um Quality is lower than usual
but I mean I hope it's fine right now I
hope it's not buffering that's all I
really want um tell me if it's looking
okay uh we had to make
some uh what's the word we had to make
some compromises because of shitty
internet right
now um not my fault it will it will
hopefully be
resolved in the next coming
days but okay looking good looking good
then all is good but I also for that
purpose I don't know I just uh I thought
it's less of a strain on the internet if
I have uh the the the bigger latency
thing going
on or at least like less of a stream
less of a strain on like the stream like
you know blah blah blah so I have the
bigger latency so but your comments
they're not even coming that slow I mean
compared to my memb only stress test
that I did that is now privated um don't
worry you didn't really miss anything I
was just testing the internet but well
we had 10 minutes delay
[Laughter]
there something like that oh my God
thank you guys for the super chats and
the
memberships man did you guys leave my
membership H I hope you
didn't ah I miss you guys I miss you
it's so weird it was so weird to not
stream it was so weird to not like talk
to you guys every
day and I was I got to say do you hear
the bgm a little bit at least before
I make the big mistake of not having bgm
on uh never
no is that about the
membership thank
you thank you I C from your internet
addiction partially I mean it will
probably come back
but partially I would say yeah um yeah
you he bgm okay you guys if you answer
to me during the stream you always got
to like if you say yes or no whatever
you always have to like add context
please like yes PGM yes so because
otherwise I will forget within 5 Seconds
what we were talking
about ah so so for this particular
stream this is uh just to get some
chitchat out of the way before we go
into the K we have a k right after that
I kind of want to lead into um I don't
have like anything special prepared uh
besides like talking a little bit
catching up a little bit um I I I okay
so oh my God I'm going to be so all over
the place first of all uh how you doing
uh I'm doing fine hope you guys are
doing
well and second of all what was I going
to
say [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I shouldn't have asked you
how you guys are I
forgot [\h__\h] let's start from the very
beginning a very nice place to start I
was on a
break um
for how much was it in the end like
three it was maybe a bit more than 3
weeks uh see it's good that I didn't
give you a comeback date because it
would have been delayed my original plan
was to come back on the
weekend um but then yeah internet [\h__\h]
me over so yeah that's how it
is and are you're doing well okay good
to know 82 years no it's not been that
long but this break was after three and
a half years thank you for super chats 3
and a half years after 3 and a half
years it was the first time that I took
a break where I would not
work and would
not
use kiaha Twitter and YouTube and okay I
used kiaha YouTube because I have like
what is it YouTube uh like the
subscription that gives you no
ads I used it for that purpose but I
didn't watch like I tried to stay away
as much as I could from like clips and
any like vtuber content at times it was
hard to um completely uh ignore what the
[\h__\h] is going on around me uh but I
mostly stayed away from it and um yeah
so
the the the premise for it the purpose
was not to get off of the internet
completely for me my purpose was to get
away from
work that was my biggest challenge
because like in three and a half
years I did not um have like a single
day where I wouldn't work like even if I
wasn't streaming there's work and uh you
know like a lot of things behind the
scenes
always like sponsorship things to like
plan and answer and like prepare
sometimes they want videos sometimes
they want voice messages and then you
have voice packs to record behind the
scenes and music stuff to record behind
the scenes and service to fill out
behind sometimes we have surveys
yeah uh and meetings and this and that
um there's like so much stuff and I
managed
to
99% not do work because I I did
everything even the deadlines that are
far far F further ahead I did all of
that before I went on my break so that
everybody would leave me alone which
meant I had a little bit of a workload
before leaving like I took also like
after the last stream I took a day uh
like you know you remember I was still
kind of a Twitter but I was just like
doing work getting [\h__\h] done so that I
could leave be left alone yeah there was
one the one% is because the on one day
um I I I did um kind of do some kind of
work but it's not really like it didn't
take effort I was just like yeah just
like
supervising and that was pretty much it
so I didn't really have to do
anything yeah but besides that I I could
stay away from everything I just had to
check one thing and that's it
yeah and that was amazing like the first
one two three days it felt
wrong and it I I I wanted to check
Discord so badly cuz it's like in my
routine I wake up I checked Discord and
then I check it several times millions
millions of times throughout the day cuz
there's always
notifications one two one two
three um yeah uh what was I going to say
oh yeah so the first few days were a bit
hard to not check Discord and not check
anything else
um yeah
uh then I deleted this ORD from my phone
not not even deinstalled I just deleted
the icon and it was that easy to keep me
from going on Discord Hallelujah it was
that easy I was really curious though
like sometimes what was going on and I
was greeted by a lot of notifications
when I came
back but they're all cleared now I have
zero
notifications yeah and then uh I did
kind of like see
the the first day where I was like not
like on my break the first day I was on
my
[Music]
break is kind of when I think the pal
World server was like about to be opened
or so but not open yet I think it opened
maybe one or two days
later and I still kind of had like this
big urge to play Power
so I I thought okay they're going to
open a server so I'm not going to play
too much on my own because it's just a
waste of time if I'm going to start all
over again so I thought okay I'll just
play a little bit just a little bit cuz
I kind of had this urge and I had like
not much to do when I'm not working so I
I played power like probably for like 7
hours or
so I explored so much and I I don't know
I played so much in a day and then I was
like yeah at the end of that session I
was
like [\h__\h] I felt
so bad I don't know I felt like I did
something wrong like I should have I
shouldn't
have spent so much time playing a game
on my break is what I thought but then
that stance completely changed later on
you'll understand
eventually um but yeah I got I I I I
just wanted to play some more power and
then after that I didn't touch it
anymore after that I managed to not
touch it anymore cuz I didn't want to go
to my PC anyway I wanted to avoid using
my PC as much as
possible and
then concerning pal world you may have
noticed it's not on my
schedule because I feel
like I missed it they're still playing
it I saw but I feel like I missed you
know everybody's like far
ahead and I missed like the entry point
you know and now I feel like
isolated and it's I don't know I'm I'm
not even interested anymore anyway like
I kind of thank God like I I didn't play
it anymore so then I lost interest
anyway I could probably get back into it
and I honestly I asked Ena cuz I saw she
only did one pal word stream so I
thought okay okay maybe if I if I catch
up a little bit I might be on her like
level uh and so I asked her if she wants
to play together but Ena didn't have
time so I was like okay whatever I'm not
going to put pal World in my schedule
[\h__\h] it we don't need it we don't need
it I mean yeah no nobody waited for me
so whatever I don't care it's surely
surely the hype is going to die and
people going to stop playing it soon
right
right what do you think guys do you
think the the
hype will
continue for a long time should I get
into
it wait wait wait wait wait everyone got
left behind once Kyla and people got
serious really I'm not behind at
all I mean the game is still early
access the game is not even closer then
Call's waiting for you what do you mean
Kell's waiting for
me nah not particularly for me right
good good not
far maybe I'll try to catch up and then
ask GAA for a session because GDA is
back that's one thing I noticed while I
was gone because I was using my kiaha
YouTube account to watch videos without
interruptions of ads and then I see I
see GAA in my subscription box several
times
wooo nice call did say that give me a
clip give me a
clip I need to see that
then but did they like I remember before
I left right before I left they started
a discussion about starting the Ian
server internally or like starting a
server for every
every uh branch and then uh I I also
asked beforehand like before they even
said that I was like hey can we have a
server together with Ian and ID and then
I said um we're making a server for each
branch separately and then I just saw
right before I left I saw like like a
lot of members being like um please can
you uh merge us with Ian and ID we want
to have it with ID because otherwise
guys were not so many members BL BL blue
but then from what I've seen is they
ended up uh having separate servers or
they made one they made separate ones
first and then later on had a merged one
but then people just ended up using the
separate ones because that's what came
out first is that how I how I is that
correct Kyla plays an server KY plays on
all
three right now everyone is playing cat
up ah how is that possible people
avoided it for a week or so because of
an update issue raising people's what
but I saw people already kind of ahead
like I saw Clips in my in in my um
suggestions that like I don't know I saw
like Palm mon pal pal Pals oh yeah Pals
I said I said something else uh that
I've never seen before even though I
really um binged the game
oh that that sexy one for
example KY doesn't have permission
for yeah I mean we have an agreement
between Ian ID uh it's funny to me that
they wouldn't let her into Japanese
server but the Japanese members really
on their own are a lot of members so I
think it makes sense because once you
let Kyla
in maybe others will also be like hey I
want to go in too and and then they're
already
full yeah
lavander I saw like a an an a really
good Korean artist draw a human version
of that on Instagram and it's so sexy so
good
looking so good um but yeah I even on
that one day where I was playing pal
world I saw one
shiny and then I'm sure that everybody
has experienced this playing power world
but my
Pokemon [\h__\h]
H My Pal I'm so sorry my pal kills the
shiny [\h__\h] why is the what is why why
does this
happen
What
I think I think the shiny was in a
dungeon I was in a dungeon or like you
know one of those caves and then yeah
the pal attacks it and it's too late
it's [\h__\h] dead but it wasn't really a
special pal anyway
whatever slip of the tongue yeah I'm so
sorry uh
well yeah
cie shiny killed
itself what but before she captured it
how is that
possible did you ever realize you missed
a shiny in your power stream too no I
did what about the shinies and power
aren't really special right they're just
sparkling and I mean mine was kind of
big I don't know if they're always
bigger but I don't know that was kind of
like they don't have a different color
so that's lame I don't know I don't
really care that much for shinies in the
other game
either oh self-destruct move ah oh yeah
right there's this one pal that invades
your base in groups and then explodes
right those really pissed me
off yeah but oh well okay so I right I'm
I'm correct right with the knowledge
that I can't use my the one World
character and everything that I used in
my private playthrough to play on a
server right I can't like bring her onto
it
right oh oh they have a buff they get
15% damage in work okay H oh that's good
that's good that's actually something
the other shinies in another world don't
get they just look different okay that's
pretty cool then to yeah
to
the chip mods no one didn't see yeah the
[\h__\h] suicide parrots
[\h__\h] yeah okay wait there what yeah they
server specific okay are you going to
play power of cobal no why does she not
play
yet but I don't know I don't really know
like starting together does that even
make sense should I not just start on my
own and then see haha but like normally
like for me it's not even a big deal if
I don't play power world because even if
I play Power it's going to be like with
Minecraft I'll be pretty much on my own
unless I ask someone to log
in if I play a little bit earlier than
usual I could meet
ID but I guess then only Kyla cuz you
guys are telling me only Kyla is in the
Ian
[Music]
server
use the to keep be care can
I I think I saw GAA using a mod so I
guess we can use
mods yeah a time slot it's just it
doesn't match whatever okay uh moving on
just talked enough about pal world so I
only played it for one day for like the
first day I was like like I don't know I
couldn't stream right but like playing
pord for seven hours while the hype in
my heart was still big
felt
right and
um I guess it kind of like cleared my
urge of
streaming H and distracted
me and then and then you might wonder
what did the Wawa do all this time there
was one thing that occupied my time that
that okay it occupied most of my time
but I can't talk about
it but it's like private life thing and
it was occupying my time a lot um and
then the other thing like pretty soon
after my break
started because I was kind of like
feeling a lot of pain in my body and I
just kind of wanted to extend my
vacation from the mold Lees I went to
a B
hotel in my
country
nearby uh like not too far away so I
didn't wouldn't have to travel too
far I went to a spa
hotel and I went alone and I was kind of
like feeling a little
bit nervous about going alone and like
awkward but turns out that hotel was
generally so freaking
empty that um like during the day I
would barely see
anyone uh so I didn't feel so awkward
but then I noticed at dinner I got like
kind of Bamboozled and gaslighted
because I I arrived like at like
check-in time like 300 p.m. it was quite
a journey to get there uh I mean I said
it wasn't far but I still had to take
like train and a a weird
bus that took quite a while and I arrive
and I check in and everything's cool and
I see my room the room is amazing really
big room with you know you know those
rooms that have like a like you know
there's like a big for hotel rooms
usually the living room is the bedroom
right right but this room had like a
divider
wall where the TV was attached on both
sides so one uh TV was facing the sofa
and one was facing the bed can you
imagine and this kind of wall it had
like uh like like I don't know like
lever cushioning on the wall it looked
it looked really nice like a fancy hotel
room you
know and the bathroom was [\h__\h] huge
like as big is the the sleeping
area crazy yeah so two TVs right but
they were like locked into the wall
and I I brought my switch cuz I thought
I might be kind of bored I brought my
switch and I brought a book oh yeah
right the book oh I brought my switch
and I brought my book for like you know
wasting time killing time and I wanted
to attach my switch but I couldn't
because I couldn't reach it and I
couldn't move the yeah yeah yeah you
guys are
shocked I couldn't move
the the thing so that I could reach the
HDMI slot so I called the reception or I
I talked to them and I told them to send
me a technician please to help me and
then one technician came and asked me
like what what I need to attach and I
said M my
switch and I felt kind of
embarrassed because I mean I don't think
anybody else brings a switch to this
[\h__\h] Resort
Hotel and and he found it was funny and
then he asked me what I was playing out
of curiosity cuz he told me his wife is
like currently really addicted to uh the
nudes Zelda game and I'm like oh which
one I also played like the newest one
like completely for and then he said oh
no the the other one I think I think he
said yeah breath of the wild
currently I think
[Music]
uh and and yeah so we were like chatting
about gaming and then I didn't feel so
embarrassed
anymore and he attached it for me and
told me to like just tell him again when
I'm leaving so he can
yeah get rid of it because uh he also
said like it might not be allowed to
attach like stuff like that to the hotel
[Music]
TV oh oh joar I hope you I hope you feel
even better
soon yeah and then I played I I tried to
play but the TV was relatively small and
the wall where the TV was hooked on was
relatively far so I was like I was like
what the [\h__\h] I can't read what the
dialoges say on my
game it's hard to play um but I played a
little bit here and there and then I
tried like on the pool side there was
like an indoor and an outdoor pool but
they were connected and they were heated
to uh like the whole year and so I did a
swims swim SW and there were like
several saas and a steam room and a
infrared cabin like with like lounge
chairs or like massage chairs and and so
I would like take my book and read it on
the pool sign and read it uh in the
infrared room which made me think uh
like it made me look up out of curiosity
like is this good for me how good is it
for me and then I came to the conclusion
I want to buy an infra red
lamp yeah because seems like it's good
for for like my problems too but I
wouldn't
even assume that it would solve my
problems but I kind of want to get it
because you can like turn on the light
and then lie on the sofa and then just
have it on for like I don't know 20
minutes or
so uh direct it towards your back or
whatever and then yeah M mhm so I might
buy
that steam room steam room the steam
room did not have uh PC
no thank God steam room you know I I I
was always like really really
embarrassed to go to saunas because just
like with onset I don't like seeing
people I don't like people seeing me
naked and I don't like me people seeing
what me seeing people naked because I
mean I don't like like being confronted
with their body and like not knowing
where to look and I don't want to seem
like too embarrassed and and like
purposefully so stup stiffly looking
away I want to be I want to make the
impression that I don't care at all that
you just walked in the room naked where
I might also be naked so I I secretly
had my swimsuit on under my towel and
then I would just like to not be judged
I I would just keep the towel over like
those body parts so that no one would
know that I'm not naked
underneath spinger
nakedness I wanted people to think that
I'm in proper sauna attire AKA naked but
I also just wanted to like play it safe
and not be naked and I I don't know also
it's like I feel like it's kind of more
hygienic anyway to have like bottoms on
when you sit on that stone or that wood
where naked people are sitting on and
sweating
and uh so I did that and then I
noticed that like within like staying in
the sauna going in and out for hours I
only met like one lady and they were
like so many different so like even if
somebody walks into my steam room which
[Music]
happens and there's like this thing that
happens when you're in a steam room it's
so steamy okay steam room is basically
like a sauna that's just really really
[\h__\h] humid it has less higher
temperature but it's so it's made to be
so humid that it feels extremely hot and
it's like it gets a bit hard to breathe
but it's nice I kind of like it cuz like
usually they have like some kind of
herbs or so so that when you breathe in
and it's already like you know when you
breathe in it's like in a steam room
it's good for your throat and your nose
and all that but when they have like
herbs in the air then it's like even
better
so break if
true steam room steam yeah so so so I
I'm sitting in my steam room minding my
own business and there's no one else
like I I checked all the rooms and
decided where to go and in none none of
this like saunas and all that I saw
anybody so I was like okay great this
place I have it all for my own there was
no one in the pool either so I sit down
and I wait a bit and then and somebody
actually joins thank God it wasn't the
guy I wish sonas were at least like on
sense separated in gender Fork but okay
an older lady came in and she was like
really excited she came in super naked
she didn't even cover herself with uh a
towel walking in because she hung it up
uh in front of it there was like a
hanger and I didn't even notice that and
then later on I learned how to be a
proper Sona person but for that moment I
was like okay [\h__\h] I did something wrong
and she comes in completely naked this
old somewhat older lady like maybe 45 50
or so and because it was so
steamy and she like greets me I she
walks by me and I try to like squint and
I try really hard to look at
her because that's just what my brain
automatically thought I should be doing
because it's hard to see in the steam
room thank [\h__\h] God I tried even
harder to see because it was so hard to
see I tried harder to see you know what
I mean but I don't really think she was
bothered by it or even noticed cuz it
was just for a moment and then she sat
down across more or less across me and
she was like so excited and she like
talked to me about how empty this place
is and and uh like yeah if I if I like
you know been here longer if I'm here a
lot
and I told her no I just checked in but
yeah it's [\h__\h] empty man amazing but
then and then like we talk a little bit
excitedly and then it gets [\h__\h]
awkward so this is also why I don't want
to
be like this so bad like especially if
you don't even start talking if you
don't talk at all I feel like it's even
more awkward but like we talked a little
bit and then we stopped talking and then
we're just like both like in
there and I'm just like staring and like
thinking to myself uh uh I want to leave
when should I leave I don't want to
leave right away and go to a different
room because I don't want her to think
that I'm bothered by here by her
presence in here but I I I also don't
want to seem like a [\h__\h] like I can't
stand it too long being in the steam
room but I've already been here a little
while longer before her how can she know
for how long I've been in here you know
I've been having all these thoughts like
I should how much longer should I stay
before I leave now that she has entered
the
room oh man and then just the fact that
we were able to talk in the beginning
but then kind of stopped talking made it
super awkward
too yeah just taking the relaxation yeah
I don't know I tried in the beginning it
was a bit difficult because I was just
getting used to the saas um but over the
years of going to Spa hotels more and
more I've been like vibing more with
saas and enjoying it more and going
there more um but yeah I got a
overthinking Champion I got a
um yeah I don't know I I shouldn't be so
concerned with what people think and
this and that but yeah in the end I left
after like I tried really hard like four
minutes or so after she joined I think
maybe I left cuz it actually did get
hard to breathe and all that after a
while in the steam room I don't know if
you if you guys have been in one but it
gets kind of
rough
and then and then I left and I took a
shower and then yeah throughout the day
I would go into different saas they had
like a we call it a bio SAA bio
SAA which uh is like I guess it's like
an organic sauna which just means that
it's not as hot as the finished sauna
but don't worry I also went into the
finished sauna for a while M the organic
one organic is like I think 30 less
so I can stay in there longer and
chill it's quite nice
mhm and the finished one uh yeah I took
it upon myself to be in there for a
while and so throughout the whole day oh
yeah here's the thing that I wanted to
tell you so I got gas lit I thought
there was like no one in this
hotel and then there was like there's it
was all inclusive uh free meals and so I
went for lunch a late lunch
uh
and then again I was the only one there
there was like a little buffet with not
much
choice but uh yeah I ate a little bit
and I thought okay no one's here for
real for real and then I come for
dinner and the whole place is packed I
think there were a 100 people maybe okay
it felt like 100 maybe it was less turns
out this hotel is not just uh a spa
hotel but it's also like a seminar Hotel
like a lot of uh companies go there for
seminars and stay
over so then I felt awkward cuz I'm
walking in like kind of late for dinner
cuz it was like come whenever and all
these people are like really loud and
and they're all like looking so adult
and mature and they're drinking alcohol
and they're already done with their din
anyway and they're just like loud and
talking and hahaa and then I'm like I'm
all alone and I just came from the sauna
again and I look like a
mess yeah I felt awkward then that I was
alone cuz I literally was the only alone
one there were I saw during dinner I saw
like two more pairs of people that were
not from a seminar because we were put
in a different like um neighboring
room uh yeah but then the next day they
were gone I was the only
one yeah I was like pretty alone only
for dinner I noticed how many people
were there oh and for breakfast too I
guess yeah yeah but it's okay whatever
whatever I had a lot of like private
time during the um day and then I you
guys were curious about a book so I
tried my best to finish it and I could
have finished it but I stopped I gave it
so many chances I went I think I was 60%
maybe even 70% through the book and let
me tell you after 20% I already wanted
to stop reading and burn this book
because it was kind of um I only bought
it cuz the title and the cover was cute
and quirky um but it was like it's not
like a story book it was like uh a lady
I don't want to give the title because
then I don't want to directly bash the
offer and the book you know but it was
basically a lady
um uh who documented her
H if I give too much info then you guys
might be able to find it it's a lady who
documented her sessions with her uh
therapist just and I just I don't know I
thought she was like whiny as
[\h__\h] and it pissed me off I was like
giving her so many
chances
but it's Sheed me so much she annoyed me
so much and I I thought I thought maybe
it could even help me cuz there's a
therapist involved and they're talking
they're talking about problems I thought
maybe it could even help me ah that one
you know what I mean oh [\h__\h]
no I was actually right oh oh no that's
not is what 50 Shades is that also
someone writing their therapy sessions
no I don't I don't I didn't even I
didn't even know that no it's not that
book what the [\h__\h] no it's a real person
writing their real therapy dialogues
down and then reflecting on each session
and and her um improvements and all
that is that what 50 Shades is
about a book with a therapist is not a
substance but I thought it would might
be like you know maybe I get a little
bit of advice from it at least
but
uh no not at all
okay but yeah uh the offer just annoyed
the [\h__\h] out of me so I eventually
stopped reading I I couldn't do it
anymore I couldn't do it anymore I
really wanted to be like hey I finished
I read a book and I finished it I really
wanted to be able to tell you that
guys but I really didn't like
it I really didn't like
it and I was deceived by the reviews
that were on on the back of the on the
book book that were saying like oh life
changing we're like this is one of the
best reads I've ever had I'm like in in
Hinds side I'm like are you for real how
much did you pay these people to give
you these
opinions
huh and the thing is narissa bought me
this book because
originally on the airport on the way to
the moldes I was like I want to sit on
the beach and read a
book so I was go we went to a bookstore
before we took off and I chose a book I
was like oh this looks cute and quirky
and and Nissa tells me oh I know this
book like I didn't read it but I know
someone else I think that's what she
said who read it and yeah they really
liked it and I thought okay okay okay
yeah all right sounds good the quirky
title quirky book cover let's go and
then I didn't read it during the males
because you know it was kind of Stormy
like kind of windy so reading by the
beach wasn't really the vibe so now I
read it in the spa and I hated
[Music]
it no I didn't tell narissa yet me and
narissa we were um talking a little bit
sometimes
um uh on like a separate message thingy
besides Discord so I wouldn't have to go
on
Discord you know but one thing I was
thinking
I was wondering if I should um confront
her about it remember when Shi was on a
break and Nissa would constantly write
on Twitter like oh I miss Shi how I miss
her so
much on Twitter and on her stream and
now me her Oshi and her bestie I was on
a break for so long and has she said a
single thing about
me on on Twitter no maybe on stream once
maybe girl did you miss me at all
narissa where are the tweets where are
the tweets of you missing the [\h__\h] out
of me can't believe it I was legit
thinking about that at some point during
my break I
realized now I realized there's not a
single I miss Kiwa tweet popping up on
my timeline not even from narissa even
though she missed Shi so bad I gu she
doesn't miss
[Laughter]
me oh
man what did she say something like that
in the Stream at
least did she did
she I mean I didn't go on kiaha Twitter
so I don't know but I feel like it would
have come up on my timeline
anyway yeah you aren't supposed to be
parasocial with people in the company
what can I do if she she's usually also
parasocial with
me anyway okay so I was in the spa I got
some good massages I got one massage per
day uh because but they were expensive
so I didn't get like super long massages
on the first day I think what was it I
got a 25 minute massage or so which was
like a welcome massage which was
decent and then on the next day I got
like a normal full body massage that was
like 50 or 60
Minutes
um GAA I heard GAA wants me to play some
new popular poppy horror game GAA no
thank you instead play that game with me
that you played with am cuz I literally
bought it for collab
purposes The Rock one I don't
know uh and then and then the lady said
that tomorrow's massage you'll have it
with someone else it's the like she says
her name and she said she says the name
of the the other massage therapist and
says oh he's the best he's the absolute
best and I was getting really hyped up
uh and turns
out honestly I think that may have been
the best massage I've ever gotten in
Austria or in Europe no all the massages
in Greece were really nice but yeah the
best one in Austria
that
guy the last massage yo even when I
shook his hand in the beginning to greet
the guy he's like really tall and big
and like I felt like he crushed my hand
when we said
hello but yeah his technique was amazing
like I've I'm like a massage
conosur I've had probably 200 plus
massages in my lifetime all over the
world
and different types like normal classic
massages deep tissue massages thae
massages etc
etc oil massages and the the the cliff
massage where there's like a like a
thing that sucking your skin uh I even
had
acupuncture uh for the first time a
while ago and and uh hot stone massage
and this and that and this and that okay
yeah but this guy holy
[\h__\h] he knew what he was doing she it's
so interesting yeah suction cups it's so
interesting how every I swear with all
these 200 plus massages every person has
a completely different technique even if
they're from the same store massage
place where you might think they teach
each other to have like consistency but
no they're all so different
once you start getting massages like me
you can't stop though but actually I did
kind of stop
recently after that spot trip I haven't
been to a massage even though I've been
in pain as always but
yeah here's really good but yeah I got
to go back to the hotel to get a massage
again from
him you miss my goofy ass you don't even
see my ass right now how do you even
know that my ass is still there maybe my
ass is gone maybe my ass
graduated like tattoo artist really I
can't I I wouldn't really compare
[Music]
that another thing that I did on my
break is I went on a [\h__\h] ton of deep
Dives like YouTube deep Dives
about like I don't know uh a lot of
people like Britney Spears and Kelly
Clark no not not Cale plx but like oh
the ol and Twins and you know all those
deep Dives about like kids who got
famous when they were young for
example and how they were um
exploited yeah stuff like
that and and all kinds of other deep
Dives very
interesting no no you didn't want to
hear the graduation word I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm sorry don't worry my my ass is
still
there oh oh you're right ah H one more
thing another thing I did on my break
um I built some
furniture and in an noraly I don't build
furniture on my own but there's one
piece of furniture that I actually
completely built on my own
wait let me show
you and I'm so
proud I'm so so [\h__\h] proud of
myself yeah it's this
one it's
Ikea uh there you go oh where' it
go oh what the [\h__\h] did you save it as
a AEF can I sometimes it works if you
just just uh change the ending to like
jpack and then it's like oh you might
not be able to use it afterwards do you
still want to change it and I say yes
and it might
work let's see
oh H there it worked this one I built
this uhhuh uh-huh is a Coen from Ika
Coolin chest with six
drawers uh I guess one reason I was able
to to build it successfully was because
it didn't have it it doesn't have like a
proper like what do you call
it it looks fancy yeah but it's like the
cheap one that they have it doesn't even
even have a proper drawer uh mechanism
like when I pull out the drawer
thingies uh there's no stopping like
there's no stop that will stop it from
being pulled out completely
so it's not very smooth but I buil it
yeah move my bare hands yeah in a
[Music]
cave I didn't get I didn't even get help
of this I did it on my own I first
thought I can't do it I need help but I
was able to do it and I it started out
looking like a like I said it looked
like a Star Wars robot
but no one was listening so it didn't
really land very well that joke um you
guys don't even know understand what I
mean probably unless you've built this
before is there anyone here who built
this
before there's some rails but they don't
have like a stop and they're like really
cheap plastic
rails it's not like a smooth swoosh
swoosh kind of
[Music]
rail be bear b a
r for my aunt yes oh you did it yeah
I have oh okay so some people are
familiar with this nice see with Ikea
people can relate Mimi oh really nice
you wouldn't get it yeah you wouldn't
get it if you didn't build it you
wouldn't get it but so I thought while I
was building it I was like so proud of
myself and I thought man I'm like Bob
the [\h__\h] Builder or like Tim Allen I
I can build things now and and then I
was kind of getting like strong
opinionated strongly opinionated about
um screws and stuff screw you and so um
some screws that I or similar things as
screws not necessarily screws uh that I
have met on my journey of making this uh
I thought I wanted to introduce them to
you and rate them on a tier list so
let's start with these [\h__\h] you know
them I don't know what to call them but
after after you think you're done with
everything this sucker who can screw
himself shows up and it's like hey hey
hey you're not done you have to pull me
uh put me on and screw me onto the back
of the chest you just built so that
everything stays St stable and you need
to put me on there several times whether
you like it or not and I hate this one
because I don't know what's wrong with
me but like this the side the part of on
the right side have you guys ever used
this before the part on the right side
you uh put kind of like you know cuz of
the back of the the drawer there's like
a really thin sheet of
wood and then you put it like underneath
that and under the big chunk of wood I
don't know how to explain it but you
like you trying to squeeze it under
there and then you screw it in screw it
in screw it in and somehow this would
always like move around and and like
sometimes almost break like it would
bend and [\h__\h] and it would never stay in
place I hate this so
much so I was going to say clearly I
mean in this list I guess it's D tier
but I would love to put it in F
tier I hate it it's the worst and then
there's this thing which thinks it's a
screw but it's just [\h__\h] cheap it's
made out of
plastic and and it looks like a screw
but you kind of just hammer
it right you just Bonk it and then it
goes in there so that's all right but
it's like
H I don't know it was a bit hard to get
uh like bonked in sometimes so just kind
of annoying but it's fine it's not as
difficult as the other one so I think
I'll put it into B tier what is this
called anyway I don't
know I won't even is that yeah the
plastic one
[Music]
mhm garbage
plug fake
screw see how we're we're we're we're
connecting over this like construction
stuff nice
beautiful s screw
te I just want to share my opinion with
you and then there's this thing I
actually even though this is like one of
the most intricate things that I'm
showing off today um I really enjoyed
this boy he's really interesting he's
got like a lot of personality he's got a
lot of uh variation to him like I feel
like there's free personalities that he
has so a little bit schizophrenic uh
screw but I like him like he's a good
boy he's fun and he's not too difficult
to handle I like screwing him in and
then because like you screw him in on
one side and then you use him to connect
another thing and it just kind of works
it just kind of [\h__\h] works and then
and then I think like uh if I remember
correctly cuz I did this a couple days
ago I'm going to put this one in a tier
if I remember correctly he works in
tandem with this boy because on the on
the right side let's say here on the
right side after you're done screwing
that thing in and you put the other
piece of wood or whatever on top of him
um on on the other side of the hole you
use this one what is this called I love
this boy I love this one so much he's so
cute you just push him in and then you
take a screwdriver and then you turn him
around and then it's fixed in place and
everything's cool and everything works
and it's really nice and feels really
satisfying yeah you use this for
bookshelves probably yeah yeah it's like
a lock yeah it's fun cuz it's not hard
to use it might not be a screw I don't
care it's just tools that I use okay
yeah he's a what a a lock
anchor something like a cam a cam
interesting I wouldn't know what it is
in German either though so this one's s
tier so this is my rating for a few of
the tools and screws that I
used honestly this changed my life
building this Ikea dresser I
mean cuz even duh duh duh guy even said
it's you should build it with two
people but I built it alone I built it
alone so now I feel like I can do
anything I
feel I feel amazing there were some
parts where I struggled where I was like
[\h__\h] it I'm I'm stuck this is not
working what and then I went back later
to it and I realized
oh I got something completely
wrong this rating is
screwed yeah so now we can
Anissa I love you I missed
you is that
[Music]
so
BR
really were you tipped off
to better come here and tell me you
missed me before it's too late to leave
a good
impression make sure that I know that
you miss
me someone told you then maybe then yeah
on Twitter maybe like hey @ narissa
ravencraft you should go to k our stream
right now and tell her how much you
missed her cuz she's doubting
it
I thought about cuddling in your bed
with you and your
cats so so you miss my cats more than me
huh I it's understandable my cats are so
[\h__\h]
lovable understandable for one day when
I was in the spa uh I had my bestie take
care of my Kito Catos and afterwards she
was
like like damn I haven't taken care of
your cats in a while
while and now I realized your cats are
like for real like they're therapy I
forgot about that but they're like so
therapeutic they're so
good H so my friend like offered her
support in taking care of my cats more
often again cuz recently always my mommy
was doing it but my cats are just the
sweetest babos ever yeah there's like
everybody falls in love with them so
much and then yeah my cats are just
irresistible I get
it and I I send me to the usual room my
wife I might have to yeah we have to
talk
afterwards although maybe not afterwards
cuz I still have a stream after
this but yeah I was going to say I was
going to say I was going to say uh yeah
my cats I think because I wasn't
streaming and all that and I had like
like the time of the day all the time I
had so much time I was like cuddling so
so much with them and I spent so much
time with them I feel like they they've
become even more
clingy and even more sweet as if they
couldn't I thought it I thought they
couldn't become any more sweet and
clingy but uh yeah I think the time we
spent together as she's streaming oh
yeah right I saw that in the schedule
you're here so they probably did tip you
off on your chat side
oh but wait didn't you just start cuz
9:00 p.m.
now
CA yeah anyway I think my cat's got like
even sweeter and even clingier I love
them so much they they've been so so
love
seeking such sweet potatoes I love
them
you
did you did you little
shits of course you
did she just left she didn't hear that
God damn it cuz I went on a cat tangent
damn
it tell her I
know now we'll talk about it n so we'll
talk it
out anyway that was my tear list I hope
you enjoyed it maybe in the future we
can do more um
screw and Tool tier lists if you would
like
that speaking of my best day another
thing I did on my break is I went to a
super fancy ice ring that I go like I go
to almost every year when I
can yeah there's like a a really fancy
ice Ram that's really special cuz it's
not just one ice cream no it has like
all kinds of like intertwining paths and
it even has like two levels you can go
up and you can go down while on your on
ice on the ice skates like you don't
have to like leave once no it's all
connected you go up and you go down and
and there's music and there's a big
screen and you know it's like really so
much [\h__\h] fun and there's a lot of
like really bad people and then there's
some uh Pros even like swooshing
through and the fact this actually I
took uh a waya I took waya there but
when I took her there it wasn't uh
completely complete yet they like
usually I guess they have it open like
like half of it open for one or two
months and then they finished constru
instruction and open the full version
for another few
months yeah and way is saw the
incomplete version and I I kind of tried
to show
narissa uh the same one but then it was
like exactly during the construction
period where they don't have it open for
like a few
days within like I don't know six months
of opening time okay not maybe not six
maybe five they don't have it open for a
few days and that's when Rissa was here
so I couldn't show her but yeah then I
went with my bestie to the completed
version and I feel like every year they
upgraded they do every year they upgrade
it and it's so crazy like how much
effort they put into it it's like a real
tourist attraction I feel like there's a
lot of uh tourists but also a lot of
like locals like mostly locals I would
say
though and it's so much fun because
there's music playing and it's it's not
just one round found big ice ring no
it's a big uh Outdoors ice ring with
trees and lights and everything and
there's some food there too of course if
you want to it's like kind of like
Christmas Market food um pretty much so
it's like a really really late Christmas
Market
yeah yeah yeah yeah at least you went
there with one blue BP yeah so
true yeah thank you for Super Chat wow
your first one even thank you
yeah it's it's so amazing I don't think
I've ever seen an ice ring like this
anywhere else I'm sure that r or
something like this every anywhere else
too but this the first time I saw one
it's so dope it's so magical yeah like I
don't want to go to a normal boring ass
traditional indoor ice ring this is
where it's at this is where the exciting
stuff happens like children falling down
and and you bumping into children like
Raina
did and yeah and people suddenly doing
pettes and
[\h__\h] yeah and so me and my bestie we had
a good time there ice skating it's
really nice Peak Peak skating cute first
time chatter thank you so much New York
has won I can imagine yeah New York I
feel like New York has like a lot of um
or should have a lot of romantic stuff
because I don't know I feel like or like
not romantic necessarily but like cool
activity
things cuz it's such a touristic place
and also I mean friends happens there so
they got to have like a lot of cool
stuff in my
head wish I'm I'm pouring some more tea
and some more honey although I'm almost
out of honey one thing I don't know why
but the
honey in the past 2 weeks
[Music]
maybe my throat was like suddenly in a
really bad condition I don't know if I
was maybe lowkey
sick it's
still kind of still going on but I
noticed that um you know it was super
dry again so I turned on my uh my
humidifier and on on
full sorry on Full Burst but then the
night before that I I noticed that after
I woke up of course everything like my
throat and nose was dry as [\h__\h] but then
I also the whole day had like
fum coming out of my throat
gener the whole time I felt like I
needed
to bring up the fum in my throat cuz I
just felt it there then I thought okay I
guess it was so dry so maybe if I
humidify a lot it will fix
this so I did that but it didn't go away
at all and I had this fum problem for
like two weeks or so I kept on spitting
out the fum so
disgusting but it was only fle that was
my that was my only problem pretty
much fum
season oh no beware to flum and then I I
I took out my what was it called
Nom Nom it's actually working against
this problem it works it's uh eliminated
the copious fum and helped
me so if you guys have a fum problem I
recommend you need humidity sensor you
can keep things at the right humity
level I don't think it's related to that
I had like I had it on different
settings and it just always was like
this
but I've been having it at 70%
now and I still feel like I wake up or
in the middle of the night or in the
morning with like a dry throat and dry
ass
nose I should have it up at like
90% need more paper COA yeah more
more I also had a lot of flum at some
point that helped me just drink I want
lot more water yeah I've been drinking
water and and Pac COA but yeah it's
fum yeah we call it fleam here 75% is
super high I know cuz like I bought um a
thing that tells me the temperature in
the room and also the
humidity and uh it t it taught me that
normally without the humidifier on I
think it's usually on
like 30% humidity or something like that
humidity really low so bringing it up to
70 is like damn that's a big change but
I still feel dry as
hell flum
flum yeah me too sometimes I wake up in
the middle of the night feeling super
dry and also like I need to pee so I
take uh and I don't mean eating and I
drink a sip of water and then I go back
to sleep but sometimes that results in
me feeling too awake and then I can't
sleep but generally I do have to say
throughout my whole break besides the
last three days I've been always going
to bed before midnight just because I
was always so tired and I had so much to
do during the day I did a lot of
exhausting things actually um and I did
I didn't nap so much either
uh and yeah I slept early and I woke up
early before 10: usually I woke up at
like 8 a.m. these days before like
during my break so it was a really
healthy sleep schedule and it was pretty
nice to wake up
[Music]
early wasn't bad also I bought a few uh
fake plants and one real plant so new
plants addition to my home
uh let's see if the the real one will
die it looked really cute it's a really
cute one it has like curled up uh
leaves yeah I wonder what my mom will
say about it so far it's still
alive what time did you go to bed though
oh I said before midnight usually like
1100 p.m. sometimes even 10:00 I didn't
even want to sleep that early I just I
would fall asleep immediately like ever
since like a year ago I or so I would
fall asleep so early I think it's like
I'm getting too
old but yeah um oh oh guys I watched
with my besti I watched a
movie in the cinema I watched the new
ovie
yeah it was so good I mean I feel like
uh before I went I saw some critiques
that it's not not as good as others and
it's kind of weird and I mean I have to
agree it's not as good as others like I
wouldn't put it in the top five um maybe
in the top 10 but not in the top
five of ji movies Ji
normally I would say gibli in German we
say gibli but it's in Japanese it's
jii so I guess it's jibli yeah the boy
and the Heron but in Japanese the title
is I think
uh which is like how do you guys live
how do you guys want to live how do you
guys intend to
live so the English title is pretty we
uh
different
but I watched it in Japanese with
English
subtitles and I really liked it because
there were also so many birds like birds
played a big role in it and I felt like
it was like
evil counterparts the
[Music]
movie so many birds and and and and and
especially I think they were what wait
now it's been so long they were
obviously there were
herand
uh yeah and then they
were uh par where the
parakeets I feel like there were three
types of birds
[Music]
mostly no chickens guys no chickens
sadly but very ful birds and most of
them were kind of evil even the Heron I
mean spoiler
alert he starts out like you think he's
really evil but then I
mean it gets better I wouldn't say he's
he ever is like completely
good but yeah it gets better budgies
yeah pelicans pelicans yeah Pelicans too
those were really evil too like evil
[\h__\h] but no actually okay I feel bad
for the Pelicans because then later on
you
realize in the movie that you know
they're not evil they depict them as
evil but they're just doing what they
need to do to
[Music]
survive more just a jerk yeah jerk
paren I guess everybody's just kind of
doing what they need to do to survive I
found the the Budgy culture really
interesting like they the other birds
weren't as far as the budgies the
budgies take over like this whole world
and have like a king who is like bigger
than everybody else and the budgies they
have like different colors they're so
pretty so cute and they look funny and
uh
quirky they do funny
things yeah but they're basically just
um they have a whole society they live
in a society they live in a Budgy
Society H spoilers spoilers okay I'll
stop
now I feel like you guys should still
watch it even if you haven't watched it
yet as long as it's in the
cinemas cuz times have changed guys I
find it fascinating like back in the day
when there would be a new jibli movie in
order to see it overseas you would have
to wait so long for a
DVD but now it really Es at the same
time
overseas even with dubbing I watched the
OG but they also released with
dubing that's
[Music]
amazing yeah that's so cool I really
love that being able to not having to
wait endlessly to watch this movie
simultaneous releases let's
[Music]
go
yeah so I watched the movie I I thought
it was pretty good not the best one out
there but it was pretty good oh did I
tell you before the break did I watch
this before the break cuz I watched
another movie I think this one I told
you about right I I told you that I
watched the uh oh yeah I remember
now
the
uh Mocking Bird uh hunger Hunger Games
uh prequel I watched that but you guys
know that I
[Music]
think ah so random but I ate my first
ever
Falafel on my break cuz that was uh one
of the lunch things in the hotel
wasn't really my choice but that's like
one of the only things they had they
gave me like a plate with Falafel and
humus and some other
stuff yeah that's
huge how was it it was actually fine it
was good um it's not bad but I don't
know if I would go out of my way to get
it again maybe maybe if there's no other
good choices I like the crunch of the
falafel and I do like the flavor it's
not like my favorite kind of flavor but
I I do like
it I know there's like Falafel burgers
out there right I might want to like try
that that sounds
[Music]
interesting
oh what the freak is a f you don't know
it's like I think like in in for for a
lot of like vegetarians it's a great
option of food out there a lot of people
eat Falla
as like a vegetarian yeah veggie
meatball I mean I wouldn't really say it
tastes like meat at all but that's not
the goal of it but it kind of you know
it's like a nice a nice
uh it was
good humus humus on the other side of
hummus I don't find that flavor very
interesting like there's I don't I don't
think there's much flavor to it at all
so it's pretty neutral and I guess
that's a good thing too especially with
the Falafel being more on the spicy side
so interesting
interesting tahini sauce
tahini try with tahini SAU what's tahini
I heard about it but what was that I
don't remember will take a while until
you guys tell me what it
is yeah
okay I'm actually soon done with my um
pents can you believe it cuz like I
wanted to say I didn't
do like that much crazy exciting stuff
where I could tell you tangents about
there's as I said there's like one thing
that took up a lot of my time that I
can't talk to you
about but like yeah even besides that I
mean I did some things but yeah it's not
that much I was just like taking it easy
mostly I was trying to take it
easy and and get my life
together a sesame seed sauce oh I love
sesame ooh
oh oh interesting I love sesame uh salad
dressing come back Cola okay what come
Kaa back
okay yeah that's the next stream right
after I'm I'm I want to rate into it but
this being a zatu stream I've been
noticing my throat uh
o uh gets dried up it's not good maybe I
should take like a 10-minute break or so
uh but it's okay we take a 5 minute
ending screen and a 5 minute loading
screen break
basically where I will not
talk I have tea as well lot of tea
prepared oh yeah so games released while
I was gone right like like Yakuza
released that one I remembered so I put
it on my schedule wasn't there other
things too also I think next week
There's a Nintendo Direct but from what
I've heard it might not be like the
usual Nintendo Direct but like a third
party so I don't think I'll do a watch
along oh yeah Grand blue fantasy reing I
really like the looks of it and I did
come across uh I think a
clip where B said she wants to play it
with
me I guess with me and other people as a
group and I was like
what is it because of my of my
reputation of playing RPG games and
stuff Persona okay Persona is not really
my cup tee I mean I feel like I would
really enjoy it if I would get into it
but let's not even get into it because I
have plenty of other games on my hands I
have to
play uh I don't I think I feel like have
we reacted to a trailer of grand blue
relink on my stream before and I was
like really excited or am I imagining
this and it was a different
one the combat is similar to tell of AR
rise for
real Tom FR is remaster yeah I kind of
want to stream that yeah yeah yeah
yeah P fre is a good place to start but
I don't even want want to start you
understand oh ff7 rebirth released what
no
[Music]
way are you thinking of returning to
power I'll have to think about it like
for real for real I don't
know yeah it's like my type of
[Music]
game Grand blue I think I mean cuz I I
saw um
like a little bit of like the visuals
and all that and I really like it I
really like it but we're going to play
yaku on now so I don't
know I don't really think we have much
time she needs a fourth for her Squad
okay explain that to me cuz I don't know
anything about the game so there's a an
online
multiplayer thing do you play through
the whole story the same as the solo
player story
the single player
story or is it different is this like is
the is the game playay different is the
story
different tell me about it the main
story is single player
okay there's four player cor mhm
mhm yeah but is that the main
[Music]
story side missions can be Co-op
mhm a it's like Monster
Hunter
so do I need to play the main game to
play the
co-op I'm guessing no like the main do I
have to play through this the the single
player
story thank you for the
pinky guys I'm doing uh uh polar wordss
tomorrow Valentine's polar Awards it
will be the last ones for a while and by
the way if you haven't seen it the
Christmas polar wordss are uploaded on
the community board I uploaded them
yesterday just so you know I'm sorry for
the Wake 20 hour main campaign before
you can
multiplayer 20 20 20 hour oh that's not
so
long no no no the only reason it was so
late because I went on a break and I had
work to do to be able to go on a break
in the first place I I'm sorry I was
late but this this time it won't be so
late trust
me I'm not going on a break you're
welcome yeah the Christmas ones are nice
right I wrote it with a golden pen
golden shiny metallic pen
ha it looks like I really wrote on there
with a golden shiny pen so
nice yeah I'll have to think about the
grand blue thing I don't really think we
have space right now for a game like
that and I don't know how long beu would
wait um but
yeah going on the break was a good idea
I don't know I felt like I had big fomo
concerning pal world I felt like I was
missing out a lot cuz I I had a lot of
Clips in my recommendations that were
like all powered like you know good out
coming back and all that felt like
everybody was so hype about it
m so I really felt like I was missing
out I really didn't feel very
nice it really made me
think there is never never
a cat hair there's never a convenient
time to take a break and I thought you
know Now's the Time there's no other
time because I mean okay there's less
less convenient times there's never a
convenient time but there's even less
convenient times and those were the
months before where I couldn't take a
break it had to kind of be during this
time and I'm glad I took it during this
time I kind of I really needed the break
in many ways but uh yeah
I did definitely detox from work it was
refreshing to not have to work and have
work in my brain all the time and and I
I do think it was refreshing to also not
stream so much that like in the
beginning I was like oh I should be
streaming this feels weird not to stream
and then after a week or so I was like
yeah I like this I'm not even thinking
about streaming and it's nice to not
have to think about it and and then
before like a few days like yesterday
and today and the day before yesterday I
was like kind of a little bit I'll be
honest I was like kind of feeling a
dread a little bit of going back to the
usual because it felt like going back to
school after summer
vacation go like or or Easter vacation
or winter vacation or whatever like
after a big break going back and like
feeling the insane dread of going back
back because school was scary as [\h__\h] to
me and usually I wasn't doing so well at
school and and just I don't know it was
[\h__\h] traumatic to think about going
back so I'll be honest I had like a
little bit of a similar feeling like I
was a little bit scared to go
back I also felt like maybe people like
co-workers and you
guys a lot of you maybe forgot me or
like don't care so much about me anymore
like maybe maybe you feel like huh
whatever about me now and and for
co-workers I feel like I don't know I I
like when I was making my schedule which
also I want to talk about a little bit
um for the stream tomorrow I was like I
want to do this thing cuz I thought
about this ages ago maybe I thought
about it even a year ago of doing a
stream where I have a heart rate monitor
on and I let people um say pick up lines
to me and we'll see if I go doky doie
doie
doie and then I was like I was about to
put it on the schedule I was like ah
maybe I shouldn't what if I ask and
nobody wants to sign up for it what if
nobody gives a [\h__\h] what if people just
don't care about
me and then I I was like whatever I
should at least try cuz I had this idea
ages ago and I've always I always always
always wanted to do this stream like try
it out I don't even know I I feel like
my my heart rate will barely
change
but still I want to do it I don't care I
want to do it anyway so I put uh like
the notification like hi everybody I'm
back I want to do the stream on
Valentine's um does anybody want to
maybe call in it will be really short
you just have to say some pickup lines
and that's it and then and then a
certain someone replied really excitedly
like oh my God Tak right ah it's back
and yes sign me up sign me up and like
and then a couple more so we don't have
uh all of I members but we have a couple
who will call in and I was thinking in
between in case I I I don't I don't know
it can be a short stream I don't mind it
being like an hour or so um but in case
it's not long enough I was thinking you
guys no not narissa I think narissa also
probably going to call in but that
wasn't
narissa uh um I was I was thinking maybe
you guys can also send me some pickup
Lins that I can like read in between the
call-ins your guys just pick up lines
but like maybe not just one liners but
like more like
a like a paragraph pick up paragraphs so
that it could maybe have a bigger effect
on my heart rate you know what I
mean would you like to do
that I did by the way also tell ID I
just thought you know generally the time
will be [\h__\h] for them like I don't know
4:00 a.m. 3:00 a.m. or so so I said no
pressure just in case anybody's awake
even if it's spontaneous just call in if
you want to just letting you know I'm
doing this
stream Mooney do you want to send a
pickup line or do you want to do you
want to you know call in although I
think for call in it's kind of sudden
cuz normally for external people have to
get
permission uh background check and this
and that so I don't know if I can do it
that
suddenly but yeah uh so that's happening
tomorrow and on that matter let me just
quickly show the schedule on that note
yeah this is the schedule we're uh we're
having the first stream after my break
right now and then in 20 minutes um
I'm going to
do my come back okay sorry guys I've
been like cuddling so much with my cats
while I was gone now I have so much cat
hair in my
mouth no um the comment kind okay I had
as I said so many epiphanies during my
break songs like I would sit in in the
restaurant with my bestie and there were
like so many songs playing on on all of
the speakers where I was like holy [\h__\h]
wait I know the song but I never thought
about it as a song cuz normally it
doesn't come up in my in my brain when I
think about songs to sing in K so I I
wrote down all the songs that I heard
and we're going to sing them they're
going to be mostly new songs yeah yeah
yeah I think most of them you will have
heard I
promise there is a lot of like
unexpected Classics where you guys will
be like wow damn she dug that one up
didn't
she looking forward to it yes now I'm
getting nervous and then on Wednesday
tomorrow we're doing the heart
Challenger
toti heart challenge they will challenge
my heart just like my second single that
I released after the Hino t as a
Valentine's Day song called heart
challenger please stream heart
Challenger on this day
[Music]
especially and on first day we're going
to pick up uh a channel stream that
people talk about a lot and I've at the
game awards and so on like I would talk
about indie game and then people would
make fun of it and be like ha indie game
and I want to know what that's about
so we're going to play Dave the
diver uh and then members only I haven't
decided what to do we'll think about it
and then on the weekend we'll play we'll
start the new like a
dragon wow and it's the Year of the
Dragon now did you know and did you know
that I think after the Year of the
Dragon is the year of the
rooster
[Music]
now I
wonder will will Wawa get a oneyear push
campaign probably not it's still a long
time to go but probably
not would be
[Music]
nice eh what wasn't it [\h__\h] okay I miss
miss oh oh yeah wait no it wasn't the
next okay then it will never happen then
will never
happen wait why did I mistake uh I
looked up all the years and I was like
when is the year of the
rooster [\h__\h] it was snake oh damn it
damn it can I red deut as a as a snake
YouTuber please
snake Okay [\h__\h] now I was gaslighting
myself I guess H oh
[Music]
well
ah I have to show you something
guys so anyway this will hopefully be a
fun week I know you guys like the
schedule coming back with a full
schedule as it should be now let me show
you
something you know
[Music]
sometimes sometimes I go to conventions
right
and uh I like to I mean I used to go to
conventions way more and I like to go to
like German conventions mostly because
they were bigger but sometimes I go to
Austrian conventions when I can cuz my
friends are there and it's like pretty
much the only opportunity to meet my
friends in as a group
uh I mean I could forcefully like try to
make appointments with them but it's
like hard like everybody has work to do
like meeting as a group is really only
realistic and easy at conventions even
then like it's usually not the full
group um but yeah so I go to these
conventions sometimes and but I realized
like I don't know it's kind of
different nowadays like I'm kind of
bored that convention so I end up going
at some point I I I I found out about
the C rooms that they have like in
Austrian
conventions like there's a lot of
conventions that are made by the same
organizer and even if they're not by the
same organizer often still they will
have this Koka room even in Germany at a
convention the same people had a Koka
room like there's a there's a group of
people who organized Koka rooms yeah
they always have like the same software
the same songs on there so I realized oh
yeah it's the same
people but I think they're from Austria
but I even saw it in in the German
convention so I more more and more and
more I end up just sitting in there and
like it's like you put in a song but the
queue is always so long that you have to
wait like an hour until your song
finally comes up and you have to listen
to all these people um 80% of them no
hate but 80% of them cannot hit a key
and also not seeing properly into a
microphone you can barely hear
them um so it's yeah you know sometimes
they sing good songs that are fun and
and then a lot of people join in like
even though one person chose the song
like whoever knows it is like welcome to
jump in and sing together um like I
personally however often choose songs
that nobody knows because I don't want
anybody to jump in there's like
sometimes when there are people jumping
in and singing with me I noticed that
when they sing completely off key it
really confuses the [\h__\h] out of me and
it makes me go sing wrong as well so
anyway so often I just bring out a
random old ass het project song that
they wouldn't know they never
know
but so the other day I went to one and I
ended up in a kre room again just
chilling
alone and I went through the list I just
couldn't think of any song to sing and I
was like looking up so many things like
keywords and then you get like a list of
songs that are
available and I I didn't even type in
anything like whole life
related I was looking
for
what was I think I was looking for
sh sorry sh song
Lami I think and then somehow yeah no
nothing came up and I looked another
keyword up and somehow for some reason I
got
oino from some whole life
members uh as a suggestion and I was
like wait that's not what I'm looking
for but wait a second H life songs
there's H life songs on there now
because it's not like they they
literally they choose what songs to put
in there because they seem to subtitle
them on their own uh and they just play
the original audio no Kadoka version
they just play the original audio like
somewhat quietly and then let the people
sing over it and then you often don't
even know which voice is the person
singing it cuz it's so badly
balanced but
H so I know there there's like somebody
purposefully putting in songs in there
right like several people who are from
the team who are putting songs in
purposefully knowingly and so now
there's Whole Life song and I'm like
H H so I look
[Music]
up
uh
[Music]
it
oopsie dangerous it's not dangerous
those rooms are so dark I can literally
not see anybody's faces and you know
people don't
know people don't know I'm just
[Music]
chilling but you know what I saw I will
tell you I did not Choose Or sing it
nobody did sadly I wish they did I wish
but I found
this they have my
song I'm there in the Austrian anime
convention K and I can't sing it I can't
I wish I could why is H not in there
twice I wonder
but they have pineapple Sparks and H
pineapple I wanted to say
pineapple and normally they always play
like the music video too cuz they just
subtitled on top of the music video I
could have like shown it all off but no
of course I didn't of course I didn't
but like this means to me that somebody
in the Koka team must be aware of
me and whole Al alive and all that but
honestly whole live is like very well
known all over the world now we have um
a big presence and I mean not as big in
Europe as in
America but people people know vtubers
for
sure yeah I thought it would be um no no
I didn't even think about singing it
it's not uh like something I would
do I wouldn't do such a risky thing no
no no no no no no I just uh sang some
other songs and joined some other people
singing certain songs and so on CU like
it was such a long wait I just put in a
song that was like TV size so like an
anime uh opening or
ending but that was like only 1:30 like
I I was i s I was sitting in there for 3
hours and I in total only had two of my
songs that I chose come up cuz you can
only choose one at the time time and
then you have to wait and wait and wait
and then finally it comes
up uh so two of them both of them is my
my fault both of them I had as TV size
so 130 1 minute 30 seconds 3 hours and I
get to sing 1 minute 30
each no but also I joined other people
because I was like [\h__\h] this I will
join your song that you chose because I
like this song
too
yeah I saw the SpongeBob thing I saw
like the behind the scenes as well they
were wearing accents
trackers and then speaking of like whole
life in conventions and this and that
another thing I saw now I'm not going to
show the picture but you know on a
certain social
media uh app
um Hest certain social media app during
my
break I saw something and I want to ask
who here in the chat was at the gansin
concert in
D during my break who went anybody
anybody
here
[Music]
I want to know if there's someone in the
chat right now it's in Germany
yeah not there but I want
[Music]
oh no I was ref
faction and the one in
Germany I know someone who did
because I was just going through like
stories from all of my all the people I
follow and then one of my friend who
isn't into YouTubers at all I think um
pretty sure he doesn't really
care
um him and his GF went to this ging
concert and she took a
video like before it started I guess and
like filmed his surroundings like in one
Circle and then I noticed something very
orange something very very very orange
sitting like right behind him I guess
right on the seat behind him someone
literally behind him is wearing the kfp
sweater who is this I need a name it's
someone with glasses and short hair a
guy with a orange KY sweater who went to
the genon concert and just St who are
you because you are getting the kfp
badge of honor for representing kfp
uh outside of
kfb but I was like hey what did I just
see and I played back and I'm like oh my
God this is the kfp ocat hoodie let's go
represent
W I'm so
excited oh so happy to see that it's so
Random it was so
Random
it stands out so much yeah reveal
yourself for real for real I want to
know and give me proof but I don't know
maybe they're maybe they're not even in
the chat but anyway we actually
installed perfectly it's uh pretty much
time almost to move you guys let me just
check one more time my tangent list if I
missed anything oh one more
thing
I think I gave myself carpal tunnel
syndrome again on my
break I maybe I don't
know I uh spray painted something on my
break
uh and it was like I don't know I don't
think I I don't remember the last time I
spray painted something so I didn't
really have a good technique I guess and
it was really really really really
exhausting like pushing the thing the
tiny thing down with my finger hurt so
much and I switched hands and I switched
fingers I mean doing it with anything
besides the pointy pointy finger is kind
of difficult but sometimes I would even
like at some point I would even do it
with both hands cuz I lost
complete strength of both of my hands
and they were in so much pain but I was
trying my best to spray paint
and on that day I used two cans 400 ml
each all up and uh after the first one
after like halfway of the first one I
was already feeling pain and after
completely using up the first one I was
like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it hurts I can't I
literally I I I can't I can't I can't
even like move my fingers properly
anymore that's how much I was in pain
uh
to yeah I heard afterwards that there's
like an adapter that you put on there
and then you can squeeze it differently
like you squeeze a spray spray thingy
spray bottle for like plants or whatever
I didn't know that that existed but it
was so bad and I I took a little break
like I took an hour break and my hands
were still hurting but I had to go back
cuz we kind of like wanted to finish the
project and I was in charge of spray
painting so I spray painted more and
more and more with the second one the
second spray can it was
so so
painful and then I wasn't even done I
wasn't even done I it wasn't enough
color the 800 M weren't enough color so
I was like okay I'll finish this on
another
day um but I finished on that day with
so much pain and no strength in my hands
and I thought okay I'll sleep a day at
night over it it will be gone then I
wake up it's still there then the whole
day passes the pain is still there I
can't even like put my thump and my
pointy finger
together I lost all senses of my hands
and every motion of my fingers hurts and
it goes up to my around my elbow like my
wrist everything
hurts and feels so useless and
broken so the whole day broken then I
thought okay one one more day tomorrow
surely it will be back to normal the
following day still like I think it was
like over 50 hours until it somewhat
recovered and then still I felt a little
bit of the aftermath even after 50 hours
oh my God it hurt so much it was
crazy I totally overdid it but I think
it was like the the the technique that I
used was also [\h__\h] and
yeah yeah I I strained my my muscles
real bad and I had to get back to it a
couple days later and this time I was a
bit more careful with my technique I was
still in pain but I did it better and it
ended up not having as insane effects I
was more careful and
yeah I took more breaks in
between a little bit and I ended up
using uh four cans not two cans before
cans yeah okay now we're going to move
over I just want to tell you I spray
painted and I [\h__\h] up my hands and my
wrists both of them left and
right now I'm now I'm fine again but
yeah oh was painful I'm going to wait
I'm going to set up
the
the the mo move movement the movement of
you guys the transportation of you guys
I you guys excited I really want you
guys to come because I'm going to sing
some really um um surprise surprise
songs like you wouldn't expect
it let me set it up before I go I should
have given myself like five minutes of
ending screen now I'm not getting that
[\h__\h] no I can still give that to
myself some resting time for my fro
um thank you guys anyway for listening
to me today I'm glad we were able to
catch up even though I said I don't have
much to talk about I I ended up talking
for 2 hours straight anyway so that's
great field trip
yay no no German
songs only English
songs it will be unarchived and it will
be fun will be fun if my FR doesn't
[\h__\h]
die okay redir let's go see you there
it's not over yet we're going to party
now
[Music]
woohoo