[Music]
w
oh
ah
KY k
k
[Laughter]
the way I'm holding chunkers right now
man it's so funny hi chunky wony say
hello say hello say
something bye-bye Chun carella bye-bye
she's so
trick she wasn't purring much there cuz
I was holding her really
weirdly my my
my my back hips
hold hurt like an old
lady right now lower lower back yeah 144
40 p
h why am I 140
40p
Kaba
Kaba I just had a funny call at the the
moment I started the stream I got a
call and I picked up and I'm like H are
you Miss Taki and I'm yeah like I'm like
I'm like
yeah and then they're like oh we sent
you an email regarding this and you
haven't replied yet so that's why we're
calling and I said no yeah I
did uh I did and then they're like hm
okay let me
check oh yeah you're right never mind
then then then that's okay I guess thank
you
goodbye
huh that's so easy why can't all things
be so easy but like if it was that easy
for you just just check before you
[Music]
call just check before you call
man nah all good I'm glad I'm glad they
didn't like you know in that kind of
situation when you when you want to say
like you didn't receive a certain email
and you you're pretty sure of it but
then you check and it is there I can
understand maybe I have even acted like
this before I don't know but I can
understand you would be like maybe too
embarrassed and you would just be like
no it's actually really not there it
really didn't go through even though you
see it right in front of your eyes just
just say yeah I don't know I don't see
it sorry can you send it again just
because you realized oh I'm wrong but I
don't want to admit it cuz I'm supposed
to be a professional so let's just say
it didn't really arrive I you know these
kind of things happen right yeah yeah
but no he just straight away immediately
admitted yeah okay it's there never mind
then so it was like one of the shortest
calls I've ever had in my
life oh that reminds
me that reminds
me
okay cuz I'm trying to get um my key
back from uh a girl who took care of my
Kito Catos before
but yeah she has not been giving me my
keys
back she will eventually I I hope I get
it back before I leave cuz right now now
I only have one key and would be easier
to have two
keys uh because you
know um because you know how so that I
can I can just
leave keys here but also take my keys
with me so that when I come back from
Japan then I can just enter my home
don't have to coordinate with like you
know
mommy or so H why did you wait so long
no I didn't wait so long no no no I told
her like first of all like in the
beginning I I told her when she left my
when she was going to leave my apartment
I I told her leave the keys in the in
the in the post box it's that easy and
then she said I forgot it and that's
that's like a long time ago now but I've
been like you know waiting for her to
give give me the keys back but then
recently I reminded her a couple days
ago and yeah she's she's
not she's not doing it
yet h i
tweeted Twitter police I tweet what do
you mean are you going to tweet that I'm
live it saids here 8 minutes
ago
hey
hey she did tweet for me yeah I tweeted
just for
you yeah no I tweeted say okay fine this
is the same situation as with my phone
call hey you didn't tweet I say no I
did now you go check and you and then
you're like ah okay never mind and then
our conversation is
over did you tweet for tummy day
no I know I have one of the best tummies
in whole life in my default outfit
even but didn't feel like like it I
probably did in the past in previous
years oh who you know I recorded like
four or five different things
today maybe
five lots of
recording yeah I did it tomorrow a bit
more two two more things
to be
recorded yeah how your froat my froat
actually kind of
fine I don't know I think I'm
fine
uh I'm just not like my brain my brain
is not
fine one 2 three
four yeah four things
things
yeah wake up
[Laughter]
waa yeah we didn't scream so much in a
warm game but recently my my voice
recovery has been pretty good these past
months anyway like if I strain it
recovers pretty immediately so all good
in Wawa's fro
neighborhood I
I'm not fine in my head I am stressed as
[\h__\h] I did that and I did other things
did those recordings but I also did like
other things like uh sending sending my
last tax payment of the year off early
early early
mhm and real
realizing that there's no money left on
my account I couldn't even have FL flown
premium economy I I would have gone into
the minus so it's good that I went with
economy I can't believe it man I can't
believe
it oh what has
happened that's rough yeah it's
crazy absolutely crazy
[Music]
here we
go it's okay I'm just not
liquid it's okay it's okay I'm not broke
I'm just not
liquid what's terrifying it's kind of
terrifying okay H guys we want to make
progress today I hope I can get really
far m why is it so quiet
though okay I just let me carry your
goods I'm
cheap uh are you guys ready for long I
mean not that long people told me I need
like 12 more hours of gameplay and I
believe that and thus we only need to
really play 6 hours today oh did I close
my chat I only see it on the screen let
me open it
again uh uh uh next icon
well I wonder what the next one is feel
like it's kind of obvious but I just
don't
know obvious but I just oh that's
me single hot mod crystals in your
area
woohoo okay well I've been planning so
many things too like wao all the all the
off collabs and stuff in like dance
practices oh it's my schedule is like
filled up to the brim I don't even
know if there when there's space for
solo streams but I know you guys want
solo streams too so I'll try to squeeze
in something
but the the
Cali
nail painting stream might even be very
very soon you don't need solo streams
okay you hate me okay okay I get it I
get
it and you know it might not just be C
we may have invited one more girl Ian
girl oh that kind of gives it away to
join us in the nail painting Salon out
of my sight Bren I mean son a
salon let's call it
Salon who is it
and anyway and beans beaches and pears
beats and
[Music]
beans H come on come on SN yeah I mean I
did say you you have to be okay with
showing your
fingernails what I really want to be is
a blacksmith what I really want to be is
a
blacksmith oh that's it no more
conversation okay
M so anyway we're going to we're going
to we're going to play this game now
okay and and we're going to play at
least 6 hours okay that's actually
nothing my streams are always like that
so not a challenge let's do
this try not to lose it again is Aio D
boo you found it yeah thank you so much
n would have killed me if I'd come back
without it there less than noral toell
and Theo too so should you you Hunter
you and your friends don't have to steal
anymore if anyone threatens you again
little louder yeah you know who to turn
to I agree we
do and we already have Mel's given us a
job Shifting The Chocobo [\h__\h] out the
Stables it's hard work and the pay isn't
half what we got from the stones but if
we stick at it we'll keep ourselves fit
uh so basically last time we came to
this place and we couldn't get through
because uh pass not pass all right I've
got it back now and all's well that ends
well and we had to do you train to be a
blacksmith right something to get be
your customer I'm going to save up all
my Gill and get you to make me a massive
sword I'll but this part is kind of
lame
so I don't really
[Music]
care it's just a filler
yeah just another
filler you guys will be happy to hear
that I I put lip balm on and it was the
one that call gave me all
right we have a place on the
wagon earlier this
year when when when myth was at C's
Place remember gos I think we're
mercenaries you hide us to protect you
maybe
mercenaries and you remember the plan
the ones with the flowers all the way to
twins side Jill and I will go with you
as far as the outskirts then find Our
Own Way in we'll go what fire to the
outt stuff I need right the stuff and
we'll scout out the Imperials defenses
there's a square with a big Bell Tower
right in the middle of town if you get
lost or out goes wrong we can meet up
there
right let's go Bell
Tower well let's go
Dogo Jill's like so so what's the what
what's the matter with this dog we're
not talking about it
ever communication
do yeah it's just like they talked off
screen seat of the Imperial Court this
area is so
cool reception chamber and you're quite
certain your father has no knowledge of
Altima I am oh the blondies I have no
difficulty believing a Sinister Force
has come to exert an influence on
sandre but be that as it
may it is yet to claim my
father For Better or Worse his Radiance
speaks his own mind
H then the fiend works from the Shadows
this is so games of frony I confess when
first you told me of this
Fiend I had my doubts and more than a
few at
that a beast that labors to plunge
valisia into turmoil all in pursuit of
your
brother but that wound is proof enough
that evil is a foot huh what wound then
I have your answer your highness you
will join me in my
fight oh I cannot not yet your highness
please as you are aware the Delan Army
is at our
gates they have lost their mother
Crystal and with it all hope of a
negotiated
withdrawal it is but a matter of time
before they invade HH they invade
because they lost their mother cryst m
is not here to meet them my people will
be
slaughtered oh will he help now are not
by Hugo kopka thanks to ultima's
machinations no I know the fate of your
people weighs heavy on your conscience
but if we do not put an end to Altima's
plans they shall face a far darker fate
the chaos he would reak would Sweep All
of valesia into the abyss the lives of
every man woman and child in the twins
are at
stake I believe what you say
Phoenix but I have duties of my own and
I'm must discharge
them come what
may understandable I
mean it's important for him no I get
it what do you know of my
blood I know that it is wholly Unworthy
of the highest offices of State which
rightly belong to those of purer
breeding
alas your bloodline runs through the
oriflam gutter from a [\h__\h] who weighed
her child's worth in
Gil have you threatened my
father of course not I merely whispered
in his
ear that his Mongrel son is plotting a
rebellion what silver listens to the
words of his
astrologers and they have ears
too you have been feeding them your
lies should you remain loyal to Emperor
Olivier his Radiance May yet Crown your
head with Laurel and not with
tar F tonged
[Laughter]
witch H in consideration of your long
years of service to the Empire I shall
forgive this uncharacteristic
rudness now hurry and make ready your
Imperial
highness Emperor Olivier expects much of
you Dion or should I say of bahmed she's
so Savage damn may your fire reduce his
enemies to
Ash till all of fesia bows to its
rightful
ruler
damn what is stopping him from killing
her H I guess his father would be really
mad I don't
know
there is another darkness that has taken
hold of
sandre and until its grip is released
the Flames of War shall spread ever
wider just as Tima
wishes forgive me my family has caused
you much
grief you are not her keeper
Phoenix this is a matter for the
Imperial household now and as a member
of that household it falls to me to
resolve it
at such time as that is done what
strength I have shall be
yours so he's in thank you your
highness happy
birthday let us take to the skies
together and bring a new dawn to valesia
sweet 18 I should like nothing
more oh Bahamut and Phoenix
together
nice what happened last time e no
idea Terrence nah
roughly my
prince Tell Me True do you believe what
I'm about to do is
wrong
I we dragons have but one leader your
highness and we shall follow him until
the very
end well I remember what happened
between these two thank
you yeah better this is my decree better
help the Phoenix than for their crimes
the crown the traitorous Anabella and
her usurping son shall be put to death
oh even the son the empire restor
SW all
right yeah wait so he changed his mind
like he's not going to help uh at
The Invasion issue at
all get ready oh
[\h__\h] it's treason treason yay treason
woohoo get ready oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] you
guys are excited it you guys know what's
coming the season of
treason yay it's good treason this kind
of treason is good cuz it's treason by
good people for good reasons you
know who's this oh okay another cut
scene
perhaps wait I haven't warmed up yet
though we don't go get into a big fight
right away right
I don't know how to fight
anymore
treason stop you eat
[\h__\h] one would never guess that these
people stood on the brink of
War well they're afraid they turned to
drink to forget their
fears anything you want to
forget
everything the harbor is empty and half
the market stores too the city may seem
peaceful on the surface but it's
balanced on a knife
edge can these two kiss already maybe
they did off screen where we to give it
a nudge it might be just the distraction
we need to reach the mother Crystal
I thought you might say that we should
send for gav we'll need someone to keep
the fire as we start from going out and
we can busy ourselves scheming until he
gets
here I'll send a stolas
then didn't they already kiss one no
they were about to very
[Music]
close
a turtle yes
Turtle he's so shiny so
fancy
oh M at 3:00
a.m.
boy n
NY
oh oh [\h__\h] it's uh is that the works of
Bahamut and the Phoenix
already
no turn around girl
run oh my God she's cute though don't
die fire fire light the fire I don't
know
tole treas is the thing I
Aspire this way treason is what I Aspire
that's that's that's good
too let's
go oh what do you call it again jumping
over the roofs of a City
Roofing
parkour wait really that is also
parkour yeah rooftop
jumping oh we're actually I go through
the roofs myself okay Fire in the Sky
why the city's on Fire Fire in the Sky
that's not in the sky that's in the for
squ in the city the one with the bell
tower in the middle of town
right
uh do I stay on the roofs e what the
what
what wait
what I he very very confusing mini mapy
is to be slain on sight but spare the
citizenry his highness's orders were
clear
people those were impu on
drons oh what the one's just running by
now so what why why does that concern
me m nice
fire that's that's big what in the hell
is going
on let's go and see
yeah let's
go
the drons ah they belong to Dion ah okay
okay
okay but first we find Goose well only
Deon has the
dragons H I just hope he's all
right what who who's who do you hope is
all right oh hi uh how do I fight
again uh oh yeah wait these
buttons
sick sick
them
kill wait draon Knight if they're from
Dion then I'm fighting the wrong person
right now but I don't know it yet I
guess
go
right now
too I don't know we're on the same side
yet
yet that's
bad hopefully we don't have to kill too
many of
those they AR enough of you are there
cut them down no
no what who healed which bastard just
healed no let
go
this
dude got to kill them
first and take this yeah nice AOE I love
AOE who's left no no oh okay uh big
boy this
one
ow
what was that oh the 50% sign uh what do
I do again oh yeah yeah
oh I would have I should have done the
deadly Embrace but it's okay I'm I'm
warming up so Avo the N
now and now he will be staggered I know
what to do when he's
staggered I know very well
a bit more I know you're done but a bit
more too slow W let's
go just like I played just
yesterday oh oh yeah yeah okay okay okay
okay
okay uh what
this
kill sounds like I'm like barely getting
through his armor but get just sound
effect things I
guess oh uh uh oh already
already man Dion drons are really not
that
good It's All Coming Back me
now yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh
hey
oh
oh good
Dodges
oh oh wow
Tak oh
very
very and that was just one hit
left nice you would have destroyed
benedicta in a few moments they're drons
what is this then yeah perhaps civil
war Civil
War
Rebellion wait the Aden song is called
Rebellion so it's kind of fitting right
wait it wasn't it was rebellion was it
and they saying fire fire Let the Fire
it's literally how a rebellion
goes wow
[Music]
so never thought I'd be glad to fall
into a sewer
crabs
honey
hone Mega crab this
one
what get him PE sewers attack make it
look easy what the [\h__\h] like what what
how how how does that end up in your
sewers to the coun CH yes
Captain wait who who just men women in
the Market District the evacuation is
complete
good remain Dethrone The
Pretender there it is the bell
tower right let's
go you don't have crabs coming up your
toilet
honestly it would be a welcome
surprise cuz I like crabs they
cute oh I saw some video of some crab
like somebody picking up some crab on a
beach and showing that they're not
dangerous at all even though they look
maybe frightening but their grab is like
really really bad what kind of crab CRA
was that what did I see maybe you guys
saw it any recommendations
too what kind of crab was
that it looked
funny so many
legs coconut
CRA horse yes Hors Sho crab where in
Grigg's name did you come from empor and
like it legit looks like a horseshoe
like it's so fun
woo very
fascinating
no uh where are they dead
oh they look really gross they look like
J bugs
yeah but they definitely don't have
as much power as a horse does in their
horse
shoe Intruders lay down they have blue
blood oh interesting is there any healer
here no ah that one on the back no oh
did I just make him join the
fight hey
stop P yours
to
yeah oh so many so many let's
go let try oh I didn't even know I was
doing that in that
moment weird animals they're both weird
and kind of creepy but also kind of good
cuz they're very curious and not
dangerous I've never seen a crab like
that before where do you find the
horseshoe
crab
and why was there a need to clear up
that they're not dangerous are they so
common people get scared of
them the beach yeah but wi be wi
Beach hor Beach this one northeas andn
American
Coast
really
a
[\h__\h] get
him it's used in
medicine and then I watched
video
about sand dollars I think that's what
they were called which I've seen an
animal crossing before but I didn't
realize that was a real thing and oh my
God I I
regret learning about it because those
kind of freak me out you have many of
them those are
pretty no when I saw that they their
bottom like it moves when it's
alive that kind of freaked me out you
know
this
one all yours to it's like tiny tiny
baby tentacles not really but you
know now to okay I used everything I
got Stand Fast you're not used to his
death we can
win from one stagger to
another
she
W damn feels good feels good a SE dollar
is that what they
called I legit didn't realize that was a
real thing I don't think I've ever seen
one of those either but now I'll keep an
eye out could they could they appear in
the
mes oh wait you stagger
oopsie realized
it's just
chilling you see them all the time
you're all
right they're all over Florida damn all
these cool things you can find in
America they're like oysters or clams
but nobody eats them though
right damn it they so weird we have to
find a way around oh what kind of animal
is that anyway it's not an animal it's
just like what is
it what what family does it belong to
see urchin if it's alive it can be eaten
e only if it's
alive so you eat it
alive ah I thought so yeah yeah it's
kind of like a starfish
mhm
M so a
starfish
that's so weird though such a weird
[Music]
thing hi potion hi potion Stop In The
Name Of His
Highness now
to that's the strangest creature you
have
seen
yeah
IRL I don't know have I even ever seen
anything
strange is this theend well I can't
remember anything right
now I probably have seen some St strange
[\h__\h] but don't remember do we get it to
see it now
no you'd think they fly around a little
bit above the
buildings but they're chilling on the
ground I kind of don't buy
it yeah yeah ah a
dagger
no a
potion who goes there in the prince's
name None Shall Pass you shall not
pass wait I want the
no
hey this dude he really wants to
protect his his leader and I understand
that but I cannot I cannot I have to
fight I don't know what I'm fighting
against very obviously but I just I just
got to fight it's a
principal nice
try for no particular
reason just the reason that you're
attacking me but if we only just talk we
would know that we're on the same
side so stupid that it makes you really
think really makes you
think get him so many
misunderstandings
over
here I am not going to heal I don't want
to heal I don't want to I don't want to
heal come on better already
nice get him staggered quickly quickly
quickly
quickly get
him that's so easy to dodge
[Music]
man all yours me misunderstanding corner
for
me I would like to think that I don't
need a misunderstanding Corner
hopefully I can communicate well
enough with everybody to not have enough
misunderstandings that I'll wear for
misunderstanding
Corner let's avoid
that
misunderstandings poor Dron suffering
from animation lock since 2010 what what
Whata what what what that sounds like a
final fantasy
jerk but I don't
understand enemies on the rampart K oh
it is
really
oh you know guys I saw uh I saw there's
a aier Risa or more like aier no I think
it was ater Risa themed Cafe that's
going to start in
Japan and I might be able to go to it
but generally I checked out the food
that they have and like most of it just
looks like like pretty basic food and
just the name that they put on it is at
related but there were like two or three
food items that do look like aier
specific food so I want to check that
out there's a there's a pa pa ice cream
paet with like jelly a bunch of blue
jelly on top that looks like a
puny py
py that's pretty
cute and then there was a a sandwich
fried fish sandwich I think with like a
I don't think it's edible but there's
like some print on top of the bread that
makes it look like a book so the
sandwich is a book and that was uh I
think a reference to the to the little
boy character the magic boy forgot his
name can you see him
anywhere that was like about it maybe
one more thing the other things don't
seem that interesting
oh
B Bahamut was a dragon
wait no Bahamut wasn't the
dragon is this is this
bam it must be one of the dra's pets
it's just a normal Dragon right this one
I mean a normal is pretty strong but all
right it's not even aiming what is it
aiming
at what who whoa
w
n what an the way it flopped on the
ground to offering its body to me what's
going on I don't know I don't know what
I'm fighting the head ideally okay white
dragon
oh
Yi guess he was like mostly aiming for
Jill maybe
interesting am I not normally
the the target
for the enemies
like the aggro
[Music]
Agro oh I'm on top of him yours
to
oh uh almost almost missed it oh my
God where am I go go go go go go go go I
don't have time for this use up all
during that cutscene of the deadly
Embrace does it use up my my cool fire
thing get down get
[Music]
down it does the [\h__\h]
okay camera is weird throughout this
whole fight and kind of hard
to get to this enemy
but oh so far so good though oh
sack all right let's go to the Head
maybe the head takes the
most
damage know if it makes a
difference
20K
SI I think has something in store for us
oh get ready to
move uh oh oh I
I
okay oh no get out of there a that's
better please don't do that again ever
thank
you no what is that what is
that holy [\h__\h]
um [\h__\h] [\h__\h] in
and
kill
oh
sick this
one go
to oh thank
God almost get him almost deadly Embrace
time ah
[\h__\h]
nice
there it
is deadly take
down this one got to make use of that
time
go nice try wa like only the last one
ever gets close to hitting
me get
him
attack ah now miss again this
one hey why do I
[\h__\h] over
here why did I say why did I ah why did
I why why why
why get
him
uh-oh this
one what is this
camera no I will never
understand get
him
turn attack okay 50% and now we have
staggered kill 50% HP I
mean
now I get in a bit more kill since it's
giving me the opening this
one what was that again I yeah oh oh the
laser
o what
the where am
I
what
happened I like healed once but then I
got quickly hit by them like immediately
after okay
whatever death
bubbles that's the only trick that he
has that like really is dangerous for me
what it set me back so
much to
e well at least I got so
heal why can I never Dodge that I swear
I'm trying to and I feel like my timing
is get him
on
accurately over
here
go oh and no I want to get out of it's
too
late
s ni
try nice view this
one
this
one okay okay
[Music]
okay feel like I'm in Jurassic part but
with dragon
attack C down coward
dragon
go oh no I hate this I hate
this can I just run away from them
endlessly yeah yeah yeah yeah oh yeah
it's pretty good pretty good just run
like
freely this one nice
[Music]
try too slow oh she didn't see you
coming
go no no no no no no no no no no no I I
hate that I hate that
uh sorry I was focused on something else
now now now I'm going to going to go in
I'm going to go all in this one did I
miss the 50% deadly Embrace better
[Music]
already
kill a I got it okay over here guess
it's just been all a while
attack come on
stagger no time to
waste
[Applause]
all right all
right
okay what are we
doing okay we're doing the this this
little
game please
please
[Music]
oh oh oh oh present time
wa are we out of the loop I think we're
out of the
loop you didn't see my beautiful finish
oh man so lame why last time we streamed
Final Fantasy we also had
issues Mama
Mia
do are is everyone back have we escaped
the
loop oh man
cursed my streams are
cursed you saw me Dodge one attack 20
[Music]
times
now okay well I finished him I killed
him death Loop
yeah it's hitting all streams really
Gemma said just
me over here
CL oh it's not safe here what are you
doing Goods there you are it was all
strange for you oh maybe
region Regional all right let's get out
of
here oh what now is it UL is it I don't
know mother Crystal's
heart the hell is it doing up there they
have
hearts I guess that's what I've been
breaking right
oh wait you trying to destroy it Bahamut
Bahamut wants to destroy the the the
crystal what huh I thought we just
killing uh
[Music]
Ultima it will be explained
okay yeah do it what a Savage move oh
[\h__\h]
oo you do be Dragon I imagined him
looking
[Music]
differently what is that attack
man let's hope we don't go up against
him huh foreshadowing
much
Mega
Flare your highness don't do this what
why I thought you guys knew what you
were doing we must leave now your grace
I beg of you this is not what he wanted
Something's Happened oh forgive me y but
I must put a stop to this your grace
Something's
Happened so it really was not really
what they were going to
do
oh nice
Sky
Stars
oh wait is he attacking the city or the
crystal because like his aim is like
everywhere all over the
place
did he just get like
sucked oh he sucked
it cuz it's
gone he
didn't is it the birth of a new Crystal
so fast right away right there h
looks nice
but get ready soon you you said that 10
minutes ago or
15 so uh what do we do now then we
destroy the
heart we might come back as soon as the
Flames die down the Imperials and the
dalmex will move in this may be our only
chance and Bahamut has gone for now you
should get as far away as you can
guts what and Ne you slot in the ledge I
can't do that if you're staying then so
am I I packed everything up before and
made a run for it so if there's out your
need just ask out use need I won't be
giving it away for free Nana would never
forgive us if I did thank you
good hold
door
h e
oh he's my shop what can I do for you
gets tall the big hammer oh we can do
both welcome to the big hammer where did
you learn that did you learn it from our
blacksmith dude right so what do
I this is better this is with the stuff
that I just got from the dragon or what
should I make this it's
only now the Stagger is a bit better 20
I should make the purple weapon
regardless
why did I do it right I guess why wait
did I say to equip it
no finish
make both future I
think that's 10 times better than it was
before you have some issues with math I
see actually wait wait what about
here oh yeah that looks did that do it
right that looks
good oh H it's already plus
two and crafting in terms of arm
cloth no need for anything you don't
want me to make is our
else good luck Clive need
out I've got some good stuff for you I'm
not no not mocking him
purple next yeah yeah yeah yeah I guess
so
yeah and wait I think I
want uh potions
I mean I might die and just get free
potions but is there else you need right
oh here you go I'll just buy them for
now is else you
need wait if I get an alexir N they're
too expensive all done then but would
they good luck
Clive take up a spot like instead of
high potion or potion or would I get a
third spot
a first SL
okay well n it's that's too expensive
like who buys
that who buys
that let's go Jill Drake's tail is right
there
Clive it's time to free Storm from the
crystals
curse oh right I have like uh need a
moment to prepare like I can use the the
tonics and stuff too right
shut
up oh yeah yeah I mean I can put the
strength
tonic
here tat maybe I'll use it in the
upcoming fight
um what were we saving up
for
one
of what what was I saving up for hey I
could upgrade the the Raging
fists have a th now increases attack
potency I do use this quite a bit
besides
that oh goo
goou allows assignment to any icon e oh
really but I don't know why I would
assign it to any other icon I think it's
fine where it is if that's all it
improves
then limit break up where was that this
one oh 2,000 yeah that might have been
what we
wanted all that's a fourth limit break
[Music]
go
oh
oh wait where's
my where's it
Zoomies the fire
Zoomies a this is it what's what do I
get for the this master allows these
these things just lets you assign it to
any
icon maybe that makes more sense like if
I get another icon and for some reason I
just want
the I just want
the the the thing but I also want this
and then you know I don't
know yeah yeah makes only makes sense if
I don't want to use the wind icon for
example but like I think everybody wants
to use the wind icon because of deadly
takedown unless there's something coming
soon that replaces it
but I don't know you know what for
now
I'll upgrade no wait that's also
Mastery no never mind
then then what about the
upheaval no wait that wasn't it the
Earth and fury
4,500 for Mastery
sheesh
[Music]
M I don't want to master anything I can
do
wait why do I not hear
sound whatever I don't know so I'll just
go Drake's tail is right there
Clive it could remember and I dare say
we'll be seeing him again before the
night is done mhm feels like it
Toco has something to
say what did
he just wow wow wow
wow
oo no more
roads we'll have to find our own
path philosophical do you feel that
Clive what
e whoa do we go in there
jump no just what we need another flood
it's already turned and there's no
reason to hold back oh wait so these
are they're like H are they affected by
The Ether cuz they're so
dirty all yours
tole no
nice yeah they're
zombies oh
y
understandable Titan kind of sad music
going on too
now oh it's like I don't know taunting
him you lose it's not what I wanted to
do okay tole show me the
way is that the way to a good boy a good
boy oh was YouTube a little bit weird
Again
YouTube being nice nice
boy uh oh no
oh
no
yum over
here all yours
to yay I didn't miss it oh it waits for
me nice good
but for how long all yours to oh oh nice
nice nice nice I didn't even see that it
was about to be
staggered now
[Music]
to yeah we like to see it we like to see
it new enemies
approach oh wait this one's still
alive too
[Music]
slow f
seconds oh hey hey hey hey I was reading
a
comment would you please
wait out of
fairness over
here all yours
tole oh wait to kill oh did I just miss
the timing but like it was immediately
gone I wasn't an attack
to
not
[Music]
good better give me some potions back
after
this there must be a way to climb up
what what what
that okay you guys are not the
distraction these enemies are the
distraction
oh some
accessory but it's for um a thunder
attack
so not really my
[Music]
thing wait turn around no
okay excuse me I want to talk to baham
oh oh
bro wow he's so pretty Phoenix yeah
wow so pretty compared to Bahu
damn what is he
doing keeping the H
[Music]
occupied Joshua
Joshua don't Clive it's too
dangerous [\h__\h] hold on Joshua I'm coming
who dangerous if we Morp then we can
help we have to save him and we will we
just need to keep
moving okay Jill
okay I mean I feel like it would be
faster if I just Morp now and fly over
there not
now this one stay
down did you guys see I saw some news
about House of the Dragon new trailer
not really officially out yet but like
being shown
somewhere this one and I don't know if I
ever heard about it before but it says
that the release will be early summer
[Music]
2024 early summer I don't think I
expected it that early so I'm
excited early summer is basically
spring what could early summer be like
June may even maybe
probably June
right
[Music]
okay Eight Episodes that which sounds
really
little but got to remember they're all
like an
hour wish they made more though DN hate
episodes there he is
Joshua I'm here brother wait what's this
about
GTA6 he can't hear you a trailer Joshua
in December
okay I did just read
something before the stream like really
quickly like some someone's saying oh
GTA 6 I'm like what what what what GTA 6
is never happening what are you talking
about sounds like you're just making up
things
great wasted my
attack
[Music]
[\h__\h] don't know what's going on
right
now 10 times bigger than wait what what
does the trail say when it
releases
no not the trailer I mean when does the
when does the game
release come
on what did I just accident no I
accidentally took a high
potion I pressed the wrong
thing
no you know what that means I have the
right to let myself be killed at the
boss fight right in the
beginning unless I get a high potion
back until
then
[Music]
[\h__\h] just a quick Revival to get
potions just beat the boss faster I can
always buy from Goods no
am I still going back to him before a
big fight and see normal potion but I
want a high potion I want everything I
guess oh The
Undertaker get him w n n n
n now to to
kill oh I didn't think it would be like
a circular attack okay I thought it
would just be in front of him so I fail
save surprise
surprise I don't think we or I do think
we have fought this enemy
before might be wrong but oh now to F
[Music]
turn
guys guys guys guys
guys get
him
nothing nothing nothing
nothing oh
what
what ible this this little bastard go go
go go go
recovery oh je oh my
[Music]
God come
on kill the spects fast cuz they're
really annoying no good
oh my God almost
died why am I so un tanky right
now no good oh my God can someone kill
the [\h__\h]
Spector only has one HP
left I guess that's a
no
now
[Music]
go God
sake we
done that wasn't even like a boss
boss you didn't get a special
[Music]
screen I feel like I I in like tails off
for example your teammates are more
useful than in this game like it it
doesn't feel like they do significant
damage you know what I mean I think in
Tails they do are those the counil
chambers it's kind of lame like what do
you have teammates for if they don't do
any significant
damage and not even their heels are
meaningful did I forget an item here
making
sure
mhm meat Shields also no because they
don't get the the
aggro a they just look nice IE candy I
guess
[Music]
um El Le is
healing he'll be all right Clive he's a
survivor he's a
Survivor I saw mum played the imemo
Mushi game again last night
right and before she played it she wrote
in our Discord
oh
Ultima this no wait what the heck is
this money it looks like somebody
doesn't want us getting any closer I
don't care what it
wants neither do
I yeah she said what is this
necrophobe what is he scared of dead
people
attack too
slow
but she was like Hey if anybody wants
I'm I'm going to going to go play a game
that like really is Rage inducing more
than any other rage inducing game she
said so if anyone wants to join me nice
Dodges so far I haven't be VC and you
know it was it was time that I would go
to sleep so I didn't join but I was like
are you perhaps talking about IMO Mushi
like I just came from playing IMO Mushi
so that really just sounds like em Mushi
to
me yours
tole it's actually it feels a bit harder
to dodge with that stuff
on
cuz when you don't get it
right it doesn't feel like cuz you don't
get stack you I don't get staggered or I
don't get interrupted in my attacks
so I'm not sure if I really just dodged
or
not too slow but when I do Dodge it does
also tell me
huh
anyway pretty good so
far
go
pretty good so far right all yours
to okay I'll give you that I'll give you
that oh what the
[\h__\h] what was
that nice try
Okay first time I see it and I still
dodged it
that's it this
one
nice SI that's better maybe some healing
oopsie take
this kill
oo I
drco
onic do you see anywhere like how how
much longer you have the tonic is there
any indicator of it being
active yeah thank you J know I know it
no don't get an indicator
great
good I like the things the way things
are right
now pretty good pretty good pretty good
run
waken Kill ah okay wo wo wo press the
attack which one I don't want to know
what that is we just any attack it says
press the attack what does that mean
what does that mean what does that mean
Bow B ra oh is it is it one of those
days what what what what what does that
mean just go all out any attack it said
press D attack
right that's so confusing I hate when
these kind of things happen uh
uh
ah whatever [\h__\h] it take the
damage all right
y energy swirl how much more time do I
have start the death in oh would there
have been like three two one I did
it a
sh it was this no get out of
there
oh there's so much going
on you guys probably can't see [\h__\h] okay
okay I have to focus again cuz uh I was
doing so
well now I don't know where all that
skill went there there it is there it is
it came back to me oh wait ah no cancel
no no no I missed
it I was in the like one of those long
attacks
it's okay we don't need
it we don't need
it too slow too
slow oh oh W I have no idea how I did
that
Dad
iuda okay he's wakey
wakey oh
oh I made it I made it I made
it
oh
oh [\h__\h] oh oh it's okay that's
okay oh yeah baby I like it I like it
this is how I like it more more more
more more more more more more
more
oh ah this this is the first time I
didn't dodge it okay okay I dodged too
early okay okay it's okay I'm using all
my potions but we're doing so well no
death no
[Music]
death
oh W went through
c and a few of these goes and then we're
done easy
clap nice yeah yeah good job good job
waa thank you thank you thank you the
fav of Earth increases wind wind up
damage wind up which attack is that I
don't remember
do I even have
it can beasts they're getting stronger
yeah what the hell was that we can think
about them
later right now there's only one thing
we need to focus on don't tell me I'm
fighting Bahamut after this he's on my
side Mr
understanding but he seems to be acting
weird so maybe something's controlling
him
uh I used all my
potions can I actually go to guts and
buy potions now
or can I like call him
here
Goods no okay then I might have to die
purposefully unless they throw all the
building now it's worth a try but they
normally don't after these big fights
they maybe give me like two potions
back one small one
big it's really
greedy so
greedy who's ready for the best
boss
quiet there's someone up
there boss I just defeated a boss and
used all of my healing items
is someone
there
ah [\h__\h] it's
you what happened here he he tried to
take him from me H oh my
boy my darling don't worry it's fine
really darling
boy is this the child you made with the
emperor oh he's mad why mother cuz she
loves why do you betay you have no
right answer
him we took you in Savage show some
respect for those who raised you um
you're not giving us any respect
either honorable elwin always thinking
of his precious Homeland but what worth
is a Homeland in a world beset by the
blight father did not seek to protect
his country he sought to protect his
people a Leader's duty is not to protect
his people it is to protect the source
of his sovereignty the noble blood that
runs in his family's veins so long as
this bloodline remains unbroken what
does it matter of a Nation Falls one can
always found another unlike him I did my
duty I preserved my line I bore a son of
the noblest blood to whom the whole
world might kneel that is why I gave
r that I might join my line with the
lares and birth a savior of this bited
land blessed by both Bahamut and the
Phoenix you sold your country for a
child why did you need another you had
Joshua I had
nothing you were always your Father's
son so very strong and bold and daring
and yet you failed to awaken now you
have what you have a we josua had been
granted a tenth of your
strength
how the Nobles laughed that elwin's
firstborn was surely the son of a
concubine and my own not long for this
world the shame of it the shame of being
slandered by one's
inferiors how could you ever know how
that
feels it should have been you why didn't
the Phoenix Choose You Joshua's every
waking moment was been trying to
shoulder the burden that you and the
Phoenix and the Dutchy foer on him
that's why I became his shield to help
bear the weight but what did you do you
betrayed your own blood and surrendered
your son to his fate
W
Joshua my darling
boy I never meant to hurt him the
soldiers orders were clear he was to be
spared why did you survive when the only
one I truly cared for
died
what have you not looked out of the
window Joshua is here the Phoenix lives
on he's battling bamet as we
speak does she not
no
oh what she lacking critical information
here
now she can throw away that other it's
useless
child
sorry Joshua josy
wasi wake
up
so calm down I'm a shield of
roseria no
and I will do my
duy oh are we having one of those big
fights oh oh he just walks up to him
menacingly brace yourself oh my God best
fight but we just had a really epic
fight like last
time
if
freit C
Joshua
[Music]
Clive like a
Starship like a
youu Mega
Flare do I have to do
something no maybe
oh
wa
why am iine so
small the Phoenix also why is this one
so
big why are we so
tiny it's not
fair
[\h__\h]
R1
[Music]
oh oh oh it's
growing it's
opening like a
flower
ooh oh
oh that is so
pretty nice mother Crystal Renovations
we just got rid of the old one cuz this
one looks so much nicer what a
flex that flower yeah true trust bammed
then the
heart it will always protect the city
from Sun H how do you do this fights
again
oh never mind I know I think I know oh
wait he's chilling I thought he was
getting ready for an
attack nice oh another
one at least I have the fire flights are
the healing right what what what what
what what the five flights are the
healing items right for me so they
basically gave me free
ones [\h__\h] I'm um I
suck e let me Dodge I saw that
coming I have a shield
attack
oh Joshi wasi healed me
Joshua finally a useful teammate
man leave my brother
alone
oh you've learned spit
flare spitting is one of the most
insulting things you can do to a
[Music]
person isn't that
funny Clive has learned the ability
split
split spit Flare from Bahamut R2 and
triangle okay
okay oh it's like
uh yeah we shoot it from far away spit
flare 2 extended exposure to the flare
will cause enemies oh I can do it longer
oh cool how long can I do it they become
partially staggered canceling any
initiated abilities maintaining the
flare for its maximum duration meanwhile
will result in an enhanced finishing
explosion
oh so like they show us when he does
that attack we might want to use
it oh like now how do I aim it though oh
like this okay I can't get it
ah
mukashi but I guess that's fun what the
[\h__\h] is he doing what is
that okay okay
okay come down
oh Brimstone right that was a thing
too but it shouldn't be used the way I
just used
[Music]
it will josy heal me more often are he's
still flying around he's still hanging
am I like Invincible basically uhoh H I
can't I can't get out but I dodged it oh
he's attacking too uh okay I have
nothing I have nothing it's
okay am I invincible and like basically
anytime I need healing he'll heal me
when I get to like a certain fresh
[Music]
he
nice nice should we test it
out oh oh
oh oh I did that by accident
[Music]
yeah B if he does that attack now then
I'm kind of [\h__\h] okay let's let's see
how how the how do you use this
Brimstone
again ah not in the yellow not in the
yellow just out of like sheer reflex and
logical thinking because of Rhythm games
I keep on putting it in the
yellow next time next
time I had to
remember I had to remember
I
know
nice damn what a damage
spawn
nice
oh is he
doing something
new cut scene
fight [\h__\h] can't reach
him uh Phoenix don't do
this King
flare
no it's okay brother it's not
okay oh
music Giga flare unlike Giga
fter
[Music]
share am am I
dead I'll come back for
you
how new system embodying the Phoenix
again uh fire charge okay pretty volum
use l while holding
Circle ah okay to lock onto multiple
targets release Circle to launch a
volume of
uh does it like Auto focus on it on
them yeah okay
whatever aim aim dou hey what the [\h__\h]
hey wait can I focus on him I don't know
how ah stop it my
God that's pretty uh pretty generous no
Focus but pretty
[Music]
generous oh
w
woo this is so
confusing was it's pretty
[Music]
cool did I get him do I get him I guess
when it says charge flare there uh okay
so
how go okay
what's
that oh my
God who heals me if I'm the
Phoenix I guess I do have like fire
[Music]
lights your highness stop
this please think he's out of his mind
out of
[Music]
mind so anyway I started
blasting or should I what is
this go oh that's not how those work
okay I guess I'll shoot them
normally
okay one
[Music]
down okay he took them back I
think stop
please
oh
no I want to I want to use my charge
attack let me let me use my charge to it
keeps me so
busy woo where is he
going
away that's all I heard now thanks to
you hold the red
star I saw it again
[Applause]
[Music]
oh I got him I think no I missed one no
whatever
oh uh wait
uh
ah
got Dam
it and the big one can we land it
yes everything's a Precision
Dodge
shaving his HP down will I have to go to
zero or am I going to be interrupted
again Kingdom Hearts segment
this I can't tell cuz I
found those things are drawing in more
ether than I've ever seen cuz I never
played it oh dear e should I not be
doing it like this is this is
ineffective uh did the too team also
help out with this
game is this ineffective can I use the
laser
okay okay
okay
not
hold
oh I understand
though
[Music]
yeah he does not
care ah
[\h__\h] ah back to a
bro is he
there pass bton pass Boton
touch back to
iFit yeah yeah yeah that's what I
thought don't you
oo CL Thank The Flounder Thank The
Flounder looks like a birp like
that it's now or never Joshua
50%
oh gamb Phoenix
CH hi g
m wo W he's doing all kinds of spe
W oh no not this oh I'll just I'll just
[\h__\h] I thought I could Dodge
all right now it's my turn uh
okay did I did I do it right now I feel
like now I did it too late but I can't
[Music]
tell oh my God stop
it no I hit the red I
swear the intent was to hit red at least
I loaded up maybe too
much thank you
brother is this good does it feel
good should be
[Music]
good stag it again oh okay here's my
time that I swear that was
red I don't know did do more damage than
usual oh good stuff good too late what
do you mean Oh you mean the red in
between the the yellows I thought the
red after the yellow is fine too you
have to spe specify then you have to
specify you just said red is it the red
in between the
yellows oh come
on you never SP the fight dad you little
shits
oh that get behind me uh in inside the
circle you mean right okay I'm
in Yeah
[Laughter]
by this looks like
Yu-Gi-Oh
oh oopsy
sorry I'm trying I'm trying I don't know
if it's enough uh my vum is not so
strong
today you just said
red
a can't believe it guys can't believe it
how many misunderstandings are we going
to have about this damage thing
oh
no
okay
ah it's okay we have
plenty
oh uh uh yeah uh wait wait for I forgot
I for what it's not working how do I do
it again whatever I just
dodged what this what's
this
ah good work
Joshua M look at that that HP going down
and me not doing anything anyway we we
we combined our powers though that is
pretty cute
oh
oh okay that didn't do
anything oh
oh H yeah
[Music]
well
we're not done
yet wait here I'm
coming ah
[\h__\h] too
early I just want to get it once just
one
no I don't think we'll see it's
day
uh oh maybe uh ah [\h__\h] no I I
panic let's just do this oh he's not
taking damage he's not taking damage
this is this is
fake ridiculous
oh it was delayed
damage they want to end it on the cut
scene I get it I get
[Music]
it
oh let's go josi
wasi he's got like two more
HP yeah together we
[Music]
strong I did that I went there
mhm hug me
brother
beautiful look at these fire Brothers
Bahamut defeated so I'm getting Bahamut
is he like dead
[Music]
then I liked him I don't think he should
have
died maybe he didn't die yet
[Music]
but oh we did not get an
item
he's if we don't get an item him oh he's
alive
oh what
no or the crystal
heart is he drinking the Ean we have to
stop
him
no didn't
[Music]
work ah
man Jill can you help us a little
bit are you all
right I'm
helping Dam it you have to be stronger
than this she eating
popcorn show us your true
power I'm we going to
PE would be so cool if we feels cuz
we're both
fire
icons are we going to fuse are we
fusing got
[Music]
got how did we know that we could do
that when did we learn
that flounder
flounder have we I can't
one this may be enough in in we can do
it
CDE we can and we will together together
[Music]
[Applause]
flounder flounder power flounder
power are you ready
ready IR one IR one IR one no we don't
even care okay no time for R1 just speed
through oh I
pun he's got a full health bar again
iFit
ryen
T this is the epitome of T right do I
say that
correctly enhanced versions of most of
effort abilities are available for use
in addition to Wildfire iford Verizon
also access to Ability light speed
which uhhuh
uh-huh okay cool how can we hope to
match such Power by how can hope to
match Power by trusting our own
W oh uh yeah
W am I light speeding ah there we go
oh dear I don't know what's going on man
it's kind of hard to tell where I am and
if I'm in R and kind of
crazy that's good that's
good just go fast zoom zoom zoom zoom
zoom zoom
zoom
H that is the sound of the deadly
Embrace although there is no deadly
embracing
now I want to
use where is he I can't see
him where is
he was he
Invincible oh
[\h__\h]
my God the chill the [\h__\h] out
man oh he's almost he's he's almost
[Music]
there no no no no no no
no yeah okay can we get this
ride
yes okay I did it ride all right let's
go oh wow first
[Music]
time oh w w w w he's screaming got to be
careful when he screams
oh 1 million
damage
sick can we can we add uh too to our
[Music]
GTI
sheesh it's
only oh this like pretty
[Music]
cool
I don't know what's going
on he's always so
far I shaved shaved me a little bit uhoh
what what
no I still got so much HP
man
okay I think I got it in the red again
pretty close call
[Music]
but all right and now he's halfway
down okay
okay shooting in the wrong direction
friend let's try
uh
let's try this
again where there there there there
there there there
there oh yeah okay now we're
talking good Dam it e
down what is this Orchestra okay that
was too early have you guys noticed this
beautiful orchestra
music I didn't mean that part there was
like this specific part that
sounded oh FL Celestial flounder
[Music]
[Applause]
flounder press the attack
oh which
one wait wait wait
wait
[Music]
I'm on it I'm on it I'm on it I'm on it
I'm on it I'm on it I'm not even taking
damage it's
nice Fring teror flare ah we can't no
no
uh take this
yeah did that do any damage on him as
well or only on the Terra flare charge I
wonder Radiance oh
oh hey not fair not fair not
fair not
fair they're having a fair on
nuts will there be almonds and pachos
too I want to go to the
spare
[Music]
enina would be proud
right oh [\h__\h] that
hurt I want to do this let me do it I
say I want to do it so let me do it
yeah he he's not even staggered but he's
just letting me do it very nice I
appreciate that for your
[Music]
cooperation
ooh I canceled his Ora burst my
Brimstone yeah I know I totally did that
on
purpose all according to
kikaku
wow it's like a meor
[Music]
here good morning
[\h__\h] what in hell ah come
on
what how how bur the
world
how Z not
flare this part not today come on Joshua
that part
the I like that part of the
orchestra this is
[Music]
now okay okay
okay I can't
see somebody got
[Music]
sunglasses
sheesh 4 million
damage
oh
nice wow but I don't know I I'm not
happy about defeating
Bahamut like will he go back to normal
like is he dead or or can we
still chill with
him
uh um
oh
reverse
mustard
is
that Ultima scream or what who screamed
me want to
go hot single mother Crystal
smashed oh
interesting meet up
now te old
mustard
Joshua
a my
brother I I'm sorry oh a I'm so
sorry you're
alive we both are nothing else
matters I never dared hope that I would
see this
[Music]
day
Jill reunited at last
useless
[Music]
Jill oh you're going to make me cry too
talky
[Applause]
walkie
is
that that
real this is for my father I Ultima is
like um deceiving him
right or was that really Ultima the
sun cuz that's uh the way he disappears
is very not
humanlike
that was
[Laughter]
alol does she know that like did she do
a pack of the devil
[Laughter]
basically was it always just a
puppet how how how does that
work it is done the demon that would
tear our house of part it's no
more father she never
knew and yes yes it was always a puppet
a but it came out of her room
right so did Ultima infiltrate it once
it was birthed or the mother Crystal
it's collapsing right we need to
leave no wait I will see
what a hero I owe him a
debt great dude great
dude oh I'm sucking in the power
wait was that what I wanted to
[Music]
do what that was not what I attempted to
do right won
it
reinfor our situation report captain
could be can nothing be done to call
them
off I regret not your Radiance the draon
answer to none but his Imperial highness
the council is powerless to intervene we
heing reports of
Rebel throughout the neighboring
District Focus all efforts on
extinguishing the fires around the
capital city
wait can they shut up daddy man
go I want you to find
out by the
Light Dion bard you taken leave of your
senses call off the drons at
once fear not the populace will come to
no harm at their
hands I am here to save you
father save me a creeping Darkness hides
in the heart of
SRE it stems from your wife the
traitorous Annabella this is what
happened right
before we like or when we were entering
the city
right roof jumping not another word
Dion father though you may not see it
the darkness has taken hold of you it
has made you forget
yourself but I bid you remember there
was a time when you ruled not with
cruelty but with
compassion why now do you turn your your
back on your people why now do you seek
to stoke the fires of
War you too have borne witness to this
change your
eminences and you know as well as I who
is responsible for
it a puppet now sits upon the throne but
cut his strings and the master loses her
power what ton you bear steal before
your
Emperor Gods take
him
huh for every citizen Who falls another
can be Brad H for every home that burns
another can be built those were your
words but when the last of your citizens
has fallen and all of their homes have
been reduced to
Ash
what will become of your Empire of its
rulers of your
god of your flounder as the mother
crystals crumble one by one and the
blight sweeps in to claim all that we
hold dear our people look to their
Emperor for
protection yet he labors not to secure
their Futures but to seize what is left
of the twins for himself
even if it should come at the cost of
everything his loyal citizens have
labored to
build
Dion you must
understand that's really intense a small
price to pay is it not oh you've been
blessed with great power Dion enough to
win me the
world so go claim valesa for me
brother
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
no how could he move so fast as his
Lance what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
no
go
Gods
no father poor father how he doted on
his
children that he would die to protect me
was plain it was but a matter of
when you planned this
you did well to endure so long but you
broke in the end as I knew you
would and now muor approaches muor put
him to the proof I would see if he
breaks go
Bahamut kin
Slayer K King k King King
Slayer yeah so it was like an order
but King Slayer is that not literally
what they called um brother Jame wait
Jamie it's a long story right
which is funny cuz they're like they
look
alike I know it said kin but he also
killed the king his kin and the King
Cann stay here mother
come take my
hand why is he so nice Mama
Mia is she also control get away from me
yeah no she sees she sees dream just a f
dream she is she okay you not take me
shadow you will not take me yeah she
sees something else
right oh my
God
no mother
hey
Shadow so was it Ultima was Ultima
controlling her too at least like now
seems like she was always kind of
evil
but oh oh oh
oh
oh oh
oh uh hope they all evacuated
Consciousness that weaves your Wills
together you think she just lost it
Consciousness that blurs the boundary
between your own will and that of
others then we shall set you apart once
more damn damn the ties That Bind you
shall be severed and Humanity returned
to it proper
place what is he
saying by Primo Genesis shall a New Age
of Reason
begin what are you
doing
relax your
majesty
oh
sometime
later
I wait
uh she should be dead
right don't you want to
play it's been a long
time if that is your wish another men
puppet you are as Meek as all the
others
[Music]
such feeble
creatures everybody nak
you gifted the power of icons yet slaves
to fickle emotions which Usher you to
your
doom and so you bind your fr agile
worlds with strands of
Consciousness The Wretched handywork of
a wretched
people the sons of fire were United at
last and for but a moment their flame
burned
bright soon muos shall become our
perfect
vessel and then shall the world be
remade not before the bonds are
severed of trust of respect of
love only when every strand of
Consciousness is cut away May muthos
return to our
side by Primal Genesis shall all be
undone mankind shall be rid of his
wretchedness
and muthos of his will but while he yet
clings to it he has the power to forge
bonds a new and so we bid
you find
muthos and S
everyone to destroy that which has no
physical form you ask the impossible
there is nothing your Black Blade cannot
cut
Odin we we shall Unite with muthos and
bring forth a new
world so long as our vessel remains
unclaimed by
Humanity it shall be done Master my will
is
yours vessel unclaimed by Humanity does
he mean with us
or
cute
Mommy Mommy
Mother no mtima mommy
Ultima oh a lot
happened
yeah
muchos
happos kind of crazy [\h__\h] going
on we have one mother Crystal
left and the
turtle
time for a
snack I'm eating white chocolate
duplos how is your
brother asleep since I return from the
Dominion T says he should be back on his
feet soon enough for a while at
least can you something on his chest a
swelling circled in
stone the
curse a for
cancer for Every Mountain we
climb another Rises up to greet us
doesn't
it
it's never
ending oh Ultima cancer
ah oh yeah did we bring tya over
too
oh sorry the key girl is calling me one
moment
[Music]
okay
um
ready
huh mhm okay
so yes yes yes yes
yes oh I accidentally activated the
voice message
okay okay back to
story even the sky seems to have grind
tired of it
All Things Fall Apart oh
no M wait so what is he
[Music]
dead wow we get
wings to begin casting a Mega Flare
mhm what you say guys is it useful
should I like switch one of my things to
Bahamut T won't be happy if I disturb
Joshua while he rest I might as well see
what otter has to say that would be
nice sadly really isn't nope yeah op
[Applause]
useless mixed opinions did you see the
pair that got hauled into
tires so what do I owe Diana well for
dear maybe I'll try it out and see if I
[Music]
uh looks fine
El G flare really good wait so Giga
flare
is
um is that just basically another like
attack that I put like on triangle or
whatever then if I master it I could put
it on without using the icon lost its
appetite
right
mhm MH
mhm a giant laser finisher attack H
Master his ultimate for sure it's a
special abil not the R2
ability ah it what eh how what how how
do you use it
then very expensive to master did you
see that
wow yeah mix opinions maybe maybe I'll
just not use it are you making them
skies in recharges
this we should call back the scouts oh
I'll I'll shut up I I might give it a
try but I don't know
Oto how fair is the realm I don't want
to learn new things anymore oh she's
just fine
as long as you look past the fat storms
at mother crystals I'm quite happy with
my set up right now but I'll give it a
try and gaav Gaff he's with your uncle
in the free cities helping mid with her
project send an ow there way the moment
the winds turn foul a turtle still
wearing on a reply
though do you have any good
news well that depends on your
definition of
good all right
fine what do you suggest we do am I good
on time I wonder I'll live the scheme
into those more suited to the task but
how their own thoughts on the current
state of things could be that they
attacking for me it certainly can't hurt
to ask I suppose not
yeah no I'm not limited I mean but I
just mean I hope I'm
not going too slow you
know do you want some lore jump let's go
show me the map how is it that every one
of your little excursions presses some
inexplicable catastrophe shut up I'm
saving the world you to blame for the
Dominion's
fate no one could have predicted the
actions of the Crown Prince I'm sorry I
couldn't save your
home my countrymen are stronger than you
think a few toppled clock towers won't
break their
Spirits they'll be back on their feet
feet in no time oh is she from the place
that we just came
from look at us blw with in a pair of
bug crabs tempting though it may be
suing will not help us find a solution
to this mess sorry for destroying
found I don't know but I am certain
we're more likely to find it if we first
examine the
facts oh no no no
[Music]
beneath these darkened Skies fear and
confusion rain over valesia mhm oh the
lands around the Fallen mother crystals
had already begun to wilt for want of
ether but not like this crystals that
filled Wells and fueled
furnaces now nothing but pretty shards
of rock and those that hang from the
people's necks cast n a glimmer of light
to keep the dark at
Bay it is only a matter of time before
the common fault convince themselves
that the end of days is upon us
apocalypse yet I fear a swift end is
more than we can hope for mhm While most
of the world thirsts for ether the
remainder drowns in it spawning aashik
in droves and amidst the hordes of
mindless beasts with Magics as like to
fail as
function even the strongest Nation would
falter Rosaria and the iron Kingdom
Teeter on the brink of collapse while
the tragedy in twins side has all but
paralyzed the holy Empire dalmia fares
little better rumor has it the ministers
fled the capital after the fall of
Drake's family no I'm still following
leaving their beloved Republic to
crumble wude meanwhile moves in earn
erest the in haar has been sighted off
storm the world in short that's the only
thing I didn't
understand it would seem our
civilization was nothing but a castle of
sand to be washed away at the whim of
the Waves a
ship audience
ship a castle of s
I can't not my best flourish but it
seemed fitting the reports I've received
are considerably more blunt in their
appraisal without the protection of
their Nations it will fall to the people
to defend themselves against those who
would take what is theirs which is only
ever going to end One
Way defending a farmhouse against a band
of Chocobo thieves is one thing but
pitchforks and Palisades will do little
to stall an Army's Advance should the
king of w you DED to invade there would
be none to stop him but
me none but us that's what I'm
saying now he just
leaves understand enough of
that going to chitchat with
[Music]
harpocrates Titan is better because of
blocks en counters but since you're not
using them maybe baham is better for you
oh you mean I should use bahal instead
of Titan I I could do that I
could depending on the skills that
Bahamut has if I like
them I could consider getting
rid of the other one
mhm let me guess you're here about the
skies is there anything you don't know
lman it doesn't take a court astrologer
to argue the obvious as for what has
Disturbed the heavens that I believe is
a question the Fallen might be better
place to answer than
I and on the sixth day did the gods tear
the Sun from the firmament visiting
Darkness upon their prideful Sons and
Daughters what but I dare say you
remember your childhood lessons on the
sins of zis only too well no you think
they're
connected that Ultima was one of the
Gods responsible well God he has
certainly exist IED powers that we
Mortals would associate with the
Divine there is nothing Divine about
him but he wouldn't be the first God of
whom that could be said now would
he yet for all the fairy tales that tell
of the sins There is almost nothing in
the way of actual historical accounts
had I the Journal of moss the chronicler
I may have been able to tell you more
but alas I fear all remaining copies
have been lost to time you will forgive
me I hope certainly
not because there is nothing to forgive
even without this journal You' provided
us ample wisdom wisdom and we will
always be grateful for
it perhaps will be more inclined to
share his thoughts when he
what really loud really
[Music]
strongly is this what happens when you
turn on a dser my dser doesn't do that
the doesn't go that
far let me
see
uh dser
dser
DS I don't
even oh this is this is the DSA uh
turned really really really really low
this is the DSA turned really really
middle this this is the
DSR can you tell like when I'm changing
it the s's get
louder and
quieter seems
snake you blame them danger noodle speak
with uto AO uto Auto auto from the
but it doesn't turn into an
F don't know does this voice actor
actually have a
list
mysterious CL we have a problem only one
that would be a first it would actually
there are three we had as many owls
arrive while you were at the shelves
Martha's got a cash Gates and talk of
monsters roaming the eels outside of
North reach has put the wind up Isabel
and lot and don't forget Dill lubor says
the village was raided by Bandits when
it
rains it [\h__\h] PS The Curse Breakers
are spread thin taking stock of the
damage in the Dominion and even if I
could get word to all of them I doubt
they get here in time to make any real
difference which means there's only two
people who can me chilling
let them know we're on our way
surprise two people and one
dog by the way did we leave uh our our
hold door
behind did we just forget about him
imagine
K I just remembered I'll go here first
and I'll I'll uh use
the the new
icon
[Music]
uh oopsie I'm stupid uh what houses work
again here Bahamut channel oh there is
still space for two more I
guess
interesting so I have 1,900 points uh
which one was
it Giga flare right so this one 2,700
just to get the skill so let's say we
get rid of our
beautiful uh raging
fists and whatever else I can get rid of
this
one Earth and fury I really like that
one
4,400 points though
nice oh the rest is like fixed
okay now I can afford a giga
flare
uh no hold should I get this one too
then I
guess what is this summon multiple light
aspected familiar that attack any
enemy even only 100 points just kind of
sounds like it doesn't do much
damage impulse is a good
[Music]
one what is that that's like a troll
attack summon multiple spheres of light
that upon striking in an enemy deal it
continuous damage but if there's like
two enemies like there I don't have to
focus on them do it does it just go
automatically to some enemy I
wonder here I can upgrade it too the
number of hits inflicted by the
beam okay so when I'm uh when I stagger
someone I want to use the Giga
flare what is this again wings of light
begin casting Mega
Flare oh wait Mega
Flare isn't this the thing you guys uh
but no this is this is maybe not doing
stagger something I want to use but just
like just in
[Music]
between you have to charge and
wait you FL strongest attack okay that's
the special skill if you equip B do oh
I'm so confused you know
oh the length of the casting determines
the potency of the spell now
okay
so here let's switch to Bahamut
turquoise and they give us this but we
want Giga flare impulse we can
keep yeah looks fun looks
funny wait so the big one is on triangle
right I hope see it takes a long time
but if you Dodge comp appears much more
formidable than your
uncle wait what you charge up Mega Flare
it takes a long time if you dodge an
attack the counter goes up by one what
counter up to a Max charge of
four
so if I dodge can I dodge while charging
it I'll see when I
okay should I be wor
married you haven't been introduced Jill
Clive has told me much about you all
lies I'm sure your Stoler said that Dam
has a bandit problem is this just filler
again any idea the oh my
god oh dead body let's just say we've
yet to reach a consensus and at this
woman oh God
F suppose we just follow the shouting
then I don't have to feel bad for
skipping the text Yoo yooo
yooo let's just zoom through it shall
we cute you wouldn't talk like that if
it had been your men whose throats were
slit Blood for Blood it's the only way
we hire mercenaries and have them Mount
the bandits heads on our walls and what
happens when those we're better off
using that coin to buy and you cannot
fill empty belly but what happens when
they that's enough any more of this come
back yeah I have a trip coming up
YouTube makes it unwatchable hi is it
again like what Victor my last my last
final fantasy stream also was like this
what the H [\h__\h] haven't we had enough
fight why yeah have the next time those
two what the [\h__\h] man Sid and Lady Jill
fine for EU fine for na what brings you
here I was about to ask I
was like first the big
loop uh
lag and now it's just like lagging
without me really knowing at
all man it's not as bad as last
time What Would S be
well what it it's so
[Music]
sad me skipping no no I'm not skipping
any time I don't know what you're
talking
about oh I can my pickax I I can choose
which one to recruit I am I am just
uh you know I'm I'm playing normally but
the
stream must be the YouTube lag yeah
sorry I'm really I can't do anything
about it I'm actually having full
conversations I don't know who to
recruit Conrad your own City guard
with you as Captain wait who's the one
with the girl I didn't see the lady when
I went over
there Mommy oh I have to talk to both of
them anyway ah God damn
it I have father I had to
choose oh man YouTube
lag all
right but you
got guys can you hear me are we back it
appears I have no choice but to do what
little I
can are we back is YouTube
okay shall we go down to their
headquarters and like have a little
chitchat with them is that
necessary seems Seems stable now right
ah thank
God we're back a
pleasure show those Bast
again I can't
believe
not convinced our roles in this ruse
were entirely necessary now it must be
stable I don't know Conrad seem quite
taken with
you oh oh you okay let's hear what
Victor has to say hope you guys can
actually all don't I'm
told this is so interesting the rest my
friend the city shall fight yeah
together together Stakes I I thought the
friend
we yeah very
[Music]
interesting let's
go
slay the women folk have come to welcome
us I'll take that one he's all
yours how does this
work what
oh like
this
to okay I
see it's like the attack that I had as
if
R farewell that wait that was actually
the the the other thing wait we want to
test the wings of light
right sick
oh there's a
counter
so too slow like this so I just
like let them attack
[Music]
me who is Max and what now what do
that press it
again they mean to overwhelm
us
oh get him
[Music]
ow should I do that
uh generally not during a stagger right
during a stagger I want to do Giga flare
right
oh I hate that you're so annoying you
little
[\h__\h]
be
yeah it's over this
one
[Music]
he still got
[Applause]
it ah how do you get rid of this like I
killed the one who casted in on
him now okay just maybe some fancy
attack so if I use it
again just got to wait for
some too
slow can I also attack during
it anyway now we have the two charges
right and if I upgrade it I can get up
to four too
slow oh damn he's a strong
boy what's going on
what's
what I don't understand there was some
slow motion and then he was up too high
let's
try
wo he's getting trolled so hard oh my
God it's like really annoying mosquito
don't flying
around oh uh well I don't have the laser
ready
so I'm Invincible when I
laser nice
try you have this one let's do
this
enough
gargling Overkill you think so that's
why you only use gigle flare during
stagger what what why the town's people
could they have held out do you mean
just like I don't hear anything this
this is why what do you think this
situation we should
hurry
ah cuz if I uh if I do it uh outside of
Stager time they move around
okay okay okay okay
okay
H conr the
plan come
now
H why does it always hit the
conversations okay we're down to this
one right next we help out up here in
Mara's
rest they could just say go kill the
bandits at the start for real for
real so we end the stream it's too laggy
yeah I don't
know it's really hard to deal with this
lag
Martha and you
Martha what do you
think
y the Flames of
War do you think there were as many as
Martha
says what are we uh killing this time
hurry to the Fallen Gate oh it might be
easier this time seems like this one is
actually sending us directly to the
problem abandoned us
Ste let me help you
guys Wawa to the front
to war we
go you guys good stand back behind me I
shall protect
thee upgrade wings of light oh I guess
cve oh no who are they evil Tori
waries and the plants that I didn't
water
oh
[\h__\h] he it didn't huh do I have to do it
again ah okay okay if I get hit
once too
slow have to recharge it
done ah it's going down no
no wait I have no potions either
come on no no
no Heal Me Heal Me heal me I [\h__\h]
around to
L over
here
hit
me a damn it I have to dodge
properly
oh it's not even worth it now I could
have killed him
already
attack this
one
attack go
I don't think this is how well how I
don't get
[Music]
it oh wait that was too I was trying to
attack too
sorry good
work
farewell are they still bringing out a
big boy enemy after this
attack
this
one no seemingly not charging can be
done in seconds of consecuted yeah but
if they're not attacking me
then these men don't have the
sheesh you are wa did he
[Music]
take going to get a massage in Japan
let's
go I know it's shocking to me
too yeah
must we'll
worry we done descend the
lift wait seems like it's not over
yet can I buy potions
here how
do please give potions thank
you thanks very much there you go I
thank you kindly sir for helping
me while I am being back one what this
way bad dogs while I am being Baka being
hit by all the
mobs what did they say okay uh they said
but wait there's more please go kill
more otherwise we are killed instead and
I was like okay sounds nice sounds good
I'm on it
I look like me
Lord behind
you tle owl
damn it do
you are you with us aade always wait to
our duty wait is fighting with us he's
such a fan boy okay
uh bring it
[Music]
on attack
me one
more
okay yeah bye I know I'm dying
again
still 100
mfps what does that mean why is this HP
not going down all yours wait that's so
[\h__\h]
up doesn't that work during a Parry what
was that
anyway nice
try tanky
bastard a
well just going back to what I know
what I actually know how to use it
uh but now I kind of need something
more this one I've got
nothing too
slow should I do
again wonder if it's worth it when
there's only one enemy on the
field yeah that would have been laser
time I know I know I I used it at the
wrong
time new enemies approach all right all
right welcome to the
party too
slow oh oh oh wait oh wait no he's not
Ah that's a 50%
stagger oh it charges on its own after a
while too
okay ah
[Music]
[\h__\h]
okay whatever what I was off I don't get
get it I can't go
on I didn't
see I didn't see my
HP
[Music]
no they don't even revive me there I
have to walk over there again my
brothers Turtle well I was doing a
tutorial is Turtle short for
tutorial I was still learning how to use
that stupid attack
man
Squire that's not lag that's just me
skipping because we already saw all of
this before
didn't
we upgrade the wings and well can't do
it now right damn
it tutorial turtoise oh can I actually
wait I
can uh oh okay no I
can't no my potions
ah uh ah it didn't save me buying the
potions
bunk
oh
I have no words but
shame shame on me anything cat your
right it's funny though it's quite
[Music]
funny There You Go much
[Laughter]
obliged then I shall upgrade it
now what did that
do what did the upgrade I'm just adding
another Mega
Flare all right all right all right all
right yeah this fight is harder than
Bahamut already died twice at this
Turtle what's this turt is it an icon a
turtle
icon the turtle could defeat all of us
the turtle we shall bring the turtle to
the battle against Ultima how about that
then we are what Invincible oh I need to
keep an eye out so
wait tle cons solo Ultima yeah I believe
in the
turtle look at this
chuner guda
[Music]
[Laughter]
I forget that I don't start off with
full
HP oh
no I'm all the time I saved with lagging
for the dialogue I'm losing again
because of this
Turtle what are you
after I don't even know anymore man much
obliged why does it not heal
me I have to do this again
too heal now dogs
alone no oh I can heal quickly in the
fight if I'm aware of
[Music]
it died threee times on
the I died free times on the turtle Lord
Ros free times on the turtle
[Laughter]
look at the turtle do you think we can
hold it's so ready to kill me
again okay I'm ready to heal I'm ready
to
heal that's
hey okay bring it
[Music]
on
I'll show you who's the boss
now too
slow nice try yeah the boss is back wait
that's the 50% the 50% Dodge yeah yeah
uh not Dodge whatever you know what I
mean ah the key
[Music]
girl
uh
okay okay one can only hold that she
dropped it in the right
box turtle go oh wait
H
okay Now's the
Time wait where is it HP oh there it's
it's going it's going down it's going
down I would say that could be
better
what's all yours tole
I don't
know I don't
know I don't know if this is really more
efficient than my usual ways what which
I am used
to oh it can't go to four now oh yeah
right right right
[Music]
uh too
slow whatever let's just finish this
attack turtle
wartle
go
to
y yeah maybe we just we can just Master
this skill ignore the
[Music]
others it's safer though since you focus
more on
dodging I'll give it a few more tries
but I don't know if I'll keep it
[Music]
make for Ran's
ride
oh do we go
up consider if you find it fun or
not
m
I mean the the the one my dogs the the
wings I feel like they're more
for like fights of many
enemies so
maybe this man's going to die one should
switch
[Music]
when uh you know you're up against just
one big enemy like a boss just PCH me up
as quick but like resk in each time cuz
that one's expensive everything's
expensive reskilling each time just for
[Music]
that hey oh so now would be a good time
to use the
Rings they're headed for the rest let's
see how much we can charge it Marthur
and the others won't be
ready attack me
don't make me lose it
now okay tou Dodge so Mega
trophy oh [\h__\h] I'm
ding over
here attack that is such a meme
reverence this
[Music]
one cuz I did the maximum possible
Dodge
noise I thought we were done
[Music]
here over
here AIC choco ball poor choco
ball
they're not attacking
me whatever I'll use it
early oh I feel bad for them man all
these innocent animals and innocent
people getting hurt
get him breaks your heart this one uh
yeah the story in general at the moment
pretty intense I like
it it's pretty like surprising too like
stuff
like the mother being like I I knew at
some point she would die but I didn't
think she would die at at her own
hands that was
unexpected
something's coming thought my game broke
for a
moment apologies my Lord yeah it doesn't
hold back it's brutal only the first
round so wait shall
we I like a game that doesn't hold
back [\h__\h] I needed that
[Music]
I don't want to die I don't want to
die to be honest my Dodges get worse
though
because I'm so scared of dodging
wrong that I dodged too much
go and then don't Dodge at all attack in
result over
here all yours
tole you know what I
mean
yeah that stagger went down fast I was
watching
it I know I was using it at the half
stagger point
but why not in that moment it worked no
I think that was the last of them but it
won't be long died three times in the
turtle yeah well you guys don't even
know that turtle was the most powerful
icon of them all
yeah Turtles are known for
being crazy powerful you know what did
you find out this it's the you know some
worlds are built on floating
Turtles a guardian
scarf oh
yeah this
[Music]
world okay enough of these fillers
now but we have one more filler
Quest I'm doing us all a
favor eight North reach in its dilemma
what dilemma can I help you with nor for
each first we find Isabelle a bloke
saying he saw ghosts on the far side of
the wall I saw it with me own eyes the
of
Isabel she's in there guys I feel like I
had a lot of tangents to tell you but I
can't
[Music]
remember lots of small ones but I forgot
to write them down these
days
H where are me tangents we were there
with
it tangents
denied
tangents more R from the C
tangerines
the two soldiers were carrying your
favorite what you don't mean it right
you're joking
right if it really is then I won't skip
Madame please half the Garrison's been
slaughtered by those things we lost the
captain this very morning we've tried
requesting he immediately goes back to
skipping
it was a
open oh
yeah oh
[Music]
dear should have brought Joshi with me
so he could heal these
people my
family you favorite
NPC but painful at least we have an idea
of where the THS might be now we should
head for more before we could even
draw
okay this way you have a plan we need to
find can I jump over
here can I exit here yeah it's shable
time it was all they could do to
escape I just left Cho it's been a while
is is buo ready go kuo in Japan again
right now I'm like so confused did she
ever go
home run like the
wind I feel like she's she never left
really I mean except that one time when
we had uh the ID collab I wonder how
long she's
there
but I don't think I would really be able
to set anything up because
I all already filled my schedule to the
brim and any like remaining free time I
want to use to practice my dances
probably Clive look I see them with
me show me show me what you got ah
[\h__\h] same SL
same yeah
okay almost
four this this really
wor get him oh [\h__\h] why did I H sorry
that that was like reflex but yeah why
not use is it why not have some fun I
can't turn that
[Music]
far well I guess I understand now what
uh somebody meant with with Bahamut you
don't even have to do anything you just
lean
back he does seem to have those kind of
attacks a
lot
mostly
[Music]
oh come on no
no was that activated at three now or at
zero
it wasn't fore
okay
o see I'm like so much worse than combat
because of this stupid you icon I don't
want it I don't want
it I'll take Giga flare that's all I
want
kill yeah I don't want the I don't want
the
old maybe if I'm really bored
but see if I don't think about it I'm
I'm good but
or not but I'm I'm generally
good
[\h__\h] I feel C oh I I don't like how it
doesn't make me Invincible the Phoenix
shift when I like Dodge through or like
Zoom through something I want it to make
me Invincible
okay that would be my request
thank
you actually
well kill still got some time for more
now yeah it
doesn't too
slow
W kill sexy carry
baby JD is in love
attack good work did you get that one
did you get that joke did you get it did
you get
it 32k no I didn't notice I don't look
at the numbers don't have time
squabs
squabs maybe I should rewatch
squabs do you think there are more
there are always
more it's funny cuz we're in
more are they making a pun
too trying to one up my pun game didn't
you rewat it recently no not at all not
at all I wouldn't remember when's the
last
time you have
the scrap is always yeah but I don't
want to OverWatch it so maybe like once
or twice a year Max but I have many
things to rewatch so honestly one time
per year should be
enough once per year I must
contractually contractually obligated to
rewatch girls Arrested Development parks
and wreck the
office maybe Game of
Thrones and a bunch of others at least
once
all the
classics
community community maybe not so
much it's
surprisingly not like I like the the
first Seasons but then I don't like the
later
ones
mhm they just kind of became Moon they
they started to feel kind of ridiculous
to me I think I don't
know did you see that I would have liked
it more if it's just kept the same kind
of humor and
whatever was wondering when you turn up
at Al from all our friends thanking you
for your timely intervention how is it
you always managed to arrive at just the
right moment look any word on the rest
of the
realm let's see Storm's still crying out
for
crystals the nations are still in chaos
right Clive we knew this was now's now's
thank
you scrubs scrubs has many seasons many
many many and also has of course the
problem that there are some bad Seasons
at the end or like one Bad
season good place I was the good place
yeah so it was not sylvesta but Olivier
who served as ultima's puppet now we can
when Dion learned of this he sought to
slay the
fiend only for his father to take the
spear that would have freed him mhm
enough to drive a man to Madness Small
Wonder he hasn't
stirred I would be afraid to
wake had I but reached out to him sooner
warned him of the threat Alam opposed
but now both an Empire and her prince
lie
broken
Joshua what do you know of
Ultima bring it very little I'm afraid
the L tell me despite my best
efforts 18 years ago as I lay buried
beneath the rubble of Phoenix gate it
was not death who came for me but
another and it was while in my rescuer
care I first heard of timer I've been
chasing his shadow ever since what if
the girl is Ultima Ultima is driven by
some deep dark purpose and for whatever
reason it would seem you are crucial to
his designs he will stop at nothing to
have you even if that means toppling an
Empire but why me what possible use
could I be to such a creature
you put on heads now answers that have
but what if it's true me yet I am
certain of this it is Not Mere chance
you were chosen for a reason of
course cuz I'm the best all dominance
carry within them the might of an
icon nigh Limitless power that is at
once acutely
limited I wield fire and only fire m
and I only
ice eight wardens for eight
elements but you Clive you're special
boy you are different you're special
you're special H your abilities begin
with the Flames of
epit but they do not end
there I am a cloud can even exist goes
against everything we thought we knew of
dominance perhaps Ultima has been
waiting for one such as you whose
potential is truly Limitless I'm just
uploading everybody's powers on my cloud
I ENC counted that thing several times
now if it or he is you say need to me
easy you guys could do it too why hasn't
he claimed me as he did the
boy were I to hasard a
guess I'd say the two of you are somehow
incompatible CL properly attuned to your
body yes his mind
mind awareness Spirit call it what you
wish but I believe Ultima to be an
embodiment of the
concept is why I struggle and fail to
contain him here inside me avilable
today inside you
cool with every setting son I feel my
strength wne and though the Phoenix's
Flames mend the prison I have made for
Altima oh they do so at a cost that's
pretty Co the end we must find the means
to bring an end to him before I meet my
own what were you
thinking it was that or let him take
Clive and I've always had a soft spot
for my brother but that doesn't mean you
should sacrifice yourself to save
[Music]
me
Joshua Clive it's it's
gav oh wait that was just Army of aashik
at the gates of
canver
yeah wait so where is the girl that was
always of Joshy was
she just abandoned her now we don't need
her anymore or is she Ultima well what's
the short of it it's all TI told you the
capital of the three cities is under
siege by an army of monsters
monocities the city guard are doing
their best to stem the tide but numbers
ain't on their side what of Lord Byron
and mid were they able to escape no but
they're all right for
now they're hiding with gav at
midship okay we have to get them out of
there the ship that I haven't seen yet
alsoo prepare a stolas tell gav to stay
exactly where he is
understood Vivian what's the swiftest
route to the free
cities that sounds like a question for
the map no look here this road through
taba should provide the least trouble
okay good it's a different way of
showing me so doesn't block my brain is
exactly where I'm bound Joshua bed is
where you should be
bound what a coincidence that's where
I'm going you don't think I told him the
exact same thing were Tia not such a
talented healer I would surely have been
inclined to
agree but thanks to her ministrations I
feel I may safely rejoin my attendant
who was to wait for me in tab if we
became separated ah the girl all right
we travel together that is important
Clive if he stays close to me he'll be
fine pretty epic theme right
now I'll look after him
oh by the way I wanted to upload the
retrospective uh music video on Monday
but I
forgot I genuinely
forgot so I'm uploading
it the day after tomorrow
probably yeah and I also I still have
like a cute short that I want to
upload I also kept on forgetting
about not exactly forgetting I was also
waiting for permission from JMA to
upload
it but
yeah no not the Japan chart the Japan
chart I think I want to keep for a while
cuz it's not really like time specific
or
so I think I might keep it for the for
January
cuz I don't know we already talked about
it right so after the moldes I'm going
to go on a
break M my is going to go on a
break so now I think I should
be collecting stuff to upload at the
time so I'm keeping that short for that
time m is not the break no cuz I'm
streaming
then there's also a break but I'm also
and doing work but I need a I need a
time where I like really don't look at
my phone and stuff I
guess it's like a dream the four of us
aren't walking like we used to enjoying
this are you gav and the others could be
in danger as we speak oh shut up I think
that's like I'm sorry yote is a fine
Scout if canva was attacked she will
already have begun gathering information
tab isn't far we should pick up the pace
what fly Ambrosia he got mad at Joshy
wasi but I feel like you know his
sentiment is toally ruins to cross
understandable assuming they would allow
it the echo have a will of their
own people are dying Joshy
wasy wait
item
bye-bye not wasting my time on
you have something in my
[Music]
eye steal so oh is this a dead
end nice curve took a
ball did you check for weapons ah Maybe
maybe
not wait after the Bahamut Fight yes
tell us about y Joshua I think so strong
will but not after the mini Quest the
the pH like cve but with better
manners sorry are you trying to tell me
about this girl and I keep on
interrupting it with
fights
[Music]
well it'll be fine I'll get to know her
on my own I don't need to hear stor
flood they're everywhere now this thing
we can't go around it then we'll just
have to be
careful but we are going around it what
do you mean we can't go around
it
caution
brother thank you I was making a point
have you been to taba before there are a
few places I
haven't okay we were forced to get off
goodbye Cho have I been here before
where now
Joshua there is a residence just inside
the city Gates She awaits us Within
no yeah okay I haven't been here are you
buying or selling I'm thinking about it
oh yeah cuz I ran out of potions
again anything else come again what a
nice voice this Merchant
has I do like the voice acting in this
game very good voice acting what who are
we looking for
oh
here plus Quest there would be one to
improve your potion stash in the camp oh
really
[Music]
now now I started this so maybe
after
that is as terrifying is Ultima don't
you think
weird wait maybe she really is
timal what if she's my Lord Marquis it
is an honor okay never mind maybe not I
am yote Knight of the undying charged
with the protection of his grace Joshua
rosfield Keeper of the flame of the the
Phoenix
H long title of course Jola it all makes
sense
now would do you care to
elaborate the undying are loyal servants
to the jcal
throne or more specifically to its Heir
they have served our family for
Generations albe it from the
Shadows since their Inception they have
been tasked with the preservation and
enactment of of the rights of ancestral
communion after the events at Phoenix
gate it was the undying who delivered me
to safety why do I not have one of those
and since the day I left roseria yote
has been my constant companion and
protector without her sword I would not
have survived my journey across the
realm
a rise lady yote I'm in
air just just you saved my brother I owe
you a debt I can never repay it's true I
have g i but did my
duty come now tell us what you've
discovered Your
Grace it is as you
feared The Vessel we spied off the coast
of the crystalline Dominion on the night
of her
fall it was the inare
Y Beyond any
doubt the black gallion what a great
coincidence that we also have a big nice
ship Nowa is the royalist
flagship what business they have in the
Dominion upon learning of Wu's
involvement in recent events at dr's
Fang I sensed the malign influence of
Ultima and and the undying matter we
have reason to believe that the black
gallan weighed anchor shortly after the
fighting began and set a course due
south
for
Cana then it is wudan knites who besiege
the
cities what is left of them
yes and the Black gallion Sails at but
one man's
behest Barnabas
tharm the
rambling that's the only thing I don't
like about the voice acting but it's
funny are we truly safe here in the
agura the city guard have been paid if
that's what you're implying all the more
reason for them to
run well you are free to leave Lord
Minister markets abandoned warehouses of
flame blackened HS choking every port in
the capital canva is
ruined the real teach is on the brink of
all you can think about his
Comm forgive us we were not aware dalmia
now subsisted on charity quite how dare
you distinguished members of the oh I
forgot about him you must forgive his
majesty this intrusion haven't seen him
in a while what did you what is the
meaning of this S A trifle
crowded but I fear it will have to serve
My
Le he's got such a snaky voice very
well my colleagues do you not
see the king he has come to save us from
the
aashik
here's a gift from the heavens divine
intervention our very salvation and of
course if it is compensation he requires
we would be most willing to negotiate a
fair price for services rendered fools
your ignorance
Unbecoming correct me if I'm wrong but I
would swear that the fiends washing the
cobbles of canva would the blood of her
citizens wear the colors of
wude H so you do not deny it Gods Fetter
them and see our guest to the
dungeons this part's confusing me
enough oh that was quite a
reach pathetic
creatures that you should imagine
yourselves worthy of
Salvation the girl is still here
somewhere in the city her Consciousness
Fair dripping with her late father's
hubris a Consciousness to which muthos
is inextricably bound and inexorably
drawn see that he is made
welcome yes your
majesty come you
thought
ooh M surely the prince's light cannot
have sated
you oh
no not
mid and GA
to neutral territor territory getting
besieged by army wud guy shows up then
he's helping how long as wud been under
Ultimus control interesting how long
indeed based on what we know of
barnabas'
actions I would guess some few years
mayap more but to what
end what does Ultima
want the tapestry show
them what do you
got
by the Flames oh yeah that thing Phoenix
gate Drake's breath and now here oh wait
now what is
it it is old ancient
even I now you know I was always
wondering we were always wondering what
it is that is maybe the GTI form of us
with our maybe with all our icons maybe
we end up gut tying with all our icons
and that's how we end up looking like
cuz it's got like several
Wings
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh and then we would be so
powerful that's what that's what Ultima
wants you think
M has it happened
before it remains of the faith it
represents save what can be gleaned from
the image
itself none could tell me what the one
in the otry meant even the
undying but I believe it may be the key
to Discerning Altima's purpose uhhuh
that is his purpose the figure in the
center the one beneath whom the icons
congregate that I believe to be Ultima
you think it's Al God or at least
Godlike his very existence beyond our
can oh but maybe it would be ultimate
their are meant to be his subjects and
while some like Barnabas have accepted
this role others have rejected it like
you Clive which is rather inconvenient
as it appears he needs you most of all
and gods don't like to be
disobeyed no I don't suppose they do
thank you good night thank you Clive may
I tell yote of the
lake
by all
means y I will be accompanying my
brother to the free
cities whilst we are a field I would
have you watch over those Clive has made
his
Wards to s m though well concealed the
Hideway lacks trained fighters to defend
its occupants should they be discovered
but it is my duty to as it is never been
my brother's Duty
remember if if that is your wish your
grace but please be safe if ought were
to befall you
I you have my
word
[Music]
H F Well my Lord my lady it was nice
meeting you we in your debt
y
underappreciated
lady
let's find our
friends
so Ultima wants me to get all these
icons
Powers but I also need them to be strong
enough to fight
him but I also don't want him to take me
me as his vessel it's plain she cares
for you very deeply and I her which is
why I had to let her
go opportunity beckons yeah he wants my
Clive AWS
system what maybe it's
gal look closer s
oh how fair is the search just random
well your grace my report shall be with
you a
long ah yes yote is otherwise engaged at
my beest and the duty of wardenship
fulfilled for as you see I've been
reunited with my first
shield I am sirel Knight of the undying
and bearer of the burning quill
charged with chronicling the Mortal
Deeds of his grace Joshua rosfield
Keeper of the flame of the Phoenix and
rightful Arch dukee of
Rosaria I entrusted sirel here with
overseeing the investigation into
Altima's Origins findings from his
brothers and sisters a field are
delivered here to be cated and cataloged
just how many undying are there not
nearly enough my lady yet we are glad to
give our all in service to the f
pH such is and has ever been our
Creed I
see you have your Associates I have mine
but you may now think of them as ours
that won't be a
problem will
it the Phoenix is our son and we but the
Shadows that quicken in his
Radiance it is from the darkness we Ser
with him and now you are you saying this
to
narissa pray accept this
token Phoenix down for as long as you
bear it members of our order will reveal
themselves unto you if there is nothing
further no you are dismissed
you're interesting a conver then we'll
talk about this
later
what brothers s seemed very
um you certainly keep strange bed
fellows bed
fellows
calling what the free cities Under Siege
what you guys are confused too
huh good girl a figure of [\h__\h] fly
Ambrosia
H it's kind of a weird
phrasing if I were to say it you guys
would be like phrasing waa
phrasing then let us be rid of them and
panic
yeah Jo she was she was very active it
seems smoke is the city Fallen making
lots of
friends while we were separated good for
him
[Music]
um not looking so so
good yeah he's got a cult just like me
just like me
forever the free men are still holding
their own
then do we have any idea where gav and
the others might be there's a warehouse
near the docks where we agreed to meet
if there was any
trouble we should
hurry
did you guys like the not stream that me
and mo did
huh you guys behave very
well was cute
right I'm I like um the idea of streams
like that where like we learn about the
production of a
product I wouldn't mind doing more stuff
like
that you know at the they asked only at
the the end to like maybe have some
ending talk ending talk just really
vaguely talking about oh would be nice
to have that kind of chocolate or this
kind of chocolate and the um the idea of
us doing little
drawings there to really show like a
like a design make a proposal of a
chocolate design that was from me genius
right I think they they must have been
really happy to see some extra ideas
added by
me the a don't worry she doesn't mind it
grew back quickly but me and Mum
actually ended up talking for like one
or two more hours after that sounds like
thunder we talked for a while it made me
quite
happy even talked about like very whole
lot unrelated stuff which
feel like you're lit nor all just talk
about work related things but when I
mention this you
g good to see you any trouble on the
road nothing we couldn't handle I knew
you'd
come
cute is that who I think it is
yes allow me to introduce my brother
Joshua C's told me all about you how
even listening most of the time name's
midad doll but everyone calls me
mid my lady is he in love hey
[Laughter]
h
confusion M wanted girls talk with me
and Arisa or burps girls talk
my
[Music]
boyon it's really
you I never thought I'd see the
day josy
wases Uncle
dad so these aashik are being
controlled that's what it looked like
empty eyes eie blue glow no doubt they
were turned but silent as monks every
last one of them your man here speaks
true
Clive we saw more than a few in this
city they moved in ranks with a purpose
and not of their
own timus
doing
perhaps what of the city the people
dead mostly mostly but not all a handful
managed to lock themselves in their
Villas before the hord arrived some in
the merchants District to the west and a
few of us on the far
bank if the aashik stumble across either
hiding place a few bolted doors won't
hold them for long don't tell
[Music]
K we did talk about wanting to do
something
what do you propose of the Ian BBS Ian
speaking BBS we split into two
parties I will make for the merchants
District while you look to those across
the
river mind keeping an ey my
brother not at all it's like a we find
the villa and try the servants entrance
subunit under H and what of
Us Mid is she fit to sail the ship uh
the myth engine could probably do with a
few more tweaks
then you better work fast even if we do
reach the survivors in time they'll
never make it to the Hideway on foot you
leave that to
me I'm yeah I'm talking like as if she's
part ofon think I can manage that I'll
keep him safe looks like you stuck with
me Byron that's Lord rossfield you
little gutter
snipe she's a bban
she is you keep Clive safe a in the
sense of both of you just being a a toi
in h
life yeah I think of her as an extension
of
H even fall Nar never heard that before
all right
togle let's find those survivors more
more
survivors damn that it looks really nice
though that I stand a chance against
those things come and get
me save them no time to look at the
scenery oh come on you can get faster
through that that's just
fabric oh no they killed him they've
been
routed they're wearing Wuda
armor
attack
[\h__\h] no I want to do
it
[Music]
oh come on come on nice
try
no use
[Music]
it okay [\h__\h]
you
enough
kill sck
wa huh what was that was that not the
50% I guess
not who who
what you're
finished oh wait why did no it's why am
I using that oh
well why
[Music]
not I would say I got the most out of
that this
one
[Music]
hey too
slow saw that coming
[Music]
buddy nice fire
spinning but I am literally fire
itself get him and you shall die by this
flame over
here fire fire light the
WWA that's not what I wanted I kind of
wanted to look at the map but okay toy
wogi thank you what would I do without
you
potion I sense
trouble okay let's see I'm not giving up
yet oh that oh they have annoying
bastards oh
man
[Music]
ah I need to I'm too scared see that's
what I mean like I dodged too much there
you go that was a good
one just bring it bring it now
guda it's just bouncing off their
Shields
no no you little
[\h__\h] I can't help it it's a
reflex
kill
arise
you love to see it you love to see
[Music]
it Overkill always fun
yeah what happened to the Royal Army
beautiful there's nothing but monsters
here got to pick up the
items where is the
okay
[Music]
I'm getting them down more you think so
I don't
know Bahamut and if kills the bit
rate yeah this stream
overall in terms of bit rate is pure
suffering Mosa
in 2K
resolution oh
wow oh my God calm the [\h__\h] down why am
I always like one second too
late get
him why did I let him do that
H don't
know
what that was apparent get
him I want I
want
oh over
here not
now
too
slow you little
[\h__\h] it's over no more of these fun
games does that
hurt doesn't look like it hurts
much oh
your now
to get
him buy
boy no why am
[Music]
I come on uh today Wawa's skill has has
been so good in the beginning
surprisingly no warm up
necessary
hey
attack all yours
to showing a little bit of fun moments
today just a little bit too
slow
this move is unfair I
swear get
him
enough mama
here all my potions man all my beautiful
potions I know I need to go there I'm
just checking for items there
picking up his
ashes at least I didn't die to him yeah
nothing beats the
turtle oh my okay what is ah he Buffs
[Music]
them I'm too stupid for this
how how do that not count as a
Dodge cuz I'm not focused on the right
guy maybe that's
why that also didn't count
[Music]
really
there we go four baby the magic
number all right um to the Mage oh
attack all yours to that was all just
warm
up
yeah
[Music]
go you're
[Applause]
finished how convenient that it only
hurts people but not like buildings and
items you
know I can only damage
enemies also can't accidentally damage
talo
either M too
good
buy more
abilities I don't know if I want to
there's not like what what do you mean
which what these are fine oh wait I
already have 2,500 though
but you know do we want to master this
then we have to save up for a long time
I could upgrade
impulse more limit break limit break
limit break
H another
[Music]
one all right I
guess Thanksgiving what do you mean
Thanksgiving Thanksgiving that sounded
big was a while ago so you'll have to
wait like almost a full year for the
next
[Music]
Thanksgiving
oh [\h__\h]
no I didn't want to activate it I but I
had to turn it back
on oh well they're just weak ass mobs
anyway not worth charging so
much wait you guys should have
Thanksgiving yet oh I thought it already
happened I guess I was just a Canadian
Thanksgiving what
I this
one you're
finished hey I forgot it was that
late I guess it was November what
[Music]
go too slow this
one
gud oh oh [\h__\h] I I activated that by
accident I thought that was on the on
this
one
uh got him I got
him
kill why not why not we have time look
how slow he is now
to oh now he's staggered for real for
[Music]
real hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey
hey kill see if with this one I'm having
no issues skillful wa is back over
here
oh already already weren't you just at
50% this
[Music]
one
rud yeah M
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah ah almost almost
[Music]
dead this is the agura where the city's
leaders gather there may still be
survivors inside
chy where did he come from where where
did they get this kind of orc
from has to do when the Harvest starts
ah oh that makes so much
sense that makes so much
sense colder in Canada so Thanksgiving
is
earlier now you have to forgive me we
don't celebrate Thanksgiving at
all oh I'll keep what I have all these
accessories they sound nice and they're
fancy but
F where are
they we have
dest who celebrates that these
creatures does Ultimus reach extend this
far what the hell is going on here now
tole I'll go on a little
ride to
kill now
tole
going
go over
here I haven't heard that term
for a long long time and
D dank Fest yeah
yeah feeling think remember is
your what does he
want oh
[Music]
to this skill is just so funny to me I
don't know kind of
ridiculous
ah go is it just weaker or is it just uh
less
time when I do like a level one flare
versus uh level 10 H level four did you
know you can detonate
impulse I don't know what you're talking
about you've caused quite the commotion
oh armor but then I would expect no less
from you muthos it looks better in armor
that's for sure like his pants gave him
small don't believe we've been
introduced you were in my family's to
say and now you're here with an army of
aashik
THS manners Lord
rosfield they are men like you and
me orbe it one's
unburdened by the wills that drive Our
Kind to
Madness they are
pure they
are
Divine
Exquisite and they are all that remains
in this once rockus
city you'll pay for what you've done as
you
wish I confess I have been very much
looking forward to this oh pardon me
this Indulgence your
majesty The Vessel shall not be spoiled
he's talking directly to
Ultima how can you kill me without
destroying the vessel huh and you will
yield show me I want to see how you do
that or
not as long as you don't hold
back
like fencing
[Music]
almost Battle of
dodges oh
[\h__\h] she's doing it
[Music]
attack
over
here ah no no no
yep came out of
nowhere
get what was that this
one
[Music]
oh too
slow sick slow motion I love
it get
him who what was that ah he's he's doing
something he put some
like buff on me oh what it was it
counting I think it was doing small
damage on me nice
try
now
to wait I'll do the G Ultra whatever in
a moment
now and he's just standing
still
kneeling steel kneeling he's literally
kneeling steel yes is cuz he's out of
steel right now
looks like he's made out of
steel you will forgive me if my
performance seems uninspired what do you
mean it is just that I expected so much
more from our chosen oh really perhaps
this will Kindle your flame fun what now
a gift from my le Lord's
Armory
G all right all right watch closely
muthos
easy yes
yes there a goody it's turning him
on you like these Dodges
huh what a sexy vessel I am sexiest
vessel ever absolute Dodge master Master
Vader ni's try you got to try harder
than that oh oh [\h__\h] oh a Parry even oh
my God
who be still my Beating
Heart that was so bad it didn't even
count as a Dodge and that really speaks
bad things about you
honestly if I can dodge your thing so
easily that I don't even need to dodge
it you know what I mean I can just walk
away from it what did that say about you
wa well that was
new my lights are haunting
him let's try you love this vtu I love
this chicken
oh all right Giga
flare time to rub my
nose now
to oh my God I got so much
time D over here one is seldom enough
would you not de man's beer why is he
drinking beer now that's how you ride
beer in
German oh my oh my well I just dodge
through it easy
easy oh well that's not
nice can you oh
oh excuse
me what the [\h__\h] was
that oh my
let's go can we stop this
bastard this one we have to stop him
from playing all these
[Music]
games nice try
oh
go enjoying
yourself creeping yeah that is of
creepy creeping
Darkness all right all right
baby I'm gaming heart my par are on
point thank
you my DOD is too my beating heart
okay that one was
bad sometimes you know oh he did the he
put the curse on me
again stop running
[Music]
away don't
stop too slow
if you keep on dodging so well like the
whole fight is just endless Dodges it's
kind of
funny
[Applause]
mam kill not done m
m
thank you for
[Music]
waiting if he does that Circle shock
wave again I'm going to be so mad but
he's surely doing
it maybe
now yep yep
yep okay okay
okay not again not
again oh I got a couple ones
though nice
try
kill this
[Music]
one nice
try here
come on that's better
go get him too
[Music]
slow getting there getting there he's
almost dead over
here nice try those are
easy
the the jump clutch
yeah if it works it
works try he's so mad that I'm dodging
everything he's so
mad okay it's over I have no time to
waste it's over liia what a weird ass
name [\h__\h] I didn't give a [\h__\h] about my
HP at the end there I just wanted to end
him oh that's why that sounds familiar
the name of odience
horse oh so Ultima be riding him all
right sanguina that sounds like a
fish sanguina in Insignia after taking
up the mantle of Lord commander of the
Knights of the royal wud their army upon
sidus telon untimely
resignation s near Harbert served King
Barnabas for the better part of a decade
intriguingly however there are no
records of a house harbored ever
existing in either valder Mark or on the
southern
continent begging the question when
exactly did he hail what that mean what
this whole paragraph
mean that he not that he didn't really
exist
or what is this
implying the vessel is strong yes I
am
oopsie my
leash that was a strong fight I would
say from
me
it's only when he spams those jump rope
attacks it's kind of rough you're all
right as are you I
see we are yes I'm sorry but we couldn't
save them it was over before we arrived
can you do anything at
all well you did what you
could I flexed so hard too late I hella
flexed hard on him what's
wrong
nothing I
hope
um
what uh uh
run flounder
flounder what did the flounder do
leaving so soon MOS that's how you
stopped me just get rid of the whole
building it's the
king indeed clear you may kneel before
Barnabas
th Warden of Ash and king of
[Music]
wud get
back we're just warmed up let's go
[Music]
you want to you want to do it huh
Barnacle
[Music]
Man this looks like Super Smash
Brothers right now
oh we
are not a
match Tinder has failed
us oh come on
Clive wild and impetuous I expected more
of the boy who bested my Lord Commander
for real for real I see why my master
covets you so The Power Within You
Mythos the potential
oh he reminds me the way he fights
reminds me although it's probably is
everything the fencing style but he
reminds me right now of the guy cor
Stone of all creation who teaches AR
Lord's vessel how to fight your
purpose probably also the surroundings
my purpose to surrender my mind and body
to that
thing
the first sword of
braavos yeah
Serio no your majesty my purpose is my
own I made a promise to my friends to my
people and nothing is going to stand in
my
way you would allow this delusion of
free will to Bar your path to
Greatness truly your Val is a
cancer one that must be
excised I love this fancy chuni
talk
oh oh
nice try it
oh I forgot I could do
that burning Branch yeah
men I I could have dodged
that easy you are as weak is all the
rest he gave me a huge
opening [\h__\h] cutcenes
oh Jilly
wiie
hot she's so
sweetie o o this way hurry
is she going to try to fight him
now if Clyde can take him she can't take
him Al Elemental Reckoning they use it
as a crutch is that a thing waste we
know it's not a thing but maybe in a cut
scene it's a thing
uh-oh don't die jly wiie I just thought
of a nickname for
you
too was carrying the sword I didn't
notice o the ship Shippy
whippy chill Wily chippy Shippy
whippy will he be all
right the Phoenix can mend flesh but the
spirit must recover on its
own I'm afraid the rest is up to
him
this place is remarkable outfitting it
must have been no small feet but why go
to such
trouble that Beauty's Bell is filled
with wonders the world ain't ready for
if the guilds caught window what we were
up to they'd all want a
piece all
right and thought he was carrying a
baby do not blame your self he was
barely breathing when you brought him
here we would have lost him if it were
not for
you no Barnabas may have severed nigh
every senu in my brother's
body but he made certain the wounds were
not fatal n every
senu allow me your
lordship he do be needing I was thinking
putting you to the trouble like
that is no trouble carrying comestibles
to my alien nephew I know but
Comm you've already done so much for us
5 hours ago pouring your Gil into the
Hideway and now the
ship I don't want to take the
piss you risk your life and for what
some girl you hardly
know
why'd you do
it you not mad or
something I wouldn't go that
far cve you're awake my
boy all I want to do is
help the world won't save
itself it was
Sid
your father who taught me
that well you have like sounds like him
yeah so that seems like uh the estimate
was accurate dare do that again from you
guys the people said 12
hours [\h__\h] off the lot of them along
with the gallion with the King on board
no doubt says YouTube recently says that
a
lot I started 5 hours
ago chill didn't come back YouTube is
drunk what do you
mean she kept the king busy while the
others dragged you
out it's all right
mid jell is
fine how do you know the ether of her
icon
endures and as long as it does we can be
s certain she is
[Music]
alive we must pursue the black gallion
Jill will be with the King I'm sure of
it well good luck catching him cuz my
ship's going
nowhere it's the mythal engine she's got
kicked like a wild Chu bear when the
hole in half that aent you have an idea
it's something
else well of course of course I do my
dad have seen this com in a league off
Scottish if I had his all
writings if you had his old writings
you'd be sitting under a fuckload of
rubble the ones utto didn't save
anyway he might still have a few pages
in his
stores we'll have to hope it's
enough do what you can to ready the ship
I'll speak with Otto in your condition
you really are
mad perhaps but the world really won't
save
itself I just saw a comment during this
dialogue that I want to go into uh
yesterday when I was like you know
singing the English version of ly
[Music]
gami that was clipped and that's fine
but the clip did not like I mean I did
say it in the clip uh that oh I found
this in the comments but it didn't
include like me saying the name so then
in the comments of the clip people are
like oh she not crediting the Creator
and then turns out that the person that
posted the lyrics in those comments that
seemed to claim that it was their own
lyrics and I did credit him or who
whoever that person is seems like that
was stolen anyway from a cover so the
credit that I gave was inaccurate I
suppose because I didn't know cuz that
person claimed it to be their their own
but yeah in any in any case there's like
this
conversation uh about me not crediting
properly but like I I kind of did but
then that wasn't that wasn't part of the
clip where I said the username but then
even that was inaccurate cuz you know
the lyrics apparently were written by
someone else for an English cover not by
the dude that's I found that weird
anyway like that's why I found why I was
like talking about how it's so weird
that I find the lyrics in the middle of
the comments of a
comment uh hidden like why why does
someone put so much effort into writing
the lyrics to just post it as a comment
under a comment really really far far
far at the
bottom
yeah yeah yeah it was in the comments
and it said something like I could still
find it now said something like oh I
just transcribed this and translate and
transcri described it a little bit here
you
go that was too good to be
true yeah so I I I'm not claiming that
those are my lyrics or anything and uh
credits where credit is due but it seems
like I haven't been deceived and then
the clip is no nothing against the
Clipper cuz they did include the part
where I said oh I got it from the
comments they just cut out the the
username but I feel like it's still
tells you that I I I didn't know they
came from the like some
singer
yeah hey it says that really I don't
know must have misunderstood but yeah my
intention was not to like claim it for
[Music]
myself
just to clear it
up
but I think that is obvious all right I
cannot write lyrics said thatto might
know something to save my
life I mean I don't know maybe I could I
could try haven't really tried properly
if it's not
you yeah ra misunderstanding
Corner let's go
Rune Blade with the sanguini
Linguini no scratches is that a
shrimp I should make this one too not
bad if I do say so myself bloody
eyed don't waste my time you got the
stuff you can thank me later
H
[Music]
and uh what Excalibur what do you mean
feter actually no now that we should
should we should we do the the plus
Quest where is it I can't see
it I don't see a plus Quest only see
normal normal uh side
quest
[Music]
a plus and mids room ah mid dungeon oh
yeah okay going to Mid
uh going to get lost
probably he's a Sly Soaker who car what
are you talking
about I don't know what these mean words
mean z heard you were in cver fet
young I
did wait this
way what do you reckon we should do I
say we should just do you think mids
ship will ever
sail there's a quest
forging no need no
need alambic
sure this makes my potions even better
or or I can bring more
potions then I would be
happy the lag oh no the
lag you'll like what this Quest
does oh this way
use the hand a bomb
King are we in a Mario game Mario game
now I've been watching uh Mario Wonder
play through from Guess
Who it's
fun not am no actually
not maybe I'll watch the am one too
uh bomb bomb bomb man bomb
King uh The Croc
SRE okay so can I go there
now have I located it the cro some
bre where is the
cro wasn't some Breck
like uh
where's what
where I don't I can't help but that's
what it
said I don't know where to
go yeah like that's what I thought but
it doesn't I guess it's
uh
uh could it be
here well that's
[Music]
connected what the [\h__\h] is this to the
right of the dragon's area thank you so
much you're the best
is it written somewhere on the
map the right to the
right I'll just go there for
now I've never been there oh so do I go
through uh
here
oh let's go
[Music]
the right when you say the right
like ah maybe here but I how is that to
the right I'll go there
now it's
uh
confusing is that yeah to the left I
would say it's to the left from this
POV thank you though you guys are
helpful very
helpful my eyes are getting tired
man stream puv yay oh is it
here
oh
[Music]
o
nice
perfect for a nice walk for the forest
to my
grandma where a wolf will eat my
grandma this is just the perfect place
for that is this the CL oh it's the
CL The
Croc even in the shape of a
BMB oh I see
it
you deserve a rest do I like have to
kill it before it explodes or something
like
that it's in such a beautiful
Arena B rank what was the rank of the
last one we did but we have become much
stronger since
so
hey look what we have here greetings
your
majesty oh it leaves the the the ground
in
Flames over
here oh I I don't
know well I already activated it might
as
well charge
it w
here take it level three is
enough I hope at least some of them hit
it was that a 50% no I felt like I heard
something it doesn't even have a stagger
bar does
it oh it doesn't have a stagger
bar no
staggering
yeah good stuff good
stuff even without staggering I can make
good use of it too
slow oh what the [\h__\h] is going on I
don't
know full yours
to
yeah lots of fancy special effects
oh no time to look at
chat
to to
kill over
[Music]
here nice
try what I say I hate
you I didn't say
[Music]
[Applause]
that no I can't turn so far that's
really
lame what what is this
[Music]
what
kill now that was
easy I didn't realize these monsters on
the monster board were actually pretty
damn
weak I thought they would at least have
a stagger bar bomb Amber
ooh some of them are you mean easy your
reain is
over now to collect the ash oh I
should
probably this looks like the
stuff let's see if there's any
more stagger bar would make them
weaker depends on how you see it I guess
if a wi needs more than
this ranks that are pretty tough yeah
what was the rank of the last one that
we fought wasn't that srank rank ass
booty booty
rank be
oh no I don't want to talk about what
sorry sorry sorry not this lady two
dresses that need s those
uh no we most certainly you wouldn't
want the this is awkward is she going to
insult me again yeah
I'm not listening to
that Cole said it was an Army The Guilt
Trip how are we supposed to do our D oh
wait let me give back my my quest
first my senses lead me automatically to
the main
quest if Amber and Lazarus oh what do
you mean cyber Soldier mixing what do
you reckon we should do I say we should
just tell me water baking soda baking
soda I only hear like that it helps with
a lot of things magical
powder but it's such an American thing
to me how use that hump for the bomh
going bomes I have it here the
bues it's
finito oh it helps for an upset stomach
Stu and plenty of it baking s baking
soda
that's that I feel like you could have
other things for you tummy to help
you that's common really
damn wait
what
I have seven
DMS
well what you reckon it certainly feels
more
flexible right told you thank
you I think no no thank you for of us
our endeavors without you we'd never
have been able to discover wonders like
that stuff I rubbed on your bag and I'm
telling you there's plenty more where
that came
from plenty
[Music]
more not
hold what the [\h__\h]
chy shagy those are kind of
weird I asked chy to make some 3D stuff
for me
poses I gotta say those are kind of
weird I love ch's listening but
H maybe maybe you're you cooked a little
bit too much there maybe you're cooking
a little bit
less would be
better uh
can you show it
well 4 six fre four Okay
cool so we're getting extra
potions
uh I I don't know if I can use this for
thumbnail
um
yeah I don't no the problem is more like
the balance of me being so big and like
it's like lengthy you know we're
like lengthy we should be like next to
each other
there's there's a another one
but they're cute but I don't know I
don't know I don't know
chy maybe I have to rework those but you
guys can have them anyway maybe as a
gift
pngs yeah yeah I know that's why I asked
him to make something for um announcing
our collab and then for the thumbnail I
could use one of them to announce the
collab and then for the thumbnail I
think I need need something
different
God but if you're here where the hell is
everyone else don't tell me they're all
right but it's a long
story did you not announce it publicly
yet well kind of I
mean announcing I mean like asking for
me everyone still breathing starting the
as for these writings submissions I'm
sorry to say Clive but if you had those
you'd be sitting under a pile of rubble
I know but we were able to save a few
bits and pieces from the ruins most of
which ended up being used to build this
I think it was members only personal
items we go to the next Ain in the case
of Sid's things that would have been
mid then I'll check the
workshop he it
was yeah me and hatama are going to do
an off collab finally we wanted to do
one long time ago and then it didn't
work out where do I
go and now that she's back I thought why
not now now is the
time yeah and my idea that came up was
doing an
IRL off collap meme review which serves
also in our role playing serves as um
us teaching her what happened in the8
months in a Mimi
way I'll explain to
her what happened maybe we can focus on
thean side but I better keep
looking not necessarily it can be
mixed what do we have
here I met her before but uh we never
did an off collab together we did a
normal collab and we hung out IRL from
canva for days but we didn't do an off
collab so I wonder how you know I get a
little bit nervous with off collaps no a
different kind of pressure are did I
miss one
no yeah I know I remember seeing this
doll I wonder if it was
mids don't break
it
huh what's this tucked inside it give
I'm a nightmares
well midad I know you like your riddle
so I reckon you'll appreciate this one
of all my inventions this one's the best
and so when you when choosing its place
of rest I recalled your opal's daughter
the the rest and now it sleeps there in
the first that doesn't rhyme maybe if
you say it in a Scottish accent I don't
know I'm going to have to work on the
last ah he admits
it Sid's best
invention huh that sounds promising
H so Sid hid something in mid's first
another
filler what would that
be perhaps my pajama my
pajama
ah you know I was
um never
mind waa never
mind what about pajamas no just got to
bring some pajamas to Japan yeah it's
getting cold you find
possibly you wouldn't happen to know
what mid's first Opus was Opus that
girls his tone death as a Beni unless
you meet the orchestrion she couldn't
have been more than what 11 12 when she
Cobble that thing together it surprised
us all not least her dad you should have
seen how proud he was of the little
Scamp that better old box have to do
with anything I think Sid may have
hidden something inside
it who surprised me
those doing their bloody treasure magnos
things in the ID way ween one time or
another what about Magnus
Opus that's
Masterpiece is both
Masterpiece
Magnum the best thing you
made if it's knowledge you seek we've
tones of Plenty to guide you in your
Sur what's the best thing I ever made
holot talk
maybe I didn't break it well I didn't
break it oh what didn't you break that
thing nothing we didn't break nothing
you definitely didn't break the
orchestra
oh what's wrong with it doesn't look
like you broke it at all broken except
when it
isn't
see and you had nothing to do this is a
tiny white hat no nothing we just wanted
to listen to all the songs at once so we
like this and that's where the the the
thing is hidden give it to me break it
open I need whatever is inside
then
see break it break it break it break bre
it kick
it or
[Music]
sparkling you would be the
pacifier something cool did you break
and you fix no I didn't break it you
broke
it now they want to blame it on
me you said more
yeah
they started playing when I removed this
whatever it is H
H that's what we need for a ship well
don't look at
me I can tell you it's important now she
show it to me once and said as much it
was the stuff dreams once wow okay
indeed what I know is it's important
let's see if we can make some I know
that
too Quest
complete
[Music]
M let's show it to
Mid
eventually just the two I was looking
for I Los atient actually yes the Crown
Prince just left H Dion left Dion
mustard unless you've another word for
stood up and walked off yes left he did
have the decency to leave a message with
obelis before commandeering one of his
dingies should we go after him why don't
we just let these people that are
important leave princess
Keepers he's AF to do as he sees fit I'd
rather he did so in bed his wounds are
nowhere near healed much like yours I
suspect Oto told me what happened in
canver what is it with this realm's
princes and their aversion to
rest ask me when I get back at least
he's alive or maybe sometime then at
least try to stay
safe
and if that fails try to stay alive
eh oh every moment I waste here the
further the flagship sails I have to get
back return to the Iron Works Iron
Works
iron
there's a new plus you don't are you
sure I just did one I just did
one yeah I guess I should buy potions
though oh
well that's also a Final
Fantasy 14
thing but there's another potion Quest
right off the other after the
other what
what what no
way I we right Clive my dad had it all
worked
out he'd be proud of you mid his
writings may have helped but this
achievement is all
yours can we catch them be I know y's
one of the largest fastest vessels ever
built and it won't help she has the wind
at her back any other ship had be our
pressed to keep Pace with her let alone
reeler in but this isn't any other ship
this is the
Enterprise and the world's never seen
anything like my dad's engine it
certainly
hasn't
Clive what do you know of Barnabas th
only what the BS
sing and he sailed to Ash from Southern
lands that it was his Mastery of the
blade which won him the
throne what oh oh really that his
sword Odin
sword can sever the very threads of
creation doesn't that mean he just
killed the king with his but don't lose
any sleep over a last tilt we do what we
must to survive
but we
must the light I thought this C was
meant to be
[Music]
hidden huh mate company hey we'll hold
them off until the ship is ready but
hurry
bollocks all lands man your
[Music]
stations
what was that toy W's
[Music]
wife what was it to everyone with
me well who are we
[Music]
fighting
oh going
me trash here they come
[Applause]
how so dramatic there's
[Music]
[Applause]
nothing they even get into formation wow
so civilized civiliz mid every moment we
could give her behind me Lord rosfield
I'll take care of these [\h__\h] behind
you I'll have you know earthbreaker here
one struck fear Into the Heart of every
man in the clean
one little shitty poke
man this ends
now
heyo
no [\h__\h]
it you
my
over here stay
out
sorry I'm just wasting so much time how
are we doing mid I thought you said that
ship was fast she is what she get going
will that take time well I hear her for
speakers give as a push you L the old
suck and
die
oh I ever felt this alive in 20 Summers
come on then which of you like fan is
meeting ogre killer next I thought it
was called
heartbreaker like the CL you I'm
supposed to be wasting your time oh well
okay then let me waste some more time
[Applause]
then [\h__\h] no not this guy not him again
no no
[Music]
oh
no
attack I didn't see him coming where did
he come
from get
him we're having a lot of fun
here
ow kill here we
[Music]
goack realize it all just happened so
fast
I mean big damage yeah but it's honestly
the most boring attack that I have I
just stand
there and nothing happens besides a big
beam of
light get
him this
one 40K
oo over
here hey that's better here you
are
no I can do that
too
[\h__\h] almost as problematic as the turtle
for
me
dude
almost but nothing beats the
turtle that was easy
enough yeah all right you lousy lot get
your asses on board she's ready to
sail let's go you heard the captain ship
time finally
shipping is allowed now Clive oh
more but but I thought he
was confounded then it is as I
feared slap near is no man but a
creation of
Odin
[Music]
oh well that's kind of like overpowered
why can't his fiery fundament have you
normal enemies create something like
[Music]
that up for another round don't tell me
they're all as strong as the first one
my boy there was a time people called me
the
Executioner it wasn't my ass no matter
heads we'll roll all the same roll can
we not just
new you leave we follow follow swimming
are you mhm oh [\h__\h] at me way
[Music]
anchor engines dead slow
ahead have care my friends is not blood
that runs through a eggy's face see
these foes will not fall easily but they
will fall like Oaks a Woodman so fast
this good thing I brought
one oh they're too weak though how long
are we meant to keep this up let's just
use
it as long as it takes unless you have a
better idea well I've already killed at
least five of the
bastards [\h__\h] it they are
weak
thank you
brother let me collect some of
this
should we make for the ship not yet wait
for my
[Music]
signal yeah good aim anything else I can
reach
now come
here kill
go oh here your minions are kind of
shitty I would be more troubled if you
just made one proper one
again not so many shitty
ones right R for it it's a lot of the
Rings ref friend you think
so you think say so the
counting ah you saying that makes me
want to watch Lo of the Rings
again
[Music]
you
rewatch we already did one this year
have you
forgotten when I was sick in
Japan January
February I think that was this
year sure yeah yeah yeah yeah Mr
bolt
mhm wait what about toi walkie
and Enterprise
escaped two
times a
[Music]
secondat
no you know what we should rewatch
before that
cats how you like
that if you really want to rewatch I'll
give you one for
cats people in ARA want to do load of
drinks well if they do that they better
call me if I'm not invited to that I'm
going to be moring
molding
mad got to bring Mo
to chil
wiie Chilly Willy what do you
want
that's quite a mess you've
made and wholly
unnecessary you are my offering to
muthos I would not see you
damaged
H Let Her Go
oh oh man but what did we think was
going to happen when we left Jill behind
she was even going to die back to your
stations or going to be captured every
Bell spent Treading Water puts another
League between us and the
gallion but we're just chilling not
worrying about Jill at
all nobody even mentions
her what the [\h__\h] man I don't suppose
mid has a spare engine solar Titan there
are archives of my Lord of the Rings you
Rose from the graes have
plummeted absolutely certain of this
quest of yours
five the foes you face are as terrible
as they are numerous yeah we're going
for her but nobody talks about her
concerned about her should answer your
question you have that same stubborn
looking your father did and we left her
behind something in the first
place on the battlefield I am but a
single Axe A Deadly one mind but a
single one
nonetheless yet what you require is a
thousand and I believe my old friend in
randar can provide
them we shouldn't have left her behind
in the care I have many more Tales of
your father's exploits to share m and I
cannot very well do that if you're
dead
again good luck thanks for the
membership gifts and May Fair Winds
attend you Uncle
dad as for you Joshua take care bye-bye
I shall do my best uncle was a nice
reunion farewell my
nephew when next you see me it shall be
with an army at my back well hopefully
oh no wobbly
Waters tiny
boat
Cheerio
mate
yeah do keep up my
boy
do
well you can't have him showing us up
now can we we would never hear the end
of
it Beware of the wobbly
Waters oh yeah it's his
light oh
Dion
Dion this
idiot sussy
Buck G have
mercy he's
beloved all
this probably also
dead good
question how he got
here what have I done no it's okay mon
boy oh is it that girl
Lord that we saw in the
closeup she's like everywhere feels like
she's
everywhere is
she is she like uh one of those copy
paste
[Music]
characters
theal
[Music]
onero maybe she's
Tima the unexpected
one nice water animation see between a
and wud but any ship heading north as to
round zis and put through the
narrow maintain our current bearing
North Northeast and we'll catch the
black gallion before she vanishes again
again what's to prevent her from
circling around ash from the south with
these winds in those Waters it taken
forever in a forn night to reach Stone
here mid knows what she's talking about
Clive better than any of us lot anyway I
see we do is she
tells sails on the horizon she's
ours Chey sent me a better
one
look alive Boys full ahead and keep
those furnaces
fed you feel that Jill all lands Battle
Stations she's enjoying
this I captain let's see what this girl
can do she's
[Music]
cute
girl boss
yeah ooh nice
armor where one leads so does the other
follow the bond of Consciousness which
joins them condemning both to the same
fate self my every attempt to strike it
from their hearts serves only to tight
paten its
[Music]
hold
fascinating what is that his already his
open form there is not my blade cannot
sever not as big of a transformation as
others oh
no don't you dare care we worked so hard
on this
ship great g go
gosh
really wow I cannot believe we dodged
that with a slow ass ship babus semi-
Prim on a port head down nor on aort for
impact
drifting
oh it's now or never I'll find
her
we have entered his domain and his
trap oh Phoenix you want to take care of
this [\h__\h]
yeah you how to stop
it
yeah stay safe
mid through the
mom where did you hide
Abus down Sick this
one
kill
guys is there something you want me to
talk about something I'm
forgetting tell me and I shall
tangent attack I want your
tangent I've not packed my
pajamas P PLS frozen
pizza get him
ah yeah the animation
oh the no no no no no the animation from
alas is pretty cool
yeah came out of
nowhere but absolutely dope love
it so much effort put into
it over
here you swimming no I don't I lost your
time oh
[Music]
dear
ah
[\h__\h] we still have 50% sound that I
heard but he went down so fast
too now he's real St dagger for real for
real get him Giga
FL and Advent
three what what an ad ah you mean the
the over here the green stuff wait what
am I
doing do you
mean Advance
f o I don't know like once I get back
once can you know I'll be done with oh
all the all the busy stuff thank
God but I want
to I want to plan something with
amen get him um in terms of for holo Ian
something to do for us for like
Christmas
season I might focus on that and the
Advent calendar cuz I I'm
like um kind of in
charge management is
management is
helping and like taking care of the
financials and all
that this year but I'm still my task is
uh and I'll gladly do it cuz I
understand it's helpful uh my task is to
organize with the not good with the
[Music]
members get everyone to submit videos um
on time and all
that that's my
job
um so throughout although this time
we're like doing things earlier so I
don't
know currently don't have it in my head
from how from when to when we
are when when I'm really going to be
BD I ran out of potions
[\h__\h] but yeah so there's a couple of
projects that I'll be have mercy taken
care of I
guer fight at last we're all going to
die I need potions not meteorite or
whatever I need to
hurry
no I don't think I don't
think if I ever you know leave po I
don't think I would want to
become a managing sort of person or
anything behind the scenes No No NOP
no that would not be the direction that
I would be
taking yeah I'm busy with kfp
obviously
I don't know ideally I I don't know if
this is like the wants him alive too
hopeful thinking hold on I'm coming the
[Music]
ideal
n the
ideal way would
be to uh do this until
I don't ever have to work ever
again is this worth
it level
four yeah these are a bit bulky hope be
worth
it I mean get him not like 20 years
obviously but
save enough money so that I don't really
have to do anything anymore afterwards
that would be
great
go over
here get
him e it's not going to be 10 what you
think I'm paying why would you think I
have
10,000 EUR expenses per
year the suit the moap suit that's a one
time
thing I mean there will be like monthly
subscription
charges but those are pretty low attack
go Ste SS well I mean certain things I
have to do and you would I I'm I can
only hope that it evens out oh [\h__\h] you
then o la
la oh I am on the wrong Mo so I can't
react to the
50% sadly get
him second one yeah
yeah
oh I accidentally dodged but I kind of
felt like you know when when I'm
fighting with a smaller M but a big one
is like right right around me I I dodge
more feeling like they could like hit me
with something y bye
anytime oh my God he's going to kill me
I might die I might die nice try but
that way I would get my potions back
so oh good good good I appreciate
[Music]
that can we survive this I don't
know that's that's ooh that's a lot of
damage I like
it 40K
basically
attack I'm really nervous I'm really
nervous let's get this one going
again get as much oh there's more get as
much HP back as
possible
oh
ouch he's almost dead though
oh get
down move to a country of lower living
expenses I think AA is fine and I do
want to stay in Europe at
least you
know um just nice to have a place that
you feel feel as
familiar but you know when I was
talking after the AOE uh collab told you
I think that I was talking like really
long
with um Ellie right and she's in
Switzerland right she did ask me like
why why didn't you like you know move to
Switzerland or something and I'm like
yeah you know it's it's not oh I hear
crackling it's not that
easy um in the beginning there were
certainly at least like after I came uh
from Japan to Austria like after the
first half year or so there were
certainly such FS
like my mom too like she she
wanted obviously just like me wanted me
to get the most out of it but it all
seemed very difficult to min max and I
didn't want to move too far like moving
itself just for those purposes just I
don't know I don't know Switzerland
would have been still I guess the most
acceptable ver uh choice I I would say
cuz there's places where they speak
German and all that
um but in exchange you have high living
cost in Switz land so I don't know where
the hell are you I don't know my neck I
can't steal my
neck that's it that's all the items you
guys are going to give
me but Switzerland is also beautiful so
just because
of just simply already because of the
beauty of the country it's definitely
worth living
in um but it's too late like I'm I'm
three years in I'm not going to move to
some [\h__\h] Island
now it's too late I should have done it
in the
beginning is there a wizard
here no
good I'm dying this whole
time I am surviving barely on little h
and little potions I should have bought
potions yeah
[Music]
nice melted D Eternal Beach episode that
would be so nice
yeah yeah there's like certain places
that are famous for people going there
to pay less taxes is
right where did I come from did I come
from here
okay what I just out of like ethic
thinking ethically I also didn't want to
do it just because of the
ethics it's just too complicated
ethically
questionable C
annoying and K
exist
can you walk out of here I
can I might stay in Austria forever I
don't know stand
still
Phoenix are you not the dominant of fire
quite I see not before me but a
guttering Flame
irand Ireland low taxes
too I feel like I may have heard about
that oh there comes the horsey muscle
horse is this a muscle
horse
in
Earnest oh I finally just jumped into
the water to like refresh himself or
like kill his fire his
flame why would you do
that I feel like it's kind of lame if
our icons are just like so
easily defeated
by others like why are there such more
much more powerful icons I feel like
they should all
be
similarly
powerful
[Music]
oh
wait a second are aren't we in
there am I not in
here huh it's a stays like that the
water oh about we got we got
Jill talky
Wy toy Wy has seen some
[\h__\h]
can you go
one I think
[Music]
so but to
where good question
ooh oh
hi nice
closeup
you what did you do to
Joshua the
Phoenix oh I expect he will
survive
huh this Consciousness in which you coil
your feeble Souls is grown thick with
desperation and thus has my master
turned to my blade I have no potions
please have mercy peace peace have
mercy I have no potions peace have mercy
the world will soon be painted in
black and all that live Shall Gather in
death's autumn
wake not if we remove the cause of this
misery not if we destroy the last of the
mother crystals and restore balance to
the
world come do you truly think it's so
simple the blight is inevitable yeah
limit not even the mighty might stop its
endless
March
your efforts will Avail us
not not that is but
suffering you must embrace the truth
Mythos accept your place with the
Lord keep
it as long as there's a chance there's a
choice ever LED astray by your blind and
resolve no horse now it is time you
learn the inevitability of your Divine F
he gives the horse for when I fight him
as an icon
myself get as far away as you
can Clive no first got to fight like
this trust me so that it hits harder
later
on I yeah bye Jill I keep the dog though
because the dog is apparently more
useful than you which is
sad whoa hey I wasn't ready my God we
don't have to do
this oh but we
do if only to remind I'm going to die
look at my HP look at my
potions
defa there is no other option I mean I'm
doing well yeah yeah but I will die
there is no
way in the short time since our last Mee
you have grown much yet as a vessel I
fear my Lord will still find you lacking
still find do every
H rise o what is this Matrix yeah
ra your all this fire and fury and for
what stopping the
blight stagger like by a foolish far
away how dare
you you know not of this world nor of
our place in it if our Fates were so
easily Rewritten we would all be
gods
[Music]
are you ready go no I'm not
ready over
here I have seen
enough if reason cannot sway you there
are other means of persuasion that
might what what what
what oh wait I make mistake I make
mistake I don't know let let Let It Go
Let It
[Music]
Go readying iron
flash but I should just fight normally
it's probably
fine I mean we all know I'm going to die
but
get wait oh my
God cast off your chains
what
how how much time do I
have uh when do I dodge what what is
this is he is this just oh four oh oh
okay I have absolutely no time we're
dying
goodbye hi is this sege and death you
will assume the mantle you've been given
what does that mean what does that
mean and thus is the last Light Of Hope
sh I'm dead
oh you would heal it does seem
impossible it wasn't
scripted
C cuz that's a lot of damage you have to
do while you have to dodge the [\h__\h] out
of
it do you not see see oh thank God your
iron will weighs you down dragging you
ever further from your purpose and what
is my purpose
methos who are we we're not ready what
are the dominants I don't know the
breath of the Creator still warm on our
lips we carry his light that we might
guide the masses in his
name then I did the first try acts of
God that's why that's why I felt like
huh like his stagger is like forever far
away his HP is like barely going down
and the me trying to get rid of that
purple bar seems
impossible now hold
on it wasn't
possible okay okay we're not ready we
are more than
that you would be nothing without what
he has granted you the power we wield is
his and yet every time we draw upon it
it wears away at our very being I tried
it breaks us it unmakes us that its
Immaculate aspect might reveal
itself the
icon it is too much for even his Chosen
Few
expert apart from you mu us something
was off you wield the might of many yet
your body does not answer for its
avarice are you
saying what I am saying what do you know
is that we dominance are a means to an
end the EV we were created for you that
you might drink deep of our strength and
thereby fulfill Your Divine Purpose
which
is to
feed as you would know could you only
look beyond the walls of your prison of
self-regard as long as you choose to
ignore this you shall never penetrate my
defenses still you may take solace in
the fact that you are not alone in your
plight the chains of alition shackle all
of mankind but there is yet cause to
Rejoice H for the Lord in his Mercy has
taken pity on his flawed Creations
flounder and shall see them restored to
their proper forms how
nice and what exactly would that
be why loyal servants to
God
no manner Lord
rosfield they are men like you and
me orbe it ones unburdened by the wills
that drive Our Kind to
Madness they are
pure they
are
Divine you mean to turn everyone
aashik not turn
Mythos turn back
for too long has mankind been LED astray
by their clamorous
wills it is time they return to a world
of quiet
equality where they might once more know
Salvation okay
salvation sounds stupid and abandon
everything we hold dear makes no sense
we don't need your salvation we'll save
ourselves and we'll do it on our own
terms not yours and not your Gods with
every defiant expression of your will
the tighter the chains of Consciousness
become but
perhaps that fact may be put to
use why is it that in every story the
deeper you
dig into the purpose of a villain the
real you go the faster it binds you to
the remaining dominance the more you
realize it's so the stronger your
superficial and stupid that you can't
really believe that they really believe
only answer there ever was that what
they think what they say my master
intended is really worth fighting over
for all the same do you really think
you're right how can you what how can is
not far huh I freeze a path you're in no
fit State probably not but I can
try like take an example from real life
villains I mean those those are also
ridiculous but
somehow somehow you could maybe
understand some of their reasonings not
a great but somehow you're like oh
okay all right
Clive
[Music]
best yeah I don't know that just that's
just um basically these villains want
to want everybody in the world to become
these like zombie people but what do you
get out of that like huh
huh
how how is that how could you consider
that a better
world he want he wants to rule them
there's not much to rule then if they're
all mindless
creatures I mean I
guess I don't know if you're
like if you're so insane that all you
think that matters is yours and and you
think that so deeply that you want
everything else to be destroyed uh okay
I don't I don't know I don't
know it's it's World
Peace it's a video yeah but like like
you know I've been I've been so
satisfied with this game so far I was
expecting a a little bit more depth to
the core of the motives and the
motivation of the villains in the end
it's like how most games go but I
expected a bit more
death you
know still a great game but
[Music]
um something something's missing at the
reasoning of why this is happening maybe
I need to play the game until the end to
understand who knows I hope the others
are safe the Enterprise was clear of the
Gap when we fell they made it Jill and
they will have seen the ice where it
led Game of Thrones we need only wait
till door
n
yeah oh dear for gamron everybody has
like this is the second time babus has
bested
me understandable against him reasons
somehow then maybe there really is
nothing else for it but to give yourself
to his
[Music]
master they are drying their
clothes only you won't do
that the Clive I know would never do
that
so you
believe but do you really know me in a
really sensual way if what have said was
true then unintentionally sensual I'm
more Monster than
man and each time I summon the Flames
from
within I burn away the things that make
me who I
[Music]
am do you though
think of what you've used that power for
of all the people you've saved I've only
done good so far it doesn't matter how
or by whom it was granted only how you
choose to use it mhm you're on the right
path and you've chosen to use it for
good haven't
[Music]
you I've also used it to
kill
what if that's my
purpose what if it's all I'm good
[Music]
for you're still that same boy I grew up
with always so eager to save everyone
around you and yet always so
alone
[Music]
because you failed to realize the one
thing that needed saving most of
all
you you
Clive You drama you never once took the
time to save yourself
[Music]
a myself
I think I might be Beyond sa M
Mia no is beyond saving Mama
M
saved you fight to survive what a pose
these
two and you survive so that you may
protect those you
love it's what you
do she what you've always done how can
anyone Focus
and I know you're not about to
change so I'm going to help
you to give you what you need to protect
us all a baby an
[Music]
air an air usually locks you in and your
position you know
chill I are you
sure oh wait it's just her giving him
the
power if this is what you want don't be
like that don't be like that oh man the
way they don't worry
C it is yeah it's it's probably better
if her power is in our hands she's kind
of bad at handling it's not her fault
it's just the the way they make her so
useless this
burden I'll give you the strength to
Bear it alone
thank you I'm not
alone these burdens are sure you want to
give it to me I don't want it at all no
no no my
sorrow I see now it's not like I've been
waiting for this all time
[Music]
no
[Laughter]
what was Callie's reaction to
this and what will ena's reaction
be oh my
God
can we kiss now to continue
on having pledged my life to those I
love come on and I will gladly bear your
burdens
too until my last breath Square Enix
[Music]
Clive can't believe what you've done
here I promise you
Jill we will find a way all the
convenience camera
angles
k at least kids you owe me
that you look
so a hand kiss are you kidding me she's
like
why one day look upon the moon again to
together
and I promise you
Clive that I will be
there no matter what you must become
she's
so I
know fallen for him all
over I don't never thought a smile could
bring me so much joy he's so
smitten let's
go oh my
God I'm
[Music]
so what has just TR
transpired what has transpired just
now maybe we are getting the
air that we that I just asked
for eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs you think
they went that
far I
wonder you just tuned in what did you
you
miss uh uh
everything conception is that the right
word man no I think it's really
cool that they show
a kiss and even a lot more than that my
God what if Barnabas I'm not used to
that do we pursue him from my
jrpgs
no our paths will cross again soon
enough whether we like it or not
yeah
besides there is something we must do
first I mean I feel like I've seen too
much Drake's
spine the Lost mother Crystal my my
these lydy Turtle the Haya is at the
bottom of the sea wude won't dare move
on storm without her the way they look
at each
other my God but they know we're coming
now we'll need a plan and a damn good
one at that it's crazy cuz like some
actors some irel actors can't even let's
go home and find one portray his sexual
tension and love Ash will have to wait
how are these 3D
characters able to do
that
damn okay I said I said the the tension
thing but mostly I really want to say I
feel
the I mean you you've been feeling it
for a long time when you look at Jill's
eyes when she looks at Clive
but yeah they're really good at showing
this
emotion when they want
to a
toie Clive bested my
ta I've I've for my personal taste that
was kind of
weird
cuz first it's supposed to be like this
emotional
thing but it was hella awkward at least
as a
streamer um so maybe maybe getting the
point across of the first part would
have been better with clothes on you
know like the the whole
transferring the powers that might have
been better with clothes on to get the
point
across
um
yeah but uh yeah yeah that's why we
can't watch Game of Thrones
together
sheesh uh Clive okay we're going here
good I survived without buying potions
let's
go you
are mid says Odin split the sea in
two she's always been partial to a tall
T how can I recover from this but it's
tall and then there's to I struggle to
believe it myself I see your uncle isn't
with you he stayed with the Enterprise
maybe this is where we
end she was in urgent need of repair
best ending point a ship
we're to join him there when we're ready
to sell for ash you sure that's wise
last I heard place was still overun with
a kashik show me a city where that isn't
true ultima's plague is spreading we're
running out of time aren't we we've done
our best to shore up the Hideway but I
doubt a few planks will still a bang
still okay P it every little helps I
suppose maybe at the end of this game
they'll tell us
she's it's been 6 hours 20 minutes so I
wonder if time plan wise we
are going on as we wanted to Ice Ice
Baby I'll figure that out next
time assuming T will allow it do you
guys think I can do it another 6 hours
tomorrow
I mean can be seven too or even eight
and if it has to be then it has to be
but mhm 5 to 7 5 to 6
M
okay nice we shall finish our final
fantasy playthrough
tomorrow
covered in Nicks and lumps the lot of
them come back same time tomorrow
yeah uh got some stuff to do before the
stream the tell me we've run out of
pepion nuts and all what do you expect
but I shall be there same time same
place if you're going to BU some it be
quick about
it yeah no side quest it's how we've
been rolling
my
God you not find a better price than
that I do have a [\h__\h] ton of money huh
you're rubbing me blind you
know maybe I'll
buy
20,000 well at the end of the game might
as well right make it a bit more
comfortable for me give me more options
to heal
cuz I'm not really I can't even remember
using the
potions
uh H the I mean the the the the tonics I
keep on forgetting to use them I had
none left over
anyway do you think you actually use it
I think I will we're at the end of the
game I should I should use
it
fin quest of stream I don't have time to
do that mm- sadly I'll be fine though I
mean look at how I've been doing so far
I think I'll be fine thanks for the
membership gift
[Music]
though yeah you you might use them
accidentally you can use them from the
pause menu
[Music]
oh I guess
so
um
Y what do you want H does anyone think
as well that I'm going to be in trouble
tomorrow for the final
fights do I have anything
new I don't have enough
Ash the
[\h__\h] anything
else all you need is potion upgrades oh
wait is there really another Quest let
me see oh yeah is that the potion Quest
again maybe we can do that quickly so
we're ready for
tomorrow lady Karen's called in a favor
let's do
this the
[Music]
turtle just get better at combat what
how can I get better at combat I'm
already I've mastered it
[Music]
can I have some more
ball is that
the I think I know what that
is ahh or it's it never huntboard Quest
are all of these huntboard quests trying
to remind you to do the hunt
board going to be in Long stream no it's
not just normal stream no more W
[Music]
stream have you tried M's lemon there's
one ability that will help a lot so
delicious I'm going to look at it
tomorrow I'm kind of tired
already did not have a nap today cuz I
was I've been recording all day before
the
Stream the L trying to be as efficient
as
possible I have some recording deadlines
you know and they're not necessarily
like right now but I thought if I'm in
Japan I don't have my usual setup so I
want to record
[Music]
here more
bble
carrot which one is the more
bble let me ask him like that with the
green the green
thing it is the car oh it's the carrot
oh okay we're getting really tired right
now the whispering Waters Rosaria okay
okay Rosaria Rosaria right yeah yeah
yeah yeah I know where R areia is
somewhere like here on the left
side
oh where could it be maybe
here Whispering
Waters Whispering
Waters whisper Whispering
Waters top left top left here this
one
there Whispering waters I'll go from
here we start
whispering
was good
morning good girl my eyes are so
tired
fostter
the upgraded diamond dust ability from
shiva I'll have to look into that
because I don't know I I can't I mean
unless I master something I can't use
all
abilities thank you be
safe try and replace Rook Gambit with
something stronger like that Rook Gambit
what's my Rook Gambit attack which one
is that judgment ball def funer one but
then I have to master it right we'll see
we'll
see we'll see how many points I
have a this one yeah yeah yeah that that
could be replaced
yeah
ow thanks toy Wy this one attack
moham
hey I don't know I just feel like it
right
now your ah not too late not too
late
nice get
down was your ugly ass face
this
one nice
try at this one oh it's
time can I get back the the
Giga p no oh nothing I got nothing oh I
got Goose I got Goose when in doubt use
over here Shiva is good so no need for
lightning anymore oh
okay is that why they kept her away from
me for so long CU she's pretty damn
strong could have scaled her damage
though the Gucci what ah the carrot I
said ugly but honestly it's kind of cute
it got like flowers all over it
can't be much cuter than
that how why I was I was
dodging get
him
oh had to cancel
[Music]
it let's do
[Applause]
this
kill
have you looked in the mirror
oh so
sweet you guys this one the cutest might
be you
guys
[\h__\h] hope you guys have seen I've been
working on the Polar WS but from now on
until I'm back from Japan I don't know I
might not be able to do them I'm
sorry now because I won't have my tablet
I've been doing them on the tablet you
know go
kill I'll I'll be done within this year
for sure
though my I've learned my lesson I shall
not always make them that cheap because
then I get too many or I shall cut cut
it off
earlier cuz yeah now it's actually hard
to keep up
[Music]
ha all yours tole
one per person oh no nobody really
ordered two to be
honest at least not for
themselves not good that's better just
healed
kill
yeah I want to do special Christmas
versions We got time we got time I'll be
done until then with the Halloween ones
[Music]
for all yours
toal all right it's almost
dead
second attack
oh so far didn't miss a single one I
think even though I was
M my mold
St the M
strip yeah the good thing is I'm not
going alone we're sharing the
cost don't kill me don't kill me oh did
I accidentally use two a high potion and
a normal potion that's [\h__\h] too
slow
stinky oh it was just one hit
left oh
well carrot has been
shredded I love carrot salad have you
guys had carrot salad
before well that was definitely anything
but
ordinary now let's get this Vine F back
to the yard no oh my God it's so good no
it's not hard you shredd it into really
small small small
pieces and then you know some oil some
vinegar and this and that I made it a
little while
ago just out of a whim cuz I had a
leftover
carrot was amazing so
good do you like carrot cake carrot cake
it's fine but nah I don't know about the
cakes that are like with ingredients
that are more the sa we
side wait I should go straight to the
dude it's all
right lemon juice oh I see I see I made
it without looking at the recipes me we
run out of nuts and all I'm so happy I'm
I'm able to
to make perfect salad
now lady Karen's called in carrot cake
with pineapple oh that makes it kind of
a bit more sweeter I like it like the
idea oh another person talks about
carrot cake with pineapples H seems to
be a thing Sid I
uh my Satchel was twitching
what an
amazing he said my Satchel was
twitching nice
blooming
[Music]
pretty
wow it is just as I
hoped I'm to you I took a Sal cook a
salad here yeah I think
generally they just count to the cooking
chef category who make the the
starters
H oh consumable potency maximize so wait
they're stronger
now inre yep yep yep yep okay nice
okay perfect that is another potion
Quest
finished
easy is the max okay wonderful
wonderful maximum potion
yay now we're even more ready for the
finale yeah maybe at the beginning of
um the next stream we can do the other
uh there's another plus Quest
right oh yeah you guys know what this
one's for is that the one that
makes my sword or what what was somebody
said
something what's this one
for I oh even more to carry oh okay I
guess we can do that one too
then yeah what what now I have nine plus
DMS my
God
oh they're oh they're from my
mom she uh shared her binge watching
series that she watches every
year that's why I have a million
DMS I'm so
tired I'm so so tired right now oh my
God
ha you know what this means my mom
watched the romantic moment
of Clive
and me lady
[Music]
Jill why not Mommy why
not Game of Thrones I haven't already
watched Game of Thrones in a
while in a while I think I'll wait maybe
until I'm really desperate
or or until the next season
of uh House of the dragons in
June Game of Thrones is only four
seasons
yeah
no no you guys are so
critical yeah Game of
Thrones good
show let's save the first time I'm
saving today damn thank God this game
and the PlayStation 5 doesn't seem to be
prone
to
crashing but you never know one save per
stream it's like I'm putting a
uh a handicap on
me like to live dangerously yeah Mommy
just so you know I'm not leaving the
laptop this time because I have to bring
it to Japan I need something to stream
with
ideally sorry Mommy I'm going to leave
you the iPad though
and you can use my PC I
[Music]
guess well last time she was playing
that one game endless
endlessly what was
it what was it again stard you
[Music]
Valley
mhm oh yeah Mommy if you play like my PC
you can play B
gate I mean you could play it uh
yeah anywhere I guess but uh my Steam
account but that's maybe dangerous cuz
then what if she doesn't finish until
I'm back and then she's so addicted and
she won't like be able to let it
go and then
and she won't she won't
leave even when I'm back she'll just
stay until she finishes baller's
gate she won't let me use my PC
anymore until she finishes B
skate I mean if she plays as much as
narissa narissa has done it pretty
quickly
yeah oh going to go guys I'm tired sorry
no Super Chat reading today we are on
top of it
anyway and I'm stressed
out I'm going to eat my pizza and then
sleep and then wake up and do some stuff
and then I'll be back for you guys for
the last the F for finale the finale
finally for real for real Final
Fantasy
16 we'll find out if Jill is pante or
[Music]
not thank you for watching guys finally
the Final Fantasy finale that might be
the title of the Stream
[Music]
yeah we can do it we can finish it
tomorrow I'm excited I'm
excited finishing another lovely game
and and my first Final Fantasy game at
that very special
so I'll see you there okay thank you for
watching today even for all the lag the
real an the fake
leg hope you guys had fun and enjoying
myself V oh
[Music]
bye-bye it was all real lag all real of
course what me
bye-bye said did I say and in German we
say
forgot now I said
[Music]
it
bye-bye oh Korean Bros you're hiding
you're
hiding oh my god there they
are why me byebye
[Music]
byebye
wait this actually this bgm is
[Music]
perfect oh CLI
[Laughter]
sh the
grunt
[Music]
it's so
nice kind of quiet
[Music]
though
oh yeah I remember the Tweet oh yeah
someone made that before a that was so
funny someone made a version of this
intro
before with the actual sound that the
piano would be
making if there was
[Music]
sound oh was so
funny
can someone find that again and tweet it
at me again thank you bye plink PL plink
plink