[Music]
do
wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
but now we have council so it's the
first almost full collaboration
of halloween
and indonesia
discord
the discord support today and hopefully
also the viewers support today because
uh today will be a very very passionate
and dangerous and fun and exciting
even
let's race that baby
yeah yeah
i was like burning rubber yes exactly
and bad drivers that's right
but i'll drive you guys nuts
[Applause]
yeah i think we shall start oh my god
productions of each member uh now let's
start with
[Music]
hello thank you for having me this is
anja melvisa from hello life is second
generation
thank you everyone i can't wait what's
your what's your goal
what's my ikigomi um to not be on the
last last place at least
[Music]
generation one
so my motivation tonight is um to show
you my practice i guess
oh
[Music]
hi
attention please and favorite rainy from
whole life id generation too my goal
today is to be
number one in your heart and also not
dead last night
yeah i heard you were good you and iris
have heard good good good news about you
oh yeah we had a good practice yesterday
right
yeah nice
[Music]
what's your motivation for today
oh well
i i want to be at least not on the last
okay
[Music]
little is okay at least not the last
oh okay lucy we have
[Music]
in someone's heart is that such a good
thing
does it sound like a good thing yeah
okay next up
[Music]
hello hello everyone i am live indonesia
and
thank you so much for inviting me to
this collab i'm so happy though i'm so
excited they go
[Music]
my motivation for today is that i would
like to have fun though although yes i'm
not really confident but let's have fun
all right
[Music]
motivation i plan on ranking top so that
you guys become my bottoms that is my
motivation for today
on top i see i don't know what else is
[Laughter]
we won't be dominated that easily senpai
thank you
did i get
all the introductions from id i think i
did um
[Music]
let's introduce the e inside let's start
with iris
oh yeah hi
it's iris hololive english project hope
v singer here um my goal today is to get
first place victorus
victor it
[Applause]
thank you is for participating looking
forward to your driving skills yeah
thank you so much for having me here so
i heard that you waited for yeah for me
to come on my friends you were literally
the last one that i needed
that was german we were 11 people
i'm sure we can understand german yeah
12 12 12
[Music]
[Laughter]
i heard you only played mario kart so
far in a member's only stream but that's
about it
yeah i won and that one too
oh
i see oh then you might be the hidden
winning choice
your course a wild card player
amazing
[Music]
thank you thank you
um
um i'll do my best i think we have a we
have a fiercer competition to be not
last and to be first so i'll do my best
[Music]
and i was also
taking this very seriously in her
practice round so a bit scared of inna i
don't know
he's still falling off maps it's fine oh
yeah it happens oh kelly joined this
night
thank you
around here
nice and let's start and let's continue
with the uh introduction from cal iop
maureen
hello everyone my name is callipe my
parents are still asleep and probably
can't watch the news this morning maury
nice to meet
low because you a bit early uh so excuse
me for that guys but i'm very excited
just to be here i really didn't think
this was gonna work but it's working i
love
thank you it for joining even though
it's such an early time and kind of uh
troublesome with some setups and all
that i'm glad you're still here and you
know what you being so whispery and calm
might be a good uh thing for driving
because that way you might be able to
focus more
i feel like cali is going to be
screaming while whispering you know that
kind of i'll do my best
it just twists but everyone yeah
yeah this is my awesome mario kart
stream
donate
i am
of hollow life english and i'm kind of
sick today and if you're watching on my
side i just need to say this now
i've had some technical difficulties
very suddenly so i am made of cardboard
i'm sorry please bring well i it was not
my fault it's out of my control right
now so anyway
i'm png tuber domo somebody does a png
tuber let's race today baby i'm the wild
card today oh yeah
i'm eating my dust
well you know on the screen there's
there's gonna be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not you anyways
[Music]
all right that leaves uh me i think yeah
yes i
welcome everyone i wanted to do this
tournament for a long long time uh i
think my viewers have heard me talk
about it since months ago and finally
it's happening uh and i'm very glad to
have all these lovely girls here
together it's the first time we're doing
a tournament like this so i i don't
think anyone has to feel bad about you
know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some
more often in the future so please don't
stress yourself out let's just have fun
today
[Music]
we're organizing
yeah thank you
i think we will go to the roof but
before that let me say thank you uh the
hats and the cards are sponsored by
minomar inanimates
[Music]
lovely
so cute all right let's everyone switch
to the rules image please thank you
okay tournament rules easy there's not
many rules basically
all characters all courses are allowed
however
uh if you choose uh please do not choose
random courses please choose a certain
course that you want to actually erase
but if that course has been used before
like if it has actually been chosen
before please do not choose the same
course again
already
understandable
to understand
number two items are allowed number
three uh we are racing in 150 cc with no
assist everyone please check if you have
turned off your assistant no
all right i think i turned it off now
okay i don't see it if uh wait a second
it's if you press y and select your
character at the point where you select
the card you can press on
plus
the plus button
where you see the the three options on
the right side if you press l
uh if if there is a
if there's a
sign that says no
then it's uh auto steering off that's
how it's supposed to be okay okay so
it's supposed to be violent yeah it's
supposed to be crossed out exactly the
other ones you can ignore okay oh
okay
okay okay
[Laughter]
i also want to quickly let you guys know
um i'm on i'm going to be on like auto
mute this whole time so unless i have
something to say i'm going to be muted
don't worry if i'm a little quiet i'm
still here with you guys in spirit yeah
okay
and next row oh yeah then there's no
more rules since this is just a system
we're doing the first cup all versus all
big mixer four races
but then we get uh we mute each other by
the way during the race and just to
focus everyone on what we're driving and
then we get back together and discord
talk a little bit then we go to the
second cup which is en versus id six
versus six yes yes yes
we
separate each other in uh the voice
channels by team this one in this one we
will actually talk with one another if
you wanna and then we uh
give some comments together again and
when we get all back together in the
same channel and then we do the third
cup with random randomly thrown together
teams no ian vs id would like all mixed
together naturally beautiful yeah
random
random random we will just like i'll
count down and and then everyone joins
eva voice chat room zero or voice chat
room one no who's this one
who's the random rapper that's not who's
the ravens
we're gonna have to do it again
just so you know the the those like
team cups would basically be
um
like the same
as all versus all the difference is just
basically like if you throw items like
red shells or whatever and there is a
teammate in front of you it will not go
to the teammate obviously it will go
directly to the closest opponent driver
uh that's around you so yeah that's how
that team system works i think yes
is everyone ready we need to fix who is
that
ready wait who is that who is that
random dude
oh who is it who's that
dude who's that where did oligarchy
seven eight nine ten at eleven twelve
who is ready mute yourself on discord if
someone's not ready then i will ask you
why you're not ready
[Music]
wait guys how do you wait guys uh how do
you go forward in the game
you push the
a button you can't go there
now yeah
the world right now okay that's what you
mean okay gotcha all right understood
thank you thanks guys love you guys
you and me now
are you guys ready
can you hear me
give me a boy if you can hear me i see
wha you say what
all right all right we good we good
we're ready
[Laughter]
oh boy
i don't know
i uh
i don't know if i'm ready for this oh
here we go
four four races
hmm
what should we do let's do something we
practiced
like rainbow road
oh you'll be senpai also chose rainbow
road
big blue
i should choose big blue next if we get
rainbow road right now
all right
[Music]
yeah what rainbow road is a good warm-up
stage for everyone don't you think kind
of wakes you up
i like how
um
who are the two that look the same
is that mario
mario kart stadium okay i don't know if
i've done this before
but i'll try i'll try
deep breaths
okay middle of the pack i think i've
done this
easy course
oh okay
warm up
[Music]
someone fell
okay we good oh
oh no it's okay it's okay it's okay
oh i tried there was an effort there was
an effort
oh no they pushed me off
oh no i don't feel good about this
fine
[Music]
okay
you just gotta focus on middle of the
pack
two items nice oh i missed the jump okay
it's fine
oh no
i didn't mean to use that okay
uh
why is the first place so far ahead
what is in first place
oh it's raining
no i got second okay okay not bad not
bad not bad oh no scary
i should post it a little a little later
at the end it's okay first game first
game
ah so close
so close so close
i think i was very unlucky in the uh
at the start at the very start
it's okay it's okay
three three more races three more races
oh actually my heart is pumping right
now i don't know why
[Laughter]
this is more nerve-wracking than
practice one
yeah i missed the shortcut at the very
front uh very star i think that kind of
cost me i also got bonked by some shells
hey are we not supposed to choose the
same course
irish
i'll laugh if we get that map
oh we're going to the beach the beach
episode
okay gotta bring it home for ian
i'm gonna bring it home for ian
oh okay i don't i've done this one
before i can do it
[Music]
all right
being at the very front from the
beginning is kind of bad
because of that exactly exactly because
of that
you know let's try and stay in the
middle of the pack
[Music]
oh no it pushed me off
okay
no
yeah orange is great
okay
good cornering will get me here
nice nice
[Music]
okay good cornering ina good corn
wait what happened to my mushrooms
where'd they go
[Music]
the ink no
yeah let's get ready
i'm not doing too well this round that's
fine it's fine
still one lap
[Music]
ah
oh no okay okay okay this is okay
ow
this is not okay
come on give me something good
[Music]
my actually
oh
[Music]
no no no no no no
okay good
[Music]
no
okay second second not fat not fat not
fat
oh i caught up
sorry i'm like super focused right now
okay and please everyone do not use
cheap cheap beach or uh mario kart
stadium anymore for your
collection thank you
i'm going to try and remember that but i
don't know
yeah nothing that looks like a beach and
nothing that looks like a fancy night
life
place
but isn't there multiple beach
uh yes but the cheap cheap beach the one
that we just did from the ds version not
anything yeah
oh okay okay
okay
getting a second when are we doing teams
maybe getting seconds we still have two
races to go
but she's muted okay
are we muted
[Music]
come on rainbow road come on rainbow
road
come on rainbow road actually i kind of
feel bad if we get rainbow road i feel
like i'm gonna get
orangey
toad harbor
okay i think i know some of the
shortcuts here but not too sure
okay focus on the corner
[Music]
thank you
i should have gone to the top it's fine
okay
get me another item i'll get the box
nevermind
[Music]
i hear something coming
okay right here upcoming corner
and a
turn nice cornering
[Music]
nice nice
good good enough
we're doing this i don't know i don't
want to believe yet
focus
[Music]
focus just give me something i can
defend myself but honestly there we go
and this course i think i'm okay with
the cornerings and stuff
pretty familiar with it
[Music]
that's a blue
hey
it's fine i can still take the shortcut
it's
okay i have i have a long ways ahead of
everyone okay this is fine
i have i have some
i i got to
do cocky there
get me something i can defend myself
please
okay it's good
[Music]
jeff
oh no not again
sorry
it's
oh iris is fierce competition
so it's so it's raining
represent
okay come on give me a rainbow
i think recording got really better
after the practice stream thank you guys
for that
like i think like before that stream i
didn't really get how to play mario kart
but after that that drifting kind of
like clicked i was like oh yeah this is
it this is it
it just clicked i was like i was meant
to drive i was born to drive
let's not let's not get ahead of
ourselves here
oh i'm really bad at this map oh
i'm really bad this map but i'll do my
best
final race this is it focus up
[Music]
set cornering
because
[Music]
welcome to my course
thank you for joining me today
[Music]
i am warmed up now
oh yeah oh no shell let's at least get
this boost never mind
okay oh iris at the shell
i couldn't really use like a defense
item you know
okay
good
okay we still have
oh i thought i heard a blue shell
okay
so the other way
maybe we'll redo this one
not the communication there
oh
i should have saved that okay
okay
give me a defense item
[Music]
okay
oh there comes
please
[Music]
so
not sure
okay about the disconnection yeah
i'm not sure like normally it seems like
in in the whole of japan tournaments
they automatically give the one like
well
like this qualification like last spot
if you
uh oh
if you are oh
wow uh congratulations or everyone
cannot mute themselves now oh yeah yeah
okay oh yeah
[Music]
i was very impressed
i think that's just how we're gonna take
it it is what it is
[Music]
uh
let me let me just uh enough was number
one right
thank you
my training paid off thank
you thank
you know make it entertaining for
everyone you know rainbow road is just a
map for that
you know
what
yeah she practiced on that one a lot i
think
[Music]
how did you how did you manage to get
number two today
i i did bad on the first race so that
really pulled me back but yeah ina
senpai was very quick uh
but i did my best i did my best
you were
oh
wait are we complete in the
lobby right now one two three yeah
okay well then shall we uh continue uh
but muna senpai is currently unavailable
yeah she's checking something out
oh she's back but i don't know my
battery is one hundred percent but it's
safe low batteries i don't know which
one is low battery oh it might be one of
those like the ones that you like plug
into what did i do with that
do you think you're fine to go or you
need some time i i think i think it
should be fine okay
sorry we're making coffee right now
you gotta offer all of us colleen
everyone who needs coffee go get
yourself a cup of coffee
on my way
a lot of caffeine shakes already so
i'm banned from coffee
i was actually really surprised about
amma's driving too like i thought you
know because she didn't like we didn't
see her practicing we didn't see her
playing
[Laughter]
yeah whatever yeah no it would have been
a waste if you would have shout casted
how you uh suggested uh amer because
you're such a good driver we need you we
need you
okay
all right then let's uh
okay ollie okay okay oh ollie is going
to be picking teams are we picking teams
like dodge balls
my full power now because now i'm
fighting for the en ladies oh yeah yes
this is where we put our all in it yep
yeah
[Music]
two of the strongest ones aren't ian
wait me too
[Laughter]
that i can i'm i'm okay at not getting
last place so that's good news yes
morrison is a good asset to have i want
her on our team hell yeah
guys
will have to carry uh indonesia's uh
back
yeah it's okay
i will support greeny
as much
[Laughter]
as long as we don't get disconnected
again oh yeah oh my gosh
[Music]
everyone uh please split into teams by i
think let's just um ian go to voice
channel 01 thank you okay
oh
and i guess so we're going to abio we
will stay i think
all right hello
wait a second
okay okay okay uh just cali is missing
you can't get the memo
okay there we go
oh ladies and gentlemen hello hello what
is our strategy for winning against
ideas
but like um you know for items do they
automatically um not hit our teammates
yeah it only hits oh okay that's really
helpful okay nice
but i've never uh parted teams yet i'll
see how we can select that i think we
will um
like every every a participant will have
a choice to catch okay which team they
can join i think that's how it works
let's see no more items no cpu all
vehicles race for races let's go
so long as watson doesn't drive off the
edge we should be alright
[Music]
uh ah i'm the one doing this okay uh
player was ollie right yeah no no wait
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no how do i how do i cancel
this no uh
if i have to like you might have to make
more
ah oh
no okay it looks fine
communication
[Laughter]
it's okay
you know what to
[Music]
sorry girls i did a little mistake
because like i thought uh
yeah you know uh open
the room again
okay
okay join on camera again
[Music]
okay yeah you can you can join in again
it's open again i think it's closed once
yeah
[Music]
as much as you can that's that's how
this works
yes i'm not overdrift you know you don't
want to like oh there it is
the bald one is back but there's two
bald ones now
ground here now
wait have it complete one two three four
five six seven eight nine ten eleven
twelve okay completely just doing a head
count everybody stand still einstein
live here from sexy
and i think we are okay
no cpu all vehicles full races
like who's the other bulb
yeah who's the little baldi
just so you guys know my mom is watching
she's not to say anything though
[Music]
hi
are you sure you don't want to say
anything
[Music]
this is how you do it
who is that anya okay okay now it's even
let's go
we can i can just do the random button
we don't have to do the voice chat
thingy
wait wait teams now i guess you have to
use the questions
that's using map oh no
yeah um
a new map a new map which one do we want
to use which one do we all have
confidence
oh yeah i probably shouldn't drink the
road
you guys are overloading
you know what maybe we have rng on our
side wait we don't have one we're gonna
choose
[Music]
oh nice okay we're blue
we're blue
when did we push the go button on the
two
a little bit
yep
[Music]
does it work with like the same people
the same thing it shouldn't
[Music]
chad told me that it doesn't hit uh your
own people unless i don't know it wasn't
a green shell oh it probably was a green
shirt yeah
i don't think you can control it it's
fine that's nice
[Music]
on this road
[Applause]
[Music]
afterwards
okay no we did okay we did it
oh
[Music]
mount wario or like the animal crossing
map is easy like easy as in it's like oh
no we gotta make it difficult for them
you know
stadium personally cheese
wait what what's up
cheese wait
okay
[Music]
let's go
i have practice in that one
the corners on this one is a little
strange
castle yeah
just has a lot of traps and a lot of um
obstacles
let's
[Music]
for one second i loved that one that was
a good second
i like this music it's hype
let's go
what is that
stop it
oh
[Music]
stable
okay okay who's in front of us
me it's me and yeah yeah
okay so everyone's in here and then okay
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
these corners are tricky
oh the lightning plays pretty good
[Music]
yes
oh
[Music]
miley cyrus
okay can i throw the red shell right now
with enough so that i can be number one
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh i hate it when the lightning hits
when you're about to jump and you're
just like well i guess i'm dead
all righty
let's freaking go hmm
[Music]
what a play bye
i feel like they uh
i feel like they're definitely getting
technical on us here yeah
oh they chose
it's a nice one it's a good one
it's gonna be that one don't worry it's
gonna be rainbow road and i hate it
um i feel like it's gonna be cheese
yeah it's too much cheese here
oh
oh i knew it was sweet i knew it the
chocolate cheese
why do they like that one so much
jesus yummy they must know something we
don't
robbie and ayna is probably really good
at that one that's why i chose oh
probably
trying to get the points back we can't
let them it's all right we'll get him
we'll get him out we have a good head
start yeah still
ellia
oh i'm gonna burn out
just kidding
i didn't even know that was a shortcut
ain't neither they know the shortcuts
were in trouble they do they do it's
okay i'm still i'm still doing okay okay
we're still good we're still good
well that was dangerous
oh it's okay i thought
i thought i said
it went to someone else in front of you
which will be number 12 i guess
it's gonna be a long road for that one
right right
i heard somebody say
like character i shouldn't have listened
oh
okay so she knows the shortcut i see how
it is
i thought i just saw it i was like oh
yeah there was a shortcut here
[Music]
at the very end
no wait that's irish
[Music]
only iris is ahead of me that's good
yep oh reina came
to the shortcut
i didn't have the livestream to use that
shirt cut okay she's first now okay
that's fine come on
give me something good
oh no not a banana
[Music]
together
okay let's go
okay
[Music]
that was a rough horse
in the ass but we have inna so okay i
don't know i'll do my best i i practiced
but you you don't know i don't know the
shortcuts for this so i don't know any
shortcuts but the shortcut is just go
down in space to sana
she'll
for that
no oh oh we're getting right up
rainbow road let's go
as long as i don't mess up we'll be fine
we'll be good yeah
[Music]
just don't fall off the edges
yep
[Music]
practice is paying off
for like cali for example i think she's
not gonna oh no
okay here we go me neighbor
oh thank god this is cool
easy easy shortcut
oh my god oh please please don't don't
ah this is so slippery that scares me
it's fine it's fine
let's get we are one two three right now
oh yeah it's all of us okay oh boo
shelling coming
[Music]
okay that's fine
oh rachel no
that was not me that was not me it's
fine it's fine
[Music]
yeah nice boost
to me don't get so close to me i have a
rainbow on my back
okay that's fine
[Music]
you're not just gonna follow you
okay that's fine that's fine
[Music]
oh no always only went around me okay
it's okay we still have one more lap we
still have one more left
[Music]
oh no blue shell coming
it's good
it was silly
[Music]
it's okay we'll get here we'll get it
oh yeah i see
i see
[Music]
[Applause]
i think
i had that i was like third and fourth
place the entire time at the until the
end oh yeah
erase let's go one two three nice
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yay
too okay
you can you have a chance in the next
race because yeah it's a random you'll
be having random teams yeah
yeah what can you hope
uh what was their reasoning behind
choosing uh the cheese one and the baby
road
i like cheese because
we liked it
that's all i was the one who told them
cheese rode because i like like cheese
it's gotta be a road where reina knows
the shortcuts and stuff yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
do we have uh
some
uh comments from the winner ina it was
number one i think uh yes uh i would
like to thank pajamas
[Laughter]
i was about to be like yeah go let's go
okay nevermind okay thank you
okay so uh we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
that i wouldn't believe that
um
[Music]
well even if you accidentally choose one
that has been uh chosen before don't
worry it will probably not be selected
so let's just
try to not choose the ones that we have
uh raced before yeah i will do the
random teams now actually there is uh we
don't have to do the voice chat thing
because there is actually uh a way to do
it here
and then once the themes are selected
oh there it is okay so uh in voice chat
zero
uh zero zero one we want uh gouda
aina
guys
which one is that
we're going on a train
[Music]
that one i think okay that's actually
good all right let's go it's not too bad
yes let's go
yes do our best
[Music]
i don't know if the shortcuts here are
worth it
isn't worth it i don't know i don't know
it is kind of risky
it's very risky right it's very high
amongst the way that's on the other team
um
let's
yeah this chocolate is very risky i
don't know if i guess
it's fine
for me
oh no
we're doing fine for now
that's right
[Music]
sorry
there's always the question who the hell
hit me
oh yeah
who must
too
[Music]
okay as long as i don't get a blue shell
i got this
wait that was a decent safe night
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is the most adrenaline i've had in
a very long time damn my heart is like
i'm like surprised like i didn't think
it would be this much fun to like have a
full tournament with everyone and we're
having a blast man
it's so funny
every half year we should do something
like this oh i know yeah
yeah
what are we picking
just what you want yeah
there's a lot of airports
i
thank you very much
i did you guys
let's go
guys i'm not muted aren't i no because i
think you're a little client baby i hear
you
oh okay okay so you're like wondering
why i might eat meals sorry
[Music]
who was that i don't even know what
everyone's saying i mean
[Music]
oh
uh uh-huh
okay this part i usually choke but okay
i can do this
you can do it
what the hell
sign up
[Music]
oh
and before we get the time the clock
or
[Laughter]
i see okay airport is okay since they
want airports so much that let's direct
your favorite chords
[Laughter]
we have two more i think two more third
one
three out of four okay let's go team
highlights
airplanes in the night skies and the
shooting stars
right now
win right now
[Music]
iris is so scary
oh my
god who
[Music]
i just got screwed over like you would
not believe
i'm gonna come back
me too me too because i'm behind you
okay we're still doing okay
i have your back
i'm bringing up the rear don't worry
i got you made up the red okay
let's go oh god oh god oh god oh my god
the blue team coming back in i mean nice
let's go i don't have a movie that's
behind me why
up
and iris okay this is fine
oh
this is not looking good
cool it's okay just gonna believe in the
rng
you still got one more lap in the rng
that's mario kart i gotta
it's not here right now but i'm so proud
of kelly
i don't know how to use the how do you
use the the paraglider
uh if you press down you can fly higher
oh then i can't hear
oh
oh my god everyone in front of me is is
bluetooth again
unless something a miracle happens i
don't know
i'm not feeling this one
yeah this is bad this is really bad oh i
think it's an item either okay that's
bad i have never gone in the mushroom
before i couldn't use any of these i
can't come back from this me neighbor
this is unfortunate
it's okay it's okay still got third
still not third time oh that was rough
[Music]
okay this is the last one yeah
this is the last one yeah yeah okay wait
what do you want okay we gotta win
someone dropped out one two one five
here from sexy
i can't count one
of you
we gotta come back how are we gonna come
back what are we picking seven what are
you picking
what are we thinking are you thinking
drop down
okay
wait i didn't worry about gold mine
and i don't know if she can join in time
wait stop someone please don't join uh
don't choose a race yet if you can and
then choose yeah um
again oh no i'm joining again
okay i'm still on this plane oh it's
starting
yeah i think this is uh
shoga9
oh oh no
they chose the clockwise or the music
oh the music one's rough okay there's 12
choices at least
i didn't want to choose the clock this
time i don't like ollie's ollie's me
it's smug aura you made it she made it
oh yeah she made it okay that's good oh
thank god oh music okay
music clark here we go let's go
last round let's continue everything
is good
we can do this
i'll do my best
yeah this one's a little rough we can do
our best but i don't i just have fun
this was the last race oh i forgot the
boost
[Music]
i'm just gonna start playing mario kart
because yeah
casually right
i don't
[Music]
ollie's really good at this map
yeah is it the one with the bouncy stuff
yeah yeah
yeah i don't know how to use it
i don't want to risk it because oh i
fell
no
i saw you disappear before my eyes
[Music]
sorry if i hit someone
yeah okay i can't i guess today i
learned that you know even though it's
tea how friendly fire is somehow
get me on the ground get me on the
ground cat and let's go
i'm so mad
i'm so mad okay one more one more one
more ring
let's go let's go let's go
blue shelling coming
that's garbage oh no
that's
oh no
oh i tried to get ollie but i couldn't
get her sorry oh my gosh i should have
held on to that i'm just very trigger
happy be careful there's a shell i threw
that don't get hit
okay
god trust my dressing skills and items
rng
i do see the red shell going around you
deserve that one people though
[Music]
lost that i could have had it blue
shelling coming is this it
oh because it only finished
only finished the course that's how the
blue shell came to
me it's okay as long as we get the top
spots we might still make it we might
still make it okay
okay i sent sarcasm
okay wait that was too fast i didn't see
who was number one oh wow
i think ollie was number one oh kidding
me
[Music]
oh
i got disconnected like right before the
last lap oh no
that was i sent my shark friends after
the wi-fi cables
that probably means that you know the
last round if if riso you know got
disconnected and the points got deleted
that means that the last round the final
result is not really accurate yes
but that's okay let's just say the last
round was an extra encore for fun
and yeah
and yeah and i would like to give out
some golden yogurts
we all want a golden yagu right so okay
they're not showing up on your stream
they're only a last name
but i'd like i would like to give one a
golden juggle to ina for winning almost
everything
thank you
yeah thank you
good job i'm into the game without
expectations
hi speedy thank you
[Music]
and i would like to give uh another uh
golden yagu um as uh to iris for also
being absolutely amazing
[Music]
i guess the strongest in the id team
being absolutely the speediest shark
i've ever seen
[Music]
[Laughter]
another golden yago goes to muna for
being amazing
[Music]
i didn't see you that much on the race
but i think it was still shining
brightly as as the moon always does
the darkest time
and now the golden yellow goes to ollie
for being also surprisingly new yeah
number one yeah
[Music]
squirrel
let's go
[Music]
and another golden yago goes to cali for
actually really you know i don't
you surprised me you surprised me callie
i was i was looking at you driving there
and i was like damn well what the hell
man she didn't even do practice arcs is
she so good
my mom was playing instead of here
that's why i'm so good
didn't i didn't get last place even once
guys that was my gift
thank you for changing me everyone thank
you
we love you
don't mind me uh chat i'm not gonna be
able to fix that now i think one two
three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven
uh
wait who did i not give up
[Music]
you weren't you were surprising me too
sometimes i haven't i had
[Music]
goes
last comment from everyone let's start
with anya
oh me
okay um that was so much fun but i have
to practice more it's gonna be next time
i don't know maybe
maybe there's gonna it will definitely
be next time yeah
there's always room for improvement
thank you
for the fun time
[Music]
kelly what's your closing comment
uh let's see my closing comment is kiara
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commissioned you
made all of this stuff ina as well for
helping with the assets but like
oh my goodness you organized the whole
thing and it was a blast and i just
wanted to have fun with my friends and i
was able to do that because you
organized this amazing thing just thank
you so much for for working so hard on
it because it was a blast
thank you i'm so glad you enjoyed it
thank you
mom and dad yeah thanks for everything
yeah it was fun to organize
gooda closing comment please
ah
thank you i want to say thank you also
to ina and kiara for all the hard work
you guys put into this tournament thank
you and i'm very i'm proud of myself for
not doing nearly as bad as i thought it
would and i would like to uh say that it
was probably because i fixed my switch
legs so i didn't have any lag let's go
gamers let's go
now excuse me i'm sorry i watched and i
won though i can use that excuse
me
even though you haven't played the game
in a long time i think yeah no practice
baby
let's go raw talent let's go rob ellen
sharpe
[Music]
yes so i'm just uh thank you for uh
organizing this i know we have uh
mishaps and some troubles beyond but yes
thank you for this golden yeah i will
cherish it and talk to you all right
thank you so much
thank you too
thank you thank you thank you okay i've
completely disappeared i'm sorry guys
okay irish clothes in common please
thank you so much for inviting me to
this wonderful tournament kiara and
thank you so much ina for the very very
cute assets
and
yes i will practice more
so that
we can i can get go against ina oh no
yeah yeah my goal is
my goal
to do this again hopefully one day
[Music]
thank you i hope yeah one day i want to
win against
inaudible that would be a big incredible
it's not that big of a goal
[Laughter]
yeah i'm so glad i'm so glad you joined
holo ian because that's what made this
uh tournament possible
i'm really glad to be able to join this
wonderful tournament being part of the
cool kids yeah yeah
all right
okay i'd like to say a very very big
thank you to kiara senpai for organizing
this i've organized it once and it was
really hectic so i can't really imagine
the links that you go through
for like long logos and stuff and even
the thumbnails those must have been hard
and also for innocent wife are making
all of those assets so quickly like you
guys really um how do i say it i really
appreciate it a lot and i'm sure all of
us do so thank you so much for your hard
work it was really fun playing with
everyone and um i may have not popped
everyone but one way or another you guys
will all be my
[Laughter]
you'll get them
thank you
thank you all right luna and bye closing
comments please
um first of all i'm thank you for you
kiara for organizing this thing and
you guys can stop
without you organizing we wouldn't be
like these
i mean it's it's it's rare to
gather all the whole life indonesia at
home and together that's true yeah so
i'm so thankful for that and also
um
big thanks to inna 2 for making the
assets it's really great thank you so
much and i hope in the future we can be
like this again
[Music]
yes yes yes i hope so too definitely i
was thinking like maybe on on uh like
around christmas or new year's eve we
should do something like this
okay
closing comments please yeah i'd like to
say a big thank you to
kiara for organizing it of course i know
like organizing collabs and everyone in
different time zones and like schedules
is really really difficult but you
really put a lot of effort into
organizing it commissioning like the
logo and everything really thankful um
and everyone feel free to use your hot
10 cards like in your mario kart streams
in the future too
feel free to use it
yeah thank you everyone for joining us
today like it was so much fun like
playing with everyone and i hope we can
do it again definitely
it's been a pleasure
cooperation this was a great cooperation
between uh kfb and taco
so well together you know
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together yeah we speed
[Music]
okay i know you said stop but thank you
kiosks
and
also inna
senpai ah thank you so much and i had a
lot of fun um there was a little mishap
there there was a little disconnection
issue but overall i had a lot of fun and
i would love to have this kind of
tournament again in the future let's do
it you are so good yeah yeah
thank you
training so i'll get better and meet
somebody next time
we're going through the training now
[Music]
okay so it doesn't end there i would
like to say thank you
[Laughter]
to to everyone here also especially uh
kiara and inna like
those are
amazing and also okay uh i'm really
happy because i could actually uh gather
and play with all of you guys here yeah
yes like well uh i'd appreciate more
more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
i
i'd love to and i would be happy to
participate so yes thank you so much i
love
[Music]
ah
well first uh i'd like to apologize
but if i was salty if i could say you
guys uh no ah that's part of my thing
okay
[Music]
yeah thank you kiara and and ina you
guys worked really hard thank you guys
and thank you everybody for
participating is really fun i know it's
hard to organize these types of collabs
everybody's so busy and different
schedules so thank you and i had a lot
of fun thank you
[Music]
we can like we don't have to relay on
these exact 12 members anymore so next
time if you want you can do shout
casting
oh yeah that'd be fun
thank you thank you everyone for
participating today um i hope i hope
everyone had a great time even if you
know maybe you were not number one
number two number three that's fine i
think today was really just about
getting together putting um two
communities two fan communities of hello
ian and her id together and just feeling
united definitely and i am always glad
to do stuff like this again so i would
gladly invite you guys again whenever
you have time for it and want to join
and i'm sorry that you know because
since it's such an international
collaboration um it's not gonna be an
ideal time for everyone so i'm so sorry
for the girls who had to wake up at like
6 7 a.m or something like that i'm so
sorry i know it's tough i it's no
problem it was fun it was fun
it's okay i just wish my parents could
watch the news
it's okay
i hope your mom enjoyed the tournament
[Laughter]
i would like to officially close to
hollow ian hall id mario kart tournament
everyone
take care of your golden yagos polish
him every day he wants to be shiny
and yeah i'll see you guys soon
[Music]
[Laughter]
you