alright guys welcome back to kiwama's
cheering guide this time for hinotoni
your cheering object of choice will be
light sticks it can be one or two
preferably in orange because that's my
image color all right
okay let's go
i i i i i i i i i i i i
oh oh
[Music]
quack
i i i i i
i i
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
you can clap when you go forward
clap
captain
cat says move is called ketchup
let's go
slower you can even do like this
[Music]
me
uh
thank you thank you
and don't forget that in the chorus you
clap you can put your light sticks away
if you want will you go like clap club
club
club club club clap clap
clap clap clap clap clap clap stand up
oh
club crap crap crap crap
get it
all right see you there thank you
geek bye