[Music]
wow i wonder what it's gonna be
guess it's time for mine
is this
four to be honest i wouldn't mind
cutting a recipe or book on fried
phoenix cuisine or
[Music]
kelly
halloween was in october and april fools
was in
well april
this doesn't seem like you callie
and i might just know why
hello morty
as much as i disapprove of you hanging
out with your friends
christmas is a time where i can close
one eye about it
the presents i prepared for you are just
jokes
these are your friends morty
you shouldn't be asking me
someone who doesn't know them at all for
advice
deep in your heart
you know what's best
i'll admit even i had friends when i was
in the overworld
and i had a sensei too
but when i wanted to get presents for
them for christmas
i thought of the presents myself
have more faith in yourself and your
choices callie
you are my disciple
have some confidence
merry christmas
and keep reaping
or should i say rapping since that's
what you're doing more of these days
death
sensei
let me get get me a rapper's 101 for
christmas
oof
yikes that sensei has a pretty terrible
sense of humor that wasn't funny at all
poor callie you didn't deserve that
you guys
aren't mad why would we be
you didn't choose those presents right
the
probably enjoyed that anyway i'm mad but
not at you
i want to go back in time before i open
that wait that's not how it works
i have to admit sensei's letter hit
pretty hard i've never had much
confidence in myself and even now i feel
terrible thinking i've ruined christmas
for everyone but sensei has a point
these are my friends i ought to be the
one thinking of their presence not
asking a mentor who's never even met
them before
hurry up
the food won't cook itself
from now on i hope to have many more fun
times with all my friends and i'm gonna
be the one who comes to their help when
they're down or out
[Music]
is