[Music]
so
take
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
hello good evening everyone
bloom are you guys ready for bloom
[Laughter]
there's some there's some people
commenting
uh on what i'm saying because they're
watching the stream
but they're commenting in the spawn chat
get your ass over here into the stream
chat brilliant
what the hell i see you i see you there
calling you out right now
um uh so for everyone who doesn't know
what's going on
we're doing a concert watch long whole
live has
uh today uh a concert
which is the first of its specific sort
um the difference to bloom uh
and uh whole life first and second fest
um i mean i've i've never had anyone
explain the actual difference to me but
from what i've seen i suppose it's that
bloom first of all doesn't include all
members it only includes specifically
those members who decided they want to
focus a bit more on their idol uh
idol activities and um
also uh bloom is as far as i
think and can tell only original songs
while in first
and second fest there were um
almost mostly coverage songs
mixed in with some you know
originals that whole life has but for
preparation
to bloom and they have released many
many many many
original songs recently which are all
freaking bangers
yeah so this is um gonna be
even more exciting because uh it's
finally i mean i like
i liked the cover songs as well because
that was really hype you know to hear
um certain songs uh that you really like
from animes or whatever
um like i was at rhapsody sung by
pekura senpai was definitely freaking
hard for me
but back then i was thinking i
wish they had more original songs would
be kind of
cool to know to you know me as a
as a um hardcore idol fan
from um hello project by the way uh
i i just for me it's normal that an idol
agency when they have a concert that
they don't perform
covers but that they perform their own
songs for me that was just
normal but yeah up until now they didn't
really have the repertoire
french wink winks trying to sound smart
but now they do
[Music]
um also today i'll be mostly
um probably just going like
oh i ain't humming and stuff but i
um even though i listened to all of the
songs um the new songs
i don't know the lyrics uh not really so
except for blue clapper because i
listened to that about 30 times thanks
to polka senpai
blue clappers one of those songs that
for some reason that i cannot explain
myself i do know the lyrics too
to some extent why could that be
but other than that i i probably won't
be singing along which you guys maybe
even prefer
anyway so yeah i'll shut up uh and um
but i will hi nina i also saw apparently
you lisa is in the chat too sorry i have
i have too many windows to look at right
now i don't know what's going on
um what was i going to say
ah one question uh i'm watching on spawn
um
last time i had this delay until i
changed one setting was it
should i turn the low latency mode on
lisa and lena here yeah we're having a
collab tomorrow on my channel with lisa
and lena and ina
thanks for coming by turn turn low
lighting okay okay
even if i turn it on though we have this
problem that turn it on
go into my chat why are you writing that
into the sponsor oh my god
[Laughter]
what was i going to say oh yeah even if
i turn that on we'll have uh
this problem that you know because i'm
streaming there will be like one two
three five second delay or something
like that uh
so maybe if you guys want to be
perfectly in sync with me
so that it won't be awkward so that i
won't be chanting out of sync
then maybe after bloom starts and my
stream
also starts to watch along maybe maybe
stop bloom
for three seconds like you can stop the
stream and then
continue and then you just i think you
should be able to delay
your stream at your bloom window if you
get what i'm talking about you can also
still then later on catch up but
yeah it's funny how to think no please
no
no no
um
i think you could even i guess you could
even stop the bloom
stream now for three seconds and then
try to sync it up with me but there's
nothing really i can tell you right now
to
to tell you where i am and what i see uh
what person of chat is in japan actually
good question because uh last time in
the last
uh concert horror live second fest there
were a bunch of other girls doing
watch-alongs but this time it's only me
so i wonder
japanese bros raise your hands go now
let's see how many
japanese bros are here
because i'm the only one doing a watch
along and it seemed like a lot of them
were excited
for
[Music]
welcome so happy to have you guys here
one one thing i've been thinking so i've
been
uh looking at and listening a lot to the
original songs today and one thing i've
noticed wait a second
pecora senpai is only in one
of the songs
but then i realized i guess that
probably means
that she'll probably be performing
maybe i mean i don't know but probably i
would i would think she would even
then like because she's in she's not
featured in many
original songs so she'd probably be
performing her original song
and the pickle miko song probably
the curry song also maybe yeah maybe oh
well there must be there wait let me
change my sitting position
there must be more there must be more
if there's nothing more peculiar than my
content
i'm gonna go freaking insane i'm gonna
boycott everything
it must be more oh my god people
literally
um quoting me in the in the
well what else was i gonna say oh yeah
everyone who
doesn't have a ticket yet uh why not
i mean if okay i get the broken but if
uh it's
gonna be starting in 15 minutes you
should go get it now quickly
you can also one thing for the broken um
nico nico you can watch
the first 30 minutes of the concert
for free again just like last time and
for the people who are um
for the people for the people who are uh
who can't watch the full concert now for
time reasons or whatever
and if it works like last time which i
think it does then you can watch it for
up to one month until uh after
the actual stream happens
tonight
for some reason my camera can't show it
i don't know there's some some bug in
the camera so it doesn't show up on the
camera i'm obviously
actually wearing mine
[Music]
okay
i want the bloomer to bloom did you guys
see the blue merch
it looks so aesthetic i mean looking at
it from the standpoint of a girl
the blue merchandise
it's so on point so cute
so cute i love the merchandise
it's like they mixed uh like all the
colors from the logo
like gray and purple and light blue and
like all kinds of you know
pastel colors i really like that bloomer
yeah well blueberries oh that's the
that's uh
can we can we just uh never use the word
boomer ever again and we're just
to say bloomer from now on i can proudly
say
i'm a bloomer
boomerang
[Laughter]
some pants that you wear
oh my god we're starting in five minutes
oh wait wait wait i'm
go i'm confused 15 minutes right 15
minutes to wait okay
bloomers of course um
you know i always wear uh bloomers or
something similar
underneath my skirt to hide
my uh
to hide hide my secrets
and if you didn't buy the ticket yet
it's in my description you can buy it
either for spawn or for nico nico
um the difference is uh on nico nico
there's that there's
different different payment options i
think on spawn you can only pay with
credit card
maybe can anyone confirm that is that
true
and then on nico nico you would have the
option to pay in paypal
um but but nico nico only has certain
sections
translated to engl like you can set the
language of niconico to english but not
everything will
um turn into english but yeah basically
on nico nicole
you can use paypal but with the paypal
you buy points and with the points you
buy the ticket
it's just uh it sounds a bit complicated
but it's really easy it's like a
like you know a gacha currency
oh yeah also apparently uh spawn has a
bit
better uh quality 1080p
while nico nico only has 720p minado
where are you guys watching it everyone
i also noticed last time in second fest
because inna was watching nico nicole
uh nikolico had less delay
i think spawn
a few japanese people are using spawn
because it's
uh niko because that's just what they're
that's like
for the people who don't know nico nico
is like the the japanese version of
youtube
[Music]
hi everyone
you should sync yourself up to me let's
just stop
spawn for for three seconds
[Music]
i love how polka is just doing a
freaking
360. oh wait is is botan senpai
like like for helping her do the 360
like is it did polka
like basically jump off of his hands is
that what's happening
bye
yeah so who managed to sync up to me now
and who is still out of sync
who did it and who didn't do it are you
in sync
guys i'm one second ahead then just stop
the the the spawn for one more second
again
you're ahead of me okay well as long as
it's not wait i'm ahead of you
that's interesting
looks like she likes it oh my god
[Laughter]
talking to
[Music]
is talking last time in second fence
they
let um who have english and indonesia
and fifth gen do this announcement
but this time this time i can already
tell you
there is no kiara there is no kiara
[Music]
no kiara this time nokia
nothing nothing at all not no also no
surprise like a song where we were
featured no no
nothing at least i don't know about it
kayla's right there exactly you know if
i'm not in the concert then i gotta you
know include myself in some way so here
i am
doing a watch along
oh yeah let me translate that too she's
talking about you're allowed to share
screenshots
and upload them on twitter and so on
please use the the hashtag the japanese
one hannah saku
but no videos and no audio
uh shall be displayed
and uh obviously don't do anything
illegal like restreaming it okay
support hello lab if you like her life
so much then support her life by getting
a ticket and watching them
concert together with me yeah
if you see anything like restreaming it
you're welcome to report it
to um uh cover on the whole live uh
contact page thank you thank you
but don't don't even mention it here
don't even say anything about it just
uh copy the link and report it to
the contact form on the homepage
[Laughter]
we're starting soon we're still eight
minutes oh my god the time is
going by so slowly right now
today was the first time that i actually
um listened properly to all of the
the new songs and i have to say they're
so
such freaking bangers and there's like
so many different genres they did like
they did cute anime songs they did um
something what's that what's a genre
called the one that
is that kind of jazzy electro swing ah
that's it yeah and i think it's called a
lecture swing or something like that
that was freaking cool um and blue
clapper is like edm style
they have some i think they did that on
purpose little literally every
song sounds very very different to me
while
i have to say that the original whole
life songs the chinese money story
and um the other one
they do have a very similar sound to
each other
um but the new ones
are all very different um kiramiki
yeah yeah i feel like they had a very
similar sound i don't know if you guys
understand get what i mean
i think it's just you know and somebody
said that to me like my own songs you
know tony and heart challenger
sound so alike and i'm like what the
hell they are so freaking different they
couldn't be more different
and i think it's people who don't listen
to j-pop at all
don't really hear a difference with
ourselves
i still think that's freaking weird but
um
[Music]
can we do another uh sync time thingy
yes and then let me
let me um do it
sparkles
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
guys
laughs
that made it worse no way
oh god let me sing i'm getting sick hey
guys i had pancakes today
and they turned out really good i mean i
made pancakes and then i added
ammo ichigo japanese really good
strawberries every time i buy
strawberries in japan
it was just so freaking good
there's never like a bad strawberry in
the package
i mean pancakes or strawberry but of
course nutella how
obviously obviously i put nutella on
there as well
i still have some in the fridge but
they're uh i think i'm thinking of
reading them tomorrow but hey pancakes
are easy to make i'm sure you can make
them too
if you can make fake takoyaki then i'm
sure you can also make pancakes
did you did you notice that the slight
burn i put in there
wow
oh
just got some inside knowledge that i
cannot talk about
not tackle about hey
[Applause]
you scare me
it could be good
ah i just wanted to say that on saturday
and sunday and having uh on saturday
uh a concert stream with kelly and on
sunday a concert stream with nene
and uh i i started planning the songs
and so on
i think it's gonna be great
[Music]
oh
yo shit's freaking going
hmm
oh my god oh my god we're freaking
starting hunting
got it
first time all original songs uh concert
oh my god
clap
[Music]
cute
yay
[Music]
[Laughter]
yay
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
pie
[Music]
is
sexy boomer bloomer
i'm exhausted
wow
[Music]
hey
seven six
five five
three
[Laughter]
oh my god i'm sweating
oh five second delay go fix it
sweating already oh my god whoa
oh the set is so pretty
oh dreaming days
cute oh my god
i thought they were gonna do like an
opening act with the uh
fifth gen
[Music]
all the stage is so pretty
is really bouncy
well mata sampa
looks uh kind of big
oh the image colors
[Music]
oh my god she's cute everyone's so cute
what
[Music]
[Laughter]
i love this song oh
i was so proud of them
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
wow this stage is so sparkly look at
those line effects
oh oh it's there's an e
on there
everyone started out so cute i was
surprised i thought they were gonna do
like an opening act of
5th gen
thank you everyone for coming to the
first concert of bloom
i think that's what i said
how was it to perform dreaming days for
the first time
oh
from the beginning i've been an idol
doing the choreo um
she likes that particular somebody likes
that part when they do like this
oh she says all songs will be originals
i was talking always and i'm not sure
but i think she asked if you all
listen to the songs beforehand
i think they're saying yes they did
oh
apparently there's gonna be some solo
sounds as well
which i think hints to peculiar senpai
rage is so cute
self-introducing she says she's the
pure pure idol
yeah yeah very pure very pre-indeed
only to this is pure
[Music]
foreign
just had to say it was earth
oh oh really
really hey
[Music]
can we can someone confirm that
really
what really number two
you say oh it is really
what really
x oh oh it's screenshot time
wow keep on twinning everyone keep on
tweeting
if you got a hands-free
she says it's smelling really good here
good scent
oh my gosh as it might be because of
your sweat
oh no it's more over there it's over
there i pick what i say smells good
what the hell hello excuse me i wanna
smell
it
oh because she's a bunny and she's a
wolf
oh we still have to sing so and we gotta
you know
uh hold back a little bit they say
with that set we will show you
how i do how much we are idols so please
look at us
and support us
and it's time for the next song
oh my god damn it
and placed it
uh
those are the next members singing i see
a question bye and mega sample i think
and i think foreign
and oh there we go around
i
[Laughter]
hey
it's so cute
[Music]
hmm
i
my
oh
[Music]
da everyone who has a towel has to turn
it around like that
okay
hmm
oh
i i i i
i i
oh my god it's so pretty it's so cute
it's so aesthetic i love the songs help
me
cycle
oh
yes
tea
[Music]
hi
[Laughter]
did
can you tell that i was doing the same
thing with my hands
you probably not
i i i i
i
yo
hi hmm
laughs
[Music]
hell yeah i i i
i i i wonderful absolutely wonderful
she's asking how her air guitar skills
are what are you saying guys
well done yeah yeah keep it going
looks very realistic
oh he
i
i i just start working well i love it i
i i i i
i
[Music]
mm-hmm
all the graphics are so pretty
i mean her whole thing being sakura
cherry blossoms is just perfect for the
concert obviously
just fits so well in
she said it just started
oh wait we just got so let's so let's
freaking go
yep
[Music]
did you say [\h__\h] you or thank you
did she say [\h__\h] you or thank you
[Music]
oh
m
oh she's so cute help me
[Music]
hi
hmm
[Music]
i'm getting dizzy
hmm
[Music]
uh
can't she get any cuter i don't think so
[Music]
look at the butterfly she had on her on
her uh
arms you see those butterflies did she
always have those in there in that
outfit
oh my god i'm a bad fan if i never
noticed up until now
what
i hear you
oh my god i love you
[Music]
oh yes
hey
foreign
i love this song
i was so sad when they didn't perform it
in the second fest
i
[Music]
well hey rap time
yes yes yes you're really hyped up thank
you
yourself guys i love no one more than
[Music]
got
this is like brainwashing
aah
[Music]
um
is the best combination ever
sorry even better than takamori what did
i just say
um
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for giving that to me i've
been waiting for that my whole life
oh
oh my god this is too much for my heart
and they're doing introductions of
themselves
and
she said something like she's gonna
crush you
and then dante was like girl this is a
idol concert
oh dante's saying she did a really good
job at being an idol in the first song
i did my best being an idol
that noise says she's very excited very
excited to perform here
oh
they're going to review the songs that
they were singing
[Music]
that she felt very uh connected with
like okay i can't speak english right
now apparently but like the background
and the foreground it was like
uh really vibing with each other
oh there was a lot of sweets in the
background
oh better not show yourself from the
side
that's indeed a huge difference
oh then they're talking about the next
song that came after that yeah miko sent
by solo
they say they were really hyped up
because of the song
i was looking from the side
um she says that the comments turned
into a
cherry blossom color
she likes that movement when she does
that when miko senpai does it
ah and you're saying that kannada turned
into
a huge pickle fan when she was uh doing
a solo song
oh she was apparently even copying her
choreography in the back
when she was watching
he stood on it
now you're talking about the threat of
pekka oh
oh no i thought she was gonna be
he was gonna be punched by canada senpai
when they were singing
but they're best friends of course
no i sent by scared of kanatan's power
she's saying what do you think how
she'll be dancing on stage
i mean i won't be scared of a gorilla
too
gotta be careful you know never know
when the gorillas
start being aggressive and crush you
next song
next song is coming up guys
who will it be
[Music]
which song was that with those members
which song was it again
daily diary i love daily diary so much
this sounds like um and it'll get
opening
i love it oh
that's honey
oh she's so bouncy
so badou
[Music]
did lyrics say something like let's do a
10-year gotcha or something like that
hell yeah they got to hell
no i know
[Music]
hmm i
just freaking love money senpai's
singing voice oh
my name is
but everyone's doing such a good job
obviously oh my god
yay
[Music]
hmm
her voice
[Music]
hmm
yay ah
[Music]
that such a cute song it's so energetic
i love manny's voice in that so much
what's going on what's going on
fireworks oh for a second i thought it
was like
real fireworks outside
oh
it's our god i'm glad they're putting in
a lot of solos apparently
i thought this would have last solos
does everyone get their solo
why she's so cute i love the whole um
the graphics the theme in the background
is like a like a festival japanese
festival
which makes sense because of her name
oh she's dancing so well
i i i i i
i i
how old is this song
since
apparently it's been around since what
june 2020 really
uh at least one year old
how did i miss the song
oh she says he's really happy to be on
stage
and she loves her viewers the matsurisu
i i
i i i i i i
i
[Music]
let's try it this is such a fun song
last time
[Music]
oh
she was dancing so much there so some
money so much that career
look at this angel look at her
for the win i love that that easy m
sound
you know our basic [\h__\h] i love idiom
cute those cute steps
she said you're the same as me indeed
we're all onions
she's spelling it out for you guys to
make it really easy q
u ay
she's so cute
i feel like her song would fit a
honeyworks song so well
sorry that's so random i love honeyworks
[Music]
hmm
i got a point thank you
yo she's asking if you enjoyed the live
concert
ah she's asking you to
uh raise your your side what's this
pen lights when she's doing the aqa
hi hi hi
hi hi
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
she's such an angel
[Laughter]
sasuke
oh now in the stage we have a fubuki
standby and akiroza standby
and doing a talking talking session
and they're going to introduce
themselves
virtual fox
and uh healing half elf
aquinos
oh she said she wants to do some kind of
posing with her introduction like money
senpai does
but she's still thinking about how to do
it so it's not
finished yet
until now are really exciting
she's singing that song where i
mentioned it's a song about gotcha it
just fits spooky so well
they're talking about all the songs that
were performed
oh she's saying that the the the the the
hanami song
was uh created right after
madhu sent by deputy made by her
listeners matsurisu
oh they say they got a lot of them
energy from the song that akwa was
singing
oh who look if ever wants to do two
things in the mc
one thing is
she wants to call and respond
oh let's go let's do it
everyone
okay you have to say she will say um
and then insert what you think about her
well it's already over you were supposed
to say i love you 3 000 times
oh
birthday
birthday birthday
what's our birthday today i didn't
realize because of the concert god damn
it
oh that's so sweet
oh she said she has a special
announcement oh
after after this
oh she's going to perform a new song for
the first time
original one a new one
what kind of song would it be
oh
a song about some uh like you know toy
someone that's uh
she likes you know theoretically
it's like a love song basically
and she put all her feelings into it
i want you to to look at her in her
song more and more
oh she'll sing it right away after this
it's the thing
please put your flowers down
oh
flower's gone one more one more
announcement tonight
on midnight japanese standard time oh
and it will be it will be sold
after midnight japanese standard time so
that's in like uh four hours
yay yay
it's asking if you're gonna buy the song
but i suppose it will be on spotify and
all those kind of uh
services after midnight depending on
your time zone probably though not sure
if they're going to release it
everywhere right away
so solo song from aki senpai
next up i suppose
oh
a gentle song
oh aki is that it again with her dancing
oh did you see that wink
what is this jazz feeling i love it
wait i love this screen screenplay
oh my god kawaii that's so cute
i love how they like adjust what's going
on in the background to hair
nice
[Music]
hmm
oh
it's like i don't know it gives me
broadway vibes
oh her voice is so pretty
which i already knew of course she's a
really good singer
[Music]
i love those effects
yo
[Music]
hmm
good dancer good singer everything 10
out of 10. everyone get you 10 of the 10
modes out here oh my god
10 10 10 of them
i we need more of those emotes who's
next
different stage fifth gen
hey she's asking if you're harped up
guys
i'm in pain though
this is so painful
now can i see
wait are you gonna perform blue clapper
but what are you gonna do about naming
parts
oh she's saying that uh her aki senpai's
new song is very
idolish because your previous songs are
more like fantasy like
well they're saying that everyone's idol
outfits are really cute
and that they're performing in their
normal outfits but still
maybe one day they'll also get an idol
outfit they see
i don't wanna see them in a little bit
oh yeah imagine putting some fine those
cute idol outfits down
she wants to uh
hype up the stage together oh
and it must mean since they're standing
here they must have a song together to
sing
are you guys ready to clap your hands
[Music]
she's worried about if she can't
pronounce the english lyrics correctly
you have practiced it like a million
times it will be fine
it's time to sing
just her heart is throbbing really
really bad she says
very nervous
oh because the same fights are
performing so well so she feels the
pressure
okay raise your right hand i can't right
now but yay
if you guys are ready to support let me
send five and raise your left hand too
so you should have both hands raised
right now
it says let's go clap i'll freaking club
i'm ready
oh
oh she said that you should ride the
wave and
go over the screen
blue clapper oh so unexpected be busy
clapping so no more
pen light
actually
[Music]
is
oh
oh me good mother shaking
little parts
my dream kanawha
[Music]
um
everybody clap your hands
clap
[Laughter]
oh show me those dance skills yeah
oh yeah those english words
[Music]
um
chop your hands
[Music]
you got focus show me what you freaking
got
hey
didn't you know
give me crazy
clap your hands
everybody grab your hands
[Laughter]
i i
i i i inaccurate stadium there's more
people watching
well no there's only that many people
you can fit in the stadium
next time then it done
oh they did great though they did really
good
okay
it's a really good song to hype up the
audience
i love the english parts
[Music]
hey hey hey
hey
okay i'll be back i'll be back in five
seconds one second
okay okay
oh there you go i thought it was only
two
[Music]
whiskey is
she's so cute
um
[Music]
hmm
okay
i'll listen to the song any night even
if it's not halloween i freaking love it
i i i i
[Music]
hmm
i can't
trick or treat [\h__\h] which one do you
want
[Music]
trick treat all of them
hmm
[Music]
oh
i
oh oh oh oh wait are they uh is going
straight for the next song that that
swing jazz song
that's as a lecture swing song are they
going to suspect
oh that song is so cool
oh nice transition though
[Music]
cute
looking thinking touching feeling
they have very they have very um
sexy voices what's the novel word for
that which one am i looking for
what's the word i'm looking for
meaning of love meaning of love a soul
tree yeah that's what i meant thank you
they're very sultry voices all of them
[Music]
i need to learn the lyrics for these
songs damn
i'm i'm planning to do a bloom um
karaoke
sometime soon though where i sing all
those songs all of them
meaning of love
i'm gonna have my own concert
oh all those heights
meaning of love meaning of love
meaning of love
yeah shake those hips
oh my god i want to hear it 24 7.
oh my god
she bamboozles me with her voice every
time
oh my god mid take one
meaning of love meaning of love
meaning of laugh meaning of love
meaning of love
[Music]
i i i
i i i i
i also want to make a song in that genre
i also want to make a lecture swing song
uh
hell yeah i just said i wanted to listen
to more of her voice so this is perfect
oh
oh my god can't even move my pen light
i'll put it down
i just enjoy this oh
yeah i'm melting took it down yo talk it
down
oh
ah marry me marry me
love me i love you
can't control myself
oh
[Laughter]
oh my god
[Applause]
oh no stop it with that voice stop it
how did you do that how did you freaking
do that
oh my god
[Music]
the way she walks too though like she
walks so slowly to seduce you
um i'm uh you can seduce me rebecca
senpai
doesn't know
[Music]
hmm
i'm gonna try to learn the song and then
sing like that
and i'm gonna seduce all of you
she's she keeps that raspy feeling in it
somehow
and like as if she's in pain but also
like in in good in the good kind of pain
she's like
she's she's you know i don't want to say
too much because
sometimes my english sounds weird when
i'm not even trying to sound weird but
my god wow
wow wow wow
oh my god wow
wow wow wow wow
wow
wow hey sorry i'm still very i'm
exhausted from that sexiness i just saw
schwa
yeah it's uh senpai and somebody just
said bye on stage now
talking to each other
together we are what one way or what are
you
some jet cluster i don't know i didn't
hear
it
a little bit about the previous songs i
suppose
okay she's pointing out that she finally
got her idol outfit to us and bye
he's so cute i love the ones that i'm
fine in that outfit
her hair is so cute though
oh with her tail cute
she says her favorite part is the back
part
i love how you can see that those little
hearts
still oh they're saying happy birthday
happy basket she mispronounced said
happy
basketball birthday
basket basketball
oh they're talking about blue clappers
anyone's really hype
well she really likes that choreo
they're doing it together the whole time
all um you're just talking about the
halloween song
oh somebody said she likes that that
part when you when they
put their hands in the front
she says she wants everyone was really
cute when she did that
and did you just look like all of the
other choreography moves
thanks for the membership welcome also
thanks by the way for all the super chat
that you guys have been sending mo
while i've been just going crazy thank
you everyone
ah they're talking about what
what is what was the title of that sexy
song
that they performed in a trio
oh she's saying that i did it perfectly
i suspect oh yeah
oh
voice i agree strongly
oh they're pointing out that they're
trying to do these uh transmissions
between the songs like a dj
oh a toy is gonna perform a specific
song for the first time
today
but i don't think it's a new song it's
just a for the first time performing
next time oh they're gonna do their
thing again
yay cute bows with wink
yes yes yes thank you very much
itadakimasu
so it is toasted by solo next
what is that combination again stardust
is it a new original
gotta ask the japanese brothers they
know more than me
this is like completely new
that's your new original song
oh it fits her voice so well
[Music]
oh
i wish i could sing that little
oh my god
she looks so cute that's just so cool
oh she really always nails those
emotional songs
oh my god so so dramatic so cinematic
somehow
damn
you're so sad
i'm getting um i'm getting the skin the
chicken skin
what's it called
did you get it too guys goosebumps good
smells not the chicken skin
close
oh my god
oh i wish i could have watched that
i would have gone there if they wouldn't
have canceled the the actual
live viewing like in in person
oh that would have been amazing
[Music]
[Applause]
i
i love that part from matsuri senpai
[Music]
[Applause]
voice fits this so well
[Music]
hmm
i
hi hi
[Music]
hmm
uh
[Music]
oh
i
hmm
[Music]
um
mm-hmm
look at all those effects on stage
i i i i
i certified banger i agree
wow wow nice style
fun that song is a lot of fun
it reminds me of a certain song oh no
this reminds me of uh macross delta for
some reason
stardust song stardust song reminds me
of macros delta and i don't
[Music]
um
maybe not mac with delta maybe maybe i
do mean uh marcus frontier
anyway this is like the the low voice
singers combination i love it
my heart
[Music]
oh they're dancing a lot too i love it
um
[Music]
whoa
feeling myself
that's in the lyrics i'm sorry guys
[Music]
yes everyone's so
dumb so cool
their voices are so beautiful
[Music]
um
song though which one is your favorite
guys this might be one of my faves
this is this really hits
it's very hard in my heart in my cocoon
that was my favorite really suspects
yeah suspect is also up there definitely
a
truck oh i love that one i love that one
too that's also at the top everything
every song is at the top god damn it
oh wait this combination means uh what
it
i'm gonna sell oh
are we getting are we getting are we
getting what i think we're getting
oh yes
okay it's freaking time
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
me
you guys ready to be okay
[Music]
sensitive
one more
[Music]
m
yes oh my god
oh this song is so sick
this song is so freaking high because
oh oh this song i love the like
traditional japanese vibes it gives me
krisky
hannah cookie
[Music]
me
oh
hi knuckle boogie hey
[Music]
bye
me
hi
oh yes give me that bass solo
and
oh
you're the reason i joined home alive
what you didn't know guys
hey oh whoa
that was so cute
that was so exciting one more solo
one marcelo frog
or are other people gonna join now that
would be fun
if other members join her on stage now
no okay
oh this is so cute
huh
she's done that moving her other song as
well she's repeating her choreo
oh
[Music]
hey
foreign
please give me one more sound of big
glass and by please
please
providing those lyrics in romaji nice
just thanking you for watching so far
[Music]
damn those romantic lyrics are just on
time
[Music]
that focus play makes me go doki doki
we might get the curry song
curry song could only happen because
they have a not curry version of it
[Music]
uh
ah
i want to be as cute as her oh my gosh
she's so cute
she's like on a different level of
cuteness it's like not even human i mean
obviously she's an onion so that's that
[Music]
how can you be this cute i'm an onion
too
somehow somewhere in my heart
yay what's next
oh okay okay that had to come yeah tell
me
forgot that we didn't have those songs
yet
[Music]
excuse me can i sing
it's okay
[Music]
is
a
[Music]
oh
yes
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
yay
thank you
hello this is the best agency event
she says quoting here
[Music]
m
yay
every time this song is so like i don't
know emotional
somehow even though it's such a happy
song it's so emotional
oh okay we got it emcee part of the
museum
hydration time for me though gotta
hydrate myself
yeah it's not the ending yet i wonder
how long the concert is
get this chicken instead i don't know
who you're talking about but i would
like to be on stage
yeah once again you're talking about the
previously performed songs and the
talking about alkalizing but i was
really cute
she's so small
she says we have we got that colored
into across
color
uh
i think they're talking about the
choreography again
uh i guess everybody wants to want to be
part of it
was dancing in the background apparently
the whole time
it's cute how they know each other's
choreographies even if they're not part
of that specific song
it must mean that they practice a lot
together
i thought they would have like unit
specific dance lessons but it must have
been overlapping a lot sorry i'm not
translating that's just me speaking
i already by the way i already put
choreographies for
hinotoni and heart challenger in the
works i mean i don't know when i will
ever perform it but it's already in the
works now
i got too excited i just wanted to you
know have my home car
choreography even if i can't show you i
already um
i'm already commissioning it yeah
let's hope that pretty happens soon
come and get me whenever you want me 3d
w i'm ready i'm freaking ready
i don't know why i just felt like it
i don't know when the reason why i knew
mani senpai's
lyrics so well is because i've sang it
in karaoke before but i really should um
practice speculation by uh song as well
otherwise what kind of nosagi am i
what kind of fan am i of piccolo senpai
if i can't sing her song by heart
i'm so ashamed next song is last
no
okay says she hasn't heard of that what
meow senpai says last song
why no no more more more
well last time i was really mad because
i didn't do an uncle dude
i was really mad oh
this might be the last song but today
oh it's the first ever performed
something they've never they never
showed or teased the coming song ever
and it will be with all members of bloom
oh
it's like a song that will put
everything together like a puzzle
i guess i did kind of tease that there
will be
some more songs that are not released
yet didn't they teach something like
that
or mention it
wait oh i know that one
wait do you guys know that song we all
know that sound don't we
wait do i or maybe oh oh okay
okay
i didn't realize this was not released
yet
am i blind
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
ah
wait anyway it's a cute song beautiful
song
i love that high voice the high tone
oh this is another one of these
here how do you say that tear tear
jacking is that a word
two jacking songs
sorry i can't speak english today
close enough
[Applause]
focus on the song everyone focus on the
song not on me
[Music]
hmm
she was able to come this far because of
you
when you're too fast i can't translate
that quick
a small steps stop stop stop
stop
thank you for the super chat
[Music]
mm-hmm
hmm
[Music]
it is so emotional
oh
no no no no no
no no no
i'm going up i'm gonna i'm gonna
[Music]
come on give me something
come on this means that they're giving
me something right because they're still
doing that
uh they're still zooming into things
[Music]
yes
she's asking if we also feel like we
don't want this to end oh it's not over
yet
[\h__\h] yes
she says there's more songs there must
be more songs
yes of course there are more songs
oh thank god i was gonna be mad
i was gonna be mad okay
oh
[Music]
mickey
hey
[Music]
money
oh
new
[Music]
oh so pretty her voice
um
[Music]
we get more multiplayer more
is it over really
curry song please please
curry song
wait they must sing one more song then
if they put in an emc here
we need one more song with everyone on
stage
greedy of course i'm greedy
i'm thinking of you guys you know you're
paying your money we want more songs
of course emperor says the song is
really deep to her
because she feels that all of her um
youth is in her life and
it's represented in the lyrics
and now she's stumbling over her words
so she's thanking you for letting her
come this far
and she wants to stand on bigger stages
in the future
let's go together can i be on that stage
next time
the secret new one are really deep
feels like she really did gave it her
all
and said you had a lot of fun
oh this is asking if you guys feel like
they improved since the very very first
live they did
which i'm not sure if you guys saw it
but it's quite a while ago
wait is this rtx time are they gonna do
the rtx thing again
at the very end
that was quite a shock last time
noise and fight
thanks ask if you guys are
enjoying your youth because she really
feels like
she agrees with aqua senpai and what she
said
she might not have original songs and
all that but
um she's happy that she was able to sing
like solo songs but she was
happy that she was able to show a bunch
of different sides of herself
with the unit songs
and she says that that that new song the
asura song really
uh really has some deep
deep meaning in her heart as well
aren't you next time
from now on oh there's a
important
this is not something big apparently i
don't know about it
what's going on
first announcement bloom
but not for concert i suppose
uh
[Music]
second announcement oh
oh oh uh some game
i like the kingdom i saw some members
playing it they'll be in the game
yeah i didn't take a look at that game
but
this is
five members won't be in the game
oh nice
oh that groove mix thing new songs will
be in there
okay okay okay
[Music]
oh
will be released which i think includes
all of the songs the previous songs
and maybe some new songs if i understand
correctly
[Music]
foreign
that game actually fubuki senpai
privately um
tried to sign up for the beta test and
now they're collabing
tomorrow in her stream she will announce
the collab once again
oh yeah they're talking about uh that
all these on these
solo songs when the members will be
included in um that
d4d uh sorry i'm not that familiar with
it
in that game thing
d4d
so yeah the album will come with all the
songs but with new songs
even more songs
oh apparently they're not even sure
what songs
oh we're gonna continue releasing more
and more songs from hello live more like
this even even now that bloom is over
there will be more and more which i
think is really good
oh please look forward to it
yeah do you know some french yes i do
there you go back on topic
wait i missed something what there is
what did they say when i was inviting
you guys
new project announcement you'll see a
little a little
teaser honey
new project what wait are we getting an
anime and i don't know about it what the
hell
what
the [\h__\h] are you getting an anime what
is this this is just a music video what
is this
hold up whole life out what nunny
what is that what is that
what
i said music video okay okay
that they're working on right now
that was really dope that looks so cool
boy i thought we were getting an animal
i was i was like real shook for a moment
like how could they not tell me
oh something was um given out in
in the whole incoming cat in winter
and this is like the continuation of it
of that project
kept secret potential i mean it
could be because it seems to be like um
whole life japan
even if they would make an anime i can i
can see that being kept a secret from me
yeah but now i wanted anime what the
hell please give me anime like a
like an actual anime that would be so
dope
let's make an anime though
i really want an anime
uh
oh they say they'll be um yeah doing
activities and various
uh various kinds um
different kinds of uh you know you know
the thing
last song
this next song is really really really
the last song
rgx times i'll sing a classic
apparently
which means
yay
that was them that was missing yeah we
waited for this
rtx time rdx time no
okay
[Music]
after like half of the song bamboozles
oh
[Music]
hey
i can't confirm what's mattered
oh
[Music]
is
space on the stage
foreign
[Music]
i wanted to see that in real life
thank you for the super chat thank you
thank you thank you guys
thank you
well yeah she covered it in the karaoke
stream
what are you guys talking about
yay ending credits
what
i understand check her twitter
oh kelly is in the
oh
only callie
[Music]
what what
wait the whole thing
it
wait i didn't recognize it
you didn't know that i knew nothing i'm
jon snow
oh i know nothing
now i need to listen to it again like i
lit hey i haven't i
legit didn't recognize her voice eh
wait was there even any voice in the
teaser that we heard on the stream
i can't watch it now because i still
need to finish watching credits but oh
my god
the whole song alone she sang the whole
song
not like in collab with other members
only her she's like the only singer in
that song
it
wow wow
wow
what
well no wonder she's so freaking busy
all the time
she does all these things that i have no
idea of
she's the only secret projects
no wonder she still didn't watch my
music video
even after uh all these days
couldn't tell anyone yeah i understand
that part that
wow congratulations
yeah i need to listen to it
i want to listen but uh because i'm
doing a watch and i need to finish
watching this
this whole thing here
oh they're thanking all the fans here in
the ending credits
every single hashtag is thanking
every single fandom
i love these photos
i love these little little like uh
behind the scenes photos
cute ariake garden ah that was supposed
to be the
i was gonna go there i was legit gonna
go there
[Music]
my feelings are like like a chaos right
now like
overwhelmed
done it should help me it done
help me
it down
well
ayton you're so quiet turn up your voice
please
wait maybe i'll just turn it to yeah i
just turned it to quiet
wow i wish they had a second day like in
second
second fest
uh
i wanted to be there i would i wouldn't
really want to meet her
goddammit but i mean if i would have
been there in person if they would have
they originally this was
supposed to be more than just an online
uh online concert they were supposed to
actually have actual audience but they
cancel it later on because of the state
uh of emergency in japan uh which sounds
really dramatic it's not that bad but um
japanese people just like to follow
rules you know um
wow
oh i don't know what to say uh i'm
really glad that they
i'm really let me let me turn on my own
music now i guess
um i'm really really happy that they did
this with like all
original songs because i think
if you if you were like an idol agency
must have its own songs and must be able
to
have a concert with only your own songs
i always thought that
and i'm glad that um they released so
many songs and put so much effort and so
much work into creating this
whole thing i think in the beginning
like when the whole life started out
they didn't know that this is what they
would become like
they wanted to maybe but they probably i
would guess they didn't grasp
the possibilities of what her life could
become
and i think what they have become
now is really ideal and perfect and
uh i'm sure that i mean even though
there's some
uh scandalous uh streams every now and
then i think that
where whole life is now and what we
offer
um as streamers and as performers and as
entertainers and as idols whatever
is um really the best form we can be i
mean there's always room for improvement
but uh i'm glad that there's so many
original songs now because that also
gives us
more to sing in karaoke streams when we
don't have to worry about copyright you
know
you know the drill we are very careful
with that kind of stuff
um but it also gives me hope
for more and more and more content in
the future and
um you know whole lives possibilities
there's so much that whole life can be
and that home life already is
yeah yeah yeah so i'm really looking
forward to that i think everyone
is looking at this
i think most people who got in the whole
life
gets to know her through streaming and
funny clips and all that but when you
look at this
you realize whole life is much more than
just streamers
everyone really just enjoys singing
everyone enjoys dancing
everyone enjoys making music it's not
only those members who are in bloom
there's so many more members in whole
life who just really
really love making music and really want
to be idols and
um this gives us the opportunity to do
that and combine it with streaming
um and it's really great great to have
that kind of opportunity
[Music]
for some songs when there's songs where
i can sing along because there were so
many new songs that i just didn't
remember the lyrics yet but wonder songs
where i can sing along and i just really
want to sing along
[Music]
i started in the whole life second fest
as well but i hope one day
or not only one day i want to make it my
goal that in the next concert
i'll be there too i don't know i'll make
it my personal goal i don't know if that
will never happen but
[Music]
did you guys enjoy it did you guys like
the concert did you guys like the song
i love all the original songs every
single one of them is a real banger
every song is so good so high quality
absolutely amazing gosh i'm so hungry oh
my god
wow um wow thank you for translating
you're welcome i i
i think uh there wasn't so much to
translate today and i probably didn't
even do that much of a good job
but maybe you got like a general idea of
what was going on
just a general idea i mean i wasn't here
to do like a full-on translation they
would have had to give me some breaks in
between because they were just talking
talking talking talking
eh
oh my god that was fun
that was fun that was fun they
they really um improved a lot with like
doing choreographies
i personally really enjoy um learning
choreographies and dancing choreography
so
i'm really happy to see them putting a
lot of
uh effort a lot of work into that
but shall we do a live reaction to
uh to kelly's son wait what will i have
to wait i'll just go on twitter it's
probably there
let's live reaction i'll i'll not play
the audio
but uh
how
three two one go
and they did play without the voice
first right
yeah i recognize once i hear her i do
recognize her there was no voice first
wait one more time that was too too
quick one more morika
shooting star
damned the visuals though what the hell
i really
wanted that in my nose wait i don't even
have her in the
credits here what the hell hey don't put
her in the credits
where's the credits to cali credits
where credit is due
oh boy wow i didn't uh i didn't see that
coming
up
yeah like i don't understand is this
just like supposed to be a
a new song right but with a really
really um
high quality music video it's like it's
like super special
because of the music video super special
whole new product i don't understand
like what about this is a new project i
don't understand
i don't understand it's a new project
but check the twitter
ah when i learned more from that
i learned nothing from that it just says
it's a it's
i like the first sentence the victory
group call life presents to you a
different
and another whole life another whole
life a second in my life
what is this idol look at the let's look
at the
official site
it maybe it is
maybe it is becoming an anime maybe this
is
well maybe the the song is just an
introduction to whole life becoming an
i don't know man i don't know
i don't freaking know okay let's read
what's written here there's a little bit
more text here
alive
[Music]
it basically says hello i've had the
members who are
the female members who i know i've er
are here different but still the same
which means
they're
[Laughter]
is
this japanese text is so like like like
you might be there might not be they
might be the same they might not be
saying mysterious it's like super
mysterious
again
[Music]
let me try to translate that sentence
this truth this story might become truth
story guys
story they're talking about the story
okay
i love the anime arts
who did this uh four creators oh
you can both of you you can um
[Music]
you can sign up to
be a creator with this project
really i guess like animators and
artists are
uh being
auditioned but i still
i still know i don't know anything i'm
jon snow like hundred percent
come on
is saying something on twitter let me
see
[Laughter]
uh oh wait that's what he was ah
wait are we becoming a game
the good thing is i can't leak anything
because i know absolutely nothing
what did i order one minute ago let's
read this okay okay
yeah yeah wrote a blog uh okay
in 2019 uh winter comic cat
and they showed something about a
different
world with her life a project yeah
that's called
uh all i've alternative and now i
started it uh
okay okay wait i got you i got shocked
by reading online game i thought it was
gonna be an online game
which one is it
[Music]
foreign
they want to build up they want to
construct
another world view like a like a whole
world
the idea of a world
by putting up mangas
and anime music video promotional videos
with whole life
oh and the reason why they started is is
because of a joke that someone wrote
on april fools last year
you kidding me
[Laughter]
oh my god
apparently someone there's a tweet here
from uk yamada
for uh april 2020 first of april 2020.
i want i'm going to make a whole lot of
anime promotional video
was a joke and then jago was like please
do
in a reply and then the guy was like
the guy was like oh [\h__\h] what did i get
myself into now i can't
take it back anymore even though it was
supposed to be an april fool's joke
well that's what happened
okay plan from now on
they want to um work with a lot of
creators
and create well a new like new stuff
together
my anime
i think i understand but i still hope
they make a full anime out of us with
seasons and stuff you know
episodes full episodes 30 minutes or 40
minute episodes
and then uh 12 episodes per season i
still want that and i will not
like now you now give me this so you're
just teasing me at this point
you take that stop you know you're gonna
go even further way further
what if i say what if i what if i tweet
on april fools um
[Music]
i will be the main role in the whole
live anime
and then yaga will answer okay let's do
it will it become
will become reality
oh man okay um
oh they're looking for illustrators
sound creators manga artists
scenario writers
anime uh people and game people
so if you if you feel like that sounds
like you
go ahead and try to work
with whole life i guess good luck good
luck
creators if you're telling that if
you're skilled
i think they're looking for you we're
looking for you
oh okay um wow what it's already 10 p.m
what the hell okay
i wanted to read super chats but i also
need to go and uh buy some stuff and
then cook some stuff and then um
i think so for today we uh is it okay if
i
uh read super chat tomorrow after the
collab
i will add it to the it will be part of
the collab
and wow
but thank you guys so much for the
support i will read every message slowly
tomorrow
the collab will only be like probably in
like one and a half hours or so because
we're doing a free three-year plan we're
we're playing momo pizza tomorrow
which is a japanese only game but we
will uh talk in english and we'll
explain everything in english
it's like monopoly pretty much but like
a really rough and unfair monopoly
and um uh the plan that we're gonna
choose is a three year plan so that
probably takes like one and a half hours
or maximum two hours so after that i'll
be reading super chats if that's okay
for you guys
i was like i wanted to prepare some
graphics to explain the game better
i don't know if i can really do that in
time i will try i'll try
but i'm also like more and more i'm
getting deeper and deeper into you know
preparing to move i have to do so many
things i've
i've been throwing away a lot of stuff
i've been packing a lot of stuff i've
been sorting a lot of stuff
and and figuring out a lot of other
things because
there's a lot more to moving
to another country to another continent
it's really not that easy and i'm
getting really stressed out i i need to
tell you guys
there is a chance that which is funny
because
it finally made itself into my schedule
again but there's a chance that i will
have to cancel
a super mario sunshine for this week
because i think i freaking need more
time
to do my [\h__\h] i'm really like running
out of time
more and more it's funny though because
i really wanted to like him
it's not like i planned this from the
start i was going to play
play it i was going to really play super
mario sunshine again
it will i will see how far it gets like
tomorrow
um i kind of i kind of really have to
prioritize my moving situation at the
moment
love makes me ex no really
really i'm i'm serious like i was really
trying to
like put as many streams in as possible
as long as i can
because next week
not many streams are going to happen but
it's looking rough
i'm so hungry now oh my god and i need
to cook
i was planning to cook today i was gonna
make
pasta with chicken
and spagel
what is that in english spaghe
the long green thing the long thin green
thing
and uh onions i'm totally i'm too hungry
and too lazy too
asparagus yes yes that's the one i'm so
hungry i'm too easy to cook but my
my chicken is only good until today
do you think it's so good tomorrow if it
says it's good until today my raw
chicken do you think it will still be
good tomorrow
no eh
[Music]
nope no really
put it in the freezer ah freeze it ah
in raw state or in cooked state
if yeah i don't really want to get
salmonella
eh it's too risky
damn it when i got all those ingredients
i mean maybe i'll eat a little snack now
and then i cook in a few hours but it's
already so late okay whatever i gotta i
gotta eat it and i gotta go
buy olive oil because i'm i'm lacking
olive oil
okay i'm so hungry oh my god
so hungry i'm gonna throw up because i'm
so hungry how am i so hungry what the
hell i ate so many pancakes
hmm anyway guys i hope you had fun today
in the concert watch along uh
apparently there's still a lot of people
who were just imagining it until staying
along i don't understand like
nice thank you for thank you for
watching even if you weren't watching
the
concert i hope that was fun but everyone
who
everyone who was watching the closet
with me i hope you had a great time
and i hope we can do this not again
because next time i want to be on stage
for
freaking sick i want to be 3d too i want
to be on stage
dance dance dance dance
i want to be there i want to be there
and i want nene john to be on stage next
time
okay i will not go on stage until
janua meets on stage in freddie
yes which i think should be fine
together like a proper one we're doing
one on sunday but that one is just you
know us
in our usual selves
foreign
in today's uh concert you'll get some
a lot of ninten singing with me
on sunday
revival
means orange friends because your valve
or
ends right yes
okay i'll go to the committee store i
think to get some olive oil
and i'll see you guys tomorrow with
uh ina retainer and this is senpai
on my channel doing a four radical up
which by the way
um i know you guys are really excited to
see that happen because uh
there's not many uh yen x
or not many kiana x indonesia collapse
and now it's happening i wanted it to
happen i wanted to do like a
english players-only moment
but the reason why i chose those
specific members is because they
understand
pretty good japanese so i thought they
wouldn't have much of a problem playing
it
and we tested it out yesterday and i
explained it to everyone
and it's really not that hard once you
it looks
confusing and you don't know what's
going on if you can't read japanese but
we'll explain to you guys and you will
be able to understand and those members
are able to speak japanese too so
yeah they can also explain i think
if they underst they they grasp the
basics of the game right now
it should be fun okay
so and in german we say
don't forget guys to watch heart
challenger every day
every day at least five times
[Music]
thank you guys for watching super chat
reading tomorrow tomorrow your school
bye bye
thank you so much thank you bye-bye
[Music]
do
you