[Music]
hello
you're welcome to start too
thank you
once again happy halloween
happy halloween
kelly kelly's still muting herself
ally darling can we come out kelly yes
kelly kelly
come out oh natalie
cali cali cali cali cali cali kelly is
shy
kelly is scared of halloween hi
hi kelly here i'm here hello everyone
yay my stream is on ultra low latency
now and i'm very excited hooray
is everyone too quiet for you guys or
should i turn them up louder
how's the audio
thank you chad for letting me know
anyway ultra low latency
from now on
so should i explain what we're doing
yes yes please yep okay so
and we all have never played this game
before at least uh like
10 minutes before this unless replay the
10 minutes before the stream
however i think i have grass grabs
scraps
grass grasped the basics
so i shall explain and
this is kind of similar to among us
and i didn't play it but coulda said
it's kind of also similar to dead by
daylight
right you didn't say that yeah in a way
yeah
uh basically we are all children
and then among us wink wink
is a secret neighbor like a really old
dude scary dude
that's always in the screenshots from
this game uh
but he's also uh shown as a child
at least in the beginning until he
decides to just uh like show himself
and so we are trying to like we're going
into a big big mansion
and uh there's keys hidden all over
that mansion and we kids try to find it
and each kid by the way has different
skills
depending on which kid you choose so
the the old dudes eventually will try to
stop us from getting those keys because
once we get all the keys
and open all the locks to a certain door
then
the kids win the game and i have a
feeling that
today in today's collab we will never
even once manage to open the door but
that's the theory
[Laughter]
that's pretty much how the game works oh
oh [\h__\h] oh
i'm on low power mode well i'll be fine
thank you for reminding me i should plug
in my my key movement
yeah that's yeah i think that's pretty
much the game it's kind of easy
um yeah that will be an imposter
among us wink wink and pasta among us
everybody wink kiera sauce
ah why me again
you're a clown we we're however we're
not gonna mute ourselves like we didn't
among us because we realized it's not
maybe
maybe not not necessary however in the
test round ina
was the imposter and she was very quiet
so
um maybe access if you're a child
just act like a child
is everyone ready to go into the first
round everyone ready
yeah you guys go ready to keep it at 10
minutes or do you want
slightly longer oh let's make 15 minutes
maybe
okay because i think we need my time
especially my brain i just woke up
okay ready up i'll find so i'll be the
detective
watson are you a detective i'm a
detective but today i'm
using my fps skills for good yeah
i guess i'll be wow
cool ah kelly you gotta return to the
lobby oh yeah okay here we go um
[Music]
here we go
i want the mustache too okay
cool i want a mustache like amelia all
right
oh yeah so this is your flashlight
all right
we have to
[Music]
stairs
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't throw that pumpkin at me don't you
stay
[Music]
what do i do with this milk oh
i also want to drink cali's milk wait
did you actually drink something
yeah i dropped i drank that in a carton
goodbye
[Music]
what how do you know that are you done
right in the beginning so i'm just
watching you
all all of you i'm watching all of you
so with
okay that's drop and then throw as you
click
i'm trying to throw okay you press the
other button okay
oh what's this hey why did i take that
key i found a key
[Music]
oh it makes you sticky
what are these do you know that how do i
know which door it goes to
the door in the middle and then in the
main room in the middle of the big door
i was like with all the locks
oh wait that's a card key oh that's for
upstairs that's right
[Music]
oh hello did you uh put it in well oh
i dropped it i don't have players you
can okay you press this
button guys hi scally i'm a gangster but
y'all knew
that all right here we go uh wait what's
up
oh you need can you need the key card
again
to open the other one i found where the
number two key card goes to
oh okay now i guess you can't really use
it again no okay that's fine
i'll do it well we're opening doors
everyone
[Laughter]
i found the way to number two oh look
around let me know
[Music]
i was on the second floor lads in front
of the uh
in front of the entrance to any of the
other rooms
i think we all know clearly it is if
you're me
okay this is not hiding it anymore it's
if you show obvious true form good eyes
show it to us your sexy body
wait what
that's you there we go
oh nice one nina no no no
no wait what i didn't even get attacked
oh it has to retaliate
no retaliation here
uh watson who was the only one who
stayed alive until
like she died yeah
gotta keep her safe yeah but i don't
know i didn't know you could get there
oh my god wow nice nice detective
oh watson on the roof wow
what no she's in the basement though
am i carrying us as always
oh my god
it's creepy just watching you gouda
officially asked for a kid
is she a kid or she is amelia breaking
the game where is she she's somewhere
she's like playing the game she's
glitched into the wall she's amelia's
breaking the game
are you hiding you're in this room
[Laughter]
oh
she's a tumor
[Music]
can i throw something on you give her
watson is
[Music]
wrestling you can't throw chairs hey
where are you come here no let me
try and turn my chair at you no
all right he's gonna go get a cold one
everyone enjoy watching
you put them in your truck with the
candy
no you know that's a little
i want to change my character i want to
be the one who gets the clues
i'm going to be the detective because we
need to
find those keys
okay return who should i i don't think i
was a very good detective i found one
key
uh but i wasn't really pleased with my
job so let's see um
is there any is there a kid that just
beats the [\h__\h] out of people
that's not gonna be fun too all right
cool i'll be right back
oh fbs can i can i hit someone with a
baseball bat
[Music]
oh he's an email yeah i think so
there's a character with a baseball bat
but i don't know if he can hit anyone
i don't know if he actually hit the ah
man i wanted to i wanted to hurt that
guy okay well let's try my
objective yeah oh okay i gotcha and then
it's a counter strike
what's the inventor do what do i do
you make items like the milk of calories
and stuff yeah not a whole dough
wait do we want to get into the basement
yes
ah yeah what's our goal exactly i'm
gonna get through the doors around the
map
yeah and then you open the big door with
like the six blocks and then you gotta
have it
yeah let's chill ideally
it's a good idea let's stick together
this time
gang up on him yeah yeah get him
dog pile on so with the scout you only
have 10 bullets
and you can only okay
temporarily
oh it's amelia all right and how do you
uh how do you
press what buttons do you press to shoot
uh q and then
all right guys so q and then mouse yeah
got it okay
that's easy enough it's milk all right
guys we're sticking together right
uh yeah oops no no no no i don't
know i don't trust anybody anymore i
trust gouda
because he's very unlikely got got to be
[Music]
it uh imposter again neighbor i don't
know
apex predator listen man by the way i
have a
hint to a key it one key is in some low
like tv cupboard
a thing oh i found it i found a key oh
[Music]
oh no i can drop my flashlight somewhere
you can oh you should turn it on
i don't know i can't go upstairs yes
well then we can go up
there whoa there's a coffin looking
place
what's in here
why can't we pick up useless items what
is it throw them i think you
can throw them boys okay hold on
[Music]
oh
i died
is there any way to escape once he grabs
you i think only like a certain
character can escape
that's enough okay
and she's like yeah that's okay
obviously enoch
are you are you upstairs or downstairs
i'm upstairs
okay then i'm downstairs
wait wait hold on wait
i can build a gun
oh no nice oh no
[Music]
people who are good at video games
wait what is the what is the goal now if
you're the last
you can only hold two things at a time
so it's like yeah well there's the one
character that can hold on
ah
yes
[Music]
bad
maybe there's some light laying i i saw
a few flashlights laying around
somewhere else
you gotta look for the key wait that
that cupboard
i don't know that was the one on my
photo
oh you have to like speed one nice nice
video yeah yeah
there's keys they're not all over
numbers
you got this you just got this
you can do it you gotta find this yeah
don't say the number don't say the
number
you don't find out where do you know
yeah i mean
very creepy
really creepy
hey what did i do
oh never mind
[Laughter]
can you feel that
not like actual key keys you can find
them in different places doesn't matter
it doesn't have to be like
a specific spot so wherever you are all
right you can still find a key for the
big door
huh yeah okay there's key cards and
there's keys
the key cards are to open more rooms and
the keys are to open that one big door
that we need big doors
yep yep we need to open
laughing yeah i think granada knows what
she's doing hey guys okay
what a pretty room so please keep
[Music]
but fear you can't stay in the garage
the whole time
girl you can't stay in the garage
[Music]
i'm good as bad with numbers
what are you gonna do with that a nerf
gun
oh does that work probably not
you put it in the big door that's in the
main lobby oh god that's all
right over here though
uh
[Music]
that's difficult man that's difficult
if tina camps in front of the door hmm
yeah it's like we i think we if we all
stay together and we have like one
person who does like uh
yeah be a good bait i can be good a good
distraction
it's easy to go that's about all i can
do you wanna do you wanna start over
since we're not all here it might be
better for all here
yeah yeah hold on wait let me let me go
back to ina though i'm gonna close my
eyes i want to test my
ah if you throw enough items at the
killer you can temporarily kill the
killer
so you can you can actually get him down
as well not only the kids
spam throwing items at him and the fling
shots shooting
or damage yeah
actually use the slingshot next time
i'm gonna do it
that's what
[Music]
[Applause]
this is a lot for one person yeah yeah
yeah i need to play we can style
that okay yes yes yes
is there like leader lobby probably a
zombie leader
yeah that's me um oh yeah it's a bad
deal
that kid is really useful because you
kill him instantly
oh that's op wait i don't have a
flashlight like that
did you just find the gun that's a
powerful weapon
how do i get out of here wait where are
you where's xena
sonar i couldn't take him
all the way to the finish line yeah did
you see the stairs
[Music]
quickly maybe maybe you know just heal
good
quickly and then we can start another
round
yes
would you like to be killed by inna i'll
go back to
i would it would be my an absolute honor
where where are you
who wouldn't want a parkour main lobby
main lobby
i didn't realize that okay it's gonna
kill her
uh
shoes on a basketball
[Music]
good are still trying to survive
just go bunk
bunk
cabbages no not cabbages pumpkins
can i let her
[Laughter]
[Music]
um let's see i like i bet i can throw
pretty well so i'll be
i'll be this kid what are the match
rules maybe we
can set it to like because you guys said
there is revive oh um
oh there's auto revive yeah it's on its
own but we never revived it
when you like fall and stuff and you
survive but when you get missing i don't
think you're [\h__\h] ah
okay okay okay okay oh wait but one
thing
one thing we can do is maybe uh the
number of locks maybe
oh get them down to five or so oh yeah
that would be good five five and
yeah and and the character that gudo was
playing is pretty op
if anybody oh then probably play i went
to inventor
of guns and then you have to build
stuff right yes but you find it's really
easy to find the stuff to build oh okay
i'll be an adventure kid maybe we should
also turn off key cards so we can go
straight to the keys
ah yeah yeah
yeah see how it goes okay i think that
makes it a bit easier for us to win
because other than that
i think we were it was impossible for us
to win
yeah wait question if yeah if there's a
neighbor
but they're an inventor does that mean
they're uh
item they can shoot the kids with their
son
i'm a killer but i actually don't like
ballistics you all know chad
chill out chill out now everyone who
knows me knows they don't like guns all
right listen
ina can you turn off the channel
keycards yes yes
thank you thank you okay
[Music]
we turn off player names so we can't
tell who suits
that's kind of a good idea i should have
thought about this before
it'll make it easier to hide then
because we won't be able to see yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah wait how come chat
is saying in-game voice chat is it
because it's proximity based is that why
you guys
are saying that
proximity based oh there's a thing to
use um yeah proximity based uh voice
ah it is proximity that would be cool we
can try that if you guys want proximity
based
okay i'm going in this room what does
that mean brexit
it means uh the closer you are to
somebody the
louder they they are and then the
further away they are
sorry
[Music]
i don't know how to play this game how
do i switch
objects
wait okay hold on two oh okay so this is
the glue what does this do
what does it do all right it's all
sticky and on the ground i'm going to
leave that alone
yeah okay wait where did you go okay i'm
gonna stay with you wait what if you are
adele what if you are the imposter
by the way i have a i have a photograph
again of
uh where the key might be to
oh where is the switch it should be in a
lower lower cupboard not one like this
in a low one like a tv cupboard oh okay
okay okay oh this is something
yeah let's go find it this
money can i where's this power
what where are you
[Music]
why is she so quiet quiet yes me
usually she isn't so quiet
yeah kind of suspicious i would
say how do i do this
me yeah
yeah yeah
[Laughter]
she's kind of quiet i'm a kid i'm just a
little innocent kid i see walton hello
hi zadon watson wouldn't i have attacked
you guys already if i was the
one maybe you're just trying to
drag it out
what's this do oh you can jump
that another flashlight there was a lot
of flashlights yeah
oh i guess you lose yours i guess
oh what's going on here what's that
laugh
i'm scared what
why are you guys so suspicious of me i
didn't do anything
exactly
yo they're about snacks in here oh
[Music]
what the hell
i can't go through there you know how
did you get through there
you know hey
voice chat next game
[Music]
the clown can transform into other items
so that's a different kind of neighbor
[Music]
that's no it's not great
thank you everyone for being with me it
was fun but i'm about to die goodbye
sayonara
i'm working on it i'm still alive i'm
still alive
nice so
[Music]
wait
why am i always so close to death
because i love death that's it
that's it no i see i
see how it is i don't know how to grab
people in this game
[Music]
i know i i pressed a bunch of buttons
oh god okay so we don't need the key
cards we only knew the what
what is that yeah we turned off the key
guys
i got excited
who is still alive besides me
hello i am i
am alive stay alive
[Music]
huh i found your bread where in
in oh my god i'm thinking that we ought
to we ought to ring coop we ought to
recoup with each other
uh and i need to make a rendezvous point
how about that
i don't know what that no um normally i
would like to uh
you know what am i doing
i'm mixing up all the all the buttons
what's in here guys by the way by the
way i
already got two keys so oh
i hear some nice music playing
that is creepy
hang on it's real dark
i wonder why it's so dark in here are
you lost kelly
i haven't seen no definitely fine i just
uh
let's go scared mom mom
who's your mommy come pick me up
was someone already here
i hear sounds why do i hear sounds
i don't like them
okay i don't need my i don't need my
flashlight anymore oh
it's sneaky
what is this sound what is this sound
oh it's bugging out what the hell is
going on
what the [\h__\h] was that
[Laughter]
my flashlight i just don't have one
my stuff that's a shame why can't i find
any keys
oh do you even lift bro oh the the crew
the curl marks where the key is oh where
who is the grow
do you see the crow oh yeah i see that
thing yeah yeah
oh wait then i i guess i found the key
oh i found the key
maybe
i saw something that i i wish i didn't
see what
oh my god where did i go i'm alive
you too you know right oh you know i see
you right there
you know wait nothing oh
hillary is not very good at the game
apparently what why
i think the killers are really bad at
video games that's probably who it is
that's probably who it is the one that's
the worst
games out of everyone they're always
lost
meanwhile in killer view
all right you know what are you riding
on you're writing on something on my
screen
oh yeah i don't know
what you gonna do with that killer
one lock done oh
one lock gun
[Music]
i
let's go we can do this
you guys got this it's only one yeah
only one left
what we need yeah
okay okay two more oh okay two one
forgot that there's only
four minutes left
[Laughter]
cali is working slow with these things
anyway it's just the breaks
is it not time there's nothing like this
is where they're scattered around oh
thank you for the tip
i appreciate that here we go found one
problem
there oh
[Music]
hey
come here kiss the body
yeah i have it now i have it give it to
me
callie i think it's time we finally meet
each other again
okay turn on your in-game audio
okay okay
oh he's on okay voice chat
on uh always on uh let's test it out
um
hello hello hello can you hear me oh
wow that's bad quality though because
it's pretty cool
that's horrible quality
oh hello yeah i hear you it's so
bad it's so bad it's so
quiet
but it gives us a retro effect really
fancy retro effect
[Laughter]
wow wow yeah maybe maybe we stay with
discord
just for fun yeah okay let's try one
round
scuffed but we can try yeah
[Music]
all good okay let me turn off the names
wait i'm gonna say something oh
am i
i also don't hear her head bob intensity
let's see how do we turn off the names
[Music]
oh then i can fix it in 30 seconds
she's going to fix it i think
and discord would like to let us know
that they liked it when discord company
was
on i'm not surprised
i'm not surprised
really oh like actually discord
this club's in the chat wait what
what discord's in the chat what
my discord hi this car
we're doing this for the experience a
discord like the real discord is in the
chat i had a check mark next to his name
so i am so
sorry it sounds just to me
in this audio they will appreciate this
card more
they say they forgive us
[Music]
this card says
very sad neighbor this coin
if it however if it's the real one thank
you for blessing
us with our presence thank you but other
than that
[Laughter]
one business doesn't have to restart my
game i think hold on
oh she's restarting the game amma is
restarting the game
no problem
what what is everyone uh i'm going to
dress up for halloween i mean for me and
cali halloween is kind of over budget
really yeah
what is
[Music]
i'm a dinosaur god
i'd be afraid if i saw callie in the
hospital described me
yeah it's a very good reason
discord discord came to my chat as well
oh my god
it's real score come to my chat discord
i'm saying hello my dad needs to why is
discord uh watching our stream
discord discord i couldn't figure out
how to do the thing where you
when you show everyone's big faces it's
kind of difficult could you maybe plug
that into discord options so i don't
have to use other applications to do
that
could you please i have some good ideas
i'm a good inventor or how you call that
i can make some
i can send you some good ideas i'll i'll
send you an email discord
let's talk business discord let's do
some business i'm a business woman
weak but other than that thank you for
your services discord
i really much appreciate it we love you
discord
[Music]
they're spending the best halloween ever
with us
[Music]
i just realized kiara sounds the same in
the game
does that mean does that mean bad or
good
i don't know but it's why is this yeah
it's about the same i'm supposed to
sound
good on discord at least now when i
bought my new microphone
don't tell me it sounds shitty on
discord
like like one of those like
megaphone things i bought a 400
microphone okay 400 or 500 whatever
don't tell me it sounds like a
walkie-talkie
maybe maybe it's my brain remembering
how your old mic sounds
i think that's what it is oh my gosh no
no really
four hundred dollars well spent
hey watson hey
maybe we should just do maybe we should
do this card again amen
right yeah yeah i don't know why
something on my microphone
sorry okay we will appreciate this chord
yes big
[Music]
they're still muted on this card oh
there we go here we go
oh there we go in the end you can always
rely
on discord always rely on discord
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay is everyone ready sorry i don't
know i was waking
you ready yeah oh sorry i'm an idiot
hold on here we're going
well i'm with her party
so turn the audio down
oh yeah it's turning down because i had
to turn it up because everyone's voices
are so quiet and now it's like blasting
over here
i don't want to be the imposter i don't
want to be the imposter
all right guys i think we spread out if
we spread out
what no why is pointing out
[Music]
who is who he is
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my god the room's changed
huh a thing that happens in this game
what is that
everything
whoa what is that it did change
damn okay now no one can show me the way
to the
to the room who is this girl right next
to me
you guys twins wait
ina is that you you're looking for keys
who are you
[Music]
inna is that you you know can you hear
me
yes okay that's you right okay stay
together
let's stay together yeah okay okay
let's stay together i'm normal wait
there's only one person in front of me
where's the don't leave me down
my own way yeah where'd you go
i'm i'm still in i'm still looking for
keys i think i got
[Applause]
[Music]
uh no i don't see anyone
i don't see anyone only the killer would
have recommended that we split up
i am uh-huh to death and i are meant to
be listen
either i'm killing folks or i'm getting
killed that's how it always goes every
game
oh god dedicated relationship with death
i am
you're in a relationship with that pick
stuff up with that
yeah why is anyone surprised
okay one feet down monkey down nice
[Music]
don't touch me okay
i hear someone say with death you silly
willies
what is that did i just get money to
make it
weird i'm getting rich money money money
money money
[Music]
hello
she gave it away right in the beginning
though
i'll be careful eh are you telling me to
be careful
it's like chiara okay what does cara
look like she's the one
that's like the the picture
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
in an fbs game how am i supposed to win
against emilia
she's an fbs pro
[Music]
i got no chance against emilia
i tried i tried i tried well i was up
against the top fps player out of
holoyen
amelia what end
we both sling shot at each other oh my
god
[Music]
[Laughter]
i agree with that statement
[Music]
is there anybody making it less keys
make it easier for you guys
yeah less oh we can get to three keys
yes freaky yeah
yeah but put the time limit to 10
minutes
okay ten minutes three keys no names
yes speed run you would run this bad boy
that's why i spread out and then you win
yeah i don't wanna be this guy he holds
a lot you said spread out because you
were the
possible before i knew i was here
she did an amazing job
oh amazing
amazing i get it i understand joke
yes that's what i wanted to be
pumpkin who have you ever things
[Music]
it's only three keys now money what does
the money even do
did you guys clean up money i think you
can buy stuff yeah
oh what does the hammer do
are you cool i'm cool are you cool i am
cool are you cool
i'm i'm cool i'm chilling are you sure
yeah all right i'll go i'll go with you
then it would have been the perfect time
for me to kill you
are you sure are you sure you're not
gonna you're not gonna
i don't like the way you're saying that
homie
i think i'm i'm not suspicious you guys
always think i was just busy
what's the man oh that's weird what's
that
nothing someone broke a pot
i broke a glass did i check that before
escaping oh who's that who is that
approach who is you is that cat you
kelly
girl's awfully quiet yeah girl is quiet
waster don't wait fix your rocks yeah a
minute
please do your best
why would he be wasting my run oh god
oh no no no wait who is this
[Music]
oh
oh wait i just don't know how to play my
flash flight's going
to the shots not even reload you make
things with this
why does shots not reload by the way
here what do the gears do
no they don't yo what i'm useless now
i mean i'm useless now
i got one key girl's coming after me oh
i lost my pumpkins
eena
i think my channel is the official
spectator channel everyone
i need to find the key yeah
has marked the key where is that
i think one of us seems to be a
detective to make it easier
why is that english oh yeah uh
if someone should be the detective
that's a good idea hi
oh wait why did that happen no my god
[Music]
how do you escape
press escape option to just go call the
phone
i know i said that before but really why
can we not just call
you call the police
did i come here before did i lose you
nice you know nice why can't i find any
keys
who's still alive besides me and ena
callie right
oh she died kelly died no
yep as i said dedicated relationship
with death no one's surprised
that's too bad okay i see someone i know
how that feels
i have a dedicated relationship with
that deaf as well
very dedicated
uh-huh i heard what's the word upon the
street
you gotta be afraid i have two bananas
now
yeah what are you gonna do huh i found
one
oh yeah yeah
girls i am dangerous again
yes huh i can fight again
so much for it a certain november
wink okay the girls don't get the joker
oh who are you who are you
wait that must be good that must be good
i don't think she's sorry yeah
wait do i want to run away from her or
what do i get away from there
probably running is the best option
nothing nothing don't worry about it
wait the crowd doesn't mark the key
anymore is it because i went too far
away
i think these bonds yeah if you get the
key
oh
oh god nice
[Music]
you gotta throw something at him wait i
thought i thought i already
threw the key oh wait sarah found
another one but he grabbed the key
somehow found the key
you dropped it in the garage um cheating
you dropped it in the garage
because i didn't want to hold on to it
oh yeah oh i want to see what happens
when you win
oh yeah it's curious huh
gonna shut up
[Music]
oh
where's the last key kiddos where's
[Music]
gangster
let us win one game no no
[Music]
you're pretty decent at it i think we
can do uh one more game i think
because it's uh uh in 15 minutes it's
half past
like half an hour before cali stream
oh you wanted that yeah oh yeah hey one
more okay
let's make it one to remember
[Music]
i thought i meant to leave one person so
they could win i thought there was two
people left
i didn't need you wait so who was the
imposter
okay okay because at some point she was
talking as if she was one of us
oh sorry i was looking at characters all
right
see oh cool okay i'll
i'll be adventure kid
okay let's go
who is it why is he so creepy look at
that
perfectly sculpted stash
quickly symmetrical
here we go
[Music]
i never dream pasta
she's smiling when she's talking i can
hear him
i'm not away from me it's not me really
i'm just happy that i'm coming for me
why are you following me
oh are you normal stick together
who are you and this is me amelia
jumping okay okay
i was just trying to find keys i don't
know what i'm doing
oh gears stay in the same general area
maybe it'll be okay i'm gonna go
okay i'll follow you up soon okay
what is this you guys seem safe
where's kiara she's uh somehow missing
out i'm trying to shine
[Music]
just trying to find keys why are you
running away
it's definitely kiara it's
500 you see pony
why are you scared of me
[Music]
oh i can jump you press spacebar to jump
i just figured that out
where did she go i don't like this is
too crowded i'm out of here
oh it's good that it's crowded because
then we can we can
i'm fine i promise you i'm fine oh god
kiara's here
oh no tiara let's help each other out
see where the gears are
let's make some guns come on come back
she's here she's here she's right there
i don't even know how this works
guys this way this way
has this place okay
i'm just giving you a chance to win this
game at least
one time oh my god it's definitely ah
i dropped my flashlight there we're good
i don't know how do you get to the front
to the front door see oh maybe we can
find stuff to build things
what what is that what is that where's
the music coming from
oh did anybody go i don't like it
where are you guys ron i'm i'm not
yo the jackpot i'm lost who's following
me
oh i can almost ah man i hope i can make
the gun soon
where am i here
where am i
[Laughter]
all looks righty a secret bookshelf
cute little kid
oh hey people nice
how do we get to you i don't know
oh man i don't have anything to help you
someone was here
well we are really high up i don't know
who else i don't know where i am
how do i get [\h__\h] up what does the f
button do
f button yeah hey there you guys are i
found you
kiara is taking the main door if you
guys bring stuff we can kill her
there's a crowbar and any gears up here
i wonder
can i make this jump camera
nope that is the answer to that question
oh wait i can help you
well you can get up by yourself i have
one too i think we have enough to win
but we just need to get to the door
all right i'll be bait i can beat a
distraction
uh-oh wait wait wait wait wait
what what what can i do with that what
do i do with that child
what do i do with it did i kill it
stop moving stop moving stop moving
the bad man okay
it's parrot it's uh callie harry is down
there she's so good
around me she's down there she killed
she killed her where's sarah where's
kiara
she's downstairs somewhere oh
[Music]
what can i take hold on we're safe here
we're safe here
you guys see any gears
[Laughter]
find any gears you guys hey we're all
alive
where
wait where'd you guys go where'd you go
the kids are trying to attack
[Music]
nice nice ah one more i'm scared
oh let's click let's take put your key
on oh
okay how come we have two blue keys
oh we need a red key and a yellow key
yeah
yeah i haven't gonna be useful and i
remember we're gonna die
sort of oh wait okay oh wait
oh wait oh [\h__\h] you're still not back
yet
it's our chance i'm sorry
[Music]
no i'm sorry did you die again no no no
oh i think she died somewhere around
here
what you doing callie waiting to be bait
we have all the keys kiara's got the red
key
all right let me pick up something to
hit her also has a gun
how do you know great news that's just
not great news to be honest
[Music]
but i don't know how i'm ready to brawl
oh chroma crow marks the key
who is alive oh we only have a million
and 45.
all right hey
wait why is it making noise like that
what
are we wait try to please try to i can
throw this
i'll throw this at him and then you can
grab the key
i'm a girl okay
[Music]
okay she's still she's still outside
don't tell them
you stalker
okay all right what's the plan here oh
[Music]
whoa
nice nice perfect okay oh do i need to
get the blue okay
oh no we already used the blue one oh we
already did yellow one
yeah that one yeah you have thirty
nothing i don't think we'll be able to
get it in time
yeah there's no way to find the last key
there's only one key though unless so
there is you have it go go go we have
i only want one there was only one i did
not think i would do this
only three keys and you guys did there
were uh
oh yeah we got two how do you throw
oh i see hold the hold one here
there is two
oh get more time when we open
[Applause]
[Music]
i can't believe that i thought i was
actually like
i was pretty close to dying at some
point so
at two points i think and
how did you know from the first second
that that it was me
just because you smell like you're so
obvious just
the way that you are you're just
obviously
but i i really didn't think like i was
thinking if i'm going to beat the
imposter i'm definitely going to
die and this will be the only game that
you're going to be able to open the door
but i did it it's good to be the killer
once
the neighbor yay did everyone get to
deal with that
yeah i think everyone did one oh yeah oh
nice
that's lucky cool
and everyone won everyone won when they
were the killer
oh yeah yeah i would say yeah
at the end um definitely definitely
yeah yeah yeah that was fun i was
trying to get it more often yeah the
clown was super fun to play
oh my god the clown the object's just so
funny
oh yeah basically everyone had a win we
are all winning
yes yeah yeah and that is the perfect
timing to end but kelly i think you have
something to announce
i do my new song is premiering in 30
minutes yes
yay and then there's a party there's a
party after that where we're gonna make
drinks
i haven't figured out what we're gonna
make yet but i bought a bunch of stuff
and if you guys go on my twitter
you can see the ingredients i bought if
you want to buy your own similar
ingredients so we can all make drinks
together and celebrate halloween
[Applause]
thank you guys how about you guys do you
have any do you have any other
announcements
friends i'm making food yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
the only announcement i have is i have a
legendary
collab with marin senpai coming up next
week
and i'm even sleeping over so who knows
what's going to happen
callie are you jealous if i sleep over
at madden senpai's place
for you what you want
we're i just want to make it clear we're
just friends okay
as are we no no no no we are boiling
then
we are much blooded uh nope not last
time i checked
that's not what the board said oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
anything else anyone wants to mention
uh i have uh i'm gonna post a video in a
little bit
uh cali is is uh gonna give you guys the
last piece of candy to the halloween
scavenger hunt puzzle
yeah and i'm to post the video after
her stream on twitter and you guys can
see the final piece
[Music]
thank you thank you ahmed for like
organizing this super cute
event scavenger hunt yeah thank you
[Music]
thanks for watching thanks guys was fun
see you real soon
[Music]
oh so fast
that was fun