[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
okay
in the cockadoodledoo no no
sounds so lame
the German version it it's kind of yeah
I I'm spelling it a little bit
differently but it's definitely how we
would say it in German
do you know that roosters tilt their
heads to block their ears to stop them
from going Deaf from themselves because
what we will do it so loud to that yeah
oh did you know I even know that
thanks for the lore
it's kind of crazy
it is really crazy actually
well well we're back
baby's gate yeah
yeah
chat is the sound okay maybe the other
chats can answer it too
oh yeah
I don't know why it is oh really maybe
it's because I'm like constantly lining
up
wait let me try to light it up lower
mine or high high because like my rapper
hat
I'm lining up for you
I mean you're permanently lit up yeah
oh yeah you're perfect
oh that's weird
um
there we go it should be good according
to the Discord my buzzing is like so
loud I'm so sorry if it bothers anyone
not that bad
at all from from the background yeah
okay good yeah wow I don't have to light
up people probably recognize my voice at
this point
Jay
oh now I can't say that it doesn't it
doesn't go dark it just completely is
not there
no it's there but it just it's just
permanently done okay I'll give you a
bright PNG yeah give me a bright PNG
yeah there you go let's see how about
how about these it's from my thumbnails
I'm the Yellow Ostrich streamer
tanakisha Korea
yellow I want this okay context I got a
super chat a while ago that was like
probably just a parody but they called
me a yellow ostrich streamer tanakisha
karya and it just cracks me up all the
time
honestly I thought that was hilarious
right uh it was great it was my favorite
clothes don't worry about it
I finally understand Cali thanks to me
using Carla in my private playthrough
that you your thing your class or
whatever is like stronger when you naked
yeah all right well see here's the thing
is that like this I mean clothing I
could at least put on clothing that
isn't armor and that would be fine but I
just think it's easier to cut to the
Chase and just be naked showing your
strength assert your dominance
yep why not hey it's Marion
hey
I've changed my mind and I'm we're
breaking up oh
Noise Okay
but he likes you all right
the nipples
are popping off
mine players death he's so naked
just confessed to me he's a vampire and
I'm very confused I thought we already
went through that
evil leave
no you can't banish him
man
can we permanently remove him from the
party no just kidding I'm joking why why
do you hate hysterion I don't hate I
just pretend
I'm a magistrate back in the city it's
all rather tedious he's a magistrate a
magistrate what's waiting for us the
moonrise Tower
neither do I actually that sounds like
adult speak yeah right big words that
adults use
mm-hmm
all right cool I get it moonrise Towers
uh well I don't need you in my party oh
game quiet okay
does this look right to you guys uh
small anyway so today's uh leader we
have decided generally will be Beetle
but maybe if we go to the tea house then
the leader there will be Kelly because
she's the only one who hasn't really
seen the tea house yet and it would be
nice to have some innocent mind going
through it I'm far behind
that's okay oh we need to get the lady
that's the first thing we should do yeah
yeah yes yes let's go I want to do that
let's leave the camp um
best best wife
where are we can I meet you guys at
blighted Village
okay uh how to how to map okay so what's
the quickest teleportation point you do
play The Village yes oh yeah I'm so
sorry that was so silly of me
uh yeah but still I I can't go to this
area anymore so uh I see oh you can't no
return
yeah is it is it like every act you
can't go back after after a part in act
two you can't go back here and after act
three you can't go back anywhere except
for the new areas
so wait there's something I want to get
from the blighted village while we're
here oh okay yeah you know how to get it
um I I think
so
people your footsteps
okay it's gone now yeah they were they
were very very bloody
oh yeah I stepped in a puddle
hold on a minute the blind the village
is so much more than you think it is
baby
Authority
um Mr cuffs
thank you
I'm not saying that what's going on
feel like something's happening
yeah I also don't see the role for
whatever reason
yeah
but mind your manners of course we will
signs and spot here
it was I don't it's in one of the houses
right yeah yeah I think I remember the
basement of The Alchemist building yes
yes I think
[Music]
no it was something I told you that when
you okay it's not this house it's the
other house it's the one it's this house
sorry
ah yeah maybe it was the Excalibur the
the the it's it's in the the bottom the
bottom uh it's in the underdark yeah
Bard sword I know yeah I know where it
is hey okay okay maybe we can get that
thanks for you nothing for me I found it
I found it yay
I don't know where it is down here I
just know it's here okay go explore
okay be careful
no potion of sleep yum yum
that's curious
I totally didn't know that there was a
lever there I didn't know that at all
did you guys go into a different room oh
yes
is that not what that book is I'm blind
we've abandoned it
it's fine I see the hatch now I just I
don't have eyeballs no I was like
where'd they disappear to I mean it
Blends in really nicely so pretty cool
where's everybody I I get you
suspicious poison that sounds fun
it does
[Music]
it look at it
yeah you think it's in this room because
there's other rooms the one that I just
opened the the door to I'll probably
the more interesting stuff is like you
know in the secret rooms
yeah sounds accurate feel free to open
all the caskets
good there's nothing in there cool I
need my book oh wait are you looking for
it
oh
surprise indeed are you okay
yeah oh yeah yeah okay all right I
missed it my run so I need it please
um
fully now you are surprised how do I
play this candy I am
you said to open all the cast forget to
play the game
I think this is how I play it and then
what do I do
nice
just a little refresher course
I'm ready to all right well you guys got
it all taken care of I guess yeah
the book she should talk to them to the
thing over there never so you already
know it right I don't I missed this in
my run through I didn't even come here
oh you didn't get the book okay we need
no the book and the book key so the book
key is also somewhere yeah
right yeah I know where both are
what's your name Mirror Mirror I'm a
mement race what are these answers
know this oh
good luck
what wow has Disney tried to sue
what oh oh my God this looks literally
like Snow White yeah
like one to one I think they invented
that
what the [\h__\h] yeah let me in you did
girl I failed once
[Laughter]
um
I wonder what that is oh my God what's
that looks like a trap do you need me to
disarm it directed knock it I think your
book's in there
oh wow okay wait let me see if I can uh
I found a bunch of Scrolls may I take
them yeah I'll tell you yeah take
everything that looks interesting I have
no idea tools so I can't lock pick this
people attack the door
oh I can lock pick this yay
oh we're in this room now
are we yeah
[Laughter]
thank you can you Cali we need you yes
you're holding a sec
please not ranged Jesus Cali I've got
gloves for you
good gloves
thanks in my inventory if you find the
blue gloves the bracers of the fence
those are for you oh thank you let me
equip them really quick yes going on
Liara Murray open
Mario
week
I'll let Callie do this
I can't uh I can't take it from you
actually here I think you got to give
them to me oh okay yeah all your stuff
is blacked out stealing illegal now wait
it also has bludgeons now I put it in
your inventory thank you
she got it there you go
oh yeah
it's the only thing I can do
it's an important thing we need that
skill we need a big tank big tanky brute
crap this my book that's your book
[Music]
bro
yeah
controller I can just spin in circles
I love this book oh
you feel better the second the book is
oh you dropped your book the voices
I didn't have an option stop they have
no hold on you
all you have to do is
what
did you do
oh it's just not he's got a little
firebread okay be careful
just just walk out of there just walk
just walk out yeah little fire breath
gargoyle dude
no one thing we got out of it yeah yeah
what the
oh
okay
there's the gem down here to unlock it
too I will I know where it is okay oh
Chihuahua knows it goes pretty deep we
have to go pretty deep for them yeah if
you want to like be fast and we could
get out of here first and yeah then we
have to jump into the into the whole of
the other building I think I don't know
well the well isn't that bad oh yeah
there's several places to get
all connected
was that the key of the the
It's gotta be a like a stone a round
Stone I think that the key I think that
was the key to the cell that well
we we don't need it yeah I can break any
any good
for your pay smash everything okay
oh yeah
we're back here still down there
oh there's nothing
where's the egg oh there we go right
here let's go through the well the well
is fun okay yeah I will even break the
the lock on Baldur's Gate
from the Baldur's Gate
smashed what does the gate go into
what's a gate Garden yeah I don't know
Boulders I guess
we sing the song of Alderaan who founded
Baldur's Gate you know oh yeah I guess
that's true oh conversation let me I
just want to open this chest really
quick the way it looks you guys can do
your little dry Stones line the wall
oh something Cali being a little bit
aggressive over there
Kelly followers
you got it just just definitely grabbing
some things wait
I'll find them sorry
you're in the well right next to you
I have no eyeballs
you have no eyeballs
that would be helpful
I think there is a forward for this one
okay where are we going forward what way
just here any any just go explore I
think the poison one might be a good one
direction to go
see you soon
there's a spider web
creepy or anything
don't get caught ladies
oh that's a save fail can I rescue
me
oh no
let's party let's ride along oh you guys
already started oh
but where is the battle going on behind
us or behind us
all right
oh now we know where we are okay oh
they're behind
are those little alligator dudes no
they're spiders
it looks like alligators from far away
they they do you're so right oh they're
kind of cute let's go
nice
nice all right I don't think I have any
ranged attacks
oh music changed
I'm just gonna yeah
[Laughter]
good luck
nice one puppy
[Music]
oh there's another one far away that's
coming up old blue one oh they're coming
all right
[Music]
yeah
let's go
no lupus not the Wolfie am I stuck I'm
stuck
you are
in the web still
yeah
far yeah um Chomp jump try jumping or so
does that works yeah
oh well good luck
wait I'm still stuck in the web you guys
need to get me out
another one I mean skill issue
sorry nerissa that's pretty rough is
there anyone else besides
okay well
I guess let's go Kelly playing music
yeah yeah let's go I'm sorry I killed
your enemy
yeah no it's cool I'll get the spider
yes can you help yeah we'll chill yeah
we'll just chill back here
two damage please
I'll come over here
okay but I have to I don't have no more
action left I have to help you next time
you can learn them this way I have range
if you want yeah I don't know do I not
have I bet I don't have any arrows oh it
hurts all right let me throw something
they'll teleport probably next turn
again
yeah Oh I thought for sure I could never
mind
you're fine you a little [\h__\h] into the
face
I'm trying to help my friend here
get out of here
go kill that spider biboo yeah beat him
up Eric Gonzalez
yeah steal his lunch money
yeah yeah doing it
let's go let's fly out of the web
my voice is so husky because it's really
early in the morning doing some tea with
honey
what did I come here for
if it makes you feel any better I just
woke up too
where's another spider
oh it's up there and I guess
we can just range attack it I suppose
or if you could just come down here I
mean that's what I was thinking too a
little
little baby oh baby baby dude
oh I'm hitting it non-stop today yeah
that's our Ranger I guess somebody tells
me we're not supposed to cross that bibu
is that correct yeah that is correct
that is not the correct
I knew that the poison-filled tunnel was
good to explore you know yes yes oh
you're going that way
naturally progressing correctly
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
yeah this is the way you know the way
this is the way this isn't fast away
good luck
Spider-Man yeah together okay okay wait
don't don't do anything yet don't do
anything yet oh I see I see the dark
amethyst that we need okay don't do
anything yet don't do anything yeah
um
like this
[Music]
prone baby
oh this is good it did Big damage
of course oh boy they can't do [\h__\h] oh
she's coming
I want she coming
[Music]
it's kind of awesome that was one third
of the health yeah we could continue
that whenever she's on the web if
anybody has something with fire just
shoot the web with the fire
okay she's currently yeah I don't think
she's on the web right now huh no she's
on the she's offline yeah
oh okay
okay I killed most of the babies
we feel very strong
that's nothing
I gotta rely on them
wow
wow what's what's going on today
we're out on easy mode are we yes okay
okay makes sense yeah a real opponent
hey that's raciality honestly
oh
come here
go up to this little spider
oh kill the spider okay I'll try if it
lets me not enough movement all right I
guess
oh you guys are blocked oh that's fine
incredible
are we blocking okay can I get another
move
yeah I can't see past nor is She's Too
Tall I'm too short
yeah Point Blank never said that all
right come and hit me
whoa
gotta get rid of the smaller ones too
that is true
I feel like you guys got the big one
handled yeah oh okay it's on there yeah
nice yeah I'll throw something you know
you know what to do
I threw it wrong Maybe
should have gone on the web more than on
the spider
okay
oh you inspired did you inspire me so I
got some garlic roll here
because you inspire me every day so
do I ah
does it go away
what am I using it
oh my music
it hit
Mutual inspiration
not the discharge when it flew away that
little coward [\h__\h] baby there it is
what a freak it's okay I can take a
little bit of pain a little bit you've
perfected us
very much
it's so big how can you make it
well you have to turn it back to
normalizes but if we turn it to Easy
Does It undo the multi-classing
oh because I still have my clerics I'm a
genius maybe next time we're at Camp it
doesn't have to be right away it doesn't
matter but um boy I might want to walk
oh now I can handle it
wizard
I want to be strong nice cloud of
daggers
and just making making me excited to
play on my own at some point because I
just got it on PS5 baby which means yes
alone
it's a different game is this rope that
the spider dropped good well are we not
done yet
be blue oh that might be good for people
oh
maybe maybe
oh Cali
stronger without armor no
hmm oh wait oh there's another just
doesn't like wear clothes just like me
for real for real oh hello
it never ends
kill one spider find five more
business armor okay okay
so some alone time with the Vampire shut
up Cali looks so much fun
excuse me sorry I mean like well your
character
wow all right because I gave that same
robe to Carla and she just doesn't look
good in it
get him
oh I killed that one
yeah
I believe in you guys
time to throw
yeah yeah yeah
path has not interrupted what are you
talking about
it's not that bad can you jump sometimes
it gets a little frustrating
here we go
yeah
all right wrote for somebody in the big
spider
are you okay
okay
oh no I've only got eight health left
is that so far fall oh at least you got
the thing right I'm about to I'm trying
to pick it up but it's it's tiny there
we go
acquired
yeah
okay how do I get back to you guys yeah
it was oh over here where I am there's a
little climbing thing
okay
and climb up okay yeah I see it yeah we
should probably short rest
again
better than nothing
oh no I'm not basking in in the the
weird God's love anymore oh wow what a
shame
no I mean I still have it wow so I
thought it was a permanent blessing oh
it is but uh it's you you have to meet
certain standards to reach it you know
what I mean so it's a it's levia Tara's
love pain is the path to Clarity when
you have 30 hit points or less you gain
a two percent bonus two attack rolls and
wisdom saving throws for three turns
pretty cool that's the buff
pretty cool have you not been engaging
in the sages enough these days it seems
not
so do we want to like explore this place
even more or do we want to move on to
the tea house
okay we go back to blighted Village
yeah we can we can just teleport to play
it
yeah let's just do it
[Music]
I got it waypoints
are we ready let's go yes yes ready
friends let's get it ladies
we gotta meet the hot lady
hot lady literally and figuratively yeah
she sets my soul on fire line two man
[Music]
but it will be mine all right good luck
I mean you can have him but
I just don't think he's feeling it
what else
I think we can go that's right over here
yeah
this was a bit of a hard one I remember
a bridge
I thought you had to jump uh yeah I
walked over a piece of a tree a long
tree log together
oh we can go on the other side there's a
side over here down here what's the Ping
again
it's up by the Risen Road
um oh yeah it's up over here
yeah and then we go up I believe
we'll find it eventually
yeah
I was loading off my weights to you
girls because I'm my inventory was too
heavy excuse me it doesn't feel heavy
okay people people has a conversation to
do I have a conversation oh all right
I'm on the way
cool I guess we go down here and then I
don't know how you guys climbed all the
way over there but we'll find it uh find
the way jump yeah Bender at some point
that would be cool
he's hurt badly
oh my gosh you can do I'm watching you
I'm watching you she looks a little bit
like Nami from the live factions
oh yeah is it good I've heard you guys
it's so good I like it a lot
[Music]
it even made me like one piece who had
nothing to do with one piece until now
you can walk over the water oh I guess
you can just walk through the freaking
one
underestimated your skills smart
not the bride
it's all right
okay let's go it might be useful
another parasite I'm a true so it might
be useful you are oh my God people oh my
gosh I'm special
oh
the last one I think I consumed so
and Theresa got one so
alien people should get one I want to
eat a worm yeah eat the worm yeah I'm
testing you the absolute is our goddess
she's going to rip down they don't know
we killed all the Goblins oh yeah well
um
like you has been chosen by the absolute
absolutely you speak with her voice and
when the time comes the truth so I can
make them do whatever I want
um
You Will Rule it flashes back to bibos
like half this person
that's comedic a crucial you have more
to learn of our faith novice I'm sorry
true soul I
I mean of course I knew it seems the
absolute still has a great deal to teach
me
um good job guys lighting her yeah just
just tell him to leave just tell him to
leave
killed that thing oh yeah I did continue
to guide your hand Madam as for us we
won't take any more of your time May the
absolute guide us okay bye bye bye you
freaks absolutely totally do
just wanted to get you out of there to
loot his body absolutely um
you can have it be boo
oh wait there's one on him where'd you
put that robe I wanted to see it oh the
robe it's uh it's in my first row oh
wait but I think I sorted by weight
transport it to me I will take the
weight off your shoulders if you want it
sure okay I gave it to you
thank you
oh
very cute little road
oh it looks nice taller than you
can I wear this
whoa that reminds me of your RPG outfit
yeah
what which one other one I'm wearing now
true
it's me
perfect wow nice
this way
the way
wait
to go this hold on let me think
um I don't think we've been to the Risen
road yet
but the reason I remember being able to
get to Carlock from here
um
but I think it's uh I'm pretty sure it's
up yeah it's up more you need to go
north we're going to hell
oh
oh it was I think it was the other way
from Playa Village the other side
oh yeah we're jumping over this uh wait
not this bridge there was jumping over a
bridge
but apparently I'm talking to dead board
but not really
examining it
I'm back at the blighted Village I've
walked back over only a few I presume we
go north from there yeah we go out the
other side and then go north
a vampire's been eating yeah
blood
oh nice okay wait where did you girls go
I believe and this over the bridge over
this side I think okay yeah
and Pumbaa is that you
know not anymore
I follow Marissa
it could be wrong
I'm saving oh
quick save oh no her Autos oh no brother
or am I that it's quick saving
in trouble
it's okay I come help to smash please
[Music]
yeah
with big fist
and Meaty thigh I like that fist meets
the eye
oh
okay I got you hold on a sec LSD where
is it I need to watch this ah improvised
melee I might not make the jump you know
so just in case okay let me use my mouse
let me just use my mouse angel
group pickpocket no do not pickpocket
bro
you don't care go on
oh wow that was pretty bloody
boo come back they're really okay
I'm not bagel
thank you
[Music]
getting thrown by catlins uh it comes
with some blood your back is broken but
what can you do
oh give him a fight
oh what happened to the doggle
fighting them I smashed them
it's not my turn
ER
how do you say it in English
definitely kill them very quickly
there I am
nice
[Music]
some some very fruity jams yeah that's a
lot
a lot of fruit chunks in there yeah
I guess they like it chunky yeah and
there we go
they're rough oh yeah
you're standing in between the three oh
no I'm sorry I have to make you wet my
turn
[\h__\h] I thought Inna was in a chat
because hyena
you made me scroll up in the chat guys
what
what where is she
inadoko
Cali punch him smash him kick him yeah I
did
again
oh okay
oh boys
no doing a little dance
Thriller
more
nice
bonus action huh
we're good
I'm just gonna electrocute us like that
I killed them very cool
this will not be the first time I
electrocute you don't worry I'll show it
to the next time
okay
come on kids wait let's take this food
because
um we need camp supplies yes we do
desperately we need to loot Goblin all
this stuff yeah I'm trying to load some
food too here and there
oh yeah nice idea
grab all that all those goodies
or you'll be fine red apple
milk
I like I like your um
rotten food
did you find her yeah she's down here I
haven't interacted I'm waiting for you
guys oh down down
by the river
um
see the one who who wrote the lyrics to
that song no that's easy
okay
you too she's on fire just like me yeah
Sparks like the flame yay she's starting
a farm every day
her Flames always make my OBS lag so
much is yours lagging two girls yeah
met some of the alturians who got
trapped in the Hills though
weird no easier
lights up yeah I love her too it's you
from the nautiloid please tell me I
found you before those so-called
paladins of tear did you not remember me
I had her in my team all this time loves
me what why good great
glad I don't have to kill don't hurt me
carlak
oh please hurt me Carla please
fiery as the hells then you're lost in
visions of Dominic Army she's so
beautiful landscape of fire yeah
you know right from above
mine
ready
I relate to her on another levels
mm-hmm
my my Burning Angel
[\h__\h] sake
that's like a bomb on my screen I love
her I love her swearing more please
I think all three of us swear quite a
big except for beers trying to get
this knot
okay I like her
I'm your girlfriend now hey you already
have a stereo don't you no no I'm joking
about helping me kill some evil she's
all yours Kiana I know you love car lots
everybody's turned their back on me just
because Darion decided that he wanted a
little poke
everybody deserves some love elf made me
her personal attackers
I mean
especially ogres took me 10 years to
probably Escape but now I'm free
congratulations goon off to goon to hunt
me down that's huge believe me when I
tell you I'm not going the latest yappy
little dog she sicked on me are nearby
posing as paladins of tear yeah
um
[Music]
[\h__\h] yes yes
they've gone far after the scorching I
guess she's great yeah we can work on
evicting this parasite and take pharoon
by the short hairs sound good
um probably my favorite companion I
think oh oh yeah I would hug you if it
wouldn't Scorch your skin off
we already have a Berserker Barbarian
yeah
sorry there's one at the camp Queen the
fun stuff without me got it
wait never mind I can't do it why can't
I use myself we go beat up the dudes
yeah let's go beat up the dudes yeah
this guy sucks Marissa needs healing at
some point too you want a potion I can
throw one at you
one of the things I had applied wouldn't
let me do my healing word so ah
okay can I do want more short rest
before this fight yeah yeah
that's a dude's head cool
it just picked it up can't wait to throw
it at someone you're welcome I'll let
you see me I don't know I want to go up
here before we start the fight okay I'm
gonna lose it oh I just want to kill him
yeah yeah we're going to be
understandable for sure wait wait yeah
you want you want to talk to someone who
will sell you things yeah yeah pass this
door there's a person you can buy and
sell things from we'll have to kill them
in the fight to come but if you want to
quick sell off some stuff you could
before the fight starts okay that's
that's awesome
oh maybe out out here out here bug it
maybe
Cyril Maybe
try try talking outside she's cute
oh yeah she sells stuff here you can go
first here okay we fear a mouse here
oh
she's going you died to her sales table
or what
well you guys are doing that I need to
how do I turn off nudity again I turned
it back on for myself
[Music]
for my private personal run I think I
turned it off private moments has
nothing to do with that yum yeah private
moments is like blocking the scene for
so no one else can see cool how do I uh
uh it's the quick way of doing this
again
is there a quick way to sell stuff I'll
just double click okay
just quickly double check and make sure
nudity off
yeah not that I would turn it on because
I don't care about those things but let
me see it's not about preparing about
those things what's it about the nurse
to tell me is it about the immersion or
something about the immersion in real
life
she wants the authentic experience yeah
I don't want I don't want little leaf
covering my my nip knobs I know what
they look like already you know all
right
I get you
yeah yeah you understand yeah all right
whatever you say
almost done
you're cool take your time
yeah
in tears name yeah
next one
I'll probably sell a couple things no
don't do it yet I'm gonna have to just
wait two seconds people
okay
we just wait for Cali I'm I'm ready
can you get away from him so I don't
make you wet sure I'm gonna go on this
side
you got a plan don't you I do have a
plan
freaking go or I can throw the Goblins
game guitar so hold on
thanks
let's do this
poison resistance could use that all
right um you know I guess that's
probably probably about it oh I have a
soul coin these coins
are they good for Carlock I don't
remember I thought I remember her
talking about them and I was like oh
I've never used this once no yes you
need them for her I think you can you
can slot it in her body and it makes her
stronger like a slot machine yeah we
also need to save the infernal irons so
if you see that don't sell it okay cool
let me see let me just grab a dagger
really quick so I can throw it uh no
yeah good idea probably good
hate having to do math
um right
they shouldn't they should really make
this a little easier to figure out but
that's okay
I'm almost done guys sorry let eight
plus two eight eight plus six it's 14.
all right I got it I got this all right
let's do it all right kill him okay hold
on I'm gonna enter turn base and then
I'll kill her
yeah
okay
don't make noise and wet
oh I didn't make him wet oh yeah he's
right no it's fine okay
now go ahead everyone end their turn
please
oh yeah
turn ended
oh rattle them
environmental turn
environment okay oh okay there we go
die
[Music]
oh I missed oh he doesn't like it
it's fine just kill him
[Laughter]
there we go all right now we go we ball
oh what the [\h__\h] what uh
Ellie
owie party time just murder exactly as
planned
she can't see
I don't want to go down to you
I'm blocking it you can't oh wait no oh
yeah he can't climb up the stairs
and take these
um
we still have some more right
yeah they wanted to fight Mario thing
I can't blame them really yeah who
wouldn't want to fight Mario okay
I need this book for my collection yeah
it's interesting I guess I should go
down though because they're all like
yeah out of my view
hey let you down
[Music]
oh we're gonna kill the poor oh she's
invisible
or bear
oh she did she turn invisible yeah she
did but she's still there you could like
if you have some AOE or something like
something like cloud of daggers you
could place it there and hope that it
hits her it doesn't work I'll randomly
shoot she's right there boom nope it's
not hard
no burning hands oh Greece
said all this stuff on fire oh yeah
Justice
that sounds kind of neat would that be
good for me that might be I gave it to
you
fan fiction
a pleasurable deal this is an excerpt
from the play a pleasurable deal a band
in no fewer than four cities for its
lewd content it Scales Nature led to a
number of widely distributed and illicit
printings
[Music]
come here Fair folk a tail now lost to
time in grief this man will sunk to
death Sublime a gift he saw to win his
lady's heart our Campion smiled for now
the game did start enter Robert male
tiefling crying Carlisle stage right
flash of smoke
weep not young man doe free your wife
has fled and comfort found in comrades
arms and bed she licks her lips and
cries his name all mine and now seek you
to be the apple of her eye
yes how does a stranger no such things I
ask Carlisle I watch you from the
shadows and I see your shame and grief
for Nature's Melody you seek to win your
lady and her bed to have your name upon
her lips instead
Robert you know my curse my pain my
grief my rope Carlisle of you I know you
seek a larger hoe to plow a fair mate
and sell sow a seed to grow but lag to
yeah Mighty horned at best with which to
guide a maid to be bad and fast
let me in let's go
it's pretty good that's the only spicy
book I found in this game
wow I respect it
um
I should have sent it to someone what
a severed head I was thinking of putting
it in someone's inventory as a surprise
I'm encumbered now what did you do
cucumber
Ed now I can't I'm too sure I put an
armor on you Mario pay I need you
downstairs yeah sure what's up please
come downstairs and help me knock down a
door without power oh if you tell me
where downstairs is I'll definitely go
there it's right here
the hatch oh
yeah I can't I can't yell I can't yell
things at the door to make it break
that's understandable
thank you
I can't burn a wooden door
okay we've got Kalia cook Memorial Day
Trap there's a trap there's a trap
we shall disarm it
my NPCs I will disarm me
okay
[Music]
okay someone come sit on the other chair
on the other side disarmed
I'll tell you what I find I guess but
be careful
Starcraft
oh there's a marble plate maybe I can
get around it jump jump all right
just a moment
let's go this is trapped and be wary
it's just all right there's 203 gold
which I'll take and we can split include
everything all right hold on there's a
great ax great sword Give Me Everything
and sell all these
I failed helmet want this
pleasurable deal hey they really like
this book here
it's another copies
on the shelves by the way hmm
the other pleasurable deal
is there supposedly
which one was with Kelly trap let's see
this one's just hold on oh oh this is
kind of good stuff yeah no there's
really good stuff in this room make sure
you take all of it don't miss anything
is that the same
a pleasurable deal
it's that book right there
just a regular pleasurable deal
s
just wanted the sequel really you think
it's more gold
didn't it say it was illegal because
it's too rude
yeah it's banned enforce it wow
I am from
the Quarter Staff
working great ax
okay get out of there before I lock you
in run
the where's that girl this great ax is
so nice just hey Kelly
great ax
no no before that
you say Cut and Run Cut and Run what
does that mean
it means get the it means get the out of
there
hahaha
thank you treat
you're sort of justice for great actor
oh they're really nice but I think I'll
go sort of Justice
book
good loot guys
to do it
what's happening what are you gonna give
to a Syrian
book oh
can you summon any small animal
oh maybe
again someone the perfect thing a rat
okay
and then and then interact with this
whole
uh
I don't see the whole
uh I'm probably too big it's so dark I'm
way too ah
oh I haven't perceived it I think
do I need to proceed it I think so
I'm way too big
also I can't walk around there oh here
let me get out of your way
I just can't get there no I'm not
perceiving it ah wait the barrel hole
okay okay
what is that blood I'm not sure if the
rat can go there
I can't if people can't fit no one can
yeah I can click on it with the mouse
with the rat
you would need you might need to Wild
shape or Mist form yeah
can we can chill you're familiar
oh I'm controlling the Familia but uh
um is there something we can can we
remove something
no it doesn't it doesn't
I don't think it wants to go there
that's weird it just says can't get here
oh you need to be a druid
um
I see rat
interesting times oh it's just another
entrance to the locked room uh-huh oh
click and dragged oh what
what what
you can click and drag to move boxes
look I mean yeah yeah
not that I know I'm using the controller
but use our inspiration
if we have any because I'm I'm I'm
reading it what are you doing oh my God
I got it I just keep rolling above 20s
because I have some things I'm just
reading the book
which book add a Necronomicon mm-hmm
oh did you put the stone in
yeah
you're very concerned
see it
[Laughter]
it won't let me in
are you guys seeing it
you've seen too much I'm seeing Norris's
cutscene oh okay
yes
are you in jail
is that good for wizards the necromancy
of Fame yeah
cool I don't know it's just as long as
you're smart it's good
oh I'm not smart yeah
I only have Charisma you're smart just
uh I am I'm really smart
yeah cool
we won't leave without you
in the house waiting for you hi hi hello
and a cute new little rat friend
with two HP sitting around
oh have uh any of you gone to the get
Yankee uh Crush no nope crash because
they crash what the correct
holy quresh in case you didn't know
what is going on
I don't know
I don't want a hyena here
yeah I don't want those either yeah just
leave it stinky here I wonder if we keep
walking down the Risen Road what we'll
find hmm oh oh wait there's a there's a
teleporter here oh way Born
Nice Discovery Bijou welcome to the
Discovery Channel
what the hell is this yeah I've never
been up here before so
I don't know
you're spooky
well there's some pretty boy good stuff
we can get if we
move on a bit from
here okay
I don't know where it is though
just exploring exploring this whole area
there's so much fun stuff you know is
this something is over there
you and me
um
sorry people you leave oh I'm being a
little nasty yeah be bullied everybody
we follow people
Mario pad like simple commands follow
people what's up here
or I'll be understand
I understand follow
there's more dead things yeah there's
lots of dead things everywhere I don't
like that you know they're feasting
can we kill them I don't have spells by
the way for this
that's all right um okay how hard could
they be yeah it's fine
probably easy
the feast is over
East is over come and fight us
we are on easy mode so uh yeah that
could it be
um
whatever Springs anyway
I'm so numbed what's that mean
couldn't tell you
[Music]
you think these guys can speak English
oh yeah you're gonna install them
yeah yeah on the bottom their mothers
never loved them
wow well my first Miss of the day
they're like hyena people oh yeah
who learned to walk on two feet okay
yeah they look like hyenas
pretty cool please Mario face smash like
red you got it
is here to do
[Music]
one bull bonus action
this
a male strike
yeah how do you like that nice hey
no no
I was sure he was gonna last longer than
all of us
gone
yeah oh yeah
rip Bales rude
[Music]
getting out of here
good luck yeah
[Music]
oh wait I can hang it
come on
nice shooting Tex
ANS
what
[Music]
what's this
attacked Kiara
oh thank you you're welcome I had a
bonus action
um
oh I probably should have given it to
the room
okay because they went for me yeah okay
I've gotta I've got a thing so okay
it's gonna rattle them
nice yeah
it's on you
what's going on
I don't know what's happening actually
a murder is what's happening
nice
[Music]
let's go
we need a little rest after this 70
chance
oh that's rough
70 minutes
oh boy
nice
I don't know much respect yeah
yeah nice
should we do a long rest or uh yeah yeah
a long rest yeah
what's in the core we lose these people
and oh leather
is Elena being oppressed
gotta go save rainy kind Fury is
this is a letter to the editor there's
this video over here
what's this thing over here oh there is
a thing shall we rest before we go in
there though uh absolutely
okay absolutely we should I'm going to
camp
okay okay
what what
Kayla
I took care of those paladins for you
okay girls we want to have uh
conversations together right not two
separate ones yeah let's talk to Carla
together yeah
um I always take care of my people Carla
glad to be counted among them
but I'm just happy they're off my tail
then again facing them down might put my
tin can into overdrive can
oh Inferno
you want my coin my soul coin baby girl
yeah I've been doing my mechanic anytime
soon so I'll just
does that cut off
we can't give her let me turn off the
filter
um
certainly can't do other things
you know so back off
don't worry about it
good now
okay sooner rather than later oh you
mean handle hand holder say this yeah
yeah uh did you have to say it on stream
I'm sorry
he might be able to stabilize things if
I can find him
um
there's some tea things in there okay we
will look there they're not there
anymore oh they're not I will be among
them no we saved them and they left a
Boulder's game remember world of good oh
but yeah they did leave but she needs a
Tiffany help uh yeah but he's on the way
to Baldur's Gate oh oh sorry Carlock I
guess
oops oops man
um
she's trying she's trying to raise up a
Syrian again
players of course I'm trying so hard
focusing on what's important for us even
though he loves Mario Fame
he does
bites made me who I am
thanks
wow
do you think that's a threat
let me give you the book why can't I I
ca how do I give him the does he have to
he I bet I can't I better yes no it's
too late you already read the book uh
what
wait I read the book it can't be used
again so you can't read the book no I
can't read the book I don't think
anymore
okay oh my God
oh my god did you learn a spell no I
didn't get anything I don't know what it
was supposed to do ah I passed all of
the checks so apparently I got the
knowledge
I don't need it on me right I'm gonna
read the book
so it's stuck to you now well my book
look at Carlock dancing I love it oh yes
she drops it
yeah cool hold on yeah yeah hold on Bust
a Move
some head spinnies
oh
I remember if you okay I remember he
killed him yeah
oh I'm shaking you for good after the
Mind Flair ship you just can't get
enough of me can you
Carlock
Advocates diaboli the stink of avernus
hey don't insult her chill will win
anything
why am I making the poisons
I am oh oh no okay it's congestion sorry
I just suggestions
oh
is he is he back here to kill me yeah
will he join us
[Music]
probably forgiveness
just ahead a diabolical figure red skin
single curled horn blazes with flame
bloodied great ax held high he chases
the fiend ignited you know Will's pretty
cool she is an infant yeah I really like
that his eye to the living
and I didn't even have him on my team
barely and I was like what you think I
am how can you struggle with making
these NPCs like you like I feel like
everybody's lusting another Vision over
Young's blade race
is hard because her eyes Dart around
seeking Escape
desperate
[Music]
no you're not being tricked
told the truth I may be an effective
Soldier but I never wanted to serve
zariel legged it away from it the first
chance I got and yet you served
ah
Stand Down
stop it no Devils cannot be trusted oh
come on will
um
so stubborn will would you listen to
sense
this doesn't have to end badly
for either of us we could be friends you
know monsters right yes
you see I'm not what you think
my man's were you not paying attention
come on man
we forgive you even though you didn't
forgive Bijou for looting your dead
friends but okay we forgive you died
thankfully maybe there's been enough
threats today
truth
he makes a little baby begging face
pranked
you're pranked Adventure I've not grown
any tentacles yet dang baldrin but luck
won't be on our side forever
yes you have my blade Your Leader
willing of course okay
um the more of the merrier as they say
no dies
I was the rampaging Beast I see the good
in you karlak I promise not to lose
sight of it even when the hell's burn
hottest wow
okay
are you seeing Shadow heart because I'm
seeing nothing playing
just gave me
my friend she's the ghost yeah well
oh no me and Charlie are seeing the same
thing AKA nothing
I don't think that's crazy she has a
little thing above her
heads listen even more glad he decided
to stick around it takes a pretty slick
mover to track down old
yeah he came out of nowhere oh yeah I'm
just glad he's not mad at me anymore
right now goodness if he turns on you
again he's dead
you've got a little butt chin here
someone wrong but what
what your character has a button
I respect someone who can admit
but he's behind
plus big behind I bet there's a good
story there
you'll see
and then we'll see you next time maybe
yeah you'll see that you have a butt
chin oh I think will wants to talk yeah
well wants to talk let's go listen to
his conversation
well what's up
been witness to a pantomime I'm sorry to
say
and I've played my part all day poorly
she is I can say only this
I forgot what outfit you were wearing
one night soon when we make Camp well
it's a hot looking ladies
everybody looks real good you too
thanks I know maybe the most good
looking is yeah and you'll love somebody
but I can't promise you'll like them
well tell us about yourself
you want to talk more of him
oh house what's going on house and whole
house
yeah I forgot he was here now let me
have a little conversation with him
yes Oak father's blessings you have
anything he wants to say oh God there's
literally so much stuff
just a couple what is this
um
those who remained are Shadow cursed
if you don't die at their hands then you
become one beautiful Memorial we have
together your face is so beautiful it's
hard for me
it's hard for anyone to
resistance
I don't know what else to say heart once
with heart once ladies offended myself
that's how it is afterwards
examine the tadpole that emerged hideous
but fascinating like nothing else in
nature I'm glad to say hideous but
fascinating like me uh yeah
praise
who are we talking about
you do not know and neither do any of
the others The Grove needs to move
beyond the mistakes of the past what it
needs is an unknown quantity an outsider
who can enforce the young father your
reps in ladies this is why you chose
Francesca you guys watch channel
he's one of the only companions that you
can date one person and also at the same
time yeah
I I believe it
um what about the secret passage in the
underdark tell us how to go there
because we definitely need to go there
there's stuff we want there one of his
cohorts where did I go there I think I
went there
didn't like it's not for the content
that's what it's for guys right it's the
content
those illicit creatures threaten the
natural order
it's my duty to do what I can to stop
Somebody's gotta entertainment
it's an affront and must be cleansed
under dark is fine I feel like that's
just a better way to go years ago but I
failed to prevent him from unleashing
Darkness across the region before he was
defeated
join you and get close to moonrise
perhaps I can lift this curse just
find a cure for your infection
okay Allison I'm kind of done talking to
you if you just really talk a lot more
your face doesn't like the clock bro
what's good
Molly smash Molly no talk
[Music]
another player is choosing camp supplies
leave it to you
I made dinner
nice hope it tastes good I made tonkatsu
last night
yeah by myself
this was a good Austrian schnitzel but I
realized I'll I can just make it into
tonkatsu because it's like pretty
similar
I love making tonkatsu with curry too oh
yeah I like thinking yeah
wait before
we go
oh and uh Gail is dying I guess
I'll check on him crazy guy
slight open
you're gonna steal the poor dog
[Music]
we played about himself maybe yeah
yeah
or he'll bite your hand off which would
be sick where's the ball
he's like what
that's not something you see every day
oh that doesn't seem right we'll try
again really quickly come on this time
it works there you go
he needs attention
and then we can leave oh will and Carla
can prove
all right
baby yeah you'll have the ball in your
inventory if you throw it somewhere
he'll bring it back try it so cute
let's see you can pet the dog why are
there two Gales I don't know I think
he's glitched so the way closer to him
oh no
he's coming foreign
somebody talked to him already
yeah I give him a magic item oh that's
so sweet you I know I gave him what I
was wearing so now I need to find a
different one but I you know in this
camp for whatever reason I can never
find the Traveler's chest
oh it's over here oh yeah okay it's just
by Shadow heart
he's not glitch to talk to him oh so he
just has another dude version of him
don't question it it's normal
yes because you win in it I can't no it
belongs to only one of them belongs to
you there's four
yeah there's four
yeah there you go really we don't know
sure no we don't share they're pretty
how do I know which one's mine
what everyone lets you open it I guess
Travelers chess traveler's chest
in there oh this is mine it must be mine
because it's got a severed head
nice I'm gonna put that in someone
else's chest now good luck
I don't know you can't yeah why it's not
the orange one
well I'll put it in your inventory then
hooded armor I'll just sell that
wait I'll store my gold
what's next
let's keep it flaring up north because
there's stuff happening up North and
then the tea house is down way way yeah
I'm interested in up north because I
haven't been there before okay okay I've
been there
have you been to the crest the crash I
don't think so
then you haven't been up north
on the camp
Square
oh
pink chest
did everyone leave yes I just left I
mean yes we just stop stop running
wait and wait for the team did you wait
just come into me
really far away from everyone okay yeah
I'm just waiting by narissa all right
we're here please hold my hand I was
alone I was so scared what was that wait
that's right
lead the way
the burning Village
oh why is everything on fire I don't
know I wonder what could be up here to
cause everything to be on fire like hey
what's happening is it like a raid Maybe
the village is being raided Maybe by God
I did not see this yet I'm in a
conversation oh okay
if the unsleeping eyes
what the beep have to cut a massacre
what is this drow and Goblin slaughtered
the lot oh please just leave it that's
no good
oh all right oh okay all right guess
what once we're doing what they want us
to do
might as well Loop
no wait if we look they'll get mad I
think if it wouldn't it be red then
it's fine
nobody's hell strange place to find it
for goblins it's probably fine but what
are they doing you guys need to open
this yeah what I'm sorry I'm in a
conversation oh at the gate
could be inside don't just no strength
push I don't ask questions I push
a little bonus yeah
yeah big muscle
Mass
there you go
too much time
[Music]
my work here is done
oh everything's on fire
that's pretty wild
nice bathtub
look at this place
it feels wrong to loot things
the goblin I mean they're not using it
anymore it's on fire might as well get
it let's go with the goblins
potato porridge Don't Mind If I Do
some trouble what's what's oh is he
doing
well we could also go in where I opened
up the door if you guys yeah yeah up
here is a dead end there must be a
reason why you opened the door
yeah we gotta go in
oh yeah girl is on fire oh I'm burning
oh this is not so uncomfortable
yeah I mean it is a burning building
I'm Gonna Save the ham I'm Gonna Save
the food good get the food oh
yeah save the kitchen stuff I saved the
sauce oh [\h__\h] one thing that I wish you
could do in this game is Cook
yeah like I know you technically are
when you're camping but like it's not
the same it's not the same as being able
to make a recipe you know
Apple
pineapple we need to cook
did you girls go to a second anyone hear
me please
look at all this food so that way we
have food for our camp
s like there might be somebody behind
this door oh boy oh
I'm in a I'm in the scene
yeah I mean I just opened a door and it
exploded oh so I mean but we can why are
we we're on the fight right we're in
based mode
I don't think so
I think we can exit that yeah okay
who are you talking to there's some oh
yeah
there it is I'm saving a guy
oh
thank you
no I'm trapped how the hell do we get
out of here I've just run out of the
building
um there's like a person underneath I
can't see a dumb thing I'm gonna oh he
just kind of roasted
right oh I'll try to keep a hug
does he follow you now oh he has one HP
uh oh
I'm like not in the same area as this
guy
wait did he die
it was there a quest that we could have
gotten with that guy yeah oh well wait
wait for me I'm getting I'm looting all
the food in here because I'm good
it's pretty rough buddy I gotta save the
food yeah that is super rough actually
that didn't go as planned
maybe not okay
a lot of burning things in here yeah
okay I saved the pool I'm coming okay
no what the [\h__\h] are you doing up there
eh is that will who's that guy yeah he
looks like will right
yeah what is he doing I'll just recruit
Pavel
table pebble
yeah that's not well just to look like
in here
the council Floric needs help too how do
I get there oh there's like so many
people up there
okay well go help him you know what I
realized is that I bet we could have
saved that dude if we had did you use
the water oh yeah oh yeah
[Music]
I was too busy looting the food yeah
that's all right you got your priorities
I didn't I didn't even mean to talk to
that guy
okay
I see a bunch of people here
they need some help do you need help
oh people hi hi maybe spread some water
wherever necessary I gotta open the door
I guess yeah maybe there are still
people to help stop wasting time oh wait
hold on maybe I can now
yeah
thanks nice
okay proper fangs must wait she says
oh
gotta leave let's go let's go Gotta Cut
and Run
run
oh there's water barrels
here we
go maybe a short rest
yeah maybe
oh Cali was damn hit you hard huh
yeah a little bit
oh it takes more than mere fire to break
me Eva Eva
everyone's beauty schools drow have
taken Grand Duke older Raven guard
Westward if my eyes and ears can be
believed oh Gauntlet report to the man
and send for reinforcements we must find
the Duke the Duke on your command
counselor the request oh she's so sweaty
count the dead I mean yeah we were just
in a burning building yeah I'd be
surprised if you weren't and you I must
ask again for your Aid
please rescue Raven Guard from his drow
captors the council will reward you for
your effort
uh why entrust this to me who is the
Duke Raven guard
um
I'll I'll travel West and rescue Duke
Raven guards
generosity comment understood approach
the towers with care yeah the land
itself has been swallowed in Shadow
reinforcements and join you when I can
to work
all right yeah oh my God inspiration
what's the reward oh
rewind no I can't read
reward rescue the Duke we learned that
the Grand Duke was captured by drone
taken Westward
you can only choose one
route whatever it's the same thing um
nothing really there's like a tried I
don't really know it would be good
there's a bow I heard there's a bow yes
yeah well I guess we can do that
I accepted it
yep can I has Bo
o I don't know I see it the jolt shooter
is that did they just give it to us
already even though we haven't completed
the quest it should be any inventory yes
it is not I took it already
okay I think I think this is the one
yeah the jolt shooter what does it do
electric blood when the wielder deals
damage using this weapon they gain two
lightning charges
Leo
thank you
no more Goblin bow yeah
shall we immediately uh look West
I guess so we can say that yeah I mean
keep going west yeah okay party members
in a conversation no they are not ah
what about short dress guys I'm trying
to short rest it says a party member is
in a conversation and cannot rest right
now oh we learned
so odd
none please let us rest
oh yeah it says it for me too wait can
everyone try the short rest oh oh
maybe now
I'm well too big to take there's a
person over here so maybe if we talk to
them it'll get us out of our predicament
yeah
and you see that shadow in the
background yeah Shadow yeah it's a looks
like a dragon
where what's the matter above whoa her
hair is popping off killed her yes that
lot is swarming all over the bridge
I don't know what they want but it can't
be good oh wow what could they do this
you want to do the same I doubt a
fighter would go your way we could just
write down who I no at least this is a
different group just another harassing
fool trying to stay alive
there's plenty of us around she's cute
she's cute yeah
you want to join me instead what
just follow you around yeah go my own
way
I understand that okay bye have a nice
day did it reset what should we go try
to get down there and see what happens
era of darkness Arrow there it looks
like there's a path down here yeah
it's to the ants before I do that well
they all kind of look
no look up that was your last chance is
stick now burn uh-oh
um it's dark in time I think you should
run okay never mind
um wow
what the hell is going on
there's a dragon Daenerys Targaryen
please calm down
no excuses question kill then move on
find the weapon the weapons the weapon
fail her at your peril
wow what a very good Yankee in response
suicide at least
oh my God
uh we should save before we talk to them
by the way
um I said we see them again
they're around here somewhere if we keep
moving
just don't remember don't worry
yes
hey I think I'm experiencing a problem
Oh wait
um
these creatures are so simple to enslare
too much about your task
forgiveness kthrak
as for you
tell me dragon's kind of big
run you through yeah
um persuade
uh I'm gonna add guidance
if I add friends oh wait so I add
guidance to friends is two dice better
I don't know oh two dice is nice
I love just looking at Mario pay's ABS
right okay I did it I did it it's mine
thank God I raised him up
much as I want to see the dice roll of
course you are not a threat you are
nothing until wow otherwise all right
can we kill them keep sucking air
necessary for you to tell me something
of worth a vessel fell from the sky we
seek a precious weapon that was taken
from suddenly feel the strange anxiety
take hold not your own but that of the
artifact you carry
the artifact does not want depart from
you it does not want to fall into the
guthrader's hands help us find it and I
will leave your blood beneath your skin
unspilled don't let him know we have a
biboo
um
foreign
[Music]
obedience is your only hope now stand
still oh he's gonna Frisk you he begins
to move his hand wait is he is
wait wait wait
um
steal my mind
give me guidance
thank you
please yeah it's mine
my mind is sealed you cannot get past my
mind
[\h__\h] Frisk no Jutsu
fito
um
my head emptied look how empty is it you
know what save the day there you go uh
can I detect his thoughts try it
oh I have minus one intelligence maybe
not oh good luck ah
no thoughts
one more time
I prefer we not die yeah
entering his mind otherwise
let's go a worthless sport if this one
was even slightly useful I might spare
her oh
um
first one why not don't be too tasty I I
just read your mind unlikely but it
costs me nothing to spare your sorry
life
[Music]
if you succeed the reward will be great
now go
see here we go I'm great enough people I
just gotta be stupid and they will hurt
me yeah I wanted to fight a dragon
dargan times oh you didn't it has so
much health
oh really
like over here okay
be aware that inspiration caps at four
so we have four again might as well use
it if you fail things okay I don't know
why I was going up there
oh I just follow you guys
follow
oh I hear kitty cat yeah she thinks I'm
done streaming because I haven't been
talking that's her signal oh no
I'm still screaming this movie
well this movie over here there's a gate
there's a gate is it Baldur's Gate I
must be
it's the first time I've seen it's only
getting things
oh no this is for the act two now
but we can come here later
also but this I wanted us to get the
quest so we can come back here okay oh
okay got it yeah there's a good weapon
in there we we less lest we lose it
okay
interesting
well where's you next ladies you might
as well go south
Tea House
Tea House okay we're going the underdark
thing right yeah there's a really good
weapon staff for me there I heard
yeah
I want to keep a lookout for it okay we
gotta keep a lookout
oh my God
well
Which Way Tea House
Village everyone teleport again okay
I'm fast I'm quick
um okay and then we go this way by the
river
by the river
[Music]
um
if you right click on things you can
move it to Camp yeah send to camp and
it'll be in your storage box thing
if one more person in chat tells me to
put clothes on I'm gonna take these
clothes off no more Nathan I'm not in
cucumber anymore
thank you okay
um
so tea house is down here Molly you take
the lead over here
once we get here we'll do yeah Dad I
baited you I'm not gonna take the
clothes off over there but I did reveal
how many thirsty strange people are in
my chat what's going on talk to them
hello
this is home
be nice to The Hags they're ages
please
I just want to go home
stop this no isn't she nice she won't
ask again yeah she seems nice how about
you all just calm down this has nothing
to do with me but bye lower your weapons
she's just an old woman sweetie full
she's with the hag don't Bloody Sunday
gaping together seems like we're going
with the same outcomes
oh I mean I've seen this summer before
we have to protect her yeah we'll Smash
and destroy you want to improve that the
natural understanding is that she's a
nice lady
that's all that she is nice imagine
being so rude to hurt an old woman wow
[Music]
she's got like blood all over her granny
gown
what happened it sounded like a heated
argument oh nice things are paid in Gold
oh yeah the non-lethals Poor Boys I
forgot about it again a girl who's
staying with me this is all my fault
staying with her she made a promise May
Rita begged me not to breathe the word
if they came looking for him and my word
wow she seems like such a nice lady
she's evil isn't she
why would she be even look at her she
stole that little girl and the dudes are
going to go protect the kid thank you
proper
all right well can we loot him at least
see what they got anything
angel don't get mad I mean it I'm only
leaving this note so you don't panic and
do something stupid I'm going to the hag
come on man you're so rude I owe it took
Connor to make things right you know
he'd do the same for me I'll be back
soon so not a word to ma'am all right
she has enough on her plate um
and then death
whoopsie doodly do a nurse is looking at
something I didn't mean to
I don't think I can roll a 20.
you roll the 20.
what the [\h__\h] I have a bite to eat oh
whoa what the [\h__\h]
what's going on
is this like some Hansel and Gretel [\h__\h]
delicious
no it looks so pretty I don't want to
walk around here anymore
who poisoned apples give me
yucky putrid bog we're in the Bog bog
beats what's going on
more poisoned apples
who is that who's this who's this old
dude
but I don't want to know
Burlington with a piece of gold hi
oh they look sick they look gangster
what's going on a creature known for its
for its bloodlust oh the red cabinet
that noise is that supposed to scare me
buddy boy pretending to be a sheep
take a deep breath and say ba
we had a little
seems like there's so much to look
around here yeah it's pretty big area
can we loot
I've been in the wooden crates
what are these stairs up here yeah
stairs are you going the right way Cali
you have Natural Instincts oh there's a
oh yeah I just have game instincts a
frog
hold on a sec let's go down here first
we're going up there there's a dude
there's a duder okay wait I'm talking to
I'm talking to a frog I think the frog
doesn't really matter until later no
what's wrong
what are you croaking on about a fellow
Wanderer he's stinky Aroma you can't
even waft of something he hasn't taken a
shower there's something wrong with the
Frog powdered iron Vine
all right okay
oh who's this
don't
Monster Hunter whatever you're hunting
your stench alone we'll kill it a quick
Witch is rare indeed it was actually
pretty slow it took me about a minute to
answer
whatever you say did you find yours
before dealing with the lady of this
house
why you came to her there I take it to
bargain it's a bargain Lady of the house
a more innocent name than someone we're
here for tea
wait what did I miss since the first the
first Darkness
their knowledge is Max not much only by
their spite it's just stinky know how to
ask I'm not a stinky man
if you're full enough to pay their price
I look so at home here this just looks
like where I belong right into the
background it does it's your swamp yeah
uh what price is that that was easiest
to lose and the hardest to do without
quit speaking of riddles bro
if she can tell me how to draw him out
I'll pay whatever she asks I guess that
she's a witch who is it you're hunting
truth is like a blade my friend we can
arm ourselves with it okay don't tell me
I guess pressed against our throat
I would not put you in danger oh good
yeah that's not what this is about is it
Barbarian I like danger the truth now
yes
gonna try I believe in Mario babe come
on 20.
this is what I excel at I'm made to
intimidate
baby
[Music]
with my words
yeah yeah a little bit
dummy tell me what's going on oh serious
don't help him back to Boulder's Gate
alive
absolutely not brother don't help him
we shared a special moment together we
have never met anyone named a Starion
ever
he's no vampire we've met you can give
up your hunts as Darien's under my
protection
my people were recently attacked in the
night our camp set upon by a band of
vampire spawn
in the chaos of battle one of them stole
away with our children
oh we've been searching for them
it would children we believe this
Astorian knows exactly what happened
that night and where to find our little
ones
okay
captured my people will make him talk
so I ask again
is he known to you yeah we've never met
Asteria we've never met
there is no we've never met it's I'm
protecting him or I know him just leave
just leave just leave
no
oh okay don't leave too actually
don't give up he's not the pipe to come
quickly you do know him quietly never
I'd never tell you where he is
help him
some people are saying they killed him
in pretty good
ah I'm going to help you find him back
off in my can we kill him yeah
you'll never heard a Starion I mean not
that I like him or anything but you know
we did share a moment oh yeah sure
[Music]
so what happens with my Lightning Charge
plus one Attack rules and deal additions
oh
what you gonna do what's he gonna do for
him
you got nothing on me oh okay now you do
never mind good job good job what if you
go up to him in hysterions in your party
I did that um and I was like I was I
literally was like hey he's right here
on the stairway and was like what the
[\h__\h] and uh and then we had a fight and
I was like sorry it was a joke a Starion
sorry about that
but it was funny
it was very funny
pretty good gandrill's aspiration
there's a brand new bow for you if you
want here I'll pick up the stuff that
one wasn't was that one good for me no
you didn't kill him you just knocked out
how do we kill him go good we can leave
him here like that I mean if you keep
hitting him he'll die eventually but you
want you want the bow qo do I wanna I
mean you already have a pretty nice one
right
but you want another one I'll take the
bow yeah
hold on what is I'll give it to your
give give to that's a crossbow area
there we go I love a crossbow
um yeah what a thing
yeah beat his ass
you dead now now he did now and now he's
dead
again girls party
will not go trap this arm kits that's
exactly what we need well let's see
um now that we got that guy maybe let's
go to the house yes
[Music]
I'm looking at the well right now okay
but I don't think we should jump in
right now we need to go into the house
first maybe we should just go in there
don't drink from the well what the [\h__\h]
no
stinky water never do that I guess we
could just go in the front yeah like we
come for tea
has bad feelings spider sense I don't
know why you would have a bad feeling I
don't she looks like Fiona
not the um
[Music]
it's a green dress The Wooden Spoon
you're eating for two oh she's pregnant
you're talking ages come in come in you
look really dirty though
and have a cup of cups
give me patience eat up Marina
I won't say it again this is messed up
poor girl
some bad news
feed all your guests so poorly I have
some bad news for her under your nose
shut oh things will get messy
be nice I'm scared what's going on
showing her outside
nothing I mistook you for someone else
you messed up
and the Ethel killed your brothers
pretty insane but yeah she did it she
did that [\h__\h] Rose sick
not very convincing and I used can I try
one more time yeah
we have four go for it
oh [\h__\h] up man
are we gonna have a big fight now
one more time one more time please I had
so much inspiration
however if we don't get it this time
the critical failure
critical I mean I suppose that's what we
deserve
don't cheer Brothers
anyway
she's just a drama queen
[Music]
anyways at last some time in the cage
should do her good we're not mad about
what I just said
regret sticking your nose in my business
oh it's just a jerk
[Applause]
[Music]
looking good
beautiful all right I don't want a
fighter
what I mean why not she should be easy
yeah no the good thing is she gets
invisible and I'll see I think it's
better if we don't manage to kill her
right away anyway
okay I don't even see her anymore I
don't know where to shoot
oh
no that was just a major Mage hand I I
was here on my solo run right I killed
her here and it broke the entire Quest
yeah that's what I'm saying don't do it
oh
that are attacking us yeah okay and then
we follow Where She Went basically
well she's still here just invisible no
yeah for now she's she's running away
though
oh okay
where are the red caps
so far bring them in what if we all just
came inside and closed the door do you
think they can open the doors
possibly I think they can maybe they're
too stupid to open doors
[Music]
Epic
yummy yummy
yummy yummy yummy
sounds like they're saying
[Music]
there is his hands kind of close to my
butt
um
[Music]
yeah
I don't know why I went the other way
maybe I can maybe I can distract you oh
there she goes okay she went through the
the fireplace run away
yummy yummy
she's gone okay now let's focus on the
red cat because okay
welcome back to help
me
soccer
you guys ain't [\h__\h]
grumble
[Music]
yeah nice one
you just stood there like a statue
oh no oh
yeah and I get up again
yeah we're gonna break you down nice
you got this get up Wawa get up come on
nice that was a stick Burn yeah for real
[Music]
there is a could you have used that
magic hand to give me a hand
yeah too true
and back up again
mommy mommy
oh what was that well thank you me be
giving you safety whoa
feels so safe
yeah with my shield oh there's soon
yeah there's more
yeah I think they're on their way oh
they're yeah they're about to enter
they're about to acquaint themselves
oh yeah play us a tune whoa little
little battle music
yeah a little a little music to jam to
you know it's a jig oh I can't
why can't I
hmm oh
why can't I hmm what are you trying to
do
oh nice nice okay one left I'm Gonna
Save My arranged weapons
that's okay
on spares I think
if you have some
oil well
or Bagel nice try okay
when in doubt
get him I wonder what happened to my bow
and arrow I need to get my bow and arrow
back
yeah oh
yeah all right I think I can throw some
I can't throw anything but why I think I
need to be enraged
um
let's see
bro get mad
I probably could have been a bit further
away
you got one Health left
yeah
whatever
cool
wow
I love that
oh they're small
gonna yes
oh well
so they're done for and she ran away
okay we fall off I'm gonna steal this
stuff I guess yeah
[Applause]
for me and Callie yeah
I'm exhausted I found the chat yeah I'm
gonna open it
open it's okay
see
potion of Greater healing I steal
because I don't give up yeah
yeah
steal everything
yeah she sucks there's also so much
bread yeah take the bread yeah buttered
buns yeah
we do like buttered buns in this house
today
cucumbers and what do you call the Smith
Lau
[Music]
is so weird to me yeah that I wouldn't
do either
there you are
because butter is like a salty thing I
associate like bread with like jam and
stuff so oh but you can still work with
the butter and there's unsalted butter I
do like garlic bread though oh yes
oh hi
oh thanks
I look like I could be related to you
actually
okay you're prettier
oh thanks tell me where the girl is what
I think I'll stay a while I don't think
we care about the girl your brain
already
leave
oh you'll end up in tonight's she's
gonna eat us
we'd like to see you try marinating
Marina I don't care we're gonna go in
and do it oh there's a lot of funky
things here
is that a headless person oh
it's pretty wacky wait what did I
perceive I perceived something I'm gonna
talk to this guy over here
family portraits for some reason it made
me talk to the tree so I'm gonna cut
soon I'm sorry yeah yeah you feel
crushing away yes
that's too bad she's got quite a few
prisoners okay I'm gonna leave so Cali
could do this but I want to talk to
Lauren
oh
this guy gnarly yeah
no what's wrong with him what's his
problem
spell
an illusion
me
dead dead
shining it does look like Legolas
yeah he's a Legolas gone Gollum
then
your own way oh please please
give a hug
no
why are you so
means
ah he's not wrong
Roar
attack
he's gonna die
such a sadist
you'll be fine dude Smile as he twitches
and whimper
be nice to him
oh my eyes are so wide and kind
dancing
whatever you're seeing it isn't real
would never lie to you
why are you talking like this
just like the others this is nonsense
I mean his stuff together always say and
it's not yeah it's separated
[Music]
not everyone looks like you do elf it's
shocking I know
[Laughter]
the monster monster
this guy must have been inspired by you
not a mind flare
no
mine I'm not a mind he's so mean
you think is there any way you can get
him to not be a piece of [\h__\h] later but
we have to continue uh so why don't you
look at this door morio Fame all right
gnarled door
open sesame
a nice ass
looks pretty good we could just stay
here and look at this for a while but
let me see
shrouded in the glow of the Divine
weapons
I'll take it
petal look
dude nice leg the head will be the least
your problems if you don't open up
top
Barbarian to Roar
do it do it yeah
little ogre Roar hmm
don't look
I wish that other guy would shut up
imagining its wooden frame cracking and
splintering in a raging Inferno
you see the hack
she walks through the door
oh somebody made the door open
oh
look
open
through
oh
I feel crushing waves disease
[Music]
let's see the gallery
you don't you just just walk through you
don't need to you don't need to talk to
it that's what I thought okay now now I
can't no I can't there you go nice
onward let's do it
let's go run it ladies
oh boy
time to battle some randos yeah
non-lethal attacks wow people fight
they have to die
yeah
who can I read unless they're possessed
but
can I read I probably gotta go anyway
oh I can reach nice incredible nice
there was something in the way
it's going up I want to go up apparently
I don't know if this is true but they
are saying pickpocket the masks and save
them yeah I picked up some masks
no pickpocket the mast like take the
masks from them via pickpocketing
um
rescue them yeah I think I don't know oh
it sounds not possible I guess we can
turn on non-lethal it's it's an insta
kill when you steal the mask but we want
to kill them anymore no never mind then
yeah let's kill him oh okay fair and
square
sounds good to me
do it oh she really doesn't want to
uh I feel kind of bad murdering all
these people yeah thank you
seems kind of complicated to not kill
them so yeah okay
we'll go ahead and kill him yeah
no one will know it's all happening down
here in the cave no no no yeah no one
needs to know yeah our little secret our
little murder Secret
murder Secret
Kelly uh
are you scared no reason only a little
bit like you're shaking I'm a Mobile
Assistant frightened oh wait you're not
wearing any boots
oh so yeah Reckless attack
the ndu and then
another frenzied strike on you
nice
that looks pretty sick
ah there we go whoops nice they're
knocked out I should just kill him
hey or just let's just take the masks uh
you know oh give it a go yeah good idea
so the masks are controlling them I
guess yeah behind me yeah
yeah
everybody's in such good shape in this
game yeah
[Music]
I love it
everyone's now he's going down so
annoying I are shooting From Below he's
not very smart is he
yeah oh yeah
cool yeah with the mask afterwards oh
nice I'm sure I think I can wear the
masks don't
it's that seems not great
eh eh I mean would they be in mind
controlled yeah you've got a good point
hi maybe
yeah maybe I mean
do they carry anything besides the masks
yes a little bit but garbage
I take slime bomb
let's see there must be another wild
right here oh
um you find something
there's a waterfall we can jump through
it oh yeah totally did not I thought
that we could not go through there yeah
we have to jump I see
oh my gosh
there's nothing this place
yeah
um I would not short rest until we get
all the way down okay
um hold on my game is glitched oh no are
you okay
oh
joining failed cannot join the party
it's really weird
are you very out of the game
no it's just every time I say accept it
like glitches out
I have to restart my game
good thing I just saved yeah yeah yeah
but you gotta restart the game no
problem niche that's gonna be a big
surprise
bye bye bye that was super weird
very super weird
well that was odd some glitches here and
there would be taken
I mean for the most part it's really not
that bad but yeah usually you still run
into them as you do with anything play
game
good job all right I'm pulling it back
up and then I'll invite you guys back
okay
[Music]
da
please sing it for me Kelly
down down down by the river why do I
still have a morning voice
I am hydrating properly are you drinking
water I'm Dreaming like every day to the
throat yeah Valen it's crazy
yeah does it hurt when you talk
it doesn't hurt but it does feel like a
bit of a struggle to speak sometimes
yeah well while we're doing this I'm
gonna quick run and take an idol meeting
so I'll be right back okay okay grab
your snacks ladies
grab your snacks will be right and then
I'll invite the ladies
mommy is not done streaming
cute yeah
[Music]
invite the game
Baby by the game
Marissa
I invited everyone thank you
[Music]
meow meow is this movie yes
back in the game
yeah
working now
shut up where are we okay here
what's in here
oh the wrist only has 21 HP
oh that's not great maybe a short rest
wait no wait don't don't short rest
until we get down there yeah okay but I
can throw it maybe she can drink a
potion of healing oh
she's so much money oh we have no short
rest left yeah oh
maybe big rest
we might want a big rest before we do
this okay
I'm fine with that
let me see actually
I've returned welcome back
thank you oh
we have to leave the the tea house
though because it's not safe
yeah really yeah oh yeah cause the map
is red yeah okay
we can always come back though right
yeah
I'm here nothing bad will happen surely
potion of animal speaking yay I wish
that was real
I think I know right
right
let's get out of here
we can see for your fancy Magic
lady
please
oh he's still talking
yeah I mean yeah
Legends say he is still talking to this
day to this day
oh we can rest up here
alrighty ladies to the camp we go yay
[Music]
yay
oh will wants to talk I wanted to chat
someone want to talk to him
I'll I'll talk
see look you have a budget
God's been taking
it Charming
older Raven guards been taken who's
Soldier forever I don't know
oh that's the guy who who the who were
supposed to rescue who were the five
yeah from the fiery building oh okay the
one that died
no no they they said he was kidnapped
and that we needed to get him back
remember okay and then you got the bow
Floric says he lives then he lives and
we need to free him from his captors
you see oh Grand is my father oh I know
I haven't said
probation was no matter of pride
not least for him oh
what do is uh
and the choice is clear we should rescue
Duke ravenguard that means a lot what
about I wonder Raven Croft makes a Duke
of Bowl escapes interesting to the
drought around
[Music]
no this is no drow plot these absolute
Nutters these true songs
he could lead Baldur's Gate to ruin
all the more reason to find him
absolutely my father but the future of
this well it's kind of cute
yeah hmm
you shouldn't keep secrets like this for
me will I know
um and you're right yeah
when I went into a mirror
yeah right some expressions are really
seems like yeah
the memory of a memory
a man who
belong I wanted you to know the blade
not the shadow he left behind
deep [\h__\h] okay
we'll do it for you
[Music]
okay what else nobody else wants to talk
I think I'm talking about yeah yeah he's
asking he's asking I told him someone
was looking for him what happened
uh
but yeah why because kazador sent him
why else tell me about this Hunter he
always sounds so offended whenever he
talks I know something ferocious surely
camp
um
okay what are those vagabonds why would
they I suppose I shouldn't be surprised
what do you know about the children yeah
but you know about the kids man but why
send anyone after me
oh yeah
um
maybe he wants to make an example of me
to show what happens to runaways well
maybe he thinks death is too good for me
I mean true
um we just have to be vigilant keep our
wits about us and kill any Monster
Hunters on site
before
I'm gonna kill you you're my enemy
narissa and shambles no all right got
your friend zoned more Story Time Lord
oh [\h__\h]
oh no she's coming
she's coming
I remember this part yeah
oh
hot whoa if even white hot
well
you've been naughty
and you know what happens when you're
naughty God's damn it
need one but her
aren't you a luscious thing
get out of my camp now
but I'm just getting comfy
I'm Will's Patron the fount of his power
will has a patreon My Pet's been nice oh
whoa she's in control
but carlock's still breathing I've taken
more pleasant shits than new Missouri
day
by the way Carlock
Zario sends her regards what up mizora
don't even mention zarya
Devils only
she's a tingling not a monster oh
precious that vocal delivery is really
good but his face does not
matching it shall be limited to The
Infernal the Demonic the heartless and
the soulless
meets the criteria by virtue of having
no heart oh
will
last
last at all
you better not lay your damn finger on
Carla don't you worry yeah oh they all
approved the sticks no it is a fine pup
must still pay his price
to wit no
oil burns in the fires
gaining their essence
light the wheel
is there any way to attack her in the
camp
come on game
oh he just got horns that's not bad
horny man he's still looking great he
got horny bonked yeah
that's best
I like that what the hell
they are I promise we're good a price
paid
you know the terms get used to the new
form Pat
there's no going back some magic even I
can't undo then why would you do it
and we had to kill her tears Fair
without their precious being made
I have a swimsuit with a cut like her
dress
I wore it today for me good pics I think
I know which one you're talking about
where it is oh I have to have a cut like
that actually oh that didn't do this to
me yeah
oh now is there a stairs oh oh so many
people want to talk what do we listen to
First a Starion no no here's mine
oh yeah
I'll come to my bed again
one's office
no
[Music]
that's what I deserved
some of you let me keep this comments
joining failed cannot join the party is
full no companions
[Music]
I mean it would be the game
trying to protect my viewers I'm gonna
commit to puku
continue
all right well hold on a second uh we
might need to
screen thing black oh no am I gonna get
jump scared with something lewd
hmm
this glitch is really bad is it like
before like last time yeah it's the same
thing if we have to I swear to God if we
have to redo everything yeah we can just
get past the tags too yeah yeah
this is really annoying
I don't know why this is what what's
your screen look like
it's uh oh my god oh hold on a second uh
it says it just
it's like how do I describe can't join
party full
party and then I say it no problem and
then it flashes again
now we wait to be invited again yeah so
we shall safe more often now if this
happens again yeah well we I mean look
all we did was reload go to Camp do that
scene and then you know so we we really
have a lot of problems
to mouse and keyboard keyboard that's
fine but I'm gonna have to relearn the
game
I mean that's what people are saying but
I don't know
yeah it's just point and click yeah
ain't no party like a memorial party
because the Maury party is full and no
companions can be
but your mouth
hmm felt very odd well maybe if I stop
using a controller it'll work all right
let me get you guys back in the game
shall we yeah
we'll redo the will scene well we'll
have to retalk the mill first and then
we'll have to do that again
I refuse
seriously
borny girls
it's for the content here
are you talking about it's for the
content you're just so crazy I didn't
expect that from you there's a you're
the one that had nudity turned off on
the game whereas I kept it on let's not
go there
what do you mean
let's not go there
there's one leader of the horny Patrol
here and let me tell you it's not me
bless you thank you it's not me
oh I just
see how do I go how do we go to the camp
oh we gotta get out of here yeah read
alicid Powers okay well let me switch
back over to game shall we
bless you thank you
foreign
yeah we're going okay chill dude
all right let's see map
map ping is it map you cannot fast
travel from this area oh we gotta leave
it I guess yeah yeah we have to walk out
again
okay
are you guys talked to will I'm just
gonna tell hysterian again about the guy
same text Skip through
okay
I have no clue where old or even God's
been taken please hold on camera I know
this is so weird to control our relation
was no matter thank you zoom around how
do you Pan the camera oh there we go you
can rotate it like that no reason to
find him okay
um
[Music]
you don't you don't have to it's it's
okay oh there it is got it there's the
door
[Music]
all right
hey thanks
to trying the camera will be a little
it'll be a learning process but we'll
figure it out
called me Stinky
oh that's not nice maybe you are a
little stinky
I took a shower today
gives me energy
now which which key do we press to go to
the camp press the campfire icon and
then leave your mouth
and I think yeah
I did so yeah after she's done talking
to Carlock we can just go sleep redo
that cutscene
yeah and today
agonizing
a little bit
so desperate for a hug as this one right
here
it's my lots of birth did you give her
up
[Music]
today what does that remind me of oh
there we go
okay we're ready for sleep anytime yeah
ready for sleepies end the day not being
able to send the day
I think uh get out of my cam oh I'm
trying to say the same things again and
his lips yeah
oh pressure yeah the criteria by virtue
of having no harm don't touch Carlos
crazy
oh that's it all right yeah
I mean I don't know what else we call
you brother
I'm gonna I'm I'm I'm I can't live any
longer if you were staring right now
I'll talk more to Carlos maybe I'm I'm
talking to will okay good everybody has
a nice conversations I'm reeling
but he chose my life over his I can't I
can't stand you it's been a long time
since I mean look Mario fetus wins by
virtue of being you know big and buff
I understand I get it I can't blame him
he wants he wants to put his hands on
the muscles can't blame him be grateful
you know really grateful
I guess
what are you doing she's happy
we're all uh doing our best here
honestly I've got a great sensor image
but narissa was trying to do was very
homey like Anyway this whole time she's
trying to steal your man like what the
hell
oh I'm getting Shadow heart plot
something hurts we're chill oh no uh
she's she's a drama queen don't don't
listen to him
she's always hurting
I'm gonna go Snoop on you guys this
conversation the Affliction that visits
me with screaming Agony on occasion
I'd be lying if I told you I please is
that supposed to be Shadow heart from
time to time yeah nothing to be
concerned about she's just it's nothing
to do with the tadpoles at least in case
your imagination is in danger of getting
away from you
it's just something I have to live with
yeah I get you
are you okay
if I'm being honest
but it always passes quickly so I can
manage
baby oh that's the kitty cat
I watched Garfield today
it was cute
I know fluffy I don't understand how
exactly when I felt it goatee
it's important we're gonna get another
Mario base scene
I don't know if I want that to be honest
I mean you don't have to are they still
making out
wait are we no I mean I'm listening on
somebody else's relationships
it likely won't let me real Snoopy the
best I can do she complained about
Garfield not showing his balls
aesthetically pleasing
like when when they do like uh drawings
of cats and they include the little cat
butt and the little cat you know yeah
round of plump you know they're cute
yeah Garfield didn't have that and there
were so many shots of his like back
where you could only see his his big
chunky stomach and not not the balls
though it was like something's missing
I am why can't we go to sleep
canceling
oh
it's gracious
right well hey this is a great
this is a great time to go ahead and let
you guys know that time to look at a
cutscene oh no oh what's this
um
maybe I have a big announcement you guys
now now great news everybody
oh it's over
oh swag I mean cool
I mean you want to do it oh well yeah go
ahead yeah yeah it's the Vine
let's go
um yeah I asked I asked ahead of time
the ladies said that I could oh yeah it
is showing her oopsies
um it was it was secretly secretly shown
there just kidding huh it's not a secret
because you guys definitely saw it right
um oh God the bgm is so loud sorry
I asked I asked the others permission to
be about the show because I have to
because in about in about seven minutes
my my brand new Ep jigo 6 the EP is
being released in a big old record hold
up look at this it's vinyl
Bingo vinyl record this is the show
hours by the way everybody's gonna show
some stuff hopefully everybody so
yeah check it out you guys in about
seven minutes correct so be sure that
you check the link there's gonna be a
big old big old Link in the description
check it okay make sure that you click
make sure you yeah you grab it before
it's gone because I don't know if we'll
restock this bad boy so you wanna you'll
want to get it quick you guys you'll
want to get it quick
congratulations
thank you you guys
yeah it's the Mori store thank you thank
you thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you for you guys Maurice store
has really fast shipping by the way the
more restore you have a more store yeah
there's a universal Universal made it uh
it's a Mori store that it ships very
fast to us
um do they ship to Europe
I'm not sure I I think it does
does it ship to Europe because I know I
have EU beats I don't know it I don't
know if it ships fast but to Europe but
it's a U.S space it depends I think it
depends on the country but oh yeah it
does ship to Europe but um it's it
probably won't be fast
worldwide you should I know but I never
wanna I know there's gonna be one person
who's like those are shipped to my
country
sorry I messed up I made a mistake but
anyway you guys can get it I have a
couple more images to Joe sorry for
people that aren't on my stream that
can't see big sorry there are two
calories to check if you if you want to
see pictures of it you want to click the
link in the description it'll take you
to where it's going to be sold
um but yeah it kind of looks like this
and then uh there's some of Uranus art
that's also going to be included it says
sample on it because no no thieves No
Stealing Oh No No Stealing yeah no
thievery no thievery yeah yeah then you
can be a thief and then you can feel it
and that's totally cool that's totally
no problem
um let me get the link I don't know if
if the if they're gonna paste the link
in there hold on a second I'm gonna put
the link in the description myself
because I am my own master
um and I can I can do my own
yeah I sure can so yeah that was what I
wanted to
um promote for today and um
the description is now updated
or else
hey just kidding uh but it is really
cool it makes a nice decoration piece
you can frame it you can play it on your
phonograph Etc so please check it out
um who's next on the the show the show
and
afterwards we're not by the way
we're gonna keep playing
hours very very specific timing that's
not bad yeah the very sorry could not
change it
but yeah Kiara's next yeah I recently
released an album it's still open for
pre-order uh link is also in the
description if you want to get a
physical version and oh surprise
actually today I released the Korean
version of do you it was so good yeah
because it was actually one year
anniversary of Julio so I thought let's
make a Korean version because it already
sounds like K-pop let's go yeah so album
and uh Korean version of do you and
pineapple MB is still out there to be
streamed yoroshiku please please take a
look at it and yeah keep on streaming
the album so because it's my first one
so I hope it can do well
yoroshiku hey
there's something for everybody on it
yeah this is my first
physical like music thing because all my
singles before are like online only
digital only and this one you can
actually get as a physical thing yeah so
very special
yeah yeah that's the extreme point of
view point of view point of view
anything else oh
um let's see oh uh this Friday or
Saturday depending on what time zone
you're in uh but Saturday for uh c
um I'm going to be appearing at Thai
company oh yeah
yeah it'll be my first panel ever so I'm
kind of really honest for it but um I'm
calling my mom so she can you know coach
me and teach we're speaking Thai better
so I can I can talk to everyone I'm
really nervous but I'm excited uh
[Music]
thank you
yeah that's it for me cool that's so
cool that you so quickly get a con
appearance that nice nice nice I hope
you get to speak some Thai let's go
Flex those skills yes gotta Flex
I apart from my streaming schedule I
don't have anything I have a collab with
biboo next week
Tuesday Tuesday Sunday yeah a chat where
we're going to talk about the first
night that we spent together oh
yeah
give us the details we will please be
sure to be their typical uh time at 8pm
C team
song covers yeah check out my song
covers so I can release another one
yeah that's all from me yay
yeah ladies being busy with putting out
things so support us please yeah yeah
everybody's working hard to give you
guys cool stuff yeah yeah
thanks for for supporting us did you
just watch this film again I'm talking
to everybody okay seeing what they have
to say this morning so [\h__\h] funny
oh man let me fix my little sensor image
I'll just keep it right in front of me
such nice weather
it's nice weather we're having today
oh wow well it's telling me his life
story oh wow there you go you can have
will yeah I guess we'll go for will or
Gail what Everyone likes me more he's
horny just like you the fancy bowls and
what drinking from gold
horny ass and he's got horns now
good morning girl the Flaming fist
who leaked you that information anyway
I don't know it's been a badges
what's up lizelle give it some time
sorry that no one's talking to you are
you lonely
[Laughter]
he brings to mind a story
the Devil with the silver tongue old
fairy tale my father read to me wait did
you hear about it or are you a member
anymore
I mean you can with a private account
get him a bottomless coin purse
the farmer's dearest fruit naturally was
no apple no Peach
beloved daughter we can learn a lot from
fairy tales
why is he acting like this
I mean the dude just got transformed
like yeah I feel a little bad for him
yeah
and given the circumstance
I do it again
my soul was a necessary price to pay for
you know I can't say more oh but I can
say sorry little guy I had but one road
I could travel
for now you have a dozen the hundred
a thousand to choose from
the road that leads to yeah
this makes me want to play more on my
own I know right let's see what happens
to all the characters and stuff exactly
yeah
there's such a different game playing
with everyone yeah
finally someone approved of something I
did
you can't please everyone it's on my
head I can't please anyone like a
mammoth's test I mean I feel these
ridges snaking down my neck you're just
two seconds
I was just born that way man I haven't
seen my reflection just yet be my mirror
what do you see oh
dude
I die handsome devil it's because you
know the heart lurking under the horns
oh she's trying to raise them up
maybe even a beast hungry but will do
you understand that she is also tiefling
now like yeah like where are you talking
trying to lecture together
there's so many there's so many people
said he approves every time I talk to
him
no one merely answers it's cool
yeah yeah I gotta get gotta get my
approval up even though we can't check
because we can't put them on our team
I'm not a child crying out from alone
yeah for real I found him in the fields
flanked by a goblin you just gotta
believe his mother's corpse bled into
this you know what if the approval only
goes to moriope
is she just blessed
with some kind of special magic I mean
French shapes tomorrow
so long for me to see the coast suffer
so I want to understand why there's two
of galaxies
don't question it why he did I I am
questioning it don't question it and
it's nice to meet someone it's just a
thing that he does having a worm
wiggling in my skin does that sometimes
in the days ahead yeah with you as my
Ally
the future looks a little oh she's sweet
yeah I heard this before Mr Nice amenity
that keeps me awake countless nights if
you want to play the hero and be the
nice character in the game will is
perfect games and play for the rules
yeah he loves when you're nice
[Laughter]
it could well be if you could flown
yourself wouldn't you what a good
argument
I mean yeah what would you do with the
clone of yourself if you had one make it
to your chores what if it had a mind
makeup with yourself the ones you'll
have to let me you want to make out with
yourself Kiana
what kind of we're standing here with
nothing but the clothes on our backs I
mean you know yourself best don't you
I'm sorry one of my jailbirds just said
something funny and I need to repeat it
to you guys but they said you should
have turned a Starion into the Monster
Hunter and gone the full yandere round
off that would be pretty funny actually
he almost turned him in
maybe next playthrough
yeah next in Another Universe I'm sure
of it no I refuse I would never mind
I already cleaned myself every single
one of our one of our things what are
the companions I'm too attached to all
of them I don't want anything bad to
happen to them we should go out we
should leave the camp and make some
pride yeah let's leave let's leave let's
go kill the heck yeah kill the hag yeah
long rest leave Camp there we go okay
all right gotta learn how to play again
oh yeah uh yeah let's go
I show
do you do you say you do feel the same
see I cloned myself and do you already
if you remember yeah yeah
they weren't they were they were raising
each other up yeah it was like a mating
dance exactly oh my God that's what no
you were rizzing me up you were asking
me if I did I remember I remember what
is she talking about she's going crazy
can someone calm her down
there's anything I can do
be careful oh
noxious oh is this the bug where you
don't see them oh
yeah I had that bug before that can't be
good do you see the fumes girls
okay that's nice action's helpful
dumb
um
we can throw things onto the noxious
fumes thingies
I I just figured out how to jump
okay thanks just just point point point
wherever you want to go
often they will just find their way
I'm gonna learn how to use the camera
you like a little baby bird oh ow when
the camera took some getting used to but
now I would not change myself play for
anything oh what's this you figure it
out yeah yeah we can like throw
something on it that's normally we
should we have a like a graphic glitch
right now I think normally we should be
seeing like fumes
if you want to see like items press alt
and you see what's lying around with
alcohol yeah
alt currently you don't there's nothing
really around though okay got it I'll
remember that
okay all right onward let's get it
[Music]
yeah it's fine sucks
in the cage you want me to kill you
maybe
do we care about her
I mean it would be cool to save a life
but I mean we don't have to
do yeah yeah wait we can just you know
go with the flow yeah
oh I see where the wind takes up
hello hag hello I'm gonna attack her
wait wait you can really use it oh
[Applause]
[Music]
you know
I'd like to see you try keep you alive
[Music]
I killed your brothers why do you care
about me
yeah but she says just get out of here
please like she has any kind of concerns
me shut the [\h__\h] up
she needs to shut her ass
she does
oh that was like half my help yeah
girl remember you have potions so mean
even though I killed the fan uh I guess
I guess I'll save her here you go
so we gotta figure out which one's real
[Laughter]
get rid of them
maybe I don't I guess we'll Frenzy
someone want to attack one of them I
already did I got rid of one clone I
can't I have to save the save
[Music]
gross okay I won't do that spell yet
then shame
and turn
okay
um they're so far yes
[Music]
okay
um
on my way can I run a coward making
clones
oh
what a cute birdie is that yours Kiara
yeah I brought a raven to the party yeah
yeah oh my God there's a murderer
right
a group of is it always and only crows
is there a difference between the group
of crowsers group of ravens a murder of
crows is yeah a group of crow it's an
uncleanness of Ravens and I'm kind and I
yeah
group of animal names so funny
two of them now
let's see I wish they weren't invisible
no wait it's the one that's not wet it's
the one that's not wet is actually her
because I I mean okay actual the wet one
I can beat up
no the one that's not what you can beat
up
oh okay the one that is wet I should not
beat up yeah the one that is what is the
one that I saved okay okay
let's see where is the other one
oh yeah right uh-huh
yeah the one that's on level one versus
the one that's on level five yeah
that's not what I meant to do but all
right actually I didn't need to do that
either
[Music]
oh
well I made our decision easier yep we
made it yeah
I got it wrong
she's really not that helpful anyway
I was told um inventory okay there we go
inventory and then oh yeah because like
when you save her she's like super
ungrateful apparently oh okay well that
sucks I'm
I'm validly yeah
what can they equip I mean well yeah
because we did kill her family so I kind
of feel yeah yeah maybe but like when
you find out her motivations
she was here by her own you know choice
so she didn't really want to be saved
yeah
so you kind of interfered and then you
know
why would you thank you for something
she didn't ask for she doesn't have
anything to do for anymore
but you're right
I'll use an action equip they need help
okay not letting me
oh no well I don't have oh
just kidding I don't have any more I get
it and turn
this is terrible
um
annoying I'm just better with weapon you
know
um
I hope your soul is in good hands
no nothing just sit on you big dumb dumb
Go Raven go
sh
oh let's go we're doing it guys
figuring it out
it's all coming together
ah man I need to get on the high high
ground
I need to find a way forward yeah
yeah me and your Raven are beating her
up it's sick
no he's trying his best pick her eyes
out
good luck great
I mean it bro
I won't get in
at least
[Music]
yeah now you're bleeding on like that oh
oops
she's wet right now
yeah you guys did just realize the girl
that we killed there was a child inside
of her body oh
baby death Ah that's no good
um well I'll keep that in mind for my
personal playthrough I guess
please kind of forgot about that just a
tank
killing me it's a waste of time I'll
find a way to return double kill then
you wouldn't be begging then you
wouldn't be begging for your life right
so how about we be civilized about this
hmm
I have something you want
[Music]
um
what are you gonna do Memorial
I could give you power anything you want
you want to be stronger tougher smarter
done
just let me go ability score plus one
that's pretty cool I mean that's kind of
cool we can just beat her up again if
she comes back to life
um give me power the more the better the
more the best choice
here
what's that you have to eat yeah yeah
I could set up shop elsewhere people
always need lotions and potions
I mean
get out of here before I change my mind
if I ever see you again you'll be
fertilizing this swamp if I ever see you
again
glad that we have an understanding peace
strength min max the strength I think
yeah I'm taking all right the marina
necklace
yeah maybe it'll be useful someday
what's up yeah
yay yay
a scalp a small price to pay yeah
getting someone's scalp what are you
gonna what what are you gonna go for
strength
so I can smash more
big smashes I don't know what these are
all these potions potions take them
free potions everything what's that
what's the mushrooms
I don't know take it take everything
mushroom Circle
is
it teleports you if you go there
all right then shall we get out let's go
okay all right you guys not everything
right yeah
okay that was interesting
where could we be
yeah just another day in the Vlog
yay
oh coffin that's her her guy marinas
it's rough inside
can someone talk to the Dead
yeah uh maybe you gave me a thing that
helps me talk to the dead right yeah you
have you should have a talk to the dead
necklace let's see
it's a necklace I think yeah you're
wearing it so you should have it in your
skill bar I think yeah it says rare
speak with the Dead
um my skill oh yeah there it is let's go
let me scroll
all right speak to the Dead
hold on let me turn turn it around I bet
I can oh yeah narissa also has the
ability now because she read the book
that gives her the speak to the dead
ability why yes Target Undead
can you use it on him I don't know how
to use it past Bell
oops okay
I don't know did I eat it I don't think
oh I think it's because the girl is dead
that you can't continue this yeah
um
that's rough that's rough buddy I mean I
understand though it makes sense but
that's okay I have her necklace should I
leave it with him no casual just wear it
or something it doesn't work on all this
if I wear it maybe even somewhere
no guy is Undead not dead so apparently
he's a zombie
that's that I guess what do we do next
what do we do
I'll leave it up to you good question
something short are you sure oh I guess
we're gonna go to the underdark didn't
we go there last time yeah but we did we
entered briefly yeah
definitely want to get some health back
maybe a short rest yeah
um how do I quick travel
um
and then click solo Knight Outpost okay
don't go so fast Cali is not even here
oh I'm just gonna grab a weapon and then
I'll be back okay
the one that's right by the entrance
just don't get into trouble
I'll try
um
there he is she's taking dick slender
Stone before you
oh my God
feels like everything
I'm gonna get it
the weapon slips yeah we killed that
dude too the Minotaur I'm not gonna go
in I'm just gonna look at what he has
nothing just kidding
[Music]
yay
yay Barn sword all right sword and my
solo play through what came to the
underdark from a different place and I I
wasn't able to enter where we're
standing in right now I just explored
everything outside
you need to collects like three pieces
or something
oh
from people Apple what time
okay there's a staff of the Moon Maiden
what's that
sounds cool fancy
all right
I think I know a good place where we
could go here in the underdark okay okay
leads away the Mushroom City
could be good I love
oh that sounds cool it's not what it's
called oh my God
whoa earthquake we just gotta get down I
don't know where the way it goes let me
equip my crossbow really quick
oh wait they're shaking isn't that a
sign of the that monster oh yeah
uh let's get out of here let's no I'm
walking let's keep moving okay okay
we're here I did you see what I'm seeing
yeah no
because it's like some voices talking to
me
there's a voice talking to you
okay he's done they're coming now we can
go
a big deal they're coming who cares I
ain't afraid of no ghosts
penny
it's like I have three enlisted
in the bathroom
yeah
oh what's this
oh
no nice stuff
whoa Olympic Powers I haven't actually
used these yet
concentrated blast yeah I haven't used
these yet either oh yeah there's a
Minotaur up there I've used one
oh I just used one oh yeah remember we
are they all combined we all share that
yeah okay well good thing I didn't use
more oh I just used one oh yeah I
haven't used one as well huh
uh
click click click on your inventory
and then you see the little things in
the Middle top of the page that opens up
click on the one that says a lithid
powers
uh yeah and you can red you can you can
manage a lift it it'll bring you to a
brain and you can't but this one
I thought
I fall yeah we we had three
but we can find more there's a lot of
them in the game
okay so it's okay for me to use
yeah this one we used one we're all
gonna share yeah help check which one do
I pick
they're not shared yes they are
they absolutely are shared I mean this
name so we collectively all have the
same amount of brainworms there's
Minotaur up there cookie
I saw it said three and I popped one
thing and then I heard people like I
used one and now there's only one left
mm-hmm
all right we have to eat The Witcher I
know I already ate the hair guys look at
my inventory
look look up here
it has been consumed
there's bad guys
oh you did your best
um
[Music]
well that's okay we can do a ranged
attack that should be fine I'm just
kidding it was not difficult position to
start in
yeah me too
oh well
we'll get through it
where is the second one
I'll find it
hi guys
oh I'm surprised I hit I only had 55
percentage
we'll be fine we won't die or maybe we
will but it'll be sick
oh he doesn't have that much health this
will be fine
it'll be fine
it's like a monster truck
that's awful oh oh there's another one
horse tunnel I want to try and use that
oh
okay okay
yeah back up okay wait I'm gonna put
something
here don't walk past it oh okay
nice
damage nice that's so broken I love it
so much
oh he dead now oh
we just got the other one nope just one
more left
nice
cool
oh
yeah
right there yeah did he get hit by The
Cloud of daggers
I would hope yeah
[Music]
yeah
nice one ladies good teamwork okay
here's a question of something I haven't
figured out how do I turn off now
how do I turn it off you should see on
the right side concentration something
something amulet baby in your hot bar
somewhere
like bounce fence you're concentrating
on it you want it I have that I don't
know someone who does that what was it
bludgeoning
vulnerability to bludgeoning damage if
someone wants it
you can just take it for my inventory
how about disarming first I disarmed one
if you would just wait can I take this
hat in your inventory
[Music]
okay I'll take you if you want something
just ask you can probably take it whoa
what happened there
she just disappeared critical failure of
disarming I'll do it again uh oh the
Trap yeah we're gonna wish the walk
through it
she doesn't care about pain did you just
I broke it
[Music]
nice guys
eh [\h__\h] the roomba's going crazy
yeah
I know I can't get down yeah you can
there's a thing over here a mushroom
jump on the mushroom yeah like Mario
yeah there you go there's stuff up here
though if you want to look goodies yeah
oh goodies I know this place love
goodies
it's looting time
threads useful friends
oh everything's lost everything is
locked yeah what if we attack it on fire
yeah I can attack it
oh
duck
when's your kids are they're there for
the taking
a nice fire
that's it
that's a trap there's a trap
[Music]
you girls being aggressive
oh my God we're a little look up
oh my God come on I cannot believe I
can't set wood on fire I know
what if we just break it salutenberg
thank you
I'm disarming it oh it's got a trap oh I
got gotcha gotcha I didn't see it had a
trap on it I just disarmed it okay
yeah there you go
eh okay where I disarmed it but now we
need a key
ah classic I think it was like
looking around here plastic you did good
lock picker do your thing
do your thing oh there's skulls in here
nice rolls that's such a ring of fire
you're worm today
I like that song I don't blame you
can just break it open good man
break it
oh that's pretty sturdy
rice peaceful friends
oh this should totally be possible
yeah there you go yeah open sesame
open
lots of goodies out there let's go Arrow
of darkness and arrow of ill Mater oh
there's an elevator here but it doesn't
work yeah I'm broken I already looted
everything here
okay okay looks like we got all the
goodies
all right let's go down
to uh mushroom land
I like mushrooms I hate mushrooms so
much I don't like to eat them but I like
to look at them
I would agree with that they're
aesthetically pleasing yeah oh typically
mushrooms are great eating not so much
like mushrooms and like accessories or
so me too except in the Milky Enoki is
the best one I don't know why it's so
good yeah but if they're coated in
delicious sauce
a mushroom sauce I think I can still I
can still eat but just mushrooms that
are not in the sauce that's what I want
for a day
that sounds good don't make me hungry
I'm gonna make you hungry oh you shoot
unless you're gonna feed me and there's
the people wait wait who's leading yeah
okay yeah hello
mushroom people
listen
to music through one creature wow yeah
they look thick are these little
mushroom villagers yeah mushroom people
cool
welcome he has come oh you got a funny
face
they all look so shiny beautiful a
single Melody rises above the others oh
it's the near Among Us world
right easy
oh I'm getting threatened The Sovereign
is threatening you
um
your best I
um Adventure
fungus look at that booty
[Music]
[Laughter]
not as good as your booty on this booty
yeah
not quite good enough
okay but true intent then we wouldn't be
a
mushrooms yeah right
yay
well do you want to live in a mycena
noise
that's the that's the sovereign
shiny like you oh yeah let's explore
this but follow one person
yeah
who wants to lead the way I want to fall
okay hello
oh is this a shop it says shop on them
yeah this is a shop hello
my face yeah that's a big old hand in
your face
at your service
if you like us
yeah does he have a worm soul I wonder
um
it's curious to find a surface dweller
here
ah
want to chill looking for sure I'm lost
a common phenomenon in the underdark I'm
afraid could I ask what you were
searching for to begin with
mushrooms uh
clean the whole stop okay
you were infected by an illicit tadpole
it's a miracle you're still intact you
must be worried sick but have no fear I
have a friend who may be able to escape
[Music]
is this Adventurer has an enlisted
tadpole inside her head but she hasn't
turned we're special
to have it
is this the one that is he the one oh
he's a nice one
yeah let's have him take out our
tadpoles try it
um help open your mind to
he seems friendly
Powers it's kind of sad yeah totally
let's do it uh okay
okay I trust you
all right let him in let's see if it's
that easy the tadpole pulses with power
Squidward it feels ten times its size
alive awake yeah smug this is most
unusual
the incubation period should be complete
as should your transformation I think it
seems nice
strange
range appears to be in some form of
stasis
wait it is the one
pad what shame
uh can you help no
B is to be shielded
and magical info
and even without the shield the
extraction would involve severe cranial
trauma
that doesn't
house I have healing magic I intend no
disrespect
one can only heal so much of their own
brain tissue
but not to worry
should you translate well I don't want
to transform that's the whole point
former New examination
damn
fascinating
I have never set foot on one myself
they were our warships during the
greatest eras of the illicit Empire we
ruled the entire astral plane from their
decks the design was lost when the gift
rebelled minion
interesting oh that's why they were
dragons or something
okay thank you I guess
I am sorry I cannot assist you in its
removal
but for Big Ups anyway yeah I know
and I need an idea
I should start taking notes there may be
a way to bypass that stasis
there are many alchemical substances
substances
uh uh what were we talking about what
kind of alchemy a tinct
from a collection
what a silly word right
I like that
sounds like sphincter
and timisk spawn
why you sound so surprised
no I don't like it anymore of these
mushrooms can be quite dangerous
confusion in those that approach them
tongue is
self-explanatory we have to eat a tongue
you
um oh they're mushrooms okay lovely so
where do I find these mushrooms the
underdark of course although they are
quite rare and their Discovery perilous
[Music]
I imagine Lenore would have them in her
possession she served mistra as a cleric
oh
oh uh all right where's she living the
Southwest when I last saw her although
her Tower does have a tendency to move
weird it's alive interesting okay
continue she is quite fond of her garden
Lenore has always been a lonely soul
that nature was her only companion I
offered one of those to join the society
but remember who asked you her
experiments on Susa bark he knows a lot
okay
um I'll I'll come back when I find them
I guess your travels be safe I like this
too
they're nice they were nice
don't you dare don't don't steal don't
steal yeah I'm not gonna steal but does
somebody need to sell some stuff oh yeah
let me no I like to people who's very
full on her inventory yeah
hmm I think after we're done like like
we can explore the city a little bit
more and then we could end it
yeah it seems like a good a good place
yeah
[Music]
oh Callie's talking but let's just
observe I mean I thought that this was
the shopkeeper but he's like going
through a bunch of weird stuff right now
yeah he first wants to talk spills
the shopkeepers always so talkative why
are they so tall yeah
but I can I can sell him stuff yeah
be possible
okay do you have anything interesting to
trade enjoy a good burger let me make it
quick oh I have a lot of selection is to
your liking
her weapons though you can keep them to
throw tea I know which is why I kind of
don't worry what about uh sell all
jewelry that isn't useful correct yeah
jewelry and all like M's
you could sell a lot of your great
swords and stuff can I throw the great
sword yeah
yeah I might want to hold on to it then
you want to know a fun trick
yeah do we still have the girl we killed
no menthara I don't think yeah oh okay
because what you can do is you can
collect dead bodies and keep them in
your inventory and then you can eat dead
bodies for big damage because they weigh
that's pretty awesome
we don't need the masks anymore right no
no okay wait with you that would be
pretty cool I do like that that is
deadly
I I enjoy that
um I'll sell all these poison apples
in my own playthrough I've been
collecting dead bodies
yeah you can collecting them at my Camp
so I can look at them and remember my
spoils oh pretty base I'm the rich okay
wow
when the wearer gains lightning charges
they also gain three temporary hit
points one of you guys might want that
oh this lighting charges help me because
I'm lightning
I think so you should grab that I also
have a weapon that gives me Lightning
charges automatically
so oh nice now you could really use that
so maybe you should buy that after I'm
done in here oh is something I'm selling
I have lightning yeah on my shoes
actually yeah he's selling something
called the lifebringer it's like a tiara
looking thing Tiara for Leo
Tiara for Leah
's hack a damage bonuses to anyone so
it's good
in general
and then I have to do math oh gosh okay
oh no you can
you get the button at the bottom to to
balance it
oh I see yeah there we go wow that's so
nice I didn't notice that okay
all right I'm done
go ahead
do your shop stuff
blurred
silly name
what a silly little guy you're such a
silly little guy indeed wow I can't look
at what's in the chest without like
opening it and stealing right
no you will you will make everyone here
fight you don't do it I'm great
it's not great let me save really quick
I'm not gonna do it of course yeah of
course of course we're just thinking
about it
no it's good because honestly here
I kept accidentally clicking on the
barrel stock and they will all attack
you if you do that because they think
you're trying to steal um
not pleasant
what the [\h__\h]
oh
the Mind flare can remove your tadpole
if you talk to them
yeah but why would I want to do that
also didn't you just say it
okay
okay I'll try really quickly too
that is not true yeah no they're lying
don't listen to them oh my God the head
should have removed it would have not
tried to kill her private collection
really yeah
yeah which is why I kind of don't want
to give it up yeah yeah but she would
kiss your eye and it would give you a
special skill too that you can only get
from the hag had you not intimidated her
right away true I guess yeah
sometimes we just gotta be true to the
characters we play
you could have looked even cooler okay
the trainer has no more no more money
okay
um wait oh no more money okay if you
need to get rid of some stuff although
your weight looks fine you can still
carry a lot I know but I have an Ingot I
wanted to sell there's another Trader
down here oh
who's that
oh they're both Merchants interesting
oh
[Music]
yeah
I'm on my way to becoming the richest
person like don't you need to trade
yeah but I okay
oh look at this little dude can I talk
to you yeah
Bello he's cute
what a cutie hello little buddy
wait I have animals oh yeah
are you guys killing people
he treats me good now doesn't kick me
anymore
oh yeah he doesn't say imagine
the lightning thing
yeah I guess I'll buy it if he still has
it oh the hag can double your inventory
space that's wacky
[Applause]
yeah some stuff though and complicated
you think so should I wear it guys
welcome back yeah made any new
discoveries
yeah Tiara for Liara hey see how it
looks on you if anything in my private
collection is to your liking it this one
oh did you grab it uh
uh grabbing now
okay I own it very well yeah at all that
should be useful for your lightning
stuff
yay
yay okay now he also got some money back
good for him
now are we all done Trading
yeah and then let's let's explore them
that's what we talked to the guy first
who wanted us to talk to us yeah oh yeah
right here this way
up here you go up these um
um
what you doing
why don't you ask him
sovereign's thick fingers stroke the
course
all over them just like you melody
greets
to you
I show you
a watch and listen
um
[Music]
right that's how I killed those chicks
in my anniversary video
yeah that was raw yeah that was crazy
Kelly you saw it
[Music]
poor
that was wild
raw and you turned them into raw chicken
yeah
survival in the wild
erness
we gotta beep up some people
mm-hmm
uh
sure why not yeah we can help a twigger
yeah
nice
mushroom powder mushroom does
suffering gifts you people your girl is
so pretty a wall of vines
I like her eyes I could stare into them
forever
do the circle of service
we will await word
Circle
um what are you doing we
've life into our enemies flesh
the dead make a fine host for my growing
children
makes sense
don't do it don't do it don't do it oh I
wanna how do I do that I want to learn
oh all right at least he was honest
[Music]
they dance to no other Harmony at least
he's honest yeah he's real for that bye
bye
um but you know if there is a mushroom
you might want to kill I can lead you to
one
we want to kill a mushroom yeah a
mushroom guy okay you mean the
dwarf looking here uh yeah
the fat one
um ah that one why why kill him we bring
him with us
he's talking to me he can help sovereign
[Music]
you better be nice to him narissa no
he's not cute he's an ugly bastard
girl what's wrong with you why is so
much anger pent up in you is there
something you want to admit to us no
he's grown secret projecting
what I don't know she's really
protesting quite a bit
she might be hiding Mario hey do you
have a problem with me see he wants to
join us
hmm
yes join yeah you can you let him let
him join you yes he will be my new pet
oh yes your new pet
s
[Music]
reply why do you think he's cute are you
okay
teddy bear friend shaped
is fun though yeah but not not rotting
slime he looks like he'd smell bad he
doesn't look like he's rotting yes he
does look at him when have you ever seen
a slimy mushroom and been like that
looks tasty I should eat that oh I don't
like slimy mushrooms
you are a nice new friend yay as long as
we stay here
yum yeah we just can't leave the on the
dark then he's gone yeah yeah but we're
staying here so all is good
what else is there to explore I don't
know much more because this is where I
ended my solo play for recently there's
just a little oh it's just a village
basically there's not really much here
though to be honest hmm
should we like ended them for today
yeah and then we picked up he looks like
it should be fine
for hours yeah we made good progress
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah yeah
there's still so much more yeah yeah
never-ending content yeah also I might I
might not like stream every time that we
play by the way I'm thinking also
because I woke up so early and was like
yeah that's how I felt last time if you
were on the early turn it's recommended
to not stream yeah definitely
a mirror now but it was nice to hear
your sleepy voice
[Music]
I need to go
eat like some mushroom pasta get
something in my throat isn't just water
help it wake up still not awoken but
that was that was fun you guys yeah yeah
very effective today efficient I mean
I'm gonna show my EP again check out the
description Link in the description and
in the chat grab the new EP it's for
sale and we probably won't restock it so
go grab it
um and yeah that's all I have to say
thanks for coming today we haven't set a
date for the next collab but it will
probably be a an a morning time again
like the first time yeah any morning
okay so I might not stream that one oh
okay
let's see then let's discuss after this
three months if we can find a date that
works for us yeah
sounds good let's do it okay guys thank
you guys thank you for watching thanks
for watching everybody and for
supporting us we'll keep doing our best
let's do lots of fun things happening
yay I'll see you soon see you soon
everybody
uh I am streaming uh I'm putting on the
schedule tomorrow and I'm streaming
tomorrow just a little Super Chat
reading like maybe three hours or so
um yeah you'll see the schedule tomorrow
but in any way I'm streaming
some not in the late evening somewhere
in the afternoon late afternoon I'm
streaming just a Super Chat reading to
catch up see you then bye bye love you
[Music]
thank you good night stream the the
Korean uh pineapple uh do you I mean
what time okay I forgot let me check
[Music]
um
uh 4 P.M time probably
yeah yeah yeah just for three hours
because I have like a meeting afterwards
and you know how it is with reading
super chats for Endless amounts of hours
I I realized it gets you know pretty
repetitive after too many of the same
kind so I think it's nicer if we split
it
yeah green pineapple would be sick
honestly Korean probably works for all
of my K-pop songs
yeah okay and then schedule after I wake
up I'll make it then okay
do you Korean do you
yeah okay
[Music]
bye