I want to kill
you tonight Lads we
go let's
[Music]
party
I'm you know what here's a little C
freestyle if you want to bite me get
wrecked you kidding me I'm pretty good
like Grim Reaper what do you expect
about sounding cool I would say so I'm
inclined to agree this is my line of
work this what everyone wants to see
bird cute kill them time to redo the
fight this is called being a Pro Gamer I
won't die right try
aiming I want to cry you off he's right
though
die hands weapons of mass destruction
[Music]
half HP in a dream boys this Fest me and
my natural lessons I'm a workaholic by
Hobby I'm cooking I need to teach you a
lesson say Les howdy this is the
West Sheriff's the best I'm going to get
a B jump ESS anything to achieve that
dream let's goori heart palpitations on
stream just let it end just let it
my friend plays the recorder better hey
your
friend hey guys two quick
questions number one what the f am I
looking
at number
two are you
ready
go that's
a me the ball that's a Mory yeah that's
a Mori check this
out in
the yeah baby that's what I'm talking
about hey everyone I'm
Kori and I want to kill
you tonight Lads we go
[Music]
let's
I'm you know what here's a little CI
free style if you want to bite me get
wrecked kidding me I'm pretty good like
Grim Raper what do you expect this about
sounded cool I would say so I'm inclined
to agree this is my line of work
everyone wants to see bird cute K them
time to redo the fight this is called
being a Pro Gamer I won't die right try
aiming I want to cry you off he's right
though
Die My Hands weapons of mass
[Music]
destruction half HP and a dream boys
that's fine is me and my Natural Essence
I'm a workaholic by Hobby I'm cooking I
need to teach you a lesson say less howy
this is the
westboy sheriff's the best I'm going to
get a B jump emess anything to achieve
that dream let's go alori heart
palpitations on
stre just let it end just let it end my
friend plays the recorder better hey
your friend
[Music]
hey guys two quick
questions number one what the am I
looking
at number
two are you
ready
go that's
aori me the ball that's a Mori yeah
that's a Mori check this out
in the
house yeah baby that's what I'm talking
about that's
my
Hello whoa hey
we're spawning into the world
already
weird it said an error
occurred you guys can see me now though
right I think they can see me
now
hello I think we're
good do question mark it said that an
error occurred
hello oh
hey hey
guys I'm awake
now I'm awake and on time for
a one last go around this is freaking
freaking insane look at me I'm your I'm
your
uncle I'll be a monkey's uncle everyone
is spread out
maybe I should
go
there how was everybody so spread
out Trader Bob I'm still going to take
your
quest how am I feeling I'm feeling a lot
of
emotions I always I always wake up and
cry the day after watching the G and the
gone
movies I'm just not
I'm not strong
enough dead beats I'm just not strong
enough can't handle
it sorry to hear
that no need for sorry it's my own
thing
Bob there's not anything really good
today is there
Bob that's rough Bob it's not like I
have any money you're so tight you
probably got burglar alarms on your
garbage bags I mean I don't really know
what prompted that but yeah
maybe yeah last night I made like what
did I make I made my own
racotta and everyone was like this is
the best thing in the freaking world and
they're like how do you make it right
and I was like well let me did you I
taught him how to make
ricotta I'm sure the people that came
over though they'll talk about it if
they want to Iris and R already said
that they were there but they're like oh
is that oh that's a mountain
man there goes guua she'll be back I may
yeah ricotta is really easy to make it's
kind of crazy though all you do is you
put some milk in a
pan and then you you don't boil it you
can't boil it cuz that'll ruin it
pop and
pills now you can't yeah you don't want
to ruin it so you just kind of let it
simmer and then eventually a a film
begins to appear on the top and then
some bubbles appear um around the sides
if you have a thermometer then you can
be a little more precise with
it um and I'm not talking about the one
that you put under your armpit that's no
good it needs to be a cooking
thermometer and then
you put as much salt in there as you
want if you want it to be salty you put
lots of salt in there if you don't you
don't basically I'd still put a little
bit though and then you add lemon juice
that's the crazy part because once you
add lemon juice it begins to curdle
immediately as in it forms all of these
these
little clumps of cheese just gathers
together and gets
compact yeah clumps of cheese that's
that's what Rau it is it's clumpy cheese
yeah they're curds and then everything
under it is whey you toss the way
because it kind of separates itself the
lemon juice mixture well it's not really
just lemon juice it's like a lot of
really it's called way no
way no way yes way and it separates from
the from the cheese and so you spoon it
out with
like a ladle that's got holes in it and
then you set it aside let it cool or you
can use a cheesecloth but I I use a
strainer the strainer was
fine yeah so you can squeeze out like
all the all the juices from the the
cheese
but strainer
Works anyway that's my long-winded
explanation of how to make it's very
very early and we went to bed
late yeah both G and the gon movies back
to
back it's it's a lot of
time yeah I think I went to bed around
like
2 a.m. cuz everybody got to my house and
we just Yapp we ypp and Yap and Yap and
Yap and don't stop yapping and I'm like
oh my gosh we got to watch this movie
before it gets too
late and now I'm up at I had to wake up
at
7:30 first time they watched that movie
some of
them um I believe that that was the
first time that Rara had seen anything
past like
episode
8ish of Gan Lagan or was it
seven I don't know she told me that she
stopped watching it a very certain part
and then IIs it was her first time
who cried the most oh I got to keep
secrets maybe Iris but we we were both
right it might have been me it usually
is me oh wow oh did they do the raid
here that must have been pretty cool lot
of
dugouts oh friends I got to
unmute oh oh oh thank you hello 15 Hi C
how'd everything go yesterday it went
good was it fun it funny it was funny it
was funny it was funny raid yeah funny
about it spikes may have been more
dangerous than the zombies oh
really what was more dangerous than the
zombies sorry the SP but the defenses we
set up around the house was more
dangerous than the a oh jeez was it
around this house no old house still
it's it's holding up wow that's crazy I
saw that you guys have a Dugout around
this house
though oh that's giggy can't stop
herself the
goer
from She's the mole putting those F to
good use I guess does anybody has any
extra clay by any chance oh we have t in
this CH over here follow me follow me
I'm following you wait that's cilia what
okay okay this chest
thank you so much hey ladies did we find
any shotgun parts by chance yes they're
in the parts weapons Parts chest ooh in
the new house thank
you weapons Parts chest there we go we
also have a couple mini bikes by now and
the forge has
grown and yeah by now the zombies that
show up are a little bit more dangerous
we have crazy direwolves showing up when
you see one of those it's so over you're
prob it's over you just got to jump yeah
I just got to
give Big B oh they're so
scary just a big b could do the
trick right so I want to try to improve
especially the armor from the girls who
have the most shitty armor right
now uh I won't have like enough armor
kits probably to get everybody like the
most amazing armor but that's okay some
parts at least yeah um I'm assuming L
CeCe your armor is probably pretty bad
and Callie's maybe too yeah I could use
some what level is it yeah I think I
think minees might be better than R but
it's still not the best okay my armor is
weak though I have a few hand me downs
at least uh there are for example
there's level free preacher gloves which
already give you 30% Undead damage oh
very there's also so many armor in the
armor chest yeah so there's there's
where the hand me downs are as well just
so somebody take the level threee gloves
and the Commando boots can we can we get
this this uh sorry boxes anything right
oh yes okay take take M okay
I'm going to have a ton of
bandages that's good we're like at least
30 but maybe more did you collect all
that aloe I'm collecting it right now
nice nice so did farming work yes well
sort of maybe not it's easier to just go
out into the wild and punch plants oh
okay true that true
that I wonder yes yes yes yes I'm I can
find some
leather and and duct
tape kaha
no she go I died again there
she but usually it's like two times and
then it doesn't happen anymore
so hope
so this one is duct tipe still like our
diffic most difficult thing to get like
a high value commodity yeah duct tape
and uh Forge steel but yesterday at the
end of the Stream we were able to get
The Crucible to forge Forge
steel okay we can also make
glue like C glue as well yes we should
have a good bit of
water things are getting better little
by
little but still we still need all of
those basic materials anyway yeah get it
now see so just do some quests and and
raid some houses and then you'll be able
to collect plenty I think ammo as well
ammo very important I think cuz you run
out of those ammo so quickly at the I
can craft am if anybody needs it I can
craft we have some materials to craft
right now too as well nice also please
let me into your
team oh yeah send me team request please
party
uh also I think one of the most uh
important things for me right now is
sewing kids
you can't craft those right there's no
way to craft them no crafting but the
sometimes the shops sell them
too I'll keep my eyes peeled if you keep
your eyes peeled for uh shotgun shotgun
parts how many more do you need I need
three just three more go to the ters the
chers should be selling some Bob wasn't
selling anything today cuz well go check
Teck Jane and wck because they sell
different things I think I saw shotgun
parts but I need to save my money for my
handgun part
understandable
understandable Okie doie kits also I
think we'll need repair kits yeah repair
kits those are important is
import okie
dokie sounds good and at the old house I
think we have water yeah we have lots of
water now oh
I'm also cooking some purified like the
good water I'm cooking that right now oh
yes the legendary good water didn't me
one hobo stew I love me some hobo stew
not going to lie
now
oh also there's apparently another
Trader in the snow have you guys found
him yet oh I just got the Quest for him
so I know where he is okay me know if
he's if he's still in the shotgun parts
uh sorry K where did you put the hand me
downs is it just
in uh wait they should be in the armor
chest there should be preach gloves like
on the right side unless somebody else
already took it and I if I took it
already uh I took some
gloves okay the command boots are good
too Commando
boots where did the nerd
have ah okay now
I have a nerd hat for you might have to
repair it soon
but thank you let
me yeah I'll be making more armor don't
worry okay I picked I took the commander
boots thank you kiaha are we bringing
more stuff for you thank you all right
here's some sewing
kids what do where do you want me to put
them uh the forge you have SE kits let's
go the forge okay okay
F
five
yo ni thank
part actually I'm just going to go up to
the trader the new one anyway uh right
now so that way I can see what he
sells okie dokie okay maybe he sells
seashells yeah buy Bu The Seashore you
guys are so
silly I knew immediately where y'all
were going with that
I need duct
tape okay I I think I can GL as well if
you
need we'll keep our eyes open for glue
and cloth here's some
glue you have glue I didn't know glue
would be so
important right it's really important
I'm cooking glue right now oh nice with
the water you can you can grab it when
it's done there's fire that's cooking
yipp yippe she's cooking all
right is it okay if a blueberry pie wow
yeah super yummy blueberry pie in the
apocalypse is pretty
impressive boy chefs can do
anything that is very impressive my
hammer is called gimly and I stand by a
forge making armor okay maybe not okay I
am
gim can you get over here
yeah new shotgun is going to be so good
we can get
it I think there's books in the old
church no I just
you completely vertical to the
floor fell into the rag doll all I'm
going up north to unlock that other tra
trador not traitor he a traitor kill him
backstab if somebody has more armor
parts I also need those for more armor
crafting kits to make more armor I put a
bunch in there in the chest but maybe
you've used them already they are very
necessary if you put them in like two
days ago then I definitely used them
yeah
probably okay I got a
couple I I'd love to get a fancy new
armor for myself at some
point um I want to look real fancy even
though this outfit I can make your stuff
I just need more
materials right it's always the
materials we all do a few quests today
and then we can gather some materials
yeah sounds good to me sounds good to me
I want to go meet the we got we got to
go to the library too yes yeah there's a
library I forgot
it's kind of broken for this kind of
game where reading is so
vital I know we're all a bunch of
readers you think she's closed she might
be closed we're very we're very literate
and very educated PR impressive I love
reading I mean honestly if you are in a
zombie apocalypse and you're doing okay
survival wise there is nothing really to
do other than learn
so just power
I mean probably there not going to be
any smart around what are you going to
do if you're feeling under the weather
anything particular on your mind yeah
well originally we said we had like a
stream at home right one with the
computer so yeah even if we can't stream
because we don't have electricity we
could act as if it we do we can we can
actually make electricity talk to
ourselves oh we can yes we can we
there's solar panel how we connect to
the internet I don't know I don't want
to scam by
myself no it's okay you'll you'll we'll
sit around the PC and we'll be your
audience okay we all for each other it's
like a little you know each day pretty
good yeah it's like a lawn party but
everyone else shuts up and one person
talks I like it sounds good to me I'm
in
um tell me when you guys are going to do
Quest grabing
oh yeah I also have one treasure map
that I haven't done yet and it's good to
do cuz it gave me like 5K and a bunch of
weapon parts so we should probably go
dig up that one too ooh
5K that's big money yeah yeah okay well
I'm going to head towards the fauna
Quest actually cuz there are two quests
over
there we took two we going to start
questing yes we can you we can might be
a good idea when's the next
raid I think 35 4 and a half
hours yeah a while 10 p.m. day 5 I need
more iron I need everything I need to
wrench cars what time the trador
CLA pretty sure nine 10 I think it was
10 minutes before 10 p.m. hurry hurry
hurry run run run run run you got four
go go go go go first okay so are we
heading to PHA gear three Quest I know I
just headed there I think so okay it's m
oats no scary bices outo by the way and
mini
bikes okay
probably do you know I think that's
yours Kelly it's oops is are you there
already can I just follow your oh yeah
just come to where I am pray I don't die
how did you get
there ah you bicycle or bike uh a bike
okay good good you're using your bike
it's so fast
yay so happy got a
bike I'm sure it'll be fine any scary
zombies come I'll stand on top of this
truck easy
oh
gosh right behind
me oh the new trator has six shotgun
parts
bro dang it we always finds the one that
have the ones that have the shotgun
parts but he's going to close like any
second and kick me out yeah it sounds
about right pray somebody has them
tomorrow that's an ambulance but still a
good idea yeah ambulance truck same
vehicle really
what do you think
tutu tutu is on my head right now she's
on my head oh oh not oh now I thought
you meant IRL no she is on my head what
do you mean oh yeah totally this is IRL
what are you talking about cute are you
balancing her like that does she like
put her claws her head she going to
balance I need four wait no three wait
hold up
three okay I have them you got them yeah
three shotgun parts for your Bo boy
thank you I owe you what what do I owe
you give me handgun parts or money okay
I'll give you the money from this Quest
that would have paid for the shotgun
parts appreciate that you know we're
going to have to put it on credit cuz I
just bought Forge steel okay I'm I'm
coming to the quest too by the way
so I'm almost give you
someing some of my cut I think I am
hearing Fox the world has opened up
since we have gotten B
pedal driving the bike do be fast yes
yes yes do you think we can get a car
today or is that car I wonder let's see
how far we are from that we should you
guys should do lots of quests so you can
get this new Trader where I'm at and
maybe he'll give us yeah I bet he gives
a car
oh you think he gives whole car
yeah why not I literally just got
motorcycle parts he gave me motorcycle
parts so maybe the next step is car
parts yeah car parts but not a car but I
need to learn how to make make a car in
the oh you can I you I when I went to
the forge I I got the make the four
thingy so you can't make it you need to
get the magazines first I'm at 47 out of
with 70 I can make the car oh so I need
23 more
magazines okay we'll look we'll look out
for it yeah Library oh can you guys
bring me some food because I forgot
bought it and then I have some I'm
coming to the quest thank you she
probably be here quick if she's using
the bike yeah I'm numing I'm gas gas gas
gas G let me know when you're ready
trying to craft
oh something down here maybe you could
do a quick raid of a rando house oh here
yeah go go loot some stuff while you're
w a rando
house you can actually loot the house
that you're raing because it's going to
reset when you start the quest anyway
really clever and then we know the
layout right away yeah
it's pretty cool oh de wow what a
gentleman got scared feel that's
somebody I went to school with the Rando
photos are very
frightening it's right oh no alarm no
alarm wake up wake up wake up this is
not my wake up time not for
today no that's okay I was happy to wake
up early
today I surprised I woke up without any
alarm I think
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm I'm ranching a car nearby let me
know when you're done okay I'm just
going to try to get some food cooking so
we have some when we come back good
mother she's mothering what what level
is your
wrena sorry what what level is your
wrench cuz I found a level four
one oh mine is level three if you want
to take my level four wrench I can give
it to you oh okay I can give you my
level three
wrench okay if you want to switch then
you can wrench cards too or do you have
your
own no I just have the level four that
oh okay I'll take it
gladly oh challenge
complete by the way the girls who
weren't online
yesterday have any of you
um in your achievements
have you seen there's a second window of
achievements and if yes have you
completed the 50 50 cops 50 cops you
completed that by new
chance why what does that give you it
gives you good stuff actually it gives
you like water filters and crucibles and
like stuff potentially maybe all of them
all of the Zombie Slayer ones give you
maybe good stuff maybe not
sure T yet prop now I can see where you
are you thank
you that's a lot of zombies
uh work I think you will reach the 50
cop zombies today at the final raid for
sure yeah for sure that's awesome wow
and then we'll have to do season two I
asked about it and they seemed
receptive oh yeah the character you know
how we can keep the characters and stuff
um when I mentioned it to them they
seemed to think it was possible okay yay
that been nice
yeah he two let's
go okay I think I'm
ready okay
probably got lots of food cooking yay
yay
okay bike is over
here cuz I feel like yeah we can go
further oh yeah the work look
big uhoh we haven't even set up turrets
and uh electricity yeah that's like the
next step yeah what about the pretty far
off yeah that's pretty far away but turr
would be so nice oh you're RA in the
same house as
me I just ran away from someone and I
went ran towards you cuz I was like who
can protect me not me I'm cracking open
a safe I forgot to take off my mod off
of the wrench if you can take it off
give it to me okay thank you quiet down
sir why won't he shut up close the door
for
now quick ranching session on the way
quick ranching on fuel dedicated always
always got to it's not just a fuel it
also gives me iron and I I'm actually
out of iron I think okay I'm here by the
way
okay y we're coming we're coming wow my
inventory is already full what
[Music]
oh
a you'll get rid of them
yeah maybe we can try to save most of
them for the raid I know I feel like I I
don't even have enough I have like 20
right now but I feel like that's not
even
enough I also have sledg by the way Kara
if you're trying to make a big
Sledgehammer H Sledgehammer Parts
yeah yeah wait I think I already have
enough but storm anyway maybe need more
I'm not
sure dang I blew him away God I can't
wait to see the next
shotgun may I grab those parts from you
viu I'll I'll un cucumber you
what have some money after this Mission
put it on my tab
please how much thank you can I buy off
your current shotgun off of you when you
get your new shotgun sure empty
absolutely you
can then I can help you fin anyone finds
any handgun parts please give
hand I'll keep it in
[Music]
mind where are is the new
te okay we have
arrived one second before we start the
quest can you kill me because I'm about
to die
I no
hesitation the B watch the sunset n
forget all of that watch out watch
out rest in peace L I'll miss you in
peace
Gone Too
Soon she left this world too soon who's
going to give the ji their jet packs no
one
no I'm
[Music]
coming there's two class we can do here
there's one for R and one for f yeah
that's why I came here cuz there's a lot
popping
off all right time to blast them I am
ready ready I'm hyp I'm ready for
blasting make sure to check everywhere
sewing kids could be everywhere okay
slash the curtains the curtains have
cloth we need embrace your inner loot
Goblin or your outer loot Goblin leave
it I am very much an outer loot
Goblin it's very obvious also I put a
bunch of food and Medicine in Kiara's
trunk if you need anything
yeah your spacious trunk Bountiful
trunk oh yes yes yes yes
uh I'm standing On's head like tutu on
my head and now it's me standing on R's
head and Tut on my
head whose mission is this R oh you got
start the mission oh okay sorry it's
okay let's do it
yipp yipp
yipp come out come out wherever you
are no I
wasn't I'll be got
it they an upstairs I wonder this is my
natural
posture you just you're just always
ready can can somebody loan me some
money I want to buy some beer anybody
got beer
[Music]
money I don't know if I can sign off on
that can I bother you for 300 coins oh
yeah for some beer what's this yes here
I am I am here I give
you here you go oh no thank you doesn't
go any lower I'm trying to look for
stairs
down I got beer for you here oh you
bought it for me thank you what a kind
so
benevolent take a while oh do we have to
go up oh yeah oh there is it
upstairs oh we're retrieving supplies in
this chest I didn't realize yeah come
back to
this we get up there I
wonder that doesn't seem
good great now I can see where you are
I prefer not to hit my friends oh are
you on fire uhoh uhoh oh I'm going to
die I'm going to die I died why wasn't I
my oh come on man what's going
on oh no dang was the damage that bad or
was it the
fire oh gosh okay no more fire
no more fire take some take some
bandaids out of the trunk some bandaids
yeah I have some bandaids put a Band-Aid
on it make it better got plenty now son
of a gun oh oh is that my I'll get the
next
mission oh it's okay we get a lot of
missions this time oh when we've got
supplies if anyone forgot fine look for
your Satchel like I forgot uhoh yeah you
got got a it's a it's a Fetch and
clear help anyway am I in the
floor I'm blind I can't I can't even see
the oh there it is a lot of screaming
going
on
here big screams oh there it is I found
mine
okay nice good job T nice oh no don't
please fire
no more lighting the fire she's on fire
fire fire they're on fire
right desire to be on fire no okay found
no we need to clear the area it's not
clear yet have you guys seen the
basement yet I think there's a
basement can we use this chain to climb
down or am I going to
die 99% sure this basement try oh
where is my
St I'm not ready I hear zombies up there
oh upstairs a
basement a
point yeah oh this is easy to break oh I
found oh
this
okay maybe it's outside the
birds just
boards behind oh coming up not mine
let's
see be a hatch that
fire be careful to the fire I should use
my arrow yeah know the fire is no joke
okay we cleared it nice
no team I I didn't find my supplies yet
be in there
somewhere oh B there's a safe where I am
oh where are you ouch I'm on fire on the
second floor
the
office there's anything second
[Music]
Flo I'll just look around oh yeah have
you read have you read this one yet you
should read this
one oh I have
not thank you never encumbered at night
yeah I I read it already so good I'm on
fire
yourself where's oh there's the sa okay
found it love doing Missions at night
Missions at night are the best got the
food oh I have
food in the face of danger yes where are
you I am in the basement what color are
you more cloth random I'm Brown she's at
the floor floor level I also need food
please I'll stick with s get the yum
yums and water if you have water I have
thank you
thank you there's also there's better
water in the
car car car wait come back come back oh
take some food ah thank you I really
need
to thank you so
caring oh my God why is it
so in here there's
water here I have
like a bunch of for you this for you
for okay I will not fail this time no
more fire nice thank
you thank you
woohoo yes for you thank you who's
learning electrical
traps I'm learning it yeah I feel fa is
the only one doing nerd
stuff I am doing nurse oh I can make an
electric
fence that would be helpful against the
raid that be very helpful what if dire
wolves come during the
raid that's fine are you sure dire there
were two there were two that came during
the r yesterday and I killed them just
fine okay easy so they're killable yeah
Hammer all right where's the next one uh
as Fest one is nearby
bye let's go to
it I need to do I need to finish the
quest so I can pay bioo
back I got a debt to bio right
now I owe her money I don't like going
people
money don't wiiz on the electric fence
yeah don't tell the zombies that I want
them to pee on the electric fence
Frenching oh there's how do you say this
this resident's name
r which one it is
PTI let me check is everybody
here no one sec I'm on my way I think it
went away really
quick I'm here everybody
nearby
neighbor wo okay
you ready
P oh
wow there's a lot of stuff going on
right now there's a lot watch out by the
way oh wow there's a jum what
what easy oh sorry oh a bird I can't I H
the bird me did you hit me twice no only
once the other time had have been a
zombie oh it's that thing
there he's dead oh my
God take care of your help
don't yes please can I have one there
you go thank you so
much thank
you thank
you everybody should take some bandaids
there's some in the car oh yeah bandages
help
you help you stay
safe don't whack the zombies with this
don't whack them with
it don't whack them with it because then
the light on fire then the light you on
fire it really that never happened to me
before oh it'll happen
really oh
yeah oh God there's this green one
there's a shre there's a
Hulk sorry not a lot of
green head still first is that how you
see us too no is it how you
see not
true I mean shk is actually nice yeah I
like Shrek heal I love Shrek he's cool
he's chill tell everybody Shrek
chill nice
belly can for you too or is it just me
no no no no
no oh wow he just will not
die it's all right he's draged all now
oh wait nope he's still alive he's dead
no still alive oh n
[Music]
[Applause]
you got to come to where I
am yes did you see this
picture hang go they're hugging oh the
cats I hope those cats are okay in this
apocalypse you think they got away I
wish we could might it been the best one
we probably found the best one yesterday
but this might pop it you think the
kitty cat's Got Away
safely don't make me think about it
ke I'm just asking you think they got
away
F they
away I'm sure they did living zombie
life they strong they're good at running
away
though oh oh
hello find something good in there oh I
help oh oh
no oh Yik oh that's a big one hold
up oh man dead
nope I like the glow in the dark just
the bat combined
Powers let's go oh think did we clear it
seems like we cleared it yes we did
mission complete ladies we go to the
tra I wonder yeah he should be open now
I still want to like just make sure to
thoroughly loot the house there's still
um oh yeah mind there's no quests around
here destroying the Everything Must
Go good oh even the bathroom
curtain
noing
why don't forget the library yeah is the
library
close no it's in the snowy area
oh okay a quick Trader run get some
money to give to bio there should
be thank you GG for the for the redirect
that was very
sweet
welcome guys ready for some last day
Raiden I was looking forward to this I
hope we get 10 direwolves
today better get 18 18 you're
cursing house the big ones we saw that
one time where we died like 20 times oh
the snow possibly yeah yeah yeah okay
well we hopefully we won't get those
yeah it'll be fine no problem more I
have stuff for you guys my
shotgun you're likely to get bears oh
God here you go
and here you go I got armor crafting
kits too oh thank you oh and here you
[Music]
go yo so much
ammo yes anything else I can't wait to
use that this bird is following me I'm
scared I've got good wow come over here
we'll save you come to front of house
I'm in the tree want the hobo stew
but where someone else can make me a
hobo stew
you need a hobo stew I would love a hobo
stew I've got some hobo stews if you
have a hobo stew I'll take your what's
what's with your specific interest in
hobo
stew she just really likes them I just
think it's
yummy it's hobo stew man do you know
what it's made of hobos right you really
like telling people that F huh what
don't worry Little Missy I know what I'm
getting into okay
[Applause]
okay okay I got a bunch of cloth yay
that's good we need that sucessfully
declo this
building we can probably make it but I
also want to give some gift duct tape
too oh yes and then this should be I
think I owe beo about this much is
oh hold on three shot I have not a
single spot in my inventory left let's
go to the tra
[Music]
I just knew you find something you like
wait do we have another Quest here oh
did Rowen just pick it up I see oh I one
ooh hey I'm I'm definitely down to down
to
help oh pump quality okay okay I didn't
see my such a
mess sh
oh I just need one more shotgun part now
if I want to get the level two you you
owe me
1,350 okay 1,350 no problem I almost
have that much here I'll give you what I
have right now I have 9913 bucks so I'll
drop it on the ground for
you Duke's Casino token they're using
Casino tokens as money that's silly
apply yeah do you think Duke is like the
final boss I wonder we ever meet him
maybe he's the tra saying that I think
the TR and here you go as a freebie
present ooh a freey oh nice 95 shotgun
shells now I have
491 cool it might not even be enough C
it might not even be
enough the shotgun fires so
slow yes please please take
these yes uh what
mm what's that for got my 9
M oh I don't know oh no payment needed
A9 is that if you need I give it to you
that goes for like armor and stuff I I
think it's just stronger version yeah
but what's 9 mm what's that for people
use uhoh Excuse me bird Chihuahua take
these
[Music]
can I take these and then you make me
some of my own
[Laughter]
weapon should I take these and then you
make me some um ammo for my weapon what
what ammo do you need uh I have an IR
and I have a shotgun oh the whole crew
is here at Trader Jen oh I just gave
Callie some shotgun ammo so you can
split with cie maybe yeah more Amo here
I have too much oh thank you
welcome please take it away from me Cece
please she's oh she giving me stuff
motorcycle parts okay I put I take these
thank you
you and then I
should I put
yours here oh thank you I $400 dues
right now
I'm sure I have something you'll
need yes for
you for
me take
thoseo I will be healthy
forever that's a very loud and pretty
can opener you've got there are you
talking about
CeCe Callie she is very pretty Callie
take these yeah sure oh thanks thanks
collie thanks and she probably can open
a ton of Cans really
well yeah does anybody need a a repair
kit I'm good I'm good but we will we
will need them yeah I give you future
okay I'll keep it I'll keep
it the gun but yeah that's too
okay I have he to repay you back here
very effective for everybody KES thank
you I appreciate that you don't need to
pay me back though I want to be nice
Band-Aids are for
everybody thank you for looking after us
F cilia yeah here that's for you for me
yeah this one I'm here I'm here oh
behind you oh
yeah oh thank you te I love te how did
you know right did she know
yeah I have for
you
this oh okay is anybody else learning
armor crafting I am also learning start
I think armor crafting is something
generally everybody kind of wants to
learn I'm maxed out on it so everybody
can so what do we need to make forg
steel Kiara at The Crucible what do we
need make it uh it's just iron uh as
well just same as for forged Iron same
as for for steel but just more of it
ohoo yeah take these oh thank you me
well that's why I keep on wrenching cars
and stuff because they also give iron
and anything in houses that looks like
it's made out of iron or steel also
wrench Thats So that you get more more
more nice never get enough who cool I
got to make 34 steel if I want level two
pump shotgun so yeah trying to make as
much as we can but it quickly runs out
so what why did you drop that to I don't
know
clo key I have some mods you might be
able to use for your Club if you don't
already have them oh definitely
thank you so much I will take those oh
metal spikes metal chain metal chain I
definitely feel like I can use on the I
think I can use it on the bat it might
be a club only thing though I don't know
maybe not how do you actually a you have
to choose spikes or or um chain it would
seem well thank you though I feel like
maybe if we can make bats for everyone
I'd love to make bats for everybody or
clubs for everybody oh that' be nice
yeah
rocket oh bats and clubs are different
yeah they're different to me they the
same thing my brain is a bad think too
much about it you just use your fists
yeah yeah CH I want to learn how to do
how to make drones but I haven't you
need
electricity or something or electrical
the electrical skill I think maybe oh I
only going into robotics
Rob I've been trying to do robotics but
you for the Drone you need 76 and I'm
only
at like end game stuff yeah Ce do you
want to change Club are you good you're
confused but I'll give it to you here
club with chain on I'm learning Ranger
and hunting if anybody has magazine some
at home in the booksh oh already yeah
crony's not in VC today guys
okay she's just ch she's chilling though
she's here so are we staking it out for
the final
day doing Quest and I'm going to be back
in one minute I'll be right back okay
okay maybe we can invite crony to the
team I do worry I hope that she maybe
she'll maybe she can like try and get
some of the
EXP from our battle she can come along
with us who's who's right now oh we
might have to split down cuz we're six
already oh we're already six six seven
yeah in total we were we seven with
crony yeah that's to much oh I tried to
invite her but I think six is
Max oh wait she doing Never Lie never l
oh okay oh that's crazy let's do
it nice nice we take another
Quest I'm like that hot Final Fantasy
mechanic
[Music]
girl yeah that that one from
from or whatever her name
was Cy Cy
Cindy where are we going F are we going
home or um I don't know I thought we
were doing more quests yeah but I don't
know do my quest I wouldn't mind my
inventory is still completely full let
me you want to drop it off at the other
house no cuz I guess there's no point
there's a pretty close Quest over here
storage so are we splitting or are we
going all together no we're going all
together okay going into the deserted
land going to I got to check the other
Traders today too
see if they have any shotgun
parts oh yeah I'm back so uh what is it
the the bottom one has shotgun parts in
the snow right I haven't met him Bob has
shotgun parts
and I think snowy guy's inventory reset
so you're going to have to check him
again Bob okay Bob definitely has okay I
W go find Bob uh towards which Quest are
we going back to the L Quest or I me Bob
I found one I don't know uh there's
there's a bunch of quests near Bob if
you want to come by Bob yeah okay Bob
around Bob's area there's quest for
Callie Kiara bi boo fin yeah oh that's a
lot wow I do have a quest there huh I
would prefer maybe the closest one first
the one where cie and waa have a quest
yeah tier to clear
we can do that one really quick and then
we'll go South toward Trader Bob is
crony going to run there oh gosh can
anyone pick up on the back of their bike
perhaps uh I need to make more seat mods
and more bikes uh let is she maybe I can
pick her up she's
like she doesn't even have a bicycle I
can give her my bike is she running oh I
have I have a bike too I have a seat so
I can go pick her up okay and I'll give
her my bike
people will pick you
up oh E I thought bi was picking up oh
yeah after bio picks her up when we meet
I will give her my which are we doing
right now we're doing your Bob oh mine
okay wait I went the wrong way need to
be my GPS wait I thought we were going
to Bob I didn't realize going to this
one oh did you guys go south no no we're
not going to that one I want to I was
following you it's over well we were
going towards B but everyone else is
going to the other Quest I see them in
the
distance wait where are we going where
do I go who do I follow so the where is
right now not for bi boo I think wait
are we going to the one North or to the
one towards Bob which one are we going
to where you are right now bi stop stop
stop no I thought we're going
north come where is is that not
where okay I
Going's first and then and then V
communication is on point
today communication
issues it
happens in time imagine if we weren't
all on walkie-talkies over C over wait
this reminds me of something over no
here we go again hold I'm not going the
right way am I I know I can't tell okay
that way that
way what's your favorite TV show over Tv
show uh I
think I hate picking but I like the
walking dead because that is very
sematic right now very topical very nice
over I haven't watch it yeah over you
should watch it at least like the first
couple episode are pretty good over
we'll do over oops I'm sorry I got off
the bike I pushed the wrong
but I I was doing stunts you like
dangerous things huh yeah Living
Dangerously okay here we go
party all right I'm
here yay Cron's learning the wonders of
the
bike uh I can exit the groups of cron
can get some XP no everybody's in that's
all right we can do seven apparently 1 2
3 4 5 I can't count wait how is that
possible I don't know it's crazy wait
okay so when you guys ready I start the
quest ready oh people Oh I thought it
six was the
max the following party members are out
of range B can you come closer okay to
I'm storing some
things I'll be there in one second
[Music]
again she hates
mailboxes when they're empty I hate them
she has a personal Vendetta against them
why is there nothing
inside but IRL I'm scared when there's I
I I I avoid my mailbox actually way too
much and then my anxiety like opening
the
letters there's no reason for me to be
worried about it I can just pay it but I
just avoid it anyway I don't want to see
like bills yeah same shouldn't can't be
help oh boy can you not do that
sir zombies are getting a bit
tougher oh the the freaking Hulk is here
get him FAA get him you can't let
another green person beat you
oh that's a strong
guy oh he's reaching into my
guts oh oh
hello I'm going to take care of this
behind you oh God I'm just
looting kind of expected
that know the light
source what's this damage oh
oh that was
unexpected why does it take time God
we're coming in full force with the SW
loot people I found a safe can you
lockpick it okay don't go uh uh can you
find on the map it's yeah second floor
in a closet second floor I'm on the
second
floor find me
I'm looking oh what are those wires
oh uh yeah might have to go the other
way let me know if we find any shotgun
parts oh we got to crouch to get down
here okay well that hurt me
anyway polymer yeah in in here in
here okay good luck thank you
de oh wow
protect the
[Music]
safe fire
fire oh dear oh dear I can my God I hear
so much violence behind me are you okay
uh yeah I'm okay there they're they're
they're going to die soon it's going to
be quiet soon so you can focus on the on
lockpicking I got did you open it there
wasn't very much in it though oh man cuz
they're scar some money
scared of my Big M is always nice dang
it oh oh I did it oh already nice R nice
yeah easy I do think if we go south
there will be harder quest which might
be good
yeah hard is always good wait big
hitters who's who's the big hitters Mory
okay I'm going to go through okay one
sec guys
thank you
nice oh yeah many many close by Quest
thankfully wait I didn't me to pick my
thing I wonder if we can scavenge these
oh c here behind
you uh take this give me some cloth oh
thanks may I need to
[Music]
pick that was really scary are you good
I'm okay oh
why think I can though thank you so much
one where we had to like pick up
something
or got six no this this was just a
nothing just a clear I love clears cuz
they're so easy not easy but confused
simple straightforward
simple okay I got a lot of cloth nice
yeah I got some too cloth for the cloth
God for the duct tape
Gods right sewing kids though I need
sewing we'll find some maybe at the next
house
MMO do you
want you want bombs yes yes thank you
take this too thank you and um take take
this
too oh thank
you not cuz I my pockets are full or
anything
obiously she's so
selfless okay well done what is the next
Quest my nails in this game are kind of
on
girl you know they
painted oh did you give a nerd tried out
the new horn on the mini bike ooh hold
up wait does Pony still need a ride no
she has a bicycle now does anybody need
does anybody have an extra seat oh ra uh
come come here sit on me I come oh hold
on
uh get on of course it here congratul
greetings my friend uh oh is
it oh nice
it's 100%
fuel yeah I F it up to your treatments
okay so we're going south to Bob now
right
yes kiaha you don't have a hat on let's
go baby my
hat hold on to
me my other armor is strong enough to
handle being hatless wear my preacher
hat if you want
does it smell like I I pressed the wrong
button Faun a
preacher okay let's go all right it's
not the drinking hat is it it is the
drinking hat oh I'm firsty as hell I
also have a drinking you need to borrow
it first in a different
sense are you going to the Traer right
now uh I think we're going to the the
the the two class that are on the way to
Bob yeah okay but we could do okay I
turned in my orig my quest by accident
that's fine
though it's fine I like to knock out a
bunch of them at one time if I can
but yes this is do I I like you know
hoarding completed class and then
getting them
complet safy feels nice I can't wait to
all the little
packages outside and lo all of
them deliver going to be okay oh this
was at the Poppin pills going to be
fine where we dug ourselves a big hole
before oh yeah yeah that
trauma it never ended thank you for the
ride I probably should have gotten some
G it was nice hello
hello G what's going on did you can you
join the party I gave you an invite is
it
possible my
G yes yay wow no
limit I think the difference is that the
UI just it just I don't know you guys
his colors are kind of like I don't know
hard to see but that's
it okay I'm satisfied with one car oh
this is a Mor Quest nice so I got to be
able to start this
one wait almost there
okay wait do I have the same Quest there
cuz oh oh yeah is it a twer
probably yeah you both have the same
class nice okay will we be making our
old house very strong is that the goal
yes okay it's already strong I will head
on over and keep
digging okay are you okay to not be the
mission is that okay it's okay I love
digging okie
dokie sounds good oh crony is going to
get a lot of money too I hope from
this a
Get Him Father get him make can
pay thought there was somebody sitting
in here we careful K behind
you they should let us use shopping
carts as like motorbikes and then we
just k each
other oh so kids
where'd you find the SE kid uh in the on
top of a shelf I'm
looting looting everything go go look
I've shot a single zombie oh another s
kid I found shotgun part oh you
did I need those thank you
Kiara oh don't thank me I'm just finding
things well thank you for telling me
that you had
them going to get to me right well
sharing and caring of course I will end
for free
funny appreciate
that oh my
god oh wait there's supplies oh yeah
yeah yeah I found
steroid steroid nice those are nice you
can carry anything that you want for a
while Mega
Crush yeah pump yourself
up I'm getting getting very
heavy cases I can get it yet don't worry
okay I just going to throw all oh we
have to find supplies I yeah I
forgot so much loot in here though I
know worth
it I need to find my white
reverse yeah
it's so
beautiful
yes is that also Colima yeah they're
[Music]
communicating I feel like you actually
know how to play it no
no I do
plinging me
too I have for you a few things
you oh y big hitters my favorite bag
wait do you like shotguns yeah I'm a
shotgun user there's that wonder if I've
read this before Oh Oh It's one of
these thank
you have you girls already found a way
down you show them your base skills shut
yeah I'm down it's out of they down I
need to go up
yeah oh I'm M
down hello watch
outo we get in there oh this way yeah I
opened up the
door classic what's down here oh I
stop there is a basement yeah stuff was
still downstairs May mine is upstairs
but where is
upstairs
roof how do I get to the
roof wow crony you found a me
lab that's crazy wow good job where's Mr
White where is he
Jesse we have to cook oh what does this
lead to some secret boar again or so
really fight a boar just a weird
lab oh my satel is
here huh I have have you read bar
brawling five no that's what I need
that's what I need yes I
have I'm on the roof I need that's the
last one I need
hold up on the last day you become the
strongest Fister oh my
goodness oh thank you yeah see if that
helps hold up there's some there's some
folks
[Music]
upstairs oh it works thank you you're
welcome can't believe I need opies
opies oh sh my my satel is
on Face I've put myself in a bad
situation ouch Hur
[Music]
upstairs I thought you were so
Invincible I believe in you you can get
through this you got
this yay oh take it take it here you go
thank you I'm so excited thank you so
[Music]
much oh my
goodness uh
well the area isn't clear
yet no oh I
wonder I get still live hit point
recovery for every punch now does
anybody have lock by the way nope no did
you find another safe yeah there's no
there's a reinforced chest here so we
can just Bon it I suppose yeah very very
over encom can I give you some of the
like stuff like the swing kits and stuff
uh yeah the so kit yeah I I have no
space in my inventory but the so kit
already takes up the space so I can take
that yeah okay okay I'm trying to run up
after you but I'm very
slow I'll come to you let try I think
you're there hello okay uh so you got
here glue do you have a glue stack oh no
I didn't mean to drink
that I yeah IR I can take iron iron IR
maybe on the roof I bet the zombies are
on the roof lead there's only one I got
it you got it okay I'm we done I do have
a glue stack oh you do okay here you go
cloth cloth stack
made oh no I reach my li
I the way K have the same Quest here so
we can re just do it again one I can't
take okay okay I'll take
[Music]
yeah wait this one we need I just it
away take a
f thank you you I'm almost
Max I can't get out of
here bab bonga this is how nerds do
things using our brain
muscles if something's not opening just
hit it over and over again yeah that's
all using your
noodle
Fest nerds we've ever
seen wait that's what's called using the
noodle yeah your brain oh yeah using
your noodle my brain noodles oh got a
repair oops I'm out of commission I
don't have any stone I can hit with my
bat though oh I have stone wait do I
have of stones I have one stone I wonder
if that I have a lot like 500 oh dang
you're rolling
one thanks father okay nice it's R back
oh what
is what is everybody on what floor are
you li I have a quest
Limit Oh yeah I'm also at my quest limit
didn't know that was a thing oh
oh I don't know if I've reached mine yet
oh this is for you by the way life guy
oh thank youcome I needed I think I can
make machete now maybe oh nice
oo it's freaking go does anybody have
there are antibiotics or honey I have
honey I also have honey in the bike I
think some of the Traders also sell
level antibiotics like the the bike oh I
have oh no I have vitamins never
mind I only have .9% infection
so that's pretty low until it gets worse
right
yeah should be fine just a little
zombism as a treat yeah teeny tiny bit
won't do you
bad this this lock hair looks funny
I'm trapped
inside yeah I love fauna's
armor she looks so scary like a Golem
that punches
[Music]
people for
sure I'm finally out I've been I feel
like I've been stuck in this building
for just couldn't find my way out ready
to go back
in oh no oh we're going back in again
okay oh my armor is broken I'm dropping
some things on the floor please take
when it applies to you dropping big
hitters on the floor dropping cooking
magazines on the floor my armor is
broken what was it the parts still a
yeah dropping shotgun parts on the floor
I learned to make fish
tacos who wants tacos for you can make
fish tacos Taco Tac
oh I'm dropping or candy wait it's
literally
Tuesday maybe not where' you get the
fish from I don't I don't know yeah I
haven't seen I hav seen fish at
all canned salmon
oh hey who needs shotgun farts I do
thank you okay welcome now where's Big
hitters somebody oh nice
okay oh just kidding it's not there so
we're going back to the trailer and then
we go oh I think we're doing this one
more time oh okay okay oh okay run back
I have a quest limit what does it
mean probably can't do this question oh
I guess I have a quest limit too can we
still do the quest of limit voes lety 3
two one
uh the following party members are of
range oh that's
fine okay we apparently we still can do
the quest if there's a limit oh it says
not available until uh 20 minutes later
oh that's not too bad usually it's
Wayward in game minutes mhm so is that
20 seconds we finish so the class limit
is you won't get progress for the like
the next Trader unlock but you still get
the oh that's for K that's from crony
wait Kiara sorry this is from crony I
stole it cuz it was on the ground and I
got
scared two Springs and 34 steel take
this this this glue duct tape did you
want arrows W I think you're using bow
right yeah yeah I'm using the B oh thank
you so much that's very helpful let me
know if you guys find Springs by the way
I need Springs Springs spr I think we
have I have
come here for just need
two here
yeah just wow everyone's so beautiful in
this thank you thank you for the two
Springs and now all I need is 34 steel
so we're just going to have to make it
at the forge I think oh we can start the
quest now yeah let's run it one more
time with inventories and this Quest
feels kind of wasteful if we have full
inventory and we can everything I you
can take some more things you can
remember you have a mini bike St mini
bike has a lot of stores yeah I know
it's already
[Applause]
oh get his head the head he's very
strong all right found steel Club
Parts oo I might need those actually but
I don't think I'll get the club that
high level this this go around
I found handgun
Parts yay oh my God this is a great
place yeah this has everything it's like
it's oh it's just hor
ruin oh this time we have to find
supplies
supplies I don't even
remember I think so oh
okay shortterm memory
I'll be Scavenging for
now y this is so good yeah there's a
bunch of glue
here by the way a good idea will be like
give the same um items to one person
because there's no limit but that needs
us to be organized and look at us if you
want to can handle this Stones no sorry
uh the the club
fragment okay and and the stone wood and
everything if you want them oh I
actually put most of them in my car car
it's
nice
oh we can organize better when we do
question so we can optimize the space
yeah food you're starving at a time like
this yummy in this economy
way exactly in this
economy that's why I am
starving yeah I'll more clay
then this seems useful right
now I also am a bit hungry not going to
lie hobo spound good right now I wonder
if there's still food in the in the bike
I have one St oh there is there is sure
that's the end of the quest we just had
to retrieve the supplies mhm oh
okay I fell into the hole oh
yikes can you uh get out okay yeah K
came and is helping me what a legend
okay I got this suppli I totally came
for you yeah I know you were you had
like 0.2 seconds um reaction time immedi
there there's a locker that needs exam I
appreciate it in the roof oh I have one
lock pick uh let me see if I
can you could just Bonk it though oh I
could use a
lot what kind of things do you have in
your
inventory uh I have polymer
cement uh rotten flesh um um Nails
lead
iron uh cloth fragment brass
clay I don't know how to get
viy behind you behind
you
oh oh okay there was a reason why I
asked you those questions thank you I
thought you were in front of me for some
reason okay
[Music]
okay
whoa your gun is
[Music]
loud but so functional has a big
Personality yeah
I don't see the Satchel icon on my map I
think if you're at your quest liit there
is no oh okay oh I was at my quest limit
and I have it no no wait you I'm going
to
die no
mistake dang
it I made a mistake now I have the gold
I thought all the zombies were gone
it's okay we we learn we live and we
learn and we die and we learn I'm lost
holding the bag trying to fight for my
life I'm just going to climb to bi Boo
from the
outside this is more trouble than it's
worth down the
hole the yeah I'm glitched I can't see
what like the distance from
my
supplies I feel like it's due to the
quest limit but I don't know let me
Focus down
no on this
level
see
okay the run back is
crazy did anybody have their Satchel
before on the the main the the the basic
the zero level if yes where was it
mine was in the garbage
shoot in the mine was in the basement
last time maybe I'll check if it was
inam we still have to find it without
the GPS yeah oh gosh I'm going to go on
the
roof I should just follow why do
icraft ah classic there's an awning but
of course though
is are you kidding me I don't know where
mine is either oh there's one
here for anyone if maybe it's
here there one right there no not
mine okay I don't know what mine is
either but it is on this level
heyab I got a lockpick for you oh okay
I'm coming back upstairs where's the
roof I'm Lo yeah I just mcraft block oh
the roof the roof is on the main the
main hall you just have to jump on the
you just have to jump on the like a I
got to deposit my stuff in the meantime
what does exclamation point crossed out
mean it means you reach your daily limit
but that's okay you can still get the
reward that's that's what that means
really it just doesn't progress the uh
apparently up Trader thing I'm oh I
think according to the voices my head
but maybe I got one guy you never know
all right here's one lockpick can you
can you do your check right
now feeding your wrong information it's
me what did I just
destroy I can't find it it's
over oh the lock pick is broken okay
time to smack it all right well at the
end of the day it always goes back to
bonking well it's definitely time to
drop off some things at home yeah the
closed after all they're
closed oh yeah then maybe home oh yeah
they're totally closed
now so we just leave without finding the
I think this is impossible without like
the L it feels
impossible um I found one where I am
right now if you want to check that one
there's one in the garbage shoot that I
found there's one in the behind the next
to the
hole always goes back to Bonk Bonk a't
that right
chat love
bonking punching can solve anything oh
yeah do you have any stone call me oh
did your did yours break no I don't
there was some down in the shelves but I
didn't take it okay have fun bonking I
don't know if it's worth it I the
supplies I don't know if I'll do my best
it's fine we might as well it's worth it
there there's there's quite a bit of
stuff in those chests yeah
who my game lagging oh there's a satchel
over here where is over here I am uh in
the corner of the
pharmacy
room
oh oh my God I'm going insane
I I see it but I can't you can't touch
it are you in the garbage
shoot no it's
like like I tried from every
angle just can't get to it it's
elusive hates me can you break some
walls with your
axe uh that would take like 30 minutes I
think true you could get the St five
5,000 Health oh night time now I can
carry stuff again oh yeah night time
inumber night time no longer encumbered
at night time it's so
good what it's a it's a perk from a book
you have to learn but it's so nice wait
which what perk again it's one of the
Night Stalker magazines it lets you not
be encumbered when at night time oh ni
how do I even get
out oh okay this is this this is mine uh
B did you check the one at the hole the
hole where's the hole okay come with
me I was just where you
were
make strength means shotgun for range oh
one eternity
later actually don't come with me I have
no idea what it
was uh you know the hole in the floor
that that leads us downstairs
yeah are you also still in there yeah
I'm still looking for the s a i don't
know if I'm going to find it though do
you not even know if it's up or down no
but I think it would be here and it's
not showing you the meters either no
yeah
either did you check in the underground
cuz mine was previously hidden quite
well in the underground oh like on a
shelf on top of one but it's okay I
don't need to finish the quest yeah it's
okay I feel like it's going to take too
long we could just go home okay if it's
if it's here though how do you get off
the dang
roof um well we got to get up here the
ladder
just
jump this is good I found a I found nine
sewing kits for you
Kiara wow and Magnum Amo this has been
so lucrative oh yes Magnum I opened it
up and Magnum rounds for bioo yay I'm
very cucumber though okay I'm going to
make you a letter
Sears
go once we get home can you guys anybody
who has glue and Claw fragments
and SE KS and duct tape and armor parts
all of those into the for chest I'll get
cooking thank you you're welcome okay
there was one
here nope thank you it's okay we can
just go home here's your Magnum rounds
get out of here oh I'll see you at the
house I'll get to you there yeah I'm
going to go there too now time to bring
all
this okay
oh people my GPS
GPS I'll go the right way for sure I can
make it I have handun Parts du handun
parts I'll meet you outside GG's working
hard on reinforcing the old
base I'm making a mo and a zombie just
came down here but there's no spikes
down here yet oh boy make sure to only
make one row of spikes down there so we
can pick up the loot yep cuz otherwise
so much loot despawns oh no time okay go
oh this one thank you
yay get them in
trenches yeah dire wolves can jump
though and there are jumpy ones so we
got to prepare for them
too all right
if I go to
the I hope I can meet the snow Trader
today I wonder how many Traders there
are maybe like six let me let me put a
marker there and then maybe I can share
the way point with you that would be
cool if
possible come
on how do I share a way point you might
not be a able to it might be
impossible
somebody who has been investing in
shotgun
crafting yeah can you make one for crony
cuz she been she has been investing a
little bit into strength and she wants a
range weapon this have to be the best
shotgun just anyone you know I can make
one similar to the one I'm using right
now okay it's still pretty
good
awesome so many shotgun users
oh FAA figured it out yesterday you can
share way points is that
so yeah I put a wayo down I don't know
how to share it but I put the Waypoint
down for the snow Traer let me see if I
can find
it hello to share way points you go to
your map and you click on the Waypoint
and then you click on the the icon
that's a bunch of people standing next
to each other which says share
Waypoint oh smart funo with the Strat
thanks comes back shares knowledge
doesn't explain okay I think I shared it
doesn't elaborate shared marker books
with you oh
nice oh we're in the tunnels yeah I know
it's our garage I parked it in the
garage oh good nice won't get bird poop
on
it yeah that's never
fun hard to clean off the windshield
okay what a lovely home we've made
here I love my
home it's a solid
home it's homey
yeah oh God I'm in the tunnels
too
hey welcome to the heck no thank
you dump my loot Co in here I got some
things you will like I got to make more
forg
steel steel Club parts that's big I'm
going to need those later I'll put them
in
here okay I just need three more handgun
parts and I can make an SMG
[Music]
o I'm going to take uh some of this
forged steel if you guys don't mind may
I take 30 forged
steel okay thank you I'll make it up to
you guys I'll keep cooking more
Steel on math is hard for
me there we
go I can H you
guys 10 hobo
stews wow that's a whole lot of hob
what what what what do you think they
made what do you think
that what of the nutritional facts of
that hobo St curious uh I'm I'm very
particular about my diet could you like
tell me exactly is it U ethically it's
very nutritionally balanced oh okay yes
no
questions only anwers thank
you okay
yay I'm
home
y duct
tape oh G did you see the wonderful
interior
design vaguely did you do something new
to
it
yeah I guess I didn't look hard enough
what you add so many Sprints it has we
have wooden wooden walls now very pretty
why would you do that I want it to be
Cottage core that don't laugh me Cottage
boore why you such a hater we are out
here working the entire day we come home
call for man yeah I'm working very hard
too in the mine where where where I
don't see it I don't I don't see
anything we're not staying at that at
home oh oh I have to be so far away from
my family to work in the in here okay
okay back we never see him
nowadays I can make her such a better
one if I have a few more shotgun
parts thought you were here then how
could you say you m messed up sorry I
just like feeling like I'm there cuz I
miss
everyone a a that's sweet we miss you
too
too you should come into this hole with
me I'm good okay don't worry I'll on
that one really interested in that oh
there's arrows in my chest if you want
some oh thank you it did everybody drop
off their glue and stuff and cloth will
I should I put it in the next to the
forge Kiara Forge chest yeah okay thank
you anybody have wood oh yeah I've
always got wood I do
never morning night so
laggy submit I will drop off what I have
uh thank you the garage I got four glue
that's got to be worth
something glue that is worth something
yeah all right I'm going to try and find
a way I have machine gun parts I don't
know if you use that if someone used
that
uh I do I don't know if I still need
some but yeah oh actually I might need
it okay I'll bring it to you might
actually use this my craf that could be
helpful machine gun here behind
you
um
what if you if you get a new weapon can
I have your hand me down yeah okay oh
okay if you're GNA take Kiara's hand me
down then I'll give my hand me down to
crony
yeah that's she doesn't have okay yeah
yes yeah I'm fine with EA cool where's
the croner just want to shoot does
anyone need steel Club Parts steel I'm
going to need them I think so probably
put them in the box over there I'll put
them in the
box which BS what a
sec yo okay I'm going to start cooking
soon I'm already cooking constantly why
is the door locked yeah what is the door
locked crap crap crap more
more I feel like even this triple mod
that's crazy oh someone's making a rifle
in here what is
this somebody cooking a
gun yummy what what kind of rifle is
that it's a shotgun it's a pump action
shotgun
oh
pretty oh
[Music]
enemies okay scamer in the
house oh that's no good I want to shoot
her but I don't want to shoot you girls
good job how'd she get in here what is
that I may have left the door
open Well it can't be we're welcoming
visitors
generally uh when is the for coming day
35 10 p.m. 35 10 p.m. okay uh see a lot
of time then well the lights really
turned off all right uh cron here's some
ammo hold
up I can make
more the other one I can get you more
no that should help I have
plenty I don't know why I separated it
like that that was
weirdo all right new gun needs about
four minutes to
cook so excited is that the best one you
can make or so no uh there's one level
higher I
believe what is the food chest I have
three points of there is any where it is
it's in the
middle I think by the Yeah the
fire oh natural healing might be good
but Olympic champion actually I don't
think I want this club after all
clage
the uh what did it go uhoh where the
heck did it go I just need one more
point to be an Olympic champion anyone
still have armor crafting
parts let's see I wonder not on me
[Music]
currently maybe we can search the
Traders tomorrow
see if we can find some
yeah I'll still look for more shotgun
parts see if I can make the twins a
strong shotgun
too so I'll look around
tomorrow oh actually it's about to be
the next day
convenient p
what level are your feet and
hands probably not all good yeah I think
yeah I want them to run around with a
shotgun it could be
hilarious I am worried about getting
shot by those
too oh well gra armor oh
okay four
you should go elsewhere Springs need to
be in
here
sandals let her
cook just a bit
longer also I also have primitive armor
by the way my my Ranger stuff died it's
gone it's done
for okay um wonder if I can repair it
here want to make do I really get elor
parts from these things too I can but
what do I I think I need a kit repair
kit a ranger
outfit what do I need tell me what I
need level one is really unnecessary I'm
just going to get rid of
these yeah the rate is day 35
yes I wonder if the pig respawned
you want to go fight him I'm G to go
fight him cool go punch him FST them
fist them real good I will
yeah leave it to F to fist the pig we
really have enough meat though what we
need is I'll get grass from that yeah I
need food so I'm going to take some of
that
oh diet yeah I don't know how to get
seeds
there's so many zombies at our old house
oh yeah I'm not equipped to to protect
myself into the did you
get into the this
rations oo fall fall into the
modat yeah shouldn't they be hitting
those spikes
though we have a lot of broken
spikes haven't haven't repaired
yet I
see that's right I can make cornbread
too
SC I'm scrapping the whole armor chest
pretty much because all of those armor
parts are lowlevel and they and they
give me armor parts back when I scrap
oh yeah I think that's better use for
now no
Pig oh yeah maybe you got sick of your
[\h__\h] he's done with you yeah I guess so
he's had
it just going to be gr wonder if we can
make stronger tools as
well my pump shotguns done
yipp have fun with it I'm
excited oh three mods I can load three
mods into it
nice see what we
got some more worth repairing any
recommended not these
right it's good to clean up I think and
then I'll just make everyone The Meta
cuz they probably don't know what they
want either
M ask nice it's
okay
mistake I think that's
it
okay I need to read one
okay let's start
with tell me please what up the what
armor parts you have currently I mean
what's what's your armor on what level
my armor is pretty random right now I
have an Assassin outfit level three mhm
I have preacher gloves level three and I
have Commando boots level three
mhm and the nerd goggles of two two okay
maybe a hat for you is most important
right now I
think if I could get uh something like a
ranger outfit would be nice if you want
Ranger outfit I think I think it's
better for me I'm not sure because I
used the bow but I don't know I'm not an
expert hey Kara make me something cool
too please I'll pay you back I just need
more armor parts see how far we get with
this well armor you can you can take
care of Mor first because I am more like
a support no no no no no you you need
armor more than I do trust me and that's
not that I'm not trying to be mean but
Callie what uh then tell me what are
what are your punch what's what's your
stuff right now what level uh I'm I'm
using primitive because the Ranger stuff
that I had broke oh no yeah what level
are they there's a lot of armor in the
armor thing oh
yeah no I took it all and I scrap oh oh
because it's all useless it was all like
level one and they give me armor parts
which I can make to make more armor
crafting kits uh
specifico I wonder what would be PR easy
to make some tanky know Rangers fine too
I think ranger set yeah are you sure I
wonder what would be good for shotgun
what do you guys
think I'll let you
know let you know biker
biker that'd be pretty cool ask for the
Met set I I put a biker armor in the
armor o biker armor right so if you want
a biker outfit there's one in there heck
yeah I mean I fit the bill I've got a
spiked bat and a shotgun but it's just
level one I'd better make you a better
biker outfit and scrap this one yeah I
want to be a biker Bad to the
Bone yeah Bad to the Bone thank you
kiraa
wa in take your time though I'm just
biking around I don't think I can make
it a max level one but maybe four five
level four five is good that's perfectly
fine SI
wheelie sure am a
biker I need to make a
motorcycle what you oh well mini bike is
mini bike not good enough for you no
it's perfect I just I'm excited about
your motorcycle possibilities too yeah I
can already make one but I feel like
it's kind of a waste with my resources
right now understandable we need more
resources maybe in season two bikes and
cars we can become a real biker gang
civilization
y
yay okay let's start with Callie's set
up uh I'm getting food just in case we
need extra food I never have enough food
keep up the good
work the tricks I can't make the
wheel maybe I'm not so high Ranger
outfits are handguns and
rifles that hand guns and rifles never
mind
um
Lea what's best source of
Lea Boors and stuff pigs I wonder oh I
can probably scrap maybe the pigs the
little ones might have respawned o mhm
they be scrapping couches too someone
made of Lea yeah
couches leather couches give leather the
Harrison nearby have fancy leather
couches
you can scrap our neighbors are not
using their couch anymore
yeah uh K how many
um um vehicle Adventures do you
need uh 23 23 okay I'll buy this one no
no everyone counts every single one he
really wants to kill those BS eh oh
armor armor part we need that right then
I'll buy
that here's your pay a leather let me
check you know I want I'm going to the
trit there as well and see what I can
find I need see any leather I do see
glue and sewing kit do you want me to
buy that too yeah yeah the more
Mar we happy in my backpack okay get oh
Springs you need Springs oh Springs are
always good we have a lot of we have a
ton of Springs oh we have a ton shotgun
parts you need that to
ear well I'll be dipped shotgun parts
yeah I was about to buy I'm right behind
you oh oh you take it then I was going
to grab them oh let me just buy this and
then put them somewhere you can never
get them I still owe B boo 400
bucks or handun parts or handun parts
need two more
house got
you a g you at the old house right now
yeah can you check if there's any
leather anywhere okay thank
[Music]
you oh
oh I already know how to I already have
a metal chain mean could still learn it
though
ooh was a big boom
outside
ow let walk into
them have L much stuff there's a can of
salmon in here for the fish tacos fish
tacos fish tacos nice
yummy love tacos there is one
leather oh wow let's take it
Crucible is so expensive oh my gosh GL
though we already got it y yeah zombies
is mini horde by the way outside mini
horde oh
yike that probably it how much more can
I get oh maybe not that
much stup
magazine nice may I don't need mini hord
outside the house don't forget repair
kids might need some help end up
stranded or have your gun I'm very far
away I got to go meet Trader Hugh now I
think we all should be able to do that
Quest if I'm able to do
it just on your own
time oh I have 76 our doors though oh
I'm calming oh that's
bad our poor
door now it up yes how much money do you
have uh
1,500 can you um buy the vehicle
magazine that he has for yes of course
we're so close to getting a car I have
one vehicle magazine what if people goes
to a bank and lock pick we can get 10 to
15K oh I I need long P though cuz I'm
like totally out some Traders are
selling them you welome I've never seen
an ATM in this game before why are we
Whispering we're not really Rob
sometimes in the grocery stores I
think I
think I've seen
some rob a
bank nice I still have 10,000 on me well
that's a lot of money you've been money
right now no need any
okay I think hord is
over okay how successfully
defended wow when we all go away
to good job thank
you are we going to raid this shamway
building maybe that's the final mission
that we
do the shamway
factory yeah it's really high level huh
yeah looks imposs possible which is why
it would be a perfect final
mission for the season probably lots of
food in there oh yeah all the
yums I mean we can try if you want to we
have to know what it's made out of we
just see like they're just churning
zombies through a wood chiffer in
there I hope not I got to know the
answer to the mystery
I need to go to the second Traer oh my
God so far
away yeah they do be spread far apart
you mean Trader Jen yeah oh come with me
I I can pick you up on my bik oh okay uh
you're still at direct I'll come over to
you yes I'm the
W you get a taste mini
bike wait am I going the right way wait
ibly
[Music]
not does it matter when sh I still don't
know the
directions okay it's difficult I always
use the checkpoints because I get lost
all the
time do we
have Jen also has shotg a little bit oh
she does heck yeah yeah I'm going to go
pick those up I need some money though
I'll grab them to thank you for letting
know I'll go grab them I can buy them I
have I have quite a bit of money really
now I owe now I owe you money and bi boo
money oh there you are yeah get on baby
let's go give me a
ride lady okay I'll hit the house
first oh can you get on I'm
trying this say repair or
honk oh okay unlock it for you
then there he go now you can get in I
think are are I think I clo fuel on are
we who CL someone someone put cloth in
the fuel so I'm taking it out thank
you our precious
resource burn that save the
cloth it's okay cloth isn't my most
needed resource right now but
before you know it we will run out of
it oh Jen just said thank you so much so
kindly we should protect her she so nice
she's nice I like Honestly though I I
the traitors have so much space like
such a
big base it's insane see yeah should
give us that base we should take it over
actually yeah just steal it and we
should like yeah yeah I mean we like
there's so many of us it's just Traer in
each of those we can you think anyone's
try to do that
before yeah yeah yeah are they
Invincible yes they are you cannot kill
them it should it would be really fun
like if they allowed that but it's
really really difficult what if she has
like insane def what if you kill all the
Traders and it's
over yeah or what if you kill one Trader
and then the other Traders are like I I
won't sell to you anymore and then you
have to do a long line of quests to
explain that there was a mistake and
that you
overtaken by G was it a mistake though
was it actually no they don't have to
know that they don't have to know
it no it was not a
mistake of course not we shouldn't kill
Jen though we should kill the guy with a
Mach with the car parts then we can have
a
car I wonder how how we can make
lockpicks I wonder if there's a
way there probably is a
way cuz then we can if somebody could
make a ton then be go rob a bank
and it would be
sick I'm I'm uh I'm trying to put more
skill points into the loot
stuff so every time I get like PR
percentage
more oh you can do
[Music]
it I see this shackle yeah that's
better your Uber is doing her best let
me see let me see the rest please give
me good rating I give I give you the
best the best rate I would hope
so ah yeah you have to have the skill
see you great rate rate me on your phone
before you leave the car five star okay
okay now I feel now I feel treated
though so I'm not going to do that
anymore well then I
shall I shall crash you into this m
my bike is too
good don't do
it
well
you I lock I am aimless what are you
doing hello I'm going to the Traders oh
okay thank you for the ride though very
kind of you you're
welcome one star anyway good man I heard
that
hello beautiful
lady need
[Music]
glue B what what why did you want
coal oh I wanted to make some good water
but I found it but uh don't don't use
coal don't use coal or cloth for fuel by
the way cuz I found them in there do you
have a good use for
coal I think coal is for the good water
that I was making in bulk and I think
you make you can help me make bullets I
think it's one of the components for
bullets like gunpowder or something like
that I'm not sure okay cuz it's
gunpowder making a okay but yeah don't
use it as fuel mhm
got you
understood what do we have anything
good
perhaps okay no glue no wow have you got
anything for me
lady no
NOP no no no really
nothing only have two lock picks so far
yeah I don't know how to craft
them I want to rob a
bank I know wouldn't that be cool yeah
if only it were that
simple where's my other quest suppos to
go
to I
guess have I not seen Bob yet thought I
did
the only one you haven't met is
hug
[Music]
h of course
of is there a place you want to go to
next otherwise I'm going to Bob yeah I
come to you okay okay I'm putting two
vehicle adventures and uh shotgun
Messiah into the heck yeah books box be
taking the shotgun one
and then shotgun parts as well let's
go does anybody I put them before you on
the
floor what what are you going to do next
somebody else read them oh I'm very I'm
feeling a little bit aimless right now I
just went and bought I got a bunch of
seing kid and glue but you want to try
to gather
leather okay killing animals animals I
guess and then you need to use like I
think theat B knife currently there's
you have knife no but I saw some in the
chest okay I think that's you have to
use it and then you got to maybe find
lever couches and stuff but I think just
going for Animals is faster okay better
okay I can do that I realize I have
absolutely no lever and without Le I
can't make good armor let me see
chy there's a lot cooking in here okay
I'll I'll do that thank you that will be
[Music]
helpful perfect yeah animals faster
right they do give quite a bit maybe try
close by to our new house there's the
the bores
and bores and corn place oh right yeah
there's a lot of bors in there what was
that again K there's 77 leather in this
crate oh okay but that's still probably
not quite enough a bit more would be
good can you mark where the the your
favorite places the the bors the bors
it's literally just north of the new
house you'll see it has a big
farm see if you scrap office chairs also
you can get leather
see sorry Kar but your office chair has
got to go oh yeah no good very good a
chair I got Traer and then I'm
putting armor I'm going to the new Traer
no no oh
cool I want to meet him
too for office chairs I'm putting armor
pots into the armor chest okay thank
seven and glue and okay okay
nice so bad you can't make leather from
zombies why would we be able to make
that
huh leather out of hum they they
have yeah that's not a bad idea so you
can make leather out of humans I guess
probably Le that is
true huh it's technically a thing huh
cool I
mean gross going turn on the
radio driving for the the radio
show ah no I fell into the hole are you
back in the tunnels
CeCe no I'm I'm where people fell
earlier the most
she's going to get a lot of lawsuits
from all the holes she's digging where
we're dying
falling I didn't put any spikes in that
one so it's okay it's not so bad
[Music]
yeah could be worse yes could be spikes
today make sure that you SC leave and
they stay still there do bears have
leather do you think I
think just got to use the bone knife oh
my gosh this place to stay there
Bob first time to
me what's wrong with you is there lag B
is very oh I'm falling the
ground that was scary I just melted into
the floor as everyone does when there's
a bit of lag
I got so much glue for
you for L
but
nothing I got motorcycle parts bundle
yeah why not
oh people you're here hello
up how are you doing a he gave me
vehicleent that is I'm shopping a bear
already had there's a bear
anyway God bears are so
scary well if scary why hug
sheet no that's it's just not true I
don't know who decid evil why
[Music]
friend why did they ever make teddy
bears bears have always been frightening
ter terrifying
creatures of Destruction and hunger
they've always been so cute looking and
you want to H
cat you hug them aren't you very durable
you can hug them is this a baby bear or
something cuz I think I once it oh did
you did you punch the bear
you killed the
baby cool oh these must be small Bears
right oh know it was a
child you killed a child the child two
child Bears who you killed two child
Bears of them knuckles kill more kill
more bigger oh you're killing the
there's no way that's the same bear I
fought
before oh he's got good stuff the Boris
not respawn there's no Boris here guys
yeah maybe they
don't is there something specific you
want to do cuz I'm probably going to
just go back yeah wait sorry puppy
dog wa you kill a
dog do you want to do this my quest
nearby my
good okay
it's h South South East Southwest of it
yeah yeah yeah I can't afford anything
but I'm
looking yeah this Trader has great stuff
I am the best Uber right now yeah you
are you change your opinion quickly
about
me it never
changed
yes people I saw you going
down unlimited shotgun
[Laughter]
parts try harder gig why are you trying
to steal her from me what's going on huh
why does no one like
digging it's really
fulfilling K while you're at it maybe
make some like Towers like platforms for
shooting every
direction you think I can do it I've got
a particular problem place can you help
me out you can always quit a job too par
I'd go down in a blaze of glory but I
feel bad every time for killing the the
animal
yeah I can solo this Quest okay it's
okay they they had a really bad life
they didn't like their mom bear they
were like oh man she never lets me play
my video games
so to kill the mom bear
yesterday
that's life that's messed up do you guys
have an idea where there might be a
different Farm does anyone know have one
think I'll die what if I just lead them
all
out there's bears in the tundra you can
find oh okay was this the
prison planning to die huh
well might as well just give a shot
right
yay those flying where could there be le
hello this is also a satchel class by oh
okay okay keep my eyes
open do what the cowards way
oh oh that's a lot of hissing oh
hello o weapon shops are good
all of these shops seem hey this really
this is kind of awesome wow I can make
my SMG now this gun's really
good okay we're going to the tundra and
going to try to kill some
bear do they give that have you tried
yeah they do okay okay I don't know how
much you give I have 29 right now that
doesn't seem like that
much I feel like sofas might get more
leather than bears killing a bear what
if we find what if we find like an
office
building yeah leather SAS tons of fun
zomes the shotgun
range yeah we were looking for leather
for kiar okay coward is okay I found one
nice I'm the only one in here so it's
fine to be a
coward oh no is it a kitty I can't fight
the
I found you is it a big
cat where's the rest of I am alone
so it's okay cowardice maybe somewhere
downstairs again where's the rest of
the this gun
rules oh yeah there's some people
here we killed a bunny success I hope a
bunny has leather I'm not
sure watch out behind
[Music]
you more
trash I need to find my my bag yeah me
too just casually solo leveling wor me
oh this place is Way Big I oh there's a
lot watch out there's the rest of the
place oh you over there oh
no the
Blockbuster get some head
shot again I heard
about reload reload oh he woke up again
ah
yay
baby door combat's my favorite
combat oh my God oh my God be
careful I should have
[Music]
reloaded at least there's no vomit
zombies oh my God disgusting oh my God
how many lives do these have yeah it's
very strong they keep on getting back up
again Phoenix like
qualities in
here hello
hello it will not die
no nice nice
nice let's go maybe in the
gun yeah this place is Big I'll Lo it at
the
end oh military chest
ooh hunting knife that's maybe a better
B
KN hey was someone making a
machete oh I already made one you made
one okay so you don't well I'll still
keep the parts just in case you want to
upgrade it yeah yeah
yeah uie
do that was frightening I can't believe
I got out of that
oh oh I think I found a better wrench
for
you for me yeah it's a ratet I think
it's like the
next high
here I'll be careful over there what
what what's going on cie there's a bear
trying to this the biggest bear I've
seen in my life trying to enter the
shotgun R and he can't get through the
door you done stay safe Kelly I can kill
him right kill him kill it yeah there a
lot of Lea right there that's probably
the grandpa of of the Bears that oh you
already did the spa has been
killing the entire family has been wiped
out this gun is insane let me see if I
can make one of these for Fu Moko bet
that help me a lot yay behind you behind
you
what weapons are fuok using shotguns I
believe oh
okay
out he wasn't a part of the mission
though he just heard the
commotion out out out out maybe all the
enemies are dead now no they're
still a
guy I got
okay now it's over good job y now we
need to find our loot scel did you guys
find I haven't got my Satchel yet oh
Kara here take this it might be it's
probably better I'm blind oh I also have
something for you I think oh yeah
getting all the leather for Kiara this
oh thank
you cuz it says 9 mm I'm guessing that's
good for you here take this
tool oh yeah does it oh ratchet I'm
coming back doesn't work the same
way there must be a place I haven't gone
into I have too much stuff so yeah I
wasn't I wasn't going to be questing
anyway but yeah I'll be driving back
what is a robotic sled I found a shotgun
choke mod I don't know if you need oh
that yeah maybe if you could grab that
for me I'll definitely take a look at it
okay oh I I literally found a turret I
think this is oh nice I don't know a
whole turret oh it's a melee turret it's
a punching
wow wow tier four Quest nice yeah I'm on
a tier four Quest right now actually
matter fact I found a
turret I might need some help
here oh what do you need help with
there's still a
important
CH this gun makes it easier be cracked
open oh oh my God
guys I do smash your
skull
oh any dudes up here oh
you oh yes I almost missed that
Bo there's got to be something I
need got to be something good maybe a
whole
helicopter or a whole
car how's the orange mole doing is she
having a good time jigging orange mole
how are you
doing oh
G I'm I'm knocking down trees now oh
thank you G orange
orange I have some stuff for you
yay if you could bring a delivery of
food and repair
kit
blushing Bing my
eyelashes yeah I'm walking very slowly
to
you oh I see you does that
hurt can you take this tape yikes take
this I'll take it
thank you take this my God we digging um
take this
ooh wait what else do you want a repair
kid take
this thank you why don't you take this
too oh my God a blueberry
pie ooh some
chili um take
these oh anything else you want do you
want some
testosterone yeah yeah yeah some
testosterone I'll extra Harvest it from
there what did you do this maybe the
poor
Bears thank
you do you want to look at my what I've
done so far yeah give me the T okay so I
have blid Spikes all outside and I'm
planning to make them three tall but
they're all around now uh-huh so don't
fall in there's a dog yeah don't fall in
all right I'm going to die and then what
I've been working on for the past
hourish is I finally made the mode on
the back side and it's too wide and very
deep uh do you see it I'm hold on I'm
going to come over I'm really slow
oh I'll just take my bike over okay okay
okay I took the rest
barely you see it down there oh
yeah it goes all the way around ow and
then there's a little entrance you can
walk into the house here but you'll
probably die to the other spikes I'll
get rid of them actually these are
useless where is the exit you have been
busy this is impressive work thank you
and now problem I S I'll be digging much
better it's freaking go good Lu thank
you thank you me
too that was awesome good loot though
Harden chest what I want to get more
wood now this item needs repair ah hey
uh would anyone with a lockpick love to
come get a ton of really amazing loot at
the shotgun Messiah uh you are going to
need to smack it that's what we did I I
can't wait at the shotgun
Messiah what I'm at a different shotgun
Messiah yeah no we we we just did a tier
four class and we had to smack that
chest so you're going to have to smack
that chest okay are lockpicks not
allowed oh it's allowed ah but we don't
have any I see not I can find my S have
you find yours all you haven't found it
yet did you check your
radar uhoh need some antibiotics either
there should be a there should be a
satchel
icon oh my god there a mannequin my
armor is and if there's an arrow down or
up then that means you have to go up or
down
yeah we're going to be here a
while I can't see the rider that you're
talking about uh do you have a bag icon
anywhere like if you look around there
oh yeah I see it now yeah go close to it
yeah yeah yeah okay okay go give me just
cool and on the top right of your screen
there should be a meter thing going up
and down depending on if you're getting
closer or further all right I see it now
okay oh it was so close when I was
like yeah I couldn't see it it was sorry
it was more I
mean I know this chest is going to be
worth it guys do you know the
exit uh yeah I can't find it there
usually good stuff in there maybe that
way yeah this
way little Brute Force should be here oh
I found it yay
oh do you guys need a back shot or can I
leave here I don't think anybody's using
that
ammo okay leave
here I'm going to go to the and then go
home yeah I'm waiting for you I'm coming
out I'm looking for the
exit can't take this stuff at least I
got the lever I've got a bunch of stuff
I'm going to drop off at home hey Kiara
are you able to make lockpicks by
chance
uh not better than anybody else I think
ah yeah I have I don't have it unlocked
so I cannot make them
sadly uh yes oh it is at the workbench
Ben actually I feel like I've seen it
some lockpicks in our chest too there's
like two I
think are you good I am looking for a
way to go out I can't find you have to
go through the the weapon shop uh cuz we
went oh I found it I found it yeah 25%
we're practically halfway there
25% is not halfway there here we go I'm
finally Out Imagine A Bear
shows there the into the bike oh back
back back back oh there you are let's go
home about to the quest Bob let's go
yeah
hello
welcome almost end of day
32 you're getting closer ladies we are
I'll turn in my quest tomorrow she be
fine H CeCe I might have a hand me down
if you're
[Music]
still H what
happened I I just fell into a canyon
with my wife she could fly in this game
she's so used to it you could
not I going to say uh if you're still
interested in using m guns I have a hand
me
down I think try to break in yes oh
sorry I yeah yes please I am currently
looking for leather and I will maybe you
can put it are you at the house uh no
not right now but you'll get it by
the for sure okay okay nice thank you I
just found a thingy so I Reddit so
that's really
nice bu my hammer got faster
[Music]
he goes how do you heal concussion uh
painkillers
okay which is not how it works in real
life
but okay I guess just put that on there
sure it'll
work yeah know this gun is super
op very exciting
go fory like you found something
cool I want to make one for other
people
hello I can buy a cash
register you can buy a
[Laughter]
don't I don't maybe I can own a little
shop I'm Bing here I have the trade
routes Quest yippe
yay but not today I think not today Q
has unlimited shotgun parts I wonder if
he has other unlimited uh parts for
weapons and
such you has unlimited shotgun parts wow
that's op unlimited
baby so I can make more of these really
powerful
guns and hand them off to to some of the
others
hi hello
here how's your thr are you okay I'm
doing my
best oh
no don't don't force your voice too much
yeah you can dig all the way over here
connect it do you see it yeah yeah yeah
yeah let's go on the other side and then
we can meet G I'm scared it's okay
please don't reset the chest just like
that okay if I use my b
I will dig and meet you
guys
okay my back to do it yeah are we still
defending at the old house you won't
okay yeah it's still think about
myle actually I would like I would like
to make a vault can we maybe go to the
new wait what what's the tunnel for the
new house
for it's the garage ah like secret
secret put your car in
there the bat's doing it faster classing
we're not the spikes are oh
no yeah the spikes are little
dangerous
yeah we're already halfway
dead and we did hit this SP
once oh
maybe in time to hit Trader and get that
M oh my
God am I going the right way
now crony and I have been hitting a
hardened chest for 5
minutes me too I'm hitting it with my
back worth it this better be worth it
it'll be so worth it one no TI four
quests are fun some of the some of these
locations are good
we don't have much food dangerous I'm
dangerous too everywhere's dangerous
stuck Escape doesn't work I'll out got a
treasure map and five lock picks this
was definitely worth
it
[Music]
yay you can also I'm trying okay come
here you see these spikes over here oh
you're still in the hole Yeah
it's working as intended
yeah
okay and then wow do you see all the
spikes
outside yeah it was
impressive these spikes I'm trying to
make them three tall so if you can put
these spikes and then make them like
this three tall all the way around
here's all the spikes I have on me I
have to restart my game okay okay
okay M rifle part let's go in the house
and grab some food first though before
we die someone's going to need
that if anyone
has Springs I just need a few more to
craft my SMG are we out of Springs I
thought we had quite a few quite a
lot did you check in all the typical
chests H I'm looking right now it's not
in the Forge one I think there might be
in the other like random looking
chests I I I saw like 50 or so I know
someone else was using Springs too
though so they might have used it yeah
wait oh Springs I didn't oh never mind
in the vehicle chest I found
[Applause]
itg there is a safe
here oh my gosh it takes 30 minutes to
make an SMG yeah I'm not surprised oh we
have time we have time we have
time 30 minutes making a big Supply
team I've broken my lock
pick oh shoot let's do that one coming
back
take your time I'm trying to find
something to drink I think I can get
from oh I have I have Waters with me oh
thank you I'll get some of your
water I'm almost back someone else can
use this baseball
bat this is a good for be way better
really
okay people can you uh make ammo I feel
like the time it's getting closer and we
will need ammo of all kinds probably I
will start to work on ammo we do need
everything no what's this Quest on the
side
maybe like
that
see yeah how do we get it we can't quite
make it stuck here back you can take
these building blocks and you can stack
them on each other and you can pick them
up too again where's my bike building
blocks there is a lot of
sh in the yeah you'll be tall enough to
put them on top I'm pretty sure okay
thank
you thank you for help me I don't know I
don't think did
you check around the corner very CU I
can't even run anymore Dude Where's My
Car hey you guys took the same Mission I
just did I think
he took my bike not to close I know I
haven't took your bike I can't no he
took it he took it oh he took your bike
no oh yeah bio just took it what uh the
same Quest that I just did that I just
soloed yeah by the way finding a moment
to mention that I soloed that
Quest this is
sick I found we found Silver Nugget we
actually found this was actually worth
it it it took 10 minutes but I almost
died though I found some we found some
armor parts more anybody wants to go
with me to dig up treasure the treasure
might have money and uh I will dig with
you yay GG want to dig GG okay we can
bring full Moco too yeah
g I'll come dig too I like to dig I'm
cuc can you pick us up yeah I'll pick
you up I mean I might buy the house
ofina it's okay don't worry about it
kill a massive evil bear true them
awesome can you give me some water ah
yeah of course he's
not there you go water we can instead we
can just like walk around in the me and
loot something around what level is your
shotgun
um the one I have now two yeah two okay
okay is it double barrel no it's a it's
a pump action The Flash hel you can give
that one to someone though yeah I put I
put another double barrel shotgun in the
chest so someone can use that
cool there are lots of dire wolves just
running around in the snow by the way so
just be careful oh my
God specific at night I
think I need to put some more on that
corner go
down right there yeah it's
probably okay I'm ready B boo whenever
you are okay con's using a shotgun right
yeah con is yeah all right uh
there is a really good shotgun
in corner time to book
it that's a big
boy where are we
Whispering like the zombies can hear
okay the Z not here no they don't have
ear holes
for us at hes yeah with my shotgun I'll
gladly
oblig
absolutely right this
way oh I'm not let's continue going
around the
way the is
the this
Troublesome also I got a bunch of
leather I'm going to put in the thingy
what are you trying to make with the
leather
Kiara I think they moved to do Quest or
something okay oh yeah
just need to drop some things off real
quick we'll be
fine we'll be F my eyes have't
adjusted that's looking good to
I'm c zombies are pretty bra a place
like
that oh yeah oh do you want to do this
tier four clear quest to be
boo yes let's just do that real I'll do
it just really quick you guys are close
to it okay uh Let's do let's do the
treasure first so that way we'll give
Callie some
time yeah okay sounds good I'll make my
way over there in a sec then we'll dig
your
[Music]
treasure oh oh
B you want to get
it I'm sorry
Pigg what did you do to the Pig come on
drive by drive by oh no Are we almost
there we're almost there okay I thought
we got stuck in the in the spikes
ourselves okay wow it's okay so stand
stand right here mhm and
then this is the priv oh no
yeah we in G G can you come here where
are you where we are on the
map I don't know if I'll make it you you
might make it this might take us a while
digging for an hour what are you digging
for
Treasure wait can you hand me the map oh
I can't uh I can't you already started
yeah
it's I have a I have a thing a mod I
think it makes treasure
smaller oh I think I have a treasure mod
do you have it too yeah it's that wide
even with the mod yeah I have I have the
treasure Hunters mod um G if you go to
the new house there are mini bikes there
that you can use to drive to
us right the mini bikes yeah if you if
you go to if you walk to the new house
there are mini there's a mini bike at
the new house which you can use to drive
here can I dual moded is it dual
moded um I I don't know I don't
remember feel like I shouldn't I don't
want to leave the puppies at the house
alone with all these spikes there
there's also there's also multiple bikes
so you guys can both take bicycles if
you prefer okay there's a lot of bikes
at the new
house
reg here are some more spikes I'll will
get a bike for us
[Music]
I still need to turn in this Quest is
that true that doesn't make sense I
don't
need do you think it's better to dig
down maybe I don't know maybe maybe we
can get
lucky wait is that stone that's Stone
accident I shouldn't take that much
that's so
fair Corners are kind of funny huh
May I'll start from direct
midle we should have brought some juice
to
drink digging easier oh oh digging from
the middle actually helps okay that's
wait does it I think it doesn't middle
of the
radius uh do we need do we need bones
for anything Mountain
yes yes like okay oh yeah making glue
for examp probably have a lot but have a
lot they are useful they are super
[Music]
useful ow
you know where to run oh I'm trapped in
the hole it's okay I got it I got it you
got it
yeah
[Music]
IR IR
I could have sworn you had regular
[Music]
iron I'll cook it why does that scary s
it is night time please don't give me
the PO things always get scary at night
time I have to see if you get the poo
poos thank you I'm gambling
we know where it's going oh oh I found
an ATM what did she say we can do with
an ATM oh ATM yeah didn't Kiara say
something about an
ATM I don't know the bank or an ATM I
think she you lock pick it steal the
money let me
see a little break from the
[\h__\h] he where's the iron
yeah for iron make for iron I think we
should eat
T I have this oh it just look like a big
metal it's the circle is getting smaller
so we're doing something
okay let me see what armor they
got ooh scavenger outfit this looks cool
I'm halfway to the house nice wait only
halfway to the
house are you walking yeah I'm on foot
oh
no
okay let's see let's see who's first
they getting to the house or we Finding
the Treasure
yeah got an extra one there yeah oh it's
different armor oh maybe my hat's in
trouble they were really cooking with
this treasure digging mini game huh yeah
really they really made something
here hold on my shoes digging in general
is like the worst what do you
mean what no no what what do you think
about digging huh it's great and what
about earlier when you said you I feel
like that was uh I was just saying I was
just saying no one likes digging with me
I just don't know why oh you took it
personally yeah it was
personal
good what's wrong with digging it's yeah
it's look they like digging
too tired
though is not tiring digging
is down down with the digging
what's wrong with with digging making a
hole it said we're getting closer yet
hold let me check the perim are we
nothing's wrong with digging you should
come and join us we're still in the
center we're still in the center need
more regular iron than I
thought although I think we're getting
close to the ends of the spikes maybe
maybe let's
see there's not going to be zom that can
go through the for these we need steel
though
huh Can you guys still hear me yes yeah
okay my power flickered and my screen
turned
off what
oh
think don't her we're still thirsty and
hungry
Hy hey guys how do you make Forge Steel
it's not iron is it wait hold on F I'm
broken are you broken should I stop
digging no you can keep digging I was
broken I see we need iron we really
don't have iron
huh Rara may I take your
iron think she's in the other car oh
[Laughter]
cute yeah I'm going deep right now I
don't know where I'm going you can mine
it yeah with my great Stone
axe why is there a around in there I
don't know was it always
there maybe it's because it's 3:
a.m I don't want to go to the tunnels
Maybe
poison
okay a rocks at someone's got a rock
somewhere just like a grand pirate
hunting treasure
Adventure I'm so immersed right
now you you still haven't seen the chest
no hey ra quick question hello ra quick
question
may I SM hello Rara may I smelt your
iron into steel cuz you have a bunch of
iron in your chest no no take all of it
thank you I appreciate we out take
yeah we out not good I I still have to
craft so much armor for the other girls
yeah okay well I'll try and focus on
Gathering some
more okay no oh oh she was I will help
you guys dig and then I will so if we M
the bike so they aren't so stuck in that
one the house some iron make some St I
want to make new house for the now no
we're still using that house but a lot
of people are at the new house for
crafting and stuff I see but it's not
that far away righty that's not super
far
away the has the
CR Cru use cruci
like don't Ste can't for it
why in the movies there's always just an
x on the ground and you right there is
it cuz I'm not you have to put the iron
into the smelter okay I got it oh okay
you right on the border
now so where is the
treasure in
please make the
steel Okay add this
place if if you see Rock that's too
that's too low okay yeah sometimes
there's like tunnels of
dirt who's Judy
Witch good Judy witch oh yeah I remember
seeing
that driving by her house oh it's got to
melt first
gotcha okay I understand how it works
now okay we don't want to
be oh gig's almost
here there's a gigantic Mountain
separating us I'm climbing it like a
goat well the trasers have a bunch of
iron
so oh RIS going of weak
huh it's going to rep all
right to
close okay it's a little close a little
this this's
SMG I'm not going to touch it wait is it
done already no it's 6 minutes left okay
I was just checking it said we're
getting close again fa where this way
this
way hold we how are I supposed to get
out of here I think so we'll figure it
out
I'm more excited to think of the zombies
that could get
through what kind of talented zombies
are there out there where are you guys
nope I see the hole never
mind I'll plate it
up St back kittens check out my iron
shovel I want to see Iron shovel my IR
just just watch me D through all of this
can almost one shot this take a
different direction there you go wow
you're so good at
digging yeah yeah I
know wow oh my God wait wait again pick
up go in this way Direction This Way
okay okay okay go in a this way
Direction wow so fast yeah I I think in
in one more I can upgrade my shovel and
I can kill these blocks in one hit
wouldn't that be impressive yeah it
would be really impressive mhm everyone
would want me they'll be like ooh you
can dig a dirt block in one hit blushing
oh wait okay this way
Direction
ow did you get hit
no car extra armor in case what is weak
what
armor the Digger I know I worried about
that
too don't worry I'll dig
up I was going to repair my
bike oh I found
it okay and now now we have to smack it
open woohoo oh boy not my
bike it's not my bike we're still hungry
we're still
thirsty classic
ow did you get
smack somebody's bike got
repaired congratulations to
them does anyone know how to make a bath
baton baton I don't but I have a
baseball bat there's there's baton Parts
in in the in the chest in the crates at
home I highly recommend you make one oh
I can make a normal one too I'm looking
to my friends so I I made this thing a
while ago it's called Uh yay it better
be worth it repuls mod so I'm looking
for a
St St baton I'm pretty sure I saw
something like that in one of the chests
there was really no money in this last
time there was 5K do you want my 10,000
and you can pretend like it was okay no
I got there was a lot of app in here so
that's good nice there's my
bike let's see how I
oh old cash is Apparently one to one you
sell old cash for the coin yeah I didn't
know that but apparently oh okay never
mind it's okay there's money in
here don't cie dot dot dot me Chad I
know
I got someone's bike got a nice repair I
got ammo
and weapon
parts okay should we go do the tier four
tier four clear okay coming I'm coming
I'm almost
there if you come do this tier FL I'll
give you these shotgun parts oh really I
love shotgun parts I'm making shotguns
for everybody
just I need steel so I'm trying to make
I can't help but but see the cie is is
pretty far no I'm pretty close actually
I see sow I see I'm on my bike you don't
understand I feel as though you're
moving in the opposite direction wait
what you're not in a snow area no oh all
right go do your quest I thought you
guys were I thought you guys were doing
the quest that I soloed I saw it and it
saido wait dzy wait come back do you
want to do the quest with us
okay I was going to return to my hole
but through here we're forcing you to
get out of the house yeah cck family
activities let me actually get some
rocks
first
hello
hello um I've heard we run out of steel
again yeah I'm cooking some right now
but it's because I'm trying to make a a
shotgun for oh yeah I used thech of Ste
to make a my SMG that's currently
cooking mhm the thing is I need that for
good armor too and now I wonder giggy
yeah are you finished with what you're
doing no I'm still still digging try to
collect more ladies I did you know that
uh when you find an iron or stone on the
Overworld oh yeah there's like a deposit
underneath
yeah there's like a whole iron vein
underneath apparently us yeah I've got
some it get you like 15K of iron do you
want me to get you some iron yes please
Beaver thank you Angel Beaver my wife
punched me I'm bleeding
[Applause]
out can't even tell the stone
apart my life
here take this the beaver time stop
Beaver time don't don't die you can keep
some
Band-Aids I don't want you to die okay
okay you're just you're so strong to
what are you doing let me in h let me in
we're doing a
real it's a quick Quest CR and I found
you now now stay seated 20 leather oh
okay okay that's good
good so keep looking for leather thank
you I put them next to your also there's
like nine weapon parts now in the weapon
box no armor parts armor
parts you're supposed to open at 4:00
a.m. open up Hugh oh my God is it cuz
there a zombie out there's a zombie
outside but I'm scared I want to go in
here without you oh where are you
sorry I was just having a
toilet maybe we should make extra I am
the strongest in the
game I can finally put my stuff
there that's right Lads I am now Olympic
champion level strength you look like a
little girl good work Soldier keep this
up and I'll put in a good word for you
with the D to make it
taller oh on fire
burning my
te my rounds
Pier his voice is so
edgy oh do these valves not do anything
it doesn't turn it
off just her looks oh dear is that the
only one in here you got iron my friend
Maxim
[Music]
SEC wonder if he iron oh a forge usually
they don't sell uh he might be selling
forged iron and forged steel oh yeah
he's got 76 forg
steel maybe I should just spend my money
on that it's so expensive though it's
apparently quite a
waste feel sound it's inside I don't
know what it is worst decision your life
I wouldn't say on the back door back
door oh oh okay I go you want money
another one like a dog oh this way he's
like you're going to do that Quest alone
okay no bi boo still definitely has the
so good with this clear the shotgun
Messiah what you have a quest that's at
the shock of Messiah I didn't notice oh
okay yeah can you wrench this what is
this I think you
can oh my gosh it's filling with water
what bad day please thank
you that's green he's
green you got to watch out for the green
with the
[Music]
puning I have a
question uh how do you improve the level
of a
weapon the level of a weapon you have to
craft a higher level of the weapon you
don't upgrade the weapon you craft it oh
in yeah if you jump across oh my head is
so dazed from that
place see they're on the
ground do you need a med kit I will get
first kit I'm so
sorry I just lead them out here
wait let's go inside do we go to the
water room this I don't know oh I think
we do oh all right uh K where where the
weapon the weapon oh oh Soldier but then
how are you going to get
back maybe it's not an idea we should
have something to drink people there's
zombies oh yes yes okay zomes right here
right here what how like the drink
there's nothing to drink yeah look
right is anyone doing or planning on
doing a quest am I can go for a quest I
have nothing to go I think we're
finished reinforcing everything
now we can split like let's go to VC to
if you want to do quests okay I don't I
don't have any quests but I join a
quest okay okay
put okay I'm I going be wait I'm
dropping you the weapon here okay thank
you you can drop it in the chest fun
though okay okay
thank you also there's no new vehicle
thingy I think in the box and some other
stuff
okay thank you okay I'll be right back
one minute and then we can go take
time I don't to to try to
jump I can supply to to bat if somebody
wants
one did you uh carry anything
interesting that I might need yes H you
can check everything like pretty much
everything on my chest you can take it
anything to should we Quest or should we
try and search for
items someone what okay owie okay good
stuff I can come back and hand you a
bike once I get out of
here I think we do we need a bike I my
is very consistent it'll be so fast
doesn't make a lot of sense bik are
probably r
no yeah let's redeem both
down let's make a there's a lot of
zombies in here yeah this gun makes solo
Quest very possible by the
way I need I wow you took a shot to the
head no problem crazy over there
did you punch me again oh no I didn't I
punch
you you I might die I might die hold
on was that's rude Callie can't be
helped assassin thank you
H we
don't are food not very good a lot time
for Plan
B I'm so sorry oh no no I don't think it
was you I think it was a zombie
you're okay it is like a 50 50% chance
with
you yeah this way boys no not but we're
thirsty they're already on fire they
don't care it must have been really
thirsty Kelly for the bike outfit did
you want a full set or did you only need
specific Parts um I mean full set would
be awesome but if you could only make
one I'd say the main armor
[Music]
B you can you can climb this here and
there's like a next area there's a find
it it's
gigantic yeah maybe go back to where
we're putting down the does the biker
set need a lot of leather Kiara cuz I'll
bring a bunch more leather if you want
it does but oh yeah I mean more is
probably going to help okay I'll pay you
back how do how do you climb it I'm not
very good at
hold W what was it kids
[Music]
nice can you not jump high enough maybe
not I never invested in parkour I make a
block what a shame wait I can't make a
block here here don't
worry how do I put it on the ground
never be a parkour Pro
no don't say that you bet train a lot
actually I'm going to parkour
[Music]
prison you make
that
yay how you climb the Rope okay how
about
this
we do it y you did to chunky to climb
the road oh oh why is the music so Terri
if you guys have any Spar spook please
let let me
know food for Spears oh
oh
spear maybe up
here
helping do you have duct tape do need
that let me
lagging I think I gave it to
kiaha what do you need it for crony
asked for it in sh oh there we are
wonder what she's
making uhoh I'm scared to fight with the
lag I don't want to punch my friends to
death just in case oh wait I already
have
a wow we're still not done I guess not
are you guys still digging oh you're not
digging no that that ship is sailed so
we head back to the new
house so many oh they came in the wall
help I'm
scared let me stand in the doorway and
protect you oh thank you you're so
strong Underground
I know exactly what those fist feel
like that's so many oh my
God yay oh good oh now we're done yay
there's a pig
outside you got out the ladder already
yeah you go on the ladder and then it
sends you right outside so you don't
have to go through that again
oh I'm over here Lads I might die that's
so many
zombies what if I shoot
them I want to check
barel I don't know
[Music]
maybe die
Pig not
wait do you learn handy land G yeah I've
been learning all
the what about armor wait bi boo was
learning armor
yeah oh no you guys left too early
there's a random there's a loot
room give me I might need some
help
okay that means there's loot right or is
there just a chest that we need to h no
there's a lot of Loot and I do not have
a lot of room something to loot the cars
uh you mentioned something ah oh
yes yes yes also by the way you're
constantly crouching press
Ctrl that you're walking everywhere
slowly cuz you're
crouching how do we get you how do we
get to you go yeah down here down here
there we
go okay there you wow there a lot of
stuff yeah thank you I got loot stuff
around have fun oh hi thank you oh yeah
come I'm I'm thinking about going to
area to to scavenge wait okay cars
aren't completely yeah let's go together
when cars look complete they will also
give gas so those are nicer to Ranch
without okay it's
cool follow you I'm waiting for we
already have one of these should we hold
on to it anyway what were we
making all right and now it's time for
the smack it
7,000 but working very hard still it's
going fast yeah
yeah come on it here I thought we
cleared the place
out so
close ooh legendary I found a bunch of
good
stuff work of it we
are
H let's just make the max of
these a lot
where do we normally put bullet casings
they
mining okay go ahead
yay there's another treasure map I know
how much you like
though stop they're probably sick of the
the treasure the you want to do another
treasure
map hold it thank getting sick of the
Treasure by now huh but the treasure was
it giv was a lot of ammo and weapon
parts though so it was worth
it be sure to take your steroids and
your vitamins do you have more space
fauna yes okay you can take the
treasure to yeah you you can look at the
treasure map
now oh who is doing like Tech and turret
stuff cuz I have a you can
[Applause]
thank you oh and you know what I'll give
this turret to
you
oh thank
you oh I think this is mine for you
maybe oh really I think I think it
breaks blocks or something I think
you're sitting on something or doors
oh that's his
guts oh can punch zombies too is a punch
we we should set it up like outside the
yeah yeah when the when the cord happens
he how to punch
zombies the auto Fister yeah yeah oh did
you did you have did you have any more
tea I have
this tea
was that
surprise oh there's two of them there's
two did
it did you hear that sound it was like
yeah it was a plane it's a a supply
drop oh uh Callie do you remember where
that one sham food thingy was yeah the
Sham Factory the Sham Wow Factory yeah
yeah yeah where is it on the map oh do
you remember where it was it's in the
desert I believe it's between the desert
and the desolate area yeah I can
probably find out where it
is yeah we can go home first okay home
is on the
way damn I'm been so loveling out here
pretty
intensely I should meet up with the rest
of the
crew can we go talk to wrecked E I
wrecked okay guy sucks yeah he's going
to give me money
yeah money money he owes us money yeah
he owes you big
time especially for all the mean
insults yeah get wrecked wreck I hope I
hope I have enough gas to make it to
wreck we can always wrench some cars on
the
way oh I should make is not not
that yeah Hugh is my best friend
now good work I love SN always more work
to do if you're
interested could be nice these are kind
of bad though okay drop your weapons or
drop your
drawers
yay I'm so
slow it's not nice night time I
know so many things in these Pockets ooh
water filter that's nice do we already
have a water filter we do need we can
always need more okay it's a little
expensive but I'll keep saving up for
it how do I get rid of weakened
armor uh you have to repair it I have my
hand with weapon repair kits or repair
kit
yeah cuz I'm trying
I un first
iside okay make a run to the
house I don't know if this works with my
thing I'll try it
let's take the Roes oh sell the cash in
Gold ah I should sell the gold that's
right I do have golden nuggets
better can me do that real quick
maybe sun is better everything
guaranteed to make okay I are you
dropping off things for me oopsie oh
I've just dropped off a bunch of random
stuff I found I found some
steel is oh is there Iron among it
too no I think I left the iron at the
old house ooh we definitely need that is
there a I was tired of it maybe a
th000 okay that's good that's good I
want that are you walking cuz you can't
Sprint I'm I'm this this is my sprinting
skin I'm full I'm very full maybe I go
pick it up RP
walk I'll head back and see uh-huh colie
did you find it get some more to
randomly check find what the I need to
gas no I haven't gone there yet we could
it's fine I'll just look around in the
yeah I'm still in the snow area I'm
heading back to the house
though okay okay
unless you want to yeah okay I can wait
for you let's see we can take it you
want to come with us then yeah I want to
go with you going to raid the the Sham
Factory I'm going to ride my bike home
since it's so close I see you
there heck yeah also I have a treasure
map if anyone wants to look to yeah of
course of course we're just waiting for
Coe okay of course of course I'll come
back home then counting you
in of course of course a how will I do
without my big
cat I need her to drive she's a big
[Music]
car yeah yeah yeah guys you know what I
realized the other day what you know ra
is a pink she's pink
and she's called
panta she pink she's like the she's like
the pink pan is this something that you
just figured out fan art I made of
her wait what wait
what just realized H every once in a
while didn't know I'm telling it what
are you saying you never thought about
it it's a joke never realized
it just H our very sarcastic I
hope are they
gaslighting we're just trying to have a
good time and you're trying to Gaslight
us me don't take everything personally
I'm taking it personally good I'm going
to HR about this
good imagine today we have a meeting
because I was gasset by them about Pink
Panther
it
I messed up can't believe you would do
that to
her that's why you said that I'm a
furry a what yes she's a furry did you
get your new gun
[Music]
bio let's go 30 minute craft
yeah the 30 minute cra
fa five minutes craft my favorite not
the five minute craft I love five minute
craft I have the first motor bike on the
server and it's
huge I want to see show show show no gas
this better be like the fastest thing
ever I have no gas in it right
now that's I have a lot of G for you
kaha it's crazy
structure oh look at the seet in the
back so cool with the this this this is
like T coated with
the yeah the biker build really suits
this I wonder how B though the animal
head is like eating the light in the
front yeah that's
cool that is a sick
bike I'll have fill it up with some gas
and we'll see how fast I have 300 gas
can yay I want I'm coming thank
you you can only two dang no rush but
let us know when you're ready um Kelly
all right I'm just I'm just cooking some
steel real quick and then I'm on my way
and Dro I'll you guys too now that I'm
done oh we're going to the Sham Factory
oh I want to go to s Factory okay let's
go you guys want to
come let's just wait for call for a
second yep I'm just putting away some
ammo I've got a ton of different ammo
here I need to organize some stuff at
home first too anyway I think we're low
on food again uhoh sh I think we have
quite a few raw meat oh it's more that
we don't have any
ingredients to make a good food oh I
found some potato that's about to change
at the S at the Sham at the Sham Factory
we're about to raid which is why I need
open inventory call come here for a
second yeah take that oh thanks sh yes
thank
you we can just keep them in here just
easier to
just way more shotg parts than this
where I put them that doesn't seem
right where are my shotgun no one else
is making shotguns I don't think right
no I you are a V okay they're in here I
see they're in the weapon parts box
okay was about to be a real sad we're
fine we're
fine are you putting gas yeah I put
everything inside here a thank
you yeah oh I want to see the speed
now oh
yes this one doesn't have a to cook some
meat is it hard to make this next seat
for the mini bike yeah if you give me
more cloth fragments I can make one how
many do you need maybe 100 would be nice
100 what what do you need to make the
motorcycle you
craft I would need a bunch of things I
have
ches I have the handle bars and two
wheels
yeah um I'm coming you probably are
missing the motorcycle chassis if you
look it up and you can see what that
needs let's go all right are you ready
I'm ready to go everybody head to the
warehouse Factory people ready yeah your
the pink one I'm almost ready sorry was
yours the pink one your old one my
bicycle or yeah um my mini bike mini
bike no uh cron is using the old Mini
Bike now it doesn't have the the seat
anymore cuz I put it on my motor bike oh
that's why okay okay no worries then is
it okay if we go to the factory with you
guys okay we're just riding over to
where you all are right
now that's fast I'm going to hit that
River it's so fast so I can probably
just stop off in a pool or something I
drop is it really that quick yeah and it
it gets curves really sharply w i can
drift I can literally drift oh drifted
that's pretty
cool oh my
God's
cooking oh yeah I'm
hungry the problem is we have like no
potatoes I don't know I have two
potatoes here you go I don't make one
potato B more water I think the Sham if
we go to the Sham Factory I assume
there's going to be a lot of food there
so maybe this is a good
opportunity for you oh is that for
me for
you thank
you thank you
K
welcome so fancy my's off I wonder I
made some m chest pieces I don't know
who to give them
to are we out of rotten flesh there's no
way right
really see uh what's on your chest my I
mean I mean no no no I mean your chest
your armor uh what did you wear for the
top again so I am I have an Assassin
outfit which is not really freaking what
level
three okay uh switch with this give me
the Assassin one oh thank you I give you
mine now
mhm here you go
bye does anybody have any rotten
flesh it's very important here here I
have six here you go put some into those
like white boxes let me
see I have a repair
[Music]
one oh did I make
my it goes
off okay um don't mean to rush I'm just
um just checking is everyone ready or
I'm good to
go pretty much
ready okay I didn't
nerd
goggles my nerd go
everybody think are on their way they're
just on their
bik okay okay take your time it's fine I
are you good what are you doing they're
trying to find their way to the house
the way to the house oh yeah see them
North oh I'm digging don't worry about
me yeah do not worry about me we're
heading over there right now
I'm going to pick up the iron gigy I'm
coming over with my motorbike okay I
have 2,000 on me right now oh let's go
uh do you need help do you want me to
pick you up
or we just we got a little bit lost on a
b it's understandable it happens
always we'll just follow
after oh I have so many explosives for
this hor
so ready okay very exciting um I I got
a a armo crafting
bundle uh I put it here in the
middle oh my God chest you mean a for in
the middle here the the the chest the
boxes in the middle I don't know what to
put it I'm a crafting kit you mean or
what did you get I don't know it's never
seen this before it's like I'm a
crafting m is a red box a bundle ah
bundle
oops oh man I did a
mess this is going to be the sickest
raid
ever yeah I'm so ready we're going to
fight so much food yeah the long last we
can eat a little bit more food God this
outfit's so awesome the biker outfit's
so cool thank you right with the nerd
goggles though The The J position is a
little it's a little the more Gap the
more Gap Callie
there's something wrong with this guy uh
B do you need sham for the Sham food you
can eat the Sham okay I going to eat the
Sham the sandwich just give you a tummy
so
fast some of them do but the sandwiches
give you a
PO
wa free spikes rolls
nicebody I have 4,000 iron
wow wow that's a lot of iron wow
impressive where is it okay um I'm in
the
hole get
[Music]
it let's make it out going oh w i a a
flip
too oh
I here take all my iron oh there you are
I fell into the hole Okay jump to the
left thankk you so much okay
okay you can take this bike if you want
or do you have your own oh I can come
with
you I only have I don't have a seat if
you have a bike you have can use your
own bike oh okay never
mind okay I was just
lazy me too okay let's go go let's
go it's not even that bad lead the way
someone wait where where are we you said
you know where I kind of know where it
is I kind of know where it is one moment
let me Mark it this is a biker
gang yeah I got another thousand Iron
where how you producing these so fast I
found it in my
mod so good I know it's around this area
so I'm inside the house right now
everybody almost
[Music]
we really are the nerd biker gang yeah
oh are we going this way wait does this
mean that I'm
theer always 500 kilm ahead of you we
ride as a model gang model we ride as a
g we we ride we
ride we ride
day we have to read again 35 sorry
okay we got time plenty of
time it's following cie she seems like
she knows where she's going on the
highway M
High to the danger zone all right so
it's not the church a scary
place but I think it's here cuz that's
where the town is right to through the
Sham Factory okay update it's actually
4,000
iron wow okay found a lot in that hole
all right I have two forges I'll be
cooking a lot of iron now thank you no
problem pretty wait gigy do you want to
see my motorbike I want to see it
you can even get on and be the first to
test it
oo oh my God so
cool wraps my arms around you it's lock
let me lock oh sorry for safety you know
yeah I can't let zombies get on
oh it's so fast look I can drift that's
awesome you're a gang leader our biker
gang leader with our cool
hat yeah I know exactly where I'm going
my
God are
[Music]
youw okay get
off okay actually no damage was just
taking you on a I found it I found it
it's not here it's this way it's this
way
me get me out of here
I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying I'm
trying it's fine it's fine it's this way
I found the right way okay you found it
this is what happens
when I'm diving into the spike I'm not
taking any damage interestingly
enough F taking damage uh no this good
that's good that's good that's good
that's good out of gas okay okay y
by get home
oh might have uh given the Trap some
damage it seems I can borrow some from
strong bik she went she went this way
okay she went this way just follow me
through the mountains
ladies I trust
you yes really
are so we ride into the
sunset the air brushing through my shins
I want to beat people up some
forever we get to the factory be like
children I think I'll find some is this
all like social structure depending on
who has a motorcycle motor bike or
bicycle
yeah yes the motorik queen she is the
queen okay wait fauna fun what does that
make you since you're back
seating I'm the I'm the sigma I'm not a
[Music]
yeah she's on a little bit of a
different level cuz she got she got back
seat right to my motorbike
too found it ladies I'm going to need
some to borrow some gasoline by the way
before we get out of here bicycles
really are the best huh we don't even
need gasoline no just our legs all right
sham way Factory ladies oh this is the
fact here it is before it gets too dark
but it will become night so the zombies
will become stronger so this will be a
great challenge for us it's okay you can
die over and over again cuz it's not a
yeah we can take it's not a
quest we'll be fine we can take them wa
die
nobody you want to die I can I can help
you with that yeah we can help with that
if you really want you guys are so
helpful but you know sometimes you have
to do things on your own I don't want to
get carried in my own death I okay I
kill you without
asking okay let's go in
ladies ow who shot me oh
god wow this is a good weapon I'm
excited okay office CH guys we need the
leather oh try the
cheers oh boy oh he's going to barf off
his chairs with
[Applause]
the hammer everybody else will get
double oh
gosh I
ouch L if they lever otherwise they just
CL which is nice
too how do I
shoot for that o ow I'm so
sorry you're allowed to shoot me cuz I
cuz I stabbed you too many
times you should see the body just in
case this is
crazy but here's my number so call me
maybe maybe I will okay maybe yeah let's
break things
there's a hole that goes underground oh
boyo yeah
sh still in oh there's a lot of boxes
everywhere here
aot green on too oh boy suffered a
deep
out I have
bandaids everybody come get some
bandaids before you die
ladies drop I want to see I just took a
peek big hitters I'm going to go ahead
and use
that I'd like to take everybody come get
bandaids a bandid we bandid that's it
doesn't matter do we have
band everybody needs a band for their o
which
me get get
get oh my God jce
J fire fire fire
fire strong than that I think
so I'm not using
anymore the B is everybody's walking
forward that was awesome good job
everybody oh good job
everyone so good I guess we can clean
the place out like after we kind of kill
everything but yeah yeah
yeah looting along the way is not a bad
idea okay let's stick
together not much more this way
[Music]
I do be a little hungry I was saving
this for the ra I'll use it
now
hi oh there up here okay let's go up
yeah let's go up I
see we can't hear you when anyone's
shooting yeah it's any game watch out
watch out I'll turn the fire people
hello
boys oh like
pictures hello oh a bed roll was up here
what the heck what a bed roll
here a
little
time I'm burning the ground is falling
yeah that's not that is not great it
does not Inspire confidence what's in
here repair kit SC them SC them SC them
[Music]
those look like they're going to
break not this
way huahua if you needed I have 6,000
more iron oh my
gosh more iron need get closer to
him let me turn off that fire though
yeah the fire is just so
[Music]
intense
okay more iron I turn yes I have 7,000
more if you need it okay I'll pick it up
later okay do you need G do you need any
armor by the way nah I'm good
okay okay oh yikes are you
good oh I'm
great oh yeah you're
fine it's saving me right now
gy I'll get you so much more this hole
has so much iron in here I have 8,000
now don't
worry I want more creepy lure about the
I don't want to e okay I'm just going to
ow B is there anything you would still
like to have in terms of armor
uh uh let's
see I think I'm fine with my
Stu I
hear got you oh when you come can you
bring repair kits though how many maybe
Che I'm going I think I'm going to read
thank you this way bye
bye okay
uh anybody has any on me
or not on me but maybe at home I
think oh okay there's a big dude how do
we
get I got
him should way up somewhere scrap chairs
thought I would have enough turns out I
want remember to scrap chairs ladies for
leather yeah as much as you can
okay ni shot thanks anything
else
one
single Don't Mind If I Do
any
other this is a new
area oh hello is he dead he's
dead he's super
dead yeah where's the big chest in this
place is what I want to know there's got
to be one yeah there's got to be one at
the end somewh this place is huge though
I will say oh
[Music]
oh hello
boys there's one there's
one thank
[Music]
you wait what let the light the light
okay I to the light okay come on my
friendly fire was such a bad
idea sorry how do you see sorry about
that it was a little hard to see it's
okay it's
dark hope it doesn't spawn you too far
away let's let's mess up the
CH all right yeah don't pick it up
yeah now I just got to find where that's
probably or somebody somebody I think
it's back
[Music]
I need that I found
it this is full of good stuff that we
need to scrap or not scrap gather rather
there's another CH Qui down let's get
that
one yeah I'm back
back we go into the ground
maybe o armored I'm going to use that
really quick cuz I do need that okay
where did you guys go I
still in the building oh I'm not in the
party anymore can you invite me again oh
yeah uh who's I just did leader oh you
fell through the floor just now okay is
that a zombie or is that a thank you
okay yeah I don't
know down all these doors are locked we
might need to break
them no there's there's another
way did you go downstairs or are you
still on the same level oh we can go
here
it's a shame tomorrow's the last day
today I know today I have 177,000 iron
now how are we going to smelt it all
yeah I know what a
shame where are you did you go out down
ah oh oh stairs that's not way I found
you yeah that looks like not the way
nowh uh there's a people way there's a
staircase on the side of guys I'm on the
other side of this wall just saw the
bars hello
hello okay okay I see you bibo show me
the bibu way you have to go outside
first a I
see some outside
parkouring yeah
gotcha got to exit through the window
okay I see and then up here oh
okay cool nice find
weu good find
yeah
zomos o this looks super creepy Up on
the
[Music]
Roof hello oh there's a lot of Mines
here watch
out maybe we can leave the zombies on
them time to shoot where are you guys we
can lead them on to the SP mines on the
roof
if you come over here we can lead them
past the mines and
spikes
good
miss good forever they're like n
TRS good we can get we don't need the I
found no ping
pong not now now it's not the time for a
ping pong at the door
to get
home I I think if I step on the mine I
won't
AC let's have some water M oh okay I'm
good this will angry dang is there no
treasure oh maybe there is there there's
another way oh down here
o let's follow
everybody not too
big for the Min this place is crazy it's
like a maze get is yeah
oh
uhoh uhoh uhoh SHO
don't know how we're going to parkour
Beyond here though
okay you crouching Again by the way yeah
yeah yeah I know I'm just like try to no
I'm not I was not cring now she's ging
you she's gasing I think that is a vis
back because everyone is telling me that
I'm crouching don't
actually weird do anything why would
keep lying to
us am I lagging right now yeah the the
the server's kind of laggy right now
yeah cuz there a lot of zombies it's a
big area watch out watch
out oh gosh it yeah they're like flying
in floating for
[Music]
me
nice I'm going to go home and craft
stuff okay
okay I think every else is downstairs
now okay we're going to follow K okay
just be careful because it's a very very
far drop this seems to be I wonder to
how we get in
here here as slow as you can this door
oh behind you behind you behind
you if anyone passes by me cuz they're
on the way can they take all this iron
off me oh there's a pack of wolves
outside um I would love I'm going to run
iron does anybody have a c repair key
there's
AAR there's Bears let's stick together
okay I'm going to try breaking this open
with a stick of dynamite okay I stay
behind M stay behind be your best I got
the
zombies oh you have to activate it
and there you go there you go there you
go out out
a
little somebody somebody's here it did
work good job yeah that's
crazy wait have we already been here
been here
before appre me good
job does anybody have a repair kit by
any chance I have one where are you I am
right there here I also have one thank
you thank you so much I need to repair
my
spear spear spear that's tons of leather
are you girls uh coming back sometime
soon or soon I think I thought this
place would treasure but oh there's a
bunch of stuff here here where I am oh
oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh there is a green
guy cuz i' love surrounded I'm going to
die it's
over uh-oh get I did it he's in my
sights
away I have a wonderful gift for
you is it yeah it's all Iron don't
expect anything else to
H got a stunk bug y my bikes can
fly oh there is some stuff oh nice there
a bunch of stuff a bunch of stuff over
might as well take everything oh a safe
too yeah take
everything I don't have lock I don't
know if it gave us oh shoot I should
have given this lockpick to
[Music]
bio mon monster F well I guess we're
breaking it over so many
trees oh this is an easy one to Break
can I plant those are you planning on
getting rid of those trees this easy one
the trees are the tanks
it's going to be hard to see and shoot
the enemies through all that all those
leaves oops are you here here by the way
yeah okay let's work together one second
get out of my hole okay I'm not getting
close to that right now why not oh yeah
you want to get are you ready yeah I'm
I'm ready Bring It On get smacked
understand oh that's wow that's a lot of
it's 20,000
30,000 oh we're still
hungry thank you you're so
crazy back to my missing something
because this feels a little bit
underwhelming for how big this area
is I hope there's some good stuff in the
safe with
money probably
ow someone hit
me I have not moved my my hand I wonder
if there was uh lever you don't have any
lever do you he no I've not seen an
animal in ages oh sorry
sorry except maybe for some moles or
what shows up down there little earth
worms and other little mole rats are
down here too is that what you have been
feeding on as well
I eat
them let's crack it open sorry I opened
it um it's there's nothing there's big
hitters which I'm going to read because
I am the club oh steel Club quality one
y and then iron arrows I will take those
just in case someone wants those that
was all that was in there it was not
very
exciting sadly pointing disappointing
wait what happened to
her search the
garage angry s Ste Club
L CL wait wait here here where'd he go
the one inside here there's an area we
haven't been to
window the is it right
there we're not going to let them in
right nah it's better to not I'll give
it to her later oh there's a enemy still
there's a angry angry dog outside
everybody's angry oh y
excuse me oh you sir can you wait just a
moment there's still quite some enemies
here so I wonder if we didn't go this
way people I wonder this way
yeah this way we this way oh they come
in from outside I guess and on this oh
maybe they Spa from the outside so it's
night time so probably
this
like
oh I deserve to get shot it's
fine really dirty today I deserve it oh
my God that's a
lot get him get him y yo we going to die
let's run away let's run
away stay in the brightness of the
fire
C uhoh
jum Bo um that's no
good he doesn't want it to
what is the server really laggy I'm I'm
walk very slowly it's a little strange
okay so I'm not
sure uhoh oh God this like an exploding
guy like a red green guy it's over for
me uh
run run oh where
is there's a lot of zomes
here
friend nice oh boy I want to find the
dog everybody you want to find a dog no
you don't want to find a dog and kill it
yes it gives good loot I want to find a
dog are you talking about the dire wol
yeah the the dire W I see okay hold up
don't need this need
that can eat food have that was it I'm
walking super
slow that must have been it oh boy
that's a big
guy have you guys been collecting some
Lea on the way oh yeah I've been
scrapping all kinds of chairs
cool does it help with our light
get away get away get
away
yeah
hello maybe don't shoot the ground no
Panic shooting no Panic shooting
somebody looks a little bit CE CE behind
you behind you CE oh there's a one of
them we can take
them how find me XP
just trying to see if there's something
here since there's a where the Sham
sandwich is at he's
running he looks like everybody else oh
I'm
so I'm crushed the I'm still kind of
slow
maybe go
down I think it's more now so we should
be okay yeah okay okay we
chilling okay where was the Sham I was
promised there was like no food here
yeah this was
insanely misdirecting I feel like we
should have just done a
quest yeah it's okay you live and you
learn yeah live and
learn you're home I am home I have a
present for
you do
like special
alcohol thank you a lot of stff we
didn't pick up here punch go stop giving
her
[Music]
alcohol but it will save us it will will
it save our family it will help put our
family back together not mentally but it
will save us
physically yeah yeah our interpersonal
relationship last get rid of my supplies
all that matters is that we stay alive
I'm happy to do more snow quests with
anybody who wants to do the snow quests
they're a little bit harder but they're
I'm for any way we can help some of
course we have a bunch of cloth you guys
are doing great I actually I want to
make you a thing really quick though to
make it even
better you guys will be even more
helpful once I make you my special
present I'm going to go work on make
bandages oh we can make bandages
yeah do medical stuff so uh fauna is
just getting meat room is on the roof
they say uh we really need more
than apparently the loot is on the
roof will take care of it we need like
potatoes rotten meat rotten meat okay
rotten meat potatoes and mushrooms
mostly and eggs eggs are good too oh yes
very very good for you I wonder why we
can find that maybe
no eggs are like in the nest on the way
oh right
yeah no problem hello
[Music]
lady okay let's
go want
amazing Che them out could use one of
these
basically oh yeah there is a cave of
mushrooms oh
yeah I think we might
potatoes more than mushrooms for now
where do you think we can find potatoes
I don't know is there a potato cave
thank you so I mean they are in the
ground I do need antibiotics she has
them di my inventory I am hungry I'm
starving I'm going to die I have three
rotten
flesh I want to go home together with
want scar there's a zombie apocalypse
out there
should we leave the fact
now
yeah and now radex no you got the wrong
story where's the food at lady where's
the
food that was a good deal trust me I'm
doct trust her she's a
doctor
okay okay I think I'm going to go to try
and Scavenging
[Music]
from I'm going to be in people panicking
means it's pretty
[Music]
bad go this
way okay hold up let me go back home up
I think
[Music]
up new house
does anyone else want to try targeting
houses in order to find food I found the
room with the loop problem is the room
is also full of
zombies wait in the sh in the Sham
Factory yep oh okay okay oh should we go
back I'm going no it's okay I think I
can do it you can take them okay also
need more cloth for
bandages may not okay
okay well by the time I get there the
situation may have resolved itself
but okay we're coming where are you B Bo
I I I'm at the roof okay the roof how
did you get there I'm
coming maybe let head back to the new
home we have done 4 180s Mory yes cuz
cuz I can't decide whether to go
out where is
she I think it's fine I think I got it
you got it the last 180 I'm
doing let's pray I can get home I'm
pretty sure I can 90% gas should be fine
don't make me turn this bike
around ladies we have 40 IRL minutes
left until the raid until the zombie
night okay boy I'm fine I cleared the
room it's good oh you good yeah I'm good
I will finish my weapon in time I'm sure
so we going to the old house correct yes
I just need six more forged steel and
then I can make it for
them we got plenty of those
now is anybody coming home lever I am
how about cloth anybody got cloth cloth
[Music]
pieces I can try to go get some I'm
going to the old home and see if I can
reinforce as many as possible clo I
don't have I'm going to like small
houses and we'll try finding cloth as
well we have cloth
right the cloth bag must be made into
cloth I think so yes clock fragments is
what we need we got a few hundred that's
good
okay and maybe I can make my steel
clove did I
okay the world a bit
Bri I mean that's enough if I was using
it alone Ias
[Music]
I guess having more iron is
inconsequential Gigi did get like 17,000
iron yeah we have we have plenty of that
now that's good it just takes a little
never ask for iron ever again you won to
ask what this got it I have so much for
you oh wow I'm so happy I'm honored I'm
going to make it so you're all relying
on me for iron and then you'll never
know what it's like without iron and
then I like drip feed it SW s yeah until
you you like desperately need me and
you're begging we already need you we're
already obsessed with you I guess I'll
never stop collecting iron
then the leather put the GL it's not a
ton but it is a decent amount hopefully
it'll help you and some glue as well I
might need to I actually need to make
duct tape there a lot of supplies here
with this gun I need duct tape should
put the hold up um can you put them in
the medicine box
medicine box okay
my that's
[Music]
fine like
cloth gra these bandages I know it's
kind of messed up oh the cooked food in
medicine one is good okay okay this will
be worth it I promise can I not make
them ow I have some more medicine we can
put
in what else do we have in here
C sniffly
whatever
okay steel cloth clo in the medicine
does we have two leather where should we
put the leather wct tap I think Kara
wanted the
Leather by probably for chest yes
the
four this one's making iron I think this
one's making
steel storage chest oh the fire chest
chest okay I just need 20 for what I
want to make them maybe it's
upstairs oh need
40 okay it should be the chest in the
kitchen
somebody was was somebody making a yucka
smoothie yes and also duct
tape I was making a smoothie oh okay
I'll give you the smoothie I oh you can
put it it's not for me necessarily it's
for anybody for anybody in the food
chest or you can drink it if you want oh
there's so much cloth fragments and okay
there's a
couple oh
no am I going
okay what time is it 7:30 oh plenty of
time to go check for steel let me show
we forging steel right we're forging
steel yeah I need some forg
steel kind have any
antibiotics I'm making some yum yums oh
I need to oh I need to eat
these going to die w wow my favorite
hobo stew thank you for cooking this
hobo
stew I thought I thought it was a
sculpture is it not a sculpture
there exposive inde not a
sculpture I thought it was a
dog explosives I wonder I will be taking
these a chest for explosives
I thought it was a robot
dog the flowers
are but we're hungry though do we have
any
food okay I'm going to have it make
steel have
to okay
we're r a
salm first we're hungry we can't get
that
far just for now so if everybody can eat
the grilled meat before the raid and
then save the good food for the raid I
think that would be
ideal great idea please eat the grilled
meat first you're going to have to eat a
lot of it but I'm going to stop this
first I think it's good to save the the
ra oh there's a coup not sure how long
feel like an hour 30 because this Tays
an hour and then is it that long till
the rain is it really it might be isn't
it on the 35th should be able to oh we
here so it's actually time yeah realiz
is kind of quite far oh 1 hour 30
minutes hour and 30 on well we still
have a lot of time maybe I'll go for
some extra
Quest could have played longer
yesterday that's just what I'm saying
yeah we should
have we hard to do ma that's good though
we' got preparations to do are we making
what are these what are you sorry what
were you making
here sorry were you making bullet
casing yep I'm making them for ammo okay
do you need a crucible to do that
bye oh oh maybe not yeah cuz I got to
make
steel and I was wondering if I could use
this to make steel if possible okay and
then maybe we can make bullet casings
over
here how much Ste you need I have like
100 in my pocket oh my god wow that's
crazy well to make the gun I wanted to
make it's like
40 okay yeah wait let me
oh but they're off for the day huh
they're offline oh dang it oh oh they
just left what I didn't even realized
yeah what they left yeah they ending for
tonight they got to go um maybe I'll
give it to I'll give the I'll give the
gun to Cody then let me invite you back
to the party I think there's now oh yes
please I might go since we still have so
much time if somebody's still doing
quests I might join yeah let's Quest
[Music]
okay I do I I was making some armor so I
got some stuff to give to the weakest
links yeah whoever that is and I'm going
to get best
shots oh did you I N now though yeah we
can use I think we'll need a bunch steel
Club how do we make steel
Club also need a workbench for this one
this one actually can be made pretty
quickly let me know whenever you guys
are on your way to a new class okay okay
what what do we
meet
potatoes
potatoes where do we meet guys which
Quest we going to
do get some
weapons
oh not sure which one yet I like the
snowy Quest though I think they're good
I want to go there too I've I don't
think I've been there before yeah I
still need to open up the trader to the
do you have to open the trade route or
can you just talk to the new Traer no
you can just talk to him
okay but I still want to open pretty
sure that's fine yeah might be good
might be a good
idea go
there I got a auto turret oh nice really
I got two auto turret I got two SMG Auto
turrets them in the finale
I spent like 10 minutes opening a chest
it was so worth it yeah that sounds like
it was worth it auto turn sounds super
cool
Auto
wrench heck yeah it's freaking I'm
coming to the house then and
then maybe I'll make some 9 mm girls who
are using 9 mm ammo is it only bio it's
only bi but I could use a lot more I'll
I'll put some into the queue for you
thank you cuz I'm also making ammo for
myself guess I could make some shotgun
shells too shotgun shot
ammo you I don't know if you're able to
but I would need uh steel
arrows um I have iron
arrows that'll help RI haven't looked
into arrows yet um some armor to take
that's a bit too much baby I I already
making armor and
stuff maybe I'll wear the Nomad
head
doing no I won't take it back it looks
cool but I look cooler
oh and I have a treasure map I probably
want to look
into I don't know if it's any if it'll
be any good though hey vibo did you want
molotovs
yes please
okay how much cloth do you
need um a lot but I think I'm I might be
in the chest in the
kitchen which chest in the one in the
kitchen by the forge if you want to take
it CeCe were you using
batons I wanted to get a uh I have a
stun baton level five oh yes I can give
it to you yeah because I have like a mod
extension thingy for yes yeah it's it's
really good I think you should have it
thank
[Music]
you I'm coming home to store some Loot
and then we can do Quest I'm ready
anytime I'm going home too maps are
based on where you look at it I'm pretty
fire oh if you read it in a higher level
you get better loot okay maybe I'll look
at the treasure map when we're in the
snow area
[Music]
everyone thank you very B thank you very
much for the redirect that was nice I'm
sorry I couldn't make you guys the
shotgun I wanted to make
you but that's okay just it's it's in
it's in your heart I deliver it to your
heart we're ready for quests be at game
stage
190 oh yeah yeah should we be worried
about that I murdered a bunch of
things maybe we should be worried about
that I don't
know hey crony's at 94 though so that's
kind
of it also depends on where you are
because I am still at the factory so I
see yeah
a I see she's in the Wasteland I'm
making a few more repair kits just like
maybe oh yeah I need repair kits repair
kits are always
good where the area head to the Rally
Point should I head to the rally
point we should wait for everybody loing
is
doing um I just see it on my screen it's
1.6 km oh that's no that's a that's
a one Quest that's a tier one Quest okay
I don't think we should let's maybe not
do that
yeah um how many people are using
shotguns in here C
crony
okay I'm a need of a little
fuel just a little fuel we'll find some
fuel
surely any gas cans you're right CE I
might buy you uh let me drop off this
weapon for you oh oh oh watch out bird
oh it's always the freaking Birds I will
eat this me will take it off your
hands a little
nice thank you yeah do you happen to
have a repair kit I can buy off of you
you can just have one taking some
Provisions what hat are you wearing I'm
wearing the nerd hat still
Level uh four I believe do you want a
higher level nerd hat or would you like
some different hat sewing kit in here um
sure I could use a higher level nerd
hat cool tur you prefer nerd hat over
anything else do
you
um well that's the ex one right oh yeah
y yeah I would prefer the EXP okay I'll
make you the max level
[Music]
one think I can make it using up one
legendary part maybe wait do we still
have an hour and a half we do and we've
been going for 4 and 1 half hours we we
timed it I thought I thought one day is
one hour but I guess not is it longer
than that I think it's longer than that
I could keep
playing yeah me too me too I'm fine
still yeah me too we're just so bad at
definitely
the though sure we we prepared too hard
for to not have a hoorde at the end yeah
definitely hope we get a season 2 we're
working on it it seems
possible
so I would love that let's do it I
really want
to have a better heart if possible mine
is level two do you want the EXP had or
a different XP is fine okay just a bit
stronger maybe yeah no problem thank you
I'll make you level five whoa I think
I'm going
get I kind of want to read I'm going to
get some mods for my spear
feel like this is still not enough
bandages I have five on my hand
personally right now so I'll just use
those I think I'll be fine with
five for the raid
yeah I I'll forget using them anyway
literally yesterday I only used
one I just forgot about them
oh be back very
quickly okay where are we going to do
Quest how about the snow area I will
keep recommending the snow area over and
over yeah we can do we can go to the
snow area since it's higher
tier um I have one up there yep tier
four clear that one's fun beo it's a fun
one okay it's a big shooty one
spy I'm trying to make ammo for everyone
right now thank you thank you thank you
thank you I've got lots but I'm going to
I'm going to use all of
it this shotgun is amazing that's why I
need to
pick action here here you
go oh wow okay I'll just focus on shot
9 mm yeah if I could have a lot of 9 I'm
sure he has
fuel oh also there is about 200 shotgun
bullets in the weapon ammo crate right
now oh let's go okay awesome I'll split
that with CR I I'll probably give it to
is
that it's poo don't mind
po tell me about poo do not worry about
popo tell me about poo popo is the
little green bird flying next to me I'll
send you a photo of
him picture expect him to sound like
that yeah he's really good at
barking he's so talented let me find a
photo of
him yeah I want to see I want to see
popo too okay what is Popo's
personality um silent until the Barking
starts and then not silent yeah then Not
So Silent wait remind me please of the
levels of each of your armor don't just
stare at my handsome face get your ass
out there and get the job done oh she's
you muted L she said she's going to be
right back a while ago okay she's
looking at me in game
messed up I have telepathically sent you
a photo of popo into your TMS let me see
let me see popo oh my
goodness
[Music]
poo
cute so rat
likee where my anv does popo like being
called a
rat I call Popo ugly so much I'm like
come here ugly I love you little ugly
one and then Popo's like hold on I got
to sign
something hold on oh here's even more
for
you love paying my taxes do you have any
more gunpowder or or nitrate uh
powder have bullet casing
I don't need those necessarily but
yeah
bet it's
done
now let's see which Quest is that I
don't want to do the tier one clear can
I ignore
it should have made more 9 mm maybe
where's the quest I took
we're wasting
gas oh sorry guys I'm back I I'm back
welcome back welcome back so my hat nerd
hat oh thank you yeah but tell me the
rest uh I have the armor is level four
and the gloves are level three and the
boots are level three m i
see take these
thank you you're welcome and and the the
ones you
have now can you just drop them on the
floor the old ones of course of course I
didn't even see the bird hold on a
sec aren't those
the oh those are the old ones okay yeah
those are the old ones should I
see oh wait is this supposed to be on
the forge at all times
yeah oh well I think uh if there's
nothing cooking is anything cooking
cute uh let me let me
check that's a cute that's a cute little
bird you got there that's a cute what
Happ birie right there very cute
birdie I'm jealous of your cute birdie
is it making stuff I know it's so so
fluffy it's uh it's it's like smelting
the iron pretty
sure forged
iron uh then that has to be done
manually like first you put in the the
raw iron and it loads up the forge of
the iron and then anytime you can cook
the forg stuff once the iron is like
loading up there's like a count on the
right side how much iron How much brass
is inside oh here's here's two
workstation book oh thank
you Happ SE one of those
long uh let me know when we do
Quest then I okay I'm just organizing my
inventory right now first
okay it took him a
second he's using the bathroom huh oops
o more chairs turn into
Le there's a lot of
them wait does the does the fire not
just like if it's burning does it save
the time and then or is it just like
wasting fuel if nothing is cooking in it
or is it converting it into
it is wasting but the forge is not
wasting if it's just
running I
see he wants to come in
here there's a steel club and a pump
shotgun in the thank you the shotguns
for crony uh the steel club's for me
though
you
good oh these look like I could scrap
them who's screaming calm
down chill it's not that big of a
deal why you said eat the meat like the
basic meat yeah eat the grilled meat
before the raid you might have to eat
like a whole stack if you're I am I'm
working on it I'm eating a whole stack
right now
yeah the red tea oh no money it's hard
if we had more eggs we could make better
food if we had more potatoes but farming
is so hard cuz you have to spend five
potatoes to get two seeds and it's not
efficient yeah or to get one seed five
potatoes to get one seed and then you
get seven potatoes back so you only get
net two potatoes and it takes forever to
grow yeah that's not
efficient is the farmer armor expensive
to craft
kiaha uh farmer
outfit the whole outfit hello and maybe
just the chest I have a hat
already uh depends on what level you
want it on cuz I will be running out of
lever if I make this not again not again
not again not again not the
bear the bear brings
Lea maybe just level one is okay I'll
make you at least level
three okay you need help you're
breathing very
heavily but I think you went away I I'm
ready for quest now by the way H I am uh
finishing a solo Quest and then I'm I'm
ready to go okay
yeah I don't know I have wait the boots
are better farmer boots okay well they
also need most important they need the
same
materials D just
c yeah back welcome back
welcome
back I don't want to do
that it's my
level think I can take
it that is a
bear I got
your uh farmer
boots he can't get here right is he dead
I'll try to get us better seeds with
this
there you go I do love cheese I don't
know how much time we have to grow stuff
I love
cheese leather though we need not much
time I should be able to grow a few
potatoes at
least mushrooms a few
mushrooms he's a big boy
uh I'm putting 61 of wble bullets in the
Forge chest I feel bad oh I found you
give me so much
ammo yeah I I just found
them did you I think you you found the
the 20 bullets that I put into the ammo
chest boo hello oh did you did I I think
I did they're gone now so oh yeah I took
them I took them yeah yeah yeah Kelly
there's a bunch of shotgun ammo in the
new house so make sure to yeah a but lo
I found a bunch of those too I found
everything except my own people I have
another unrelated
presents
take thank you that if you need more let
me know shoot okay why am I using the
lock
[Music]
picks come on
yeah and
and this will surely help I think I have
one more right oh thank
you it will help it will kill one zombie
yes the one head
shot make the difference D do you want
to make metal
spikes yeah how I I have a I have a mod
for metal [\h__\h] I want to make metal
spikes yeah
okay I run back to the all house is that
I'm at the new house oh can I run back
to the to the new house I can drop it
off for you I'll come
by well oh
well oh I'm
hungry I Got No
Seeds there's there's almost 400 uh
shotgun ammo in the shotgun or in the
ammo
chest oh hello farming is a
scam there must be another way
around yeah
I
have what's in
here that looks
good oh he waved at
[Music]
me oh
Sho I dog
you you're my favorite customer
stuff we need those I wanted
separate
seeo chill this isn't about
you is there a good way to get
eggs ra chicken the there's got to be a
way to raise chickens or something like
that right too late to raise chickens
yeah should totally be possible
right
up is too calm to make
this but only on level
two get
better I take that I wish I could take
take the
photos wor I'm coming on your
direction I'm also going to head in that
direction oh oh okay me wait wait oh
I'll I'll I'll carry you give me a ride
of course I will thank
you uh just give me this one more
moment okay do we have some
[Music]
yeah be wood in one of the middle chests
you can also check my own chest I should
have can I use your
gunpowder you have gunpowder in your
chest Cey can I use it yeah for making
ammo for
everybody yeah got some good stuff wood
in
the maybe not or maybe I deposit some
there's 84 wood in the top middle chest
top
middle ah thank you I am blind as always
me too okay G I'm coming to drop by a
present for you D please make are you
eating
something no
yes I just Ed for to I was
hungry it's dinner
time oh mean lunch time it's lunchtime
no never mind I read it wrong it's much
for clubs you don't actually make metal
spikes
I'm our metal
fight that's really
bad there was more wood food hello I
mean if we can put it on a club we can
put it on the ground
a loud loud very loud very loud in your
house very loud yeah
ending I'm punching our house
def he really beautiful
house did he fall through the geometry
radi
definely R
okay know why did that
the zombie still at the
house
um she's deing with it will handle
it okay 100 bio ammo thank you who is
vomiting at my back door oh oh sorry I
got
him battle music stops okay I think I
think I think I can uh in 55 seconds I
can go
okay so we take this guy with us when
it's time oh there's still dudes this
guy but the melee turret yes we should I
did it though so that's good oh yeah
they keep
coming maybe I left the door
open
oh this going to be
rough okay okay I'm all over the place
I'm like everywhere oh nice
lucky
[Music]
hello Forge head two treasure chests
what's this about Ammo you already have
one of these I'll take it more right
here
do you need any more forged ahead iua
yes yes you do many many many gotcha I
figured as much I wasn't
sure okay good to know good to
know mission complete oh oh hey what's
going
on I'm helping I need to stop I need to
stop I need to stop cracking hopefully
the mission is complete so we can get
out of
here I'm I'm heading toward the snowy
area Okay anymore I think now I need to
claw my way out of here we have the
sealed shipping crates
too oh and this okay we found a
bunch
of clock the thing can you bring me uh
should I bring you the the the should I
bring the pump shotgun at the steel club
with me sure if you're coming to the
snowy area yeah I'm coming there be
there I wonder thanks
oh if you're using Club do you have the
mod for
spikes my spikes mod I do have one in a
club I'm holding I have I have a
schematic for you can make more of to
yeah that's cool I'll take
that since it's not placing
[\h__\h] yeah okay I got a bunch of cloth if
you're still available to make this seat
oh right now mhm I am quite far away so
I don't know if you have some then uh
yeah I
think we can exchange the club I have
enough to make it right now and you can
give me the one
you uh
gther um okay we are coming home but let
me see how far we are the zombies we're
doing some good not too far
um but you can also just leave it it's
up to you press the
button depends on if I have enough
leather
honestly might be missing one Le oh okay
now then I might need you to come over
unless I find leather here
okay on the
wall leather
leather wall button of course not our
most needed resource now is letter and
potatoes I guess okay potatoes potatoes
thanks for coming to help
me why you ended up there drop from the
ceiling other
office oh I see there it is oh there you
go I open
it hello are you two right now traveling
with two bicycles yeah oh
yo there's so much good stuff in here
back to you you have room in your
inventory by
chance yeah I have there's a pump
shotgun too oh my gosh this will be
great to arm people see if you can carry
some of this stuff I I can carry
everything okay cool I just got here too
so if you need any hands I have hands
awesome yeah I'm very cucumber at the
moment so okay I like cucumbers really
no what they were in the salad cuc
they're so tasty yeah cucumbers are kind
of I had a funny story I was at a
grocery store and I was buying chili oil
and this like man who looked like like a
like a wild like Lumberjack kind of man
that kind of man came up to me and was
like did you see the tick to
cucumbers oh sometimes you got to eat an
entire cucumber yeah
yeah it's a nation thing everybody wants
e cucumbers because of that specific guy
which sucks because there was already a
cucumber shortage so I'm mad at him for
exposing how good cucumbers
are I was not expecting this like
Lumberjack Mountain Man to be on the Tik
Tok cucumber
[Music]
meta go get the direwolf he's over
there the gate over there
okay my favorite is the one where
there's like this guy when he's just in
in in a like a lake or something and he
goes I think he dropped I just want to
see what the loot is I just want to look
at it oh he
dropped
oh oh shoot hold I'm sorry I'm I'm I'm
waiting for the lever delivery to make a
you want biker gloves I sure do want
biker gloves beo okay hold on well let's
clear this out first yeah bit delivery
from who uh CeCe crony gang
okay then they can go around faster cuz
I think yeah they're the quest
maybe don't worry we we'll catch up
super fast bike and then we'll wait
though for the ones who
are catching up doesn't mean anything
yeah I feel like I should go look for
stuff right now I'm not doing anything
I'll just go on my bike and then and
then if you find me on the way you can
pick me up okay easy what is in there
already red shotgun Messiah CeCe mhm how
much 7 point those ammo do you have I
currently have uhoh
outside
150 okay uh
take that thank you when I see you I
will don't mind if I do maybe until the
raid maybe focus on close combat so that
we don't waste too much ammo on the
quest okay we'll do
uh-oh excuse you do you have any mods on
your
gun right now
no I don't I haven't found any gun muds
actually there's a lot in the chest that
my I have I have all of the
recipes nice are there
actual oh yeah actually you can probably
take should work for you I'll take the
ones that should work no don't go
through the wall you the one to kill you
I'm so sorry I'm so
[Music]
sorry magazines take this oh o shotgun
shells so sorry about that no worries
you guys ready for
question yeah I'm
ready leather for
you cuc that was fast yeah okay here
okay 12 leather here's for you 236 cloth
what two sewing kids you want you want
to be hit yeah machine gun parts
oh armor up actually you can use if you
want it's okay I'm on steroids for 19
minutes I I put roting Flash and food
stuff into your food
area Okay in 1 minute your seat mod will
be finished
yay ah ah wait wait come over to the
middle uh I I chose some mods for you
for your gun for your rifle thank you
and then here's some ammo but don't
spend too much before the raid okay
thank you and I can upgrade my shotgun
but I wonder what materials I need let's
defend Row's stuff okay thank you got it
60 forged steel that's a lot of Steel
take this schematic cie oh thank you
hold on just a sec drinking some
water if we're foring a lot of rotten
flesh that's
good I have some ammo for you kiaha I'm
just going to put everything in this
chest the shotgun was for crony right
Kelly
yep it's my gift to her and this the
steel Club is for you yes oo
okay giving I'm giving her the the
shotgun right now and some other
stuff okay so got to make tons of duct
tape oh gosh they're coming in
oh good job B all right um we got it all
I think we're ready to go fun do you
want to head towards tier four beoo in
the snow sure I'll I'll go toward snow
boo where snow I'm going to stop all
wait tra is already closed so
noisy we can do did you take any quests
you took the Shaka Messiah Quest right
people yeah no that's the that's a tier
four clear beo next to the trader one
yeah you want to do that
singlehandedly or double-handed
destroying our house though
no not our beautiful house not our
home on earth oh the turret is
working
zom need to work a little bit
better not good enough no Cor
no
he's use the gun the side where are you
guys
again inside the building ah look at
this oh my God it's electrified wait is
crack a book the book it's just
stunned why is he walking on all fours
weirdo I'm
dying I wonder is he broke the house oh
no does someone have words to fix that
is it that bad no I'm sorry guys no just
the two blocks are gone no worry that's
fine someone who
died me we had two dead ah
casualties oh so many dead bodies oh my
God dead bodies everywhere dead bodies
everywhere oh see
see
man um but at least your seed mod has
been
finished woohoo woohoo wait see see see
see I'm going to put it down here on the
floor you pick up your your bike then
you can put it on there in the modify
window
okay uh it
was this one no that one's
locked oh wait uh you want to put it on
a mini bike right oh yeah I should store
some stuff do we have a leftover mini
bike right now I think we had
one it's here one here yeah let's see oh
yeah M mine probably my old one
I back sorry that's still locked by
music no actually no it's not who who
last used this one uh crony right oh
yeah crony
you got to unlock
it so that we can put the seat mod
on
yeah how's it going Gigi are you I'm
checking out the farm I'm looking for
eggs now oh thank
you I also have um 100 cloth if you
would like a 100 cloth kind of need Aloe
now okay it's in the desert go to the
desert start punching in the
desert where is she oh there ah do we
happen to have repair kids oh wait we
have two many
bikes ouch ouch ouch ouch park it across
the street hello hello just parking my
bike across the street near this
mountain you guys near oh you guys left
me alone no no no come here come here
come here you come here come here I'm
coming Callie while we wait let's us
loot the place oh yeah you just want to
loot it while we wait well it's going to
reset anyway so you might as well loot
the place okay but I think um it's over
for me H where would I find rep do we
have any or is it
over it's not over till it's over I can
pick you up if you
want no no no no uh uh uh CeCe yeah it's
the other mini bike I don't know who
locked the other bike but uh there's one
mini bike that's locked by me I'll
unlock this one okay or
wait no it's unlocked it's unlocked yeah
if you pick it up then you can put the
seat mod on so pick it up take and then
I modify
okay yay now fa did you ride off with me
I did you can you can pick me up though
okay are you on a bicycle or what yeah
I'm on a
bike uh where's the real go here where
bio is okay yeah where bio is where the
quest is I'll wait for everybody to get
here yeah just doing some light looting
beforehand CU in oh I should have oh
thank you we did it thank you
ketchup bike
Queen uh how often do we need
oil now and then but you can get it from
like in uh cars that are still
intact um when you wrench
them who's making these noises yeah I I
hear scary sounds out here too oh I
meant bicycle bike noises oh that's
we're spamming the honk noises oh call I
have level five biker gloves come here
wow even better gloves these instead
thank you what should we do with the old
ones give to someone else probably
probably give to someone else yeah you
can yeah
find uh what I going to do see it is
worth it to loot before you do the quest
true yeah extra you get extra
goodies mhm
you waiting for me it's
me I lost my
backpack did you run on your map yeah
yeah yeah yeah I just
respond oh you aren't too
far this Quest is going to be super easy
with all of us here for sure oh my god
do we have anything for infections with
us uh usually Traders have those but I
only have
vitamins I too am very infected
oh are you yeah I'm at 4.4 yeah you have
honey with you but I don't have any with
me
but we'll figure it out I'll find a tree
stump on the way hope
get he's when is the raid again uh uh on
this current in game day yeah 22
o00 on this day no yes this day 22: oh
the new one that we just passed midnight
so okay is about an hour in real
life yeah okay I think I'm going to go
on a quick like 5 to 10 minute break I
will be back down in our house going to
get some food I'm
starving okay all right nice food see
you in a bit in a bit have a good
break but there's
fauna I'm here my
fauna oh I think it's going to be the
four of us fin what gloves you have I'm
coming I'm coming oh
I I'm coming Raider five gloves oh
probably fine biker gloves give melee
damage bonus they do I think my Raider
set is good for me I also get melee
bonus okay
good um if anybody has um magazines
for treasure hunter let me no treasure
hunter okay oh yeah there is such thing
as Treasure Hunter magazine everybody
needs to take Band-Aids ra oh thank you
for everybody stay bandaged up Callie
take these thanks I'll take my bandaids
let's freaking go bi
boo take these thank
you if only I had a
GPS follow the Road North wait oh you're
going that way no oh no well I I wanted
to go north but I can't find a road that
goes north it's a bit of a windy
road is there an actual Road uh you
could have just taken the road from the
same Road North all the way was there a
road there's just Mountain the one from
our house oh no yeah yeah there's like
an intersection and then you go up into
the snowy area yeah I'll go there
now we'll probably anyone need food
I will never turn down a meal FAA okay
here's some food thank you how about
water ooh going for the mountain guys
anybody water Bott of water I need I
need water ooh pure mineral
water what V's got all the goods water
thank you bio do you need water I have
water okay dang it I feel like we've
finally really gotten into the groove of
the game and now we're going to stop
playing it dang we're so efficient
now I got so good yeah definitely the
first few days were pretty rough yeah it
was hectic but once you learn the stuff
that's what season 2 is for day one
things are going to up does anybody use
axes look how big this map is just for
chopping wood oh okay uh here's a level
four axe for chopping wood stone or
steel or iron
iron I only have a stone still oh like
yeah maybe gigy has yeah gigy what's
your uh axe
like um I have a level five iron fire
axe oh okay mine's level four so that
yours is B
okay is everybody here
[Music]
coming wait she got my steel Club
too yeah more basball bat steel Club
time it's so beautiful here I know it's
my favorite area snow
area no that's not
is don't run in any dire
wolves no not yet Are there many here
yeah diols are easy now though are they
are they yeah they they really are they
really are mind if I just never mind
he's not
open the traitor oh yeah you'll open
tomorrow probably by the time we finish
this to be
honest oh this will be a quick one am
here oh hold on I found I found some
more loot boxes in in the place that
we're about to Quest let me just open
them up thank you my
people oh you ran off mods off
okay coming back me mod my club real
quick brand new
club I know I don't need to drag them
but just let me drag
them did I bring this okay wait ki do
you have
Band-Aids yeah five oh boy
okay
water you think it's strong uh water I'm
fine right now why don't you take one a
bite of food would be nice okay have
some food
thanks yipp I wonder if it's
strong okay are we ready I'm ready know
who to give them
to let's run okay I am starting
woo um uhoh I don't like on my
microphone right off the bat oh yeah
lag oh hello he's really having a bad
time with the
club nobody likes to have a bad time at
the
club I always have a bad time at the
club same not much of a to clubs anymore
this G I mean that sounds like I ever
went to clubs but I really
didn't I know what I like and I know
what I don't
like h
the uncomfortable spaces
greed oh wow y'all Raider outfit level
five are you for real oh we just crafted
that
brao for
free this is making me mad this place he
goes oh there's stuff happening over
there
yep lots lots of stuff happening
yeah I I yeah we can
out hey they sprayed my knee these jerks
what
ouch
[Music]
again it's just too fun to use the club
I I know the shotgun is better
but
you're do that I'm bleeding ah okay hold
up not
anymore faa's bandage makes it
better yeah thank you haven't touched a
single enemy
yet yeah I'm sure more will come out in
fact there's some up here around here
some
workers just taking their time
oh well hello don't run past me
what level of cooking are you by the way
shouldn't you be Max by now no I wish
I'm
only I'm only 47 explosive
magazine take
these we explosive magazine right surely
I will get an electric shock if I try to
rench this right
chat possibility the
tra yeah there's a high
probability no they scaling all the all
the freaking
walls
wow but that's
10,000 not worth my
time how get out there yeah how didon we
have oh this is a
bar oh
no
who using these blocks for
good wow
Minecraft actually they don't have much
HP on these Gates there's a there's a
hole on the ceiling on the roof right
here yeah oh that's the the chest that I
hammered out for a long long
time oh there's a lot of there's a lot
of dudes oh hello uhoh bad doggy
hello dog sorry dog go away
dog bye
dog nice we did it we have that big
locked crate wa let me let me lock pick
oops how difficult is it to kill a bear
um without you got this O level five for
some yeah you're probably fine F that's
totally going to do the
trick oh there's more stuff back here
too oh wow
good uh here's bullets for kiaha bullets
for cie thank you also there's a safe
back here oh level five nerd outfit wow
w
um I partially unlocked it I think bi
will do a better job though which one
back here where I am I'm a little far in
but there's another I'm dropping ah
there she goes there's another Locker oh
I was muted I said does anybody has on
the nerd outfit or I can use it thank
you you can have it okay use it thank
you thank you that's so cute
didn't even need to make it where yeah B
will probably do better
inlock shorts your box
see that is cute is it Ultra silly style
I would definitely go around like
that
100% it's going to be cold in the snowy
area for you no problem cracking it open
oh safe uh what's in it do you do you
use iron Knuckles
fine no oh okay I'll give them to you
anyway anyone else who needs a
weapon
uh here's some
arrows do you want to help me wrench the
save okay I can wrench to wait you guys
have Salvage ability don't you wait it's
already open they just want the metal I
want the material
oh oh it does give you
stuff although I'm really I don't have
iron problems anymore Chad I our iron
problem days are over thanks to
Gigi never need IR again never again
wait I have ammo for you B boo I have
ammo for you guys
too 9
mm thank
you Callie I have a book for you oh is
there a shotgun Messiah book it's
Shooters weekly shotgun weekly a shotgun
weekly let's go thank you finana you
might want to learn this schematic this
might be useful for drones
later uh here you go thank you thank you
don't forget your ammo B
Boo there's some so nerdy oh thank you
thank you oh thank you thank you what
does it say yield armor CRA armor
crafting
also and then here's explosive explosive
weekly
oh here oh thank you also baseball bats
I can't kill this
bear don't push yourself figure it
out harder fight harder
I shot it with so many arrows oh
no you did what you
could yeah ranching the cars makes more
sense need the
gas yes are we going to a different
quest uh the trader just opened so I'm
just going to take TR tra okay good oh
to the tra
to get oning
I'm already the traitor I'm already
there why would you do that I want to
flex my B my my motor bike turn on I do
want to ride on your bike where's this
entrance to this guy was it here you
just got to open the doors won't open
for you is the thing what yeah it's
messed up what one how dare he not open
his doors for us oh because you you
don't have the quest yet him F okay
thank you oh I coming in anyway are you
breaking down the door oh I opened
it oh is that easy of
course oh
[Music]
yes can I put this on my
Knuckles he's so cool wow he's seen some
[\h__\h] try my little flashlight at
him hello let me talk to you doesn't
even need batteries
please oh another infestation
Quest a cigar I hope you're the b type
oh I need these
but oh I need Pockets I need antibiotics
do we have antibi we don't have
antibiotics do we but I can probably buy
these from trade J I don't know oh he's
not selling antibiotics
huh that I'm also infed yeah okay
was bunker Buster fing
Stone people have you read Pistol Pete
volume seven before let
me I'm going to heal myself yes I'm done
okay maybe these um es be good I'm for
confronting how do you when you have
different kinds of ammo how do you
choose which one you're using or does it
is there no way to I don't know I don't
know how to make it use my piercing
ammo hold R to when ah holding it you
can choose what you're reloading I guess
okay oh I see can I steal his
stuff steal I
can I'm looting his stuff you're looting
it he doesn't care I know he has a sign
that says you loot I shoot but he
doesn't seem to enforce it I don't know
I I think he might he might change his
over here ky dropping just a little bit
of ammo for you thank
you I'm going to make a shot his stuff
yeah steal his stuff there's a lot of
ammo around armed in danger Stu like
drop this way K yeah oh got a lot two
times shotgun shells behind you thank
you here here ni
sir very
helpful I'm
lost his
walls here C I can't believe he's just
letting us loot him he's nice I guess
he's afraid apprciate it oh can I use
this Forge no I guess not he thinks
we're super scary destroyed Forge has a
forge
head what a man he's got a couple forg
ah heads I have a forg ah head for you
too the cement mixer also had a for
welcome
back welcome back welcome back
enjoyed guns
ammo I wonder the other Traders have the
that kind of stuff I think I put it
away oh yes everything I need
all of them should have destroyed
benches and stuff I guess so I never
tried touching them I thought they would
like get angry at
me what's the worst they could
do oh yeah guys does this work on
non-machine guns too oh it's a schematic
again I need 70 steel and maybe a couple
more shotgun parts I bet would be good
steel is at home yeah I know we got
steel plenty of Steel that's good for
shotgun parts I think we also have
shotgun parts I'm not going to spend all
my money here you kidding me we might
have something yummy think Joel's gear
will save you not from what I'm
selling
cucumber does he sell sell good stuff
I'm so cucumber I think his stuff is
good it's better than the other Traders
the sweet smell of gun powder take a
look he's cool this guy is cool you do
know there's a do you guys remember when
we would get
dent I still get are you still
do sometimes you got to eat the
sandwiches yeah about all that so
hungry I don't know about all that I
just don't know all right I'm running
back to the house unless did you guys
take a quest um I took a quest back to
the house yeah I did take a quest all
right I'll go r I got the
quest everybody got I took one
too okay there's quest to the West FAS
and K is to the West yes shall we take
those real quick sure we real quick yeah
fa's first cuz it's on the way and then
Kiara's okay yeah oh FAA where are you
I'm coming Okay g are you still at the
old house yeah I'm not going to eat the
Sham sandwich
me okay I look like to you you can look
at my work I'm very excited to see the
Beavers work that's the sole reason I'm
coming don't worry
yeah I'll get Myck up by a hot lady with
a hot
motorcycle yeah oh I like that
horn I don't even know how to activate
it how do you x x
x yay
Dy we got to go up the
hill I I don't have my hands on your
waist anymore though sit in
the chilling can anybody give me a ride
oh yeah I can give you a ride and I'm
encumbered I'm outside
here no now I unlock it one
second oh this is the wrong way actually
why did I follow B boo
West West West you got to go
East oh this is nice this is luxurious
mhm we're really fast now
yeah the mot you are the queen of the
biker gang I am I provide all the bikes
I'm jealous I got to get a
motorcycle uh season two everybody will
everybody's on motorcycles next step is
everyone motorcycling CL W hey I'm in
here
here I think lag must have happened
again oh I hate
this through the Mountain St Mo's
Cathedral res Evil Six I think we're
going to the church up the hill yeah
there's a path there's a path look at
that ready for Halloween there's a
little line oh there's a bear kill it
kill it bear go go go
go very excited to kill that bear
oh he's
mad we
go I got to level up from
that leeching exp
yeah
y oh
wow lot of stuff okay if only he was
here we could renew our Triple R this
take this ra
no oh that's my I have to go to the
church why do people renew their vows
was one time not enough like do you not
believe each other no thank you I got
the wooden they want to have a big party
again just have a party then sometimes
you just need a party for no reason
sometimes I wake up and I'm like good
job me party party time yeah but why fra
itele myself that's kind because I just
want you to look at how in love we
are oh so you're just trying to show off
yes what happens when you
anymore and then you haven't Reed them
in like 40 years doesn't matter anymore
we're still in love it's okay we do it
when we
die you say
so exclamation mark is over here
okay God I hate those
churches there's always wacky [\h__\h] going
on
here
wait where you guys going Church we're
following I just told Cathedral why is
she biking over there what about me guys
where you guys headed yeah we got to
dock where are you
[Laughter]
going
everybody wait R yeah R is here wait I'm
here here okay where I'll take the wheel
wait oh oh yes
he I
was is everyone here yeah I was
[Applause]
[Music]
running ooh wow
ooh oh boy watch out there's a hole okay
there's a
hole check it out
holy oh oh you like it you know what I
do yeah it's really cool go all the way
around it's it's it's it's great thank
you big M
wa wa good job good job worked really
hard on this I can't be sarcastic or
insulting you're you're impressed
genuinely ironically good genuinely
impressed by the
I love your weapon
War it's over yeah you fall down it's
kind of over shotgun is very op and
don't fall in the trenches when you're
in the battlefield cuz you will not be
able to get your stuff
back oh yeah during the ho be careful
cuz we definitely won't be able
to I'm in the dang C catacombs oh wow F
found the
catacombs the
catacombs no cats
though what the point welcome to my CRI
than you to my
crib thank you oh actually that's
supposed to be a good thing oh drop
loot F said you stay down you hear that
sir listen to her oh down here's the
catacombs uh-oh there's
I hear a lot of
noises I hear a lot of noises but I
don't see figures zombies would be
they're up
here how do I take off uh a weapon mod
that I put on my weapon uh you unequip
your weapon and then hit modify and then
you drag it
out oh it's not letting me it's like
it's locked or
something okay
unequip I think I think I'm going in
circles don't of me oh there's
bookshelves around too to don't get lost
if you don't I mean I don't really know
how I would to say about that cuz you
know I am
okay oh I fell into a hole do not fall
into a
hole no I haven't maybe avoid any of
that try remember which way I went yeah
she's fine she's living
open up FBI didn't know we were playing
is here what are you
hiding oh maybe
nothing oh it's a book I can't where are
you where did you
go oh do you see okay come to the when
you're facing the house all right fall
in where you at right now fallen I am so
oh
my I
was they're never going to come
here why would you go this I was
thinking is this the most impressive
thing you've ever done I think
yes oh my God I'm going to leave again
of mine EXC careful excuse me I got to
go this way oh on fire that girl is on
get out of
here that seems
bad how do you get out of here
whoa who okay I opened up a big
congregation is here oh no did I punch
you Ki Oh maybe it's okay you have
bandid secret Hall yeah oh my God this
is a
lot you found something nice too oh lag
lag lag lag lag lag you should probably
get out of the way before I get myself
hurt Hammer Time Hammer
Time another
one we just Disturbed the big zombie
party they deserve it was it a wedding
oh behind you a beautiful wedding
there's some other stuff you can look at
though I just took uh what did I
take it forgets immediately what she
took classic more interesting for
someone
else I'm full zombos
at the
zomos I'm very F there's a still a
cooking magazine up here I have no space
for
it oh I'll read cooking yeah well she
still got to make us more delicious
foods wait I picked it up out theall one
slot but that one I don't know maybe if
you can pick that stuff up too I can
pick it
up actually have two
magazines oh I'm actually done with the
fist I don't know if anybody
[Music]
else I don't really I don't really
personally aspire to be a a Fister so
maybe Gigi should be read made it in
there
yeah her Destiny shut up
where did you die shut up G how did you
die shut up somebody behind this wall it
sounds like it oh yeah of
course whoa who was here where's your
loot should I do I need to break any of
these spikes for your loot no I got it
are you I'm at the top of the
church oh
Jesus are you on the roof oh there's
birds at the top of the church ah
that'll do it who would have
thought get down oh
here
oh this is cool how does one climb
higher that bird was the last
one
okay where is where is the big area with
loot cuz there's always got to be a big
area with loot so we got to find that
maybe up there roof you think maybe how
do you get up there ladder ladder on the
right ladder on the right wait I think I
see something suspicious that might have
surely there's a better puff but I just
don't have
eyeballs oh gosh I feel like I'm going
to fall off the roof it's
slippery careful it did feel
slippery I found the loot where was it
where's it's it's in the it's in the
tower at the tippy top I know I'm going
to need help though cuz I'm almost out
of space okay uh let's see where not
sure how to get
there I'm bird forcing my way in right
now with my hammer through it's very
scary up here oh I think I see it's okay
there's no bades left but it's so
slippery I'm the jump King watch oh oh
this
how did you get there people I'm I can't
find the right way I'm on the roof
though let
me no I'm not no I'm not I'm dying oh
like without dying my hardcore broke my
head my entire leg I was like oh did you
miss the jump I saw that you didn't see
anything you didn't see anything from
there I guess just going to have to be
encumbered B
where's somebody else I think yeah 37
I'm
coming I'm here welcome to the
St what's in
it lots of stuff you got to be more
specific you got to be more specific
don't have much room either but the mega
curtain Mega curtain spans two
stories this curtain all the club oh I
have four available points what the heck
uh who's learning wiring electrical I'm
learning sort
[Music]
of and electrical trap crafting yeah
that too sort of oh I found another
Millie robot
turret we have a friend oh we're going
to be so decked out for defend es for
this
hord nice yeah should we start preparing
about now might be
yeah okay I guess that's it people right
I took some things did you did you take
the stuff out of all the boxes yes you
did okay cool looks pretty empty
mhm uh how to I guess let's see for here
again oh lockpicking I probably should
[Music]
oh robbing some grapes
again
oo I like that I found another shipping
crate nice that I have no space
for yeah I got to eat
then I'll probably head back to the
house well we do there was one more
Mission wasn't there uh I don't have
room for
the going home might be the best idea
then I too am cucumber the
max the Trader's on the way
so right yeah yeah they're mad at me for
some reason I'm not sure why you
but
why yeah why are these zombies so angry
at me after I robbed the
grave gee I
wonder really doesn't make a lot of
sense we're taking a
shortcut WR is that damage your bike by
chance uh damages
me I got some exp though he so mad
bro chill I like shortcuts and I like
crying too no problem
50% carrying capacity ohuh oh you woke
up
again didn't expect them pretty
resilient there's so many graves for you
choose
one
okay where is it's so
loud are still fighting
FAA no I'm headed
home house how with what how on my on my
my little bike why why why why why why
why why why why why why why why I got I
got to get going I got to get home every
minute you yeah I'll I'll catch up to
you
now I'll make you regret that you took
your mini bike or
bicycle I built this to impress you why
I am impressed I'm very impressed but
you don't like it do you not like
motorcycles are
environment so
cool this is
like like a married man in the middle of
Crisis getting himself a motorcycle
while his wife wants a
minivan why didn't you get a minivan for
our family
they said I don't know I just really
like them like can I not just make one
of my dreams come true for
once you can you can you're free to ride
your motorcycle well I thought you would
be happy about it and appreciate it I do
and that we sh ride into the desert to
get a bunch of aloe really fast got wait
my
turn keep your head where I can see see
uh so all
this okay we have plenty of these but do
you want to ride home yes please okay
I'm so heavy now maybe try another
trick oh oh sorry sorry do we need
robotics Parts I don't think we do do we
let's I hold on I'm going to hold on to
them just in case though because I'm
going to be so mad later on if it turns
out we need them taxi driver I'll leave
you a good review later yes please Uber
good review thank you here
shovel and I have a discount you li
where to go I don't think there's really
anything that I need to go here I feel
like my timer wrong
again oh no can someone
make eight metal fences and railings
they seem to be pretty cheap but they
need a forge and I'm at the old house I
can probably make some why why
just uh because I'm making like a small
Tower and I don't want us to fall down
so I'm trying to snipy snipy Tower yeah
a little snipy
Tower
nice that would be very
useful how did I break my leg you broke
your leg a little boo I have trails and
happy H I also need honey again hunting
that's a
ride yeah isn't it look I have a you
have a drink to the side so if you get
thirsty you can drink yeah
exactly I'm eating right now yeah okay
back the Uber come it's like the high
the high effort Uber with like you play
games in the back and
with yeah and they're like you need any
Adil any
[Music]
ipren any
mirx what does that one do
I don't know I never tried it wait isn't
that LAX D is it LAX oh yeah good
thinking
vibo yeah that is what that would
be I'm getting really hungry
too you know who was also getting hungry
K the zombies tring to cook no I mean
IRL yeah but the zombies are getting
getting hungry any banana today no no
banana banana
you have like 20 minutes I think to get
a snack IRL oh yeah you got some I'll
myself and eat my Pringles
Pringles I don't know what I want to eat
sounds good
yeah do you think this is High Enough
full snipy tower pretty good yeah looks
good honey honey honey honey honey honey
yeah honey got real honey
[Music]
gotcha
good
actually meat out of
meat okay that IRL hunger and the
in-game hunger
are unbearable both getting in h I'm
pretty hungry too I have not eaten
today not at all today or no well
typically I don't eat until like
NE it is like almost 2:00
p.m. it's like 10 p.m. for me oh and you
haven't eaten all
day all day really bad it's normal it's
normal just kidding it's
normal
huh huh no that's just my normal routine
make some rice dang it well then again
if you go to sleep you you won't really
need that energy so
I just playing games I don't really need
the energy I need the carbs until
later yeah we're just playing games
games doesn't take that much energy yeah
just some mental energy I guess checking
out some things gamer eating schedule
oops thanks for all the amazing work on
it I'm so glad I have things to say but
I'm waiting till the
end but I've been having a great speech
speech speech spech speech speech speech
spech
before before the ra oh yeah let's do
like a motivational a motivational
like thing where you go down the line on
your horse and we like you die not this
day yeah it is not this day it is not
this day what say you you know all that
stuff I see I think Brothers Brothers
yes that's right for the
emperor for froto in the ring
yeah that too I suppose middle her yeah
what
you oh I huzzah huzzah I don't
think we have enough steel for me to
make my gun oh I need to make sure I can
make my gun in time let me get that
steel I just put 100 Steel in oh heck
yeah thank
you ooh crunchy ooh
M I made a walnut bot salad yesterday oh
that sounds really good it was yum it's
definitely yum ladies enjoy
it see um steel
Springs can you take the shotgun shells
out of the chest no I haven't taken the
yet you should take them I will I will
too a little bit thank you need more
wood all right let me make uh shotgun
really quick cuz it's going to take
time CeCe shooting at me please
L what did you do to make her mad is the
question she didn't like it exactly
thank you she was flashing at crony she
no wasn't went away and then she kept
running after her I wasn't I was showing
her my bald head side here
yeah it's very unco BL trust cannot
carry you far the
ammo shotgun shell wor believe some
thank you I'm on your side screamers I
hear time for you
oh she's in the
pit yikes I got
you where's everyone oh I'm
coming oh the turret's doing work so
cool when they rag doll it doesn't mean
they're dead I got to remember that
yeah this two is birth RP what are you
talking talking about nothing what no I
want to know I know I sound incredulous
but I just want to know what does that
mean I don't I don't
know I I say it Gigi I I
don't why say it I don't D they told me
to say it she's silly say it of my own
will gig is always silly this maxing 24
I appreciate it say what this this two
is birth role
playful what put on your head now sorry
okay wish I knew what it
me this needs to be another chest um B
did you need grenades yes please okay
I'm going to give you some grenades gig
are you the only one using arrows I
think R is too I am using arrows yes I
have exploding arrows but thank you oh
oh oh I'm going to put a picture on the
wall yes take these exploding arrows but
I need to explain to you how to
knowingly use specific
armor if you are on your bow I guess you
press R you hold R and then you choose
the ammo you're shooting with now make
sure when you're using exploding arrow
that there's not any funno or so around
it could explode in the
vicinity take this beer I
have Bo boom bo
yeah I'm excited yay every time I'm in
the street I hear you do you want rotten
flesh in the ingredient chest or
elsewhere yes in the ingredience I have
the shotgun mod for you you do what kind
of shotgun mod I'll take it regardless
shotgun mod oh that's a good one you can
go ahead and put it in the mod chest I
think
that that will be
nice thank
you story still fighting out there huh
are they I still hear sound do I need to
go help how to use armor piercing I
wonder I guess no what are they
attacking maybe a tree or something
oh the turret oh yeah I think they're
quiet now can't find them anymore
turret's doing
work some good baseball bats here for
oh where are they in the huh maybe
inside or in the no huh not in the M
could they be on the
roof could they be why why would they
choose to be on the they might be deep
in the maybe or maybe cuz they're
smart I found
it it was in the mold oh okay I'll be
[Music]
right
finally armed and
ready okay I made a lot more gun
who's worried about their ammo not being
enough I think I have like a
thousand
okay you think you got enough ammo yep I
have plenty I have like over 500 round
for a shotgun is just a lot sure if
that's enough you don't think
so I mean I'll take more are you going
to melee
too well M melee I'm just going to do my
you know Club this endless
ammo end and in terms of uh armor do we
have anybody with a chest piece below
four probably not at this point right I
think so I made it for nothing where's
my mini I have a forged ahead for you
I'm putting all the boxes all the books
in the Box the tech ones too can use
this we
should I made my bow pink it's so pretty
yeah yay yes sir I've already read the
shotgun
Massi I'll read a couple of
these team
work good idea fly Decked
Out G look I got an electrifying stick
why are you trying to hit me with it I'm
I'm I'm 5 m away from you oh sure 5 me
right next to me ladies
ladies I just wanted to show her my
stick I don't understand hitting me with
her stick
not okay I'm going I'm going to the
whole house okay I'm going to head there
soon
too me
too see my houseing thank you one thing
I need
is food but I can get it myself no we
got plenty of house welcome back I got
it thank you can you bring us food okay
I bring you food thank
you what did you want for steel iron uh
it's called let me see see it's called
metal fences and railing it needs iron
and clay
uhhuh how
many 10
[Music]
okay I
course um I'm going to try to get some
more aloe can I borrow somebody's
car oh is it like wait car you can use
our bike
where is
it somewhere outdoors in front oh is
this it need the truck the cool one
thank you I will be right back so close
to being a make definitely be right back
with that speed yeah K would you also be
able to uh give me any armor if possible
that's need the truck because I am I
have time for this I don't have time for
this do I it's already not yeah it's
already probably should go IE what the
what are the levels on yours CC I don't
have that much time anymore but let me
let me know uh the levels on my
hopefully we have enough bandaid don't
don't forget to break oh I'm going to
I'm going to grab bandaids and healing
items from the the new house uh
soov and
Sho it would be nice I'll give you a
better uh need Alo cream I have one nice
[Music]
um I wonder if I can make it
so okay are I don't need
them we're looking
organized oh that was storm is starting
storm
scary it's almost
time H luy docky luy docky fine this
will be easy bring in everything I've
got yeah everybody bring your
aame got P shot level four when I have a
level for example in my skills right and
then it says like level one level two
and then the third one even though I
have skill points it's like a lock how
do I you have to uh level up your main
stats so whatever attributes it is level
up the attributes stat and it should be
unlocked as it levels up c a better
level one so for this one okay I cannot
make more than that I I don't have time
have time no problem I think we're
good so for this
one and how do I know what the head uh
so it just it's the stat on the very top
of the page so the same page that you're
looking at should say a tribute whatever
oh okay so level that
classic going back to the original house
the first one that we on my way
to in that it all comes full circle
yeah the house that we built together
the first one we found together I want
to set up like three different turrets
hopefully that'll be good
too yeah let's do it yeah for
sure have no doubs we're going to do it
no
matter no I don't want to break a
leg no don't break a
leg I found a
chicken is there food at the old house I
suppose yeah
no did somebody pick up all the food and
take it to the old house I'm bringing
some I think somebody else got some cuz
the crate was empty when I looked in it
I'm bringing all the the health items
but I I didn't bring food oh maybe I
have all of it we don't have that much
hopefully it's
enough we can share with each other I
got gr meat for days repair kit I
haveen what did I put them in did I make
them oh God oh God
God come to me I put the food in the
food box in the old house
okay thank you very
[Music]
much here we
go very soon you better get over here
I'm almost
there oh this scary
it'll be fine it'll be fine snip the
chicken they heartless where should we
put our bikes I Pi your food comes from
I put the bike inside the house if you
can drive it into the house I would
suggest doing that okay we'll do what's
a braan is that what I have right now oh
you need a
Band-Aid oh yeah okay that helped I
think oh my God it's so well
fortified I wish there was a way to so
hungry to shoot maybe a bit close in in
the my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God oh my God oh my
God she fell she's dead it's
over get out of
here I don't know how okay guys don't be
very careful my
backpack oh no oh no
care get it out I thought that I drive
my bike
and I'll get out get out that's why I
said be very
careful oh there the one thing to not
do stay on the
bike I wanted to ride the bike into the
house but I should have just picked it
up dang
it well at least we know that the
zombies really have a hard time getting
in the house I was just testing it out
yeah test I'm here weap are you using
again I'm using a bow do you want to
come with me on my tower on my snipy
tower yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah are come
here come here all
right okay your backpack should be free
are you sure the spikes kind of look a
little oh God it work that's a nice
[Music]
place eventually I'll go into the field
and fire everyone
okay wait who's that oh people right
behind you is a dead chicken if you want
to scavenge the dead chicken Jes oh
Jesus I'm going to die wait we have more
no over here over
over I I put the healing in the
ingredients chest okay oh God I
man C dot dot we can we can pick up the
it's fine it's fine backpack for her I
know it's hard it's fine all her loots
in there it's
okay it's on the top this time it didn't
fall to me wait where's the ingredients
chest that was the plan wait you don't
mean at the new house do you no no no in
the in the in the old house where it's
going to be very good the fortification
wait did you take the ones out of the
healing chest yes okay there's my bag my
bike though in the old house or new
house old house okay uh
it it's in the F bike yeah wait we had
way more didn't
we uh is that all we
have yes oh I have some in my inventory
I can put some more in a thank
you have like six Stacks before we did I
thought so
okay that's all that's all I found put
the B okay well that's that's fine
ow I am so ready maybe I gave a lot out
maybe see hair
kit is crony
here not in
thec can you leave real quick I want to
build rail
links is that okay thank you
had the better shotgun did you make an
even better one no it's just a level two
pump action instead of the one that she
has yippe says crony I'll go find her my
hero she up there she might be up there
oh nice fence
H trying you in the hole it's kind of
annoying oops she was behind you of
course she was behind me can I pick up
stuff that I've built or do I have to
destroy
it I honestly don't know I think you
have to pick it up um but it might it
might be effective who claimed this land
maybe the person who claimed the land
can pick it up only maybe oh who claimed
the land
I don't know who claimed the land who
claimed this land whose land is this
whose land are we on oh did she pick up
the wrong thing land are
we Kelly is this your land I mean kind
of can you come and pick this up for me
pick what up hold on I got to give sh in
the middle of nowhere a fence I didn't
put a fence down no I put it down but
apparently you might have to pick it up
oh okay hold up I'm coming I can break
it stop
break I think she got it okay we've got
lots of food and Buffs in the food chest
and make sure you have food and water
and heels and everything I think we're
good okay let's break it they not going
to be able to take us can I break it
yeah you can break it jump too high why
you sto
me cuz I wanted Cy to pick it
up specifically we have Palace like this
in the back too claimed the land so you
think that you have to
like I'm going to get down a bit
more I'm more of a lower
shooter dang this is well
fortified yeah SP really are just kind
of broken honestly like we can survive
to any
hord this the spikes is just there's so
many if we had one more week we could
have iron spikes yeah yeah we could make
sure to eat four bites in the in the
chest those will give you damage
reduction how long does that go on 6
minutes oh okay oh it's in a chest
okay here we go I will yell before I
throw my fire F okay nice
okay right here we go you can try to
drink recog too it will increase your
range damage but I don't know if it
makes you
drunk oh is it starting let's
go
fin let's freaking go do your best
they're coming from the back the back
hill back hill back hill okay good thing
I put a trench back there too there's a
trench well oh
boy oh it's so dark
we go go go something hurts you you are
so like uh you're blending in with with
the darkness on it's hard to see hard to
see the green as
well wait why does this make me drunk oh
my God I thought I was immune to this no
the alcohol is it's just not beer well
that's fine I can deal with this it's
the first time I'm using
this
you oh gosh oh that's okay that's fun I
must watch
out there's a lot of cop zombies
spawning huh not surprise what are you
arresting us for what did we do we do oh
yeah my leg is broken I have you not
harboring a criminal oh someone got
inside what uhoh that's not good I
definitely closed the doors uh not
inside inside yeah close the front door
if you can you should be closed but I
mean someone got inside
I fortification
maybe oh great should have checked that
first it's
fine I'm so
far where are they all coming from there
he's going to blow he's blow oh
God uhoh I can't do you have
a I'm going to fix my spikes I have PS
too you need some no no I'm see
double yeah it definitely gets kind of
laggy about this point seems like I
can't repair my assault rifle that's
weird
okay wait how are you trying to do it I
click on it and the repair to me is
spray out for some reason do you have
a I have six my leg my leg it's okay
I'll go out on the field with my rod I'm
fire watch out okay in fire
run run
okay are they still coming from the sou
you to blow watch
out
I
um you dro the r
that's another door hold yes can you can
you give me back I'm I'm outside right
now but okay zombies are on the back
uhoh oh they're in the house oh
God okay uh we can take him we can take
him I'm taking a med break see
oh oh is that setting our spikes on fire
uh might it might be but it it is also
helping Kill the
Zombies true
that yeah it is I need just one yo that
range on his bom is
crazy oh is this not what I
mean that's you hold line C Hold the
Line
that oh not this one this
one I don't want to use
that where are they I can't see the
back it's so hard to see we should light
up the area
yeah you think they're changing where
they're coming from they all want to
come from that side today I don't know
why they're switching it up yeah she's m
they
know nice does it kill them when they're
SP or oh they're coming from the front
now now you want to come from the front
really really they're testing all our
defenses I see how it
is this isn't much of a long range
weapon I will say is fa there I don't
want to yeah that's I am there okay I
know you're always there you're
everywhere oh that's
CH like naked
that Z yeah she died I think oh no I'm
going to throw again for a
run where am I oh
hello protecting my front
porched slipping into
them keep running keep running
it's good when you amass these hordes
you can just shoot it right in the
middle like a hurting
dog run in C oh no that's C I'm
sorry okay you didn't hit me it's fine
keep
running really hard to tell keep running
we need to dye our armors just so that
we can tell each other apart that would
be a good idea actually ouch
oh boy spray pray spray spray oh gosh on
fire yeah yeah I'm throwing a lot of
fire fire fire am I right ladies night
to
fire which one
je oh that's good that's good that's
good that's good
uhoh my arm is broken no
you do not want's arm to be broken yeah
it's so lagging it is really lagging
hard is it
fire I'm just wildly swinging hoping
that it's hitting something in real
time oh God we don't oh God is it the
fire it can't handle nothing's moving
nothing's moving we might we might die
cuz uhoh oh wait wait wait wait wait
coming back com back coming back so back
at least it's not just me the zombies
are getting fast forward pretty quick
though I'm going to pause on the fire
throw down oh God what's
happening I oh please no fire oh ah
because
my oh God play the
leg bling the lag I'm going to blame the
lag for that that was ridiculous
a cast that was ridiculous okay is a
cast better than a splint definitely oh
far as I'll be
fine I freaking
away I wonder if this is any
better right now the lag is okay oh no
that's it's okay it's puning at
everybody okay this is a bad bad place
to spawn H turret help
me oh my
God where are
you are you dying up there uh I was
dying but I'm back inside now I'm just
going to get some he oh go oh no so I'm
struggling a bit but lag lag lag lag lag
lag I'm really drunk right now so don't
walk in front of me cuz I'll almost
certainly hit you by oh the game is not
responding I'm just drinking and
punching oh no Cy did you get kicked out
of the game I got DC yeah happen to all
of us I have a feeling no yeah let me
see
um oh man that was
intense This Is How They really beat
us so crazy up they knew it would be the
only way to beat us yeah exactly hope
you get back in Callie I'm doing my best
I'm doing my best also join the party
again when you're here oh yeah let me
uh let me know when you're back in wave
over maybe you're doing great G thank
you
Shori get him get
him F when the next enemy come comes
please look when I when I Boop them with
a with the thing they fly away I've seen
it I've seen it amazing it looks so
silly is somebody out there right now
can oh they're coming from the side the
side okay would be good to loot in
between but no not enough time oh I
guess so
yeah the I think it will
despawn
Hy for the first raid it wasn't too bad
wait I can Loot and shoot I don't mind
me tooing from too many spikes you think
oh there's a cop inside in the house
it's okay it's okay spikes had no ping
he already fell into the ow into the fit
a pit he fits into the pit that's
probably fine
then how did he get in there I wonder
[Music]
okay do good it is definitely struggling
to load but that's okay oh
no it's like wow there's a lot going on
right now in the
server going on right together by gum
duct tape and duct tape maybe there's a
way to strengthen the server somehow for
season ah he's
[Music]
jumping we got a
jumper it's okay there are definitely
enemies that can uh Jump free blocks
high I'm so good right
now how drunk are you how many fingers
am I holding up yeah how many VI have
you had
tonight bird bird bird oh my god oh
another bird what's that oh my God back
on my
porch is that a
bird the hole
wait oh that was I'm so sorry I thought
you were zombie oh
no spr the hats got handled over there I
have night vision so everything is in
black and white so I can't tell who's
wearing what oh that sounds so terrible
okay oh my god oh wo wo wo welcome
back I'm so sorry it's okay yeah come
from the side let's get him bird bird
bird bird got
it coming up the
hill without lag I feel like I would
shoot a little bit better yeah the blame
is not completely on me it's okay we're
doing good good we're hanging in there
we are we
are nice the go look so
funny got to back
up good thank you guys might be
concussed only good to have you killed
yourself I died don't kill kill yourself
yeah maybe don't do
that sexy poers like in Minecraft that
can collect the
loot can't right a Zombie
Farm definitely like something like a
farm that you can build but I don't know
about if there
hoppers Chad are there
hoppers need Hopper mod for this game
I'm getting smarter about the spikes
he was avoiding oh yeah let me let me
reinvite call I think that wave is over
call get in the party thank you is it
over the wave is over does anybody have
honey or
antibiotics yeah right now are we don't
tell me the music stopped the music
stopped but it stopped yesterday too and
we still got oh wait no it's still going
it's still going it's still
going which side is it this time loot
loot can I did not see any
antibiotics in the chest yeah I don't
see oh there is one in my chest next to
the laundry a medical chest I have it
yeah take it take
it oh the music stopped which chest my
chest is next to the laundry there chest
there's the
laundry H yeah in the basement floor ah
that real laundry
it's over oh it's over it's over you
really think it's over I mean the music
stopped yeah we could we could take more
zombies that was we're so strong we're
so good we are strong they need to
spread them out a little bit
more they always end early and we're
getting like no freaking loot I have so
much stuff
left
H wish we could get pick up some lo I
got some a lot of loot but it's next to
the spikes
spes if I want to go all right yeah that
makes sense I can't I can try to jump
okay I
jumped like a giant CR someone someone
did we did it we did
[Applause]
it we did it there were some ises but
honestly it was fine we're so good
[Music]
the way our Fort is fortified by now is
kind of
[Music]
crazy we got really really really
fixated on how to how to fortify this
place it's a little too good they can
barely touch us
yeah can't touch
this it's the song that plays at the
credits kids tou this
[Applause]
do you want to tell us some words
yeah none of
[Music]
you well well well well well well well
well well well well well well well well
well well
well Victory Speed my my soldiers my
soldiers yes um so boy soja boy tell
him hey um thanks for playing want to go
up there yeah I'm getting to the top of
smack position and talking down above
everybody uh I just asked for the server
to be made and tried to figure out dates
so I don't really I also asked for art
to be made that's all that I really did
but to be honest people people joining
in you guys made me very happy joining
in the server you know I wanted to do
something more casual
G um I wanted to do something more more
like casual just play a game with each
other kind of thing instead of like
something that was like super hardcore
RP or like a hardcore server seven days
in a row was pretty rough though I think
next time we'll maybe space it out a
little bit seven days we die yeah days
yeah but it was it was a great time and
I am very very grateful that you guys um
made time to be here CeCe are you good
CeCe I think you're dying Cece Cece uh
oh I just I just did all I just had such
a nice
time she going crazy no I tried to get
some loot sorry that's okay
understandable um but yeah I'm very
happy because um even with you guys I
feel like um why me say even why am I
saying even with you guys no you guys
how do I say I feel like we all got a
lot closer
and I'm very happy I get I don't know
how to get close to to people very
easily without doing things like playing
games and stuff like that so bonding
experience together I feel like yeah it
was just fun playing a game together you
know I hope we get
to yeah let's do it again thank you for
[Music]
[Applause]
organiz wait wait can we somehow take a
group picture maybe if we're on our
bikes we could
yeah get my
motorcycle yeah Kiara's got the cool
motorcycle oh no she worked hard for
that motor oh
fa I don't want to
die no my sweet get out of my Spike trap
I don't know how to get
out SP traps okay they're too deadly
excuse me I'm scared I'm so scared right
now excuse me all right I'll go and get
my I'm stuck wait wait wait wait wait
take this exit thank you thank you you
made it you made it
[Music]
so okay I made it
yay all right let's line up our bikes
yeah maybe with the house in the back
yeah yeah that's a cute idea let's do
that can I have my SP my
you have your
what get on your the
back the
bik I think this might be the
wrong oh no this one's
mine it it it has my storage in it
yeah does anyone have space on their
bike I do you can get on you can you
unlock oh okay oh wait it is unlocked it
was the other
one okay I feel like I'm in
anpg and I at the cash Shop Mount that
is like super
expensive how about we I think we're at
the wrong angle guys I think if we want
to get the spikes we got to do like here
let's get in front of it and then back
into it so like right here and then back
it up just don't back into the SP down
the hill just do not back into the
spikes it's very
important I'm scared okay is that the
only one without a bike right now and a
bike partner brought one I think there's
one at home oh wait I have I have a
bike got a bik you got B okay yeah yeah
I think I can get a good shot like this
with the sunrising in the back oh
God watch out for the
[Music]
spikes manuver this thing
wait wait I really can't I don't know
how to get into into position H okay you
got to back it up got to back into it
back it
up up I'm really bad at
that I'll do a big turn or like oh yeah
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah I wish I could
make the names go
away if there's a way to do that don't
erase our names they're just kind of
overlapping weird we all look the
same we do all look the same never
[Music]
mind this is really
difficult gamer skills gamer
skills I have an idea why don't you pick
it up and position again and then you
jump you're so
right so smart
Okay easy easy here uh oh perfect yeah y
oh wait it's locked again it's locked
again okay unlock okay there we go yay
oh we look so cool in my picture oh my
[Music]
God ride seven seven ride
days ride seven days to
ride more can can you mention that we
are exactly seven right now we are
exactly seven people seven Riders to
ride wait buty is eight right yeah we're
eight it was almost
perfect almost perfect follow me in one
line let's ride into the sun run the
sunlight
together Bad to the Bone plays in the
background or can't touch this or
something
everyone I know what it looks like we'll
see you in season
[Applause]
two thanks everybody for
playing See You Again somewhere out
there and they all rode off into the
sunset the
end
yipp well technically this is sunrise
the biker gang so cool
yipp yeah oh don't die don't
die to
die I guess that's it fun
[Laughter]
yeah still not very good at riding this
bike bye everybody uh I will I will be
reading some I will be reading super
chats and the like so I will continue
for a little bit longer oh yeah let's
see let's see catch you later everybody
ha peace out everyone playing thanks so
much everybody thank you girls it was a
pleasure it's been a lot of fun I
enjoyed being your
armor you did a great job I'm looking
forward to my motorcycle next next
season yeah next season yes motorcycle a
little bit different times maybe yes
different probably different
time all right bye everybody I'm mute
lat
peace this is probably the oh I probably
should have press Escape when I took by
it doesn't matter
bye oh the people are leaving I'm I'm
going to leave too and so myy also
decided to to head out from the server
she said exit and
left seven days to die
the end I have some super chats to read
so I'm going to be reading those uh I
can read the ones from this stream first
though that seems
apt seems like a good idea to read those
and then we also have some from the TCG
card simulator stream as well did I not
read those I guess I didn't read
those okay let's see great job y oh that
was fun that was fun I was very happy to
organize I use organize Loosely because
I feel like I organized enough I just
asked for the server really and uh got
the art commissioned and figured out the
the schedule a little bit you know with
some help from CCE cuz she's way better
at schedule stuff than I am but yeah
that's that's all that I did but but I
still am really glad that I was able to
pull everybody together and for
everybody that did that did uh get
really into the game I feel like you
know we got closer and it was fun and
yeah I thought that it would be good to
have something like that together that
we could all enjoy as hello it was more
on the Casual side that's not a very
casual G well uh how do I say it's
casual kind of in a in a way it's hard
to explain I feel like though even
though for example crony didn't play
every single day she still was able to
to participate in the battles and such
so we helped each other and I think that
that made a big
difference um so
yeah it's not that casual it can get
intense depending upon yeah casual in
the sense that we didn't have to RP the
whole time exactly I didn't want like
rping Etc unless they wanted to do it
but I I just wanted us to be able to
play a fun game together and I I think
it was I think it was a great success I
feel happy about it definitely think we
would to tried time next time and maybe
like different number of sessions at one
time Etc but I'll be working on that so
leave it to me and yeah I think Kiara
will also probably yeah I I hope she
participates again she she had a lot of
fun she really wants to season to I
think that we'll probably do a time
that's a little easier for her and
Cecilia this time around what time are
you thinking um I don't know it's
probably going to need to be like
nighttime Japan time or so but we will
see we'll see which is going to be rough
for PST
but but we got to make sure that it's
it's a little a little easier for them
this time
around
yeah if time doesn't progress when
nobody's in the server then you can skip
days or even a week in between yeah that
is true we can definitely skip sometimes
uh to to make it so that we don't have
to play seven days in a row so I think
we should try that oh Big Ups to jprs
NSR one last raid with the ladies bonka
I'm good cie thank you very much to G
Harden and Jimmy Hernandez thank you
sorry Jeremy Hernandez why did I read
Jimmy is my eyesight really that bad
right now Jeremy Hernandez thank you so
much for the Supa and also for the
gifted membership a big UPS to p b thank
you so much and a big UPS to lean thank
you so much to Brutus salad as well and
bacon Slayer who says bacon bacon bacon
bacon bacon bacon bacon bacon jedar that
does sound yummy I'm not going to lie
Chase Hunter 22 thank you so much and
the Big Ups to tr D try fingers butth
hole it's not funny myy it's not funny
we're not playing that game right now
even when we are playing that
game it's a little funny sometimes thank
you to Gigi for the redirect Big Ups to
V faction thank you so much show them
your base skills
hahaa we will have a base Arc once I tun
it properly AKA when I have time for
anything
else a big UPS to highly flamable man
thank you for the red super chat that
was very kind of you highly flamable man
you hanging in there being highly
flamable and all that not standing next
to any open Flames are we not cooking
too intensely are we be careful out
there been a dead beat for years just
recently in a position to show it I
suppose thank you for the countless
hours of entertainment you are very
loved take care of yourself to all the
other members I love you and your fans
too hugs and love for all take care what
a kind thing to say highly flammable man
wow youve set my heart on fire thank you
much appreciation a big UPS to osaki and
a big UPS to smelly Mayo wow
stinky a big UPS St frony 18K thank you
thank you to kondik Saloon as well as
highly flammable man again hope that
you're sleeping well and of Big Ups to
endless for the red super chat who says
and I quote just wanted to say a big
thank you for organizing this event it's
been a lot of fun to watch over the past
week glad you've been having a good time
I too really enjoyed myself I wish I
could have played yesterday but it was
just not possible but I still had a
fantastic time every single other day
that I did play which was every day but
I didn't stream I think the third or so
a big UPS to chase Hunter 22 thank you
so much big UPS to you yes big ups and
future nice sponsorship Yesterday by the
way that was fun it was fun fun silly
game silly maxing with you guys as
always always my favorite a big UPS to
sarth Lynn times 2 thank you so much and
a big UPS to FCO for the redact and
thank you to chase Hunter 22 thank you
thank you the big UPS to Dylan thank you
Jacob langlet thank you and a big UPS to
donger bread thank you the server broke
before the guard did Shori show showed
up to cheer us on by saying you're doing
great G and U Chase Hunter 22 says dang
it serveron thank you again Chase 122
for another Super Chat PR's Ru thank you
so much that was a great series I look
forward to season two thank you so much
I hope that you enjoy season 2 I hope
that for North America beats it isn't
too difficult for you guys but it'll
probably be night time in Japan just
maybe maybe like late Japan nighttime
would be good cuz I don't mind staying
up a bit later than usual especially if
we play in like 4our segments or so
we'll see a big UPS to
KI for the red super chat and the but
but but p
b thank you so much but but but B but y
really appreciate it thank
you hope that means all the I and and JP
can play I will definitely invite
them a big UPS to Don bread thank you so
much great pilot season and really glad
a good core group was there every day
for the zoms indeed yeah they really
banded together I'm so happy to see how
many people got into it too really glad
Big Ups to Moon hang and thank you
to thank you thank you I'm glad that
that we were able to entertain in some
way by shooting some zoms getting
stronger slowly but surely together
thank you to Aunt brny 18K and Maxwell
the first thank you so much a big UPS to
JP RS NSR was so much fun thanks for
organizing it C 10 out of 10 seeing
y'all Kill the Zombies meet balino says
thank you so much for making these 7
Days Unforgettable you're welcome look
forward to more thank you to hang thank
you for organizing this collab it's been
a really fun week and AAS AAS sends many
Dancing Dead beats thank you so much
ataz that was seven days to
die now let's see about
yesterday's sponsorship stream just a
few to to read out to you guys a big UPS
to oniton 3 and thank you to jprs NSR
been seeing this game floating around
apparently there's an anime for it I
didn't know about that a big UPS to
zator for 20 gifted my memberships hope
you guys are looking forward to the
membership streams this month the one on
the 31st you guys are not going to want
to miss so get excited for that thank
you so much zator for the many gifted
memberships a big UPS to
spank kfp andhe who says and I quote
y'all y'all that was by far probably one
of my favorite like little moments was
the the name not being not being a way
to say hey and just be in the dude's
name I didn't know
that I thought everyone was just like yo
was freaking silly it was so silly like
what a silly inane thing to to laugh at
but it gave me a chuckle thanks a lot
spankenheimer
to assas assas Y Mori thank you to NORAD
clips and thank you very much to kwalk
Big Ups Big Ups to vampiric otaku thank
you thank you and a big up to pk5
IR for two years he did not know what
pot of greed do pot of greed best
Yu-Gi-Oh card ever a big UPS to Bri
thank you so much a big UPS to Jacob
langlet and Makai ryer 56 for the five
gifted memberships bones Malone what it
do damn friends owned already thank you
to Reagan and a big can we call him
shiori yeah actually that's a great idea
I'm going to remember that I'm going to
call him
shii we have the matching hairstyles
what can I say brilliant a big UPS to B
Bash thank you so much and a big UPS to
Chad maximum we got a couple raids this
time around too thank you so much for
the redirect and a big UPS to Bones
Malone thank you the death flags were
obvious thank you to Jimmy Hernandez
again and a big UPS to fauna for the
redirect fauna man I love fauna I'm so
glad I feel like I got I got to do
something fun with fauna you know
something I don't always get to do but
Faun is so fun to play with so I'm glad
she got to join us in a big a big server
thing together you know made me really
happy yeah I hope that we get to play
more things together that would make me
very happy vs to Mr VG and Jeremy
Hernandez thank you so
much yeah I'm so glad the TT RPG was
super fun too
so yeah fauna Gigi c b boo combo popping
off lately it would seem so especially
after gun I wonder if we if we got our
Social Links up quite a bit from that
who could say that no good bones Malone
was too good thank you very much to gaha
Callie you sound so different with the
studio mic I didn't recognize your voice
I have to go listen to that again cuz I
know that the studio mics are like much
different right I prefer this one
because it's you know it's tuned to my
voice I've spent a lot of meticulous
time uh talking with you guys through
this mic and setting up this mic so just
very
different Big Ups to Grass thank you
very much for the Super Chat how do I
send Super Chat guys thank you to buor
in the Atlant guard say
Kawaii who's that I don't know who that
is where is she I can't find her not
here a big UPS to Nathan Cooper thank
you so much and a big UPS to No Name a
big UPS to assas assas and thank you so
much to V faction a big UPS to Richard G
this is Extreme the running was so funny
and intense but funny a big UPS to jprs
SSR thank you so much really glad that
you enjoyed the playthrough and I hope
that you like the demo as well we'll see
what happens when there's you know more
to play hopefully sometime
soon we shall see whatever the schedule
ends up
being and then let's see we've got TCG
card shop simulators super chats let's
do it we got a big of wait I already
read these I think
oh yeah I read these I remember talking
about talk I remember El Le Pen
mentioning the the cards the Pokemon
cards whoopsie doodle yeah ah they still
haven't been tagged that's why okay no
worries well I guess that's about it for
now then um but I need to find more time
to read the anniversary ones hopefully
sometime
soon um fingers crossed but I will get
to those and the ASMR ones I can feel it
in my bones I'm getting closer I'm
getting closer to finally clearing all
of these but of course New Year's party
is going to wait until New Year's it's
going to be a bit of a Time Capsule so I
don't know how we're going to do the
nezumi ones but I'll I'll get to them
what what a time capsule that'll be how
things have changed but the backlog is
weakening and I feel good about it so
thank you so much everybody for
supporting me thank you for supporting
us I will be playing Space Marine 1
tomorrow very excited for that I don't
know what to expect but it's after I
have to do some really special uh
location recording for a special stream
that's coming up next month you guys
will not want to miss I have to go do
some on location recording though uh so
that's going to take up my morning and
then when I come back I'll play Space
marinees so hope you guys are excited I
heard that I get to meet the Orcs I'm so
excited to meet the Orcs the ones that
like the color
red yeah the red ones go
faster very
exciting so bar I want to understand the
inside jokes so yeah please look forward
to Space
Marine then hopefully um whenever bioo
is finished with Space Marine 2 we can
do some
operations yeah that is my hope so with
that being said I am your Mory I hope
you'll remember me go enjoy iris's
stream I think that's it for now I'll
see you guys tomorrow but thank you so
much for always supporting me and being
with me and cheering for me you guys
make it worth it wow this is almost a
7-hour stream let's go I'll see you guys
later I'm sure that I'll have lots of
time to talk about the lore that I've
witnessed tomorrow which is I still feel
like I've only barely scratched the
surface though bye everybody peace