[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h] is this rat doing in my
kitchen
oh i got caught hello ew
get out of here
okay goodbye get out of here nice good
stream
beating you goodbye i told you not to
come into
i'm in desperate need of a job
a job you didn't come for food you came
for a job
i i mean you get the job you get the
food right
right that is actually true yes yes yes
everyone uh who works at kfp gets a free
supply endless supply of foof indeed
what's your favorite kind of burger
burgoy
i like
um
cheese burgers
of course of course of course of course
is that is a is that a cheese patty with
cheese on it
um yes cheese patty with cheese double
cheese sandwiched in cheese nice
that sounds no
i mean i'm not the biggest fan of cheese
what's your favorite cheese
[Music]
oh i i just yesterday i made uh i made
pasta i made carbonara and when i when i
bought ingredients
um i was too lazy to find the red cheese
so i picked up just what i what was in
front of me i picked up mozzarella
cheese so
i made i made culinary yesterday with
mozzarella and i realized yeah you're
not supposed to make carbonara with
mozzarella cause it's oh yeah no once
you put it in there it immediately like
like it turns into
a hot mess of cheese it's
not a good idea but it was yummy anyway
you would probably eat it
i would totally eat it your teeth
fascinate me
did you see like uh during your debut i
was like putting your mouth on other
people was that okay for you i hope that
didn't like i said
i was kind of scared i'm not gonna lie
the blue worst images kind of scared me
but it was funny
thank you they actually don't even look
that bad on some people
i mean there was some you know everyone
is meant to have bottom teeth i guess
but just the the unsafe the the ungodly
images of bottom teeth
um
again i put them on like cali and myself
and
i think oh did i put them on good as
well i put them on a lot of people
i distinctly remember yeah yeah i think
that's the one i i put on
on twitter i think and i put some other
cursed ones on discord only to
to
amuse ourselves sorry i i just found it
really really fascinating and i kind of
like when i look at you i cannot
sometimes i wish that my teeth were a
bit more visible ah
this is uh my tastes are beautiful hey
you can see like inside look
uh look at the beautiful
[Music]
um i've been hit by the internet probs
again hold on oh my god
oh my god
i just needed to refresh
myself also from australia you know
or i can confirm we make an australian
citizen right here yes yes
yes yes yes
i am love mine
what's up white bloody hell mate you're
looking gorgeous uh uh wait uh
dad um help help me out jeff help me out
you you i've been having some
australians uh uh teaching me some words
every now and then uh how to tell
um well there was this one mate and one
want me to
okay keeps on teaching me words why are
you right now
i need help for communication
cracky cranky cricky cracky cracky
cry crankys
that's a good word right
what's still
that's mcdonald's right
what's the word for like doing something
like uh
really
really strongly
really strongly uh
what was that word
come on my australians
wow okay even that's a word i haven't
heard why the phone you're a fake
australian i knew i knew i don't know
you think you're an imposter
yaka
no i think we have already proven from
the get-go that i am the real australian
here
oh definitely i mean it took me a while
to remember but
i've been getting used to speaking
proper english with my viewers here so
what's what's your
what's up what's a word that you can
teach me that i don't know yet
if you are so australian
um
yes do you know
let's jet
yes
actually actually
uh remember when we were in discord
voice at uh
oh wait
before you w that you you said that and
i was like oh yeah hell yeah i'm gonna
use that before she debuts in in my
streams and i used it but they didn't my
viewers didn't even notice uh so that
was a bit disappointing
[Music]
my shout what
when we go out to food and then you say
oh don't worry about me my shout my
shower what does that mean
yeah your shout you're gonna like invite
them for food
um
it's like you will pay yeah yeah yeah my
oh my god there's a huge drill drilling
into my apartment right now okay okay
my munch out wait how did you how do you
spell it
no like shouting shout oh okay okay okay
well my dear dear bae since you are my
little kohai
uh no matter how many bombs we make boom
today
uh it's my shout i'll pay for the the
costs of repairing everything around us
don't worry
is that food involved
no
oh
i think shout out is normally useful
food or like purchasing of items yeah
i'm purchasing i'm covering the cost
yeah the repair costs the repair cost
okay my shout out let's jump into the
gaming screen screen mate much thanks
all right moving on volume okay can you
guys hear kiara can you guys hear the
rat
it looks so cute
perfect okay because you learned a rat
okay i'm moving
you carry diseases don't you
no i keep myself very clean
oh really what can you wash yourself
with
oh i
cleanse myself
as
well as everyone else what does everyone
else use body soap oh well i
[Music]
it makes me
smell very nice okay
okay okay okay
don't i hear some doubts there i hear
some x's but it is something you know it
is just o's
no no x's just those
well today my dear bae is our first
collaboration and um i thought we should
uh
uh choose a game that lets us practice
uh our communication skills and today we
will not only be playing this game in
normal english but we will do a round
where one of us speaks japanese and we
will do a round where i speak german and
we will do a round where we will speak
english but we will ban some words that
uh
also the chat uh provides us so if you
guys say bad the word
uh
wire
then we will not say the word one
sounds good don't be good yeah i i'm
sweating but we can do it
it doesn't matter that i know zero
german but that's okay ah google
translate help me well
uh
you know
we're feeling you you probably will
understand it sounds maybe sometimes it
sounds a bit similar did you know that
the word kindergarten is originally
german
oh
yeah no but okay that will not help us
in the bomb diffusion but there are some
german words in english language
the only german wait is that german
yes the only word i know how to
pronounce i'll say in german is burger
which is bugar
is that right
that's not german no
oh that's not german
how do you say burger german i mean
there's a word uh that sounds similar
which is a burger but that means um uh
um
a person who lives citizen
citizen
but that's a different way
yeah
where did i hear bulgar
bulgar
well i mean there's a city that's called
a city that's called hamburg and the
people from there you call
hamburgers
oh
yeah that's funny yeah there goes my
limited german everyone
exists
today you'll go out of here with maximum
german knowledge yes delorean yes i'll
teach you some good words
okay
i will be guiding you on how to
defuse
the bomb okay on
my perspective you'll be able to see the
manual uh this round and also you will
hear this lovely elevator music yeah i
was just saying how amazing this
elevator is hell yeah
okay a gym i will i will start with uh
is it okay i mean this is probably
already gonna be a bit difficult but i
will start with the 2.2 which has six
modules
and 2.2
okay yeah
or should we start with an easier one
oh yeah you're not cool yeah
okay let's start with 2.1 2.1 2. 2.1
like my giant mouse everyone people keep
making fun of my mouse
are you using uh yourself as a mouse
no i've just got a giant arrow oh what
the hell
that's disappointing what's wrong with
mine
that's disappointing you got to use
yourself you're you're around wouldn't
that make sense to use yourself as a
mouse i do but i haven't found one
didn't you use that in your debut stream
why am i imagining things
no i used
a giant arrow
okay we'll get you one okay we'll get
you one then let's start with normal
english for the first round
okay
please lead me through the bomb
diffusion
okay mrs rat
this is that oh how do i turn on the
light
oh there it is okay sweet yes oh it's
been a while how do i play this uh
let's start with the like there's uh
four buttons with some
hieroglyphical
signs let's start with that part yes
okay uh can you tell me the four signs
you see please yeah it says one of them
is a star one of them is a copyright
thingy one of them is a upside down y
with one line crossing through it
and the
last one is
it looks uh
like a
cursive
see and then half walt disney yeah
something like that maybe
okay sweet can you please press
copyright sign yes
uh the the cursive
yes the y and the start
very good
next up we have the same thing again but
with different signs
oh my
so one is a c with a dot in the middle
it's the right direction
okay and then there's a p that's that
looks in the other direction and is
called black
uh
[Music]
there's a there's a trident trident
trident
and
there's a free that looks the other way
and has a tail and has bunny ears yes
yes yes yes yes yes
yes okay so trident yes then
c
yes then here then three
i was like hearing sounds i thought the
game was doing it but no my my room is
currently falling apart apparently then
we have uh we have a we have a field
with four colors they are blue yellow
green and red
oh is it in a diamond shape yes
oh okay um uh which one is flashing the
blue one sometimes the blue one is
flashing okay the original video
i don't know how to read this okay
does the serial number contain a vowel
uh
a serial number
ah
yes
yes it does okay yes
what's up
okay press uh
wait uh
can you press the red button yes
[Music]
now now now after i did that the blue
one beeped and the red one beeped
it's telling me something
beep beep
is is there a new new color
no but but it keeps on beeping at me
blue and red blue and red blue and red
in between
i think maybe blue next
yeah are you sure
okay no
wrong wrong wrong okay i'll press red
again no oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] okay ah i
already got two strikes i shouldn't have
done that okay blue red is beeping
okay blue red yeah okay we've got one
strike a blue two strikes i'm smoking
two two strikes
okay repeat oh we need one
okay so if it's two strikes so blue
okay can you click blue red green
[Laughter]
oh yeah because you said blue red green
or whatever but but before when i
clicked blue again it it it was a strike
so i thought i need to continue and go
on with green and that blue red green so
i clicked green first
because i it was blue and red was
already activated right but i i don't
know
i don't know
this one confuses me because it doesn't
say which
button to press but
well well well should do you you want to
do you want to try this one
no
[Music]
are you here
this is the australian internet mate
oh my every time i boom i swear every
time that happens so often for you
um unfortunately yes
i think you should uh
leave australia and move to australia
oh my god
i want you to be like my little sister
maybe you're cute yeah yeah i mean i am
cali's little sister doesn't that make
me technically your little sister as
well excuse me what you're kelly's
little sister
yeah what when the [\h__\h] did that happen
when the [\h__\h] did that happen
when the [\h__\h] when the [\h__\h] did that
happen and why
i don't understand we we have the same
we have we have the same father oh that
does not matter
yeah no no no no no no no no okay let's
go back
no no okay no
no
no okay now i
i will read the manual to you in german
is that okay for you well we haven't
even complained at the first level
can you okay you need to can we can we
try um okay we're actually uh disarm one
bomb before we move on okay okay okay so
you want to do the manual again here
yes i'll do the manual okay in goodreads
understand simon says i don't understand
oh that was like uh
ah
well simon says it's basically just
remembering what has been said before
i know but it doesn't say if we're meant
to press the original button
oh you know what this time that one is
not here so we can ignore it okay
perfect let's start with some wires
okay i got one two three four five six
wires
and why i will now tell you from top to
bottom
which color they are
okay
black yellow
black
red
white
and blue
thinking time for the red okay so
there's one yellow
how many white and one
[Music]
is there a red wire
yes
indeed
okay can you cut the fourth wire one two
three four
okay
let's go are we good yeah
very good now something that looks very
difficult we have a maze
with black dots and and two green
circled
squares
and one white dot and one red triangle
that is probably me
oh i think this one is difficult should
i tell you where the green circled ones
are or where the whites yes where are
those oh wait wait wait wait wait there
should be two
so you are the triangle and then there
should be two like circle things on the
map right yeah okay can you please tell
me
uh where the circle thingies are uh at
one is at the very top row second from
the left
second from the left and one is the
second from the left on the very bottom
oh okay and where are you
i am
wait am i the white square or am i the
red triangle
um
maze with matching
must navigate the right oh okay so you
are the white light whereas where is the
white light that one is and on the very
very left side uh from top to bottom
third row
top to bottom third row on the left
angle the triangle is in the same row so
top to bottom third row but it's uh
from the left side
oh
four
four one two three four oh no okay so
can you go up three all the way to the
top one two
three
yes okay i'm at the top yes
you're in the very left hand corner
right yeah
okay sweet now go to the right one two
three
uh okay one but you mean you mean
um to the third one from the left or i
should actually click the button three
times and be on the fourth fourth
four oh oh sorry yeah yeah so be on the
fourth one okay
okay okay
and then go down one
one
right one one
wait why am i getting lost oh wait no
okay we're good up one up one
right one right one
okay and then down two
two yes
uh one left yes
down one yes
uh left two
yes
up one yes
and then the right should be the
triangle
dream team let's go
okay
i don't have much left on here i have a
button a white button that says press
do i press it
node
hold hold
oh my god they're drilling so loud babe
please can you destroy them or something
boom boom
we should maybe let the bomb explode so
it explodes on them wait there's only
one minute left okay what do i do
yeah it says press
okay um is there a lit indicator with
the label car
no
um so on the side there's no like oh
oh my god no
i know it says nsa nsa on the side
oh this is nsa is there batteries in
this bomb uh
yes
one how many one big one one
okay 20 seconds 17 seconds
okay up hold the button and then um let
me know what color comes up
red
up when it has a one in the timer you
can let go
let's go
one second left because the moment you
said that i had eight seconds left so
the only one that i could really wait
for was one second left
what can i say
you know yeah that was all i got time
remaining 1.69 seconds
nice
[Laughter]
very nice oh
that was all all according to keikaku
right
we wanted it to end at the last second
exactly what about the tensioning guys
that's how you build
engagement yeah
it felt chaotic that's for sure
uh-huh very good
all right are you ready for a german
rounds
don't worry i think i think with watson
when i did it in german i think we were
understanding each other better than
when we communicated in english so
you should be good why is it loading so
long game
why are you loading so long
hello game oh no my game i think my game
is dead
that's okay because i'm not the one
playing now i'll be the one reading
yeah let me close the game
what's it what's it recently with my
games crashing
um
yesterday apparently it was a part of uh
it was it was a common bug though anyway
so which do you know which you want to
do an easier bump
please
if we do the first bomb
uh should we do the first bomb no
no you'll do the third one
two point two no no no no no no no no uh
from from one point is that one point
three yeah so the first problem so one
point three right
yeah yeah yeah yeah one point three what
do you do okay not one point one that
would be too boring
okay okay okay okay wait a second two
seconds my
my manual wait i'm back in the game but
i won't be the one doing this so i see
crazy
oh
your friends really i see where is she
where is she
oh no she's just she's on my leaderboard
you're friends with crazy ollie on steam
but not with me yet
uh we we'll change that afterwards all
right
all right okay okay
uh
are you ready because i'm ready i think
hey let's
[Music]
something about one
[Laughter]
how i turn
um
okay we've got the
i got the four symbols
the four um that yes okay one is a
copyright symbol
yeah button
looks like a nose with a really big
pimple on top yeah yeah
and then
one looks like they were gonna write a
three but then the hand
and the last one looks like um a
butterfly with an eye in the middle
okay
uh copyright
uh
nose okay yeah
okay so my description about the button
about the stream was very long so i'm
guessing it's the butterfly
yeah yeah
oh
try
[Music]
[Applause]
one blue
two black
one red
[Music]
okay that sounded like is the white
important
okay so
red
how many one
oh oh okay okay okay
with
[Laughter]
yellow was that yellow
yeah yellow
again
one yellow okay
uh-huh
uh
[Music]
um and then come in um oh we've got a
button that says white that it says
press
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
oh hold on it's to be a while
boom
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
you did a good job so
uh you i think one one word that you
will take away from this is
schmetterling it's butterfly
schmidtling have you gotten that already
schmidt remember nine nine nine yeah
nine is no and yes yeah that's basically
the only word you really have to know
okay okay
we we did it
german round completed
seven round completed okay
then uh should we do the the english
round where
some words are banned
yes okay
look at the manual
so i think we came up with no saying
colors like we have to just describe the
colors yeah yeah like we can't say red
blue canal also yes
still speaking german
and uh
how about yeah we say we don't say wire
okay no wire and we don't say button
okay okay so no wire
no no yeah we should we should write
this down i'm gonna forget it uh no
no wire
and button
uh colors
we're gonna make it really difficult
no buttons no talking at all
[Laughter]
um what else do i have in the menu i
mean something something that makes uh
explaining those
hieroglyphic uh symbols
uh more difficult
um
i mean i feel like that's already pretty
difficult yeah
all right okay maybe we can start with
these three and see okay
no
no color
no soul okay uh no soul what no soul my
soul no soul
i lost myself okay oh should we do 2.2
um
okay
okay are you ready hold on hold on let
me change back to the menu
oh we could do a singing only around two
let's do that afterwards
that's a good idea chad thank you okay
no why are there no colors okay
okay okay
let's go
[Music]
lie down please
hello
hello there we go why does it take so
long okay uh
four
uh
the four the four things with the with
those with the
signs on it yes yes i have two of those
okay so let's die let's start one of
them is a star one of them is uh
a boobie with a belly button on top of
it
the one oh yeah then one of you called
nose the then we have the disney
squiggle and we have the y that's so
the other way around before
upside down yeah
tell kiara we're trying to see her
scream eh
oh [\h__\h]
i still have the men
[Laughter]
half walt disney
and then
well upside down y and then the start
okay
works next one next one also has a
upside down y and then it has a
butterfly it has a copyright and it has
a bubba
was that too fast
okay copyright
butterfly why nice oh speed run let's go
then we have some pretty strings strings
wink wink
if you know what these strings yeah we
got four of them two black to blue
what
okay game over this i mean
well i'll just cut some random ones here
okay kill me already
it came so natural okay one more time
yes oh my god one more time
lights on please for god's sake
okay okay
okay
uh we have
two two panels with strings
two panels yeah
okay one has one two three four five six
okay
now listen there's two that are the the
the color of the blood
okay okay two i'm allowed to say the
word color but not not any colors okay
and and one is the color of the sun
one is the color of the sun exactly one
okay yeah one is a two are the color of
uh darkness
two are the color of the okay
and one is the color of the sea
one is the color of the sea okay cut the
fourth
i'll give you that one the first one no
cut the fourth pretty little string the
fourth one
the fourth string okay
nothing happened
[Applause]
okay we have another panel with four
strings
two are the color of sun and two are the
color of c
are there only four strings in total yes
indeed one by two of the color of the
what two are the color of the sun and
two other color of the sea
okay
what color is the last string um
i cut the last string
done okay turn around
oh my god there's so many we have three
minutes left okay two panels with uh
things with with with sick girls uh
signs yes hero gloves okay one is a c
copyright c one is a butterfly
one is a three that's not finished
writing and one is the turn around why
without
uh c butterfly three y oh that's exactly
the
way i told you okay and then we have
another one that's a star
and a bulba with a belly button and a
copyright and a butterfly
oh okay
see yeah
and the last one i can't remember what
you said stop
nice oh very good and we have two big
big
things that you can push
two big things yes separately
both say yes abort
but what is the color of blood and one
is the color of uh
the c
okay
we got two minutes left and by the way
batteries i have uh four batteries
four small ones
okay um
one is the color no wait there's more
there's four small batteries and one big
one
oh okay so the one is the color of blood
did you say uh yes
okay um
what does it say
abort
a boy oh
okay can we start with the color of the
sea let's start with the colors yes
okay um can you press it and tell me
what colors right
[Laughter]
right
can we get let's work
[Applause]
okay can you just hold it tell me what
color comes up
the color of
of of of a bright brightness
um release one timer has a one in any
position okay
we're just finishing this now it
works good
oh my god i just said with so much
confidence i was like white but then i
was like
five ten seconds later i was like
i never
[Laughter]
that you had i thought you were getting
mad at me for saying the color
oh no i didn't even hear the color
oh my god okay okay again
um what was the next round singing
okay you're gonna you're gonna defuse
and i'm gonna sing the manual
okay
let me find it where did i put it
this is funny all right which one should
we do
uh whichever you desire i think the
maybe 2.3
2.3
okay
let's see
oh god help me okay uh we've got simon
says because we got to figure out how to
oh
oh [\h__\h]
uh okay yeah let's go
what do you say flashing oh we both have
to sing it's flashing red
it's it's oh
wait a second i've never read this one
before
[Music]
that's okay
repeat the sequence in order using the
color mapping what is it that isn't
singing
i don't understand
um
what's up red flash okay uh
ahahahahaha
[Music]
please press blue
if i
read again
[Music]
red
red oh
well please press blue
is that really it
what's going on i don't know
eh did you press blue again
i did wait
oh
oh i see i understand okay sorry
i don't know red blue
what red red red red blue
okay
um
i don't understand
wait a second let me read this
one of the four colored buttons will
flash using the correct table below
press the button with the corresponding
color the original button will flash
followed by another repeat this sequence
in order using the color mapping the
sequence will lengthen by one each time
you correctly enter sequence and then
one lines to sound i don't know if you
still understand i still don't
understand
what color should i press if it's
flashing blue
please press
red
baby
okay okay we're
[Music]
six wires
six wide
if if there are no yellow wires and the
last digit of the serial number is a cut
the third wire otherwise there's exactly
one yellow white one yellow one yellow
wire one yellow one yellow uh
is is the more than just one white wire
there is only one
only we only have one minute and thirty
forty forty seconds oh folks just cut
just cut the full fire
very good
three wires three wires
two
cut the second one cut the second one
okay
um and then we've got um some number
sequence we got a big number
and then we've got four numbers but oh
i've got one minute to save my life i
don't know what you're talking about
i don't know there's just one big number
yes yes what is it
three
three press the button on the third
position
[Music]
third position and this is three press
the button in the first position
[Music]
um now if it says
um it says two
okay
press the button of the same label you
press in stage one so the front position
okay now it says
three
i'm going to die
i'm going to die press press press the
one that you pressed at the second stage
[Laughter]
[Music]
singing wastes too much time i thought
this would be easy but it wastes too
much time
we went boom boom
boom boom
that's what i like to see baby
we went boom boom forever that's okay no
no not forever
not doing it
yeah um
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] singing
let's do it um let's do japanese rounds
nihongo but only one of us
only one of us so
i can read the manual in the homegold to
you and you try to diffuse in ingo issue
okay
keep singing and nobody somebody
explodes
um
okay uh shall we do the same bomb that's
so much that's pretty difficult but okay
we can do it okay
retry yes um so we've got come on light
yeah what is this okay i'm gonna start
with the numbers one that we just did
because it takes a long time hey
so the number in the top is two
uh uh
that's
the side
okay now it says two
that's okay
that's wrong
okay number three okay it says three
but in which stage are we now stage one
no we restart restart restart okay
okay now it says
four
okay
now it says one
ah
[Music]
uh
[Laughter]
i trust you i think it was the third
position but oh
not there
okay thank god i didn't listen to you
okay
last one number one
i know
um
okay so the two green circles um the
first green circle is in the third
column um and second row from the bottom
i have one minute okay okay
okay so third column and then second
from the bottom row and then the second
circle is the first row first row um
second column from the right
okay and second row from the bottom
yes
[Music]
and then the other one is first row i'm
going to die second uh column from the
left okay up from the right okay right
from the right side no no what
where where is
[Laughter]
i swear the numbers one takes forever oh
my god
[Music]
i'm going to eat you bae i'm going to
eat you you're going to regret forgiving
me
hey should we do it the other way around
you do you want to do the manual in
japanese to me
oh sure that's probably going to fail
but
it's okay 2.3 is so difficult
yeah and here we were saying we're gonna
do like level three one
never never happening
okay okay
come on turn the lights on people okay
there we go
let's start with the maze
let me let me know when you're ready
hi hi okay sorry um
the circled ones are one is second row
on the very left
and one is on the third row on the very
right
hi
yeah that one is uh on the very left uh
on the
fourth point from the top
yeah i am at the very bottom row
and uh
on the on the fourth point from the left
very bottom
fourth fourth spot
that's two
[Music]
yes
well i mean i'll be explaining them to
you so no it'll be fun so we have one
star
we have one disney squiggle
we have one
round e
that looks the other side and with two
dots on top
and we have a tennis racket yes
yeah disney
[Music]
okay then we have a yellow button that
says abort
[Music]
hero
two small ones one big one
and we have my my thing does say nsa and
frq
f r q naught
nsa
three batteries i suppose
red
now we have a we have a panel
with a big number at the top oh no not
that yeah
oh no
[Music]
this one's gonna [\h__\h] us up okay so i
have four numbers at the bottom yeah
right now it says three in the top oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
11 page 11.
[Music]
remember we have to get this one it says
one now big one big one one one
uh
one third position four second position
one third position four seconds four
four four one third position for second
position four four
one
side
okay okay one third position four second
position three three three three
one
[Music]
foreign
10 seconds left nope that isn't
happening
[Laughter]
that one is so difficult when you when
using one of them springs japanese
it's also no it's really difficult to
remember though
oh
yeah because i was like i remembered in
which position each number was and i
remember the numbers well except at the
very end i was getting a bit loose on
that freak
bloody hell mate
what's your your nihongo was totemo
she didn't take it like that all right
all right uh
do we want to try the last one in proper
english
again do you end up on a high note yeah
and try to with no we've no nothing to
stop us just do normal english and see
if we can do it this way
okay
okay should i be diffusing or do you
want to diffuse
um up to you okay i'll confuse let's go
okay let's do this baby
let's do it if you help me defuse this
bomb i will let you work at kfp
okay
okay we got wires oh [\h__\h] there's so
much here holy [\h__\h] wires one two three
four five six wires
six three of them are blue
one is red
one is uh white
one is black the last one is black
does that help you
wait how many wires again
six six
six okay
um there is one yellow no no yellow
no yellow um
and the last okay what what's the last
digit of the serial number oh
uh zero
zero
is there a red one yes
okay
oh one two three four
[\h__\h] okay
let's do symbols symbol symbols
copyright c boobies turn around y
butterfly
all right okay copyright c we're quick
with this one
yes
butterfly did you say it easy okay done
that's we're good with that one okay now
we have a new one that we haven't done
before ever
it's a panel with words uh it says like
there's a there's a screen that says you
were
and then there's words six different
words that wait how many more little
panel um how many more do we have so we
have this uh we have one with the colors
the four colors
and we have oh yeah this one i think
that's it yeah okay
all right we'll say this one first okay
so what was the word on top
uh you're
you're you i
you wait oh wait does it say
you
are
like how is it can you read out the
exact letters for me yes y-o-u
apostrophe r-e
straw can you say that again the finger
thing on the top the little
i know can you say it again
a poster a pen or a piece or fee
what is apostrophe word on the second
row to the right middle
middle oh right right very right okay um
then push the first button that appears
in this corresponding okay okay so i'm
gonna read yeah out a bunch of words
okay can you push the first one you hear
oh
okay
okay blank
blank ready
no
okay
no spelled
why no
what
yes
okay
okay now i i see display on the display
oh wait don't do it again okay okay okay
okay
this display
yeah d-i-s-p-l-a-y
can you
what's the word on the bottom right very
bottom
s-u-r-e
s-u-r-e okay so um
press the one that you hear first uh so
you are like two words y-o-u space a-r-e
what
no okay i don't have that one i think
done
yes okay okay okay
next one they are t h e y space a r e
they are
they are yeah
wait wait t h a
what's the middle one to the left
right
right um
okay
uh yes
no
nothing
ready
no
um
no no
press
yes okay okay okay our four colors
battle we have one minute left uh the
blinky one is
come on
green green green is blinky simon says
oh [\h__\h] this is gonna [\h__\h] us up okay
green yes um
flash can you please
flash uh
oh does the serial number contain a
vowel
no
no it doesn't contain a vowel it does
not contain okay
okay green can you press yellow please
yes and we have 26 ah it was wrong wrong
it was wrong
oh what
it's flashing green and we have 20
seconds left
wait is that an oh no is it zero
zero oh zero um
okay um maybe that's just green
green okay no wrong that was wrong [\h__\h]
okay come with legends ray you did not
get the job at kfp
what
sorry today is my one month you know and
i had to prank all the myth members that
i could and i may have read you the
wrong instructions
are you just making excuses are you
making excuses because you actually
read the right manual but you didn't
know what you were doing
i don't believe it i don't buy it oh
okay you can watch the re you can watch
the the archives wait why would you read
why would you read the wrong manual
so i can prank you you can go boom
did you not want the job at kfb
no because i'll get in anyway because
i'm a rat
you little [\h__\h]
i'm so bad
i'm sending you to the usual room
you can't you're welcome at the usual
room you'll see it you'll see how fun it
is there you little stupid rat
[Music]
love you too
that was fun
yeah yeah that was pretty entertaining i
had a lot of fun
i had a lot of fun
well
well my australian mate uh
in the future
you better not prank your senpai anymore
just kidding you can prank me
it's okay i think i think we need
someone like you uh to you know bring
some life
into whole life you're welcome to prank
any of us
create some chaos we need some chaos i
mean that the whole myth was always
always chaotic but we need more more
chaos
well your wish is my command hold on let
me let's go back to the main all right
i'll also go to my cake okay aldo i
don't want you i don't really no i don't
really want you in the kitchen anymore
here i'll
i'll i'll put you in the fryer
hey
you sure there you go
is it hot over there my dear gray
not as hot as
no shouldn't have pranked me
it's okay i'm just chilling here in some
oil
because actually should be down here
we smiled that was fun yeah it was fun
i'm glad we did a collab together and
i'm glad that
i could be your first one
okay
are you not happy that i was your first
one
no i was very happy i just remembered
that you also said the same thing in in
discord and i responded with an
inappropriate joke and i'm not going to
do that on stream oh well then let me
read out what you said back then no
let's see wait scroll scroll scroll ah
yeah yeah okay
okay so i said i said on the first
september uh
i will take your senpai collab virginity
dough smug emote and then she says ha ha
ha ha ha omg dot
and then i say your mind smoke emoji and
then she says please treat me gently xd
xd i don't know i love how you use xd
and both in cable capital letters by the
way that's uh i don't know i'm i'm um
that's that was a face for me too
i was a face a certain point in my life
i was writing xd and capital letters as
well but that time is over
people just gotta use xd yeah what's
wrong with xd it's a very good
expressive you know
i like
it i think you you're okay you're good
to go you you can use it did i treat you
gently enough though
no that was actually quite rough what a
rough night
wait wait i wanna i wanna put you i
wanna eat you wait uh i'm catching oh
i am a cat after all you're sure
[Music]
[Applause]
well thank you for hanging out with me
you're gone now no more kitchen for you
uh you're from now on banned from my
kitchen and we can still be friends
though but yeah you're just not welcome
in my kitchen anymore
you cannot order from kfb via uber eats
or something if you really need some
food you're welcome to give us money uh
but we we can't let you into the
restaurant anymore but delivery is okay
we can deliver to your place i don't
know if we really deliver to
um fake australia we'll see about that
oh i'm sorry i was putting coffee up
your nose okay
what the [\h__\h]
stop it i don't like coffee stop it
stop playing around with me
okay
we're good
okay um
i'm looking forward to many many more
fun collabs with you my dear baby
me too this is really fun i hope you're
feeling uh welcomed and happy in her
life and if there's ever anything that
you're worried about or that you have
problems with or anything you want to
discuss i'm always here for you bae
oh
thank you
i'm a good senpai okay i can i i can
help you
oh um okay i can help you in many ways
um
with that being said thanks guys
what's your ending greeting
my ending greeting um i say goodbye in
english japanese well another japanese
and then korean and then ice cream
oh my god okay you today you can add one
more language to that because my ending
greeting is actually in german so you
can say that
okay
that is uh yes in german and in german
we say
alf v thousand
alvidazin
yeah you can actually make it shorter
you can just say truce but no we're
going to make you say the difficult one
auf wiedersehen
[Music]
i'll see you tomorrow for minecraft with
my mom oh oh oh
uh hopefully not at the same time as you
oh okay just kidding
i don't know if you want to meet my mom
you're welcome to come by
uh oh no it's just i'm also streaming
tomorrow minecraft so
we'll see if we're overlapping we'll see
we'll see
if we overlap i might have to hire you
after all for my construction company
oh
well
i better see you tomorrow in minecraft
yes
bye-bye very good bye-bye
[Music]
do
you