[Music]
so
do
[Music]
hola
[Laughter]
hello oh [\h__\h] music's so loud sorry
wow
how are you
[Music]
oh
don't tell me how to pronounce t h or s
i have problems with that
yes yes
hello
welcome back to another
wonderful
snack box
experiment
world snacks with takanasi
kiwawa
yay muy brand muy bien muy bien
fact snack snacks snacks snacks
yay
snacks can never get enough of snacks
because snacks a day of the
night and today
right stream snacks
boy y'all no boil where is boyle
you're a boyo
i'm a snack that's true
and today we have oops wait i still have
the happy easter thing up in the back
oopsie noodles
[Music]
spice is not today i don't know i did
not really look uh inside my snack box
but people
have doxed my snack box found out where
i'm getting my snacks from and have
apparently
decided that my snack box for today
is pretty legit apparently i mean
apparently i will like it people have
said i will like it
well hopefully that is true
because you got my hopes up already uh
previously we had some disappointing
ones but i think the reason why um this
might be a good one uh is just like with
the swedish snack books because they're
from europe and i think they have an
easier time
to and we're an easier
you know easier time to to um
get snacks from europe because the
company is also based in europe and they
can i mean traveling into european
countries is also pretty easy to like
actually study
and um investigate what the people there
actually eat and what sells well and so
so i think in general the thing probably
is that if you if they send you a
european snack box then it's probably
gonna be a good one but if it's outside
of europe then
good luck
because the one that we got from
guatemala which is obviously outside of
europe was [\h__\h] and did not have a
single guatemala snack
and
which other snack box was disappointing
which one which the korean one was not
from that company
we had an international one
and
uh
sweden was fine
well married that was not an american
snack box that was an international one
swedish was fine although
i i added some things because i had
access to them
[Music]
oh yeah ah there was one more that has
been consumed by the void which
i will never know if it was a good one
or a bad one
i gave that one to my sister by the way
i look laggy
really
oh really
i think i'm fine i think i'm fine
i think i'm fine yeah i mean
maybe my
movements are a little bit robotic today
but maybe that's just me
oh wait actually
i do feel like
you might be right i look a little bit
robotic today
not not for the fps or so but
is it just
is it just my imagination maybe maybe i
do move a little bit
um stuttery
but
nothing of concern
i was busy the whole day i literally
just came back home uh
half an hour ago before the stream half
half an hour before the stream
the classic is
um got some things done and now we're
ready to eat some snackos
knuckles
are you guys ready
where are my other other wait wait let
them answer if they're ready
you know we don't want the answers to
mix
are you guys ready
don't ask too many questions at once
kimawa
okay
okay and who
who here is actually from spain or lives
in spain
because i need you guys to um judge
if the contents of this snack box are
legit
maybe
oh actually
surprisingly many
oh thank you guys for coming i'm glad
i'm glad to see some of you nice thank
you hola hola barcelona away from from
where the spanish the spain people who
answered which where where where which
city i want to know madrid
[Music]
i was hoping for someone to be from
valencia argentina oh cool
alicante
tenerife oh
very popular destination for travelers
from germany
[Music]
don't know that place but cool
why are some people saying
cities from outside of spain
i didn't ask you
oh but of course everyone else is
welcome to non-spanish people are
welcome too of course
um
we might have you know snacks that are
just uh popular in other countries as
well and you guys might just want to
know what is popular
in spain what kind of snacks do they eat
there you might just want to widen your
own horizons and knowledge
yourself right yeah
okay so let me show you
my snack box for today
although how are we going to do this
webcam oh wait
we gotta do this properly
wow
there it is
beautiful beautiful and now there we go
snack
box here it is and today
white gloves wow
i got i found new gloves in my closet
old old gloves but i was like oh my
black ones are dirty so why not make use
of my
white ones yeah yeah
yeah they look say so
don't they
yay
fancy
all right um
oh i already see ladies all right wait i
don't want to spoil it too
ah
wait let me just um i don't want you
guys to
see it like that no don't look at the
snacks okay don't look at them don't
look at them
ah we're look at the
look at the pamphlet first okay as we
always like to do
because they have some nice pamphlets
there
don't look you spoilers don't spoiler
yourself here i have something i'm out
i'll put this here
don't look don't mind the mother oh gosh
okay
yeah yeah i have some japanese uh sheets
for um legs that are pretty nice i i
rarely use them though because i don't
want to run out of them i really have
this
illness that i have this in rpg games
too you know me right you know i i get
like
really good healing items in rpgs but
then i don't want to use them because
uh
in some rpgs they are pretty scarce and
then i just
try to go through the game without using
my healing items
and this is the same thing my problem is
i have this and i like using it because
it's pretty good
but i don't want to run out of it
because i can't easily uh get it again
[Laughter]
oh
yeah hoarding rpg hoarding
it's ridiculous
[Music]
[Applause]
all right
so let's uh get some basics down about
spain here first first page okay
and uh capital
is
guess what madrid
madrid their language is
espanol
uh
people living in spain
47.3 million
that's quite a lot and they use the
glorious
euro sugar
typically spanish
they say
is
the sun
i guess they mean that it's always sunny
oh like pretty much always sunny and hot
this relationship here typically spanish
the sun
every every
sun doesn't belong to spain but okay
um
[Music]
you know the dish with you know usually
i think it's shrimps and and all kinds
of
you know rice and
stuff like that but i think there's a
non
non paella paella and a non shrimp
paella too but seafood is the most
common right
um
so all right we got the basics done
[Music]
gosh
is this the next page
i can't flip pages properly
oh is this the next page i think so okay
next page there's some
there's some um
more information here saying that spain
is one of the most popular
travel destinations in the world and i
will tell you that especially within
europe it's very popular because
traveling to spain is so easy so so so
cheap
there's so many
um cheap ass airlines that go to spain
really cheaply and then in spain
things are pretty cheap too
uh
and spain has a lot of party that's like
great destinations that are well known
for like party visitors like uh
madrid and barcelona for example i would
say i think um i've never been there but
i know and ibiza ibiza even suck
i forgot my yoka yeah even south
mallorca are the top two
probably for german
german visitor visitors not only to go
to the ocean but mainly their main goal
is usually to party in nightclubs
not really my thing
um
i i prefer not partying
i just want it's quite a quiet vacation
but yeah
i am
but um yeah we we europeans appreciate
spain for being cheap um i kind of want
to go again because it's also very fast
like
uh i think the flight would be what two
to three hours probably
depending on where exactly in spain i
would go
[Music]
is also very cheap but
a bit further away
and greece has more islands so some
places are a little bit difficult to
reach
um but yeah they're both cheap travel
destinations i love greece and spain
also the people are awesome spanish and
great people are awesome
yeah they're all very very
open and fun and positive
[Music]
cool people
all right so what else does it say here
uh architecture in spanish cities uh
is um charming which i can confirm i was
in valencia on a a
solo trip
and valencia is not one of the most
well-known or most well most popular um
cities but
um
and i i noticed because
this the
city center
there was like this beautiful square
with like marble floor
and a fountain and it was just huge and
beautiful architecture and there were
like
no people like there were okay not no
people but there were barely people
there i was really surprised i thought
it would at least in the city center
would be filled with people but no it
was so empty oh you know visco valencia
i don't know what it was called but i
just remember um
it was so empty and i didn't understand
why valencia is just um not the main
goal for tourists so i felt really lucky
that i chose uh
a destination that was not overfill the
tourists this was actually in this was
in in spain and what this was in summer
i wanted this obviously it was in spain
but this wasn't summer so it was you
know high season
yeah but um very empty wow yeah well
really
i want to go again i want to go to
different places too but i really liked
valencia even though
like i went to some beaches
um
[Music]
with like the bus like i went to the
city beach and it was so overfilled and
i was alone so i was scared that people
would steal if i would leave my bag for
a moment yeah so instead of going to the
oval field city beach i tried to find
like
random uh beaches that are a little bit
outside of the city and i would go with
a bus and it was so [\h__\h] hot and i
was
carrying my my [\h__\h] and it was so
exhausting every time i died every time
and uh my my feet were like full with
blisters
yeah it was really bad and then um
especially on my way back it was always
even worse because my blisters would
then be filled with sand
um
yeah that was
really really really
it was so painful
but um i was able to find some
some relatively empty beaches
um
which was nice the only problem was
i don't know if it was because of those
beaches or because i was just unlucky
with the wind
but the waves were so strong
every day i went to these beaches the
waves were so strong
yeah
and uh i had a hard time swimming but
anyway it was still great oh yeah no
no
no no no for your normal chilling i
don't really want big waves it's really
tough i i got a little bit sick from all
the wow
oh yeah okay what else
[Music]
fun facts spain
produces
the biggest amount of olive oil
worldwide
maybe my olive oil is from spain too did
you know
did you know
another fun fact is
uh
in spain if you
marry someone in the church
uh
[Music]
husband
will
will traditionally
gift his wife
gold uh coins
and one platin coin
12 gold coins and one platinum
coin the groom will gift it to his wife
why
why i don't know she don't say cheap
though cuz
is that cheap it's real gold coins man
i don't know this sounds very super chat
i'm not sure why there must be some
reason behind that some some traditional
reason i
it doesn't stay here why
oh
spanish people built the first u-boat
which is a submarine submarine
they built the first submarine
there is um
what there's a restaurant in spain
called sobrino de putin
uh it is in um it is active since 1725
and is the oldest restaurant in the
whole wide world
what
what oh and which city it is it just
says it's in spain but doesn't say in
which city
[Music]
i don't know how to pronounce it
i don't know that sounds more french
um
spain has uh
what do you call christian linea in
english beach line
of 4964
a coastline yeah coastline of almost 5
000 kilometers which is i guess pretty
long
and the country has
altogether 164
islands
[Music]
okay you know what we'll already start
eating one snack and then we can
continue with what's written in this
pamphlet
[Music]
so by the way there's a postcard too
here
pretty
a city called sevilla
is that motherland
it's pretty
[Music]
wow
maybe i can visit it sometime
sevilla
or not well i mean the first thing here
is
whistle
is lays
er with oh
is that garlic tomato
it looks like garlic tomato but it also
says grit jetta which kind of sounds
like a cheese
what is it
those are amazing um
tomato uh garlic mmm i'm from garlic
ah recipe
recipe
it means recipe [\h__\h] flavor okay
these are really flattened uh
see they look so flat
they feel like they were really squeezed
oh i know why because my cat
smoothie just jumped on this whole thing
um
a little while ago
like a few minutes ago before the stream
started i can't open this i need a
scissor i'm gonna have a scissor with me
right now
ah come on
[Music]
get out of there
yeah let me try to open it like uh
i can't get a grip of it with my gloves
no not noodle arms it's just like i
can't i can't hold i can't hold it
like i'm trying to open it like this but
[Music]
i can't
i can't hold it
and i can't open it like this deeper
[Music]
let me try to
poke through it with a pen
that should work
yeah it worked
expiration date check
just just because i'm curious oh it's
fine it's june
the smell is oh
[Music]
the smell
smells like
pasta
um
okay
i mean i opened it weirdly but
uh
here have a look
we shall
you know that's what chips look like you
know what chips look like
[Music]
looks like it has quite some flavor on
it all right i'm digging in our first
snack
tomato garlic potato chips
[Music]
very good let me eat some more to get
that flavor
[Music]
not very um
um the garlic is not really
that prominent
it's more dome
the tomato
yeah i'm not really in a potato chips
mood right now
but they're really good no problem with
these
i'll give them a
a 9 out of 10.
it's just potato chips you can't go
wrong with that
[Music]
yeah another 10 i'll give it a 910. is
there a drink in here yes there is ah
this is orange
we always want to try the drinks
oh it is orange
it seems to be an orange drink it says
i don't know
some some
corn gas so it's um
with
fizziness
[Music]
[Laughter]
or maybe it tastes a bit more natural
than fanta
uh
let me try to open it
[Music]
i
i need my scissors to help me now i'll
use a pen because i don't have uh
scissors
okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
i should have cooled this ah
it smells so good
oh it smells so fantastic
oh
[Music]
i would say
it probably tastes a little bit less
sweet
than fanta
which is a good thing in this case i
think
[Music]
only a little bit though it's very
similar i would have to
it's been a while since i drank fanta
i think i would have to
have one with me right now to make a
proper comparison but i don't so i'm not
sure but i think i remember fanta being
extremely sweet
and yeah
it's hard to ruin orange soda that's
true you can't really do much wrong with
that either
it's very yummy it's very similar though
oh is this uh popular in spain where are
my spanish people
is it a popular drink do people prefer
to buy this over fanta
in spain
[Music]
off-brand fanta no
yes yes yes popular
find out the sweet for my taste my momma
no fanta is more popular well i mean you
know fanta has a
very big name so
okay but good to know this is a popular
drink in spain and i i understand why
would not be popular
[Music]
i'll give it a 10 out of 10. 10 out of
10.
they're very good very good i'm glad
they put in like um
um
a soft drink yes yes
yes yes a good one
a good soft drink that's cutter
[Music]
okay okay i'll go we're zooming through
this let me go back to my pamphlet
we have a page with
must-see destinations i want to look at
that for a moment the first one is
obviously
[Music]
the madrid one is madrid and it says
blue
capital of spain
has a
an
uh a fascinating
um palace plaza
the king's palace
um that would was used over the
course of history for many different
things for example for
markets
uh
public
[Music]
uh
soccer
plays and uh uh
soccer tournaments and uh future um
black hanky
future
thingies and
uh uh-huh blah blah blah and so on the
second one
is
[Music]
granada
oh
oh looks cool with like oh those
buildings with the mountain
in the back wow
oh
i wish
i could pronounce
it
oh that thing on the back is called
sierra nevada and that is a
unesco
world
thingy
yeah
very close to whatever i don't know what
you call that in
in english but it could culture
a world heritage site yeah
it's also
a popular city for students for some
reason
um
and a lot of
hip bars
and colorful markets and of a
unique nightlife apparently uh-huh
a third stop
ah
first up is uh from uh the postcard
sevilla
here oh that looks like a castle and all
mountains in the back oh
oh
so this is where
we got the postcard from
that is a city with spanish guitar music
architecture beauties and
impressive
uh art
statues
apparently
[Music]
okay i can't translate the whole thing
and last but not least is uh palma which
i think do they mean palma de mayorka
yeah they mean well let me try to show
you the picture the picture is pretty
i'm so shaky yo whoa oh people really
love to go to party in mallorca as well
we forgot to mention mallorca how did i
forget about mallorca
yeah but even though mallorca is so well
known i can say this from my own
knowledge it's so well known for
partying
but if you have a car
or can rent a car then you um can drive
around the island and you will see like
really really beautiful um
scenery
outside of the city
yeah
uh it's not only
not only like partying in mallorca but
yeah for hiking
and
traveling
through the
island my yoka is
really beautiful yeah
been there done that oh
yeah the scenery is very beautiful
apparently
um the north of mayaka
[Music]
but usually people
like to go to myocar for partying i
always like hear about it on
on german tv or i used to hear about it
on german tv
there was also those
that was there's this one german rich
celebrity who's just well known for
being rich forgot his name but he's a
[\h__\h] idiot and uh i think like there
was something about him going to my your
girl
cringe guy
um
that dude is such a idiot hate him
[Music]
yeah
prince marcus
we don't need to talk about that
uh dude
i'm sorry spain that you have to deal
with so many
idiotic
[Music]
german-speaking people
[Laughter]
you get all those i know you get all
those
obnoxious
party tourists i'm so sorry especially
the people who live in those popular
party cities
oh man
oh man you just want to enjoy living on
a beautiful island and then you keep on
getting distracted by those
obnoxious white pants wearing party
people from germany
i'm sorry
oh man okay that was the knowledge that
we get for now
and let's get another snack
and
yeah next up we have this more potato
chips ruffles but the taste is
meat
[Music]
it's just meat with bacon is it bacon
sabor
[Applause]
okay i'll have a problem opening this up
again oh dear
oh dear
oh it's a little bit open
it's a little bit open here oh i i i i
wait if it was open then it lost to the
air
this is okay
it's gonna be okay but it's okay
well i didn't open that up wasn't me
was not me
it was just a tiny hole let's hope not
too
much air got inside
um i try to open that from there
nice
oh
oh dear
[Music]
wow
what
the smell is really strong the scent
wow it does smell like ham it does i
think
both of those
it seems like both of those potato chips
are more on the
i cannot describe it on the
on the
rusty cat rust rustic coke
[Music]
what's the right
the right
word for it not savory that's not what i
mean
rustic
on the rustic side i would say i know
that's how the impression i get because
like i don't know it doesn't seem as as
how to say refreshing and light as
something like
um
salt just normal salty
uh
potato chips or so would would be or or
what do you call it what what do you
call those cream creamy ones what creamy
tasty ones i don't know i don't know
what i'm talking about let me try these
uh ruffled
ham
potato chips digging in yeah strong
flavor strong hearty flavors that's yes
that's what i meant thank you heavy and
hearty flavors yeah and i meant yeah
sour cream and onion as an example for
the opposite
thank you guys i cannot communicate if
it weren't for you guys
[Music]
wow
that is so confusing
that's so confusing
[Music]
this is so confusing
i'm so confused
[Music]
it tastes
exactly like
a strip of ham in my mouth
but
the texture is a potato chip
what
what is this what is this sorcery
[Music]
oh my god
it freaks me out
[Music]
mohammed
i don't think i've ever had potato chips
that so successfully
recreated the taste that they wanted to
recreate
how
it freaks me out man
what
i mean
i mean you get you get exactly what's on
the package so i think i have to get
give it a 10 out of 10.
i would probably not
really go for it in the grocery store i
just always like my simple
salty
potato chips i just go for the normal
ones to be honest
but that is
yeah that is exactly what they're
advertising i guess i'll give it a 10
out of 10.
if you guys really like ham
you will go ham over these potato chips
wow that was so funny
no that was not funny that was too
obvious
wow let me drink some uh
liquid
[Music]
what the hell man i need to try more
ruffle chips maybe they always
recreate everything perfectly
no
you're so funny i'm dying oh my god i'm
gonna pay your hospital bills
okay nice uh
nice is there like
[Music]
is this one popular in spain
i mean ruffles so far we have lays and
ruffles which are worldwide
internationally popular
brands
in any way so i guess they're popular
everywhere but i wonder if these
specific tastes are popular
or just you know ruffles itself very
popular flavor really
only this flavor
the flavors are specific to spain
wow okay yeah
oh
well then
[Music]
wow okay oh there's some ketchup slap oh
i
then i'm satisfied so far
very good okay next snack
next snack
sukima you mean which one should we go
for
i'll close my eyes
[Music]
i said stop because i knew there was
something chocolatey there and i wanted
to eat that but now we see already what
what is this
oh advertisement
oh
i don't want that advertising no i'm
going i'm going i'm going for this
because it's on the top
what do we have here oh that looks cute
what
what that looks cute what is this
the [\h__\h] is is that supposed to be a
chicken
what is this
okay it looks kind of creepy when i show
it to you in that angle but it's kind of
cute
yeah look at it like this
is that a chicken and it's eggs
a naked weird
milky
um
chicken with hands
and lips
i don't know it looks kind of like a
chicken
[Music]
or duck is it a duck
but that looks really interesting it's
called congruitos
blanco i like white chocolate i do like
white chocolate um
if it's from
europe
the white chocolate i've eaten from uh
japan i did not enjoy and the white
chocolate i've eaten i think i've had
some kind of american white chocolate
before i also did not like it if it's
from europe i trust it
white chocolate and peanuts with some
cute
signs on it i don't want to know what do
i not want to know
what does congoitos mean
the forbidden snack
is this a yeah it's a oh
[Music]
oh
aha
well let me eat it um
let's we just eat it and then we'll
never talk about it ever again
just hope it tastes good
let me try to open this up
[Music]
that is so weird if that is true then
that is really really weird but okay let
me smell
oh i smell the peanuts
okay okay
peanuts
oh it's cute inside
it's kind of cute these little balls and
they look cute and they have some
some letters and stuff on it
why does it look so cute to me you guys
don't even understand why
but
this is cute
this is cute look how shiny they are
sorry
[Music]
are you
cute
yeah
that's cute okay what do they say
oh one has number four can we play um
what what is that called again that the
bingo can we play bingo with these
i have a four and uh
what is that an sr5
i think it's an
s
and a small
no a one no okay i guess it's a five and
a one and a four
wow
but there's also letters
and hearts and and hashtags and all
kinds of stuff
why
we can do bingo
lottery
today's numbers are
five
one
and four
who wins
who
wins i win
okay i'm digging in
[Music]
hmm
oh
i love this
[Music]
very good i like how
the balance of
white chocolate
and the peanuts is
there's more chocolate i would say the
peanuts are not overpowering them yeah
they remind me of the m ms
but there is more chocolate than with m
m's i would say
you know there's m m's with the peanuts
inside
yeah but i i
i think for the mms the
nuts kind of overpower the chocolate
but these are great
these are really good
the chocolate is really good too i will
give this a out of 10. yo is this gonna
be our best snack box ever
i mean best as in
the one that i like the most so far out
of all of her snack books oh my god
oh my god
i like them
i want some more
[Music]
this one is a
what is that it's some kind of face on
it
it's not a number it's not
what what is that
it's partially cut off it's not properly
printed
[Music]
um
maybe it's the mascots oh yeah it's the
mascot's face
[Music]
okay
yeah
all right
oh
there's filipinos in here i've heard of
those
wait what
no those are not it
what
they lied to me
where the ah here are the filipinos
[Music]
filipino filipino filipino that's a
black opis song
filipinos aren't they also popular in
other countries
[Music]
where else are they popular are they
popular in the philippines
i've heard from these
and it's with white chocolate again do
spanish people like white chocolate
oh why is there so much white chocolate
i love it
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah they're popular elsewhere too
i have those in finland too really
oh
papa well okay uh
so i guess these are probably in spain
hopefully
they seem to be uh inside was like kind
of like something that looks like a
brownie texture or
i don't know covered with real white
chocolate what's what's fake white
chocolate
oh my
[Music]
it's real white chocolate
it's like a cookie but in form of a
donut
uh-huh okay
i'm curious
filipinos never had these before again a
weird choice of name for a snack but
okay
oh
cute
oh that is cute
wait that is cute
why are these snacks so cute
these look tiny little donuts
[Music]
wow the coating looks nice too
and they're small
oh
okay
but so it looked like brownie texture
from the packaging but someone said it's
more like a cookie
okay i'm digging in
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
ah let me eat the second half
okay
the white chocolate
really good
a good amount of chocolate again here
the balance is once again
very good i think they nailed to the
balance it's not too much cooking not
too much chocolate it combines
nicely and melts nicely inside your
mouth
do i sound like a professional food
tester
it's real it's real
and um the cookie texture is
magnifique
it is
uh
it is um divine
i do have to say
[Music]
even though i like the cookie texture
there's um a slight hint of some kind of
taste in the in the chocolate cookie
that i don't quite dig
um but it doesn't ruin the whole cookie
it just kind of
um
i think it kind of just not fits
perfectly in my mind
but if if that hint of taste wouldn't be
there it would probably just
taste like a oreo or whatever
um
i don't know i don't know what it is i
don't know what i'm tasting there but
there's something there that bothers me
but besides that it's pretty good the
balance is good the texture is good the
the visuals are really good
um
i will give it a
uh
i'll give it us um
seven point five out of no no you know
it deserves an eight actually i don't
know i feel like even good numbers today
eight out of ten
eight out of ten i'm nice today duncan
and milk
see i never dunk anything in milk but i
can see how that might be good yeah
[Music]
i'm really nice today i'm i have a good
day so far
stressful but still a good day
um
yummy yummy
oh
oh oh oh oh this says it's a spanish
classic
cacao kickstarter
from
[Music]
so
again a good snack i think so far these
these snacks are all
um
popular and well-known snacks so
awesome we're having a good run here
yeah i guess there's a normal milk
chocolate or dark chocolate version of
this because this seems to be just a
white chocolate version of it but with
the other with the original one i wonder
if the inside the cookie
is also
a cacao or is it white chocolate on the
other
hand is it like the
[Music]
opposite there's a dark one but the
white is better oh that doesn't happen
often that the the the the like um
different tasting one it ends up being
the more popular one than the original
it's also cacao it's a regular cookie
oh
regular you mean just a normal
thing a normal cookie that doesn't taste
like anything besides cookie
so the white one is better i can see
that
yeah and then it seems more special
[Music]
okay okay
next snack
[Music]
this is next rulies
snack demise snack
it looks like cheap something cheesy and
puffy
you guys know these it's like cheetos
probably yeah
a coin snack
[Music]
spanish cheetos is it spanish chips but
people seem to be excited about them so
they seem to know them
oh
prepare for ketchup oh it's a ketchup
flavored
off-brand risque oh
uh-huh why did they not send me the real
deal
is the is the real deal not spanish
[Music]
is this more spanish than the real deal
espana okay
all right
now let me open it up she's ketchup
flavor
they cheaped out yeah
well ketchup flavor i don't know i i
guess i would like it more than cheese
flavor i'm
i'm not a huge fan of cheese flavored
things okay
inside
[Music]
looks like that
uh
and let me get some out why am i only
getting tiny ones
okay this is what they look like there
are different shapes some smaller ones
some lengthy ones it's kind of weird
really random
all right
[Music]
they do smell
i guess a little bit like ketchup okay
i'm digging in
oh
oh there they are hollow inside
[Music]
not really like cheetos
oh wait are they hollow
[Music]
felt like they're hollow
anything i attached will be orange
forever
but so far my gloves are looking okay
[Music]
no maybe not they're not hollow they're
just really puffy really airy inside
[Music]
the flavor is a bit weak
it still kind of feels it still kind of
tastes a little bit cheesy even though
it's supposed to be ketchup
um
not really my thing but they're not bad
they're not bad but also not really
blowing me away
[Music]
i don't know
i'll give them a 5 out of 10. well
they're not that impressive um
maybe the yeah maybe the reschedules the
original ones would have been better
you guys seem to say the same
reschedules are the real deal
of friend
gonna be your friend not your huddle
i mean they're not bad but she's just
not impressed
yeah they should have sent actual
reschedules
[Music]
not the best of spain no
no we agree we seem to agree nice
everything is in harmony
[Music]
a divine looking snack box it is what do
i go for next you already
see
the this yellow one pretty well and it
looks very interesting
[Music]
look at this
a square packaging
says la casitos sounds very spanish
[Music]
what is this this looks
cool it's like a
it's like a one of those um
chocolate hippos
with uh smarties inside
interesting
[Music]
something with milk
oh
[Music]
no omg
no oh my god is it not gonna make me go
oh my god
okay i'm excited to eat this
this is interesting really interesting
oh okay so inside we have
uh these packages
let me take this one out
oh
oh the packaging looks um
uh like i don't know fresh
like well designed and and
like someone who has graphic design as
their passion did it looks very um
catching eye-catching i would say
[Music]
apparently we're now rating the
packaging too
but i'm saying this because like for our
korean snack box for example a lot of
the things looked really old you know
what i mean
mini hider
okay oh
uh-huh easy to share
[Music]
can break it off there easily
and i'm digging in
[Music]
oh
hmm
[Music]
wow it is
softer than i imagined
there it feels like
it really melts very fast
inside my mouth
and the smarties in there
disappear fast
because i bite into them and then crunch
scrunch crunch
and then it's just little tiny tiny tiny
bits of smarties
[Music]
but they kind of leave some some kind of
sparkle in my mouth while i'm eating it
which is fun
it is fun it seems this seems like a
snack kids would enjoy a lot hmm
the chocolate is not as good as kinder
chocolate whoo
if this was made with kinder chocolate i
would eat this every [\h__\h] day
but
it's so good chocolate it's okay it's
frizz um yeah decent chocolate what are
you calling saying pimp toma la casitos
what is everyone saying is that like uh
the tv advertisement
ping pong tomatoes what does that mean
it's a meme
spanish memes
[Laughter]
that's so funny
i i i bit into the middle so you see
what it looks like inside
um
[Music]
focus it doesn't want to focus but it's
low-key um hollow there
and you see some kind of smartie in
there
[Music]
yeah the legend the letter the milky
cream
is very
very very soft mmm
okay
[Music]
how should i rage this one
it would be better with kinder chocolate
so i'll give it an 8 out of 10.
[Music]
no
okay
oh my god
i'm impressed holy [\h__\h] okay okay more
chocolate more chocolate here we go
juicy does super chuck wow
nuevo xl whoa
wow look at that xl wow
okay
more chocolate
more chocolate let's go
you know this one
seems like uh
waivers crispy
crispy cookie waivers in between
um
yeah with a lot of chocolate in between
and outside
whistle
so
here we go oh it has the snickers veins
oh did you see that tweet
was that photoshopped by the way
when the the one where the snickers was
smooth as [\h__\h] and then snickers was
like we are not removing the veins in
our stickers
was that photoshop
i think that was photoshop like how can
you accidentally
make an unveined sneakers and sell it i
don't i don't think like it could at
least not only be one it would have to
be like a whole batch i would say where
the machine
just didn't work properly that was
producing this i don't know
it's weird
that was that was weird but okay here we
have veins real veins in the chocolate
bar
wow
god
all right
all right all right i'm digging in
wow
[Music]
hmm
wow
[Music]
oh i love the
waivers inside oh it feels so good
biting into this
by by looking at the packaging
i wasn't sure if it was gonna be
wavers or cookies i was hoping for
waivers and it was wavers
and several layers of waivers so it
feels so good to bite into that and it
was like the moment you bite into it
i see like particles of wavers flying
around my mouth
[Laughter]
it reminds me of uh mana mana chocolate
in austria we have this really popular
uh waiver um
chocolate that people also like to buy
as a souvenir to bring hope
but it's by far not as chocolatey as
this one because this is covered with a
lot of chocolate there is indeed a lot
of chocolate
oh but i love the i love the waiver the
waiver
you know what i mean then this is a good
one chocolate wafers
oh 10 out of 10.
i really like the snack box wow spanish
friends i love your snacks
wow
i'm not gonna eat the whole thing now
though i still have some other things to
eat and this might take a while to eat
it all
no no no
[Music]
ah
oh interesting
it's like a swirl
and then inside several layers of
what is that biscuit
and milk and something like that
[Music]
is this well known to mosquitoes fake
mosquitoes again with the all-friend
snacks oh
i see i see well this one better be good
mosquitoes but from myocard
[Music]
mosquitoes are the real deal
oh my god
what
but it does seem to be biscuit uh inside
so okay i'm
i'm
i'm hooked i'm interested you have my
attention dear snack
i'm opening it up right now
if i manage to do it properly
you know what it's time to visit spain
again there's so many places i want to
visit i should do a europe tour like
one or one or two nights per country go
for europe go go everywhere
i i miss
greece
i miss
spain
i miss france i want to go to
switzerland i wanna go to the north
you know where finland and norway and
everything is i wanna go there
i wanna go
i also kinda wanna go to england again
if you guys let me
okay
what do we have oh oh oh the shape is
not a perfectly round shape it is uh
like a
snail
[Music]
oh it smells good smells good smells
good
[Music]
oh my god
it
tastes like milk or tender
i [\h__\h] love milka tender
oh my god it tastes like milk it's in
there
[Music]
it's milky tender
make a tender do you know america tender
i love it so much it's so so expensive
i'm i always wanted mega tender as a
child but it was so expensive
but they're so good
it tastes like milk or tender
[Music]
it does not only taste like milk tender
it has the same
amount of biscuit and the same amount of
cream and the same amount of chocolate
no maybe a bit more chocolate than milk
or tender hmm
maybe a big one
or i'm not sure
[Music]
that's really good
ah you might have a bit more cream
actually
[Music]
you need to what do you mean it does not
taste like michael turner i say it
tastes like milk
it does
okay maybe not 100 but for me it gets
pretty close
um
wow wow
no i mean the original milka tender
would still be
better but i suppose this is cheaper
now i'm curious what the the
non-off-brand version of this
uh
is like you see my box again
what did you say fosquitos
someone sent me some mosquitos mamma mia
sent me those mosquitos amigos
[Music]
they are fluffy huh mosquitoes are more
fluffier
[Music]
hand over the fusquitos
give it to me
i know you don't say mama mia but i
thought it was fitting and i don't know
how to say mamma mia in spanish how do i
say mamma mia in spanish espanol
not mosquitoes i don't want the
mosquitoes [\h__\h] the mosquitoes i want
the first quitos
[Music]
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] mosquitoes get out of here
mosquitoes love me though
[Music]
okay okay yummy did i rate it yet i'll
give it a 9 out of 10. holy [\h__\h] this is
really our
best rated snack box
oh my god imam is
[Music]
there is
one last snack in here you know what i
was worried about you know
recently for the swedish snack box and
also for the korean snack box i
bought some extra things because i
thought it wouldn't be enough what's in
here but because of a good track record
with this box now
um the fact that you know it's not like
how many snacks is one two three four
five
it's ten snacks including the drink so
it's actually a good amount and because
they're all pretty good i have no
problem with it the last thing is a
jelly thing i'm glad that there wasn't
too much jelly [\h__\h] in here because i
usually don't like them that much i
don't i don't really buy jelly snacks it
was mostly um chocolate and some potato
chips but this one is
finished
and what
[Music]
i don't know maybe
um
yeah maybe something like that
filled twizzlers
legalize
vietnamese a brand of a lot of different
gummies
i wonder what the flavor is maybe
maybe strawberry
a better version of tweezer who knows
licorice
oh no
red licorice
[Music]
oh wait but it smells good
oh never mind licorice is only bad when
it's black
nice okay
it smells good you scared me with the
word licorice but
this is fun wow
it's a beautiful perfect shape
shiny
wow
wow look at that
dynamic shape wow
it makes you think of your
spine perhaps if your spine is twisted
like this please go to a doctor
ah
[Music]
um
is this really licorice
it's just it just tastes like normal
kind of like jelly something but
uh
there we go
um there's like an outer layer that's a
little bit thicker do you see this and
then inside there's a different kind of
jelly you see that the color difference
yeah the inside is like a bit softer
than the outside jelly
inside is like just normal jelly and
outside maybe is licorice i don't know
red licorice isn't licorice not a huda
learn something new
and
taste is good
doesn't taste like licorice
very good it's not sour or anything
though
attends in supakunai
normally with these kind of things i
always expect them to be sour but this
is not sour doll it's just normal
sweet tasting
[Music]
i guess yeah kind of like a
jelly strawberry taste
[Music]
yeah this might be really good as well
if you put you know one of those uh like
those uh sour
um
sour sugar thingies around it if you
coat it with that that could be
really good too
what are people singing is that like the
advertisement again or meme mercha
[Music]
yeah
did i sing that in the advertisement on
tv
supermarket ah
[Music]
oh it's a supermarket
i see him
okay well
this was really good too i'll give this
a
8 out of 10.
that was the last snack they're all
really good
wow
i'm impressed guys i'm really impressed
now don't leave yet spanish friends
although i mean maybe you could leave
because you're you're also you're gonna
know the answers to the quiz
i have a quiz for you
ah
our spain quiz is ready everybody
sit back and put your thinking caps on
it's quite time
[Music]
are you ready for the quiz
all right um yeah let's see let's see i
don't know the answer to the first
question already i have no idea what
that is
where can you don't google it by the way
don't google it
um
where can you visit
[Music]
the first question
is a boxing question
where can you vision
barcelona
or
sevilla
valencia
[Music]
there you go
don't google
quiz time
where can you visit the sagrada family
[Music]
what is that family who are those people
oh
the spanish people know the answer
[Music]
barcelona is winning and it's it's
a church
what it's a cathedral why is it called
family
why is it called family
i thought it was a family
maybe like a like a royal family
a big funky looking unfinished cathedral
oh i want to look it up
family
ah
wow
it does look
interesting what is this architecture
[Music]
called wow guys you're allowed to google
it now look at that
it it does look
insane oh it even lights up
wait that looks so
like out of place
like i i would imagine to see that in a
game or something not in an actual city
like that
it takes so much time to build and mix
this stuff yeah yeah this must be mixing
styles this is weird
but like not in a bad way but
weird
i did go to art school yes for a while
what the [\h__\h] is that especially oh my
god the entrance
what is that
entrance
thing
what is this
the more i look at it the more funky it
looks to me
and what is inside just a normal church
you can just go there for normal church
things like saying amen
[Music]
it will be finished in a few centuries
wow designer was an artist
[Music]
wow
antoni gaudi
his work
on the building is part of a unesco
world heritage site
construction started
and they're still not done
completed after 2026. you guys are so
close
1882 until
2026. you guys are so close to finishing
it oh my god
where's we're gonna be alive when they
finish this
wow
almost there
like 90
let's go let's go
almost finished installing this building
well come see we got skye
oh damn
okay okay cool hey this building is
really interesting i need to go to
barcelona and check it out
yeah
okay question number two
oh
um okay to which
island group
belongs
this one i won't say it out loud yet so
you can't google it so fast
and bye
[Music]
um
okay i'm looking up the english names
for all of this because i
don't want to mistranslate it
uh-huh
[Music]
and what the [\h__\h] is that name
oh that's like a school
okay wow beautiful oh all these google
pictures so beautiful okay here we go
here's the question to which group of
islands
belongs
uh
maybe i mistranslated the name actually
you know what i mean
[Music]
the valley eric islands the cannery
islands or the gymnasian islands you
know obviously
there's a lot of people from spain
watching right now and they know the
answer but guys
do your best
don't cheat
try to answer
do your best fighter
yeah this one's easy
i wouldn't have really known
i would have had to guess to be honest
know of the island's name um but
yeah i wouldn't have known i want to
visit
it looks so pretty
the [\h__\h]
what is that
and what is that they have like on the
beach they have like some huge thing
that looks like a like a pool
is that um
what is that
is that from some kind of hotel or
hotel playa player
can i
oh it's a famous hotel apparently
it really stands out from like pictures
of the of the beach
hotel playa orleans
oh can i stay in that hotel
are you
these pictures i don't see that big pool
[Music]
yeah are we talking about the same thing
that doesn't look like it
[Music]
is it
no it doesn't look like that you guys
know what i'm talking about it's like
pretty round and it has another island
inside
gymnastics
[Music]
yup probably
ah
[Music]
i don't want to show them because
copyright and stuff you know
[Music]
it's an open-air swimming pool complex
located in puerto de la cruz
the laser park of a total of
approximately 100 000 square meters is
centered around an artificial lake
lago martinez includes several islands
gardens so it's not a restaurant it's
not a hotel
it's a
a leisure park
cool
coolio
okay the answer was the cannery islands
of course of course no yes yes of course
all right next question
oh
cool
of these
spanish actors
has yet
to win
and oscar what kind of question is that
[Music]
i feel bad for that person
oh but two of these names only two of
them sound familiar to me i don't know
about you guys but we have antonio
banderas everybody knows antonio
bandells i don't know where i know this
name from but i just know it uh javia
about them and penelope cruz
oh penelope cruz is from
spain
is that soul
[Music]
at zoro
she's from spain wow
i didn't know she was from spain
[Music]
oh by the way crash cars crash quiz
crash course spanish buenos dias guten
morgen adios bye bye
pardon
me sorry excuse me
llamas
llamas yamas
what's your name habla english do you
speak english
tengo
ambre i am hungry dolces sweets
hasta ponto
see you later
[Music]
cute llamas where are the llamas
what's your name okay the answer uh
seems to be according to you guys
antonio banderas is that true
yes it's true
wow such a famous person and he has yet
to win an oscar is he not that good at
acting
roasted
absolutely taken apart by takanasi
kiwawa
okay
oh what is the
hardest
[Music]
okay
next question
what is the tallest mountain of spain
picoanetto pico del veletta or pico de
tede
which one is it also i'm going to turn
off the webcam by the way
[Music]
goodbye screen
goodbye
easy really i don't know
i think if you don't live in uh if
you've never been to spain then you
probably don't know the answer
so don't feel bad about it
um but we seem to have a winner
pickle dictator according to
the chat
according to our spanish visitors
the answer is
um
c pico de taylor
congratulations
another question answered correctly by
the majority of the chat
a one more
one more we have two more questions
next question
[Music]
what this is interesting
might come in handy what does a spanish
person say one day
when
someone
[Music]
jesus
okay without there there is supposed to
be a
turned around exclamation marks in front
of it and then after it's the right way
but i don't know how to type that so
what does a spanish person say when
someone sneezes
jesus
well you would probably pronounce that
hit jesus or something like that maybe
they hello
oh wait a type of a h but it's j
i just typed it the way i would uh say
it it's supposed to be with j they jello
but you said the hallo and i was
thinking it while i was writing it so i
messed it up
do you is it really jesus oh my god
is it really jesus
that would be funny
[Music]
not salute apparently not maybe that's
also an option
either salute or or jesus
[Music]
jesus
yes it's correct it's jesus
why do they say that i wonder okay one
last question
[Music]
what
instrument
is played by
women
who
what is this
[Music]
ah monica
castanoelas
[Music]
and uh
okay the first one seemed familiar it's
an our harmonica and
casta casanetos or something like that
you guys already know what what the
question is
what instrument is played by the woman
who danced sevillanas
[Music]
what does that mean
is that a special dance like tango
you know what i'm gonna look it up on
coco
castano
are
[Laughter]
[Music]
but they don't have i don't feel oh my
is it do they really have something in
their hand
do they do they really have something or
do they not always have something
in their hand
it's flamenco a type of flamenco
[Music]
let me mute it okay
let me mute my audio i want to hear this
i'm curious now
seven hours flamenco dancing in
barcelona
oh so pretty
i can dance this too
oh i know how to dance like that
yeah yeah yeah easy easy
but they don't have to cast casta
nuellas
why do they not have the castanoelas
guys
[Music]
oh
wow
they have the casta noellas in their
hands
it's legit
cuando quando
oh i love that sound yes let's go
[Laughter]
[Music]
looks like fun
let's go
let's go i sent you guys the link in the
chat so you guys know what i'm looking
at wow
oh the fire i feel it
oh that's fun i wonder if that's easy to
to do while dancing
or if you need to be very good at
multitasking to do that do you actually
need to learn this like you know like
you learn an instrument like a guitar or
is it easier to pick up i wonder but all
in all you guys have answered the
questions correctly there's just one
more thing here
um there's always like a
um a
a recipe
that they uh have on the last page guess
what the recipe is for for spain
it's an interesting choice
arroz con leche
spanish
uh
a porridge for me
no
why
[Laughter]
it's an interesting choice it's a recipe
and and how to cook it
it's a pretty easy one
i don't really like porridge but yeah
it's some kind of spanish porridge
yeah why not paella maybe maybe because
it's too too obvious
maybe it was too obvious
okay let me turn on my music again
[Music]
okay
thank you everybody that was the spanish
snack box yay
[Music]
was really good i think i don't even
need to like compare it with the others
i'm pretty sure this was our best
snack box so far
oh
thank you
thank you thank you
gracias
guys yes for all the new spanish people
who checked in today
uh
for the first time maybe please
subscribe
maybe i will visit spain again sometime
soon and then i'll need you guys's
advice
where to go
and all that yeah
were they popular they seem to have been
popular i checked for the snacks with
with you guys in the chat and the
reception was very good so
yeah there were no what the [\h__\h] is this
never seen this [\h__\h] before
reactions so um
thank you
thank you guys for watching
yeah i really like the snacks it's nice
to have a snack box where
it really
i really like the taste of it
some off-brand things yeah but
maybe they had problems getting the
original
and the offbrand things were just easier
to order
in in masses as well
maybe
yeah i want to visit barcelona
i want to visit barcelona and tenerife
now i'm for i want to see that big ass
church and i want to see that beach with
the
with the pool
i want to see that
yeah i'm excited to travel again
sometime
thank you guys for sharing the
information indeed yeah yeah yeah always
really grateful to have
help in the chat to judge whether or not
something is legit see i don't want to
you know
announce
that i have this snack book stream and
then people come in being excited to see
me react to snacks from their country
and then oopsie doodles it's snacks that
no one has ever heard of or snacks that
are not really representative of their
country and so on
but
yeah i need you guys to judge that and
uh today was pretty good i would say
thank you for helping me out we are
going to read super chats so you're uh
very welcome to stay
i don't know why but i feel like
my rib cage is
threatening my life today
i feel like i got no space today
in my
in my um
upper body
a bit tough to yeah
[Music]
i started physical therapy today and i
had a stressful day and then i put on a
bra for the first time in a long time i
know you guys can't really relate to
that most of you guys but
but and then that bride felt like it
wanted to strangle me and i think um
i think all bras are out there to get me
brad's [\h__\h] hate me they have me on
their radar they want to kill me
they were trying to strangle me
suffocating me
yeah
it [\h__\h] hurts
oh
you can't breathe bad breath yes i don't
i don't mind pants let's ban brands
i need to get
get new ones maybe that fit properly but
that's girl's talk
maybe
someone
can go brass shopping with me when the
whole en girls are coming to visit me
uh
yeah i don't know all the ones i have
are so uncomfortable
but that's girls talk
[Laughter]
uh
you're so stupid why would i bow arenas
who says that that one's gonna fit me
[Music]
even even if
even of size ones it would fit who says
that we have the same size of
ribcage
but then then the under
measurements are the same and that's the
important one that's why i can't breathe
when i wear more anyway this doesn't
matter
what a stupid idea what a stupid idea
okay okay
[Laughter]
i'm not wearing one now by the way that
that
turquoise thing you see that's a bikini
that's it's not a bra
it doesn't hurt it's okay
[Music]
can we go to my normal office
moving
we were
oh my god
what happened
every time every time i turn on one
layer in the other um
layout it always messes with this one
it's so weird and confusing
[Music]
are you too brave i can't breathe
i can't breathe
[Music]
okay this week is dead
we started this week with today and the
there won't be any
there won't be a schedule for this week
but i can tell you if you're curious i
can tell you
uh i think tomorrow is portal
yes
yes tomorrow is portal 2
[Music]
at
6 pm my time probably
yeah no this one is alone this is not
collab yet i'm playing solo lolololo
first
hashtag
it's gonna be two days in a row
hopefully i can clear it in two days in
a row
okay
yeah we're gonna learn how portal 2
works and then use our knowledge to
collab with kobochang
i need i need to still discuss with her
what time we're going to do it uh i hope
i don't forget
[Music]
by the way i asked i asked navi mama i
asked navi mama i asked nami mama about
um
about about about teaching me korean
and she said yeah anytime in may is okay
because i asked if we can do it in may
because i mean april is pretty much over
yeah navi mama will teach me korean
in the club in may
and then i also asked
if if i were to go to korea
if she can show me around
and she said yes
so
i'm gonna
meet up with navi mama in an rl
and have her is my tour guide i'm so
excited
maybe we can even do an off collab
an off collab with amelia's mom
wouldn't that be fun oh my god
i'm so excited because like i don't i
wanna i don't mind traveling alone in
general
but
um having absolutely no one to like help
me or show me around or so
any friend or so in a country where i
don't really speak the language is
scary so
the only person i could think of was
navi mama
and i was a bit worried about asking her
but she was really excited about it
yeah
yeah yeah
and i also asked
in genma as well if it's okay it should
be okay
other korean people
in the chat right now
let me tell you papa go
i will visit
[Music]
but before that she will teach my korean
and may in a collab stream
what a collaboration
yes
i need some help
with some help from navi mama
navi mama
[Music]
i'm excited
she's so cute i'm excited to meet her
yes you'll be my
navigators you'll be my navigator
i'll have my navigator for real
[Music]
the dream come true there's a dream come
true
oh my god navigator tm
i'll copyright her
i will copyright her
yata
i mean we didn't decide on any dates yet
or so i just asked her if she would do
it and she
she said yes so
it's at that stage now so
but i am i'm really um
looking forward to it already in my mind
it's set we're doing it
okay yesterday we started reading the
super chat from this one so i will do my
best
to finish it today and also read the
others that i have fallen behind on
eh
nakata
[Music]
um i know we stopped reading at
uh
and some
english name was like
right after what was that one
well i said they would remember
um
[Music]
see i don't really like stopping reading
super chats in betw like in the middle
of
one i found it i think i found it
moonlight butterfly there we go i found
it
okay
moonlight butterfly thank you for the
pinky
tips for tensile if you travel to korea
oh perfect this is literally what we
just talked about
you should always prepare three weather
types of clothes there are four distinct
seasons in korea but more than two
seasons are mixed in a day
foreign
[Music]
ah
you mean there's a high chance of rain
maybe during the day that it might be
really hot and then it might suddenly
rain or it might be super hot and then
suddenly it might be super cold in one
day really is it that random
is it that random
[Music]
but the weather is no joke the weather
is no joke apparently
really
oh okay i mean so always bring a jacket
i guess really
even in the in the middle of summer like
july
august
really i don't i can't imagine it's
getting cold in july and august
if it's anything like the weather in
japan
i feel like it might be a bit similar
uh aren't they like kind of on the same
height you know what i mean
world map
aren't they like kind of
maybe not cho
maybe i'm talking [\h__\h] right now let
me
not embarrass myself
google maps
no no they are they are they are on the
same like you know
you know middle thing
but
uh i probably want to go
or i can't go until probably i don't
know august or september
oh because until then i'm busy anyway
doing other things like going to the
mountains and having my birthday and all
that so i printed i think the earliest i
will go is august or september which
will probably be very hot
same height but geography is different
hong kong
just very humid and hot with a classic
occasional heavy rain well
the very hot and very humid i know very
well from japan and i hate
the humidity
so much so i'm not looking forward to
that
maybe i should go in september it's
probably less hot in september than it
is in october in august i mean
i really can't like my body just can't
handle that heat and the humidity it
just eats me up
yeah just standing outside you feel like
the air is hugging you but it's like the
worst hug that you can ever imagine
[Music]
cat hair
i went to physical therapy today here's
a tangent
i went to physical therapy and um
uh i mean
all the exercises are obviously things
that as i know as i knew it i told you
guys
it's stuff i learned before
[Music]
but there was one funny thing
they
[Music]
there you go i got the cat hair
they have like they put me
for like two minutes they put me on this
on this wobbly thing
that goes like
[Music]
you know what i mean
it's a
[Music]
[Laughter]
it actually goes like
[Music]
i know
um
[Music]
yeah
it's like really strong
i actually the problem was i didn't eat
breakfast
and um
i
i didn't know what to expect and this
was like after the physical therapy part
where we just did like
really basic [\h__\h] like turning your head
from right to left right to left wow so
impressed and then yeah
it's like a balance board i guess but
like you can make it really strong and
they did turn it pretty strong
um
and my body was shaking
and then i said oh my god i don't know
if i can keep this up for two minutes
lately because i'm starting to feel
really sick and she was like okay we can
turn it low and i'm like sorry i think
it's probably it's not because i'm sick
i think it's probably because i didn't
eat breakfast yet and then she looks at
me and she's like what
you didn't eat breakfast and i'm like
yeah don't worry about me the thing is i
just got up like two hours ago don't
know one hour ago don't worry about me
i'm gonna eat breakfast after this
and she's like
she she was really like looking at me
like so shocked like as if that was
like a really weird thing i just said
maybe she was worried that i don't know
i just have like some kind of eating
disorder
but no i it was just because you know
don't worry i'm i just sometimes i skip
breakfast and eat it later
because i have no time
and wake up right before the appointment
[Music]
but then i made sure to tell her i'm
gonna eat breakfast after this don't
worry
and then she was like
really insisting that next time i eat
breakfast before
and that i should not do this
i was like
you should eat breakfast at least
something
eat breakfast and i'm like yeah yeah
yeah yeah i normally i love breakfast i
eat breakfast all the time i love
breakfast
i told her i wake up i woke up late and
then she was like oh do you work like
all night i'm like
no but like
i work i do home office
everybody calls it home office so i say
i work from home office and and you know
i'm flexible so i tend to kind of like
work i guess somewhat late but then i
also stay up really late so yeah it's
not that i work at night it's just uh
yeah i don't know
i mean i do work late like until
midnight
but
yeah
yeah no but yes but nobody yes
um
yeah
anyway yes home office we like to call
it home office it doesn't exist in
english well in austria and i suppose
probably in germany as well ever since
the sea thing happened and everybody
started working from home more people
really coined the word and and really
everybody uses it everybody just says i
work i do home i do home office
like uh amazon delivery guy
uh also
today
uh i probably was impressed that i'm
always at home at this time and
therefore asked me yo
do you like work do you do home office
and i'm like yeah yeah yeah
everybody says that word it's so common
now um
home office
do you do home office or don't you go to
uh
your company and i say uh a home office
it's an english word but now we use it
in german
without translating just like that yeah
[Laughter]
i do home office for two years now yeah
that's what people would say exactly
home office yeah yeah same here in
mexico same in spanish now no hodo
[Music]
karma
no that that's not cool of course it has
to be an english word otherwise it
doesn't sound cool things just sound so
much cooler in english
when you use it with a different
language like inside of a different
language you know maybe maybe it doesn't
sound quite so cool when
you're using it while speaking english
anyway in america or wherever but here
in germany or austria or so it's really
cool to use english words you know it's
fancy and hip
yeah
also yeah the word freelancer too
[Music]
what do you what do you mean what
what detroit would
[Music]
anyway
thank you moonlight butterfry uh you're
welcome to give me more tips for korea
because now i'm really planning my trip
i'm excited
uh okay next support me
me
oh oh oh oh
no don't sit on the chair
no no no no no no on on
close
enough oh yeah and that was not e that
was an ah
e
it doesn't if it's a circle there
doesn't the
n
g come
first i would read it as mang
g
no
but it says my no
i thought it was ng
[Music]
i just accept it
close enough
[Music]
yes yes
like that
why i thought the order is like in each
sign from left to right or or left
top left to bottom right
but
it says
ah maybe because the
ng is like uh
uh silent
maybe
that that makes sense
but why is it silent
when do i know it's silent only makes ng
silence at the end
[Music]
oh wait that's a placeholder for the i
ah
that makes even more sense
that makes more sense
that was not the ng it's just
[Music]
that makes so much sense
whenever i see a circle now i always
read it as ng but that's not right
[Music]
icarus fall packaging for the pinky
duolingo prepare the special gifts for
attention fox milk cucumber milk
i give free promotion to duolingo and
they pay me back with fox milk and
cucumber milk what the [\h__\h] so
disappointing give me something proper
stupid grain bird
i'm gonna make cucumber milk out of you
no one's gonna notice because your green
cucumber cucumber is green
people are not gonna doubt me when i say
this is just cucumber milk don't worry
about it i just threw a cucumber and
milk in the mixer and this is what i got
but in reality i put the duolingo owl
and milk in a mixer and that's what i
got
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay i just just a disclaimer
i'm joking
[Music]
there was just
i mean this was obviously a joke right
can i tell you guys something that i
thought was
stupidly
unnecessary and
somewhat funny
um
[Music]
remember
oh remember my um kibaba stream
first of all you know how much i love
cats right
you know how much i love cats i would
never do anything to hurt a cat i love
cats they're my life okay i love them
so
in my kibaba stream i mentioned um
amen bringing me
alien cats
right and then what was it the alien cat
was like
dangerous or so
so
what did we do
did we feed it to the other cats i don't
know what happened with the alien cat
ah i fed it too you know oh yeah right
[Music]
yeah because it was attacking my other
cats i think it ate the other kids
because it's an alien cat it's an alien
cat okay it's a it's not even a real cat
it's an alien it's a it's a fictional
made-up alien cat it's not even a
made-up normal cat it's a made-up alien
cat that we're talking about here who
knew who imagined that for reason
someone would bring some kind of
alien cat from space to us in reality
obviously it would probably not be
a normal cat it would probably not
behave like a normal cat if it's from
space it would probably try to kill us
or eat us or poison us so whatsoever it
would probably not be like a normal cat
right
so anyway just
keep that in mind maybe that an alien
cat is probably gonna be dangerous for
us to deal with
but
the fact that i said
i found this really funny
the
fact that i made
up from the top of my head by the way
this was just random babbling this
wasn't even planned
um
dad um i basically had this alien cat in
my story that also it was
ended up um eliminated by
being made into food and triggered
somebody
one one particular
listener
um
was so triggered by that
that they after that spammed me with
hate comments everywhere
how could i possibly
joke about cats like that that is
horrible and really are you terrible at
such a bad being robot got such a bad
person can't believe it i'm so
disappointed oh my god how could you i
could never forgive you you suck you
sucked it's not funny
[Music]
they were so upset
they were so upset and i looked at their
twitter and
um
and i saw other replies to other people
from this person to other people who
said something
remotely like probably it was also just
a joke
um and and that person was immediately
triggered by it and
stopped being a fan from that person so
this person was originally a fan from me
but was so triggered by that alien cat
that i made
that they
immediately hated me and spammed me with
hate cards but like it's not it's not
even a real cat it's i'm not it's an
alien cat that i'm made up
i mean okay
maybe i would understand it a bit more
if i was talking about a real cat um
even if that's still a joke
okay but this is an alien cat okay an
alien cat that infection harmed my own
cats
if you were triggered about me harming
an alien cat
but then be triggered by the alien cat
that harmed my cats in fiction
right i'm just protecting my own cats
it's self-defense yeah infection i mean
all of this is made up
but
um
it's funny because as long as you don't
say anything
about um harming cats and let me tell
you i would never harm cats you you guys
know
everybody who watches me knows how in
love i am with any cat on this whole
wide world especially
except maybe the naked cats um but i
wouldn't hurt them either
but you know how much i love cats right
right right
no that was not a troll that dude was
serious and it's okay i
i
i muted that person so i don't see their
hate comments anymore i just thought it
was really amusing
oh because it's such an overreaction
it's it doesn't even make any sense
consuming cats one mouthful of hair at a
time
oh god if he knew i'm eating my own cats
because i'm eating their hair
oh [\h__\h] if he knew
if he knew yeah april fools it was april
fools
it was obviously a joke the whole stream
was a joke and um
everything i made up was a joke
oh my god
um
i'm gonna have a fur ball yeah
soon yeah i mean
i understand you know
joking about harming animals or
something like that i i
i wouldn't really do that but this
wasn't like an alien cat it's not even
we're not even talking about something
that actually exists in real life you
know what i mean i feel like there's a
difference there
from for me at least i feel like because
we don't know that such a thing even
exists
there is a
certain
um how to say
[Music]
um
i don't know how to
describe that but it just feels like
it's nothing because it doesn't exist
it's tolerant i guess yeah
i can't explain
but yeah
it's an imaginary thing yeah yeah
a disconnect yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
what i mean
no no that person was doing that for a
long time to anybody who said anything
about um
harming cats and you know if if it's a
serious
like if somebody's seriously talking
about harming cats i i would not be
happy either i would not support that
either
obviously but that's a different story
so anyway
anyway
yeah getting mad about imaginary things
is uh well you do you if you want to be
mad some people just want to be mad
right
that's that's the thing
i love cats though i can tell you one
thing and everybody knows this is true
i [\h__\h]
love cats
and i will protect them with my life
[Music]
i'll do anything for my cats anything
the movie the movie is all right too
[Music]
wasn't loud enough do i need to say it
louder
louder for the people in the background
[Music]
the
um
i do i do love cats oh my god i saw a
really cute dog today as well like a i
think it was a chow chow
i think i think it was like a really
young
almost puppy chow chow well it might
have been a puppy they're just probably
pretty big
or maybe not a child i'm not sure
looking it up right now that might not
have been a chow chow it was a little
less chunky than a chow chow
although chow chows are [\h__\h] cute
what the [\h__\h]
how dare they be so cute
oh my god all the fluffy beings on this
world i love all of them
all this all these fluffy beings
how dare animals be so cute
i want that cuteness share it with me
this is
not it cannot be legal to be this cute
and cats love kiwi
yeah only my own cats
but chow chows are really rare in my
country so yeah i don't think it was a
jojo
i don't think i've ever seen someone
with a chow chow in
in austria
not a common breed here
[Music]
none of those chickens are illegal
you're convinced of your own cuteness
huh okay that's okay
go chicken go
[Music]
okay i need to read super chat
that was two tangents in a row
tuna
but your korean name reads
like um
[Music]
did i read that right
i'm so excited
[Laughter]
like a huge accomplishment you don't
understand it's like a whole new world
opens up to you when you learn a
language and especially even more when
it's a language it has its own writing
system
yeah because like even if it's a
different language as long as it has the
same writing system you look you you
look at something and
at least it doesn't look like alien
language to you right
but if you stand in front of a sign
somewhere in a foreign country where you
don't know the writing system and the
sign is just
for you and your brain
you you just you don't see anything
there you don't
your brain can't come comprehend it at
for as as anything
and that makes your brain go like
explosion
so at least like even if you don't
understand the meaning but at least you
can read the letters that's like at
least like you can like see something
there you look at something and it's
like
if you can't read and then it's like you
you need glasses you you don't have your
glasses with you and you just see
everything blurred kind of like that
right yeah it's fascinating
so chumpty
your red super chat thank you very much
is korean fortuna that's why it always
said tuna
it says i respect tantra who is good at
german english and japanese and tries to
learn more languages i'm looking forward
to when change will frighten the green
bird
[Laughter]
i was thinking about throwing it into a
mixer but frying it probably ends up
much more tasty
yeah i should probably not throw
duolingo in a mixer
probably should fry do lingo in my
airfryer
probably way better results from that
yeah yeah yeah i'll keep that in mind
thank you tuna chum tea
thank you
for the red super chat and here's a
purple
mwah
champion
the permissions that's okay i'm not
going to use duolingo anymore
i have i have nabi mama now don't need
duolingo anymore
i have my navigator now
navi mama
okay
me
[Music]
something something
it's a long name let me just put it
and
oh
[Music]
how do you know before i even read the
whole name i think you even know
do you guys have a list
are you guys even are you guys looking
at the list as well of people who are
super chatted what how do you do it
how do you do it
oh look at research alive what
[Music]
there's more restocks
oh it's true guys
kfb people
oh
here's the url
you heard it here first
you heard it here first go now go now we
have uh omoka kfp ringer shirt is still
sold out
but the the hoodie and the pixel pocket
t-shirt
why is that ringer shirt not coming back
i really like the ringer shirt why is it
not coming back
why is it not coming back
um to be announced kfp ringer shoot
not all products are restart due to
supply chain issues but we are working
on getting everything as soon as we can
there's still hope guys
yeah right the ring shirt i really like
it but i also really like the the
pocket the pixel t-shirt you don't see
it but i'm wearing it right now
it has such a nice color
[Music]
you can get those glasses
it comes really fast it's not like the
birthday marriage that comes uh in 6 to
12 to 15 to 24 months
yeah go get it go get it i'm wearing
your omega orange t-shirt right now
thank you
you're always there in the pixel t-shirt
and cancer oh that's not no that's not
necessarily true
ah someone have your birthday marriage
oh my god
well that's not the normal that's not
the norm okay normally you should
already have it what the [\h__\h]
i'm sorry that you don't have it yet my
next birthday is coming soon
and you still don't have it oh dear
[Music]
hmm
maybe soon what you're also still
waiting what the [\h__\h]
still missing the six month anniversary
shirt
[Music]
six months six months
there's two people
who said they're still missing the six
month anniversary shirt what why
is there like no update
you should try to
contact them that is insane
is there a lot of people who are still
missing the six-month anniversary shirt
if there is a lot then you should give
me a list
i don't know is it because of geekjack
is your order with geekjack
is it because of the the country that
you're trying to get it shipped to
everyone in canada
[Music]
if you live in canada everything from
japan is banned oh
oh
what canadians haven't been able to
receive their emerge from japan
at all
oh
well yeah okay well you can't really
blame hollow or kick jack or so for that
they only have dhl
same with germany for ems non-jehovah
japan's postal service refuses to ship
to canada still
[Music]
still hasn't sent it to brazil either
i have some noida goods from 2020
waiting oh my god i'm glad you're still
a fan
because like in the course of two years
someone's interests can
naturally change and
then you might have lost interest in
whole life altogether in in like you
know two years i don't know things can
happen
um
oh my god i'm so sorry that's like that
really sucks hopefully things get better
by the end of this year
[Music]
you're too lovely to lose interest in
oh god
[Music]
yeah i mean worst case yeah you should
maybe try to send it to i don't know any
other country where you maybe have a
friend uh in that japan would send it to
and then have them send it to you but
that's complicated who knows if you can
even change the address at this point
but if you contact customer service
maybe they would help because like i
mean the customer service of whatever
geek jack for example
[Music]
i hope i hope your stuff comes soon for
everybody who's still waiting for things
to do
[Music]
m
don't
don't uh give up yet
all right let's see and what do we have
uh
says korean and japanese have similar
grammar structures
japanese ah noticing the similarities
between the two languages will help you
learn yeah
i think so too
that's that's helpful
i haven't really taken a close look at
the grammar yet because i just really
focused on
the writing system first but i'll
probably sooner or later have to take a
rough look at it you know
wish me luck
thank you for the pinky
no glue
down
[Music]
last one looks
complicated no way that was
no no
i was completely wrong i was not cut
i forgot i need to repeat my my
my hangul
[Music]
i know it is
oh
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
i don't blame your cover for my shipping
blows okay thank you
but i totally understand that must be so
frustrating i'm sorry guys seeing other
people receiving it like half a year ago
or like one year ago
that is
just uh sad to see him
it must be the sponsors of duolingo our
hyundai samsung mcdonald and cucumber
seller
who is that mysterious cucumber seller
must have like a monopoly over cucumbers
in
korea
a cucumber mogul
i like using that word recently because
i picked it up
it's ena
is inna the cucumber mogul
oh my god exposed
you know loves cucumbers really that
much i love you i love i like cucumbers
wouldn't they love cucumbers i don't
like them though
pink foil hats
thank you come sanita for the pinky
moondog
what is this name
[Music]
oh it has the double the double thingies
thank you a super chat
thank you super ted
[Music]
hey
is that silent again
all because of the um
why is that circle silent
are
[Music]
adam
thank you
why is that circle silent hmm
probably because
they can't put
no it's just an a it's not it's not the
ng circle it's just the a
it's just the a
okay you're learning what you learned
was absolutely perfect i'm really proud
of you thank you so much and also i want
[Music]
says kiana is cute today too i was going
to say oh only today
no no no no every day
thank you
yo
[Music]
i just bought your shirt from old cat yo
yo thank you
nice
glad you were able to get it thank you
for the support
[Music]
yeah today too
yeah it means every day cute
thank you
[Music]
oh
okay okay okay okay okay no problem
thank you very much i will do my best i
i hope i can pick up some more thank you
for your support
[Music]
now this person was praising me for
studying korean and
registered as a member recently
new member korean egg yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum yum
i gotta do my best everybody has high
expectations oh no
i feel pressured a little bit
yeah
but it's okay i'm also motivated
pressured but motivated so
it's a good combination
thank you very much ryan vs duncan jw
slade thank you jw oh that's a rainbow
[Music]
oh
rainbow
rainbow rainbow i forgot we learned the
word before before
no no not a rainbow
lame boo no no no not rainbow
what was the actual korean word for
rainbow
we've learned it before
before
rainbow
rainbow once again
[Music]
it's my first rainbow super chat oh
thank you so much
fighting
i will do fighting
who are you fighting i'm fighting
duolingo
you very much for your support
[Music]
hope you enjoy my streams please
continue watching
thank you thank you thank you thank you
oh thank you
not a fair fight
what us fighting duolingo of course it's
not fair but this is just how the world
is you got to deal with that
you gotta accept it the way it is if
you're too weak then you gotta get
stronger
wow so wise
if you're too weak
you gotta get stronger
wow
never thought of that before
non-found for p4 danke g1 park thank you
for the pink super chat thank you
this is not an exact explanation but i
hope this might be of some help
uh
that thing is similar to uh in german
plus modern korean don't distinguish
the other one e we pronounce both as a
somewhat similar to a
aha okay well that's good because they
look very similar so
if i don't have to think too much about
the pronunciation then that's helpful
thank you for teaching me
[Music]
songs
uh
[Music]
what was that one again with the two
two teeth on the side
ah
i am a
little [\h__\h]
get out of here
out of here get out of here
[Music]
i am a chicken no no not now
what do i do with you
linda
[Music]
thank you
um
thank you for the rest of the chat
[Music]
hello i'm get a strong motivation from
10 to studying hard for korean now i'm
start studying ielts
for getting a 7.5
from the test oh is it like uh
university studies
i leave a special trap for tanza and all
the kfp workers
a special trap
nanu
part of that was um
[Music]
what okay i got part of it trying to
speak uh
german from korean i see i see oh
english test oh
thank you very much
for your support and i wish you the best
7.5 you can do it maybe even better than
that go go
you can't bamboozle me
i'm the tencho
i bamboozled you if anything
but yeah er english
your english so far and that super chat
sounds pretty good
um
i don't know how good you gotta be for
7.5 but i believe in you
[Music]
yes believe in yourself study well okay
and uh focus on studying don't watch too
many youtubers when you're studying
thank you very much for supporting me
hope to see you again soon thank you
so much
for
[Music]
papa
[\h__\h] it's the one where i was confused
that they were all like um
they all had the same reading even
though where it actually has a
what actually has a meaning
according to papago
says
i'm trapped like a god bark bark bark
bark bark
well i mean the lather is just
but the first part is i'm trapped like a
god uh huh
according to papago it has a meaning
bike bike bike back woof woof woof woof
ka
papa
yeah once when all the
the same ones had to say and all that
all the different looking ones had the
same reading and you confused me
thank you
duolingo you used to drink cucumber milk
oh
i want cucumber milk
confuses me
mr caspix duncan bryce hollandsworth
thank you i know come on
pinky i think i saw you in the chat
hello
good evening
it was so cute to see kiara pronounced
in korean and recently i'm hearing the
song orange covered by kiara and nana
again and again thank you
it was so grateful for me to hear my
favorite animes ending covered by kiwa
oh it's your favorite really
oh well that's perfect and you're
welcome
but um i think the idea for that song
for choosing that song in particular
came from energy so you have to say
thank you to nanny
but um
i did my best singing and i liked the
song very much too yeah
[Music]
thank you for supporting my song cover
don't don't forget to watch cinderella
as well though yeah stream orange and
cinderella okay
yeah
color is beautiful i've been looping it
thank you
thank you thank you it is beautiful
it's from toradora
stream cinderella stream choo choo
stream everything
[Music]
sent me some korean reading tips here
but i can't comprehend why they are
uh supposed to be read like that
makes no sense from what i've learned so
far
grow grow tree tree
look thanks for the pinky your korean
skills are improving little by little
really
but very slowly i wish i could take more
time
every day with it and then i would be
much faster you know sorry my progress
is not very
speedy or not very impressive but thank
you
i appreciate you guys helping out and
and cheering me on thank you very much
[Music]
faster than mine are you sure
uh
it's about syntax
huh
wait what syntax again
you won't learn by rushing yeah
[Music]
um
did you catch that kiss
today it seemed pretty useless that
duolingo teaches how to read some korean
names but i'd be very happy if it makes
sense to read my name correctly later oh
which was hard for every youtuber
oh really but you wrote it in romanized
letters for me so that is very helpful
thank you
[Music]
well is it so difficult
i think if you can read korean then your
name is not difficult to read right
but if you're super chatting to people
who can't read korean i think they're
very very grateful to you for writing it
out and
romanized letters thank you i'm very
grateful too
and thank you for the support
is speaking to us in
korean it's like the gods are talking to
me
and you guys
she said hello
hello
to you too
andy right back at you
oh my god
he can speak
cat fluff that kissing the gamer created
[Music]
is
the pronunciation of how consists of
only seven final consonants seven final
consonants
other consonants only differ when vowel
sounds come
i think someone needs to explain that
stuff to me in german
because
having someone explain grammar to me
from a different language
but explaining it in another different
language that is both not my mother
tongue
uh
it only gives me question marks in my
brain
yeah but thank you for trying
i'll try to get a german speaking
a korean one-on-one online teacher
you know the thing i i talked about
before
yeah black friday thank you for the
pinky another year another birthday
bonus
that i wanted to share with you about
keep on soaring you mean the world to me
and many more around the world you're
the best around the world around the
world around the world around the world
around the world around the world around
the world around the world around the
world around the world around the world
and
around the
[Music]
you activated something in my brain you
use some kind of secret
code in your super chat probably on
purpose right
and something in my brain
something just activated and went like
daft punk let's go
around the world around the world around
the world and run around around the
world
do you like that funk
you say this your best birthday gift me
singing around the world for you is that
is that you like that punk
and then that's that's that's perfect of
course
happy birthday to you though
you're wonderful thank you for being
part of kfp
it's a bit late now but
thank you for being patient with me
always
not only waiting for my super chats for
your super chats to be read out but also
in general you gotta be very patient
person when you support someone like me
um i take time to to understand games i
take time to play and finish games i
take time to
end sentences i take time to
end tangents and all kinds of stuff so
you gotta be a very patient person
ah you're so sweet thank you love you
too
thank you soon
i hope you had a wonderful birthday
and many more to come
stay healthy
okay take care of yourself
he said korean is difficult and thank
you for streaming no problem you're
welcome i enjoy streaming
i was drawn with castano
really
[Music]
oh my god
i can feel it i can hear it
[Music]
it's me
doing the custom nuance
it's beautiful oh
look at that passion
[Music]
the clock quack
[Laughter]
wow
beautiful thank you
bonkers
thanks bonkers
anyway thank you
please continue supporting me
i'm always happy to see your name
because i know how to read your name
confidently
did i read that right
um
that was one of the names in duolingo
oh i was happy today for my name being
called so much time oh i thought you
changed it because of the duolingo but
your name was actually that that's funny
yeah we had that name come up a lot in
duolingo
oh all the leaguers all over the world
must have been really happy when seeing
their name in duolingo so often
the pixel art has been updated too
oh yo yo yo yo
yo yo yo yo yo
yo yo
oh what is it oh
wow it's getting bigger and bigger
[Music]
oh
that's so cool oh can i put it on my
screen
download twitter gif
jiff
[Music]
i want to put that somewhere
but
um
[Music]
i need a wide screen tv
why are all my tvs in this office so all
day
where the wide screen of white
wide screen tvs
[Music]
god damn it isn't kfb earning enough
money to
to afford some uh
widescreen tvs
huh
eden
you cheapskate
is that the rat wood
make the window backward
this in the window you mean like all
over the window i was joking by the way
about the wide screens i was just joking
[Laughter]
like this over is that what you're
talking about
that would be an interesting view
outside but it would be um i think very
busy
it would be a very busy outside scenery
so this is you guys gotta check it out
on twitter i'm gonna retweet it
olivia's
are you watching
wow
cool
ah
cool there's a there's a kiwawa
um rack rocket oh the kicker kicks
obviously the kikkity kickstand looks
like something you could see in las
vegas
i don't know this is like chiara vegas
last quiet
yo
beautiful
[Laughter]
if you get very close to the sign you
can probably hear it go
[Music]
someone really needs to oil it
oil that leg
next intro screen ah
um the format
wouldn't be
perfect but i know it would be so cool
as an intro screen
it also says subscribe there's a hot air
balloon that says subscribe but i would
feel bad because like we had duck on my
loading screen for like over a year
and i would feel bad
to replace dakota's splitting screen
i'm feeling a certain kind of loyalty
towards dakuma now
but i was thinking too like i want to
use this but i don't know what i would
use it for if i can't change the loading
screen
right
now
skydive
[Music]
uh
like um
[Music]
did you guys see dakoma
and some uh other people together put
out like some
fan merch um
it's already sold out uh the kiwa stuff
is already sold out though
um but it looked really cool
i like the aesthetics
um
[Music]
yes yes
like the aesthetics graphic design must
be their passion all right we have to
finish these crandall angles
let's go
[Music]
thank you so much for learning korean i
can feel your consideration i can feel
your love moon moon thank you always
here thank you so much
thank you thank you thank you love love
love love love
[Music]
[Applause]
one
[Music]
uh
i wrote today super chat in korean i
always cheer you on i hope thank you
always healthy and happy and i hope that
all the chickens at kfb are full of
happy things are you
you are filled with happy things
[Music]
love
in your heart
and lots of kfp chicken
food consumed
by you guys only happy things only happy
thoughts
[Music]
thank you for that message i feel the
love inside of it thank you so much
i also hope that everybody in my
audience is
happy
and healthy
at all times
especially when you watch my streams
thank you everybody and thank you to
miniature pizza chang
[Music]
uh
there's quite interesting news oh yeah
coming to korea it's not confirmed news
for the students that can invite a whole
life to korea true or not very exciting
news so i i'm still not sure what that
meant maybe it just meant that i don't
know maybe korea was
closed for tourists but now it's open
again or so i don't know
a bit confusing
ah
related information is spreading at the
anime festival in seoul it's called soul
popcorn well then why don't i know
anything about it maybe because i'm not
invited
why do you know about it huh
so
popcorn
[Music]
i can't find anything probably because
i'm not looking in korean
[Music]
why do they have insider info
they have to invite me
they have to
i want to go
so so popcorn is the event or
a popcorn or
popcorn what
you wrote popcorn but it's popcorn right
in august
ah
popcorn like pop convention
i cook with popcorn soul whole live
okay but even googling the right thing i
can't find anything
oh
maybe it's
why do you know it maybe it's like eh
why do you know
why do i not know anything
it would be cool if it's true though in
august apparently i have time in august
right i was planning to go to korea in
august anyway what a coincidence maybe
he's the organizer um or he has ties
with the organizer or someone who spread
the rumor has ties with the organizer
i need to ask genma
[Music]
what's happening
hmm
some of us have come last year
oh really
oh
popcorn
so it's not really an anime mainly it's
just
all kinds of
mostly idols probably
[Music]
oh
when i google it i see that idle grip
crayon
with the funny outfits
it's probably also
uh now kind of pop culture but not
really like an anime con just more more
generic uh pop culture which is cool we
can uh
if we were to
um
be part of that we could reach a really
big audience you know
[Music]
that would be cool
i hope it's true
i hope so
let's let's uh hope for the best yeah
what about japan excellent friends are
you interested still
well i mean yeah i'm always interested
but it's not happening this year no no
super chat
[Music]
a raccoon like a raccoon that's so wise
yes i agree
yes
that's exactly it
thank you for
understanding my struggle i saw a clip
a japanese club that
um showed you know
clearly um you know talking about the
news of me having a raccoon and then
talking
having me talking about the struggle of
um the whole situation it was funny
it's turning into conception
um
because i
i i can never confirm nor deny
um
what animal that was no it was a raccoon
bonker is popular yeah yeah and then
a lot of people in the chat in the chat
down in the chat in the comment section
uh it was all japanese comments and they
were like oh oh i really thought she had
a raccoon oh good to know okay thank you
for clearing that up
it was really a big misunderstanding
some were really like oh the paws really
looked like a raccoon i was fooled by it
i didn't think people would actually
take that seriously
because
the paws
i mean they totally look like a raccoon
yes yes yes yeah yeah yeah because why
not because it is raccoon why would it
not look like a raccoon
anyway mm-hmm
[Music]
thank you
i just wanted to hear attention read my
nickname thank you
[Music]
there you go i read your name
you're welcome
thank you for supporting me
thank you i appreciate it
[Music]
um
so i'm putting it into papa go one by
one because i just want to
let me skip those hallelujah
oh that's a lot of flash chats
wow
thank you everybody for flushing
[Music]
thank you for the fun streaming i got
one month from being a kfp oh one month
ago you joined you're starting to hatch
so cute
the little hatchlings are just the
cutest
ah they just grow up too fast don't they
so cute when they're so small and tiny
my name may be hard to read so don't
mind it oh oh oh oh no no no
well it was a little bit difficult but
thank you no problem i always try to
read your name
thank you very much i hope you will stay
for a long long time so that you can be
turned into a crispy yummy kfp bucket
looking forward to the day when i can
serve you
to my customers
thank you
[Music]
mate thanks mate
any one day come sign up for the pink
super chat i saw that
you want it
it says pspps
you wrote other messages that i didn't
read probably because it was not a pinky
or so
um
could you say
[Music]
a cheer up
him nay
i saw that you want to do more stream
when you do collab with coyote and you
tired yesterday spending time with you
so priceless for us but your health and
happiness comes first not only for you
but also for us
ah
thank you
i'm i'm mostly fine and
yeah don't worry it says here too don't
uh i hope kiana doesn't overdo it
yeah but don't worry i usually i know my
limits and uh when i don't feel so well
i just
yeah
i i
know i can always cancel a stream or so
and i don't feel so well but
um
i'm doing my best to balance
[Music]
certain things right now you know um now
i'm doing physical therapy again so
and some other things at the moment uh
kind of busy
many things behind the scenes happening
too that i have to take care of
like sponsorships that are in the works
and other projects
and
so it's a it's a bit more work that you
than you guys actually actually see on
the screen but
um
it's still totally within human
limitations
and uh
i
i always make sure to have down times
and all that canceling the bus pass no
no no no oh did i not tell you guys did
i not tell you yet what happened with
that
all right it's an update so um
um i was
like to be honest for me
even though i haven't been using it i
would be fine with
at least
having you know the the actual pass
so that i can
use
public transport whenever i need it so i
uh i don't have to
buy an extra ticket just so that i have
a ticket that i can show if there is
a check
and
so
but the thing was that they sent the
card the new copy of it to an old
address i think i never saw it
and and i couldn't change the address
ever and bleeble blue
um
so i wanted to cancel it but
for me either way was fine either
canceling it or
actually being able to use it
so
and now the other day
the other day a friend of mine
showed me something i i i told them
about this issue it was actually um
a
rental
rental bf
and
i told them about this
[Music]
he was like oh you don't know about
just try using the app and i'm like
yeah
i can i can i don't need my physical
card i can just
use the phone app what
but that was apparently not always an
option like that is apparently pretty
new like um
one year ago or so that option didn't
exist so it's not a surprise that i
didn't know about it okay
chill
yeah um
uh
so
i lo i downloaded the app
i logged in
and there we go
i have a digital version
of
my pass
the future is now
if i want to use the public transport uh
when i need it
without buying an extra ticket even
though i already have one just because
i'm scared of getting caught and then
having to explain that i am paying for a
pass i just don't have it with me and
all that that's why i didn't want that
confrontation that's why i kept on
buying single tickets
and paying even more than i already paid
uh but yeah
so now i can actually use it so i'm fine
with it you can uh all now take off
that thing off of the list of things
that kiara has to do
i'm not canceling it now that i actually
can use it i'm fine with it this chapter
is closed okay
uber yeah i um
i do use uber a lot but you know there
are some cases where maybe i'm gonna use
it so
and yeah
yeah
i mean i still kind of feel uh robbed of
that one year when i was not even in the
country and i was pretty sure that i
did
knew that
i wouldn't need to continue paying for
it i thought you know those few bills
that were still on my account that they
were like after payments
um apparently not
apparently
it was automatically renewed yeah
and then i wasn't able to
uh but the thing is like in japan i was
really not able to cancel it because you
know i tried canceling it for email as
well uh after i came back but um in
order to cancel that [\h__\h] i would have
had to go there in person apparently
it seems so they don't do that on the
phone or per email i think
which is really stupid but what i could
have done i guess is uh
tell my bank to stop paying that maybe
but i didn't really think about that
no
no whatever
it's all right
[Music]
that's all right
it's all right now
what do you mean i have to cancel my
church subscription
i haven't been paying that since way
before whole no i cancelled that uh
my church subscription
canceled that as soon as i
was done with my with a certain
um job that i did
yeah yeah
no no i'm not paying for that if i don't
even go there
no
no subscribing to jesus
[Music]
i don't know where you get that from
i've told you guys before that i've
canceled that
oh yeah someone sneezed apparently
someone snows
oh okay
and looking for the top thank you
i forgot that again what was that again
oh my raccoon friend
the glitch
look or gentleman thank you for the
pinky
we raccoons congratulate our secret
agent codename bonkers on the successful
infiltration of the kfb headquarters and
cheer for the future activities
ah
bonkers is one of you guys huh
you sent bonkers
well
you know what i i happily
adopt
receive and adopt your
agent
he's mine now he's not coming back
he won't come back first of all because
i adopted him and second of all because
he enjoys it more of me
i give bonkers lots of or she give
bunkers lots of snacks
and uh
cotton candy to wash in the bathtub
so
you basically
lost your
your one agent that ever successfully
infiltrated kfp
because it's just too much fun to be on
my side
welcome to the dark side
bonkers is mine now
he will never come back
double agent no no no more double agent
my agent
my raccoon my baby
he
gets all the good food
here
yeah and all the good cuddles
yeah
and all the good choo-choos
[Music]
could not resist kiwawa's love yeah once
you have tasted it once
can't go back to
being a secret agent anymore
no no more secrets
this love the world must know
[Music]
this love has taken its toll on me she
said goodbye
to secret agency
i want those yummy kibbles from my sweet
mama
she gives me love and pets i love her
well well well
wow wow wow
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
i love my room five
love the good old maroon 5.
hi hello thank you for the recipe
dreaming too
much
thank you
thank you guys for listening to dreaming
tutu
thank you thank you
dreaming choo choo to hi heather mwah
because of the red super chat you get a
dreaming tutu
a dreaming too
what's it dreaming to i wonder well well
well
this is a chill that you will receive
once you're sleeping you will receive it
in your dream that's when it arrives
[Music]
it's not in my description right now
really i thought it was in there
[Music]
how many super chats are there
chrome 78 documentation skills damage
and misfits damage and chronic
extinguishing mk dance and cruise
dancing
red eyes
hey boss i found a sent dopamo footstool
a kiss dedication on the last super chat
but i might be wrong here's another just
in case no restaurant get it in the next
super chat reading
oh was it uh
dopamos birthday or just just oh because
you wanted him to receive a kiss
in any case
dog hood has gifted you not of a
subscription no no but with a kiss
thank you both of you
thank you for the support
very sweet
the kiss charity has arrived
16 more oh okay okay
but then we have other streams
it's okay i think this one just had
particularly a lot and it takes more
time because i have to read the the
korean ones
uh
[Music]
i didn't doze off are you sure
that sounds like a lie
and or an enhanced truth maybe
well we are chick
would you tell a lie to your attention
well you better have caught up with the
archive where you doze off i hope you
did
otherwise
otherwise you're gonna land on the fryer
[Music]
thank you though i understand i
understand
sometimes during super chat readings i'm
sure it makes people feel sleepy
sometimes
that's okay
it's like i'm trying to hypnotize you
guys with all those donkey shoes
um it's like sleep therapy
[Music]
and today with that music too it's not
very energetic is it
[Music]
but we almost done with these ones
exercises
[Music]
thank you guys for your patience
i will change the music now so we
don't all fall asleep
because we just have so much more
super chats to
read
which one should i pick i think this one
oops
[Music]
energy
come on
legend of zelda super tattoos
oh that was so much fun
i hope we can play it again soon but for
now we're doing porto
alright
mysterious green
leave
behind chihuahua
[Music]
ah
i wonder what that is
excuse me but can you move out of the
way bro
[Music]
i don't know what you're talking about i
don't see a green sleeve no no no
i don't know what you mean
[Music]
i don't know
did you wake up because of the lovely gm
very
good i'll turn it down though
[Music]
that's so weird
it doesn't even loop nicely oh [\h__\h] it
[Music]
what is this
oh
doc hood what the hell did you do
[Music]
you bad bad bad
chicken bad bad bad chicken
instead of sending one red one
he sent
a red one
uh with only
fives but you know what in cash
that looks um
like more money than 100
uh
thingy
piece of paper does
because look it's more and you can you
can go like swish swish swish swish
swish swish swish swish swish you know
what i mean
you didn't see the hand movement now
um
but i mean you know the swish swish
swish swish swish like handing it out
like swiss
and make it rain
[Laughter]
not that i would do such a thing except
for myself maybe
nah
make it rain for my cats
should i make a a money bath for them
look luxury cats
well they would probably love it
they would probably love it that would
be like uh you know jumping into autumn
leaves
but they can't go outside because i keep
them inside so how do i recreate it with
um
cash
no my cats don't even understand money
nah
and i don't want them i don't want them
to
to you know turn into
spoiled kitties okay they're already
spoiled but not by money they don't even
know what money is they don't understand
the concept of money
oh you know what um speaking of money i
i thought of something
random that probably exists already but
i thought you know wouldn't it be cool
to have like a mod for minecraft
that
gives you like a
a money counter and adds a currency to
the game and to have the enemies drop
some money
and then you can actually i don't know
use it for
buying stuff at merchants or so i don't
know
it probably already exists i would
imagine
yeah having a money system in minecraft
a lot of service do that really
oh i thought so i imagined that a mod
already exists but i just i was just
thinking hmm
[Music]
i was thinking randomly like only does
minecraft have a currency and i was like
no wait it's only emeralds
what if minecraft has a currency what if
minecraft had money
could turn it into an rpg
and that's what emeralds are but the
thing is emeralds aren't being like
dropped
by
ah i mean i guess on it
was there one enemy that sometimes drops
animal animals emeralds
okay but generally i think you know
things could
be switched up a little bit
yeah
they'd play some minecraft rpg mods that
were super fun oh
cool
i wonder what there is
what kind of rpg mods there are that
sounds cool give the give the npcs some
quests like you know those those those
traveling
merchants
if they had quests that would be cool
like you get those traveling merchants
coming to your city and then you're like
oh
oh yes they have a quest for me
and you have to try to
fulfill it before they travel to the
next city and you lose track of them
yeah the wandering traders
um
that's just terraria
i wanted for minecraft though
okay
where were we thank you for those crazy
tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny red super chats
you change it up a little bit huh
thank you for the support
bring me 20 blocks of dirt that's too
easy
[Music]
could even send you to like do something
really difficult like um
big dungeon aka do the the one of the
one of those water temples and bring me
back this item
that would actually give certain items
even more like meaning and use
like bring that item to the npc and then
give you something special i don't know
some cool
really buff diamond armor with some cool
effects
oh yeah oh yeah oh rpg minecraft
[Music]
hell yeah
you wanna play modded minecraft well i
mean i i always wanted to play um one
block minecraft oh since a while ago
[Music]
hmm
i think i'm yawning so much because
there's just no air in my room
thank you for the pinky i love wind
waker i played much as a kid and then
again in 2021 i'm sure you will love it
i hope you do a lot of side steps so you
don't finish it in one or two streams oh
i i don't think i'll be able to do that
uh i can't wait to see your reaction
reaction to mr tingle it was not my
first time seeing him but he's a funny
guy
do you have teeth or lip gloss in the
front nail
what do you mean
and this one
i didn't change anything
always the same as always i mean yeah my
lips are if you look closely a little
bit pinkish there
but um i always had that yeah i didn't
add that
did you just know this now
a little bit of pinkishness
yeah
a small detail
in your shop
really so
your show
but yeah no we talked about it at the
end of the stream anyway it's probably
gonna be like six streams or something
like that
[Music]
and uh
as you saw
already on on the starting island
i didn't just immediately run up
but i did all the side quests that i
could do
on the island so
i think
yeah oh i'll do as much as i
can or feel like
the game mccree duncan jeff star thanks
for the pinky jumpstart for the sticker
thank you
jeff style you don't wanna talk to me
send me a message huh just a sticker to
get it over with huh
thank you though thanks for supporting
me
the
[Music]
i really like the
drawing that you did i guess i'll
probably use it for the whole
um
play through even though there were a
lot of other cute great um fan art from
me
in
windbreaker style but this one fits so
perfectly as a thumbnail
i put it together to look like a proper
thumbnail
background so
that's perfect i'm probably not gonna
change it you know yeah
yeah it's gonna
stay there until the end i think
yeah maxwell the first thank you okay
[Music]
thank you can i dedicate one of your
kisses to ollie
her frozen sore and i want to do
something nice for her i bet it's hard
when you want to stream for your fans
but health stuff gets in the way thank
you plus now let's wake
ah
[Music]
olly
olly get well soon
yeah hopefully she feels better soon a
sore throat as
a streamer
like we talk so much and that's that's
not nice
my throat is getting sore too right now
can i get a kiss too
[Music]
please champions can i get a kiss too
not that it helps or anything but
please
thank you
you guys are fast
you are ready
thank you oh oh yeah
i got your tickles stop now stop
um
[Music]
m
just want to say i've been quite
addicted to the original songs oh they
always motivate me you're amazing love
you kiara and thank you for such
entertainment you give thank you too
oh
really
i don't have that much music out um like
original songs so we gotta change that
this year i'm working hard on some
releases
i will do my best to have a bigger
discography
yeah thank you for liking my music and
my song so far it means a lot to me
thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
oh someone got bunked for being thirsty
and there's also artist thank you ginger
ranger duncan for the pinky one reason
why i love this game is for the music
it had no reason to go so hard but man
you're making me want to play have fun
ah don't worry you don't need to play
just watch me play
it's more comfy anyway
and you'll have the whole experience
it's it's perfect when you feel like
nostalgic about it and you you want to
say it again how the game
and like the whole story goes but you
don't feel like playing it yourself
just watch my
playthrough you're welcome i'm i will
gladly play it for you
if you'll be my audience ginger ranger
you're the school and you're the music i
love it so much too i'm like vibing so
hard every time a new a new area uh
music suddenly comes on i'm like
[Music]
yuppie i haven't heard this one in a
while i love it
kamen rider kfc
[Music]
thank you i'm having a lot of fun with
wind waker so far
[Music]
dump alex plays duncan dingle ringgold
oh thank you for waking up for my stream
oh the early bird catches the worm
remember
american kfps
and akfps remember
you can catch the worm if you wake up
early for kiwawa
dump alex plays down questions
from the pinky fingers
pretty convinced your left stick has
drift but you're doing so damn well
despite that thank you yeah um it might
help
dory
but what's better about
yes guys guys
yeah it was um a bit noticeable in the
stealth section
um but it's okay
it didn't bother me that much in any
other section
about the pro controller
i didn't feel that much that it was
necessary
if i could just use a different
controller and connect it to the
um window that would be cool but
at the moment i'm not really feeling it
i don't think it's necessary yeah
yeah
[Music]
yeah i think we're good
thank you oh nice dream
ex-casper the friendly can't be
[Music]
caspi husband
casper
beloved what made you show up again
oh because of ah
there were rats in the game oh
i missed you
nice to see you too
the return of the king
yes
[Music]
thanks for the flash chats everybody and
the sneeze chats oh my god
sneeze
flash and sneeze
in combination or was all that a sneeze
chat no i think it was first flush and
then his knees
thank you guys thank you
thank you for the pinky
thanks for sharing as usual though
you're welcome i think it's about you
know just streaming probably that's what
you mean well that's my job
i
i mean if i didn't have this audience to
to play with i probably wouldn't play
this many games yeah probably not i
wouldn't have time for it because i
would have to get a different job and i
wouldn't be able to enjoy life playing
all these beautiful games with you guys
so thank you for giving me that
opportunity yo
yo
oh it wasn't about that oh it wasn't
about the doctor oh sharing that story
ah
okay
then i was totally off but thank you
anyway guys yuki duncan for listening
to my
rambles
oh i think i already reacted to this i
sang you a happy birthday didn't i thank
you it's my birthday today just want to
say that you're amazing that you always
make me smile i've been a bit busy
because i started my first job so i
can't catch every stream but i always
watch the vlogs and i'll always support
you in any way i can
love you kiara thank you love you too
happy birthday
i need a fruit candy happy birthday once
again
ah
it's truly today oh that's true yeah
it's monday here now too mm-hmm
thank you
yes that's right
[Music]
anthony webb thank you for the pink
super chat i imagine a phoenix in a
supermarket would be a fire hazard
i remember this
thanks for understanding
it's tough out there anthony
danke
santa punch 565 duncan
thank you
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
thank you for understanding yo
santiago martin thank you for the right
to bachato
yokela zumba is my favorite saga i would
love to hear you singing just a little
the zelda lullaby or the epona song sing
it
it has lyrics
it was a long time for my last super
chat i wish you the best and you're
still my favorite thank you good to hear
hey you mean just humming it because i
don't remember those songs having a
lyrics you just mean humming it maybe
i don't remember the melody right now
though
but maybe we'll come across uh
any of those
do you come across any of those in wind
waker
[Music]
don't
don't hurt yourself
[Music]
not opponent that makes sense not my
opponent wouldn't be there
tree overlapping in the whole turquoise
it makes your eye glowing
not oh
just looks like i have some graffiti on
me
[Music]
and
not little dancing for the pinky my
homemade flushes are finally arrived on
friday they're so cute
nice oh congratulations
i'm glad they came to your place safely
now treat them well okay
don't separate them they like to stay
together
i mean i separated them because i have
um
i have
only one of them
but
that's okay
they have the cats instead
for company keeping
[Music]
james jackson dancing
thanks guys for your advice about the
wii u e shop tartier sauce
[Music]
brandon duncan black version
again do you change it like every day
pbnk thanks for the pinky
[Music]
oh
i actually wanted to remake the
thumbnail
because
um i made it with the twitter version
of that art but then later i realized it
looks really pixelated
um
so i asked for a bigger version and they
sent me a bigger version but i wasn't
able to put it together yet so it might
get replaced later but you won't even
notice
you wouldn't even notice because
yeah
[Music]
i'm just going to change
just just tell
the art
resolution so
no
[Music]
they posted the hd one on twitter
publicly
[Music]
what
but only with that one no
no
did they really just
wait you know what's so confusing
[Music]
i go to that artist's twitter it always
bugs around for me
it always gets buggy
[Music]
it's so weird
it's just this person i noticed that
when i was looking for their twitter to
you know
find you know all the fan arts and i was
looking through if i didn't save one
if i missed any any of the fan arts to
save
what do you mean he's hacking
[Music]
but like
i'm so confused i got confused because
like i used to save
their their um
fan art in my folder with a different
name so i'm like did they change
their twitter username
it used to be
something else okay
so
anyway i was going through
the fan art and then
you know i go for the gallery and you
click on it and it gets bigger right and
then on the right side if you're on the
pc
it still shows like the description and
the name and all that and then it would
change
from their current twitter
id to the old one and i'm like what's
happening
what's happening what's
happening and then like i don't know
everything would bug and look weird like
like the names would the name would
change like all over and then i would
refresh and like
wait i was acting weird now it's not
doing
that it's not really doing that
no now it's doing something weird again
but
wasn't that just
[Music]
something weird is happening
did he today
um
today no only to
those
two
they replied to themselves with a big
resolution of
their fan art probably prompted by me
dming them and asking them for a big
resolution
but i don't know i'm confused
it's all good though i got what i needed
okay
neither do
[Music]
i'm confused too
and where was that oh yeah so now we're
reading super chats from today
also forget the weird stuff i was just
talking about
a moment ago
i am weird
we are weird everything is weird
secretly i'm going to give kiara 5001
secretly that's not a secret pbnk it's a
public pink super chat thank you very
much
not much of a secret
i wouldn't tell you any secrets because
you don't seem to be able to keep them
thank you thank you thank you
mission failed
cruise thank you for the red super chat
oh kiwa i hope you enjoyed the spain box
i won't be able to make it to dokomi to
see the live concert don't worry i don't
expect anyone who's not in germany to
come don't worry
i was wondering if we'd get something
like that and ate this here i'm sure you
can't keep specifics but is it safe to
remain hopeful
um
like you mean like a concert
i don't know there's um i guess still
oh a chance i think
especially close like
[Music]
from at least from
my point of view what i know of
things are only really planned until
like
i think like
july august
after that i haven't heard about any
plans of things like anything really
um so
we still have
a lot of time to plan in things but um i
mean i want to do a kiara solo concert
if possible in winter now that might end
up being
um
2023 if
you know it doesn't
mean
go that well and then we need more time
then it might be 20 23 as in january or
february which is still winter
uh but sooner or later you will get
your kiwawa concert and that's better
than anything else isn't it so
let's just look forward to that
[Music]
it's um
it's so it would be a huge
endeavor um
[Music]
yeah
um i'm a bit worried about all of that
uh
um
i don't really know
like how planning all that will work
because
it's still a bit too early
um to start i'm currently planning my my
birthday concert
um
but it sounds like a big endeavor
i hope it can happen
um
it's the future kiwawa problem here
future kiwanwa is worried about it too
though
ask what a man callie for advice i think
i could ask vladimir for advice but i
don't think i could ask kelly
[Music]
i think things work kind of different
for kelly now
than it does for me
because she's a
with a universal
now
in at least in
terms of music
[Music]
so
you know
um when i do a concert then i think i
have to
uh cover everything
like venue costs and
um
merch costs and
all of that
um
but i want to do it anyway just for even
for the sake of accomplishment even
let's say if if uh if we went into minus
even if that happened i i still want to
do it just just because of the
the goal and accomplishment
[Music]
ironic oh yeah well then yeah
we'll make it happen at least once at
least once i want to make that happen to
also
take that off a list
yeah
but as i said i really don't know
because i haven't started planning it
yet currently working on birthday
concert oh
i got all the songs that i requested to
[Music]
perform uh permitted uh
acknowledged
i said yes you can do them
a live song it's gonna be a birthday
concert filled to the brim with
song performances
um i'm gonna be pretty busy living
choreographies i might
uh stream less in the next months up to
my
concert because i really i really need
to learn a lot of choreographies and um
um the thing is like
back in the day i may have been able to
learn a choreography in one day but now
days maybe not so easy anymore
need a bit more time
um
yeah
i hope i hope i can learn like there's
choreographies that are not even created
yet
like the upcoming song from may
and
already planning for another one later
on so
choreographies that are not even created
yet i don't i can't even learn them
right now but you know i have some time
to learn heart challenger for example
right now and
some other things um i'm thinking of
um like you know doing some cover songs
where i wanna use the same choreo as
they use
so
i
i'm gonna
be dancing a lot
[Music]
so
yeah but i want uh
um
i want to take the chance of doing a
birthday 3d concert
um
by you know making it really into
something exciting a huge performance
and
making the best out of it so it will be
filled to the brim but i also want to
have a little bit of a gaming gaming
portion like have some call-ins as well
and have them play a game with me for
calling in and all that
so
not only performing songs but mostly
performing songs
so that
um you know up until then i won't really
be able to do much with my 3d or
anything at all
uh but i will do so much with my body in
my birthday concert that it will make up
for all the lack of
body movement until that point
you know what i mean
yes yes yes yes
[Music]
perform all the songs all of them
more phoenix cakes
yeah
so
high
[Music]
look forward to whatever happens
yeah thank you for
your
thoughts and support
the gamer created
for the pinky hi boss some of us
chimpkins were discussing yellow
birthday merch and the idea came out for
a lot of boy voice pack since a lot of
us find your voice very soothing good
for sleep what so obviously whatever you
decide on for marriage we will love
um
i am planning on doing another voice
pack i actually
didn't decide yet on what to do for it
and actually today genma
tried to remind me
to make a decision to tell them what i
want to do actually i don't know yet
i actually don't know i might do a
members only poll
asking
by giving you guys some options and
seeing what's popular but even when you
say lullaby i don't know what what do
you mean a lot of my voice path what am
i supposed to do in a lot of my voice
path
sing or
talk
tell your story
or
act like that phone thingy
kiwa girlfriend on the phone
i don't know what you mean because
there's so many things that i could do i
guess
not gonna do asmr though
we
but i don't have an asmr mic i don't
know as a voice pack you know it's a
joke on the stream
for a moment it's fun
but
for a voice pack if i were to do
whispering i feel like i would want to
do it with a proper microphone
to get the most out of it
um
[Music]
pretend you're soothing your cats to
sleep
ah ah
the listener will be the cat no no no no
i'll just be like oh
the whole time throughout the voice back
what the baby baby
no no you don't want that
you don't want that stop kidding
yourself
[Music]
point of view we're stray cat
nah i would be more careful for stray
cat i wouldn't be so lovey-dovey
i'll maybe think of some options and put
it up as a members only poll because i
need to decide anyway
yeah yeah yeah
did he stutter
come here
come come come baby
[Music]
hmm
thank you very much
[Music]
how do i do a spanish
kiss in spanish
[Music]
[Laughter]
i guess i can truly afford to watch
kiwawa live it just feels like yesterday
that you told me you can't watch me
anymore
not just vlogs shall sacrifice sleep
schedule these few weeks and spend it
with our beloved kiwawa well how long is
your vacation i hope not too short
because this week i'm actually busy
[Music]
hope the snack box is yummy i'm hungry
now it was really good
it was really good yeah
i
i liked all the chocolate more than the
potato chips because i don't know maybe
i'm just not feeling it today
but it was very um
you know
i said rustic or hearty
i don't
i want to eat the chocolate i'm having a
phase where a little i i eat a lot of
chocolate again these
past days
even though
i didn't eat that much in the past
one two years
recently the past few days or weeks i've
been eating more and more i'm getting a
sweet tooth again
what is
i can't resist someone stop me
is it a face it's never a phase
it's not a face mom i love chocolate
chocolate cravings
and
[Music]
i have been reborn welcome back no no no
welcome back we never had the white ones
before didn't we
did we i always had black ones
but yeah the the black ones have been
reborn and now are white gloves
i'm no longer the gray
oh it's a lot of the rings reference oh
that's why it's written like the white
after the gloves
that went over my head
absolutely
i saw japanese yen was the currency and
i thought that's why it looked kind of
weird kiara's gloves the white
oh no it was just a reference to panda
okay
[Music]
i like your humor even though it flew
over my head punk pimps and skyshield
snapbox playlist oh yeah i didn't make
one i currently have it in cooking and
similar
um playlist
yeah yeah it's they are in the playlist
but they don't have their own playlist i
should make one at this point yeah i
actually
[Music]
i am
i originally
um
booked a six-month subscription
and i was i was gonna maybe extend it if
i if it was a success as well serious
um now this was the sixth box i think
and
no the one that's coming next is the
sixth one
and
um
just like two or three days ago
i cancelled my subscription
thinking that
it's in time
because i was like i'll find a different
service
[Music]
but
turns out
it was already apparently renewed i
didn't even know that you know this is
another one of those bus card moments i
didn't even realize that it was gonna
renew itself for [\h__\h] sake
um
yeah
it's all
wait that reminds me
that was that thing that i purchased
and i wanted to cancel before it renews
just the other day
[Music]
i'm not sure anyway
anyway
[Music]
uh so now i have it for another six
months you won't get rid of these snack
boxes until uh what september or
something like that
um
which is okay i guess the sweden and the
spain snack box were fine but then there
were others that were just really
disappointing
um let's just hope that the coming ones
will be good
welp
well at least the series goes on
yeah it's already paid so
yeah the curse of all the renewal
no it's okay
the french snack boxes no but those were
would be really limited like
i wouldn't have that much choice like
what would i have america canada
australia japan indonesia
that's about it
that's really
not much
i i like how these ones at least come
from like all over the world
[Music]
and that's not much also japan doesn't
even count because i i've eaten
more than enough
okay maybe i actually you know what i
was just thinking of holo girls i guess
i could ask real friends
to like
i know someone in france who could
probably sent me a box and all that but
yeah never mind it's already renewed so
we're just gonna
just gonna take what we get
yeah
and you know what if within this coming
half year
they do a
french snack box even though i think
they would probably do a good job at it
i could ask my friends to send me some
extra snacks
yeah
another one that i could help with would
probably be like a neverland's
snack box
and an italy snack box i could probably
also
buff it with some extra snacks
yeah i wanted to exchange a snack box
all day
[Music]
she said that she was gonna get some
stuff but i think she probably forgot
about it i should remind her
[Music]
i like the cat in your profile picture
cute
thank you
star tail dancing gns mobs thank you for
the red super chat thank you
and fun fact about game of thrones in
spain dorne and dothraki territory were
filmed in granada in other parts of
andalusia huh cool i feel like i may
have
heard about that before
and the sixth season was entirely filmed
in
uh guillermo or girona so pick places to
go because there's a lot
wow they filmed a lot in spain not only
in spain but in europe overall um
what was that one city that i told you
guys about i think
uh where my sister and my brother they
went there
to check it out
um that one game of thrones
city
i mean what the name was in real life
you guys remember
[Music]
yeah
i do baltic yeah
for example
yeah we have a lot of really photogenic
places in europe
in croatia
decoration
yeah that city looked amazing it did
yeah
more reasons to travel game of thrones
thank you
you brought me very pretty yes
i agree
a lot of history here yeah
yeah i'm proud
thank you gina smarms
[Music]
a tasty hate from black licorice comes
from a herb herb called aniseed ah i
heard about it has a very medicine taste
to it it was used as a herbal medicine
not only carissa has flavor it's
flavored with it now
but people i was confused in the chat a
lot of people were like red licorice
it's not licorice no well what is that
about confusing
[Music]
the doctor nightmare duncan
aztec duncan anders
[Music]
for translating during the stream oh fun
famous i don't know if you're still here
but
a kiss for you
love thank you
also thank you pudding for helping
translate during the past coyote stream
thank you bilingual chimpkins oh yeah i
saw i saw pudding transplanting
thank you too
thank you both of you
thank you very much appreciated
[Music]
very smart chickens
so proud
couldn't be any more proud you're here
oh
thank you
[Music]
i guess you uh translated to spanish
was it spanish
[Music]
pudding is the only reason this stream
was more than cute noises and titty
oh mohammad
sasuka
very helpful
oh
thank you
punk pimpster
i'm glad i'm glad we can
have some translators in the chat to
make um it's more
you know open for everybody to
understand
although i assume that most people who
listen to my streams understand english
most or almost all of them at least to a
certain uh
[Music]
oh we're almost there oh i can't believe
it
i see the light at the end of the tunnel
thank you
i am
[Music]
maybe it's all the sugar but you're
being extra cute and genki today really
was i
even cuter than usual i'd say okay by
now i've lost my energy though
right now i've lost my energy i'm
getting tired my eyes are tired my
throat was tired but maybe was i really
energetic really
it was probably because i literally just
came back
from outside
um
i went to
physical therapy
and then i went a little bit shopping
i treated myself to something
[Music]
i feel kind of bad about heaven
but sometimes you gotta treat yourself
right
yeah i won't tell you
[Music]
no also there's a cute girl in my
physical therapy group
it was we talked a little bit because
she asked me if she can go first and now
i was like
yeah here you go ahead i can't wait i am
not stressed out
maybe we can talk more tomorrow
i know it's just like she's the only one
who's like kind of
she looks like she's around my age
uh
she even looks like she has the same
body type
while
the others are like
older
[Music]
no
no flare no no
no i really liked her coat though
i wanted to tell her
nice coat
i don't know i'm not gonna ask her for
lunch no get out of here no
no
this is not no no need for
becoming friends privately
just nice to have someone
cute in the group
i don't know whatever it's not important
[Laughter]
it's not important i just told you
randomly on the side and now you make a
big deal out of it
[Music]
thank you navida maybe
you're not so stupid
[Music]
good morning
like a mother oh
no
[Music]
no okay
ticket check bus train ticket almost got
it king blades acquired hotel triva i
mean check
oh you got the king blades
boys where did you how did you get them
were you able are they on amazon
in europe
i thought maybe they're only like a
japan thing the real ones
what is that brand worldwide cd japan
oh
you ordered them from japan
you have to oh wow
is there like no nothing comparable that
you can buy here
so weird
[Music]
you could probably make one yourself
though i saw people making stuff like
that themselves though but you gotta you
would have to
you would have to first learn how to
make it and you know that's some effort
that is unnecessary i guess
settle for a cheap alternative that is
totally fine
that is hundred percent fun it's not
like you know also those those really
bright orange ones are not banned in
germany as far as i know
if you really want to stand out
like that one guy
in the middle of uh
um birdfest lincoln wish in the middle
of the audience with the really bright
orange ones
you want to stand out go get those
uh ultra orange ones
mint chocolate chicken in korea
mint chocolate chicken
don't try it oh yeah i wasn't gonna try
it thank you for telling me to not try
it is it not yummy
i don't like mint chocolate ice cream or
so anyway
and mint chocolate chicken sounds even
more
terrible
so i'm not really interested but
thanks for letting me know stay tuned
if you could be any kind of tea or blend
to create a tea what would you be i'm
thinking something bright and maybe a
little spicy
[Music]
nah no no no
i would be
um what's that one called again
ah i would be
now i don't know if this
uh combination works well together
because i never had it before
that would be orange hibiscus
i only had hibiscus or something else
combined but how about orange hibiscus
that would be me
[Music]
yeah obviously a fruit tea dough
because i'm fruity
but not too spicy because i'm
[Music]
i'm gonna look up if there's orange high
but high biscuit
i think that would be really good
[Music]
yeah
and one hundred times
[Music]
don't you dare i'll take back that kiss
i gave you
um
oh my god we're close to the end jake
it's monkey dangerous
and prince john danger and thank
[Music]
i've heard it's really really comfy i
have one but i didn't unpack it yet
because i i don't want to wear it too
much because i only have one
but
i've been told it's really comfy and
really good quality
yeah
please enjoy look forward to getting it
the hoodie is really good
[Music]
thank you guys thank you oh my god thank
you
[Music]
not applicable thank you you know what
it's a bit too early for the concert but
they will be used for the birthday
concert
i have to pay for it choreography
choreographies instrumentals for the
uh recording studio
um yeah
that'll use it for that thank you very
much for investing in kfp it was on
danger another applicable technician jim
tracy
yeah thank you let's fund this concert
yeah well in one way or another you know
maybe it will be in one word that will
be used for the concert oh for the
pretty birthday stream
thank you
i'll do my best to make um the concert a
reality too though yeah
thank you thank you
it's
it's a dream
and in my world
we don't let dreams just be dreams
[Music]
that is not acceptable
thank you
that's okay
oh thank you for the rest of the chat
april has passed we had to keep
people's cookies did you think i would
read this
after april has passed hey hey hey hey
we had kibala's cookies and quebec
started to take care of own health
i mean i started holding earlier but
yeah it's been a busy month
and uh
now i've been really
trying my best also love working out and
stuff of course you've heard of tantra
cinderella right man's family month will
also be together all day all the time
and can't be like family together wick
oh you sound like a newsletter
you sound like a newsletter miniature
fincher john
thank you very much yeah in advance
that's okay
thank you for always being here
yeah
always paying attention always
supporting
always staying up to date and loyal
thank you
it means a lot to me to have you guys
with me my korean viewers as well thank
you very much
can we get a hint for birthday merch you
kind of already got a birthday merch
hint if you checked
the members only polls
[Music]
yeah there was a poll between two things
so you can already be sure that it at
least includes one of those two things
probably the one that won the poll
and for other things well
um
i wanted to do something cool
that has been
i don't know if i came up with it or if
you guys came up but i think i came up
with it
um but that was too technical
to
you know
unsure if that would work so
we went with something more safe
but again something that you can use and
i will definitely get a use out of it
myself
so i'm looking forward to receiving it
in
december
i think you'll like it it's pretty cute
and i feel like it kind of matches with
the previous
merch
from my previous birthday
um
[Music]
yeah i think it kind of matches there's
something that matches the slippers
and there's something that matches the
apron
almost as if i did it on purpose but now
i was just thinking about what could be
actually useful
and could work as a
you know
as a kfp design thingy
yeah so look forward to it
i mean it's still quite some time until
you see it
so
we are all a little bit too eager
but it's coming it's on its way
no mug no i'm not doing mugs because
i feel like mugs are too basic everybody
else is doing mugs and i'm like i don't
i'm not doing stuff that everybody else
does
because like imagine imagine people who
buy
merchandise not only from kiwa but also
from other whole live members and then
everybody has like a million [\h__\h]
mugs by youtubers
in their closet
that's not cool
we don't all want mugs that's boring
boring as much as i would love to do one
of those mugs that change color when you
put something hot inside
i love that but i'm not doing that
because um you know
too many other people are doing it
mugs and cups and glasses and blah
oh the hair color
oh how you know how i told you my hair
changes color depending on my mood that
would actually be so smart with a
color changing mug
oh
[\h__\h] maybe we can do a color changing
something else when i was younger i had
um a color changing
shampoo
not the shampoo itself changed color but
the the outside the bottle changed color
whenever the hot shower water would hit
it and i really thought that was so cool
and so fancy i found it i loved using
that shampoo because it would change
color
[Music]
shampoo
it will be you know what that will be
gravy so better use it fast before
before it goes bad
okay let's finish this uh kakun dandesh
and myth has done
[Music]
we're done and i'm tired
uh thank you everybody
yeah i'm kind of the only one now am i i
noticed that before yeah it's kind of
sad what the hell
why hmm
oh i'm so proud i did it i caught up
hey
look at me now kfb
look at me now
[Music]
but at what cost my face hurts i'm
trying it
[Music]
i'm gonna go now
don't know if i can put up portal 2
today i'm too tired
maybe
i'll do my best i'll do my best i want
to put it up before i sleep but
well
i should i want to i want to
want to
[Music]
i don't want to make a thumbnail right
now but i have to i will do it i will
have to do it
um maybe i'll wake up after i eat
something
put up with a temporary oh yeah that
works i guess
i'll see how
how usually you know sometimes when i
get
tired at the end of a stream
once i leave my pc
i'm like
quickly i feel awake again maybe it's
because looking at a screen for so long
hurts my eyes maybe
partially
yeah
okay guys i love you very much shows
thank you my beloved cute sweet
chimpkins are always supporting me
[Music]
thank you
thank you nemo
thank you for and
helping me out today
spain bros
and everybody else thank you too for
your love
i see you tomorrow
for an exciting
episode of porto
let's jump into it into the portals
oh i hope
i hope it will go well look
i i
i blew some of your chimpkins minds when
i did so well in the beginning of portal
and now i feel like i want to impress
you guys again i hope i
don't uh act too stupid don't embarrass
myself too much
i heard there's like
more mechanics no
in portal 2 so
then that in one's in portal one so it
might be a little more difficult right
um
peralta is easier you think so
it's harder
seems to be a thing
that people perceive differently
[Music]
depends on the person probably
but it doesn't matter i have you guys to
help me
okay
look forward to it i'll go now uh thanks
for watching today and in german we say
auf wiedersehen thank you
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] i still need to do something
i just remembered
[Music]
remembered
ah
[Music]