[Music]
do
[Laughter]
cakey
hello hello
hello can you
hear us everyone hello
can you receive our messages can you
hear me
can you hear me i can hear you
oh that's lovely
ah we have come together today
to the special occasion of the first
ever
collaboration between holo live
and we shoujo
jo
holo live and we showed you that is that
is a history
in the making i am very honored
to be here today me too me too
we just talked in the loading screen oh
you missed the precious conversation i
said that that you are legendary like a
legendary card in the gaza game and i
would wait for you
sealed well for me yeah you're like the
ssi
with the with the rainbow frame and the
sparkly animation on it
you would spend your life savings on me
yeah i think yeah i would probably even
go in into the miners for you
but yeah i think maybe we should because
we're similar
yeah by the way we're simultaneously
streaming this both on youtube and on
twitch and so i got i got
and nyan chans links in my description
if you want to check them out
how about we introduce one another to
one another and to everyone else so you
want to start with an introduction my
dear kitty cat
um uh i guess
uh i'm a i am a cat and yes i do things
on the internet and i'm really scared
and
now i want you to tell more about
yourself
more like blanka where well what would i
you tell tell me about your activities
like how long have you been around
and what's your main platform i mean
it's obvious but
anyway so uh i've been a
youtuber for about a year now actually
my anniversary is next month
oh and i like to sing and play games
and hang out with people meet friends
and i'm really happy that i got to hang
out with kiana today because she's
really nice
you seem um you seem a bit nervous but
that's super cute
very nervous i am fearing for my life
when it should be the other way around
because like i'm a cat
and you're a bird oh i mean i mean
okay okay we get right to the topic that
i wanted to discuss
i am okay i'm officially in phoenix but
if you look at me now i'm more of a cat
than you are because i got a tail and i
i heard you i saw you don't have a tail
explain that to me
how am i less of a cat than you are
maybe it's because i'm a cat imposter
a cat and what you catching pasta
oh sass well okay well there you go then
that makes sense that's why you're
fearing for your life right now
because i'm the real cat then you're
getting no
we're both imposters let's be real
but i'll introduce myself too before we
go too deep right now that it's too
early it's too early
we want to give them some time to think
we're very safe
so i am a takanasi kiana from whole life
english actually and you are my senpai
because i have not been around for a
full year yet
not yet just yet because i debuted last
year september
and uh yeah i'm from home i'm english
and
and i'm a phoenix and i'm a part-time
warrior i have my
my my casual outfit on right now but
normally i have a
sword and shield and i got a
transformation belt that i'm not even
allowed to use
and yeah but i am a phoenix not a
chicken
just to let you know even though i have
cat ears on right now
and also i have a fast worldwide
fast food chain called kfp stands for
kiana fried
phoenix yeah yeah yeah so we are trying
to
dominate the fast food industry and i
think we're already doing it
yay chicken please wait um
we don't uh my employees are all chicken
so we
obviously don't sell any chicken
well i mean free
free phoenix meat bird yeah
phoenix officially we sell phoenix
meat felix me yeah
which um makes total sense uh
because i am the only phoenix
surviving in this world uh don't
question it don't don't think too much
about it
uh we definitely don't use chicken meats
yeah not i'm just has to be made clear
because some people question it but it's
it it's called
chiana fried phoenix kfp for a reason if
it were it was chicken and it would be
you know the other one of the sea at the
end
i i'm not familiar with that
establishment
that is a very good statement
you are not familiar with that is that
okay okay i like you i like you thank
you
that sounds good to me you made extra
points sympathy points with me now
okay we are here today to play some
games in this game
um yeah there are games in the game this
is
uh this this game is a
51 uh
clubhouse games was that the title
it's different depending on the on the
country there's like
uh two two titles i think it's called
something else in america
uh and something else in in uh
europe what yeah a club
clubhouse games or
wait there was another title but i don't
know what the other one was
what what area 51
smash cart 51 wait is that for real
smash 51 in australia are you kidding me
wait that's is that a meme why is it
called smash
smash craft smash cart no way that that
sounds very um i'm logical
smash mouth
i will not trust the chat on this one
anyway
so this is the first time that you're
playing this game i
um let me let me teach you we you're you
guys already see i already won
one game uh i'm gonna be winning all the
games of course
i won't let you win you will not let me
with you okay okay
we'll see about that there's a bunch of
games from all over the world is mankala
do you know mancala
no oh i didn't know a lot of these games
eva but they're pretty easy to get into
then dots and boxes this is the game i
have absolutely mastered
do you know this one no no it's very
good very good
do you know dice it's called dies here
oh yes yes
okay good uh i'm not that good of that
one but okay
four in a row we tried that one and
you failed
don't just leak that to everybody it's
on the top right of the screen
that was a good glitch sure says yeah of
course
oh do you know this game because i
remember that from my childhood i think
hit and blow no
it's uh i remember it being fun but i
don't remember the rules anymore
yeah there's a lot of games there's also
chess
what do you think about chess what are
you feeling towards chess
i feel trepidation and fear and dread
and i feel i feel like an energy
radiating off of you
um i would just like to state here that
when i was in school i was in the chess
club
so that should uh definitely make you
scared
i am a chess master of disaster
yeah oh
wow and there's a lot of card games but
we won't really be playing any of those
except maybe blackjack because i
recently learned how to play blackjack
you do you know how to play blackjack
i don't know how to play it pretty much
all these card games
except for one which one
uh
you told me that what two or three days
ago that the first time ever that you
played uno
yes a couple days ago yeah
i i don't understand that haven't you
been uh alive
for many many thousands of years and how
the hell did you not learn how to play
underground
i i've been buried underneath uh
a lot of rocks for many years yeah
okay underneath rocks
are you sure about that
i mean i spent like many many many many
years there
and they didn't have any kind of uno's
just rocks what the hell
that is so like uh i get that a lot of
these games are like popular
in its particular country where it was
created but
but uno is like worldwide
yeah but should we try should we start
with that one
uh i suppose so okay oh
no no no no no no no no
press the wrong button almost
killed me no do we want to get the
explanation of how to play uno
i think this one has like by default
like its
own set of rules maybe that are a bit
different maybe than normal only tiny
bit
i guess i could get a little refresher
no
no refresher no not granted
but you know what you know what for this
first game since we're playing
uh again okay
against two npcs we've been working
together okay
okay game
finish what is this two first place to
all places i don't get that i don't
understand
well let's just let's just go no more
normal difficulty yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay let's go let's go first game the
match is on the battle is on
yes i believe in the heart of the cards
uh this is this is ah now this makes
sense that we're streaming on both
channels because now people can see both
point of
views uh huh
okay let's go seven seven lucky seven
it's very ominous to see the words kiara
is in control
and i feel so scared
i'm always in control
i pulled the strings are you gonna are
you you're my marionette dear
you are the puppet master
you're my little doll my mom my baby dog
my baby
oh you didn't know it was your turn no
it was all grayed off
wait it's dangerous on on twitch isn't
it to be like singing
things if you sing it they're not gonna
send the copyright police at you oh
they're not
i i hope so oh i i heard it's a bit more
dangerous on twitch than it is on
youtube but i've been
i've been challenging dmca on my channel
continuously
all the time my manager is probably con
constantly face-palming
when i stream
there's a trick to it when you play it
you're in control by the way
oh shoot you she didn't notice
i got this you're in control again
i reversed again no you no you
no uh one
skip [\h__\h] okay here have some
have some kites oh wait no why did i get
a panel oh because i didn't say oh no
was i was i already down someone oh full
focus no that you say uno no you have to
yeah actually this is the thing like um
there's a button you have to press in
order to say you know which shows up
uh once once you reach that point damn
it
i didn't see it
i shouldn't have told you this now
because maybe that helps you know
oh well oh well i said we're working
together on this one so
i don't know how i'm working together
yeah for now for now
only for uno uh
uh-huh skipper
you're sure about that okay since we're
working together i'm gonna let you draw
two cards
does that make sense yeah yeah yeah
okay and now we do last card there we
freaking go i did it this time
oh no
damn it not anymore
[Laughter]
oh well i'll be winning anyway i feel
it oh
can i ask you something emotional
yes since you don't know a lot of these
games
did you just not have any friends
how did you know isn't that why we're
all here
you're in control by the way
hey i didn't really have many friends
either but i know many of these games
just that's the way you know did you
just play it
with like imaginary friends then oh i
played with works i mean family do you
you don't have from
family oh
okay
did i distract both of us did we both
not say huh
goddammit that's karma you're in control
by the way
[Laughter]
um i apologize
because well luck
you know more like uh um
yeah okay that's okay you you know
that's okay
yeah yeah you can say that let's let's
roast the freaking game
have that game yeah all right all right
you know what we're gonna play now
dots and [\h__\h] the one that you're a
master
i am the absolute master at
this game i have destroyed so many
people of this game
but it's so easy you will see i will let
you i will grant you the explanation for
this one
thank you please please listen carefully
ever played this one before no don't
think so
where's the board and the pieces
all you need for this one is a pen and
paper
that's it pen and paper the rules aren't
too complicated
no no not complicated you draw a line
basically just
two on your turn you draw a line and
then the other one draws a line too
when your line finishes the box you get
a point yeah you try to finish
others boxes or your own boxes
oh so always try to draw the last line
of a box
basically or try to make the opponent
not in the clothes any boxes
so you have to close them off yeah you
get to keep it you can make your own
property yeah cause you color it if you
do the last line then you color it for
yourself
dots
what does the cat have to do with dots
and boxes well
the cats you know they see a box and
well
no matter oh
okay i do the first line um
i haven't played this in a while but i
should be able to win
okay good luck
you're very confident yes i am
um have confidence
that is the key to winning in life
see i already see that um you are
not understanding my strategy
which is good your strategy
there is a strategy you know this game
seems so simple
but uh there's actually a key
to winning but once the opponent knows
it as well that's when it gets uh
difficult
i can't even comprehend what you could
be
thinking right now universe galaxy brain
it's spiraling you have to stop thinking
like a cat
don't always aim right away for the box
think outside of the box think about
that yeah yeah
think about it on the long run you know
yeah
yeah the long haul yeah i guess so
[Music]
okay you know what i guess i wouldn't
normally do this but i'm already gonna
use one oh yeah once you fill out a box
you get a second
turn and there we go you already
made a perfect pattern for me here thank
you i'm gonna be taking those and i
think that's it for now uh so i'll just
uh draw another normal line
i played right into your hand
no impossible no it is real
it is real
by the way have you because you love
cats i love cats
have you ever watched the cats movie
because i watched it recently for the
first time of my life
yes you have the months ago it was
bizarre
did you like it i i didn't believe that
actually
oh i see we're on the same wavelength i
i'm very happy about that
ah i watched it together with ina
um we did a double collab watch along
there you go good job
good job uh now you missed something you
could have connected this one as well
and then had a third
turn i'll do it for you
i'll take off the workload for you wow
thank you so much that's so nice of you
did you also get a lot of um
confused people for liking
cats the movie they don't understand
they don't understand the like
masterpiece of cinema
yeah yeah it was not that bad there was
great songs in it
and and great actors
and i mean the story was okay the
costumes yeah
i like the part where the cat took off
her first oh no
more fur on underneath oh yeah uh
sorry um cat you see what you did here
you closed that
and now i can continue and this one's
really bad because i can go
up this way and then this way
but then okay there you go it stops
again
now let's see
if i would continue to draw a line here
or here then that would make it too easy
for you
so ah but oh we've come to a point
where almost
everything not on
okay found one
oh but you do have a you don't have
options just look look closely
you do have an option so
right here think nyan think
think oh um the thoughts in the boxes
yes yes
yeah yeah yeah but i guess it only was
one
oh wait
and might have only been one mm-hmm all
right all right
so see i could i could close those two
or i could aim for
higher goals
no way that the moon no that's actually
ah okay so now i have to think
tactically
i know you weren't before yeah
okay um yeah okay i will i will i will i
will take those
and then have mercy please
let me teach you for the future so you
can
walk in in my master of disaster
footsteps one day
okay now my next turn i have this choice
either
do something in this area which you
could then continue because i can do
only one stroke and that won't finish
the box and you could continue then
finishing this
this this can go down that way right
that's uh one two three four boxes
or i could go here and then finish that
one and you could then continue to
finish it and get way more boxes
so i don't want to give you those many
boxes so i will go for this side
because i don't really have a choice
anyway i will have to give you some
boxes
but i'll give you the fewer ones
make sense get it
did you understand
[Laughter]
yeah i'm reading the thoughts and boxes
encyclopedia and this is an
actual a special move that not many
people understand
what do you call out when you do that
it's something like comic comics
which one is it a pip dip
that's not very impressive no no
it's the pimpest dipping that's the
latin name for it
it is a ancient grease technique
dots and boxes because this game was
invented
in ancient greece i would know i was
there
okay you know i'll give you the benefit
of the doubt it might have been invented
there
you sure so you gave me eight boxes i'll
give you
i'll give you these couple ones ah
thank you so much another one
a goddess of mercy
very close you were so close
yeah it was really close game and i
definitely
understood everything you wanna
okay you know what you can choose the
next game so
you get something where you got like
more more confidence at
can you can you move this or not because
it's my room
no i cannot okay then just say stop if
there's a game that you want to play
you wouldn't go for chess of course
because i'm um i was in a chess club
when i was younger right you remember
that
i do not see here's a few games that you
might know how to play
about tennis yeah
as long as you know what tennis is you
have a chance
yes i understand tennis it is a game
with rockets
and buzz and uh the report is really
scratchy
and uh
actually tennis is really cute because
instead of saying zero for like the
score oh
you say love so
yeah i did not know about that yeah
is that true it is true dennis is cute
you're cuter no
wow so smooth
super smooth
all right let's play this you cannot
move very much you can only move like up
down right left right
basically okay i surf
uh let's go
[Music]
gotta go faster
okay impossible oh she really did say
love oh i didn't notice until now
there you go you do have a chance with
this one
and also there's i think some kind of
time delay for the
game capture this is not an excuse there
you go
saw that that's the power of the phoenix
[Laughter]
i i did that on purpose oh
i was letting you have that one oh thank
you and we keep on letting each other
have one that's so nice of us
so polite
well victory cry as you hit the button
wait isn't that a word for never mind
no no no no no no no no no
no you know english is
really not my first language by the way
my first language is german i was just
asking you
for a little bit
again what what the deuce
gotta go fast
but you were really good that that was
fair i think a fair and square
i didn't feel like i was being like
mentally broken
[Laughter]
should i do you want to feel mentally
broken again
no no okay then i guess we shouldn't
play chest and
[Laughter]
all right i'll let you choose the realm
of class
let's choose another game maybe one more
of these where you don't need to know
the game maybe boxing
oh dear okay relaxing okay taking the
gloves off
yeah yeah you might you might beat me on
this one depending on how good you smash
those buttons
i'm so sure i'll win that i'll do your
chores
i don't think we need an explanation
here you can block and you can hit
basically
guide is like is b and attack is
by the way do you know any japanese oh
a little bit oh because i've i
i heard you you do have uh quite the
japanese fan base as well
maybe a little i don't know but
definitely
[Laughter]
oh
we are at a standstill an
unstoppable forest meets an immovable
object
don't hide yourself behind your face
nice one help me i got some cat hairs in
my eye they're
good do you have that too oh
yeah i have a lot of cat hair in my
lungs because
there's so much cat hair around the
atmosphere
see because of that like my my viewers
made me buy
they kept them like trying to make me
buy an industrial strength air purifier
and they were annoying me about that for
so long that i
actually did buy free industrial
strength
purifies yeah for each for one room each
one do you have an
industrial size and industrial strength
purified air purifier you have one
i don't have an industrial one i have
like a baby size yeah you need to get an
industrial
strength air purifier
industrial strength air fryer yeah trust
me on that one
air fryer that's exactly the one get an
air fryer
you will feel much better yes
just fry the air in the air
it makes a sauna i guess so
that's really how do you do that for
your for your business you can fry
the phoenix's with the airfryer i mean
that's that's
what we're already doing cut off right
phoenix
i'm an industrial size air fryer
yes of course we do i mean we're a
worldwide leading dominating fast food
business
we needed industrial sized what's up
do you know how to play
[Music]
i guess you you must know how to play
diamond no i don't want to play this but
you must know how to play dominoes
it's a french game where you capture by
jumping
over the other players uh coin thingies
okay it's really easy
like leapfrog oh yeah i think i guess so
maybe that's another name for it
giraffes checkers checkers
i think is it what does it say in your
vision
uh it says chiaro as prepared again
oh okay oh wait look at that look at the
this this
introduction you can only move
diagonally
only diagonally and when you jump over
someone
then you'll get that point
and the game actually is very helpful
with this it it won't let you do
anything else uh
if you if you are able to jump over
someone
it will force you to do that that's a
verb
and not do anything else and yeah if you
go to the other side if you make it to
the other side you can turn into a king
and then go
the other side back you can turn into a
king
yeah you are king sorry
we can be kings oh you're thinking of a
different song
excellent wait we're not thinking of
anything except kings
oh so wait did you get that did you get
the explanation
yes okay learning by doing though
no don't don't hands on don't be scared
to ask questions
i'm here for you okay
it's your turn see see the game is so
nice it really only shows you the fields
you can go to anyway
oh
[Music]
sorry i had to hydrate myself so now i
get to capture the first one
but actually you'll be able to capture
me afterwards
yes nice each one got a point
not checkmate yet no no
this is like simple simple chess i would
[Music]
say
i'll go here
simple simple chess that's what i said
yeah if you go there i will have to
capture you
i'll cancel your heart
i like that segue that you did there i
challenge them
stream it stream hearthstone
oh thank you i like your original song
too it had this like city pop vibes
right yeah
i love it it's really cool
that's so nice of you to say are you are
you planning on doing more original
songs
yes oh cause that was wait was that your
first one
yeah oh kinda we need more
more more more i need more kia ora music
well there's i got two original songs
right now
but of course i'm also planning to do
more
you don't have to move that one i think
you can yeah move others too if you want
but see i cannot capture you there
because uh this one is in the way
and i can't go back anyway so i'll go
here
stream foolish heart
foolish heart challenger
combine it into a like a
fusion
nice oh my god i need to okay mashups
when
we work on it guys we need to hear
mashups
that would be so cool i wonder how they
would sound together
i'm imagining it now oh imagination
i'm really excited i'm sure someone will
work on it right away
where are you going huh where are you
going kitty cat
this one okay and by the way um
we had a we had a talk yesterday and we
mostly talked about our cats which is i
think
i i just i got so excited that we are
bonding all the cats it made me really
happy
because we both got we both got two cats
by the way my
my cats are that they're the racist
secret
but i got i got so excited i got so
excited about our kitty cats yours are
so cute
we sent each other the photos and not
only photos of now but like the baby
photos as well
and and and she showed me the cutest
baby photo of her cat's eyeballs
so
did you did you ever show that before
that you sent me to your
uh beerus do they know it yes yeah
yeah it's the one where they are they're
cuddling well that doesn't never
down very much but there's a lot of
those but
because we are both so into cats that's
the reason why today i chose to be a cat
with you
i'm so honest i just want to be cut ears
and tail are
so cute everyone's happy
i wanted to be a cat like you
want to become a cat what is what is
life is not worth
living if you can't be a cat all day
or have cats yeah how can you live
without cats it's impossible
to fill the world with cats yes more
cats
cat dominated world that's the way to go
so literally literally the cats movie
that is the
ideal future that i imagine
[Music]
don't you don't want me
a cdi a jellicle delicious
[Music]
i did not understand what the hell that
means but i guess it's just
like i don't know what good
the made-up word apparently it's from
like a poem about cats
oh i should have explained that to me
oh wait i didn't look for a moment i
don't know where you went but that's
okay
i i will go my way
also one another thing that we were
kind of bonding over with jrpgs
right yeah you told me about the tales
game
yes you have to i'm going to now
oh tales of symphonia good choice good
choice that's the one that made me get
into you can't do that
that that's the one that got me into the
tails off series and just like japan in
general
as well i don't know tails off me the
tesla sinfonia made it all possible
it's a great game series but what's your
favorite jrpg then
uh final fantasy 10 oh
i see it's actually pakora was playing
that
oh
it was really really cute oh so you
actually you watch
whole live streams yeah yeah
i am a lurker in the shadows what's your
favorite whole live streamer then uh
from japan
from japan don't make me use there's so
many of them i could just
say like a million names like i love
well there's not a million members but
oh my you got you had good taste but
every everyone obviously
everyone's whole life is great
yes oh where do i
go
you kind of you might actually win this
one i don't know we're both doing pretty
much
the same no one is like specifically
winning i'm surprised that i made it
this far
i'll go for another king i guess maybe
maybe that will help me
no
[Music]
move your forces
are you for glorious oh
oh i'll move my king
don't run away little girl don't run
do you like horror stuff no i can't
handle it oh
i can't sleep at night after i watch a
movie like that oh me too
that's why i don't watch any horror
movies at all i think the only
maybe i've watched oh [\h__\h] oh yeah right
i've only watched maybe what three or
two
horror movies in my whole life and one
of them was scary movie that which is
absolutely ridiculous
ridiculous i was i was forced to watch
it when i was younger
with my friends yes they forced you they
forced me i didn't want to watch it
i i don't want to watch you people made
me people made me play
a horror um game
they wanted me to play a horror game for
last halloween
and i played one but it was actually
pretty bad it was not that scary but i
guess i kind of
purposefully chose one that was not that
impressive
yeah oh well uh how do i win this yummy
uh
okay diagonally did you just tell me to
move diagonally
yeah you can move anyway right now
that's the only way we can both move
that is great advice thank you you
actually i mean at least you're
you're telling me the game rules which
means you are you understand the game
rules
technically that is correct yeah
yes what do you want to do huh
what's your next move smarty cat i'm
gonna go
this way oh really are you sure about
that you think that was the best move
you could do
huh uh i don't know you're making me
question myself now
uh the seventh edition of the checkers
guide
uh what from ancient
yo dot you don't even know what you're
talking about you can't fool me
you can't follow me fool his heart there
we go again
you can't uh challenge me
actually maybe you can yeah sorry
[Music]
yeah yeah okay okay you saw that one you
got two kings now huh
yeah two won't help you
maybe it will
off we go so helpless
what do you do with kings you move back
and then you go the other way and try to
chase me chase me away
oh chad is saying i lost
apparently i lost are you are you sure
i'm taking your king now
no i can't [\h__\h] i can't go the other way
[Music]
you're in the lead but don't get cocky
the guide tells me all i can see
the future oh
what is in the future for me can you
tell me
what is it what's in your in your glass
ball
what's up yes do you want to be my magic
8-ball
okay i'll ask you a question okay okay
um in the future
will i have uh will i have been living
in a castle filled with cats shake shake
shake shake can you shake yourself a
little bit
and
[Music]
maybe
you could have given me a yes for that
one
i'm a magic apple okay then i'll be your
magic
bulma ask me a question um
will i have any friends in the future
shake me
yes finally
because you already have friends
what about me
what about me but i don't know how to
play any games well that has nothing to
do with not
like having friends though you just have
to ask them to teach you more games
you're right you're absolutely right
king me
timmy fred king what's up here
what's going on what
what's happening
thank you for that inspirational heart
to heart oh
you're welcome to see more clearly now
okay that's let's do it let's look it's
faster come on
we want to play more games we're gonna
speed around let's go let's go
no thinking just feeling it no don't
think
okay that's wonderful thank you we are
indeed filling it down
all right mr krabs mr krabs
spongebob yeah are you into spongebob
no into spongebob like romantically
yeah that's that's good to know but why
are you
suddenly giving me all these coins
i'm floating in space okay
well now i have to run away from you
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
okay i'm gonna quickly go and get some
more kings then
oh no no don't don't maybe you should
move your kings down there
okay oh okay
thank you
sorry i really got you out of the
concept you were doing so well
[Music]
it fell off of my desk and it's on the
floor and i can't read it anymore
i'll go get another king good morning
oh come to this ah
why did i turn off my brain ah because i
told you to do so you
you followed my instructions wait
oh it's okay oh my god my my hole
do you do you hear me
huh do you hear me yeah i hear you oh my
god my whole
my whole pc just kind of blank
i got like a oh oh wait
my yeah my i i get good that you still
hear me because um
my stream is dying right now but wait
it should be back soon no i got like an
amd um
amd problem
and all my monitors turned themselves
off for a moment
am i not screaming
what the hell what the hell
what the hell oh my god my whole
obs thing is like messed up where are we
no no my whole screen is like
it am i back but what happened to this
whole screen
i'm back i'm back live do you guys hear
me
like oh yes hello
oh i don't hear you anymore what wait
one second i'll be right back
oh i don't know if you hear me but i'm
gonna leave the the
moisture for a moment okay
because i think maybe that will fix it
what the [\h__\h] amy
ah
hello hello hello uh uh hello
hello wait my my thing doesn't work wait
she doesn't hear me what wait i need to
discord
my my voice thingy doesn't go through
anymore
wait you you're not muted yeah no you
you guys hear me but [\h__\h] let me restart
discord maybe
oh my god oh my
oh all of my free monitors we hear you
but not yeah yeah did she hear me
did she hear me
[Music]
and the game actually wait it ended too
when what happened there
let me restart discord why do i have
some why is there so many yoshi she
can't hear you well now i'm not in this
squad yet but
oh no the en curse
i'm impossible
yes it's me
i am back let me try to set you up again
i don't know what happened
my graphic card just kind of did
something and restarted all of my
monitors for some reason and messed up
everything
can you explain that to me that's okay
um that's very strange and i i
definitely did not do that
oh well you know i i wouldn't i wouldn't
think you did that don't worry oh wait
um my thing is also i have to restart
every application it seems
okay um i don't know if we can
wait we might be able to play games i'm
not sure
but i have to restart everything
that is so sorry about that it's very
sorry at least you can hear me again
yeah
it's this absolutely happen
i missed you i missed you so much i
thought you were gone forever
i was you know i was scared mommy
i was scared mama here
i'm i'm i'm i'm showing you myself again
i hope you see me
okay okay you're back
let me try to get you back here as well
on screen
[Music]
technical difficulties please
but now i only the last thing i have to
do i think is restart my game capture
and then we're back in the game
back in business i'm i'm kind of smaller
now
i feel like
on my side ah thank you for holding
game capture card is being a little
[\h__\h] task manager hello my best friend
uh there we go
there you go this is by the way the
second second
time this happened last time was ages
ago though
i need some technical
yeah and then we having to restart
everything
there we go it's back yeah
yeah i can lose now
this is what you have waited for oh wait
uh oh why did i do that
what did you do i i went back but now
you can capture me
i'll give you this one i
i will take it yeah you have to probably
the game forces you anyway
okay now i had no choice could you
please
um surrender yourself
[Music]
how do you surrender oh is everything
okay chad
is everyone back to normal on my side on
my string
kiara looks weird on her stream
yeah it's like kind of pixelated
uh yes seems fine now
okay
wait no you you look a bit you look a
bit small
wait sorry sorry sorry sorry
you you can i think you're you can move
up uh
to me to surrender yourself in in the
game
move up like oh
yeah just your your last you last thingy
like move here yeah yeah
anywhere yeah yeah i'll come for you
yes yes wonderful there
[Music]
maybe choose one last game uh
you can pick the last one really okay
yes
[Music]
did we play this on stream 2 or only
off stream only off okay then
you know this game so let's play it am i
when why is the chat still
say um 140 p am i
have you come to how am i on your side
in a row before me
on my side a little bit pixely
it was like normal at first but then it
changed falling circle counter
[Music]
okay i tried changing something in
discord i don't know if it will change
it looks better oh really okay
hopefully it stays that way no it looks
better okay i will
oh [\h__\h] oh i left it somehow
i will stay still i will not move
i'm freezing you freezing time
okay let's play this shut
shush we don't need your instructions we
know how to play this game
easiest game ever the only the only game
that
nyaniris has learned in her childhood
apparently
[Music]
um
i played this with the rats in the sewer
they're all really good at it
i um that's a
rat song
yes they're very good companions
i actually for a while had to live with
i would like to think it was a mouse
in my ceiling and it was um
terrifying in your ceiling
yeah until a little while ago i lived
in japan in a house and it was a really
really really old house
and yeah and therefore
it had mice in the ceiling and i i had
like
professional people come to help me out
with it
and i tried everything but it seems like
the mice were some kind of
like mutated super mice
super nice yeah nothing did the trick
like they withstood and resisted
everything were they like chewing
through the walls
yeah they were doing that and like like
one time when i was like at the door oh
i'm winning
um
we're gonna do another one that was so
fast
i was too invested in this super my
story
i'll tell you more i'll tell you more so
there was this one time i was streaming
and it was a really long stream so i
ordered food
er with uber and and then the food came
and i went downstairs to open the door
and and i i took the food off of the
hands of the uber driver
and in that moment on my side of the
door
um a mouse ran up the ceiling next
to me and i saw it in the corner of my
eye but
it was so embarrassing i did i didn't
want to like freak out in front of that
dude and
make him think like oh my gosh what the
[\h__\h] is wrong with her
so yeah i just i started to stay really
cool while i was taking my order of food
and like in inside i was screaming and
dying
maybe the mouse wanted some food well
yeah probably
but you know how for example like
chocolate is obviously
um poisonous to cats and mice and most
animals i guess
so i had this because like i lived in
japan for a while so i was kind of
craving um chocolate from my country
and i had this stack of chocolate from
my country called
rita spot have you ever heard of it
no it's really really yummy and i was
like looking forward to eating it and it
was quite
a big stack so i bought it in in masses
and i had it downstairs in in the
kitchen and
that floor and then at some point when i
wanted to eat it
i i i looked at it and
half of it was like eaten
half and it was actually it was actually
wrapped in bubble wrap and eve that the
mouse
went through the bubble wrap through the
plastic wrapping and then to the
chocolate and ate
all of that and they were still alive
afterwards
they are mutants yes
they are like they resist all of those
traps and points like they actually um
what they
what they gave the mice was like a
poison
that like makes them blind and therefore
it should make them like i mean this is
a bit sad but it should make them starve
at some point you know um so after a
while
that's not working out nothing working
out i decided
to just give up uh because i started
feeling sorry for the voice
i was like oh they just need a home and
some food
and i can't get rid of them anyway now i
feel sorry for just trying to destroy
them and killing their family because it
did work on like their their parents but
it did not work on the child
so yeah played right into their little
hands that's what they wanted you to do
to to give to make them blind
no to surrender um
making them stronger yeah they make me
feel sorry for them
i guess i guess you could because
they're so strong
and couldn't be killed by anything i
guess you could call them
iron mice
wink wink wink winkling i got that one
from the chat to be honest that was not
even my original joke
thanks chat
you thought you were getting that one
huh or did you even not know what you
were doing
i i usually don't know what i'm doing
okay to be honest
that is maybe maybe uh the great
and bestest way of living is not knowing
what you're doing and just
just going with the flow ignorance is
bliss
oh
[Music]
okay no not necessarily i guess i
wouldn't necessarily agree with that but
but it's it's one way of living
are you winning am i
you could you could win soon yes
if i but the thing is i know how so
it probably won't happen
uh-huh see this is not going to happen
no no no no
you blocked me of course i did
you blocked me too we and we are
together we are forming
one big block see that this is beautiful
don't destroy it don't destroy it
no it's it was so pretty but that's okay
thank you
i got i got so smart i was like oh i
have her i have it right
[Music]
i have to turn in my smug cat bats
okay i kind of want to do one last one
okay let's do one more game let's see
let's see what what is easy that
ah oh can we
can we do blackjack
it was really easy i just learned it uh
yesterday or the day before yesterday oh
no yeah the day before yesterday
in in yakuza i was playing yakuza like a
dragon
i've been playing that for months now
and
awesome in there there's a lot of
handling no no no no
no no no i don't have gambling addiction
okay i am fine um yeah i had to play
this in the game
in order to get like something specific
a specific weapon
and i will teach you so basically see i
don't know
any card games so i was really scared
but you don't really need to understand
the card games and card
numbers and card values and [\h__\h] you
just i need to look at the number
at the corners of the cards and you try
to get the number 21
and not a buff if you if you get a
number that's above
like if you add up your cards like for
example you get a four in the beginning
and then you choose to stack up on that
but uh i think the highest stack that
you can get is like a number and a
number 10
i don't think there's anything bigger
than that so then you would get to 14
and then you have to decide are you
going to stack up again
yeah probably because you want to get to
21. but then it could happen that you
get to 24
and then you bust it oh you can't go
over you can go well but you're not
supposed to
you should try to get um 21 that's
blackjack
or a higher number than me at least or
a higher number than the npc and no then
the server i guess
the the serving person whatever they're
probably gonna explain it as well let's
listen
okay i'll be the dealer she's the dealer
beautiful carts two plus four is six can
you do math
yes a six i think a long way from 21.
[Music]
yes many numbers in between hit me
hit me and you say when you say hit me
when you add another number
you hit each other you hit your cards
that makes 20. oh my god yeah 20 is
perfect you shouldn't you shouldn't hit
yourself when you're at 20 because you
will only go above 21 well probably
blackjack okay oh you gotta be kidding
me
when you get really close to 21 you
stand
yeah you should probably always stand
around like
13 14 15 nah nah i don't know it depends
on you
on your feeling i would probably
okay i would probably stand when i have
a 15
but yeah and you can also double down
double how do i explain double down
um you double your bet and
hit with another card but
well if you lose then you're losing
double
does that make sense
i guess you know what i'll turn double
on off because
that's too confusing let's go okay
we can do it that's it you'll learn it
yes you learn by doing
i'm feeling the cards fail the cards
have you watched
oh i really want to that's all my
netflix right
i guess so i watched it oh ages ago when
the first season came out
it's all about card games it's really
crazy
what what my bet wait how many do we
have hundred okay
i'm gonna bet at the maximum bet
okay no wait that's not the maximum bet
oh well whatever
it doesn't matter just bet like 15 or
something or
50 i don't know
17. oh it's just the same as me okay
okay
let's win against the cpus
oh see they're so nice they even do the
math for you you can see
what the total is right now we all got
pretty close numbers so i think we
should all be standing in this situation
so i will do so
even though i got the lowest number out
of all of us
damn yes oh they got 16 they're adding
they go to 17 okay oh let's see if he
used one now
you got a draw because you got the same
number as the billa
yeah oh yeah what's the first round next
one round two
now now you get the gist yes i
understand though
perfect and feel my soul being overtaken
by the spirit of gambling
don't don't let that happen that's not
good that's not good
is it good but it feels good as long as
it's just in the game
and not in reality then that's okay
oh yes oh i got a good one from the
beginning
i'll stand with that normally i like to
hit a lot
[Music]
what will be your choice yes you should
be hitting but now probably not anymore
but it's your choice i'm pretty close
yeah i don't know stamp okay
cpu oh they got a 20
12 fifteen seventeen and face the owl
you guys are wrong the others win
because we got we got
uh at least more than the dealer yay
and we got some more coins
i would love to bet even more
35. oh
are you comfortable now
if you get an ace and a queen then
you're automatically blackjack and i
pretty much already won this round
so lucky no lucky cat
he's so lucky
i love people like rub off on me a
little bit so i can have some look
when you wrap against me no
i mean on your screen we're together
right on my screen we're separate
but hey let's rub rub rub rubber
you have some luck there you go what
this is say so okay there's nothing
wrong about this cats like to cuddle
sometimes okay i don't have noise i
promise
do you don't have one headlights
all right all right very well prepared
for this uh by the way you're in control
you have to do something
hit or stand hit me
oh bad choice you busted real hard
they busted two and now i'm standing
okay obviously i'm winning this round
unless just
you're the only winner
lucky cat
maybe you could um maybe you're the
blackjack this round
this is all about i rubbed it on to you
i'll give it to you i want you to win
i wanna go hey
[Applause]
i got struck
[Music]
you don't really have much choice anyway
you should hit maybe you're lucky and
get black too come on come on
i'm so close i busted
no that one got blackjack too and this
person copied me
well you bet more right oh yeah i did
one more
a bit more yeah yeah
was that the last one we have one more i
think we have one more
i think there's one more round this is
this is the time
this is your turn to shine
this this time
i believe in i'm going to bet
a lot can i do this is the last round so
i i want to go full in but i shouldn't
because i already have the most right
now i shouldn't [\h__\h] around with that
let's go oh no you've been pretty lucky
oh i i kind of unconsciously entered
yeah for yakuza
oh oh wait no no
[Music]
no that would be that would be eight
nine three
eight times three would be yeah that
makes no sense probably right now but
eight the times yakuza came from from
uh wait but i got miku
niku yeah okay that probably makes no
sense to people who don't understand it
but it's because
three can be read as as well me
in japanese and and nine can be read as
cool in japanese so
people like to make up uh words with the
numbers that
i can't explain it oh well i'm gonna
stand stand
they both the recipients busted yo
losing oh this is my chance this is your
chance
hit it
oh well we all lost in that round
and the final winner is
well i never had a guess oh my god what
you got
oh yeah yeah yeah okay your final round
zero
zero what's sad it's love
in a different game it would be love
very positive
thinking i like your positive thinking
thinking
so wait this doesn't did i win
all i think you won
every single game no
that is so
uh love i won zero you got you got my
love
i i had lots of fun with you and
want to say thank you for collabing with
me
thank you so much for collabing with me
i'm so
so so honored i look up to you so much
you're so cool
i'm glad that i feed your gambling
addiction oh
yeah and i i'm glad i could introduce
you to the gambling addiction
and also the tales of series i hope
you'll play it on one day
and maybe even on the stream
yeah i'd love to and well guys uh if you
want to check out nyani's her channel
but she has a youtube channel and a
twitch channel they're both in my uh
video description
i think i guess you don't stream on
youtube at all you just upload the
videos right
yes and the streams are all on twitch so
if you want to check her out
do it do it do it please check out
kiara on youtube and kill him
she's amazing
you're amazing um you are totally
a cat legendary cat yeah yeah yeah with
no tail
but i guess i guess the the mice uh the
rats under the rocks spit off your tail
or something like that right
yeah it fell off and then they used it
to make a rat nest
wow wow it sounds very comfy i love like
sleeping on my cats
like when they're like curled up like a
ball yeah
i love putting my head on that i love
that i look like a little like a
muffin yeah
oh you know when they sit like bread
loafs that's so cute
i love that i love when they look like a
monorail
yeah yeah yeah
i hope we can continue bonding over cats
and all kinds of things thank you so
much
for this collab and i hope everyone
enjoyed it
it might be who knows there might be
more collaborations between her life and
bishop
soon in the future perhaps not by by me
i don't know who
i don't know who could possibly be next
i don't know
who could it be no clue we all don't
know it's totally unexpected
big surprise a mystery
yeah but look forward to it keep your
eyes open guys
um is there anything you want to like
say at
the end like do you have an end greeting
i
just say thank you very much and eat
something delicious
oh spicy that that sounds very kind and
and sweet and wholehearted and tasty i
usually say something in german do you
want to say it with me yes i would love
to
okay do you actually know any german
no oh no no okay then this will be i
guess your
your first german word ever
okay so i i i the whole phrase is and in
german we say
auf wiedersehen oh yeah
so so you can you can join in from
a vida and i say and in german we say
auf
wiedersehen can you repeat that alfredo
yeah it means see you again auf
wiedersehen
perfect perfect
okay free to wait don't don't say it
three two one and in german we say
auf wiedersehen
okay let's try again one more time one
more time
your face is like tearing up it's so
scary
what what the pixel yeah
it's okay now it's okay oh god okay i'll
stay still
you were laughing and my face okay
no no you have a beautiful face it's
okay i've got a funny face i know i know
you gotta you got a big head though yeah
a big brain full of mystery
all right one more time okay and in
germany
[Music]
thank you and thank you so much bye bye
bye bye
[Music]