[Music]
me
cakey
i'm already here
we're just waiting for kelly i think
kelly's still not present transitioning
[Music]
hello oh you're just just
waiting oh is she there
kelly i don't know oh yeah right she's
she's muting us whenever she does that
coming soon can i
it's only a matter of time she'll be
there soon
i am naked today i took off my hats to
not uh disturb
kelly's face i think she wants to eat my
hats
i think maybe she chickens on my
on my hat no
no
is kelly's still doing her intro oh damn
it
oh damn i can only hear you oh you wait
you can't hear
oh oh sorry you can't hear enough
goddammit
oh
you can still do it you can go ahead and
do it i'm here
it's your boy that's how i sound
wait
that's how it's supposed to be
that's just my that's just me this is
real this is me
i'm exactly how i'm supposed to be now
gotta let the light
[Music]
okay
can i go to the room now or guys look at
my question in the chat do you think
it's okay should i go to the room
which one it's fine you just come in
come in
it says you're from usa alabama wow
wow yeah how is
alabama how is that place it's fine
it's fine is it cold is it hot how is it
decent enough
isn't enough is it where is alabama is
it in the north of america
i forget sorry i feel like
somewhere between the east and the west
part
oh that sounds very smart you know well
since you're so smart yeah would you
like to would you like to explain what
we're doing today since you're so smart
ah so we're gonna be playing uh rio real
pictures too do you guys know what puyo
view is
no i know a tetris miss i've played it
before [\h__\h] football
well you have these like colored jellies
and you gotta line up four or more of
them
and then it's kind of like tetris yeah
you get rid of the blobs
by matching colors and
uh you try to uh get as many combos as
you can
lining those up and then you can get
more planks
and then you can kill your opponents
quicker
no i see yep i i already ended up
everyone's audio is just still so quiet
what the hell are you they're like
really
just in his voice
am i am i turned up on this score she
sounds to me as loud as kelly
sounds the same to me yeah i don't know
good now okay
you don't allow one to speak i'll just
speak louder
which you said while whispering
i was closer to the bike right anyways
i would like to say that we all have
practiced a tiny bit before
the stream and while i was an absolute
horrible mess
in the first two rounds i have since
then recovered well and
uh got a basic grasp of the game
kelly is basically around the same level
as me i would like to
say although she has uh pulled out some
great moves like
throwing all those stones at me good job
kelly
yeah you're i mean yeah thank you that's
kind of you to say
hold on hold on hold on i turn up ina by
the way
only you have the
oh my god hello all right should we go
into the first round
okay yeah you guys you can have a full
coverage
i'm sorry i told you and they
immediately
left i told you how i thought it was
friends online i don't know
oh wow i don't think there's a friend's
only uh thing
all right all right
girl yeah well let me put up let me put
the cali
the password is in the upper left corner
but i thought it was for friends okay
let me let me hide the lobby for once
well we're gonna have to do this hiding
all the way okay i hate my screen to
join your room
[Laughter]
[Music]
i thought it was friends only damn it
because it says join friend
join a friend's room
welcome to the membership i'm just gonna
do my usual business
maybe do a more complicated password
like one two three that's like super
complicated one two
four sorry yeah that's the new password
is one two three four
what one two three four
with the small image will be fine
where i don't know i don't know where it
is though i'm just gonna join for now
i can't find you okay okay let me give
you a screenshot screenshot of
my my screen oh thank you never mind
oh no i'm in the room oh there i see i
see where it is
oh i don't have it right now but i'll
use a chicken
because i have a new pc so wait so ah
um okay
that should hide it i think yeah
now don't show it don't show it kiara
don't show it i'm gonna make the cali
pog
is a little smaller now
don't show it
oh amelia's here hey amelia oh my god
amelia's muted someone unmuted amelia
she loves it
why are we stealing her ability to speak
that's just rude
[Music]
okay i'm ready
are you guys ready for our first warm up
game hell yeah
i am okay i'm ready
so in this game we can choose between
puyo puyo mode and the tetris mode
i'm gonna go for puyo play i was better
at put your face
for your mode
how about we also moon that's the show
just to show everyone what it's like
and but you also don't have to make a
line like in tetris you just have to
connect
four or more yeah and it doesn't have to
be in one line it just
can be in random connections just has to
touch each other
sorry i forgot to play press okay
i'll show you what i got can i hide my
my password thingy now by the way i
wonder yeah i put it away oh yeah you
can put it away for now remember to
bring it back
out yeah when you're in the lobby
all right what is that great thing don't
do that no darn
did
[Music]
ryan and why are you making mistakes
you're the best out of us
no you guys all looking for the prophet
remember oh i remember
and the history has been recorded on on
twitter no one can take that away from
me
exactly
[Music]
that's right
i don't think so
oh
[Applause]
insert on that one oh callie is dying
say a prayer for kelly here we go first
one out
babies we love it
we love some of my some of my viewers
have placed some bets
saying that i will lose especially after
the first tweet that i sent but i think
they're rethinking that
now
[Music]
that's right in the end it doesn't even
matter because you know what
no no could you stop
oh god oh yeah
i gotta get those combos oh that's no
problem no problem i will do that
right now
wow
[Music]
is
i like how the chicken that i placed to
hide the the password is perfectly
positioned in a way that it implies that
the chicken is
me this is now on top of my
puyo puyo screen like in my facebook you
guys probably don't know what i'm
talking about because you're probably
just like oh yeah sure
just keep on talking kiara whatever
focus on the game here oh we're focusing
[Music]
this is my background this is a bad
round
okay say it stay safe
give me a combo come on
show me those sweet combos
[Music]
okay
i love that you have that
i usually forget the sensor myself and
it just comes too late
[Music]
what a beep
so you two love me ladies what did you
have for dinner today huh
i mean it's weird to ask that ina
because i guess she's in a different
time zone but she also lives in a
different time zone
like then she actually like sleeps in
don't worry about this so did you eat
the dinner yet you know
uh i had a meal i don't know what meal i
would call it
no wait i had fried rice fried rice
[Music]
i put like the uh mountain of hot sauce
on it oh
delicious to make it to make it spicy
yes you like spicy stuff oh yeah right
you did say that before you were so
excited when the indonesia second
generation girl said that they like
spicy stuff
yeah and then they're like i'm not gonna
eat this i see food but
spicy food i'm just like oh i understand
i understand
all right we're going back to the lobby
guys get your image ready okay here
image ready
it's always been there yeah it's okay my
image is there permanently
i'm deleted to remove it kelly what did
you eat for dinner
um i had pasta
what kind of pasta ah it was tomato
tomato pasta mozzarella
uh-huh
i'm gonna be this uh this emo kid who
looks like he's a fan of my chemical
romance you know what
i mean your name it's a fish
sorry it's tuna tuna yes so i'll call
you tuna now
i'm gonna suck it yeah okay that's fine
oh uh i'm gonna focus again
oh man it's tetris versus food for you
oh
[Music]
i'm not a big fan of jelly but sure sure
you don't like silly i mean i couldn't
eat it but
i used to like jelly stuff much more
when i was a kid
but now i'm a phoenix that is a million
years old so
i'm kind of over that stuff you know
you're a million years old
and i don't even know i mean i don't
know man i've been reborn so many times
i have no idea
after like a few millennials yeah yeah
it's hard to say you know i mean
oh yeah amelia recommended it to me
kelly
it's really good it's so fun to use
and ever since i got it everyone told me
that i sound even crispier i already
sounded crispy
after getting my short sm7b not
sponsored
but but now
it's like a whole new world has opened
itself to me here
[Music]
can someone stop sending me all that
[\h__\h] over here
[Music]
stop it
i'll take the time to hydrate myself
everyone hydration time
drink you're working
are you guys interested in what i ate
after i asked you
nobody asked me okay
wow so i ate a uh
nicoden which is basically a bowl of
rice with a bunch of uh uh
what kind of uh i don't know
[Music]
yes
could you girls eat a raw ass
depends if it's like what people call it
pasteurized or whatever it's called
what packaging
like they do like special treatment on
there but there's like no salmonella and
stuff
oh okay you would you would actually i
mean i'm asking if you would want to do
that
yes apparently it's like really good if
you
lift and stuff if you do wake up
yeah who needs that kind of stuff huh
let's just keep on eating pizza and
chocolate i didn't know that's
okay
[Music]
yes
i say that in my super chat reading
that's probably how you picked it up but
um i tried to like mix it up every now
and then and say
for example it's also it also means
thank you but i said uh
feel and dunk and my viewers would think
i'm saying i'm feeling dank
oh i'm not feeling dank at all
us
i'll go slowly i'll go slow
[Music]
one more try you guys want to retry or
you want to change your mood
oh
[Music]
i might as well change to tetris right
now ah
okay i'll try to put it through then
okay i'm not as strong
let's experiment let's work
i wonder if they sell people candy
that's probably dude
i mean it's probably like at least
there's candy that
looks like that probably let's see what
we can do
the thing is with tetris how do people
have the time
to look at what's coming next i don't
understand
oh yeah this is real pros
oh god i already messed up i already met
should have never changed
there we go how do i get something in
there though
how do i fix the bottom line no
oh god tetris is not my family
i don't know i feel like clifford has to
think to maximize your uh
what you'll call it combos
chains
[Music]
can't think yeah you can like stack them
up
certainly so that it'll like hundred
percent combo no
yeah okay i can't do that in puyo puyo
either and i definitely can't do that
in patrick
okay okay
[Music]
my brain not work
um i haven't been awake
yes you already told me that before
the answer is always the same i know
i'm messing up
oh no i'm not i messed up so i'm not
getting any pain
i panicked
oh no no uh
oh
i don't know i feel like i'm gonna get
destroyed if i actually try
it's like when you like when you like
don't try you do better but then when
you actually try you like mess up
i'm gonna try to do the things that the
professionals do
where they leave one line open and then
try to
keep on you know clearing it all up i'm
gonna try that
okay no i'm gonna pick up that one right
now okay nice so
okay i'm gonna try to be cool now
i can do it i believe in myself i don't
know what to do
no already failed
oh carol's doing better really i don't
think so
oh god
[Music]
name yeah i saw her play and i was like
oh i don't ever want to be against her
but that's just no no no no no no no no
no
it could be good if you want to just
believe in yourself
no confidence
oh will you make a comeback here no
probably not
do you believe if you're trying to
challenge
me here you know what happened to
youtube when they terminated me if
their service went down yesterday so
you know what happened there my revenge
is bittersweet
this channel your inner gamer i believe
okay maybe
oh yeah hold you can you can uh press r
to use a different keep you can keep one
and then you can uh
hold it until you need it and then like
you can like switch it out for when you
when you want to use that i don't think
i have the skills yet
to do something like that first need to
get used more to the room to the
to the the whole situation
[Music]
cali kelly want to team up against ina
okay let's do it let's
[Music]
[Laughter]
not the old ones they want to give me
the power the old ones
they're all quite old so you're not
wrong
[Music]
oh
we'll
[Music]
combined
the enemy is just too too strong and too
big
i mean she's into on top of us in my
lane
please believe in selves
um actually no it's actually looking bad
for me oh damnit
she's going all out now
she's ready to destroy us she's not
playing anymore
oh god
[Music]
what is that one down
oh
[Music]
oh you might make it fight for takamori
[Applause]
[Music]
i believe in you you believe in your
enemies
do we get some sleepy asmr reaper reaper
sleeping
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
my dude is so cute playing pinsamo
there's still one more round i can make
a buck i will stay alive now
i will stay alive thank you
for doing the hard work for us
it's so nice to have someone i can rely
on you know
oh god is already like getting all the
stones oh my god
really that powerful goodness gracious
it's okay not to make mistakes it's okay
don't worry about it that is indeed
i'd encourage you to continue making
these please no it's okay
[Music]
i don't know if i can make it out of
this one alive
yes
[Music]
yes that's what i wanted thank you
i thank you
are you stressed out you know are you
okay
are you fine
[Laughter]
relax your senses that reminds me i'm
going to go do that after this
i just want after the stream
fried chicken oh i can send you some i
have a line
i have some people who sacrifice sorry
and that people are totally not
i mean like you know
it's not like i fry my employees or
anything like that
my child is panicking my cat is
panicking you didn't hear me
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
just really chilled she's just
all right let's do this again okay
for your only
let's do all against each other okay
then it's time for me to kick your ass
callie
wow okay that escalated quickly
you're allowed to feel that way i in
turn will hurt you severely
[Laughter]
bring it up
[Music]
here certainly it'd be my pleasure
bring it up
oh my head hurts gone down
it's okay it's okay it's okay
let's go concentration
concentration 64. what did you ask me
for hesitation what i'll go first
what are you talking about wait what
kelly's saying i don't understand
i have an idea the person yes who the
person who went uh
who loses like who has the least wins at
the end
must in their follow-up stream whatever
it is
and puyo at almost as possible as many
sentences as possible so like pick it up
and it says
pickle you would be like hello everyone
how
[Laughter]
okay no are you talking about the games
before
this yeah everything everything okay
which i i guess it's uh maybe maybe from
now on because me and kelly play
together two times
not sure how to count that
from the game before so this is the
second game that we're counting
let's see let's see well i should
already try to learn how
if i can do is it it's a practice right
now and i'm practicing brielle
how's it going is everyone doing good
i'm actually enjoying it i would like to
get this batsu game
[Laughter]
i like it i i wanted a you call that in
japanese you call it
does that that's the part at the end of
the sentence i don't know what you would
call it in english because no one does
it i guess
real
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
yeah i should turn it off for you yeah
i just ignore all the friend requests
for young there is no
meaning inside of my friend requests
guys for y'all give up
[Music]
i heard you guys rejected carol's
marriage
[Music]
you're also saying
i'm not that smart i think you all got
you all know that i'm not that smart
though
but it's working i don't see
cats
oh it's doing that
and that's two ways for me oh wait oops
i accidentally pressed free try
uh you guys okay with yeah
okay
you will not get me to say
okay i don't know how to do that you
think my brain is down either
oh smiley isn't it either it's a
conspiracy stop
it don't you want to hear it
don't chill out here kelly go for you
for you i want to hear it i definitely
want to hear it
here it's not funny when i do it i've
been doing the whole time now
it has to be cali
exactly she's working towards it
[Music]
[Applause]
when did you get so good for y'all
[Music]
accept it stop it
wait are we only counting the last place
or like
i don't know really i think it will be
very obvious in the end who had the most
losses anyway
i don't even think we need to think
about it
are you already preparing for a campaign
yeah
what you're saying i mean i'm okay with
it for y'all
it's cute for y'all it is very cute
[Music]
[Laughter]
you have to do it so that i don't lose
only cali loses you understand
enough i don't know i don't i can't eat
my face
i'm sorry
when you try to last a little longer but
you don't succeed
when you get what you want but not what
you mean
here we go again
[Music]
wait oh it's cause is that my my second
nose or my third loose
i forget my memory is not my thing
i think chad knows yeah god knows bird
that was
[Music]
i'm so blessed i just don't like you
guys
that's sweet i also want to hear you
cleo why don't we all say brian
yeah i mean
[Laughter]
cali i would like
maybe she is maybe you're right
absolutely
no wait i messed up absolutely
oh god accepted now oh my god
kara we got it we gotta get we gotta get
cali to stay i'm free
i'm trying you're not making it easy for
me
we gotta try your best
difficult very difficult now very
difficult
come on give me give me more give me
more reds come on
you did it oh my god yes
i can stay alive for a little while
longer but cali is doing pretty good oh
god
oh okay i gotta focus
oh no i'm fine i am um
i i'm dead saying i'm i'm what are you
calling me
[Laughter]
oh no it was a nice time
i had a great time
but it's still we still have a long time
to go there's so many chances for me to
win puyol and turn this whole thing
around for you
[Music]
she's like really desperate now trying
to not say puyol
all right i'm putting on my gamer hat
cassie gotta get i gotta get kelly's
wheel never and that's not gonna work
because i always die first
how did i win before huh good job
uh i don't know let's just do the way
whatever way you want to play that
okay i'm not gonna do it it's your
choice actually stresses me out
i i just wanna i wanna give now that i
know the whole thing i'd like to try it
[Music]
damn kelly is getting too good kylie's
supposed to be bad at this
warming up
it is simply beginners right for you or
tetris
oh yeah do i pull you or do i touch your
status question
yes yes yes ready set go
[Music]
okay i will do
i just realized am i getting the same
things and what if i copy exactly what
she does
and it's already too late for that but i
feel like we're getting the same like
wheels now it's already too late yeah
[Laughter]
i gotta kill you in order to kill cali
[Music]
but like do we come i think we come for
i guess i mean i guess kelly loses as
well when i look
hmm
[Music]
oh
um
you know did you forget how to speak
english
[Laughter]
sometimes i get to speak english i feel
yeah
when i get too lazy
i'm speaking noises if i get to leave
but oh god what am i doing huh
[Music]
how is it impressive how i'm still alive
i mean like that you gotta give me dad
i'm still alive
i'm proud of you thank you
hold on a little longer until you can
get cali because that's right you're
almost there
we're almost there oh no well
whatever you're sending me is not
helping me
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
i'll master it like right now i'm going
to play i have yet to
not die first i should have done that
now i'm backward i think yeah we're
really
getting this same claim i think so
i should just really maybe next time you
try a bit slower and
so i try to follow you and then we can
defeat cali
[Laughter]
but no i don't think i can do that and
then that that requires some skill
looking good on my side
give me purple yes thank you
[Music]
oh
oh up my goodness just dropped on me
oh callie bye-bye
it was nice knowing you guys going crazy
me to do that
[Music]
a win for science
all right all all right
you do so good each time well thank you
chad i don't know
getting better you guys are getting
better every run
[Music]
this one time let's see how it goes oh
oh i have a feeling kelly's gonna how
he's gonna combo us
i can see the future whoa
i want to win
i want to win damn
wait
same you've been waiting the whole time
don't worry about it hey that's a good
point
because i'm worried about it
oh no no no no no oh no i got greedy
[Music]
i need a long boy give me a long boy a
long boy
okay whatever i'm just gonna do this
that's okay
no wait
oh
are people gonna actually force me to do
that i guess yeah
it was your idea though it was
all right yeah it was your idea i mean i
don't
i don't i don't mind i see it's cool
let's go what's my next stream oh my
gosh
in which is your next my next game is
like tomorrow i have the day off oh
my next stream is five minutes which is
gonna be a long stream i usually
stream fire emblem for like six hours
good luck for you
maybe i'll just do a quick gorilla
tomorrow maybe for one hour
mario kart or just all the time
for six hours well maybe you should have
died
it's not cheating shut up chats it's not
cheating
is that cheating i can't just really put
you up for six
hours
rules okay you are not the one to decide
wills
it's on my parents is anytime it's mine
you mean six hours of me saying puyo yes
i just have seven
thank you
hello
no just kidding
oh well he's okay
it's okay i i'm used to
it i'm used to it oh i believe in you
you want to kiss me in the practice room
yeah
but that was when callie was still a
noob and now she picked up some basic
knowledge about the game
even though like i eat right before the
sun
you're always hungry whenever you stream
then you should be eating value stream
how about asmr eating stream
yeah people will like that i don't
understand why they would like that
because i don't like them
yeah if people like something that i
don't like i just don't get it yeah
why do you enjoy eating noises it's so
weird okay
i mean you do you but like
[Applause]
i mean people people be people who like
just been singing
i actually have to focus i can't focus
when i'm hungry
i'm forcing myself to do a gorilla
tomorrow instead of uh
taking my voice oh man but that's better
than doing a six
hour
six hours
what if i what if i do a stream where i
just literally say nothing
then i also don't have to add peel what
if i just don't talk
like a stream just look at the camera
for one hour
and just stare into your soul
i'm sure enjoy that very much holy
i think yeah there was a youtube a
youtuber like in boomer times
who did that like she looked uh into the
camera
for all of her videos and said nothing
and sometimes she would say hello
does someone know who i'm talking about
i will not say the name but do you guys
know what
i'm talking about i think weebs knows
people in my channel are standing out
yeah one person said it one person said
it
do you know what i'm talking about
[Music]
no no i'm not talking about the girl of
the peas
much older than that
[Music]
you're welcome for all the kiara noises
today well you also made a lot of weird
noises there young lady
i don't know what you're talking about
it's just a normal day for
chocolate noises yeah compilation
there is a aren't there like
compilations like clips of weird youtube
noises
with weird uh v trooper noises i think i
saw something like that
yeah yeah yeah today is a great day for
them
to collect content
[Music]
i think we don't even have to count
anymore
it's pretty obvious
i love it i love it
kind of walked into that one you know
when you came
[Music]
maybe things would have been different
maybe maybe kelly was just lucky
you know oh god oh god oh my god
okay
what am i doing
i'm trying to make up for it callie
concentrating so much that she doesn't
talk
what do you mean tell us about something
that happened
today did something happen today and
you're trying to excuse me and make me
not learn
no i already
[Music]
i'm actually practicing your song as
well
i am i'm pretty good at it at this point
why are you doing this why not
okay good job yeah keep going keep going
no
i hate that
[Laughter]
no just everyone's spamming green hearts
why are they doing that back to the
lobby i want to play tetris again
why is it green doll white ring because
i sang many shrek songs look at him
infecting my child
and many tracks off and i replaced some
of the lyrics with the with the word
shrek
started spamming the green heart oh
that's
cute yeah deadbeats love shrek
did you sing somebody once i did
yeah i was just about to be i know i
just have to like slide in just like
yeah somebody told me
once okay can we characters um we all
the green characters from around
characters all right there's a bunch of
green characters
there we go green let's be green
[Music]
together
[Laughter]
fitting that i'm on the green team oh
sorry oh
yeah can we all be we can't be the same
team right on the screen
yeah well here we go
anyway i also hit eight eight uh
yeah yeah i did
i did did you reach it during this
during the cutout
yeah well i i i did i reached it right
before the karaoke and then i mentioned
it and then i said please don't
unsubscribe and then many
about 100 subscribers but then they
subscribed back when they heard that i
wasn't going to die
to keep hearing this thing
i did one of those before but then um i
reached it like after like five minutes
or so
so i was like i'm gonna keep on singing
so i kept on singing for an hour or so
ah that's one way
yeah cause i'm still i mean at that
point i'm celebrating now
celebrating for reaching the massam
which means in my phone recently
[Music]
and there's also a lot of stones on my
field can someone like stop
like i'm trying to
celebrate our
oh my god oh wait that was the wrong one
stop it
[Music]
thank you
i wouldn't say i'm really bad at it i'm
i'm not good at it but i wouldn't say
i'm really bad at it
um
is someone whose first language is not
english that sounds very weird to me
you're boning yourself
isn't that kind of a wrong way of like i
don't
it's family friendly stream
now listen here we don't do that here we
don't do family friendly streams family
we don't do that like friends things
here i guess we don't i mean i
definitely don't
oh i've been doing it wrong this entire
time
no not wow but you're doing it your way
you're saying you're family you're not
extremes this family are family friendly
can someone
can confirm that yeah
i guess they are here it could be
nope i'm done have you ever seen have
you ever have you ever said the f
word on your string i said
fudge wow you can control myself
respecting yummy good guys
[Music]
like completely you know not saying
anything at all
of those words
yeah i'm doing good how long is this
gonna be like that
there we go wall of stones
yeah yeah we're planning on it
eventually
is there is there like english songs in
japanese karaoke i forget
yeah yeah yeah there are there are
you mean like if they are in the mouse
yeah they are like plenty of them
the new songs come in kind of slow but
they do come
[Music]
get it
my hp is running low
are you implying that dr oopsie doesn't
raise your hp
here it lowers it in the long run
it's like
oh god here we go again some say
look at the skill so you know okay
am i winning this oh
[Music]
you don't want to lose it one more time
against me do you i don't think we want
to see you losing again
it could hurt your reputation right
i can't lose a reputation if i never had
one
that's when i gonna come back my friend
congratulations okay come back come back
to our phoenix's uh
sessions exactly but i think i think
it's a bit too late i already lost too
many times to make up for it
by now
you never know at least you came back
how are you
come on come on
[Music]
stop it
that was an accident oh no
[Music]
come on
yes
only happens when youtube terminates my
channel hashtag feelings down
thanks guys for everyone participating
i mean phoenix town is a revival item
yeah
in which game yeah
see people pointed that out to me but
not here
oh yeah i already said oh god it's
coming close the death is closed
coming hope no no no no no no no
[Music]
send me heaven i don't know what i'm
singing this is a random song that no
that doesn't even exist so copyright
can't strike me cause copyright got
nothing on me
oh yeah yeah youtube got nothing on me
try to terminate me again if you can
but you got nothing on me youtube you
got nothing on me
youtube you've got nothing on me
youtube phoenix down only happens
when you close your eyes and you
have your ass in luke
[Laughter]
it died for a moment how do you know oh
it's my child seeing it
i want to change back to puyo wait what
why is your channel saying that my child
is down
it was time for a moment what how did
did i take my singing
my child was just uh telling me that
your your
chat was broken it was i was i was
noticing that when i was singing what
the hell
was it i thought it was only me maybe it
was my
wow maybe it was your beautiful singing
yeah it was then lyrics
couldn't handle it it was like a magical
spell or something
hmm okay
i think we are getting closer to the
final matches all right i think uh we
know who the uh
who the boss game i think winner is
i don't think it's that obvious i think
we have to start some recounts
[Applause]
[Music]
i mean
pounding weighs differently and then i
would have won
make sense right maybe i'll just i'll
just terminate
uh youtube again
again you can
people people um have made up a theory
though that it wasn't me but it was cali
as a revenge for me
or it was ami like there's these two
theories either it was america with cali
what do you guys think was it ramen is a
little more likely
ground pounding you know yeah
i mean there has been evidence
everywhere on the internet even on my
debut re-w stream i showed the evidence
of uh on the ground pounding
uh coming into the youtube offices ready
to ground pounds looking really rips
oh my goodness i mean that was a bad run
for me so
i saw that coming
i was a little quicker than i thought um
got them
nine
from where i'm from we celebrate
christmas only in the evening the
christmas morning on the next day is
like nobody cares about it anymore
people
don't care so we give gifts we open the
gifts in the evening christmas you can
use that in the morning
yeah we usually open it in the morning i
can't wait that long
to be fair we usually just like you know
open it like we even know what's in
there already
oh wait why would you know
[Music]
because they're going to hide what
you're asking for
wait is her eyes wide open yeah staring
at the street
oh
yeah those are those australian um
traditions yes this is australian
oh it's uh it's a little angel
riding on a kangaroo bringing us
presents kangaroo
oh the other
[Music]
how many rounds left in like this like
run until we go back
oh if i win once more then we go back to
the lobby
okay so if you win i say no more
say no more cuz i'm looking at the time
we said like one and a half hours
yes and this might be the last match
what what all right let's make it count
i will win oh god hold on
i don't want to be drunk no no no no we
don't need to have space bd you can be
slow you know you can just take it
easy
no reason to stress yourself
[Music]
yeah you guys don't hear the voice of my
character you think
prepare your puyo
y'all
[Music]
oh
i'm desperate
no i don't believe in anything
you believe in yourself no i don't
believe in anything
i'm confident
[Music]
oh
we got another
and i actually concentrate i have a
chance for winning
i do oh my god but i'm an entertainer at
heart you know i'm an entertainer
i have
oh my god you guys disappeared on my uh
room but that's okay oh you also
disappeared from um
never gives up i told you this guy a
phoenix
never gives up
[Music]
this is the way i pop up never surrender
never gonna give you up
never gonna let you down
[Applause]
i'm
stop it just stop just stop stop stop
you know if you could do me this honor
and
play maybe you don't have to give it to
me but like at least like
give me a chance of re-re-thinking
resulting my honor i can speak okay i'm
focusing go for it go for it
go for it ladies and gentlemen
[Music]
oh
oh and she connected the great the the
little bit
i'll give you ten more seconds until
what ten that's it what
nine until what eight what's going on
what's going on what's going to happen
what's
[Laughter]
okay
oh my god
you made me really nervous there you
know made me really nervy
if i just stay calm if i just stay home
you have a chance
you do it's the final countdown
we're just really nice trying to get
those copyright strikes today aren't we
it's okay i have challenged my luck with
that many times before nothing happened
so
[Laughter]
this this game is taking a while huh
maybe i'm not getting better
now it's not looking so good anymore
[Music]
that was good i mean um it's not so
obvious who
who has to do the bachelor game i don't
think it's so obvious so we will have to
count the
scare um yeah it's
well you sure about that
yes i think so oh well i don't know
let's do it let's do an account
uh let me check see here it says
kiara that's the number that's not
counting it's just
that's just saying words
[Laughter]
i i will i will take the honor of doing
the battle game of
in my following stream which does which
doesn't have to be the final one it just
has to be
the following stream uh saying puyong at
the end of every sentence i say
for the whole stream okie
[Music]
that must be wrong what the hell but i
believe that you that eno one eleven
times i do believe that
it's very confusing ah at the time
wait actually
kelly won one time you know
won thirteen times and i won two times
ah i have one more afternoon i have one
more often than kelly but lost more
often than cali
what hmm what now how do we count this
we just
what we didn't specify does this mean
that we get a puya
from cali what nope i'll never do it oh
how did it come on down
tables doesn't it oh my god
how about we both do it yeah i won't do
it why would you collide
i want to just do it don't let your
chancey dreams what's your next stream
darling
do it don't you i never agreed to it
well
how about how about you do it uh because
you said you have a
a segment after after the stream and so
you might not i'm going to do it
at the same time
all the time because i don't feel like
it
doesn't have to be every sentence but
just like as much as possible
yes yes that was fun wasn't it anyone
who has some
something to say like announcement or
whatever it put on
ah you guys go ahead i don't have much
i've got nothing i think
just a regular all week i guess okay
same here
i think all our schedules are up so if
you guys want to check those out
for when we're streaming oh but we
finally after a long time we have a
a full member collab
like friday for some saturday for others
um
i think that wraps it up doesn't it yes
are you dying oh no
she's just trying to get away from the
queen
all right everyone in my stream at least
we say at the end of it
thank you thank you guys and you don't
have to join me
okay okay i'm glad i need to go get a
drink that's a good choice okay
which is why you guys are getting dj joe
for the odd show again so i know
we were supposed to stop but i need to
go get a drink so yeah
okay thanks everyone
[Music]
peace peace bro peace
you