thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
questions
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
chat come here
oh wait is that a shotgun or a rifle I
don't know should it be more like
pew
cutting
[Laughter]
oh that is
okay well
it does whatever I tell it to do okay
foreign
[Laughter]
how you doing I'm fine by the way uh
yeah
fine I think just a little bit of a hmm
hydration lack lack of hydration
uh
[Music]
Genghis Scott
Put the gun down be reasonable
what's not reasonable about a pink
shotgun huh
I'm jumpy as hell me too always that's
me always
you stay hydrated
always
um
I know I know I did put the pink skin on
the weapons that the game told me to buy
yeah anyway you guys go back up there or
else you know what happens or else
and then we're gonna play some more GTA
today
well GTA wow wow wow we're gonna
unfortunately have to deal some more
with Trevor that [\h__\h] ass rat
is not beautiful insult I need to learn
more insults here ass rats this is how
we start
it only gets better from here
oh
in German we don't really use that or do
we Ash
na
ass face is something we use a lot you
[\h__\h] ass face
yeah yeah
ass hats Ah that's a weird insult Ash uh
Ashwood
[Music]
um
it was uh so I think I you know I
spawned in in the house because you know
of the way we
uh the way we left it off last time
uh okay let's see if I remember how to
play this game
uh okay I'm being sneaky sneak
oh
she has a makeup table I got myself a
makeup table now too I used to have uh
one but uh
after a while I've used it so many times
that
it's like after moving several times in
the past
it kind of like
lost legs several times because it was
really cheap now I got myself a new one
yeah and I put up the big big mirror for
it
me
look at me when you talk to me uh yeah
big big ground mirror I put it up
yesterday so I can properly do my makeup
at my backup table again
game mode volume
what what
so much I interrupted your menopause you
mean I I paused your menopause
damn that's some sick skill you should
be respecting me for that that's
something no no doctor can do candy I
don't know I don't really know what
menopause really is is it when okay we
don't have to talk about that but I
guess it's like a women's midlife crisis
or so
anyway
uh so
uh I I suppose I have to like start that
one Mission Again
uh so we we go here right to to the L
oh sure I think
I'm assuming
yeah okay okay and
wait I once again I tried to put some
songs in here let's see if it worked out
uh
wait do I have to wait self radio right
I have to I would have to switch to
there we go self radio
and then let's first
perform a quick scan
there you go oh and let's test
baby
underneath the show
I don't need no drinks tonight give me
that be give me that sing feel it Mash
movie
foreign
[Music]
oh
feel it rise through me
need no drinks tonight give me death
amazing okay
I don't know is this like for for car
car radio volume we think this is fine
I mean there's gonna be a lot of traffic
noises too so it won't even be maybe one
more there you go oh wow
the MCA buy my own music now please no
okay so that works
should I do that what's that even
so
that works now
will it always be
ah no it doesn't go on my on my finger
by default why would you not go
[\h__\h] off [\h__\h] off uh how do you do that
again out no uh tab no wait
thank you
why please just stay on there will it
stay on there now once I selected it
once
oh what is this oh what is this
recall what disease
you hear it it's too quiet maybe but now
here it goes
[Music]
I put in the instrumental version
but also if I don't want to be too
distracted I won't be too distracted uh
what ah
dude
[Music]
tell me I can hear it clearly tell me
foreign
[Music]
s but also not even that many songs but
I put some some songs that I thought
would be fun to hear while driving in
this list
this is
I just love this this melody it's not
really the melody but you know
the Rhythm I can hear it clearly tell me
get out
oh no the music is
[Music]
anyway let's listen to this again I
guess
so we can recall what we were doing
music stuff sit down and face forward
okay now I don't have a lot of time all
is normal money yes Mike will tell you
about life Invader oh [\h__\h] y'all two did
that look forward we're two strangers
Straight Ahead friendly chat and don't
pretend that you liked Jane if it was a
friendly chat wouldn't we look at each
other I mean yeah the dude our source
worked the child slaves the stolen sold
everybody's private information and even
ripped his own friends ideas off and
walked around like the Messiah while
doing it but what happened deserve to
have his [\h__\h] head blowed off on TV
oh well aren't you just a Moral Majority
you know that's why the world is the way
it is today when a paid Thug it's all
Namby pambi when someone asks him to act
like a paid Thug and for a good cause
man check this out homie I like blowing
[\h__\h] Fool's ears off just as
much as the next time
well now you can because it's not Fool's
heads it's [\h__\h] hands and not just
heads you know trashing cars or planning
lies forging evidence anything we can do
to take the battle back to these turds
you know we'll fix the market in our
favor and we'll write a few wrongs while
we're at it oh [\h__\h] okay cool right so
you heard of malice hell yeah no again
it's giving the living rigor mortis only
Brett Lowry CEO of bilkington research
paid off the FDA he's addressed for
giving desperate middle-aged men in the
world over heart attacks damn man that
sucks yeah
at the Von krastenburg hotel in Richmond
of course he'll be well a hotel if he
goes away back to using malice and beta
Pharmaceuticals gets a big bump in the
price of their stock damn man all right
[\h__\h] it I got you I thought that you
would now consider using a sniper rifle
or sticker all I think of when I see the
latest RPGs role play game I'm gonna
make the investment
RPG now walk away and I'll stay here
until you're gone
I can improve my stats after all just no
real level right and go to the hotel
wait are we like just going there and
checking the situation now or are we
already gonna kill someone
right it was let me check
just for sake of credits
uh it won't let me tap out
it won't let me let me there we go ah
uh I should wait go
let me let me credit what credit is due
I'm gonna go to Art Of Ashes there we go
it was made by CK pun open thank you
it's in uh kiasano yeah my pink gun
thank you very much you guys are also
welcome to make me some weapons or
anything really anything and anything to
be honest glasses
hats but no ass hats please
have enough of those in this game
okay so uh apparently we need to go here
but should we stop by the weapon store
or am I good
whatever
I put this song and hope you like it
it's uh the add track song
[Music]
first oh does he not have a sniper oops
how do you look up your weapons again
[Music]
I guess I can't in the car
I don't know
lyrics to these songs please forgive me
while I da da da
good
[Music]
I hate this every time sorry every time
I'm like in the car there's a good song
on the radio it makes me so mad when we
suddenly stop
and then they're like get out and I'm
like what do you mean get out I want to
stay in the car and listen more to this
what the [\h__\h] sometimes I I purposefully
stay longer in the car to finish the one
song because that's like kind of like
isn't that like so OCD into inducing
when you can't finish listening to a
song that you're really enjoying just
because the person that you're driving
with decides to arrive
when you're not [\h__\h] ready
right you did it too
nice nice okay so we buy sniper because
apparently I really don't have time yet
was that shotgun rifle uh okay have a
nice [\h__\h] day yeah you too uh
something in the back heavy sniper
seems like the only sniper anyway
okay
uh we have a [\h__\h] ton of money
what do I add to it guys what should we
add
uh what is this noise maybe the
suppressor
oh is this dmca well for [\h__\h] sake man
it probably really doesn't matter
because the videos of the stream is not
monetized
um suppressor
how many bullets one two
oh there we go is it this is nice to
sniper we don't need that money right oh
sick
but obviously obviously I have a big
difference
happy
baby okay Advanced scope okay okay this
is all I really need I would say
uh huh uh how do I own it now
let's see yes I own it now
it's my arrive I really [\h__\h] hate
this menu
okay
bye bye now we go to the hotel oh should
I get some armor I heard armor makes
everything really a lot easier
oh stocks I did buy stocks before but I
think that was just Michael
oh I wear one of them all the time all
the time even in bed hmm
um well we do have the money for you
know anything really uh we can just buy
the best thing honestly
it's funny it's called but why is it not
available in pink what the [\h__\h] no don't
get too crazy crazy and how do I how do
I put that on is that like under my
shirt now automatically
oh
[Music]
okay I have it on okay
what's this song called
Blue Bar oh
what what what the [\h__\h] you want I mean
sure whatever the blue bar is my armor I
don't know what it looked like before
but okay
all right all right all right let's take
this car again my car
Black Velvet is a song name oh
what's my
my car did no I was dead
is dead
you will beat hinotori what I'm hearing
but we're gonna
to listen to it for too long
[Music]
do you hear this
should I go upward
what what's with the mini map I see yeah
but where do I park
in front of the hotel and wait a second
it should be inside the parking house
oh I'm that's what you mean
be clear with me
a conversation communication skills
maybe I need to be up here
I don't see
I don't think I need to be up here
what do um wait maybe they want me to go
to the top
um
wait
oh I don't see a yellow Mark here
bottom floor
um
really
ah when it has the ever going down oh I
never noticed that it means I'm uh too
high
up okay I see
okay one more
and now now we're on the Red Bull ah
okay okay there it is
at least I got to listen to the song for
a bit longer
hi
no one's talking guys have arrived to
pick up the target from the hotel the
plan his head quickly and find a
location with a good advantage point of
the hotel
planned what I feel like they just
[\h__\h] throw me into the cold water it
says are you for real
no no it's just good
what the [\h__\h] am I supposed to do
buy stocks what the [\h__\h]
okay
I don't even know how to [\h__\h] I buy
stocks
I'm gonna type in
too late for stocks what the [\h__\h]
no
no go away
yeah I won't leave the area now what
this is for authorized personnel only
what are you talking to me
no one's here
anyway whatever [\h__\h] that
I don't care I'm not going to check up
why is there no what 30 seconds until he
walks out of here or what
you [\h__\h] came what
I need backup now all nearby units
reports why are they shooting me what
why are they shooting me
why why the [\h__\h]
is shooting me
huh
I see
I see how it is
I see how the [\h__\h] it is
What if I
go to
but then the Escape will be difficult if
I go to the if I go to the very top of
this and then shoot him from the top
won't my Escape be really difficult
[Music]
or do you think they've just not noticed
me
um
there's a ramp above how far above oh
okay I'm gonna try to get like a little
bit higher
[Music]
welcome back everybody
I have killed the target successfully
you missed it unfortunately it was a
god-like moment uh I was such a Pro
Gamer I did a 360 no scope yeah
just kidding I didn't
of course I didn't
where's this [\h__\h] ramp
anyway I don't really have time
uh so wait uh
I know what he looks like who am I
shooting
I can't see [\h__\h] ah
that's
will it come out of here
who will I shoot
but the person who looks important okay
this doesn't look
safe
oh
three two one
assessment Target
huh keep your eye out for anything
unusual if we can get through one day
without some wannabe hippie waving an
anti-globalization sign in my face is
that the dude
he sounds so close as if he's like here
he's not
oh wait here let's go
this guy no yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
was that him
not here I'm just chilling [\h__\h] I failed
the mission
I mean how
well that it was me oh that is still
okay how would they even know oh God I
mean that's kind of suspicious Behavior
[Laughter]
that is very suspicious
I mean I'm stuck here how could I
possibly shot anyone in this position
now
God damn it
well can I redo the mission Blaze
yeah it's time
that was not good
but
he will be in the car now no he won't
get up huh I need backup now well nearby
units report immediately
okay we'll try this jump again if we can
make it up to the top very fast
where did I go oh I wonder
what floor
um
give me a [\h__\h] second guys they can't
be better at this than me
oh my god wow
I wanted to kill me though because I
failed the [\h__\h] mission
okay there we go
that was a smooth jump though if we just
do that again then everything will be
digable
um
so do I once again try to get to the top
I will
as a practice run I don't need to but
then on the first floor why on the first
pillow though I want to use the ram to
escape now
don't I want to use the ramp for escape
pool
three blocks me I mean that's true I
guess
okay then let me at least get the client
position
got the ramp
can I see him from here
oh I should be able to see him from here
do I do that I don't have
I don't have a [\h__\h] plan
okay so this is a bodyguard I suppose
two body guys
okay
maybe I should have I mean I should have
stayed on the first floor because I told
you escaping will be really difficult
now
I don't even know
oh wait
did I do it
[Music]
give up Mr Laurie I think I did it but
well I can even go up or I can go down
and for standpoints
go up
they didn't even find me yet oh they
didn't even notice me did I kill him oh
wait oh I didn't have enough momentum
well I can play some tennis now no one
will find me here
I'm stuck in here
perfect hiding honestly yeah can I just
wait
[Laughter]
I couldn't drive over the net come on
can I go here
okay
do I just Escape now
they have like no idea who did that
was very [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] me what the hell yeah
let's go wait that's that's dancing what
the [\h__\h]
okay what now next mission please Lester
but before that I've got to tell you
something our Investment Portfolio is
getting a little uh successful so I
figured we needed some tangible Assets
in your property so we bought a house in
the Vinewood Hills yeah sure man
whatever you know best about this [\h__\h]
and we needed someone to live there and
for tax purposes so some guys are moving
your stuff in oh [\h__\h]
it's yours enjoy it 3671 whiskey Mound
Drive
ah [\h__\h] radio
uh I live in a new house this location
can only use the safer okay
sorry I think I stopped him from talking
because I wanted to change the DMC I
couldn't turn down the audio because
then we wouldn't hear him anymore anyway
I guess I'm going here
new car it's a nice one I think all
right let's see if our house will be
just as nice
good
[Music]
ah what do you what do you call that
stuff in the back here
it looks really fancy
spoil it what oh okay I was like why
what do you mean what can't you tell me
just be open and honest with me what you
mean
what do you mean with white house should
I go here
that am I living in the White House what
White House ain't in LA
what should I go there
oh okay
spoiler alert yes bull alerts bullets
and coming don't look at this car
I am the spoiler
[Music]
wow oh nice no crash oh no crash oh
this is by the way one of the Hino Tony
remixes
[Music]
oh it's a good bouncy song a car should
go really bounce
bounce bounce bounce
ah [\h__\h] I missed my I missed my turn to
my dad
[Music]
my car is worth millions better not bump
into me
oh I will snap your ass
why am I like in the middle of nowhere
to get me a house in the city center
next to Michael
I want to be Michael's neighbor that
would be so sweet
I'm still in a good mood because so far
I haven't heard anything from Trevor
so I'm happy
I guess this area has nice houses huh
a lot of people have cars and drive
around with cars with public trap public
transport sucks
so wait is this um
it's my house sick
[Music]
so I guess it doesn't matter if you live
in the city center or on the corner of
the city there's one you save house what
about my Mamas and my aunt's house
can I have this car forever thank you
that's everywhere okay
let's take a look oh welcome to my crib
MTV crib with Franklin
oh
fancy why is it already furnished noise
damn how much is this place
costs
oh but he doesn't even have a real
fireplace he has real wood but not a
real fireplace it's like how much are
you trying to
fake it till you make it huh
real good I don't get it
what it's a randomized
imagine what really what
oh I love this kitchen
the big middle kitchen counter
a million [\h__\h] Ovens that I'm never
gonna be using
oh I'm gonna go out
where is it open here okay oh
oh
they're not bad oh and of course two
pools two
a place like this in L.A
definitely costs like 50 100 million
oh no
a place like this in Austria costs maybe
10 million
Maybe
at least 15 million okay not 100 okay
am I overestimating
oh wow let's go for a swim and we can
get some of our athletic skills up right
or does this not count swims yeah yeah
oh good boy
but I don't really see it doing anything
oh yes good good Park yeah you better
protect your owner choppy choppy job
and does this really not do anything
[Music]
um
I can see the hotel from here
oh my God it's an infinite in an
infinity pool
okay I guess this doesn't work
what about yeah I guess we can go on a
walk does that help me with my
rest love plate what
let's take a right click I don't get it
this the way they show that to you I
don't know what which one they mean are
we walking now
how do we because I I kick
it's a left click or right Clank
ah it's uh the chat uh it's covering it
but
no I didn't wanna wanna kick him
hold right click and click left
let's hit the pavement
uh Brandon can play fetch using the ball
in the weapon wheel ah you come with me
I guess we can go here I don't know can
you climb walls
I
can't
and he climb here
[\h__\h]
I think this was too much for Chop champ
rights no
[Laughter]
he's just admiring the nature
no no you're not dismissed
oh
tappy
come here stupid dog
he'll teleport okay
good boy come on come on no I don't know
where the [\h__\h] door is open yeah
driving with a car is easier now than
walking for me
where is the exit of my apartment
what are these doors
these doors even lead
like can the dog will go inside because
he's not following me
oh no no
okay chop
wait no I kind of dismissed him by going
inside
I think oh God
damn it okay whatever what am I supposed
to do oh [\h__\h] not the gun
um
should I switch to Michael or should I
go to like
the L
perhaps
B is the main mission B
be
b b a b
don't go to L travel no [\h__\h] Trevor
[Music]
I got to be
we'll go to B and we go with my bike now
my green bike
okay now
[Music]
I'm special about you when I see you I
know it's true
no no no
just miss you
baby
[Music]
the same do you do you do you
ever let yourself
did you guys see yesterday I uploaded my
face
it wasn't even my first
the one I uploaded in the Maldives for
me and Elena were singing It's Raining
Men
was my first YouTube short and
everything after that I failed uploading
but besides that
this is my second short oh why is there
a Red Dot there
baby
[Music]
it's a shark on my list in my shorts
list it's in there it's too short it's
definitely a short what do you mean
can't complain I know the same don't you
do you say you don't feel the same
and anyway
I'm hoping
the people who ARA will participate in
English
yeah and now you guys said you will try
but no pressure but it would be cool to
see some people
try it out
um
oh shitty kind of surprised
I swear okay
okay
I was pressing out but it doesn't work
when I'm like hiding in that studio
this is not working
show man I'm holding it on it
there you go I needed to go away for
some reason
baby
amazing I really want to meet nanaji I
want to go to Japan to see energy
been talking with energy a little bit
and um
about a topic that concerns both of us
and uh yeah it's been really
ah nice to talk to someone who
understands
yeah and then she was also like
super happy to talk to someone who gets
it and I'm like I [\h__\h] love you you
get it girl you get it
get it
you understand my worries
it's our worries it's not my worries
it's our worries
yeah someone is
you got to
um
if I mean I can go but doesn't mean that
if I go that I'll do my 3D
showcase I have to wait for all the
other girls so
yeah we're watching a horror what
what is wrong smoking in my house you
know ever since that psychotic pile of
yours turned up you turned into an even
bigger [\h__\h]
thank you
you support me you start something a
different Mission I've supported you I
left
to come here with you and still that
crazy bastard turns up I'll handle it
how I don't know oh you know what just
keep him away from me and the children
you low life whoremongering ass wipe
another word no I think she said
um hello Fabian darling
I'm ready to practice yes oh yes she's
very center a regular Oasis
anger issues and we're friends no wonder
I'm so upset please
Namaste Namaste we practice
join us please
no please no no no the yoga is for
sharing awesome
okay
you make me as happy and mellow as my
wife it'll be a job well [\h__\h] done we
are all on our own Journeys Michael yeah
no doubt very important Mission every
mission is important such is life
Michael
now here is good we have the Sun
and the murabunda
to the earth I will put something in
your [\h__\h] but if you don't stop if
you never say [\h__\h]
yes he's actually enjoying it
looks bad
okay now you're French apparently
hey this time
this time
what are those hips what the [\h__\h] it's
like she
what is like as if she has no hip bones
I don't know about this
swap Mouse and keys for left and I am
left-handed
wait how what
this is the first step on a very long
road what do you want me to do walk with
me how do I
huh
my I mean I'm left-handed but still like
I guess I'm used to right and keep it
down
it's not [\h__\h] doing it oh what
you are an ugly man
yoga
[\h__\h] ugly
these are the basics you must Master
them what do you want what do you want
what do you want from me what what
resume
move Mouse down hold and lose yourself
you are just one mung bean inside okay
well how they did not tell what
what
okay everybody relax everyone [\h__\h]
relax maybe I need this maybe I [\h__\h]
need this my child okay I understand now
let's go one time and this is what you
do take a breath what am I supposed to
do now there's two mice next to my
fingers I'm not allowed to let go of I
don't have free mice connected to my
[\h__\h] PC
what do you want what is it what does it
want from me
let's just hold
ass click
I'll be playing a [\h__\h] rhythm game
now please ah
strong like an erection of your youth
are you saying is um erectiones are not
as strong anymore
man he's he's got already some
confidence issues
don't make it worse
it's already going for some [\h__\h] man
uh-huh inhale
and how do I out hail uh-huh feel all
that possibility security and
self-centeredness Drift Away
is this really the whole mission don't
tell me this is so much absolutely
Hotel wouldn't that be like you know
does that make sense
intake
outtake how to lose the breath yeah I'll
take who would have thought it possible
not me it's gonna have to do now we'll
do something more complicated
sometimes
I weep uncontrollably for hours
start that's why
we [\h__\h] controlling me when you do this
ah oh wow I want to [\h__\h] drown him in
the pool you feel that
the emotion inside no Let It Go
Michael join us please no this is why I
don't do yoga I feel like I'm channeling
[\h__\h] very much I [\h__\h] agree with
you so much I couldn't agree more of you
Michael this is why you and me wear one
I'm surprised you're doing this so far
come on I'm Loki disappointed in you
Michael but I see we're still on the
same wavelength later you can show a
stripper how flexible you are I will
breathe baby I will stretch brought me a
[\h__\h] dignity if you don't shut up
shut up shut
up shut up
you feel that
what what what am I I feel that I want
to kill you
um I want to rip out your limbs so you
can't do yoga anymore strong inhale
out through the mouth yeah where else
would it go out my butt
see I'm better at this than you guys are
anyway
because I can control myself at least
please
Michael it's Michael
how's it so hard for you guys and how
many years of marriage and this is the
first time he's taken an interest in my
hobbies nitrous I'm about to feel some
emotions all right
do not fear the unknown
we are the unknown oh show us a man I'm
known attention
[Music]
oh my God this is why I don't do yoga
this is too much for me
when I had a yoga course they told me to
feel how my body touches the ground even
the parts that didn't touch the ground
and it sounded like a whole lot of
[\h__\h] to me I'm sorry please please
Michael just bring it I'm such a yoga
hater
go
fell
you want me to breathe your lungs they
work yes shut up shut up
now if you could just get Trevor on a
yoga mat oh my God don't even mention
his name makes me [\h__\h] aggressive
release it I hate him more after the
stream than I did during the Stream
because the more the more time I spend
away from him
the stronger the hate Grill I didn't
sing no where's that love
is okay
Breeze please Michael mm-hmm
I have to say though these these Mouse
instructions are [\h__\h] I found yoga
before I didn't have you guys
telling me how to do this I would have
never figured out
your lungs they work yes
Trevor is an acquired taste can you
thank us now for saving you from this
yeah and anyone who says Trevor is their
taste they have no taste
must have lost their tongue or something
release it
let it out you're turning red
hey you have come a long way today
Michael yes later you will cry like a
baby
right okay chakras are completely
blocked don't worry about it
unbelievable those chakras yeah what do
I do I'm glad we have helped please
your sexual energies have been blocked
for too long
back into my pelvis back what backpack
yes there you go yoga
and we are never coming back you are
alone you pathetic psychopath
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you indeed first the
tennis teacher now the yoga teacher Yogi
Yogi
and we don't need that [\h__\h] Michael we
don't need it
because Jimmy's room why he's still here
there's a steel Jimmy because my chakras
aren't open well there's we're too
[\h__\h] open
especially her chakra was way too open
leave me alone right in front of my
[\h__\h] eyes too you you know what if
there was a rape button I'd be using it
right now huh it's nice TV
did I pay for that yeah you smashed the
other one didn't you
friend
get out of the house I'm not going alone
it's [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] threatening to molest your
online buddies is [\h__\h] they're not
my buddies people you speak he's getting
yelled at for being a bad boy
oh
all right 26 let's get in the car
what are we doing though
so where's your friend Burger Shop
[Music]
wait did I
did I enter or is that all
yeah nice all the kids are still hanging
out at the burger joints
[Music]
go down to the diner after class every
day you know get milkshakes fries ew
please you know you're really creeping
me out I'm trying to relate to you no
you're trying to take me on some
Nostalgia trip you're such a cliche oh
says the dope smoking game playing live
at home world owes him a living
Millennial I knew it I knew it the mask
was gonna slip the monster's been
exposed
that's bitter vindictive old man you
pretend you're being a father but you
hate me don't you I don't hate it
oh why is he so sensitive I love you
sorry if I don't express that correctly
here together
alone oh now you're an armchair
psychologist
the rest of this city you brought me
here Michael don't get surprised with
some of the Razzle Dazzle rubs huh well
I thought you'd keep your head you'll
see through some of the [\h__\h] maybe
that's what I'm trying to do oh do you
think you're walking around
picket fence values here
wake up oh wake me up inside I can't
wake up
Wake me up inside I have to meet my
friend yeah I really do I just don't get
weird for once in your life don't be
weird you can't
oh nice car
cute
excuse me 70s Vibes friendly
neighborhood drug dealer what that guy
yo oh no
man good to see you what are you turning
tricks to pay for this
young man it's my dad
[Music]
some drugs
excuse me bro you're dead funny man you
know other people they go for a walk in
the park or to a I don't know amusement
park or to uh come on what the swimming
park or whatever
oh all right all right what about the
burger
hey let's bounce bounce bounce bounce is
that what we're doing yeah
all righty then now
the house please
I mean Jimmy might as well be trancing
very soon
yeah this is my music yeah so uh want to
drink I'm driving because normally
you're such a between the white lines
spend to The Pedestrian kind of guy fine
give it here
wait what
what what give it here oh
wait did they put something into that
drink or is it just a normal drink maybe
when we get home
now
[Music]
forever can't talk anymore oh I know I
think so far no casualties I am a pro no
oh stop it
on the bus these people need to get
somewhere you don't neces me you [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] protecting you for yourself so much
money from your bank account and I'm
moving out okay you're crazy dad goodbye
good riddance
don't need no drinks never need [\h__\h]
drinks nope nope if this is what happens
then I don't need any drinks
nope nope who's taking me is that who's
that Trevor please don't say it's Trevor
it's dog dog
what
if monkeys
[Music]
she sounds like me
reveal
nice I'm joining eophie
[Music]
oh dear
Goofy's senpa's family
she did not take after them thankfully
oh are you going for the anal start
I heard that's what they do
now they didn't do [\h__\h] okay well that's
not very gentle to say goodbye to me
were you unhappy with the offering
oh
[Music]
let's go a free falling
that's my psychopath cycle
cycle cycle therapist or whatever
[Music]
oh really you ruined my life
mean
that's just mean
do we actually land there
someone came me in my pants and I you
see what
are we normal again Jimmy you little
[\h__\h]
just like me for real for real just like
for real for real
he said it
she steals my phrase but that's okay I
forgive
ah
um I
Marathon I'm back to normal how far do I
have to go
oh it's pretty close
there's nothing like a good run guess
wait I guess we can walk around a little
bit get some stamina
[Music]
we all wanted this
is Michael Michael's meme
takanashi Ki Michael
oh that's my home oh
so I don't quite understand
the
The Narrative here we went from doing
yoga with my wife and then she [\h__\h] off
leaves me I guess so because I was
feeling immediately lonely is that why I
went to Jimmy and then
he wanted to get a drink so get a drink
and then he [\h__\h] drugs me and then
leaves me too is that what happened
sad what about my daughter at least come
on
Michael oh I think you finally lost your
mind
recent behavior in the company you've
been keeping already had me very
concerned
[Music]
now you've taken to attacking my Fabian
who is a close friend
and then Jimmy said you took drugs while
driving them in your car
[\h__\h] bastard
I'm disappointing him now for a while
promise me you'd change and you haven't
changed a bit
I know you say I always act like I'm in
a movie well this isn't that
I think I'm gonna speak to a lawyer I'm
just really confused
please don't try to comment I'll try to
not [\h__\h] the lawyer too
Amanda
[\h__\h]
[Music]
foreign
this is why I hate yoga
this Mission if ever anyone ever asks me
again why I hate yogas because it
destroys families
that's why
[Music]
oh man
oh the music is so sad
oh it's over I like the music
oh wait there's a yoga icon I can do
yoga in my house now why would I ever
want to do that no
why would I ever want to do that does
that give me any new skills [\h__\h] no I
don't need that also my car isn't even
here
the [\h__\h]
oh man
okay we go to the B
go to B huh
I got no wings Pop there's too much to
deal with as well as moving out so I
took urge until I'm on my feet I'll
bring it back when I'm all set up he
took my car
I
have failed
and when I say I I'm speaking as Michael
I have failed as a father
I wouldn't say I've failed as a
as a husband because I think he did an
okay job as a husband
but I know man honestly it's not even
his fault with the children you were at
least from my from this perspective oh
God [\h__\h] yoga I should kill them
people destroy themselves anyway at some
point you know what we don't need to
kill them they are doing it by
themselves already
I know they well anyway what was I
saying yeah maybe maybe
like before his mid-life crisis he was
an actual
bad husband
and bad father
but
she'll come on
wait
um
[Music]
I can't
now I really want to see you well I
don't want to see you you need help come
on
if you don't get it get
it Tracy
you don't know what the [\h__\h] you're
talking exactly right
all I could do
this music is sick though
anyway
oh I think it's at track again
talk to him what's the right icon though
uh
what's the therapist icon
let me see this is written here
Trevor oh well there's nothing for
therapist a question mark
oh
call him
no therapist
on the left side this one
[Music]
I feel like I need to talk about it
blah blah blah
guys I'm like
the worst person to have in the car
if there's a song on the radio that I
know I will even go as far to look up
the lyrics on my phone sing along in
order to sing along if I don't know the
lyrics by heart
and then I was saying really [\h__\h]
loud
I mean I
think so it should be a pleasure to have
me in your car but I'm assuming that not
everyone thinks like that
uh
but most of the time the people who I
drive up in a car they're not much of a
singer
they don't take the initiative to sing
themselves
so it's like I don't know maybe they
enjoy having me singing I don't know who
knows I never had complaints but
huh
best passenger
thank you I would like to be your
passion gem if you let me sing do you
let me sing
do you let me be your passion passion
job
[Music]
go away guys
that's not my therapist
wait is that Tracy
message for me get off your fat ass
I see this little exercise stuff's about
As relaxing for you as it is for my wife
no I don't want to sleep with you and no
I don't care that I'm 39 and single it
doesn't worry me a bit please I'm not
stressed out at all now go [\h__\h] yourself
are you okay yes I'm okay just [\h__\h] you
Olive Garden
I seem a little upset I could still
remember the [\h__\h] ground
okay hey I played high school football
all right sweetheart Allstate QB
whatever ladies don't have a coronary
let's go wait do we know each other
[Music]
[Applause]
the bicycle ride I had with my son
exercising with your ex
oh take that traffic head on yeah I
could have guessed you were one of those
[Music]
depressions
ouch and where are we going if I can
hear you baby
oh faster go faster what the [\h__\h] why is
he going down the stairs so slowly yes
such a joy for life no
uh-oh you broke my Cadence you [\h__\h]
come on come on come on
maybe I should have taken like a
H like oh no the goal is
shortcut I thought I had issues but you
you give me hope
if he runs faster sex officers
because you're a walking advertisement
for therapy
is my health going down holy [\h__\h]
not too shabby however he's like dying
while she's still fine here I already
did it 10K today Whatever Gets You
Through It oh my [\h__\h]
man
Marianne what was with her
exercising demons
[\h__\h]
I want to go to my [\h__\h] therapist
yeah
I guess I need to call him
uh was it Dave oh no Dr friedlander
come over today
at his office is here
well I'd like to have a session
there's no one here right now leave a
message and we'll book you in as soon as
we can be well
[\h__\h] now
uh
is it marked in the map
I have to finish my quest
she's not always available no way
doesn't sound like this at all
there's a dude running to him what's he
doing
what is he doing
oh because of my gun
I didn't know I have I had the gun out
I'm so sorry dude is it because of me
nobody else is running though
[Laughter]
[Applause]
oh I want to be your friend I need
for me
come on come on
come on I mean this is fun too this is
helping me with my stamina again yeah
there you go go Michael here's my
running buddy
buddy thank you I feel like we're
developing a friendship here
wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait let's be friends
I'm innocent I I just I didn't know I
had my gun out I don't even know what a
gun is I swear to God ask my chat
[Laughter]
guys I have a I have a hunch
that
he's scared of me and running away from
me could it be
that
and away
okay now dude I'm I'm like running out
of breath
you're lucky I don't have a sniper
you know what a pistol does Trick
you were asking for it
is he not dead he's still alive is he
where is he
he did
[Music]
I am 100
innocent you guys have no idea
I'm sorry
[Music]
oh this is just car slow
oh they're losing me already
uh radio
nice raggy though
this is what happens when a man goes
into midlife crisis don't underestimate
Michael guys
he needs [\h__\h] friends too what is
this [\h__\h]
look out anyway
oh where do we go
therapist didn't have time for me you
know if he would if he had time for me
all of this wouldn't have happened and
every oh two stars and everyone would be
fine now
all right all right two stars really
I take this as an insult
me y'all are so mean
guys need to think of
my psych my psych
e
[Music]
wait if I just hide OH police is coming
there though
I'm not here
I'm not here don't tell him I'm here
guys
I swear to God if you guys tell him I'm
here
[Music]
almost my dream car
okay get out of there
I'm gonna close your money in my car
okay I guess I'll do that at some point
that was orange guys it was orange and
what was it purple or so
it was really nice
anyway when do we want to go next
me that's why they told me to go with
Michael right
don't do that don't do the wheel don't
do this to me
no no
no
[Music]
I I just escaped let's not do this again
we have a really big ass crack lady
might want to cover that
hear it clearly
that's where we're going right B
[Music]
oh
by the way yesterday yesterday
[Music]
yeah so happy it's been such a long time
like
she said she saw the cats last time
and not me so I think she was like cat
sitting at some point I don't even
remember what for anymore but I wasn't
there so she has seen me
uh less often than my cats
this year probably
yeah it was almost a nice reunion
I'll tell you a little bit about what we
did
oh we're going to the FIB oh oh
rmt rmt is my old roommate that I used
to live together with
uh
[Music]
look how cute he looks at the cherry
blossoms behind him can we take like an
Instagram picture oh let's open up a
Instagram for Michael I feel like that
kind of fits him right now
I think he needs something like that
something positive in his life hi guys
David
what's up well isn't this nice she
didn't tell me we were double dating oh
okay
this part of Love is All Mine
brilliant Steve Haynes Amigo but you
probably knew that already no your name
tag must have fallen off no [\h__\h]
onions
I love what I I gotta remember to write
that down and to shoot you in your head
you annoying dick
have you seen my show my show you mean
how to dress like a Salesman on a cheap
golf weekend at a third rate Country
Club
so
who wants to do it in the background
friend Mr K my pleasure
especially with itself
did I cupcake you should keep your
[\h__\h] voice down before I close your
[\h__\h] windpipe
the joke stopped now pal oh you will
show me my so serious
respect maybe you could Define team for
me
is that just the three of you
or the greater FIB or the entire
government because I'm tempted to argue
that thus far
we haven't shown a lot of your
colleagues a whole lot of respect
and why don't you start with me genius
you got it jokes on you that's Michael's
fetish
we have received Intel that they're
keeping Mr K at the local agency station
I just dealt with that guy the agency is
stepping up to questioning because of
your moronic Antics down at the
coroner's office we need to get him out
of there before he blabs I did what
agent Norton said
then I guess you getting involved with a
clapped out old agent who's been living
off of past glories was your first
mistake
you are my boy now Amigo my career
depends on this
and that's very important to me so
seeing as we're all boys now boys be
boys
they'll run along kids
see there you go Dave you can teach an
old dog new tricks let's go
to go
let's go makes me want to start the
wheel let's go
the bureau owns a lot out in East LS
Covington supplies off El Rancho can you
take us there sure sounds nice and
secluded kind of place you'd run in off
the books operation huh so what so I bet
Federal ain't on the deed that's so and
we all like our federal government open
and transparent are we taking that Blue
Cross closed in opaque suits I'm just a
puppet you're the one pulling the
strings I like the metallic look on it
Volvo is fresh
all right your car but I'm driving you
what's a nice color not only baby you
expensed this ride to the taxpayer
[Music]
radio
so how far is this
pre-files I need you to make a couple of
calls get some people on board first
guys Franklin Clinton well I barely know
that kid
fixing up my car call him or we'll send
some Gmail our Franklin right okay
nice nice nice nice nice
Michael this ain't the best time I'm
kind of busy hey sorry about that listen
you know that thing we talked about
before it's happening I need you to come
to a lot off L Ranch not far from where
we met before all right that's cool I'm
in LS anyway
now Trevor Phillips oh you're crazy
I thought you might say that so we had
him picked up that's a dumb move Dave
getting Mr K out of the IAA
stationed across the street keeping an
eye on the proceedings Phillips flies
you repel down make the extraction and
I'm the best guy you got for this with
you we've got good leverage great and
you brought trip
my reaction about Trevor reminds me of
how Michael Scott reacts to whenever
um what's his name the HR guy is around
he's like no no no that is no no anyone
but him no yeah Toby yeah
[Music]
we're telling them I'm all cozy with the
f5v
control of the situation discreet
control
yeah good luck trolling discreet driver
I wonder how controllable and discreet
he'll be when he sees the guy who killed
me and put Fred in jail maybe I'll hang
back yeah yeah that might be a good idea
okay
anyway
let's talk about something positive
[\h__\h]
so the first we met up in my place so
that she could see the kitty cats again
and we could decide what to do
yeah damn they definitely recognized her
but uh chonkers is as always like such a
[\h__\h] tsundere weirdo
yeah you try to greet her and she's she
like is like you know you get you go up
to her try to say hello and she's like
and then [\h__\h] up runs away
like two meters and then you go up to
her again and then she goes like boom
and she [\h__\h] off again
such a weirdo
foreign
but uh rmt she knows chunk as well so
you know we know chocolates doesn't
dislike people it's just she's a little
bit soon
yeah she's [\h__\h] cute I had a good
cuddle with her today very good cuddle
both chunky and smoothie but anyway so
then we decided just because I haven't
been to the movies in like a million
years
I just had to go to the movies
so we looked through the like
um movies that they have in the cinemas
right now but like nothing really spoke
to me nothing really seemed familiar to
me except like four in Spider-Man but
both of those I haven't watched the the
prequels I guess and
yeah I mean four actually interests me
Spiderman would be like nah to me before
I would be interested in but I would
need to watch the movie from before that
I think because it seemed like a like a
sequel you know what you better keep a
low profile yeah I think I will see you
later anyway is that cagey [\h__\h]
huh
[Music]
wait
the letters are
golden
oh
why did I translate that for everybody
well you guys have ever known what that
shirt means frankly that's such a jerk
you better take off these GTA developers
are so funny ha ha what am I detecting
some uh some sort of uh Sun I never had
[\h__\h] here Mikey huh Hey listen if
you want to replace some father figure
you can do a lot better than this fat
snake all right this [\h__\h] would eat
his own kids like I said Franklin
deranged don't take him from
exactly four sucks that's Trevor best
friend that's Franklin the son I always
wanted
all right guys listen it's more to me
then I don't have you lifting on this
job okay Trevor all I need you to do is
fly me to the Target Franklin you're
going to cover me from across the street
we're going to make these [\h__\h] happy
and walk away from this thing clean got
it I got you all right and we do this
and they help us bring Brad
yeah we'll talk about Brad later all
right I gotta change you better grab a
head start
nice to meet you homie hmm whatever
having Trevor uh Franklin is still
available
let's go wow
Michael you look cool in that attire do
I have to fly even though Travis
uh yes okay
all right W and S okay eight five four
six
the bank
[Music]
to the old crew
what is the difference between a and d
and four and six
kids
anymore
[Music]
okay I think I can
somehow do it okay okay okay
in theory flying a hot air balloon is
more difficult
okay okay
and then we look for all the movies and
as I said there wasn't really anything
really interesting at least from what I
could tell
yeah so then we chose a relatively
random one was supposed to be like a got
it let me go forward
I don't quite understand how we go
forward
can I just go in curves only
[Music]
the day before yesterday
can I just
foreign
[Laughter]
I have gotten into cars and out of cars
of the FP so many times downtown how how
do I think that it would have any
different function when I'm in the
[\h__\h] helicopter but you know I was
really hoping for there to be in an
autopilot because this is [\h__\h]
oh God damn it okay
[\h__\h] hell
oh I don't have to do anything
exactly
not anymore
Lean Forward
um
but then it goes down too
oh [\h__\h] no oh [\h__\h]
oh s s no w w
sorry guys I'm not Landing here don't
worry if I do
W and eight
there you go Oh I thought it would go
down because like it tilts forward but
then then it settles down okay okay
ah now we're talking
and then we go up on the top of a
building
I'll drop
a focus on the drop point
oh no
What west side of the where is West and
meet on the side of Washington left left
from here or
shut the [\h__\h] up I swear to god let's
just go to the
yellow Dot
uh-huh
here
what what how how no
ah
the west side we need to be on yeah give
me a [\h__\h] moment
how about here and then
and then I press F or what I mean isn't
doesn't he need to get out what
they're like where here here and then uh
r no no
is this not what you want
[\h__\h] out
is it really F though we need to get
closer to the face of the Tower
just had to go to the exact point and
then it happens automatically
aggressive and what s to raffle Jump by
pressing
right button to descend faster hold left
right button after jumping for a longer
jump okay
okay how low are we going I wait it was
it was left but not right
[Applause]
[Music]
here we go I don't know what we're doing
here but I'm just doing as they tell me
oh this looks like a party
next she's so far up your ass your
tonsils will be playing Shadows
it's in our guidelines
you're talking about
because you totally wouldn't do that if
it wasn't in your guidelines right no no
no no no no no no no oh
you think you're impenetrable I mean
there's worse worst torture to be honest
Yakuza Style
18 inches deep inside with a loop I
don't really [\h__\h] the loop let's Dry
Dock him Smash Bro I want to watch this
though I want to see how far they go yes
already
okay
I should have done it earlier yeah
[Music]
okay
36 flow gotcha
what am I shooting
[Music]
what's happening
how's it going
how's it going please
oh yeah baby
swish
doesn't seem like
huh
but how do I that get us killed you know
that I'm gonna go up I'm gonna just
continue shooting
okay
I don't like this girl
bastard
Franklin
[\h__\h]
did I do that
oh my God
hey what the what the actual [\h__\h]
ers
what
no I switch again oh [\h__\h] they're so
fast how am I supposed
you'll be fine
got him
it's not one of them huh
do I have to fly again
oh no that's bad
um
[Music]
[Applause]
I got some friends with the barrel
they'll explain everything
smoothie
thank you hey I did it first try no
complaints guys no complaints if I be
they will make everything okay
the things those people did to me
I'm an American citizen I have a yeah
don't they do that in school there
don't be such a [\h__\h] nah for real
though yes
not nice
not nice at all
how exact do I have to land
it's good
plan
oh [\h__\h]
oh come on
[Music]
it doesn't
get
amazing
guys we're out of there
who are you people oh shut up all right
let me turn this down I wanna I'm gonna
tell you guys so so we chose a movie
that was actually like kind of about
um dancing with Dance in the title and
um
yeah like a girl who can't dance anymore
blah blah blah not really you know I
mean we just went for something that
would start relatively early
and yeah but then we arrived and we
arrived late
we came to the snow we're too late so
then we were like [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what did we do we were only like five
minutes late but still you know
so then
instead we looked at the what they had
in the menu and there was one movie that
had like really fancy
features to it like 4D and stuff
so I was like you know what if we go to
the cinema then we should watch
something with an experience that you
only get in the cinema
so we chose
there we go there we go
how is this how's this how's this
we chose a movie called Beast I think it
was just Beast
maybe it has like a subtitle or
something no no no no no no no but that
for the experience we'll have to talk
about that it was ridiculous
uh
we'll talk about that
you guys know it
yeah with the lion the lion the crazy
Lion and the new running
running yeah he's more of a protege yeah
well you're gonna teach him to be old
before his time it was quite spooky
actually yeah
Michael I look at this ah new city new
set of problems but the idiots ah they
stay the same yeah cause you're here yes
as long as you're here all right chair
I'll see you later you better believe it
buddy he's however rocking the
helicopter so confidently that's
actually
kind of funny but okay
all right we did that
was my mission passed
oh
where's where's my
Mission pass what the [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
I can't even asked for it though
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
all right we got it we got it that was
so fun
was that as a help no what oh
it was like a health kid okay
and next
uh question mark
do you go to the
only Trump no no
I'm hiding from the church
[Music]
I hate him no
no
he sucks
the FIB Townley why does it not surprise
me
huh wait wait there's so many questions
what are we gonna do uh
what does that even mean it's Escape
we'll go to T
oh Jimmy
ah Jimmy likes Trevor all Angry what
hey Uncle T it's drizzle Jimmy Dean to
the [\h__\h] ass so glad you are
back my dad has been acting like a
wackobiatch recently all angry and
chiseled call him the [\h__\h] down let's
hang out sometime I smoke a lot of weed
now and maybe you can take me drinking
or something
no I have to handle two of these
douchebags at once
it's gonna be the end of my sanity
okay
um
send a reply oh it must be an imposter
or something he's dead I saw pictures of
his funeral I know why don't you come
here and visit me in posture
was that a text no
now we're into time for visits
that's his response wow
okay anyway
is that radio that's running
around here we go
but no I want to turn it down when I
wanted to be quiet please be quiet
everybody so I can talk a little bit
so okay I
uh and me and rmt we went to the to the
cinema to watch
um
and a movie called beast in like 4D it
was something something for the blah
blah and I wasn't quite aware of like
what's gonna happen and we didn't we did
not even watch the trailer because we
were standing in front of the the ticket
counter and we're like well [\h__\h] we
missed the movie that we were gonna
watch what are we gonna watch now
um so I was like well I mean at least
that one looks Fancy with all the extra
attachments to it all the features and
then we were gonna buy it and the lady
at the counter tells us you know what 40
is I'm like
um and I not sure in this situation so
she tells us it's like oh well sometimes
you know there can be like there can be
wind blowing in your face so they can be
there can be a rain falling or or uh
snow fake snow falling and stuff like
that and your your seats will be shaking
light effects like flashing light
effects and [\h__\h] uh and I'm like what's
not she's like no well in this case no
because this one's um well
it plays in the desert so there won't be
any snow but still
um wait what I'm going towards the f I
don't want to go to the f I want to go
to the T
oh I should just go without the
helicopter what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm gonna try to go down what if I just
let go of the helicopter
in the middle of the street
is that a problem
oh
okay nice
can you just leave it there
is that acceptable
smooth Landing now my brow okay nice
hello
I'm just gonna run a little bit now
I I want to tell you guys a story
yeah so actually that's sounded really
exciting so we were like okay you know
what this is what you go to cinema to
now nowadays nowadays that you know you
get like so much program on Netflix and
Amazon and everywhere like people don't
go to the movies anymore that much I
assume you really only go for the
experience of
eating the popcorn if anything and those
like special 3D movies and [\h__\h]
so yeah I might as well watch a movie
that has that kind of stuff
but when I did not know is that I was
hmm
oh my oh yo his stamina is really low I
didn't know I was getting myself into a
action Freeland movie
uh because like we really didn't look it
up at all
so anyway we bought some popcorn I got
sweet popcorn rmt got some nachos with
cheese sauce
mm-hmm
and then uh we sat down and I've got
some photos I might upload it later on
my heart
how far are we
oh it's fine
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah the seats are
like uh like four seats in the in like
one set kind of what are you doing
and
like they're stuck together and those
four seats will always like move in a
set I guess
um now I got some good middle seats the
cinema was basically empty it was
literally just like
three four free free like groups of
people like me and rnt and then like a
daughter and her mother and then a
couple like just us three sets
really empty the whole Cinema was really
empty it's like what the [\h__\h] happened
like like 10 years ago Cinemas were so
like
always full of peoples kind of sad
actually
um
yeah
well listen you get a good seat well
that's nice
no I wouldn't say that uh the sea thing
happened I would say that's really just
because nobody goes to the cinema
anymore because you can watch like
everything at home
that's it right yes that's it right
but but the thing is um I've been with
that many women
and Deborah I mean we're getting married
so oh that's beautiful
but I'm scared that she's gonna leave me
whoa whoa now Mr raspberry jam
he died when I had a noble death
joy to a lonely man
this is the magazine I got a very big
penis some girls laugh when they
calculus
show me I don't want to
look yeah I'm sorry no
I see I see why I need to send search
tomorrow
why why are you mine ain't nothing
special but this boy gets the job done
all right
now Wade here says that I have yet to
see his pee pee yes look at me
put your Johnson away so Johnson Jesus
delay
is it safe now
that's all okay anything uh interesting
there for a man like me well I mean I I
don't rightly
rightly no wait what was this one I was
so I was so distracted by the fact I had
to censor it and I don't quite
understand the logic why he pulled it
out in the first place why did he do
that
to show that to give to give the other
guy confidence what
I'm in that kind of person Floyd I am in
that kind of person yeah oh that's so
sweet I guess let's
get Wade and that little
tormentored down there
to put these on
we are going encouragement
gentlemen I can't wait to America awaits
run we got an inside man I'm gonna send
you some information I need you on point
to help plan things
okay not this car again I'm going to
Park City then this shitty car break it
in
don't fall out
[Music]
again it's not my radio oh it's so funny
well tomorrow tomorrow
oh my God uh don't rightly know what we
got you're going to have to be more
exact in your question
uh the Texas accent
something to steal
a pencil in elementary school and I've
been regretting it ever since
look I hear doing really slightly so
just tell me what you want and let me
focus on the dialogue to assist you in
finding it here's the problem
I don't know what I want well like
pornography or a perfect turn I can't
quite describe it but I'll know it when
I see it you ain't aiding my
comprehension all right all right well
how's this
236 billion dollars worth of cargo came
through the Port of Los Santos last
number
inside track on what's coming through we
don't know what's in the containers they
certainly don't put price tags on them I
haven't noticed
Kelly talks when she's trying to do a
cardboard accent
anything's so funny it reminds me so
much of her something like I connect
that with Kelly
these uh Merryweather folks
Merryweather security maybe this should
be this
this seems easier to do for me than than
a British accent apparently even though
I thought I had it absolutely nailed and
covered but
so wait now now they both sound the same
to
meaging Outsource Shadow Wars in 20
countries Shadow rage Legends on U.S
soil that um
sounds like them so there's a private
militia in the port what are they
guarding this one freighter I guess now
that you mentioned it it ain't quite
right
can I get on board talk a bit more no
way they won't let you anywhere near it
they're kind of [\h__\h] about it
actually the other day my colleague
Ralph I don't give a [\h__\h] about Ralph we
gotta take a look is there anything else
out by the Navy Warehouse
they got boat s
I heard they was testing something they
were testing that as well
okay right now
[Music]
hello
that was perfect timing Bridges
they even
they even talk again
you're straight on the highway I feel so
satisfying
keep on going until he runs out of gas
the national office of security
enforcement monitor the whole area the
something goes off in Port City every
road around here gets shut down in no
way anybody could come in or out
[Music]
we'll do
so much
[Music]
satisfaction baby real quick that's what
I'm talking about ending the song right
when you park oh I got a slot on the
cleanup crew there is nothing that Wade
here ain't gonna do for a warm meal hope
you got a strong stomach son
go in there
get in there
follow Floyd are you Floyd
you're gonna take me to see this
freighter
here we got helicopter
a big full container
space this reminds me of the uh fights
they had in
was it a railgun
railgun and the the guy
oh man they were fighting in a place
like this you know what I'm talking
about
[Applause]
[Music]
anime I did watch
Violet evergarden today until like the
sixth episode I think if you're carrying
something maybe I'll have to saddle you
you're getting mine anime knowledge back
up guys
yeah
um
versus accelerator was really sick it
was really epic
but but these are marked military
government anything weird about that the
government stuff is hot freight pulls up
goes right we're looking for like an
expensive looking container right you
are beginning to arouse my
curiosity
over there two o'clock
uh-huh
you you we need two guys summer is my
favorite guy from the anime
get on it
you got some good characters in indexing
railgun what about me am I getting up to
up here okay
get in the Handler Handler
help
oh there we go yes I gotta pretend I'm a
dog worker if I want to stay
I'm in I'm in how about I run that prick
over in this thing
we don't get the containers they're
gonna check your card
not always sir
just around you they don't take any of
these this is Waits on his own he better
hold it together stick to the story
he'll be fine Boys on a waste clearance
crew he's never happened when he's not I
didn't notice [\h__\h]
I'm gonna lose my job
I don't think that that was there when I
took a look a second ago
anyway okay so we got into the the
cinema we sat down and we already
noticed that the the seats had like
um like on the seats they were like
there was like a little like a tube
looking thing in the end or the opening
of a little tube or something like that
a metal tube little a little tiny so I
already knew
um where to expect it from
um
and then
are these ones
containers
movie started but I think I don't know
if this movie was made
with this in mind it's chill a second
trying to get like a good angle
but the movie basically like starts with
um a scene where they're like in in the
in the desert and the hunting monster
you know a beast
and it's in the night and then they they
use their
rifle and they
that when they go
I mean I can't pick this up
what
I can't go lower than this
ah baby I'm picking it up on the top huh
okay never mind
basically for everyone
the whole Cinema was like lit up with
like a big Flash the whole Cinema you
know so flash flash flashlight flash and
then at the same time the seats would go
like like really bouncy too
so it was really intense like right for
the beginning and we were me me and RM
team we were like what the [\h__\h] is this
and we already got like a like a feeling
that this would be kind of weird
yeah you guys are saying sounds amazing
sounds awful
um you seem to have different opinions
so the thing is
I feel like it did just it wasn't used
quite well in this movie clamp it on now
that's it now we gotta bring it over to
Bay M okay
handlers because they handle like a
dream this ain't a toys because it's
heavy machinery it didn't even have a 3D
music
I would feel way more immersed and so
those are facts if it was 3D as well
Under the Influence if you're not
careful but it wasn't pretty I wonder
why they don't do it with 3D in
combination 4D with 3D
so yeah it was like a lot of it was kind
of awkward to be honest
and like you would you would think
that a lot of it would be maybe in first
person so that the effects that the fact
that you feel them too would make sense
you know what I mean
oh nicely please
[Laughter]
like that
tell me they're like super super soft
all the time with these things
all right sorry sorry I learned my
lesson
you're always nervous you're saying I
need some water not always sir
just around you yeah cousin Wades on his
own it's fragile we're gonna hold it
together stick to the stories he'll be
fine Boys on a waste clearance crew he's
never happened when he's neck deep and
[\h__\h] sorry sorry sorry
coming next time
okay where was I oh yeah so that was
kind of like the start introduction and
then you know story started I thought
the story itself was like nice overall
um but
I'm I'm not
such a thriller fan basically the whole
movie was like it felt like a horror
movie to me okay we got it let's take
her down to bayf
running from the Beast really
dramatically
I liked the story Parts but the the
Thriller part which was most of the
movie I did not like that much
unfortunately it was kind of like yeah
the the whole like story behind the
family was cute
okay is this low enough now I'll get the
other one for you okay beautiful
beautiful I'm gonna need a better view
of that freighter I'm sorry but this is
as close as you going to get no no no
but then take some pictures send them to
my guy hold on I'll need a proper view
it's a talk game perfect
shoot let me talk thank you
um where was I
oh yeah I thought that it was really
unfitting like some of the effects like
like you know there were some some
scenes where you were in a car they were
in a car you were looking at them from
first person look at this job being a
stupid or used to be back-breaking work
now you're paid brain surgeons such an
oversized shopping cart I did not
fellatiate no one to get this job shut
up shut up
darling Debbie probably did [\h__\h]
chatty probably enjoyed it
okay okay okay so like when they were in
a car you know the seats would move like
Rumble like in a car that was okay that
was interesting but like then I know you
would you would
um have like birds flying by and even
though normally like if it's easy like
right now I'm GTA you know I have a bird
flying by it's not like there's a
[\h__\h] tornado in your face but the
effect was basically a a really strong
in your face from the seat when a bird
would fly by like out of nowhere too
like really surprising and like so
uncomfortable too that rmt was like
covering those tubes with her hands at
some point because she didn't want to
get hit by that anymore it was really
obnoxious to be honest
is that not the exact uh position you
want so there
yeah that looks a lot of the effects are
really weird and like
um
a lot of them were unfitting too so
he's done I'm going up the game again
I'm done yeah
go to the crane can I walk or does it
have to be in this thing all right I'll
take this thing I'll take this thing
yeah there were no no water effects no
bubbles the bubbles were also apparently
a thing that happened sometimes and no
no snow and all that I feel like
this can definitely still be very much
improved this whole 40 oh yeah smell it
you can smell things but
there's no smell at all throughout the
whole movie that was disappointing but
I was saying to rmt like it might have
been disappointing but the only smell
that would have made sense is the smell
of dead bodies because there were a lot
of dead bodies and
yeah that's I don't know if I really
want to smell that
yeah about dead bodies besides that
nothing really to recreate I would say
why am I following him I need to go to
the other thing
hmm
this thing right this crane
I'm going up here
oh stamina yo his stamina is insanely
low
dear Lord
I'm not one to talk
yeah so I wanna try something like that
again because it was funny like we were
laughing
I'm waiting on a crane driver nearly an
hour we were laughing more about it than
we probably should have
even though it was a scary thriller
movie
I feel like we shouldn't have been
laughing the thing is
the thing is the 4D effects huh 4D
effects are making it funny
and it shouldn't have been funny but
like the the 4D effects were sometimes
so ridiculous
that we were just like giggling like
what the [\h__\h] was that
okay it's like kind of I guess ruining a
little bit but at the same time I'm
thinking like
if it wasn't for Dad why can I not do
the music
first you gotten up the cabin over the
container
the lights on the bottom of the spreader
I wanna mute the music
I can't change your radio
thingy oh
uh in in VR it would have been probably
better and if the whole movie wasn't
like first person that would have also
made sense
uh what
do I stack them
sorry
do I put these ones on top of the others
I'm in position
sorry guys I have to make it quiet
because of the dmca
it's like a mini game
uh huh
oh
I have grabbed on to it
move it down to the end okay
Bay five bay five okay oh [\h__\h]
or higher higher higher what
it doesn't go higher uh yeah we're
playing like Tetris kind of
ah
hey it doesn't go any more left than
that does that work
what the [\h__\h]
whoa
oh that's not right
oh no I I scrolled the wrong way never
mind
ah anyway yeah as I said at least it was
an an
experience I wouldn't have gotten if I
would have watched a movie at home
so in the end we said yeah that was I
guess worth it no but I want to
experience this
in a more fitting movie One Day
my frame of the track yeah yeah
easy easy easy
nice
oh is it lined up though
nice Coco Trucking
same thing again
hi
no dead body smell too much
yeah
oh
oh Avatar
it's out of the way
I saw an advertisement for Avatar Two
and it made me giggle because we had
this new thing before you know remember
do you remember when I was like oh I
[\h__\h] one of the blue people when you
guys were like no not that one
but I never even watched the first
Avatar movie but now the second one is
coming out so you know what that means I
need to watch the first one
so that I can watch the second one in
the in the theater sometime which maybe
maybe they have that in 4D as well and
maybe it will be water
they're blue people so there will be
water right
first one was Sensational oh
[Music]
really where's the truck
oh there it is
oh there it is there it is
is this a mission by the way
or just a mini game
okay
was that it
you get eye strain if you work any
longer have a break it looks gorgeous
stories man
I mean this is some view ain't it I'm
gonna take a couple shots for my boy
um
you want me to take pictures
what
vantage point at the end of the cat
we're taking pictures
criminals
no no wait ah wait that's just him
acting as if you know that's the reason
why he's doing that okay but in reality
we're doing it um to be criminal never
mind I get it now
this is good
uh I'm a guide on board of the ship okay
oh he's got a rifle
oh take a a long shot of the back of the
ship a long [\h__\h] on the back of the ship
a long shot what do you mean a long with
a long shot where's the back
where's the
oh that's the back
it's a long shot though
[Music]
um
zoom out
it's a front
I thought I was stupid
they have the whole thingy in the
control room or whatever there
what
kidding me
I guess I need to go boating a little
bit to understand boats ships somewhere
send them to Ron
nice okay
good job here's done
we sent the crane to the dogs floor
okay wait I used the crane again okay
okay no no
go in there
am I doing it
just leave oh
I thought I had to move the crane again
okay all right
all right
[Music]
since there's no conversation going on
let me continue to tell you a story
after the move
we went to like an arcade because we
were not really hungry we were both like
so full on the Natchez and the popcorn I
was munching on them for ages I actually
wanted to go to like dinner with her
afterwards but I know we were so full so
we went to the Arcadia but it's like a
lame arcade we don't have like round one
or so
take you over to the warehouse huh this
weekend being used where are you
I don't see you
hi are you in the car
in the truck okay
yeah I was like
like
um I mean
I guess they had like similar machines
to what round one for example would have
but like in Wood you can take a look at
it but no one's allowed around there but
like in in kind of bad quality
is running
and really old one like partially the
functional
that what a merciful
[Music]
on Halloween and how the [\h__\h] do I do
this
[Music]
no no no no no no no
how do I do this
wait do it
[Music]
it's fine because this will resets the
the whole thing for me
it's fine this is exactly what I wanted
nice
makes it easier to be honest
I'll just be careful now
hi
let's just
think we have a big butt it's on the
other side
David Garden one of them dry dogs no we
can take a look at it but no one's
allowed around there normal rules don't
apply to us Floyd I can't go like that
way around maybe that's easier
you're in a Loveless relationship what
do you mean
I have a bad feeling about this
you she'd be here wouldn't she but she's
not
um I'm insecure you've got a dead-end
job what dead end or no Floyd it's dead
end being a unionized longshoremen so
one of the best paying jobs in the
country you tell people around okay
that's what you do they liable to rob
you okay are we good everyone's jealous
of you Floyd
woman you're abused by these slave
drivers I mean I've never worked so hard
in my life oh they aren't so bad I've
been doing this every day for 10 years
the criminality I don't know how careful
I need to be it like broke off so early
before we turned up when we didn't
saving you from yourself
we ain't heard from Wade but he was
Mother he's fine no spillage shouldn't
take this long to contain
there must be a lot of it
keep him busy while we get to work
yeah we're truck simulator
yeah finally I'm playing that too
welcome to Europe I guess
La truck simulator
ah yeah anyway you know we played
um like for example there was
um two two Nintendo machines one of them
was Luigi's Mansion
with you know the sucker vacuums
so I was like
empty I wanna do this one I want to play
this one
so we got in we activated it but then
um
team was really bad at it
she had no idea what she was doing I I
at least had like a rough idea because I
played really just mentioned on the
GameCube back in the day
so then we didn't get really far because
it was actually surprisingly difficult
it's pretty challenging
didn't really get very far and then if
you want to continue playing you need to
put in more coins and we didn't have so
many
um
it was fun anyway uh and I got to see
some Luigi
and some ghosts I like that game
and then and then the next one we did
was some some air hockey
and first I was doing pretty well
but then suddenly rmt got really [\h__\h]
good at the game
and absolutely destroyed me so she won
that one oh
[\h__\h] up
go back
go back I swear to God
okay
I should play let me just mentioned oh
maybe I can play it on my German Channel
oh maybe we can play it on my German
Channel
hmm I wouldn't mind playing Luigi's
Mansion
mention do we just humans
please don't make me feel the mission
guys tell me how to there we go okay
and eventually it's gonna connect I
don't want to fail a mission I'm like at
the finished finishing point
it really is really age I don't believe
it I don't believe it you're like
bullshitting me again aren't you
no
you're bullshitting me
it doesn't work H doesn't do [\h__\h]
no please don't let
come on why doesn't ah I'm in like the
worst position
huh well just because I see I popped
against that dude that was the problem I
think I was trying to be careful like I
was in a shitty ass position
no
okay that really [\h__\h] sucks
I was being really careful yeah
[Music]
damn it
no I was trying to not turn it too much
they've been guarding one of them dry
dogs we can take a look at it but no
one's allowed around there normal rules
okay one more time we're going in I
don't know the rules applied to me my
whole life I like rules and look at you
you're a failure you're in a Loveless
relationship okay what do you mean
Loveless I love Deborah hello Deborah
you should be here wouldn't she she's
not
oh I'm insecure
[Music]
dead end no Floyd it's dead end that's
so depressing he's depressing him be
nice to him Trevor look around La Puerta
that's what you do they liable to rob
you they're so jealous no one's jealous
of you Floyd they pity you you're abused
by that woman you're abused by these
slave drivers I mean I've never worked
so hard in my life it ain't so bad I've
been doing this every day for 10 years
only usually with less of the
criminality you're wasting your life
Floyd it's lucky we turned up when we
did I'm saving you from yourself sure
you are from Wade you're such an angel
Trevor everybody thanks to you so much
gratitude for you there must be a lot of
it good good keep him busy while we get
to work
anyway don't
oh yeah and then after air hockey and
which got really intense
but not as intense as the one that I saw
you know Cali playing
against I think Ahmed was it Kelly was
so serious
uh last one we played was like another
Nintendo machine
this one was like from the Olympics the
2016 Olympics
I don't want to [\h__\h] this up again
come on don't don't [\h__\h] with me now
okay
I think we're fine
yeah and then then we got to do like
yeah
three different things one was like um
jumping can't come through here
and running and jumping Run and Jump
I mean we did a bunch of dozens it was
fun and that in those ones I won by a
landslide but only really because
I am teasing jumping mechanism was kind
of broken
it didn't recognize her jumps at all
um
[Music]
[Applause]
you should have switched roles so mean
should have been Trevor
but okay nice nice distraction
can I should I just run
I'm Gonna Leave unnoticed
you have to be stealthy here
what if he sees me
oh he doesn't care
with the bag in my hand all right okay
okay uh
okay so far
easy yeah thank you
well thank you for listening to do you
um the tick tock will be uploaded
shortly I hope
shh be quiet
[Music]
Trevor these photos you've really
stumbled onto something the ship
Merryweather yeah yeah I know tell me
about the ship if we put a man with a
gun on the bridge next to it and get a
guy on board I think we got a good
chance of taking over the way it looks
to me there's a container below deck
regarding it for the government keeping
all the books serious military
technology most like
of course I just found a manifest
they're testing something out at Sea
it's got to be that now get back to work
the TPI conglomerate ain't thriving
there's only one man responsible of
course yeah but I'll start pulling all
the Intel I can get on Meriwether at the
same time I got a file here somewhere yo
this car can drift
damn all right okay can I finally turn
this [\h__\h] off no thank you
okay
couldn't change it during the dialogue I
tried pressing Q
it's okay
fine it'll be fun
yeah anyway I wanted to upload the
shorts that I uploaded on YouTube on
Tick Tock but I'm just waiting for
um the company to do it I don't know
maybe they already did it at this point
I hope they do it soon because I want to
get the challenge go
I want to get the challenge going I want
some random people to dance do you let's
hope that someone will take on on the
challenge but I might
purposefully because this wasn't really
my original intention of the dance I
should have thought of this earlier
um although I I like me some complicated
dances but in order to get like a tick
tock challenge really successful I think
it has to be a a variety of simple
but still cute dance
um so if I ever do a 3D music video
again like that
oh even an animated one with just a
chorus animated or so
and
um I might want to really like have dads
in the back of my mind to have a dance
that could like really work well on tick
tock
like this time it wasn't the intention
but we're gonna try it anyway
and then next time I'm gonna
put some more thought into it you know
I hope for my job music videos
I'll try to
try because uh it's such a joy to look
at this one
[Music]
um although now as I said before I feel
a little bit pressured to always put out
stuff and that quality
and 3D and all that I I will not be able
to do that always but anyway
um I'll do my best
um
and will be hard to beat this Envy
indeed but I already have like more
ideas for more k-pop-esque music videos
like what they like to do often in music
videos also is like sit on top of
actually I guess it's like rap music
video sit on top of like really sick
rides cars you know
uh and and sing on top of those stuff
like that I want to see in my next music
video
oh yeah sit on top of a Wrecking Ball
but that might be too much of a
reference to a certain famous music
video
naked Wawa on a wrecking ball hmm
totally original idea
I mean no one said naked I just added
that because you know
it's supposed to be
foreign
she came in like a wrecking ball
yeah Oh wrong turn
we have arrived
Twitter
[Music]
foreign
I got the important stuff with me with
some
wow
[Music]
name of all things holy oh what is it
what's what's going on I I tried to stop
it stop what what it just can't
[Music]
how would that get on your face
hey what is that what no what why would
you even give him a hug
this will do
get a [\h__\h] shower
even five no she ain't even fine no one
understands why Floyd lets her use him
so oh
that's a low selfish empathetic
now
oh you're writing your plan on the wall
wow oh no all right so based on my
observations I'd say these Merryweather
security [\h__\h] snots are sitting on
something real valuable I think they got
two of these things but we only need one
first one it's on that freighter in a
container below deck they got guards all
over that ship soon baby they're keeping
it on ice indeed the air land and sea
routes into the port will be locked down
as soon as we make a noise at these X's
here which means we have to blow up the
ship and grab the thing
mom's a guy to look out from with a
rifle and a guy to grab the thing
whatever it is underwater that means
stealing a submarine of course but you
can find us one of them huh now the
other one is off the coast being tested
they're running the operation from the
dock where I last saw your cousin we'll
need a submarine for that too and
probably a chopper a big one we go out
there okay easy water locate it bring it
back here and find out what it is here
to Chicago
all right so what do you think container
ship or whatever's offshore
what do you think guys
uh
hey if you hate helicopter I do hate and
helicopter
yeah it's got to be the container right
although are we missing out on the
submarine then
you and Floyd can help and we'll bring
along Michael and his unpaid intern
okay all right what is that smell oh no
okay are going straight to the local
union rep wash your [\h__\h] your face at
least the performance of his duties
human waste has seeped into his very
pores and I am sorry to say this but I
don't think he's ever going to spell
normal let's go to the union yeah
probably not you know all right and you
vouched for us all right you look at him
man smell him the smell
Trevor Trevor you you're planning to
robbery on my place of work
you violated Mr raspberry jam and God
Alone knows what else
damn Supra oh Deborah my lady in my
union
that's all I got
so why don't we just uh why don't we
just let this all slide huh
if you're comfortable
with what's happened to your cousin
then so be it all right but I would give
him a bath and rinse him off no
he's these people are such [\h__\h]
weirdos man
ah couldn't be me
I relate more to Michael
cookie cannot
be that stinky no [\h__\h] way man
Chester let's go
okay I didn't get jump scared baby
I did get jump scared a few times during
the movie though
Michael Michael my angel Trevor hey
Mikey Hey listen get here in LS really
settling in getting my first enema
tomorrow
I heard about some action yeah huh yeah
okay oh you bet it's okay listen I gotta
do a little prep work but so far it's
looking pretty tasty I'll need you to
bring along that kid you've been hanging
with Franklin
all right we'll have Michael and
Franklin with us okay that makes it a
lot better
a lot easier to handle thank God
I can't take this car I like this one
it's actually pretty smooth
and then we go to f
do we go to f
okay we go to question mark question
mark
Trevor Franken okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh oh no number
who the [\h__\h] is this the guy keeping
keeping eyes to face Warehouse off Dutch
London and banning oh we can do more
than talk my friend
eh
they want me to go to Michael
what
quarter time
educio that's another new mission
why did they alarm me about Michael now
though
quit that [\h__\h] man yeah I know I take
speed mostly and look at me best [\h__\h]
for my life yeah
don't don't guys don't that's because
you're [\h__\h] please don't not because
you're in good shape straight edge
[\h__\h] crunches and feeling bad about
yourself all right pork chop
py [\h__\h] you you know I'm beginning to
think that's exactly what you want to do
Jesus
Jesus I just said the same [\h__\h] thing
to my wife
t-shirt man
you you back there I know you but you
you I don't got bad shoulder just like
me I see a reason otherwise why don't we
just keep it that way Steve what a
pleasure bro oh
brace yourself well no one of those guys
you see advertising the mission is
intense I can't get erections yeah
in Weston
very good friend of mine connected watch
your tongue because let me tell you
something that guy gets more tail than
uh
what does that mean
I [\h__\h] remember that line
you
where did we meet
nowhere pal yeah we did oh hey oh what
are we doing here huh this is
away from me no no Ferdinand he's gone
he's gone it's okay I've got some new
friends here now
Michael
and this
this is prep no no no I'm here
claims he doesn't know I don't I don't
know what what are we think he knows oh
nothing nothing I don't know and
anything
no I don't want to torture
azerbaijanis I do audio visual Hi-Fi
audio visual it's top man good price VIP
you know dude you're a [\h__\h] spy
really and the ass wipes at the agency
know this
is
[Music]
worse
I told him what'd I tell you uh-huh
it's so intimidating hey what is this
doesn't hurt you're sure
the man who owns it he works at the
consulate oh that's all I know that's it
that's it that's it
[Music]
[\h__\h] is all this huh I think it's a good
time buddy you know go for a drive wait
ing you get to work and uh I'm not here
oh oh it's Caesars around the corner
from your house
make sure we switch to Trevor
foreign
ER
hey
see this is
this sucks
he thinks it's okay to do that Michael
wouldn't do that Michael leaves Michael
goes somewhere else
but Michael you should have stopped it
just it's too bad
he knows nothing lost the more I like
him he's from snow won't be so critical
of who others associated with
so is it going to be a problem for sure
but there's nothing we can do about it
if something happened to him right now
I'd be right under a microscope an
electron microscope of bureaucratic [\h__\h]
and that would make it very difficult to
keep old secrets
you know who else is having trouble
keeping secrets [\h__\h]
oh
me after you brought Trevor in on this I
only brought him in after you put out
your press release townley's taking
stores again the Los Santos reboot if we
didn't control the situation and heat
Unearthed disconnection then what then
Trevor flips out beheads me kills my
family or raises him as his own I don't
know which is worse anyway no more car
accidents anyway any of that could
happen at any time
let's think this through
I'm listening guys he knows I'm alive he
knows I got money and now he knows I'm
working with the FIB wait that was the
FIB you've been working are those two
different things how long wait no it was
never FBI either you were in line with
us before the cash Depot job you walked
your crew into an ambush one of them
spent 10 years on the run and the other
landed in a federal penitentiary or or
we stumbled on the cash Depot job Brad
went down you went down Trevor got away
the FIB country with you on your sick
that faked death and you
sorry sorry continue
who's to say which of those is true that
there's any doubt probably accounts for
you being alive back there Trevor made
you right away the second he saw you
sorry I was focusing on the subtitles
after the bust I was in all the papers I
was on the Evening News the man who
killed Michael Thompson yeah I was quite
a trophy a good head to hang on your
wall back then sure
not now
okay okay now I can focus on driving
and my drawing was still fine shut up
unless someone in order to get this
story to somehow enter my head I need to
read but even then it's uh
breath
pretty difficult
I have a very small understanding of
what's going on
a really rough
and insecure understanding
it's good enough
no reading and driving they're literally
asking me to do it
[Music]
as you may have noticed I don't have
that many songs on my playlist but I
feel like they're good for good songs
and you know I need I need to put songs
in that are
within my rights
I'm tired of the same song
oh this place
is surreal concert Suburbia here the
last week
[Music]
I'll call Steve
I need a eurobeat remix apart Challenger
you have the right to remain Bop
to make sure we're silencing someone
we're silencing the right somewhere
get me another address
okay he wants to do it right
coffee
wrong
we need a new address from Mr K choose
oh no and go to work on him
wait
what are you talking about the wrong guy
no who do you want
tell me what you want no oh man ah
please look at me please
this is an important part of the Great
Democratic experiment
are we pulling nails like toenails
there's German on that one feels
familiar let's go with that please
I'm gonna burn him
please don't oh teeth oh no
it's
no I don't wanna it is torture
a flip chair
no
[Music]
oh it's water and it's fine
that's fine but we're gonna burn him
hydration baby
I am there's someone some water some
water do you guys want some water I'll
drink some water come back
[Music]
sorry should I let you talk that's mine
have something to say
no
but how long are you gonna make me wait
let up okay help me pick this up
poor guy though to be honest like I have
no idea how that feels like but
apparently it's really terrible
oh God Mr Phillips ask him about Tay
here Javan why didn't you ask me I know
it's out here but but I think it's a
nicer way of torture than pulling
someone a tea for or cutting off some
fingers or so I don't know man it seems
like the most gentle cause there's no
aftermath I would say at least
oh no permanent damage
um
oh Peter he lives in chuma right isn't
it I mean he always is so gentle but you
know what I mean
did you get that you hear him
lives in Chumash
the Western Highway
this is the worst
you're driving
remember of course I'm driving of course
taking the cups with us but okay
oh yeah there is no good choice
anyway
so give me a [\h__\h] break
I didn't want to do it
guys probably if you play this game
you're just like whatever it's just a
game and then you do it there's Steve
and Trevor getting along my heart broken
there okay now like I said he's got his
useless and as you can see we're trying
to take full advantage of him then what
the agency
can rest and we don't need you anymore
right and what about Trevor what about
it I need some resolution Davey you let
him walk you said you'd clean the whole
thing up back in North Yankton and you
told me it'd be a clean job no
casualties there were more eyes on that
town than there needed to be
Trevor's your problem Dave as much as he
is mine he's not a problem at all we're
monitoring
has he said anything about Brad [\h__\h]
yeah he has plenty I keep changing the
subject you know he thinks you might
actually commute Brad's sentence when
this is all over that's good fine work
we'll send another letter it's about
time anyway oh so that's you who's been
sending those [\h__\h] letters to Trevor
huh yeah he thinks they're from Brad who
he thinks is locked up in high security
and not well not six feet under in a
grave Mark Michael Townley the trainee
is right and it's a good exercise
[\h__\h]
how'd that get started a few years ago A
letter came to the federal prison system
addressed to brat wasn't signed but he
gave a PO Box in Sandy Shores I played
the part of Brad and we started a
correspondent yeah thanks for telling me
Davey I was doing you a favor didn't
think you want to know he was in the
same state yeah so now what I just sit
back and hope he doesn't figure it out
it's worked so far he's a time bomb Dave
and you
[\h__\h] know it
already there wow that was well timed
world times okay
hmm
he funny no
all right I would like I project these
people into my real life and I'm like
when I like this person in real life and
I'm like hell no I'll take care of it so
I hate him up oh no no please
no please
what does that mean loosen him up oh
I could do the water again I said loose
right at least I feel like there's also
no no permanent damage
oh unless death okay well but we'll try
not to kill you
I'll try not to kill you
[Music]
nipples
at least
samples
[Music]
am I doing this right it saves bikes
excited fire today
what
[Music]
he's done I'm so sorry are you supposed
to like burn down okay okay
oh my God now huh now you ready to talk
I've never seen that before
no back in my day and they used to use
stretching oh yeah this guy working you
know in medieval times back into tutor
times
sounds like you're stalling this better
be enough middle age middle Height
Middle Field whatever he's dark okay
azerbaijani for God's sakes look around
that enough for you
hey I'm here find it find find the
target
what do you mean find a Target
is that him you see anyone down there
who might be in azerbaijani [\h__\h] do I
know you might be in as a vagina for all
I know what's one look like they look
Eastern I had this town looks Eastern
Davey you got to follow the shot and the
collapse of Communism to thank for that
anyone stand out no they all kind of
blend in make a call Dave
we're gonna need some more info on this
guy they're having a party down there
you go switch
what if I just shoot
when do I need to switch now
I need more Intel okay let me let me I
don't
know what he's doing today I don't want
to hurt you no you remember okay
members why don't we have to torture him
more give him his prize
give me Miss Brown
Yeah I want to I am a reasonable man you
want a new one or I mean I could still
do the same thing I I remember is this
what is this though just let me speak
very painful I
don't know
even the biggest tool in the room what
oh that's so heavy
much
[Music]
like me
oh wait was it Oh I thought we were
going for his knees we went for his
balls oh [\h__\h]
you tried to shake up he took it quite
well though
oh my God
[Music]
looking at the right person
squishy beard got any beauty types at
this party huh yeah he's giving us
no you know I'm thinking maybe we uh
just take two bullets
[Music]
who am I looking for Steve's saying
beard what do you got anything specific
or is shoot him stop talking what is
wrong with you yeah
listen anyone in that Point's got as
much chance of being a [\h__\h] National
Security is the next guy Steve it's
blocked I was obviously hit it
bye
that was obviously him don't be like
that
wow
land of beach hipsters we need more do I
need to trap no
no no
one day until you give us some Intel
really why not YouTube she's got beer do
this again he smokes this looks like a
[\h__\h] chimney I don't know oh wait no
it's um it seems like a continuation
he smokes that's all I know
are you waiting to see it's going to be
the same P the same person after all
[Music]
it's gonna be the same person after all
I feel like that dude was smoking Blazer
maybe not I feel like he was smoking
[Music]
no no no no I'm sorry
or take long
am I doing it I'm not looking
[Music]
ah
they're all I'm [\h__\h] hate them
this game was like jokes and memes on
funny and haha what happened
what happened hasn't this man done
enough for National Security
wait he's like dead
all right
can we give him like um
that thing
to make him oh he [\h__\h] died
no
no adrenaline yeah yeah I saw that in a
movie
starting in Cleo
okay learned something there
that's okay
[Music]
that's such an important information
as Mr K says if he smokes like a pack of
two a day
I feel like that dude wasn't there
before they just brought him out now
you're telling me to assassinate a guy
because he's got facial hair a cigarette
and he's left-handed um yes I see
someone he fits the profile and he
definitely does yep fits it all the way
I got a good feeling about as good as
you can get while clipping a guy who
probably don't deserve it I'll wait for
the dialogue okay
well guys I've always been telling you
smoking kills you baby I got someone
definitely a lefty Redwood smoking
bearded Maybe
could be Follow My Lead guys become
straight edge forever Steve it's done
[Music]
my friends excellent work the pair of
you it literally killed him so Trevor if
you take care of Mr K I think we're all
set what the [\h__\h] do you want me to do
with him I would say he's outlived his
usefulness
[Music]
that's a sport just let him kill him go
thank you oh so sweet thank you so much
for letting him go
come on
let's just go okay I'm looking at those
G-Man [\h__\h] scumbags
you just tortured me don't ask too many
yeah
come on up the [\h__\h] stairs
balls no
no
[Music]
to catch
okay
save me fast
I hate travel
hey how's your mouth it hurts
are you gonna hold it together I don't
want you to go home I want you to get my
family no no no no you have no home you
have no family that [\h__\h] is over
[Music]
during the Hollywood I love him very
much oh you shouldn't have told him it's
your old life that's over now you're off
the grid you're one of the invisible
people just take me home I am taking you
to the airport you're gonna get on a
plane you're flying a long way from this
country and you're gonna spread your
message I don't have a message you're a
torture Advocate Advocate the media and
the government would have us believe
that torture is some necessary thing we
needed to get information to assert
ourselves did we get any information out
of you I would have told you
exactly tortures or the torturer or the
guy giving the order to the torture you
torture for the good times we should all
admit that it's useless as a means of
getting information
I [\h__\h] strike this is unbelievable
this is [\h__\h] unbelievable
foreign
[Music]
I thought we really bonded but now I'm
having my doubts
[Music]
all the same if you're not playing a
game I'm so [\h__\h] pissed off no I
can't find the feelings and I won't hide
them
Trevor's so excited him maybe you decide
do we want to model the game or not [\h__\h]
him
[Music]
the same one complaining
he'll never be the same cause he's
missing balls of teeth his nipples are
not doing well either
[Music]
like a problem I can solve it I really
can't it's already a problem no one
drives me to the airport
coming too deep and I love the rush oh
no
I had a wrap time of this Mission thank
God they're not the only person here
with compassion you're free and then
caffeine but my family your family is
probably the ones who got you [\h__\h] in
here all right
and look trust no one all right
all right you're alone now I mean yeah
really now let's go [\h__\h] off
come on good good you guys are trying to
make me think better of Trevor but this
does not change a thing
oh my God I'll put that oh
[Music]
so there
can I take a look like okay I'm so
worried about him
yo you here man
are you not here
and no one's like how he's not getting
on the plane obviously he's trying to go
back to his
family right well I I wish him all the
best like damn
[Music]
what
I seen a sub Trevor down at the docks on
a ship called Daisy Lee you could like
Snap the Rope somehow and maybe they
use some switch to drop it Wade
sandwich
what what how many days this is old
hahaha
he disobeyed yeah well
cool wow makes him such a hero wow wow
we're gonna forget about the fact that
he did all the torturing huh
I'm totally gonna forget about that you
guys [\h__\h] kidding me
crony like this
so um
where next h s or F or question mark
emoshi now you back
gosh let's switch to Franklin
okay sorry I'm like still
not understanding if
like these things are orange and I'm
playing as
who I'm playing right now
then the orange ones are for me right
and then the green ones are for Franklin
I think
okay because like in the beginning I
thought if it says F then Franklin needs
to go there but that wasn't right so
it's it's it uh according to the color
right okay okay let's go to the app
all right and then I finally feel like I
understand it
okay
both true
it's frozen okay yeah I thought so much
like also how L involved Lester or Lamar
okay
alrighty
let's forget about
what we just had to endure and look at
and try to cheer up
foreign
instrumental of myth and treat is
bopping
[Music]
down
is this mine
wait why are they shooting me were they
shooting me
but they have green cars not because
they're all tasty and got style but
because the gang gang area right
okay
now I went wrong house
oh
chit chop
what are you doing here I say
let's say right I say become a doctor
you say become a patient I say
who is that hello Missy wow Franklin
told me that you had a sister
Franklin's house me damn Charming
shut up shut the [\h__\h] up
here darling why don't you go get
yourself something nice okay oh my
God Seven dollars unbelievable nice not
expensive
wow here comes the [\h__\h]
here comes the disrespectful [\h__\h]
with the boy the boys what [\h__\h] new
in town I'm making friends all right now
let's party look I had plans on getting
some rest until this clown and my aunt
came and [\h__\h] that up my [\h__\h] I just
came over here to holler at you about
the little thing man I said I'm tired
dog what [\h__\h] thing I love things I'm
the king of things I ain't talking to
you homie hey let's go do something
about the thing okay what thing you're a
sicko if you love Trevor [\h__\h]
beautiful perfect it's a gang bang let's
go come on
why do they humor him
from the van
get in the van
look out of it where's this thing
happening down Grove Street
all right let's go let's go
spraying some [\h__\h] I can drive
by with the best of them behave yourself
man Lamar what's happening what's your
stress set up we buying weight homie
something that'll move us up the food
chain [\h__\h] for real nothing's real in
this town [\h__\h] particularly where you
in stress concerned man this is an
investment opportunity you got to
speculate to accumulate first rule of
business hey since we're out here
banging whether you got some dust fool
want to get butt naked I'll get whatever
it takes me home boy homie she's crazy
man so I've heard
hey look everybody be cool man Lamar
about to do his thing all right
okay
um
[Music]
what is this game
what is this game I feel like
I have so I've come so
um
and acquainted
accustomed to the way
people talk and dialogue Works in like
RPG games you know like Fantasy games
stuff like that
um
that modern modern
dialogue is not
I I don't I what
service
package to collect
you got the grip
president accounted for
like that openscoat shows
shows his bikes February Knights all of
that now exactly what I need to give it
to me
you got the good [\h__\h]
not that
my throat getting numb already so we
good [\h__\h] right well let's go how about
a taste no man
you heard what your boy said you're
leaving hey
[\h__\h]
[Music]
are you did we ask for a key or a
[\h__\h] ounce man this [\h__\h]
drywall we got some [\h__\h] boss
remorse out here
[\h__\h] hustler hustler
ah
we gotta get off road
okay we're doing this again
what's up bro okay with the car on no no
we're not taking the car we would make a
lot of things easier I think
this is too easy
not even trying to hide
and not even trying to get me
I'm nice of them well
open
foreign
[Music]
that's very nice
oh this is so small I've yet to take any
damage
so nice
this is so nice
[Music]
so smooth
okay okay oh
okay okay okay okay okay okay
do we want to try to go like oh [\h__\h] oh
no
where are they
do I need to be worried about Trevor can
he like die oh nice nice nice shot
yeah okay I'm coming
hey we out of here
oh
take me
okay
that one is hard to get
wait there's a what three size
get the car
[Music]
[\h__\h] you oh God okay
oh wait uh what's my what's my thingy
again what's my specialty
oh [\h__\h]
I went I was to write because I thought
they would
guys like [\h__\h]
oh come on
surfing them papers as if I was a lawyer
I'm serving them death
you'll get one and you'll get one
nice nice all right what the [\h__\h]
I mean this is good practice for me
though like it's nice that we have to do
it again I have to practice
okay more who's the creepy one well
that's Trevor for y'all
oh baby a triple oh baby so many triples
baby
[Music]
food
all right
are they still think I'm going back up
and now he's dead
but what do I do when the police come to
try to fight the police
because they didn't get into the car
even though I thought that was the best
option
okay
[Music]
oh wait
unfortunately I'm calling them friends
now oh wait that's my my bunny
um
oh I saw you there I saw I saw you very
well I have good eyes
even when it's really [\h__\h] tiny I'm
playing on Window mode small window
[Music]
get
nah nah I'm just saying this now because
we need to be a team but besides that
[\h__\h] Trevor
oh here they go here they come
police is coming oh sheesh
oh [\h__\h] it says Paula Lamar
[Music]
okay oh we're running we're running
we're running travel time or die that's
fine with me too you're welcome to just
die
[Applause]
at all hold up hold up
what's going on what's going on that's
our way up out of here
we take these
what now
Travis taking the lady
ah wait did I have the choice to get on
that one I feel like it was perfect dad
the Trevor took that was of course he
took that one yeah
can I change the radio no
oh I need to switch to uh Franklin uh
Trevor
oh oh he got rid of her oh no
is this even radio
[Music]
[Applause]
that was Little Brush with another
celebrity they flocked too
oh let's not sabotage each other
all over the city
what's with this AI huh
let's split my [\h__\h] and keep our hands
there split okay lose them okay bye-bye
guys
why do I have to be traveled to a lot of
old people oh you're too close
you're going there then I guess I'm
going somewhere else
so I have to stay on the boat
put them in the big wide ocean unless I
get like on top of these things
I can't
I'll speed them okay
but there's nowhere to hide it was like
in the ocean unless I dive
can I just go and land
a shark
this is thank God I did not start diving
like someone in the chat said because
that shark would have killed me
yeah I'll try to land somewhere
oh but it seems like I am losing them
oh yeah because they're all over there
and I'm going somewhere else now
[Music]
get out of the field of sight
that's correct right
[Music]
it's rather easy
and what now what now
first of all
get I would be so scared to fall off of
this me and rmt we're using one of these
when we were in Greece I was on the back
she was in the front and she was like uh
jumping so much over these big waves and
I was like wait
[Music]
that was so so slippery everything was
so slippery
and I had like nothing good to hold on
to besides rmt who you know was bouncy
too so I hated it I liked it but I would
have liked it to be a bit more smoother
even though I know that's like kind of
the fun part of of this kind of boat
fun part is to
you know get bouncy bounce bounce bounce
obviously but I didn't enjoy that part
okay
um
that car looks broken
let's go to
what does HS stand for
Heist
I guess that makes a lot of sense
but let's do the heist see how far we
were doing a heist
I thought we were doing a heist
fire please
oh there's one
hi can I borrow your car it would be so
nice
actually a cool car but is that like
like that color
oh it's the same color as you
Lord your suit oh this music is nice but
I have to switch
alrighty
nice car nice car
Wyatt Brown yeah that's
no
good color for a car I'm sorry
I'm sorry
nah I like light brown and dark brown in
cloves
like especially for Autumn which we are
I think in Autumn now I think summer is
officially over
so I have to get all my cold weather
close
out of the uh
of the basement again
I just recently put it all down there
and suddenly I need it all again
huh
so hot here really damn I almost Envy
you even though while it was hot here I
was like [\h__\h] summer please end it and
now I'm like wait that was way too fast
can we go back like one month please
I need to get like jackets and [\h__\h] I
have no jacket right now no proper
jacket retrieve the sub
are we talking about a submarine is that
it the dead yellow thing oh cool
what's up they say how
how do you expect me to do that
they say that as if it was so easy do I
just walk up there and take it
cables oh
I should have come here with like a
speedboat
does that really work
what's it
works oh oh no my submarine ah stop
shaking stop shaking that's not checking
nice
okay it's in the water am I supposed to
swim there
I hope there's no sharks nearby
oh I'm really bad at swimming wait uh
so I go back up
go up go up you [\h__\h] idiot
how do you go up guys before I drown
please tell me how to go up
[Music]
shift
oh okay
well at least I'm up
okay okay okay okay
we're fine
Marine
we are living in the yellow climb onto
yourself okay
okay yeah let's start Marine Yellow
Submarine Yellow Submarine oh
I didn't know
this game I know they were helicopters
and [\h__\h] but this oh my God
wait oopsie
submarine we talked about it is
[Music]
work
as things work
hey we're not hurting anyone not yet I
mean no so far we've heard a lot of
people though
do some research on Merryweather
security Consulting friend they'd be on
trial for human rights offenses of the
U.S government didn't protect all its
contractors from any kind of Suits
or civilian they're immune
immune Behavior
murder
murder dealing high on for guns and
anabolics there
Lucky Bastards
oh
Man look
oh [\h__\h]
I won't be able to go through there I
was just following them
the dots but
I don't think I'll be able to go through
it do I have to go around no [\h__\h] way
unless I go through here maybe and then
there
[Music]
it's more like it
that's nice isn't it
wolfish oh
I wonder is it like really expensive to
like
like get into submarine like are there
any like offers like that I wonder
I never heard of anything like oh you
can try
try and get another Super rain for one
hour uh 500 bucks it's cheap really
they're not expensive really depends on
location
it's insane like I've never heard of
anything like that anywhere before
submarine would be sick in the Maldives
though but I wonder if that disrupt
still the fish
do they just see you as another fish
be for motion sickness
huh
there we go oh
it does not give me motion sickness
I am actually
pretty immune to that it seems
sad to enlarge meaning
oh ah never mind though wait am I
okay I'm so far very far
imagine that in VR yeah speaking of VR
like when we were setting up the last VR
collab together
I was looking up something uh like I was
looking up how to do like expressions
with my VR because like somehow it
didn't work with I didn't figure it out
I'm like well
it's been a while and then I found
something interesting
oh apparently
apparently the VR that I have so I think
mine's a five
it there's
oh my God that's what
I thought it sounds like me sometimes
oh my God I thought it was me
cute because
[Music]
I can totally make an M dolphin if
that's what they sound like
also sounds a little bit like my kid to
cut those
anyway
are they really dolphins
like around the harbor of LA
is that realistic
anyway I found something for my VR uh
there's like um
like uh like actually a decent facial
tracking for VR apparently for Vive
it only however tracks your mouth it
seems but it's oh
it was not 52 blend shapes but something
like 32 or so
and I looked at the video and
it looked pretty good yeah I'm gonna try
it maybe because the the mouth
movement looks so so nice and if I want
to do more VR stuff that might actually
be worth investing in
they want to play
wait is this is that orcas
what
bam that's sick
[\h__\h] I'm going inside there
cool
there one there's not like pretty rare I
I don't really know much about
sea animals
you know is that realistic oh [\h__\h] okay
I have to go around I thought I could
maybe go underneath that but well this
is such a pain in the ass
[\h__\h]
I mean it's fun though it's cool
it takes a while
there's not even an interesting phone
conversation going on
I guess is there no reception on the
water
what would there be no reception on the
is that a stupid question
I mean sometimes you have reception on
on the mountain if you don't go up too
high
f for five so now now now
I'm not gonna press f for faster
nope
I I would think so too that it absorbs
the signals but I didn't I'm not sure
like how
maybe if you're just right above the
surface it would still work but maybe
also this whole building blocks it this
building of a submarine
what do I know
f for fish yeah I've already
basically
it's fine
stop [\h__\h] with me
some dead body
and fulfill exactly that's the only
correct thing in the chat right now
thanks
Phil
this submarine stands out way too much
it's way too yellow should be orange
would be much better
orange submarine yeah we all
we own the orange submarine it works
[Music]
are you always so [\h__\h] aggressive
like for real
is that sub covered properly it'll be
fine come get there
no no no no sir I'm certainly not being
shorted I'm just not used to this kind
of pressure if you turn a crew onto a
score you got to be ready for the heat
that comes with it I didn't turn anyone
on to anything you threatened and
controlled and tricked me you don't want
to cut just walk away the cake walk away
so intimidated the show from my home
Deborah's home no cut for you you saw
nothing dude for Deborah
you saw nothing
nobody's seeing anything here
foreign
no
[Music]
foreign wait a second I'm gonna do this
proper
[Applause]
please don't tell me please don't tell
me Mission stop stop go backwards go
backwards
please don't tell me I failed admission
I'm not gonna fail the [\h__\h] mission
where is it where is it oh
before the sun goes up please
okay careful careful
you can pull up
I did it guys
I'm just trying to get in there but
without like too much of a
sudden curve you know
but going backwards is really difficult
for my brain
anyway we'll almost have it ah there we
go that's good that's good that's that's
very good good
[Music]
bye
yeah look at that
[Applause]
beautiful
you'll be okay there
um sure all right if you're wrong I'll
eat your sweet meats
I love we can trust this but okay
and now
we wait for him to leave or what
hmm I think we just have to wait for a
mission passed or so
what
there we go okay okay I I anticipated I
it made me unsure again but this time no
jump scare
no it's Oscar no I'm just scared
yeah stretch oh
okay I'm gonna try to finish this Heist
and that might be it for today but I
don't know let's see what's next
wait what is next why is there a racing
thingy here
uh
well what I want I want to continue to
Heist maybe I just wait for a call
Heist place
I would like to do my Heist there we go
hey Loco just gave me but you're kind of
cool we should chop it
up sometime with Franklin all about him
no double dog I thought for a second
that uh since the picture is chopped
that the game was basically having chop
write me a SMS
I need you all at the lot in Elber
Heights for face to face don't be late
what about what about the heist
oh The Heist
is that the B
hi shanila okay federal investigation
Bureau
hmm
are we sure we're just gonna leave this
here oh wait wait
so it looks like we're ready to go with
everything and there we go don't kick
it's a good idea for us to meet at the
condo so maybe we should tell Floyd it
is a good idea at the condo it's a great
idea and tell him we need chips and dip
and prostitutes
I would like some chips now
but okay now see this is what I wanted
to continue so now we'll go there we'll
go there
there's so much like stuff running at
the same time but I think we should just
continue with the highest now
I just need a car
oh there
there are some Kai's
calling a camp no I am the cab
the world's my cab
oh his stamina are you good buddy
you could really use some extra stamina
or escaping and [\h__\h]
get the stamina come on Get It Get It Go
Get It Go Get It Trevor
you know what I would love for you to
diet on a heart attack so maybe not
maybe you don't deserve
stamina
taxi oh it's faster oh really
oh
don't mind my loud car this is just um
my heart rate monitor
let's go
[Music]
it's the condo
safest place to be at
my safe house sorry
sorry are you sure you want to talk to
Trevor like that
he is absolutely insane you don't want
to mess with him
ah
anyway it was really nice meeting rmt
yesterday I should do stuff like that
more often I need more
social interactions I guess ow [\h__\h]
hell what the [\h__\h] man [\h__\h] you
yeah yeah
had some ice cream too
[Applause]
more grass time and touching grass you
know
[Music]
[Applause]
I want to make my bestie it's been a
while with her too
she was saying to oh we should meet up
again
an advertisement
[Laughter]
I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry what's the song in the background
um that was a remix of hinotori my first
original song I got some remixes on my
channel just look at Pino Tony and remix
the remixes are not on Spotify but my
original songs are on Spotify and Amazon
music and all that
Apple music go check it out
[Music]
my fifth original song but this is again
a hinotori remix
they're really good all of the free
remixes are really [\h__\h] good
definitely worth a listen what's about
you're showing off
they really are yeah
[Music]
get up
hey you guys I'm expecting company I
want this place clean Wade you tidy
Floyd really they're gonna clean it's
unbelievable
character development guys no no you're
right you're right hey bro what's up and
it didn't get far
[\h__\h] record oh yeah
oh here's the assistant on his way my
shoulders were so much in pain no last
night
for once like I try to save on them you
know those sheets that I showed you guys
before the sheets that we will put like
where it hurts
um the one that I got from Japan
I rarely use them because I I don't
wanna like
stop talking oh oh
I think you need to reflect on what you
just said
respectful this is
you know what what we do here with
Tangent okay and my my viewers
appreciate that
I [\h__\h] appreciate that
yeah if I I don't want to be the
streamer who plays a game and says not a
single [\h__\h] word besides any
everything that's game related okay
because I think that's boring and if
that's not your kind of streaming then
you're wrong here okay fishing okay I
was talking and sharing my pain yeah
here it can't be we share our [\h__\h]
pain and I'm telling you I had so bad
shoulder pain last night because I I use
this I don't think they're called
Salonpas but anyway I use them yeah yeah
yeah
that's all I wanted to say really that's
that was two seconds of dialogue and you
can't even wait for those those two
seconds of dialogue huh
you won't even let me talk for two
seconds
if you don't want to hear two seconds of
personal private dialogue then you
should watch like one of those muted
playthroughs or just play the game
yourself I guess
anyway
yes yeah whatever man so what we doing
here we're working amigo
taking a score yeah oh I see you guys I
see you guys being like do you really
need your character
oh oh it's it's interesting to see which
ones are the ones that say that [\h__\h]
that have complaints
stop pausing oh does that trigger you
you'll trigger you even pause in the
game oh you talk too much kiwawa oh
really does that trigger you too then
why the [\h__\h] are you here
done most of the planning and I think
we're going to literally make out like
Bandits on this
did you talk to Lester yeah yeah I
called him apparently oh
oh does that hurt you oh I'm so sorry
sorry that I paused he's in the hospital
having his vagina cleaned or some [\h__\h]
he's got a wasting disease 20 saved
no that's not how we work well you'll
forgive me but that's how we're gonna
work this time all right we're doing it
my way because as I recall the last time
when we did it your way we all got shot
at you got buried resurrected turned
into a [\h__\h] and Brad ended up in a
[\h__\h] prison yeah and Lester told us
not to do that job but we did it anyway
unless this thing is pretty good man
would you shut the [\h__\h] up all right and
you Michael owe me all right all right
so this time we do things my way yeah
and what about after this after this we
think about things
so what's the plan
easy all right
we are sinking a freighter into Los
Santos Harbor all right now Daddy's
Little Helper you're gonna be on the
bridge his mission is quiet you what's
the word crater and planting charges me
a I'm running the deep water system
starts with Asian With a Little Help
from her friends
where'd you get the [\h__\h] Mikey I'm
insane [\h__\h] you
ambitious yeah ambitious [\h__\h] you
compared to our previous size which was
just basic don't be a dick oh your wish
is my commando
[Music]
stop dragging your heels kid we need
some transport do I need to do this as
Trevor do I need to
together
we're all together
a vehicle okay we're taking this one
now what about Michael in my car
okay I'm taking you
to support City side of the Miriam
Turner overpass
almost forgot
the rifle with a thermal scope I almost
forgot I was kind of sold on like a
well-organized job planned out with
Lester's weird out for detail
I had an eye for details kid little
details like your brick of blow being
drywall okay man I'm grateful for that
dog but buying cocaine is a whole
different thing from sinking the
container ship into a harbor
I really kid it's all about what's
inside
cool so what's the thing man I don't
know what it is I know it's important
you heard of Merryweather uh yeah maybe
what time they mentioned Mary weather
the company
Creator it's all over the planet they're
the Army there
so are you only they're private so they
cost more and they've just got fired to
take government contracts on U.S soil
and what's one of the first on the list
[Music]
exact Commando so it's gotta be valuable
right anyway it doesn't matter because
your job is not to understand it's to
shoot at peoples who try to stop us they
name themselves after this game
your music is better than everyone else
that's music for you
radio hype up dialogue
you're going to like it you will like it
we know you're going to like it
music
F M P music
radio
that's one of the Austrian ones that's
your Shooter's nest and call Mike
okay man soon
Vantage Point don't hurt me
don't [\h__\h] hurt me but hey we're
Franklin
what for how long
hey dog I'm in position let me know my
gun
is our sniper boy
all right coming first
so make sure I don't run into any
trouble when I get there [\h__\h] Trevor
all right I got you homie
[Music]
yeah they're a nasty Bunch
oh you want me to take them down is
there like a good choice of who to take
down first because those are two but
also like who sees it these he seems
pretty alone
fast but maybe we can like go through
both of them we did that before
oh we did it there's Dad
their schools were not hard enough to
block the bullet keep an eye on me okay
Michael and Franklin while planting
bombs
uh bull pillar what this thing
how do I do this again okay ready to go
moving up to position two
[Music]
okay we want to switch to make sure that
everything let the position is safe
right but
I'm doing it down do I jump quick or I
can do it right okay
do I try to jump over there
oh no that doesn't work oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] come on
cool you're too old for this [\h__\h]
if you were like 20 years younger I know
this doesn't help you middle life
midlife crisis but if you were just like
2 years younger
you could have done that jump easily
is that me
chill chill dude wait I saw someone I
saw someone though but is that Michael
[\h__\h] Michael you're stressing me the
[\h__\h] out because you're going too fast
this is for it's all free now
I see what we're doing I see
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] idiot Michael
why are you so close then I'm doing it
automatically nice okay okay
nice
it's clear I think pretty clear but
moving up okay wait I see some here but
I don't know where exactly you're going
okay
very clear
very clear this yolk
um
moving
some Clipper uses like that as a
you guys you guys remember maybe you
guys watch the same clips
I use it as like a in between
so cute
yeah it's a Korean cooker yeah
well there can only be people like
visible
to me from this point of view right
there won't be any like behind the
containers I would hope
door's here nice
I'm not gonna screw around in here all
right oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh was that Michael
uh is that
where is he gonna come out from
that's a problem
uh uh what where do
oh God oh God
I
[Music]
wait maybe I can do uh how do you do he
can't do it now
is he coming up that one dude
anymore
episode
I think he's taken care of
1999 there's a lot of red dots where are
they
huh I hear oh still down there okay
ah
there's two more where
huh
where the [\h__\h] are they
must be
look at the people oh [\h__\h]
you guys are not covered well enough for
someone like me
hey what the [\h__\h]
okay
okay everything's taking care of Michael
I love you
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
not bad nice
where the [\h__\h] do they come from yeah
look at me
this is fun
I wonder could we do this from Michael's
point of view too I do prefer this one
though I do prefer
this point of view
go go come on he's so slow
spawn man
I'm gonna try this
get away from the ship they going up in
three and a two uh open contacts
that was a wheel
uh-huh
do I have to wait any longer can I do it
okay
I am once again very big fashion style
sake that is
very dramatic oh
nice snapping thank you
I felt like that was good too oh
okay I'm in the drink tea where are you
at
okay oh God what sort of signals are
giving off
I have a bad feeling about
this but uh
we can't drown right
I should be closing in on it
how do I go down
I feel like I'm going higher good time
go down
[Music]
this is just like aiming downwards with
the mouse because I don't feel like he's
going down
shift for Speed aha thank you oh my God
no
what the [\h__\h] the controls
ah
I should prepare a [\h__\h] controller
wait this is like
visible on the map no but I see the
signal coming from like far far far far
yeah okay okay
there we go
huh
oh
no wait um I I try to
get a hold of myself
I'm doing this with controller and uh
with the keyboard and mouse
but we did it
oh he's got the submarine
all right I'm on the way I'm on my way
mmm they're matching the thing and the
submarine
I'll go down
wait it's like a missile
just take a shower after healing sheesh
how are we gonna sell that don't we want
to like make money from it but who's
gonna buy that
[Music]
how how do you sell it without being
noticed and stuff
I won't question it there we go
Michael is fish it seems
fine come on yeah
I'm so fun now I took care of everything
I wish them good luck in retrieving all
of those [\h__\h] containers
but at least it seems like there's no
like oil spillage or whatever like you
know anything that makes the water dirty
dirtier than it already is
something kept it relatively clean
as clean as we could
oh that reminds me I think we talked
about this before but
remember when we talked about these um
or is it like dolls
showing up
and on the shores
these creepy horror dolls
like Barnacles all over them
must have been some doll shipment but
they were like different looking dolls
so it's like what the [\h__\h] how many Dole
shipments have been
drowned in the ocean before
it's kind of beautiful
yeah
say whatever you want about traffic but
[\h__\h] that's so ridiculous yeah let's
hope so out of all things that could be
in the ocean Garfield phones oh look at
him he's really happy good for him
I need you should be in there yes I
should be I would be if certain known
associates were busy making themselves
enemies of the state
FIB Meriwether IAA you can [\h__\h] with
them all day long but when you try and
steal
weapons they sell it to the Chinese you
and everyone you ever knew was gonna be
[\h__\h] in the ass you [\h__\h] chumps
hold on man a super weapon the Chinese
what what you think is in there
I thought he talked to you
all right man so what now
well maybe I can organize to have it
taken back and found among
disgusting I was like oh is that like a
like a rope from the hospital I guess it
is wow
do I have to censor just butt holding on
and looking good you have any idea what
you did here yeah pull the score what
are you jealous because you didn't get
your 20 that thing doesn't go back then
we will all end up on every watch list
in the entire place
they kill idiot we'll all be dead within
a week think
listen Michael being the reasonable one
here once again reminds me of um Trevor
Arrested Development we're also the
Michael is the reasonable one and they
actually look similar
than you and the patient shiny bug take
it all back
God is that what yeah is that what I
mean this [\h__\h] was all for nothing it's
not from there put the hood all over
again [\h__\h]
come on Franklin
you owe me Michael
I am all really really do huh we owe you
something I gotta get Franklin some work
too yeah I'll take this Michael Michael
Bluff is amazing okay Amigo tell me
about it there's so many protagonists
that are called Michael huh Michael
Scott Michael blue
he's the way his body was like like was
shaking because of Madness
all right we passed the memory weather
haste which was
oh I liked the sniping action but
besides that there wasn't even that much
action it was a lot of uh you know
diving in the water and trying to move
the submarine
huh
it was a lot of fun
I always found
huh
and what if I did the other option ah
then it would have been annoying really
oh I'm glad I took this option then yeah
right we could have done it differently
huh
I'm glad we did it this way it seemed
like the smart way
yeah a good way
what what did I mispronounce oh
probably shouldn't steal a car right
next to you huh
oh
oh I mean I'm Trevor although can I
what are the others doing
what's Franklin doing
Heist he's not Heist is
and I thought I was gonna end it but um
a little bit more won't hurt
uh
B oh yeah we were told to go to B can I
go there it's green green is Franklin
all right right yeah I think so too
[Music]
the next next those crazy freaks are
going to tell me to stop singing imagine
[Music]
ah
come on
[Music]
oh my God I'm dizzy okay I feel dizzy
hello because I was told that if we
helped out important meeting here going
on
indiscretions would be forgotten who
told you that did I tell you that I'm in
charge here fruity
you understand not quite well can you
explain that again what I was saying
oh you're good the three thank you
we need help with something else some of
the government some of it is pretty
corrupt just play if you're keeping you
sane nice oh wait
the monkey meme can't see can't
can't
uh talk
not your bed right yes but we're corrupt
in a good way but the agency I want to
encourage Panic so they can guarantee
see their budgets that's how they do the
major problems they do be some stupid
monkeys man
funds that we need to use in our fight
against Crime as a way of bribing
corrupt officials really and where are
they getting that from drugs those
bastards love to sell drugs who doesn't
use this money to finance a war on our
streets and we need you boys to
requisition that money for us the bonds
are leaving the terminal in an armored
car yeah [\h__\h] you Dave we don't have
time to prepare the right way
not my concern I cannot allocate any
more resources to this
you'll be fine [\h__\h] you Dave
nice work slick we're gonna be doing Pat
Downs at the airport before I love the
passionate [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] this game yeah
man it is what it is it's speaking my
language let's get this done I don't
know
he's doing the thinking pose
I got it well classic Blitz play it's an
industrial area right so I'm thinking
Vehicles trash truck to block tow truck
sack em we get some disguises and we're
gold we just gotta hope like hell these
are the kind of agency men that don't
carry a panic button with them they are
we deal with it if and when
if and [\h__\h] win
I will my eyes peeled General
oh
torture
don't peel your own eyes
no problem
no really
now why do you default me back to this
[\h__\h] no
why do you want me to play Travis so bad
no no no that's from fans in order
foreign
[Music]
okay
I've left the area
oh my guys a few more details we'll need
boiler suits and masks for this job
and there's an auto repair place by the
airport where we can get a tow truck
what else uh oh yeah yeah get away that
would be nice get something fast and
discreet we park it off the road a good
distance from the lot and make sure it
ain't near something we'll crash into
driving off that's it all right man I
got you uh what huh I missed that maybe
shout a little louder fight me
what is going on here
hey police
yeah but he was rhyming wait was the
difference
it was rhyming the police car like so
mean bullying
was was she down for someone else and
was that just a coincidence
brother O'Neill
you're the guy stealing contracts you
burped them off killed my brothers you
had too many brothers they needed
calling you're [\h__\h] dicks aren't we
all we live and we die that's our curse
hey you want to expedite the situation
come [\h__\h] fine
Vespucci Beach Los Santos you inbred
hillbilly [\h__\h] I'll be there man I don't
know when but uh
it's gonna be a rainbow reunion
beautiful
uh but anyway that one's coming Franklin
I don't know when but I'll be there [\h__\h]
those dudes yeah
imagine kiwama singing some raggy Style
music huh
chill
all right oh there's so much oh so many
choices what the [\h__\h]
it is free HSS
oh go to l
go to l
B
why are you guys saying four
four
there's no four four ah here's one more
oh Franklin you ain't been home I got
worried thought about calling she never
pick up so I did some digging and found
you ain't been home because ain't your
home no more ideas oh you're a little
bit late on the news
I got a sick house now
I wouldn't mind you moving and you know
need to be there for your family
but we should at least visit and then be
jealous
look at my home and be jealous
and do not go for album
believe to chat
oh that's just oh it's a side mission oh
well I mean t is right there
is that Trevor
Trevor
[\h__\h] do you want now
oh wait it's you
[Laughter]
it's just you all right let's go to HS
wait there's a closer one though
there's a closer one here
um oh wait do they want me to get guns
why is it right there
I go there
[Music]
don't do
no no no no no no no no no buy a free
boiler suits
boiler like cooking suits what
oh my good night
I gotta take off my helmet we'll be back
in again
like
um one of those
about I love the hip hop Jackson MC clip
no no of course not
sure
[Music]
what that's a boiler suit why is it
called a boiler suit
is there a pink one
[Music]
background
oh man all right well we'll take this
one
[Laughter]
um I'm Waking in a boiler room man makes
a lot of sins and one for Michael uh
everyone gets a different one oh
okay
that's it
my helmet is gone no more safety oh
mission
[Laughter]
really really
okay number one done
no
and I guess let's go here
so we have all different kinds of
preparations to do huh
hey y'all
okay that's it
can't we have a conversation I thought
we were homies you know
not that way
sorry
foreign
[Music]
call it taxi that's [\h__\h] lame unless
I steal the taxi and then drive it
myself then that's fine we can talk
about that
[Music]
see how smooth it is with this bike yeah
smooth
sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry we're
buying masks
they're pizza too
laughs
I see
oh well that is yeah well horror movie
we don't want that no no oh
oh these are maybe pretty good Phoenix
Franklin my boy you're getting the
Phoenix wrestler mask yep
and then
uh Michael I like Michael
he gets this one and then Trevor could
Trevor [\h__\h] sucks
gets the
the monkey mask yep
happy
I'm happy with that
[Music]
it's gonna stand out and that's good we
don't want him to be part of our group
our titty
[Music]
I handled the mask man don't worry about
them
[Music]
some machines so lonely lonely
Franklin's so lonely
I have no Daddy what the [\h__\h]
what
happened
I need this
[\h__\h] need this in my life right now
wow
it's so cute
come on look it even got green whales
fitting for a Franklin
imagine
the weight turned wow it's got so much
dynamic
Dorito
oh oh [\h__\h] now
before placing the what do you mean get
away oh vehicle no
[Music]
no no no
foreign
[Music]
oh no way can we try that
what the [\h__\h]
whatever
[Music]
[Laughter]
fun
yeah
sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
oh God the police oh no
[Music]
[Applause]
mom
please
job right yeah baby
what if I hide like here
candy why don't you
go to the
burrow
S I think I'm hiding
death of a protester the day before and
you're pretty safe here Jasmine a local
porn star is upset at the new law
they have no idea where I am and they
found me and then they lost me
[Music]
uh there's one like coming kind of this
way
oh
please lose me now
he won't see me right let's see what
happens
set up a getaway car are you saying this
is not a good getaway car
find one leave it somewhere secluded
wait does this count as a getaway car
it does we need like a four-seater yeah
no
no Army nation is that a word actually
that sounds like a regular word
[Music]
I Don't Wanna Stop it yet playing
English and relax Yeah Boy as soon as
it's a nice car and it's yellow
and now
um
there's something special about you can
have this beautiful car you're [\h__\h]
welcome
I'm doing you a favor let's be honest
saying
okay and now uh
is this where we're supposed to drop it
off this HS thingy
no play that here
I know I can fight the feeling I know
maybe you decide anywhere how do they
know
this is the one
[Music]
I
call First person check my my camera on
my car that was their fault
not just like a text and the main thing
is so common no problem I can solve it
I'm just a woman love knowing that this
one in a rush you can't save me I'm in
Duty and I love the Horizon I just can't
resist you
oh I think we're losing them already
you let me go
[Music]
if you know what a [\h__\h] banger
I'm just waiting got me oh they're
coming now
looking something so wrong oh that's not
okay so I get out and this is my car
uh-huh so like the market away after
when phoning Michael okay
I hope there's a relatively good
selection uh oh yeah and placement
you see wait how do it
how
hmm
if I was supposed to call him and then
you know isn't there like an option
Michael Michael
I need to be in the car oh
I need to be in the car
I go hey I got a ride for our getaway
homie well done where's it stored here
Cypress Flats
did did the voice actors
and the voice actor Franklin have to
voice
the name of every [\h__\h] location in
this map just in case you know
where that he can say oh
no he could have just said oh I'll send
you the GPS data or whatever or the
Google Maps address what
what
is
symbol
um
damn it's the little things yeah I was
like yo no way no way I mean like no way
no [\h__\h] way but okay next we go here
but I guess I can't go with this car and
there's no any [\h__\h] other cars here
why did I park here because I want to
hide
where are the cars
where are the cars I did this to myself
there's one here
not the best car but
Mr Mikey
oh could he do all of these things too
or does it have to be
Franklin
something new it doesn't matter
drinks tonight give me that please
oh okay well Franco is doing all the
homework
and uh speaking of homework [\h__\h] I need
to make the more Goose something else oh
it's gonna be a pain
I'm making thumbnails for so many people
is actually quite difficult because all
of them are on the thumbnail and then I
have to keep on realigning them and yeah
last time I did that it was pretty
painful
sorry about it so emotionless
[Music]
oh yeah
but I'll do it then I could probably say
I made all those thumbnails
[Music]
until you feel the music I I remember I
actually
um you know we all get you know these
Cosmic Cubes but we have to unlock them
by playing the game
um unfortunately I guess there's no way
around it but I was thinking of like
playing beforehand a little bit but
um maybe we can do it during the members
only stream
you can play I'm all good Skies
I originally wanted to play more slaves
fire but we can play sorry oh he died oh
[\h__\h] he died we're gonna play his latest
fire anytime
yeah and the Mongoose is one of the
games that I can play in members only
and you guys can participate and we
haven't done it in a while and it's a
way of me getting back into the game
back into the groove so I hope you guys
have no problem with it
[Music]
foreign
hello
oh [\h__\h]
so much smoke do we want to like kill
him first or
doesn't seem to mind work you piece of
junk and I look close to
this top and like wreck his head with it
oh man the smoke
junk
crap [\h__\h]
anyway I think
oh he's doing like this
come on
come on we could probably like snipe him
from like far away oh this this doesn't
seem to have any consequences night
suits
okay
I need to turn around
[Music]
why was that so easy
uh yeah oh I'm so [\h__\h] sorry
wait then let's crime is what I was
gonna say but that dude oof that was
dangerous
[Music]
sorry I really only have like five
tracks on this radio
[Music]
very repetitive I know
what oh
you're going to catch such a beat
the owner
so good luck catching man
[Music]
do I need to kill you
I guess I can shoot you too guys but we
don't want the police on my back oh
kind of stuck huh
we're just ignoring and we're not even
dealing with him but it's kind of cute
that he's trying
[Music]
we should just attach him to the tow
truck
[Music]
oh sorry
what am I doing am I drunk
[Music]
here again
I thought I lost you
[Laughter]
man I would have more problems with that
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
trying
he's making an effort yeah
I'm having quite a lot of fun
foreign
[Music]
this on his own I respect that
I can't even see him on the map anymore
though I think he's gone
[Music]
you gave up already
oh man
[Music]
what does Duke mean
what does that mean
is he still there or not
oh
ah stylish torch
oh this is so fine this is so unusable
yeah
[Music]
I joked him I misled an opponent oh did
I
told you
yeah we have one more what are we done
with the preparations
I think there was one at yeah here
um
another car please oh well I'm gonna be
ignored again so sad
hey the tow trucks at the lot dog ready
to go
why are you
yeah
wait wait wait wait wait wait no no
God damn it oh wait they're standing
there no wait wait wait there's my
chance
there's my chance
oh nice music
and would like to listen to more of that
man the radio is gonna be a lot of fun
if you don't have to worry about dmca
we don't want to overdo it
we
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
you are a Spanish club I want to learn
to learn Spanish
I would like to learn Spanish
I wanted to and was one of my goals
so sorry right I'm sorry
oh
are we buying shoes here wait this place
is called cornies
[Music]
what am I doing here
feel like we were here before
[Music]
dude why did I go there
Miami
mindless
oh wait is it moving it's moving
mindless GTA yang
and you
shiny car
I I say
yes what am I supposed to
uh
feeling of course of course what else
what what else would it have been
[Music]
done
is that where we're gonna hide out the
bodies hmm
[Music]
squishy
I just wanna have a quick talk with you
oh there's two people in there what are
we gonna do about the second person come
out you got the day off homie yeah I'm
gonna steal all the garbage for you
you're lucky
oh [\h__\h] two stars how the [\h__\h] am I am I
supposed to lose the cops with this
thing
it stands out so much
all right oh he's coming there ah
all right I am
oh no
ah
you know
[Applause]
[Music]
in this neighborhood
I know
it's so slow
and they're so close
honest that's pretty good
um
um I'm so sorry you're in the [\h__\h]
way right now
leave it somewhere high on foot
I
believe
one
who is policing you huh
who's gonna police you buddy is gonna be
me and a hero
I'm fully seeing you and go there
yeah learned your lesson now hopefully
and what about you
it's a good question though
it's a good [\h__\h] question um but yeah
I got them so close on my butt
that I don't know how to get out of this
oh oh yeah that's not the smartest thing
either
[Music]
a little bit of time guys
the whole deal of this accordingly
I'm just doing my job here
um
[Music]
what what do I do with my special
ability
kill them
oh
we got some leeway now
where are we going guys where are we
going with this
oh I see him coming
okay this is really not nice right now
go away
yeah I'll just I'll just keep on driving
I think we have a lot of distance now if
I keep on driving
oh God then uh
yeah yeah we're already losing them
but the car is not doing so well
oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh I lost
nothing right
hey it was just coming from that side
time
so lucky
yeah so lucky how do I cancel like um
this one how do I cancel that there you
go of course I'm so hungry now
crime makes very hungry
I got some
leftover fried noodles
vegetarian for some reason because
actually you know sometimes I go for
vegetarian options because I feel like
the volume
and like
um take away stuff and like order stuff
is already like they oh the volume of
what they give you is so much
and then
I just can't take
any more food so I just go for a lighter
option
bring the health no no no no I got them
last night
I
it's about crony sandwich I tried to
catch up a little bit yesterday
but she can't be [\h__\h] serious
I wouldn't do something like that though
not me I like me a fresh sandwich
I could actually make one
[Music]
um
before the Super Chat reading because I
have some sandwich ingredients nothing
special but
got a nice Moon Becca
to put some
uh I think it was called biaksteiger
sausage sliced sausage
yum yum yum yum
what did crony do I think she ate a five
day old sandwich or so and her excuses
to um you know always have a sandwich
ready
uh when you need it
she can't be serious at five days it's
definitely gone bad
just have the separate ingredients put a
sandwich ready
those you know separately
if they're like in the plastic and all
that they will be fine for five days and
then just open it up and make the
sandwich when you want to but okay
apparently that's too much too much to
ask for
got it from Subway you know all these
whole life girls they're all just
lazy
so much ordering yeah yeah they should
take an example from me and cook okay
now all of them some of them actually do
cook yeah respect
some some even cook more than I do
but Kelly for example she even orders
[\h__\h] water bottles
last time when we were preparing for
them
for the um VR
actually you know what I don't want to
hear anything at all right now last time
we prepared for the VR she was like hang
on a second I gotta order some water and
everybody in the voice chat was like
Kelly
what do you mean you're ordering water
she orders literally everything
oh my God like I tried recently I I
tried to you know save money
for whatever reason I just feel like
it's a waste to Uber too much and to
order too much so I'm trying to save
money here and there you know
cook a little bit
have a
cheap meal
but also I I have the advantage that's
the garbage truck okay that's everything
come back to the lot now okay
Steve says we got to take it to Devin
Weston the guy we met at that
interrogation it's a big investor or
something anyway that don't matter I'll
handle the drop off okay I hope the
advantage dad in Austria you know
Austria is one of the oh let me realign
the sentence Austria has
one of the top five I would say cleaning
cleaners drinking Waters out of the
tapping water
that what tap water can't speak uh in
the whole world so I don't need to buy
water I get it out of my tap I just
drink the tap water
oh in in Japan you can if you buy a
filter uh in in I think in most places
you can drink it but I feel like it
would still be
more desirable to buy water
bottled water so I get that you know I
get that but I was just thinking she
should just get it from the supermarket
or so
instead of ordering it that's so
expensive for [\h__\h] water
hey hit or miss in the states
right there
so we really finna do this [\h__\h] we're
gonna risk Our Lives to Rob some
[\h__\h] government Killers again
yeah hey
all right so listen up one tap all day
wait till me too Trevor yeah I like trap
water often more than bottled water give
me a heads up when the armored car comes
by in Austria at least yeah I'm gonna be
right here in the garbage truck blocking
the roadway Franklin you're in the alley
in a tow truck hope is they pull right
up in front of you when they do you come
at them hard bam [\h__\h] here's hoping Pam
yeah after the hit if we blast open the
doors grab up all the cash bonds
whatever it is I take it to Hanes guy
saw a little hole for home as long as I
am not on the ground when the [\h__\h] goes
down okay when the [\h__\h] goes down we'll
handle it you stay up here on your post
eyes peeled yeah we'll take the risk
sound cool nice peels mission is my
favorite clown outfits there's a plus
right and we're not wearing Cloud opens
when you're wearing something special
and I picked out Jack
Jack you Trevor
what real professional you got a problem
with that
hahaha
[Laughter]
yeah
does he know that he's got [\h__\h]
hey
[Laughter]
nice
[\h__\h] nice
oh man
you can't see
hahaha
um doing a Cypress oh man see I was
thinking like should we like
oh wait it's not even that far aha I
thought it would be super far away I was
thinking I should put it somewhere where
it will be handy because it's close but
I had no idea where I was leaving it
smooth smooth funny smooth
for Trevor hi don't you dare PN at
Trevor he deserves no sympathy
nope now that
what is this music
soundtrack was very repetitive what the
hell
I like it if it had more variety
all right T I'm in position what's the
ETA
hmm
you guys are waiting nice travels [\h__\h]
what does it say about you guys incoming
get ready to do your thing what's my
what's spoil what is my opinion all
right Mike
I'm so happy So Satisfied
I'm so happy about that
and you want me to
wait say you say that like it's so easy
um
here we go okay okay well I mean they
could just drive on the path you're on
it on the Walking path
change their schedule
why is there so much German hints in
this case hey man I got these
[\h__\h] okay
and this is group six in German
you didn't understand Trevor are you a
Trevor White Knight or what
okay okay
land a stick around on the rear doors of
the truck uh oh yeah okay
how many
why is knock no
[Music]
you know
oh do they want me to place all of them
are on the door
all right
like this
thank God I have so many
okay that was that was actually
um useful let me uh drive away with the
car no okay I thought I would be safer
uh sheesh
the alarm's been tripped the cops will
be swarming here in 10 seconds you
better run shut the [\h__\h] up come on good
you go you're here
what no running no running no running
friends
oh he's alive
hey this gonna be a nasty [\h__\h]
oh God wait wait wait cover cover
yeah I got your back just let me know
[Music]
hey guys
more cops on the way
how long take out the newest
reinforcement coming from the rear alley
what's a rear alley what is that here
back left for the loading area 5-0
coming at it back up for the loading
area man what Costco Mass
okay I'm here to help
wait no no no no no what what the [\h__\h] I
have to I have to
go okay
easy easy easy Claire
be more
[Music]
[\h__\h] was that
hold on
oh look
up
what the [\h__\h] is sniping me
oh my God I hear a helicopter beautiful
thank God I turned around
oh
is he dead
come on
[Music]
whoever's over there take care of that
side or or am I done here I think I'm
done there
oh ah there you go
a window I would say
goodness huh
that's my question
um
so alive
yeah yeah he'd do be like can you reload
a bit faster yeah
[Music]
I don't see anything
all clear here oh no clear
okay okay okay
I got you covered my bestie Franklin I
knew it was more dudes in front of you
easy
I'm protecting my son
I would never never
let you die
over to the right
she switch
one two switch stay out of my line of
fire do I have like a bum bazooka or
what
well where do we where do we want to go
to oh no this is a I got the snipers
oh okay stop this would be in high
places right is he dead
um
I don't see anymore where the [\h__\h] would
they be oh oh you're not a sniper
oh
same building oh [\h__\h]
opposite oh
I mean
oh
this doesn't count as a sniper though
does he
there come here
can I go back to shooting the the bottom
ones because like I don't know where the
[\h__\h] these [\h__\h] are
sniper dude sniper dudes
well I mean right there
can I switch
all we gotta do is write this out
good job please for me
he'll do it right when I'm like doing
someone else
wrong
do it
hold on
this feels like
too long it's going on for too long man
oh there's one here I see I see okay
well I can take that one down I'll try I
know
computer
[Music]
there was another one there before too
huh
okay
okay now we do a little bit with Frank
oh wait why do we have to go back to him
oh wait wait oh no no no no no no no no
no no no no no there we go
did he just want me to go back to his
sniper rifle
because I don't see anyone
hey
oh there's one of them there though
hey what's up oh no they're shooting
they're shooting Trevor
take out the helicopter okay
I assume as Trevor
oh oh I have to anticipate
[Music]
would he have been able to do that alone
no
no no
that was so fast
[Music]
make a play
I'm looking at the mini map
I got your back just let me know
at least I know the positions of the
snipers now if they're always there
what the [\h__\h]
see now uh Michael is up here
uh okay
wait why why
was that necessary I don't think he was
calling for the snipers yet
uh I don't like this position for him
I'm going down
um
clearance pretty much
what the [\h__\h] does that happen huh
hold up
he's playing hard to get
okay
it's hard to see if I took someone out
in this mode
well I think I did let's wear some good
shots
okay
another Speedy sniper team on the roof
opposite you just oh okay
[Music]
I [\h__\h]
yeah
I'm gonna take him out on a date
why are you running why
[Music]
why are you shooting two is down oops
there's another one
[Applause]
[Music]
speed running
because I'm trying
I'm coming from the left
how did you know
as you
back down
[Music]
there's a lot of them over there
it's a bad idea
[Music]
[Applause]
the pressure man the pressure though
it's like a window to get out of there
deal with the trash truck I'll get the
bus to Steve's guy
[Music]
get into the garbage truck hi
yeah
[Music]
I knew I had to like kind of aim to
where the chopper was going to
oh okay get away location all right all
right all right all right
um I need to do like a turn
okay
what about Michael Michael gonna be
daijubu
Michael Daniel boo
Michael
Daddy
that was a good teamwork I would say
the Dream Team these free huh
and we got rid of the police because we
just killed all of them I guess that's
that's one way to do it
they first have to find a few new
employees
before they can come after me again
Michael got the fancy car
yeah good for him he deserves it
oh [\h__\h] the wrong way
[Music]
teamwork teamwork it's all that counts
and honestly it's hard to find like
people in the sniper gun
thingy when it's so dark and they're all
so dark
how how how am I supposed to find them
Joy do I have something oopsie
to destroy it with
ah
it's sticky sticky sticky bump
how many do we need
I only have three
so I hope that's enough
oh just one was enough oh [\h__\h] can I
take it back
oh wow I mean
I'm around good explosion stop it's not
destroyed completely as in like it's
turned into dust but I hope that's fine
oh yeah and away from the garbage truck
got you
I got you
I'm away I'm away
do I get a mission accomplished or what
where is my mission accomplished
take that down wait this is not really a
street I need to go back I think I'm
kind of wrong here
and I I felt it
okay I have to go back to the garbage
truck
oh smooth okay it's kind of in the way
all good
we should have pushed it into the ocean
this is like the evidence is still there
is like right on the street
but what do I know I'm not a criminal
I don't know how to do this I guess
everything cool yeah man [\h__\h] that trash
truck is trash dawg you good nice work
I'm about to meet this guy I'll tell you
how it goes hmm okay oh
switching
to Michael
yeah
criminal jokes move criminals Joe please
did he just ask if women are made from
Sand
no
no we're made from sugar
because we that sweet and
got it almost right though sand close
enough
I'm really hungry please don't [\h__\h] with
me now
package for Mr Weston
and I'm telling you that I don't give a
flying [\h__\h]
there you go there you go well you
really gave it to him so long
[\h__\h] wow Devin Weston destroyed
you
the weekend interrogator
invest wisely okay hold on hold on we're
not done here yet I got a job for you
bro five top quality scores Big Ticket
cars major payday bro okay that's great
I got just the guy for you I'll put you
in touch Trevor please I want you no
you're a crew I want Pros on this yeah I
don't give a [\h__\h] what you want pencil
neck I think you can use a break again
oh you're interested I guess I just got
you figured wrong man hey what's the
figure tell me something you like how
about you do it yourself staking a
sports investment I always ask Gunners
name your poison man you do you just
like sitting around watching old movies
oh there we go how about I hook you up
with Solomon Richards
[\h__\h]
the movie producer yeah he's retired for
a daughter Maybe
I will make the connect just as soon as
you
how nice
all right it's not for her oh man
don't we want to do her a favor you know
we want them to get back on our good
side no
I performed a classic Blitz play
what's that is it when you kill all the
all the
officers all the cops
and then that's how you escape
Kill Everybody
football turn
[Music]
I know this is German hey man listen I
got an interesting opportunity for you
acquaintance an FIB contact are you
joking relax guys private sector very
well could be lucrative
oh no
I wanted to look at the map
no talk to me and talk to me
[Music]
foreign
too much of a stunt man what
European level why because I didn't use
the road
ah
The Landing was too good
all right but
um you know what I'm here and then next
time we'll hear the dialogue again I
think because you know it will restart I
think I think maybe not maybe not but
whatever
uh
now if I don't save now it will restart
right away where we've just finished the
mission I would assume
right I don't have to
have to save because I'm I'm hoping we
hear the dialogue again
[Music]
oh what
what I what are those oh
the how do I is this like
the more yellow the dot is the more
completed it is
click load game
oh
oh yeah that was fine that's fine okay
all guys over that's the one
[Music]
loaded okay
I'm gonna like that [\h__\h] I'm gonna
comment and share it yes girl
cute cute duck lips yeah cute
peace peace girl
ew why why didn't we switch to him why
when eyesore go back to the girl
go back
and go see that [\h__\h]
I'm sorry I interrupted you
hey what up Michael hey man listen I got
an interesting opportunity for you
acquaintance of Daves an FIB contact are
you joking relax the guy's private
sector very wealthy could be lucrative
why don't you meet him and see what you
think
all right all right yeah yeah I think
about it all right me and Trevor will be
there too I promise you it's a step up
for you a real opportunity
oh that barely was any more dialogue oh
well yeah I thought so
I thought so but still we did it you
know for the sake of Franklin because we
love Franklin
I love Michael we love their
interactions
yeah anybody home by the way
I'm guessing not because everybody hates
me for some reason
okay sweet
yeah well
you know you just have to invite some
people have some fun Michael
have a party or so
I'll read that
I can't read it it says something like
Amanda XX at the bottom
uh
it's really hard to read
oh oh I can drink oh great
us
the good stuff
um oh that went down smoothly
does that like give him exercise oh I
give some mom the yellow stuff whatever
that is
what's that
it's a yellow stuff
no Condes
God damn it stamina
all right guys thank you very much for
watching today we're gonna read some
super chats shouldn't be too many
um
it isn't it is not too many is it I hope
so because like I need to evaluate
whether I need a snack now or
um
letter
thank you guys for watching we did a lot
of progress again today a lot of good
shooting a lot of good snapping
hope you enjoyed it and uh I forgot what
we have tomorrow either
the mirrors tomorrow or German stream or
what are we doing tomorrow
you guys know you guys always know
what's up
German Channel tomorrow
oh
is it is it already Friday tomorrow oh
oh it is oh
I'm still like not 100 sure what to do
but I really need to make up my mind now
I'll make up my mind
soon
[Music]
um but I might take back my idea of
playing Luigi's Mansion there because
that'll be a whole series now I don't
think I want to start a whole series on
my German Channel
um more like you know
games
for like one stream only or so man
I will think a bit more I've been
thinking about it for days
can't make a decision but
I'll figure something out now let me
check
[Music]
um
I also need to go to an idol meeting so
I'll definitely do that the question is
will I come back with food
or not
foreign
do you
yes okay it's really not much so I think
I don't need a snack
but I will go denial meeting
okay see you in my office
in a second
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I'm back
have you guys been behaving
[Music]
foreign
loud as hell
hello
let me fix chat
[Music]
I'm too big
perfect
perfect right
seems about right
I could be small without being small
[Music]
hello
you hear me
Compact and jariable oh no no no don't
you dare put me into a jar no no I'm
gonna break out
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
you cannot contain
these hips you know that
okay
and we're gonna read two chapters
[Music]
I already have it open just need a
thumbnail
a bigger jar
hahaha
no
doesn't matter how big the jar is
I'm not containable
I'm not terrible
I can't do you like to party no I don't
like to party
I mean I guess it really depends on what
kind of party but the the general idea
of what a party is that's not really my
thing no
yeah break them with like a booty attack
oh my God I got uh so many messages what
the [\h__\h]
okay
oh oh
my choreographer Kiana joins the do you
challenge let me see let me see it
see
oh beautiful
beautiful
hand movements how it's actually
supposed to look like
yeah so if you take anyone for reference
you should probably take her for
reference I'm gonna retweet it
this is more more like it
Fair bit of an advantage yeah
real hands
yeah that's pretty sick oh what is this
oh
oh it's so cute but I guess it's seen
from my GTA stream
it's so cute though
thank you for the fan art Apple Blossom
tea
it's when you guys told me to press F
and I
where at the hand of the chicken is an F
and you're laughing like evil evil
chicken
[Laughter]
like what the [\h__\h]
why would you do this to me
[Music]
amazing
um
oh my God
oh
um some some good stuff
it's happening
um
some good stuff and some bad stuff
I mean not really bad but the
disappointing stuff
but also some good stuff oh well
okay okay
uh-huh
all right tell it to a strike I can't
Secret
these are informations that I may not
share with anybody
unfortunately
even if I wanted to
but one of those things you will find
out eventually at least
um
all right keep your secret I will for
now
for now
info from the FIB you know fyb now just
feels so normal like the default
it sounds like nothing's wrong with that
it's not FBI it's fib
I'm gonna go for this one today this
classic
what is that double or let's see
there you go now it should be once
[Laughter]
because what you learned kiwawa
[Music]
it's all amazing incredible song oh
thank you why thank you
thank you
do you like it
do you like it imagine that yako saying
that I think he said something like that
before
a thank you to right Ghana
thank you for listening to my song I
hope you're having it on repeat or
listening to it at least a couple times
per day but I think
yeah very supportive chickens all
I trust you
no ah wait why do you think of Yahoo
that's not Yago yeah yeah I think that
was from the Nintendo Direct
um did you did you like it
well I guess yagu could say that the
same way
um
anyway thank you
for
me
thank you for another incredible
Masterpiece that I can listen to Forever
Chihuahua I absolutely love every single
thing about it so much the song is a
definition of perfection I'll definitely
be streaming it non-stop like my life
depends on it oh
thank you
as I told you you follow my orders
perfect
wouldn't ask for anything else
thank you for being such a delinquent is
that the right word chicken delinquent
um
or is that the opposite of what I'm
trying to say
devoted
a diligent diligent that's the one I was
looking for delinquent is the opposite
huh
Dylan said that sounds very similar
ah yes diligent
I knew there was something wrong I heard
that in a in a bad sense before sorry
that's not what I mean you're diligent
not delinquent no no thank you unknown
kitchen
[Music]
once again an amazing bagger of a song
and something about those outfits and
those dance moves none of us are going
to survive above for knee life are we
think you will you can't be dropping
moves like this and expect Tiny Bird
Hearts to make it from inside oh
I think yeah everything
was put in place perfectly and Polished
nicely The Outfits worked better than I
even anticipated with this music video I
was just hoping to kind of
drowned out the
fast food theme out of my body
and yeah who would have known that just
changing the colors a little bit and
removing
some details
would be helpful enough
will there be another GTA stream yeah
yeah I'm actually
not against finishing it
I think so far it's been on the horizon
it's just a long game but it's not a
first for me I finished really long
games before
um
gonna break YouTube I laugh and breaking
YouTube since my debut
oh
you already say that before you go good
night
I'm already past where many stopped
nice
another one for the boasting bag
I finished this game and you did and I
finished this game and you did
[Music]
game finisher I literally like entered
I snapped your necks and like you're
finished
I win
Halloween no thank you I I
that was my choice
sometimes I will make a choice for the
sake of my own sanity
uh Islamic fellow thank you on the binky
not one but two chiaras cute and
adorable scary and cool the singing the
dancing the Envy the Phoenix's
absolutely back here 20 out of 10. thank
you thank you yeah I'm really happy I
included two kiwabas because that makes
it even more powerful and the impact is
actually pretty strong too once you see
them together
oh once once uh black Kiara reaches out
her hand to White Kiana and wants to
dance together
um
that's like really hype moment
pretty good at Elden ring
I don't know about that hmm
it was just really frustrating for me
and really pressuring because at that
time that game
brought in just so much backseating
that's
in theory it's fine but just even for me
that was I don't know it was it was
different from usual I'm used to to back
sitting but that one was different from
usual
um
[Music]
brings out the worst of people
oh yeah a band somewhere oh yeah wasn't
it like stop dodging or rolling yourself
I I banned that word wait is it so bad
I think it's not bad anymore because you
guys are able to ride it
oh that made me so mad
yeah it was really annoying that was so
annoying
um
stop rolling
oh my God anyway spicy mayo chicken
recipe
is insanely good Kiana pop adds its
finest the monochrome twins are so spicy
I wonder what the inspiration was to do
black and white Chihuahuas plus how you
coordinated the outfit coloring like I
had some pink blackhead a little orange
both had the same socks well I think I
talked already quite a bit about it but
um
yeah first I I just said I wanted them
to be you know black and white and
the thing is for the black one it was
kind of easy to make the main color
black and then the rest white but for
turning
um the other Chihuahua into white
I didn't quite know like what to do with
the contrast
but then just as a test we used pink and
it actually looked pretty cute kind of
like I don't like almost oh so
yeah
actually it worked out pretty well and
the socks as I said I tried giving them
different socks giving the black Kiana
black socks but
that was too much that looked like it
was just too much same with the sleeves
um
very simple yeah it was pretty say so um
like especially in the scenes where a
lot of like light surrounds the white
kiwawa
she looks like an angel
yeah it's just a glow around her so
pretty
so pretty
angelic
anyway thank you Trevor D I'm sorry for
hating so much on travel today it's not
you it's not about you okay obviously
you are not such a [\h__\h] [\h__\h] so
we all know that thank you Trevor G for
suffering through it
hola
Navidad for the thinking you're nothing
out of the park again Kiana I don't
listen to Kpop but maybe I should
because I'm in love with do you oh
Danielle maybe you should the Corey I
was captivating the visuals are the
treat and the song itself gives me
shivers it's so damn good top three
original for sure thank you
I'm happy to hear that yeah
K-pop is just insanely catchy you can
really not do much about it it's just so
catchy it's gonna catch you no matter
what you do no matter what you listen to
normally it's okay
it has that
that recipe for
catching people
no matter what you are normal taste is
stuck in my head nice
please help yourself by listening to it
on YouTube or on the streaming service
me
wow
what are you listening to now I like
eating yeah itsy and um
I mean izone doesn't exist anymore
well that's sad but twice definitely
um
I I mean I like their songs
they're very catchy as a group I'm not
so like interested but the songs are
great
if it isn't smoothie hi what are you
doing saying hi to Mommy
this movie was so kind today to let me
use her as a pillow for like an hour
um so soft of course I don't put my
whole weight on her
there's just partially and she doesn't
mind
yeah so soft it's the best thing ever
wannabe wanna be a good song
number nine oh I remember that one
Lumina luminous I think I heard it I
think
Chong is gonna let you use her as a
pillow she will but actually not as
long
a smoothie like smoothie will even fall
asleep while I'm using her as a pillow
you know it's just a little weirdo she
likes
you know my attention and my cuddles and
my love but she doesn't quite admit it
that's the problem that we have
I know she likes it though because she
always purrs she she loves me when we
know this thing when we when we blink at
each other slowly
you know stuff like that she loves me I
know it like she wouldn't share the bed
with me if she didn't like me she would
try to be distant but she doesn't try to
be the older that [\h__\h] there was one
thing that I noticed you know I talked
about that new shelf thingy that I have
but she was like putting her paw through
a tiny gap of the drawer and then she
was like continuously dragging out the
things in there and then I looked at it
closely yesterday and I see scratch
marks from like
um there's like a a white paint coat on
that thing
and yeah seems like
cheese who's very aggressive in her ways
on the edge of the drawer you know
on the top
ah it's okay
I'm not mad
she left her Mark how do you know it was
drunk because I was watching her I have
like I have proof
you've got video of her doing that
watching her doing that is really
amusing and cute
but then seeing the aftermath
um
I forget because she is cute
ah where was I oh yeah looking for the
top tanks
afternoon oh thank you for the rest of
the chat nice to see you
uh truly epic song and envying your hips
don't deceive I missed my chance to send
you my thanks for being with you for two
years with your first karaoke thank you
for everything you've done
I try to sneak in at work and make sure
to send a message so you know I still
looks like yeah thank you
it felt like it's been quite a while
this one
oh
a bunch this movie says hi too smoothie
also misses you
thanks for saying hi
and I hope work is not too busy not too
stressful I wish you all the best thank
you for your support and for thinking of
me not forgetting about me
um
at work
yeah glad you liked the song too
Cruz thanks for the pinky I love all
your other songs and listen to them
almost daily on commutes while at the
gym and this one is no different for the
longest time heart Challenger has been
my favorite for all of her life
Originals oh really
I think it's my challenge keep it up oh
damn oh I'm happy to hear
you know whenever someone says heart
challenges their favorite that looks
very happy
um
I think to you is however a better song
to listen to at the gym
then uh heart challenger but I mean I
guess hard challenge or challenges your
heart rate when you work out so
it is it is actually
surprisingly fitting
but I hope your heart rate is not too
challenged in general
and can take up on that hard challenge
[Music]
the Pooh Bear is gonna come and take the
honey container away from us now hi hi
now
hide it
he's coming I hear him done done
done really heavy footsteps
dipping into the honey container oh no
we can't let it do it
hide the Honey hi honey no hide the
honey
oh yeah Sparks
Sparks very good spikes is a banger too
[Music]
I'm thinking for the words of a chat wow
do you love do you because I sure do
yeah I'm happy to hear that I love the
YouTube for the first moment I heard it
I knew holy [\h__\h] this is a banger
the like that evening when I heard it
you know I I didn't want to listen to it
like endlessly because you know I was
with banana so I didn't want to ignore
her or anything
but I had to listen to it at least a
couple times because
the thought of me being able to sing a
song like that made me so happy
yeah
Elena I don't know she was bopping and
enjoying it well I don't remember like a
specific comment about it
and oh thank you and miniature painting
to attend your song Always motivates me
and very
um love heart message thank you thank
you
I'm glad you like my songs I want to
make more music please continue
supporting me
please
thank you for listening
and joining the marathon as well thank
you soon
[Music]
lyrics
pinky love it oh I don't even have to
ask you how you're already giving me the
answer
I love it too thank you so much
Jacks also for the pinky thank you very
much yeah you're dancing in the enemy
was so important so the best in her life
to be honest you rocked at stage 100
thank you
dancing I would like to say is my
specialty but the other girls
do
seem to keep up pretty well surprisingly
they're all
surprisingly talented
yeah
so we need to need to stand out a bit
more it's quite um difficult but
I think Kiana will be helpful
in the future as well to make some sick
choreography so that I I can stand out
continue standing out
[Music]
positively
hopefully
I mean I can't do ballet and like I
don't know
certain things I I can't do because like
I I learned
I had like dance classes but those were
like
um
specifically
like those kind of like choreography
style dances that I did for like I don't
know hinotoni and heart Challenger and
that style you know so I didn't I didn't
never learn
like you know classic dance or ballet or
breakdance or what what whatever I never
took like hip-hop dancing classes or any
kind of western style dance class
um
so in that since Bae would probably know
more stuff than I I would say but I
don't really know I've never really
talked with her about it deeply but yeah
yeah Aki has belly dancing going for her
that's really cool
you still need to need Cali to teach you
the ones oh yeah because I don't even
know how to
I mean roughly hmm roughly I do
a Mr Freddy dance somehow but I'm gonna
watch it soon what do you mean you
missed it did you watch the music video
do you how did you not watch it yet you
have to also my shorts my YouTube short
that I uploaded yesterday
hmm
I can't breathe
yeah also yeah it's up there on the top
right as well but you should watch it
directly on YouTube
what short my YouTube short I posted
about it on Twitter too
it's on my channel
[Music]
thank you mental Yeti thank you
yeah I love it it really feels like your
style oh The Sassy energetic smug Joe we
love so excited to play this on repeat
and hopefully see you dancing live I
don't get to watch it live much and more
of a vlog game because you work hours oh
yeah but always cheering you on
I feel like even for your workouts no
I I start streaming
around the end the usual end of the work
day for Europe so
I would hope that out of everybody I
should be you know the best to watch but
maybe you have like an evening shift or
so who knows yeah
well then I can't do really much more
for you
but I hope you can catch as many streams
as possible
[Music]
thank you so much for supporting and I
do agree it seems like my style and
you're not the only one who said that
and I'm happy you think so I want to do
more like that but I also don't want to
repeat myself too much so I will try to
you know squeezing some other genres so
everybody can enjoy kiwaba singing but I
do want to go back
every now and then to like Kpop style
and oh my God actually
I'll tell you guys
I got into talking
with the lyric writer from do you
and she told me that she and Johnny
wrote The Melody
they have like written made a lot of
songs in cooperation with like a lot of
Kpop producers
like not like like super famous ones I
would I would assume was saying because
those samples I was sent I didn't hear
before
um but then yeah she sent me some
samples and she's like
um
I I can I can reach these people for you
if you wanna and that's perfect because
like I was trying to get a hold of more
like K-pop style producers or even you
know just like western music which is
like at this point pretty much the same
K-pop is trying to be very much like
western music like pop music so I was
just trying to get into that genre but
like really hard to find producers that
are in my reach and answer or actually
credit it so I know who is the [\h__\h]
producer
yeah and then those samples are [\h__\h]
perfect I was like holy [\h__\h] I will
definitely keep in touch
yeah I got some good options now I think
ah which made me so excited last night
I was like listening to a lot of samples
and then
already had so many ideas for album
songs
so excited so motivated
foreign
[Music]
hmm foreign
I'm really grateful for that
um
so
uh
thank you for the pinky
thank you for blessing us with your new
song it's an absolute Bop the Trap was
amazing and really gets the blood
thumping oh
do you flew instantly to my playlist
just hope this doesn't work as a getaway
drug for Kpop addiction a gateway drug
ah
if you want it
ask yourself do you want it is that what
you want is that what you desire
it's good music it's really high
production value music I would say
um do you
do you
it's your choice I'll leave it to you
deeply but for now you're also welcomed
you just listen to my music
maybe that's what you actually meant
anyway with K-pop quinoa plump hmm
thank you
soon
for the red super chat I haven't been
able to get do you out of my head since
the release
Korea was especially spicy and it got me
tapping my foot along to the beat oh
which is a horrible thing to do while
driving but I can't help it well then
you have to tap with your fingers
also I'm sorry to enter dark you always
now my Oshi oh I did want to ask you
guys like on Twitter
which Chihuahua is your favorite and
like have pictures
of them and then make a although uh I
can only do a poll with pictures on on
YouTube Community though I think so
maybe I'll do it there don't make me
choose
I thought that black chihuahua would be
so cool and I would like her the most
but the white koala the pink is just so
cute and she works so well and all the
bright scenes I just love I just love
let me know what to say so wow because
that reflects me the most I would say
but very cool
but you know why kiwawa
just looks so ah look at her look at her
just look at her
my God
look at her
my God oh my God she's got something
special about her
she's got that glow orange
ah stop it stop
cute
pretty cute thing to say guys image
sticky thank you
[Music]
ah
okay I think Lala is the one you show
off to your mommy
it's all the same lovely Kiana
love hate all the same
black white oh same if you know play the
game I like that but beside no one can
fight the feeling and I won't cry
and every sticky did I give you a kiss
if not here it comes mwah
Optimus Prime thank you Nathan cotton
thank you for the pinky loved the new
song and then beat Angel finally I kind
of forgot you were even singing a song
the first watch through until the end
what I was too captivated by your sick
dance moves what
what do you mean you forgot I was
singing you forgot you thought it was
just like
like a random singer like just you know
any track and I'm just dancing along
maybe that's how good it was
it's so good it doesn't it doesn't sound
like a whole lifestyle it could be like
any song and that maybe sounds negative
but for me in that case it sounds
positive because I wanted it to be like
I wanted it to have mainstream appeal
um
so maybe that's good but maybe without
real just really also just speaks for
the for the dance moves fact
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat I'm in
awe of this amazing collab of talent
you're singing dance in The Courier
lyrics music and MV all combined into an
addictive result yes yes yes I'm glad
you were able to put together such an
amazing team I can't stop listening and
look forward to more originals thank you
see if you want a heist to go perfectly
well it might be worth investing into a
full
High skill team don't cheap out you know
on anything
go high skill for everything
treat yourself sometimes to a high
quality Heist or a high quality song
yeah
my way of thinking
oh
what
humanar I've already completed the
remodeling of the do you in Korean
versus I want someone to sing hey where
is it where can I find it
where where where where where
where where
I want to try
I want to try yeah Korean lyrics I
suppose
are you a lyric writer
yeah that they have experience
I want to see
I haven't uploaded it don't
do it immediately
now
I need it now
[Music]
I'm waiting
waiting
just gonna wait here
hey what do you mean I'm looking for
someone to say just give me the lyrics I
will sing it
Lisa do you in Korean right
I was singing
no pressure
I'll sing it
how should you send it I don't know if
there's like a like an online memo
oh is this so cute Among Us um account
posted
and Among Us Amelia with cookies what
the [\h__\h] is so cute
what the hell
that's so cute
oh paste bin yeah yeah yeah I think that
would work
verified oh there is a bit alignment
we can figure it out
ah you mean like a singer to
help me figure out how to sing it no I
can figure it out I could try and figure
it out myself
I almost unlocked all of Amy's clothes
and Among Us can you tell me like how
much work it is like how much time it
takes because I don't I don't need
everything but a few things would be
nice
and can you like choose what you're
getting or is it like randomized any any
whole live related items
just a couple would be nice for the
Stream
there's a tree
an unlock tree oh
you pick a path
yeah no I mean it costs money but I I
have a I get a cold but then I still
have to unlock it
100 300 points per game so about 10 to
15 games for one item or for One path
and I mean I guess we're playing it as
members so it should be fun
we can play like for a couple hours
two hours for the Army skin okay that's
good enough for me although Ami will be
in the collab if I dress up as almond
and there's two armies Maybe
hmm hmm maybe I'll go for a Japanese
member
instead
let me go for like
[Music]
fake Gosling it scares me
I'm just considering the fact that I'm
it might get her own outfit and I have
the plenty of time I can get more
5 out of 10 this do you have 5 out of
10k9 so keep going keep going keep it up
guys
too [\h__\h] I need pecula
maybe a mix of pecula and fubuki you can
watch however you want after all
right how's the how's the Korean lyrics
going
where are they
uh Korean bro there's a there's a thing
called paste bin
and then that way I think you can send
it to me
oh
[Music]
on Twitter Maybe
Maybe lyrics of soil lyrics
[Music]
please send me the lyrics
Twitter
oh
[Music]
you can use
ah I don't understand English but I made
it by using a translator dictionary oh
oh as long as you speak Korean then it
should be pretty good
in
oh it's uh it separated the word paste
bin
in paste blah blah blah in
it's paste bin
I Can Read Super chats well
well
I'm excited and I want it now
so I'm holding it was hospice
do you do you have the super chattels
and the the lyrics
I want to sing it now
[Music]
foreign
don't
feel pressured
foreign
[Laughter]
how can I forget about it now
hahaha
no no I know you saw
yourself
okay yeah it's okay okay
my disappointment is immeasurable just
kidding
okay well I guess not then
back to my super chats I'm waiting for
it
I'm waiting
but thank you for answering to my
request and so fast as well so speedy
thank you for answering my request
s
[Music]
foreign
that had to be said because I think I
came across very scary right now
okay next up hmm
yeah oh wow let them rest but if they're
if they're here
and wake them up they choose to be here
I'm not keeping them awake it's their
choice
anyway they're adjusting okay I can wait
I can't really but I will
no thank you so much Reynard for the red
super chat another kiss in case I forgot
Nepal donkey
donkey
[Music]
intimidating but still cute thank you
I'm not like this in a restaurant no not
at all I'm very patient and sweet and I
compliment the the food a lot
when I like what I'm eating I go like oh
oh my God this is so good oh my God I
love it
I'm very open with my feelings towards
food
anyway not Lou thank you for the recipe
oh that was when I was singing the speed
version which is actually pretty good
doing you on speed not so bad sounds
pretty good
did sound pretty good didn't it thank
you
723 Maps
Maxwell the first time
or rice pieces thank you for two pinkies
the red ones
I gotta live in the past month or so I
managed to get my first post College job
and this subject comes from my first
paycheck oh nice you graduated from
college congratulations and you got a
job nice too your streams have kept me
entertained during the day during my
final years of college
um
and they have continued to do so a while
I'm on the computer at work so here's
100 US dollars as a late two year
anniversary gift another 100 as an
extremely late birthday gift also
congrats on your new song and MV release
through you as a banger that would send
another 100 for that but I need money to
eat that's understandable
much function
oh I'm so happy for you that you got a
job
I hope you like it I hope it's like
relatively chill it's nice that you are
on the computer at work because that
means you can continue watching kiwawa
even after getting a job
relatively smoothly hopefully like some
others do
um
thank you for being here still
yeah thank you soon
thank you so much for the love and
support yeah very convenient even yeah
if it's just a podcast still good enough
it's fun to have one while working I am
working
close to be working right now are you
working right now
and even extra
boss but you thought you were done with
anniversary super chats yeah I did
converts are two years of amazing
memories and fun content also thank you
for providing a push for me to get back
into art which I had stopped making for
a long time no problem you're welcome
you have helped me so much with my
backgrounds if it weren't for you I
would have not had this many backgrounds
because I don't think I would have
wanted to Commission
anyone else because like it was really
easy with you thank you so much
I even saw didn't you make the new
background for Dana ah I feel like the
people that I commissioned
uh very often are commissioned at some
point by other whole life members even
though like I found them like Spirit
snares the go-to logo person
and I'm good at uses unadun a lot these
days even though I don't get to use
unadun anymore
and then I see some members followed my
choreographer Kiana which makes me think
are they think
ing Cora of asking my choreography for
choreography
interesting
yeah I am
I mean fine it's not like
um jealous or anything no no no
I'm happy for you guys
just you should know where the priority
is yeah
that's the priority
give your love to me
first and foremost
I have an eye for talent
yeah
I do
I do it seems so
hmm
it seems so it really seems so
Cal is going to get your choreographer
is she though like I mean so far it's
not like she was lacking choreography
she's she's been learning choreography I
think like probably in person which is
actually better
then doing it the way that I do it like
she has some I guess some choreographer
that
they get for her in Japan
but but
um yeah I
I can't have an in-person choreographer
so that I go with
I go with Kiana and I learn it through
the video I I think like normally the
best choice would be to learn it in
person and if you have that choice then
you should go for that
um
she said she wants to
did she
did she when did she say that where did
she say that she said she wants to
commission my choreographer really
are you sure about that
interesting
fine fine with me
she did
I'm fine with me
sure
you know it's just like when you find a
[\h__\h] diamond
that you're so happy with
Hearts to give it away
it's my diamonds
I looked so hard for these diamonds
it was difficult to find these diamonds
but I was so proud to have them
the wondering everyone wants to one ring
power
he had a Golem
my diamonds
my precious
precious Kiana
are you precious Spirits now
well I already lost the spirit snow like
so he's already done so much work for
others
I mean he's still obviously will do work
for me but no
purple
a precious
I'm warming
ah
I wanna know what these people think
about me being like Gollum to them
I won't lose them nah nah never
also I'm not like possessive it's not
like I tell them you can't work with
anybody else
it's good for them that they're able to
find more work
get that money get that cash
go get it
I'm happy for you
get that though yeah baby
the bag get the bag
oh
God
oh no no no no no I understand why Colin
freaked you out Colin freaks me out
still to this day
um don't worry I'm still kiwawa
uh anyway where's my lyrics huh just
kidding
just kidding I'll be waiting just let me
know
where was I here
I don't know
and then you need to chat thank you for
the pinky do you use a song I really do
love a lot I'm so happy that you have
such a banger K-Pop song in your
portfolio now the dance and then being
the whole vibe of the song is great it
fits you so much thank you I admire how
much work and thought went to into it
went into it I can't read anymore well
done thank you
yeah I have a K-Pop song in my portfolio
I wish I had it a bit earlier because I
really really really really really was
planning and was hoping to sing it at
um popcorn
I was planning for it because I thought
I would be able to release
it like ever like right before or if it
had to be on the day or so
whatever I just wanted to release it in
time so I could sing it there but it
didn't work out so that was a bit
unfortunate I was a bit sad about that
but I have other Banger songs and then
I was able to sing a twice song instead
which I normally
you know is a bit difficult in my
streams
I'm glad you guys like the song yeah
better
that it came out at all then it doesn't
come out at all
foreign
who knows it might actually get clipped
it might actually get clipped for you
the lyric writer
no idea what's going on huh
I'm sorry Mia Mian don't worry about it
I'm waiting I'm waiting
um where was I oh yeah
eight five three six times
[Music]
version my beloved
I'm guessing this was not the slow one
but um
the the one with the voice changes oh no
no no that was terrible
you guys kind of asked for it so I take
no complaints thank you Skye I'm a tea
thank you thank you for the pinky
pacifier let's go yeah we had a baby
bubble bubble version
thank you for being so supportive of it
you only have laundry done kitchen L
John
91.
thank you Christy thank you for the
pinky comments on the Amazing song
release time so I'm really a big fan of
you taking the style of real life pop
and beans and bringing them to the V
tubing space feels very fresh thank you
hope you're able to keep putting out
bangers in the future thank you yeah
actually
you know
um the background ideas a lot of them
came from my suggestions
made them into reality
I I knew I wanted like big polished
clean spaces and
hmm
yeah some slow motion scenes like that
one
and then the running slow motion scene
is one of my favorites so I said I want
to run in slow motion during that very
exact moment I feel like that would fit
so well and it did fit so well
yeah
I think you know
kanawuru does all the heavy lifting for
making a video but I think I'm also a
good director
yeah
because this is like exactly
exactly what I imagined hmm
oh the throne was not my idea
um prone was
I didn't I didn't ask for throne but I
deserve a throne let's be real
um
thank you
I love the new song do you do you do you
do you thank you Nick
how you doing name thank you for coming
by and supporting me
down ah there you are
super chat but choo choo choo back to
you thank you so much
[Music]
Pinky
yes yes please wait it will take a while
but I'll do my best thank you TT for the
pinky
Sapphire kitten Duncan growl Danke
Schoen flaming pants Duncan
I am done
nice
thank you everybody
four
all the support today once again
tomorrow
I'll see you I guess on my German
Channel and maybe I'll upload another
short if it gets ready on time who knows
um
uh my my throat hurts so I am happy
huh
it's super enchant no [\h__\h] I can't my
throat really hurts I'm like really weak
but remind me next time thank you
what's your German Channel
um if you go to my to this channel
um it's in the related channels
in the list
or you just look up
German Channel I think that should do
the trick as well
yeah yeah
okay okay oh my God oh my God Christina
[Music]
I didn't want to be like that
um
[Music]
I'm traumatized
it's funny though I guess it's funny
oh
yeah okay
I'm gonna go now
do you
love kiwawa
yes yes
right
do you plan on
coming to see me tomorrow on my German
Channel
say yes just say yes
yes yes
do you until then
want to continue streaming my songs on
YouTube and Spotify
Etc
do you do you do you do you do you
please do please don't we're over 500k
now we're gonna get to 1 million
sometimes sometime
one million banger
foreign
[Music]
I think so too it's my best performing
song yeah it might be
but I don't really know anymore how well
hinotori did
but I'm happy it's doing so well really
really happy
that's it bye bye bye bye bye
bye-bye good night guys
uh tomorrow is I think also Pico Park
goes out one day later that might be one
day later that's the one I had wrong
yeah that's that's the one so it's only
German Channel tomorrow wait [\h__\h] it's
from oh oh have an important appointment
tomorrow
okay okay
[Music]
foreign