[Music]
oh that that wasn't too bad actually
that was a pretty decent batter
oh yeah i mean if you want it's not like
i want to hear it you can if you'd like
you know what uh i know why you like the
word god so much
why because if you turn it around it
means hug and i know you love my hugs
that's why every time you say god you're
like
yelling uh out like please you gotta hug
me
huh i mean that's a pretty that's that's
a very
how shall i say it's a controversial
theory that you've got going i don't see
everyone agreeing with it per se
all right man i mean look
look believe what you want believe what
you want god is simply a sound i make
when i when i drink something here look
you can listen to this
ah it's just it's literally just an
instinct okay
so you know you can you can keep your
conspiracy theories
and whatnot who am i to crush your
dreams chiara
who might accept your dreams you could
never crush my dreams you are my dream
what all right well
it's been a minute since we collabed
yeah a long time
also you have a typo in the title i do
yeah oh there is really only one s huh
sorry i was
scrambling a little bit here let me go
ahead and fix it hold on
i'm no problem obviously
english is not the the first language in
the underworld is it
it's not it's underworldy and people
seem to forget that i might be
fluent in english speak on the world the
end for me let me hear how it sounds
i will but honestly causatory you're not
gonna understa you're not gonna even be
able to hear it
to be honest it's on a frequency that is
un unparcelable but you better should be
able to hear high frequencies
it's not a high frequency kiara it's a
low frequency
oh okay okay okay i can see that yeah
but
what if i
[Music]
do this does this sound someone like
this sounds nothing like that
kusa tony stop making fun of my people
you know actually um the other day i
don't know if you saw it
like oh my god i played diablo 2
resurrected on my channel right
oh yeah that looks sick yeah it kind of
reminded me of you sometimes because you
know diablo the devil
doesn't seem too far apart yeah i love
diabolo it's a great game
did you play it no i watched i watched a
bunch of play-throughs back in the day
oh my god i feel like it would be
something you would like even though
it's like an
rpg but i don't know yeah maybe maybe
i'll give it a shot i always thought it
looked interesting but
never really got around to it that's how
it goes with all the games that i play
here we are mm-hmm yeah speaking of
games
we're playing this game this is the game
that we decided to put hold on
we will play it takes two starting from
next week probably yes
yes we will start that game next week uh
things didn't go according to plan just
don't worry about it we're gonna do it
next time
so for now let's just play some freaking
games
yeah we never played this one before
together right nope
i played it with a bunch of other people
would never review now i played it with
watson before but that was it so we've
never really quite
tackled this game together this this
journey
i don't really know what game we should
play to be honest i mean half of them i
don't know how to play we should start
without
for connect thingy to get into like a
nostalgic mood you know oh
you mean okay yeah the they changed the
name of it
here because they they haven't changed
the name connect four
yeah and now it's it's something else
let me see if i can
even locate a four in a row uh there
yeah that's what it is
left left left left left left okay
way left uh
there it is 400 here we go
yeah four in a row what to do last time
i remember
how aggressive you were playing that in
a way out yeah well it's just because
i mean even i could i need you children
to be very quiet right now so the only
reason that i
like got that angry you have to hear me
out it's just such a simple game
and everyone here knows that i just i'm
not very
into the i'm not good at games well this
game is so simple it just really hurt me
to be unable to do it
i have to be vulnerable with you all for
today i kind of get that i understand
that
yeah anyway i'm definitely going to run
this
kiara is in control this is going to be
a quickie
no no i see what you're trying to build
i see that
uh-huh i'm gonna be i'm gonna have such
a large brain about this
we'll see about it i love the music
there is that a banjo
yeah i mean kind of sounds yeah it's
very calming
hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on
hold on
let me see twice your favorite number
two this should be one of your favorite
games yeah i know
[Music]
interesting none of us seem to have a
strategy
no i don't think that this game should
be played with strategy i think that's
uh a fool's errand i don't think that'll
work for anyone
you just gotta kind of go in blind
[Music]
we made a pretty pattern you made a
pretty pattern there
yeah it does look kind of nice i'd want
it on a quilt
oh yeah should i make you a quilt
no i'm i'm good thank you i'm absolutely
fine
[Music]
i don't know
oh no no no no no no come on sorry just
let me
not happening just let me why are we
ignoring the left side completely
i don't know
hey
so have you been feeling lonely these
days ever since i left i hope not
are you trying to distract me from the
game i'm just trying to do the small
talk
okay well it's fine
yay i got one win
of course of course there has to be one
more i have to lose at least
once yes
it's the prophecy um to answer your
question
i guess uh i don't know i'm pretty much
used to just
in on my own but i would be lying if i
were to say that i do not
that i that i do not miss our
interactions
[Music]
by the way yeah
yeah i miss you too
miss you
yeah i that i mean yeah
that that's those are normal feelings
man
but it's not like it's not like we're
not gonna be able to hang out anymore or
anything
you know um
we can't lean hang on virtually like
that that's the good thing about being a
virtual youtuber
yeah exactly oh no
oh wait no why'd i do that ah
interesting i don't know why you did
that
[Music]
i told you i boned myself it's
it's fine i didn't deserve that win
it's okay i didn't i didn't why not we
were we were chatting
no i i messed i messed up it's fine you
just you messed up but you won
i mean yeah yeah it doesn't it doesn't
feel good
we'll play again best best two out of
three i mean well technically that is
two out of three best
three out of five yeah why am i going
first why are you not going first
well we're both ladies ah that's true
we should both just throw them in at the
same time yeah why not
just play high speed high speed four in
a row wait no
gosh
maybe not maybe not maybe not
[Music]
[Applause]
how's the weather been over there
recently
in the underworld it's been whatever
you know i mean i don't really go
outside much these days to be completely
honest
yeah there's not a lot just not enough
time to do so i guess
not enough motivation you feel me
[Music]
but didn't isn't spring nights in the
underworld
yeah it's pretty nice and i went out a
bit for that but then it immediately got
hot again
so what can you do
i've got sharp eyes just like you my
bird friends
i don't know hold on
hold on a minute
by the way here it has been like really
crazy because in april we get like
really crazy weather
like it snows on one day and then it's
it's super sunny then it's super warm
rainy and then snows again even though
like like in in march and all that it
would never snow but in april suddenly
it started snowing
hey it's very strange i do not envy the
weather there
i prefer every year it's the same
uh where should i put it
i gotta see what you could do
it's hard to talk while playing this
game isn't it kissatory
dude do you see how it feels to just not
throw it down i i was like
it awakens something inside of you and
you can't win this game would you like
to try again um
now okay well this part of me wants to
but the other part says better or not i
always continue losing
it's up to you next game is up to you
kusatori what would you like to play
i would like to play dots and boxes oh
um you got to tell me okay you got to
tell me how to play that
left left left it's like oh that's next
dots and and boxes oh i know this one
okay you know i had to play it i think
me and amelia played it but
let me see oh because i think i thought
amelia had to play it i think and i
totally owned her because she didn't
know how to play it i think i think oh
well then you may probably win this one
yeah that's probably why she
was then trying to play it with you but
oh my god i don't remember
quite well maybe we didn't play this
actually just kidding we didn't play
this game
but i've played it before in in the real
world so
okay i see
basically but you know you know the
basic like idea of it right
yeah you're supposed to if you make a
box then you can
take control of the area that you put in
the box that's your color yeah
the the box that you close the last uh
the last uh line that you will
draw that's your box if you close it
with the last line
oh i see
so like what you just did i see i
exactly okay that makes sense i thought
it all had to be your color that's fine
no problem you used to get another move
oh wait oh yeah i got another oh my god
yeah once you've
uh closed one box you can close another
box i see
okay i'm i'm pinky
oh wait oh i got enough sorry i'm so
stupid what the hell
you're distracting me no i'm not
so happy to like be with you again yeah
that's cool
[Music]
it has been a minute to be talking about
anything i mean
well yesterday we all talked oh yeah
it's true we did we did all the time
that was nice finally like getting
together
with everyone again and we actually
really don't do that much
yeah it was cool i think it'll be
happening a lot more though you guys
because there's their stuff we're doing
stuff yeah
and we too are probably gonna be
collabing like every week
for at least one and a half months yeah
or even two months indeed i'm very
excited
yeah wait you're playing shadowverse
tomorrow right
uh-huh so actually i'm also playing
shadowverse again soon
and uh i don't know i'm really allowed
to say something about that dude i have
no clue
i'd like to i'd like people to know what
to look forward to
but let's just say that it's not a
coincidence that we're both picking up
shadowverse again
yeah exactly there are no coincidences
there
get ready
you you have uh understood the game i
think
kelly yeah this is a sneaky little game
but i'm starting to get the gist of it
this is the hard part now no not yet
not answer still see a lot of
possibilities and options
imagine yukio tournament no no
oh yes tournament between us would be
perfect
we definitely know what we were doing
yeah
100 percent
it's time
is yeah you don't know the yu-gi-oh song
actually no in my channel i always uh
was like never interested in
yu-gi-oh i was more of a if anything
pokemon type of
girl i see i see
[Music]
yeah well that's how the song goes
there's a part that goes
oh that's where that's from oh i
actually never knew but i keep on using
it
yeah wow that's a lot of different right
i feel like it's probably a lost cause
to be honest at this point
no matter what
you just uh need to find
uh well
i mean i feel like every line pretty
much is going to lead to you being able
to close it
so i mean yeah then you have to find
like the
oh i kind of okay no i got what you were
saying
oh i have to find the line that doesn't
lead to you making another box
oh yeah yeah yeah of course i was trying
to say something else but yeah
yeah yeah basically that is that is of
course the main thing
[Music]
ah
ha
ha okay i could
close that one but you won't
well ah
this is a bigger brain game than i
thought actually i'm quite impressed
yeah i think now we've reached the point
where
[Music]
i just have to
hmm
[Music]
i don't i don't see
an option anymore
ah
[Music]
thinking very hard uh i love my cool
stuff
about it but then yeah
wow i'm thinking you want to tell a
story oh gosh
if only there was any anything
interesting going on besides me just
always something interesting going on
with you i mean i guess
uh i don't know i i suppose that i could
actually tell about what
is going on next month because there's
no it's not like it's
it's meant to be kept by a secret by
anyone besides me i guess
but basically um
oh wow you found the line that would
lead to my demise
i think yeah yeah it would do so
um hmm what shall i do
uh anyway what was i gonna say
what were you what are you saying yeah i
know the thing that we're doing the
thing that we had the the little meeting
for and everything
um so yeah we're basically i know i was
talking we were talking about this for a
long time actually but um
we're gonna do a tabletop rpg
yeah so look forward to that we
basically set the date for a character
creation stream
so yeah i told my people the wrong thing
i was saying i was telling them that we
were creating
characters like yesterday but i got it
wrong
oh no yeah so that's that's what it is
um look forward to it uh
ye so basically hold on i think i'm
going to go ahead and just
start closing boxes because
just i don't know what else to do
this game is for people with large
craniums and i'm not one of them
so large crayons no large
i mean that too but just huge brains
that i don't have
oh yeah it's a shame but
yeah that's how it's got to be
it is how it is
okay my turn
[Music]
now
okay but the problem is here
i'm gonna get stopped but
i'm gonna do a smart move uh-huh
i think okay cool
so you start filling up
beautiful beautiful
this can only go for so long though
exactly
but you still have to start something
for me
i see i see so how do i keep it from
being that side
you can't keep it anymore i think yeah
it's impossible now
oh you're gonna make a snake
i see yeah you have no choice
thank you yup i shall close the game
[Music]
this is such an easy game and it's one
of the few ones that i usually win
at when i play with someone are you sure
easy is the right word
but the probably the following games
will we will both suck at let's choose
something we both will suck at
okay how about shooting range
shooting range okay yeah neither one of
us is very good with fps
so yay seven and seven seventeen
yay congratulations thank you
you got still three wins in a different
game so
it's true
oh i am pretty good at connecting my
favorite number after all i was just
under pressure because i was
who who's the guy the police officer
hank
we are allowed to say it huh or just say
what
the whole shadow very swing oh okay cool
sick yeah hold on wait you guys are
telling me
hang on vincent vincent yeah that's
it
okay yeah shadowverse we're making decks
and we're gonna
battle each other with them yeah so
first like you start
you roll you make a deck then i i think
in the following week
do the same
we end up uh like having a tournament
against each other but we also get
a coach both of us get a coach to help
us
like the professional shadowverse player
or something like that yeah it's gonna
help us out
so that's cool very exciting stuff and
then we're gonna compete
yeah we're gonna be at our fullest
potential
how does this work um point your
controller at the screen and press
oh you gotta take this thing can i not
play it with a pro controller
hold on you have to take out so you take
out the things from the controller the
little red and blue thingies all right
yeah and then you hold it like this hold
on wait why are you not sensing my oh
cause
uh wait can you not is this
where is the switch hang on oh wait i
flipped it around
so it's what if it's like wait no what
if i am i using this
not sure what my screen is still like i
am oh
dude where what the f
okay why do i have to point it to the
sky that's really strange
uh can i
put i have no control
joycon wait actually i'm not sure how to
play that
point point it at the screen and press z
r okay i did it
but it's not reacting to my joy condo
did you take your did you take the red
and blue thing
you already started oh wait no hold on
cancel cancel the game i can use my yeah
i can use my pro controller
[Music]
i'm not using the motion control thingy
i'm using
just the stick oh i see i see okay i
gotta actually
shoot for this
yeah why is that you fools here you
probably couldn't shoot yourself
skye partner i'm the fastest gun in our
stats
oh my god hands to the sky fastest gun
in our stats
[Music]
reach for the sky there's a snake in my
boot
ufo
yeah oh oh train coming
is my voice tired you mean the sheriff
the sheriff's always tired
the sheriff is solving crimes every day
putting away
criminals root rooting cowboy shootings
oh my god oh wow
you're a rascal oh you're a family i
thought i was you
i thought i was doing it
oh my god
i got a combo down there that was pretty
good
okay you got double that mean wow
it's all right i'm the fastest gun in
our statska no problem
okay how about we're playing
[Music]
bowling okay oh you know i'm gonna suck
at that game don't you know me too me
too
i suck at bowling in real life and i
will stuck it bowling in
uh this game did i have going for
what i do have you done bowling right
right right right right
right right top left left left
i don't have eyes never never played it
in in this game but i
suppose that will suck oh i don't don't
uh sell yourself
short right away because i enjoy sucking
and and bowling
show let's have the bumpers off not
support it oh my god do i okay i don't
think i can use this one is this does
this actually rely on moving the
the joystick yeah you got to be a real
bowler you see
they want to test your bowlings
okay let's do another one can you
actually not play it okay
yeah and not not not like this
okie dokie um how about matching it
tests your memory i lose it every time
so maybe
you could do that yeah cool because i
have no
shortcuts short time bird memory
okay so it's basically just a battle of
who has the worst memory well i guess
we'll find out won't we
first move i'll let you have the first
move um
not like it'll matter because you'll
definitely beat me okay two cards
after a match flip again sure why not
okay okay
here we go matching yeah
okay my memory let's find out
[Music]
okay good
yeah it makes me think of amelia right
yeah i thought of her immediately
[Music]
oh
it also reminds me of the pink panther
do you know that
yeah i know the pink panther oh oh wow
lucky
oh that's a match oh okay
[Music]
oh wow more oh yeah
oh i already forgot what you flipped
let's see ah
nice wow i can't believe i remembered
that
ah oh
[Music]
ah no idea
ah
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
yeah damn it fatso ah
ah damn it
oh god thank god okay
that's rough oh did we ever see a two
before
definitely not there maybe oh
ah
[Music]
oh i have my wife damn it this is still
reaping my
soul here
i thank you oh thank god okay but still
i don't i don't remember if was that i
don't remember what was here um
i don't know
i could have gotten that
[Applause]
that was because you love me i know yeah
sure
go ahead and say whatever you want
oh who won
[Laughter]
we must have a clear winner yes
memory strikes again
you must continue yes
you gotta train your memory yup
if your memory is so bad then how do you
remember all the lyrics
because they're different they're
they're burned into my brain
oh they're special ouch yeah
it's painful
yup
[Music]
oh something new
ah nice okay
f ah wait i just saw seven somewhere
[\h__\h]
god damn it oh why would i do that
[Music]
no no no ah wait
oh that was in the very beginning i knew
that was a five here
oh my god okay oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
oh four your favorite number oh damn it
[\h__\h] where was the four
of all the numbers i should have
remembered
where is your partner in crime
actually it's me of course
damn
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] are you alright
ah i don't know
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
this is gonna be another tie oh did you
see the other four yet
oh
[Music]
what is that eight here oh thank god
no you're lucky you're just freaking
lucky
you're lucky kusatori but it's fine i
knew i'd lose this one
[Music]
do you want to do it again i'll play a
different game and we can do a different
one
darts isn't that probably another one
with like motion control thingy like we
can see
that lets you do it joystick we can let
you see it but if
it won't let you then
shut up okay broken draw not supported
damn that's so dumb well let's see
do toy boxing yes let's go
lucia actually once killed me in that
game
oh yeah
shut up get out of my face you sillies
all right
i don't know how to play this game i
think i did it with amelia emilia won
oh just gotta remember
yeah cool i'm good at that in games but
not really this one
oh i see
watch me
[Laughter]
that was fun you can do it again okay
this is kind of something where you need
to read the other's mind
yeah you gotta ask my game it's not all
about anticipating
yeah it's intuition a women's intuition
yep all about anticipating i love to
[Music]
anticipate
[Laughter]
can't see me don't done up
i won that one damn it that was close so
i think it goes
better you want to try again
okay one more time okay
yeah yeah another shot
you got it sure i'm sure you'll you'll
beat me
i want to play i want to play it again
thank you
here we go
sorry oh
[Laughter]
oh
you managed to do it you anticipated i
was
i was very excited about that oh my god
each
each punch makes me go yeah
double or nothing you want to play again
yeah
okay next game
sure
i can't believe you can't stay so calm
by boxing
yup i mean it's it just has to do with
my training
that's all you have
hockey looks fun okay i think that
should be possible with pro controller
sure
let us play i think you just use the
stick yeah
oh we'll play a few let's
yeah it's quite fun i need an
air hockey uh table in my new apartment
yeah that'd be awesome oh wow i do that
to myself
it's nice it's super metaphorical
actually
wow i'm my number one worst enemy
everyone knows this
can i just go over to your side of the
oh nice wow
actually i'm just lucky at this point
yeah just just wait for me to do it
i'll end my own there we go by the self
here
just shave it to me
[Laughter]
it gives me so many points thank you
callie sure
you're like throwing hot [\h__\h] i do it
too
it's easier to hurt yourself in this
game actually hurts
my fans like to tell me since i like
throwing so much i should play baseball
or something like that whatever that was
oh yeah i could see that yeah
oh [\h__\h] free free
hey at least we're like on the same
level here in this game yeah
oh gosh if i don't score it on myself
i'm gonna be pissed
what if you don't yeah i'm very wrong
there
what do you mean nothing i better not
say it
okay if you say so he won by being super
defensive
you won by not playing the game that's
not true i was crying but i was really
hard to move with the stick dim
yeah it was pretty hard i think you
scored one
point the the point is i won against
myself
we now you lost you gave you gave me all
the points
i gave myself points wait no i gave you
the points but i i was on your team
want to play checkers uh how do you play
oh yes
okay i know how to play it that's super
fun it's called
it's called draughts on my side because
i got the european
version of the game
all right well let's do it then you just
jump over
another right but but
diagon diagonal now or
[Music]
just kidding you can't go straight you
can only go diagonal okay okay
unless you're in front of someone then i
think you can jump over them straight
you can only move diagonal and then uh
[Music]
can't go straight oh
interesting
[Music]
yep checkers is a very special game
oh i think the game
forces
you can't you have to do the move that
like the game is helping you
you're it should be lighting up the on
the left side
no i don't want your right side i don't
want to do that though but the game
forces you too why that doesn't make any
sense i don't remember that happening
it's helping you no it's helping you
huh i wonder if that's though
that is a game rules or just still ah
that is the rule oh it's actually the
room oh we said that as a rule
why interesting the game just that's how
the game is made if you see something
if there is a possibility then you have
to you have to do it i
see that's not how me and amelia played
but oh well i'll roll with it
huh i have to that's bizarre
okay
[Music]
i guess it's it's a technical thing
though tactical because like you're
you shouldn't bring yourself in a
position where
next time i could take oh i can't
explain it but
but then you can't you can't put the
pieces in place to dominate in the way
that you see fit
unfortunately now you gotta think a few
steps forward
yeah and now
hmm
i see you need to use your big brain
move here
that'll get me [\h__\h] up
aha uh okay no i can still do whatever i
want
[Music]
oh wasn't it something like when you get
to the other side you get like turned
into some special bob
yup you can be a king hmm
i would like to be a king i'm sorry come
on over
stay behind for a little bit longer when
you're kidding you can go backwards
right that was it
yes indeed i mean where else would you
go
um oh it's all right never can go off
the board
i mean i guess
oh i see
[Music]
i'm not sure what's happening you're in
control
well i'm into the chat i'm there yo
emilia
we're playing this game this beautiful
game it's something all right
[Music]
well if i'm gonna be in a position for
you to take me out i should at least
make it so that i can come back against
you so
let me see what i can do that's that's
role
change like you're you're gonna be taken
out by me
but then you wanna be in a position
where you get back up again
i would be the one being taken out by
you because you're deaf and i would be
the one
normally getting back up and then
because i'm the phoenix you know what i
mean
so the game gives me two options if i
jump over there
which it's basically both the same
not a hotel
i'll do whatever [\h__\h]
okay oh wow you get two in a row
oh what oh oh okay i'll do that before
oh yeah that's that's yeah
if you have if you get by taking someone
if you're at this
again in a position where you can take
another one then you can do two in a row
i guess or endless oh i see
i'm king yeah
have you ever thought of covering that
song king
yeah i'm i'm thinking about it oh really
there's like millions of covers of that
song yup
it's been done a lot but i feel like i
could do something different with it
oh i might want to do a wrap cover i
don't know
oh yeah why not i mean it's already like
there's really fast lyrics already so
it's almost like a wrap already
actually did a really really good cover
with that like i like the original
version
i liked the remix instrumental a lot
actually king me
yes me too let's see
i covered king before so yeah yeah i did
i did
yeah it was very good
yeah really what part of it was good all
of it
[Music]
i'm glad you listened to it yeah i
listened to it 50 times
you don't believe me do you i don't i
don't
if i told you that i've been the future
sorry
you've been in the future yes
oh okay
that's your only response i tell you i
can go to the [\h__\h] future and all you
say is okay
[Music]
such a shame i think i am i am king
times free yeah triple pink
dang this is how amelia felt
because she distracted you huh no
i was just really good last time ah
no it's okay i don't i don't really it's
a game i don't care
but you know it's cool it's okay you
wanted a lot of other games you're
better at shooting
oh i mean i don't really i don't mind
either way it's just it's just having
fun
that's the important part when you're
bad at games you learn to just enjoy
because it's fun
and get better each time if you want
i'm also like super excited to having
you as our
um ttrpg like like
how are you called the person who yeah
the master
yeah i hope that you didn't you didn't
you feel like you maybe want to like
play on your own like
be one of the players is that more fun
or do you prefer being the master
oh i like being a player personally but
i i have experience running
games so i thought i might as well you
know
yeah and it's been a while since i i
made a story so
i thought why not give it a shot one
more time i guess
for old time's sake looking forward to
that
someone who knows what they're doing oh
you're a kingdom
yeah i mean knows what they're doing
that's a very generous
expectation i've maybe run two games in
my existence and i've existed for a long
time see
we'll see well i did i did play it like
probably like a million years ago
uh with my family but we played i told
you
we played dnd oh you mentioned that yeah
oh yeah i don't really think i can get
any further from here
[Music]
i guess i could go back
will that's what you got to do as a king
go back and protect the
one little one in the corner when are
you gonna make him move
never never the game will never end as
long as i have that one in the corner
we will see about that i could just go
back and forth and back and forth
forever
i will catch you eventually nope
i will you won't no you won't
i will no i will
no we'll just do a redo of uno
i guess so this is my
my chess power that i've gained from
playing chess so often
[Music]
it's over my beautiful queen
let me be your king oh no thanks i'm
gonna pass on that one
oh yeah i pushed you against the wall if
you do that you don't want to know what
happens next
you're gonna i think i've seen like fan
art like that before wait a minute hold
hold on a sec
huh i'm very confused with the rules of
this game because i feel like
it was definitely different when amelia
and i played but oh well
maybe you'll play a different game maybe
you mentioned no it was checkers i'm
sure
oh well do you want to play chess
[Music]
you sure about that that's gonna that
could take very long we're not playing
[\h__\h] i'm surprised you offered me that
ooh uh sevens is pretty actually no i
forget how to play that and forget yeah
preferably nothing with cards because i
don't
know how to play with cards no i see i
see we could play tennis
oof that's okay i'm gonna be really uh
scuffed but we couldn't we can try sure
it's available
i'll give it a try let's see oh
well you can only move in those like
lines it looks like
it would appear so well let's see we
don't know how to play but i guess we
will learn
oh i see i see
i don't see okay right swing left swing
and move
oh okay oh oh
oh oh
oh wait this is fun yeah
oh
[Music]
you don't need to let me win kiara it's
fine
what match point already
smacked out whoa that was crazy
he spiked that right out of the park
i did i did that's pretty crazy
i fired that ball up with my fire
yeah that was pretty much
that's fun i got one you can do another
if you want yeah yeah okay
here we go
game can you let here let's do let's
play
a two-game match okay
let's get this party started
have you ever played tennis in real life
yup
didn't go well not a game for me
i feel like the only the only sport ball
that i enjoy is basketball other than
that i like to run quite a bit but
that's it
basketball i was always love that bag of
any kind of ball games
oh yeah [\h__\h] they're hard
i agree we're always very scared of the
ball
coming down meaning hitting you in the
face dodge ball am i right
yeah i like dodgeball though i was very
good at running away from it
but i could never catch it oh yeah
yeah i would always try to catch the
ball and get hit and die
gosh this reminds me of wii tennis
though you remember remember that
you could actually play with like your
controller like as as a bat
yeah that was so fun that was such a fun
one
yeah i have very fond memories of that
game i need a new
i need a new uh wii yeah
i'm gonna buy an old one yeah that works
i think that on on switch too
perhaps i feel like they could do it
yeah perhaps i think there are some wii
games you can play on like newer
consoles i'm fairly certain
but don't quote me don't quote me my
hands are sweating
oh it's palm spaghetti i i get that
deuce two more points to victory
here we go
yes
okay okay we'll do another
we shall do another i have no problem
with this
[Music]
now everyone oh don't make them bad
i mean you can if you want but
no money of course yeah with with your
with your love and
and undying affection i went for my body
wow
that did have a lag actually i will say
i noticed internet
please [\h__\h] that's okay there's still
another one go it's your serve
wait
please kill me softly huh
i mean you'll need softly if you're
taking requests i suppose that i can
i can take those requests of yours
we've done this so many times why not
unfortunately it's not up to me it's up
to the game right y'all
i was flapping my wing there oh that's
okay i saw that you were trying to fly
away and i i
i admired that whoa it was quite high in
the air
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah we can play again i'll make sure
you get the serve this time
was i forgot to do that so no problem
okay here we go play a two game oh i
don't get to decide
what ah that's dumb
well it's okay at least you get the
second serve so that's good
[Music]
wait throw it
that's because that's because you look
really cute in those tennis clubs
stop trying to distract you're the one
distracting me
by saying that thank you tennis skirts
look really cute just want to say that
that's true but i think oh [\h__\h]
tennis pants for me
oh i see the tennis fan night incoming
takamoni tennis fan art
sure everyone's very good
oh my god if you get the timing just
right you can kind of slam it huh
it's lagging a bit though yeah it is i
noticed that too there is a lag oh
oh pull the fast one on me
wow that was very quick
oh
[Applause]
i moved is i know you did
thank you yeah no problem
oh not bad
yeah game point whatever that means it
means the match can be decided by this
point
oh that's a high one
here we go two more points to victory
the
do you want pressure play do you want to
play again
tennis is like the new chess that's way
more exciting than ninjas
i mean you can if you want to it's up to
you kusatori you may decide
come on please okay sure
we can go play draw in the boxes a
couple times if you want to get your
points back up again
no once you figure that out once uh then
the the possibilities that you're gonna
lose again they're very low on that game
[Music]
wait wait wait could you wait for a
moment let me close the stream on
youtube so maybe there's less lag on my
side
sure okay let's see
uh i'm ready okay here we go
i'm sure my roommate loves me screaming
like that
say big apologies love cali
okay i'm going to say exactly that kelly
made me scream i'm sorry
wait don't say it in that kind of way
you need to say it in a different way
she understands she knows our
relationship
what i don't like i don't like the way
you phrased that
you got it this time it's your serve
okay
serving some ice cream you know what's
the best thing in summer eating ice
cream
yeah i love eating ice cream in the
summer but i prefer kakigori
really i'm actually not such a big fan
because it's just
so watery i don't know i mean it's great
when it's super hot
but yeah i just think it's kind of
refreshing
my favorites blue hawaiian we could be
professional
i mean at least you maybe we could be ah
a professional tennis player
sure i'd be on your team why not they
have doubles
oh no [\h__\h] for [\h__\h] sake oh my god
it's okay
you got it i was doing pretty well at
the beginning
i would like to say that but you are
learning too fast kelly
i just like these kinds of games that's
not like
no you ended my life too quickly there
i'm sorry
i'm sorry i'll i'll take i'll take it
okay nope
i mean you'll always you'll always still
you'll always still beat me at drawing
the boxes
and matching that's the check checker
was
yeah you really you really clowned my
ass to kingdom come
in checkers so you know what no worries
man
we're even maybe there's one more like
last
smaller game
play to finish it off yeah what would
you like to play i'll let you i'll let
you guys
wait that's not small but ludo is that
um
is that yeah i love that game
oh oh it's a popular easy to play dice
game from
from europe so australia right okay i
played that in my childhood so often
but they haven't played it since like a
million years oh i mean we could play it
if you'd like
i want to try i'm not sure if i remember
though how to play it but they'll tell
us
sure yeah let's let the little
mannequins narrate how to play the game
for us
the whole little family all to ludo okay
it's a dice game that was invented in
india
huh
pieces back to the start if you land on
them oh that sounds fun and very
agonizing
maybe there's some judo there it reminds
me of sorry a little bit
all the way back the game sorry yep
setting your opponent and you gotta
bring your four
um players into your colored boxes in
the middle
[Music]
oh so it's sorry okay a lot of people
are saying that it's the sorry game
it's not sorry it's trouble oh okay
i'm ready to play it wait that's the
name of the game in
another place yeah in the underworld
it's called sorry i believe
oh it's like sorry but
it's it's it's pretty similar okay so we
got a starting
threshold no rule blocking off i don't
know what any of this means
so and we have two entities not a pc i
think the way it is now is
fine yeah okay we'll just play it then
we have two uh computer players
yay
[Music]
please let me ah that's so nostalgic
but move a piece okay not to distract
okay
okay let's go roll the dice
rude what ah i have to take it okay okay
i'll cook it
ah it's a lucky game oh you're
oh the npcs are fast
yes six nice
you can roll again ah because you got a
six so what i see
maybe okay just the one oh okay just the
one piece
you can move other pieces too i see
yeah those those uh those computer
characters are very scary to me
okay they got no faces no nose no mouth
no eyes
i can go and suit yeah wait no don't
stop i didn't mean to do that i didn't
mean to do that
why not well at least you have to go
around there anyway
i could have used a different piece ah
well i'm getting the heck out of there
[Music]
moving on i jumped over him noise and
now he jumped over me again what the
hell
well can i can i take one of the i can
oh no i can't
no we gotta move ah you can only have
one out at once i guess
i get it one in the future so it really
is just a game of being lucky huh
i mean what strategy is there
no strategy i guess yeah so it's just
who has the most luck so don't worry we
i
definitely i'm not gonna make it through
this but we'll see what happens
i'm always getting okay i was just about
to
complain they always get little numbers
oh wait now i can choose someone who can
get on the field please
why would i that's very strange i might
do that
oh ah if you roll a six then you can
send someone out but they are not
allowed to
to walk those six uh oh
nice i said him back well played
eat yellow bye bye
okay okay
oh wait i can eat yellow back again
assert your dominance oh no he hated me
i barely saw that happen i think it was
green we know it's yellow maybe
oh ah because i oh that yeah that was
not smart on me because i was waiting
basically on the on the starting
point oh [\h__\h] no
there's a little strategy in here
[Music]
the figures are moving it's kind of
therapeutic almost like asmr sort of
yeah so cute it's like a satisfying
sound
oh no oh that's that's that's dangerous
oh that's only dangerous if they roll a
six next time
yeah well we say that now but i think
we're gonna be in trouble
like you just did rolling again
a five
i'll stay there
and let's go no i knew you [\h__\h]
jinxed it
god damn it kiara that means that it's
just stupid npc look
goddammit it's not fair i will
about to say to hey guys you want to
take a bet on on uh
if they get a six they put you back in
there again now you can eat them though
you can eat them if you come out again i
know not anymore i can't they boned me
i hope you win the game kiara because i
just don't think
[Music]
nice wow what a shame yellow
you can roll again oh nice double row
oh number six what you can get a whole
army out on the field you can roll again
that's it okay cool uh who can i harm
the quickest likes it well
uh here we go we'll see what happens
get someone out or move the ones i have
currently
oh i'm gonna
wait and move
[Music]
rolling again oh yeah right free
neck breaking asmr
what
what the hell is the problem of yellow
yeah yeah yellow is pretty much a power
player i would say
she didn't even say sorry yeah yeah
you got to say sorry that's part of the
rule like with uno you gotta say
green see ya green this is also a game
that could go on for maybe millions of
years
yellow also needed green so green is
back uh
in his own uh headquarters
with all four
[Music]
i'm working on my strategy to get yellow
here we go me one six nights you got a
six
i did i might as well move someone out
why not yeah
all right two damn it i wanted to get
yellow out but i guess i just
i can't wait for it
the time will come yeah maybe
[Music]
i'm very sick of that mother f word
a very strong computer player
oh my god no they're gonna win
i hate that yellow yeah it's freaking
[Music]
worse
please green don't kill me okay okay
okay
oh my god i was close they're very quick
at this game
yeah wow is there any what gosh i always
get so close to being able to f word up
the yellow one
i want to keep my pieces very nicely
separated out on the board
we can destroy who needs to be destroyed
oh five ah
[Music]
they're going to pay for that i'll get
them let's see
yeah i'll move that one
but maybe next turn you can kick the
green one away i know but he moves
before you
i will also get someone out there and
well again
two
moving on i can barely see what the
other
like what the what they're doing because
they go so quick
i don't like it not the biggest fan of
it
getting close to
my headquarters but i'm still going to
use that one
nice okay let's see sure
riveting riveting game really
with my parent long time ago
nice who can i kill no one
that's a shame something that
is a phrase that we hear a lot from
death
i mean yeah that's pretty much to be
expected i would say
ah so close to getting revenge on yellow
[Music]
i just want to beat him up i want it to
just be you and me because
i don't want these computer characters
they actually oh my god they both
already have someone
in their fields yup it's just us oh my
god we gotta get somewhere coincidence
is it sorry is that the dice is also
controlled by the computer
yeah you get what you get when
you're picking up what i'm putting down
you picking up what i'm putting
the game is rigged well i can't ah wait
that's you no
you get hurt you can hurt me cause sorry
it's fine it's always fair in this war
game
and do what you have to do no i choose
not to
you're too nice to me you're too kind
one [\h__\h] only one
damn it all right what just happened
yellow came in i guess messed with you
[Music]
why wouldn't it let me move it on its
own no matter yellow is such an
unpopular color even though i personally
like yellow in general
kind of a nasty color to be honest
[Music]
the game is rigged this game is rigged
i mean that's a gift we already got
doing
all right here we go
can we infiltrate the npcs
i'm moving in slow motion oh
what are you doing green
all right i can roll again
oh let's see where can i oh i can hurt
you
but you know what cause it's already you
get one you get one free because you
spared me once but you don't need to
feel the need to spare me
i'm just saying okay oh great bye-bye
ass they pass they're they can't do
anything interesting
yep i cannot do anything
what a coward yeah you can't do anything
you can't move coward okay i'm in with
one
oh we're both okay you also got someone
in nice
yup skirt
i do did you get a deal with the devil
please no
i don't know what you're talking about i
don't know what you're talking about
i don't play these lucky games
come on i just wanted to let's see how
far can i go with
this one here this buddy here we go
oh not bad enough six hmm
[Music]
here i go
you knew already gosh they're so quick
they scare me
i don't like that they scare me okay
it's okay you just do what you have to
do
oh man well now i can't no i can't mess
with you
[Music]
i don't want to
is that a part of your strategy as long
as the npcs are better than us we gotta
work together
i guess i feel like it's a part of your
strategy though
you you me you make me not want to take
you out
you know it doesn't have any meaning to
take me out anyway
i guess here we go we've all got one now
except for you green
yeah it's definitely the uh the
strongest player
definitely a little bit extra lucky
because of the game algorithm so
um there's always got to be one super
powered cpu
[Music]
it's got the real luck on their side i
don't like it
let's see there we go
at least galo can't put any more out
oh cool oh get your last soldier out
there
i think i'd uh i could or i could get my
homeboy in here yeah that's safe
that's safer get into the safe zone
gotta get a safe zone
get me in there nice
oh look come on only rolling these
horrible numbers
i'm fine you were not lucky it's right
there's nothing we can do because it's
already the game is rigged
i behave yeah
a burning passion everyone everyone
knows blue and fake is the best
everyone knows they're just they're
jealous because they they can't be as
beautiful colors as us
that's the only reason can i get yellow
i don't know i can't i can only barely
i'm not going to take my chances ah darn
it either way ah whatever
i hope yellow doesn't roll a one i think
that it will now that you've said
i'm the only one rolling once anyway
moving slowly like a turtle
i'll keep the homies together
oh six is standing up
finally something bigger nice
nice screen yeah yeah get them green uh
still hate
you i'll take it
wait i'll take it
oh come on you really are getting a lot
of ones huh
yeah they don't like me
yeah the enemy of my enemy is is my
friend
yeah that's the saying is it not i can't
wrap my
brain around that what is that the enemy
of my enemy is my friend
do you get it because if you're enemies
then you're friends with the
you're it's if you're enemies with
someone no the enemy so if you're if you
have an enemy and they have an enemy
no listen you gotta l okay if you have
an enemy imagine you have an enemy i'm
sure you have an enemy
you have one enemy a total of one enemy
okay that
and that that enemy of yours has an
enemy one that's not you
okay the one that isn't you
okay so the only the only saying i know
is keep your enemies close your friend's
clothes book your enemies closer
i think that was something something
like that
was that it that we were trying to say
uh no not quite
um i mean you can keep your enemies
close i guess
um i mean i've done that several times
as well
um but what i'm trying to say is you can
bond over mutual hatred of someone
that's a sad thing to say out loud but
it's
oh that was what you were going at okay
yeah that's like the mean way of saying
it that's the mean way of saying it
like my arch-nemesis your arch-nemesis
uh if they hate someone then you can be
allies with that person that they hate
because you both hate your arch-nemesis
um you just gotta think about it for
like a little bit
yellow is so close to me you'll get it
the enemy of your enemies your is the
friend of your enemies
best friend cousin uncle twice removed
something like that here we go uh
either way it's dangerous green is gonna
get me for what i did i must attorney
finally i'm in i'm in i'm finally in
thank you
okay
[Music]
i'd like to get away from green here we
go
oh that's dangerous for me
[Music]
it's fine i wouldn't dream of harming
you acoustic sorry i still
have a thank you i owe you one
and then i start playing the game before
you start playing
no before you start playing the game
correctly kusatori i'm telling you
it's not it's i can't help it it's just
i it's a tacoma collaboration after all
we're gonna co-op
[Music]
yes oh i can't control my fingers you
know you're not safe there yet by the
way though
green is uh on on the other side
now very good get in there
please i can't oh yeah yeah yeah you can
ah they've got my number i
that probably feels pretty good huh no
that [\h__\h]
i knew that was going to happen i knew
the computer was going to start getting
lucky
actually yellow is shooting out there
again oh man i'm
back at the beginning but actually i had
no choice though
to i only could go there damn it yes
oh [\h__\h] i need a six i need to roll
until i get a six
[Applause]
oh i got over there really quick oh just
kidding never mind
uh sure i'm cursing so much on your
channel oh no i don't
everyone here is used to it by now
you're just fine yes
[\h__\h] hell that really hurts
free passes in the room green is just
they're evil their computers are evil
this is really bad
the game no the game wants this to
continue forever
okay the game is destined to let yellow
win
it's how it was always meant to be it
was written in the great books
we can't really happen i know we have to
stop fate
but it's been written in the prophecy
since the beginning of time
that yellow would win this game so you
know the computer is just doing what it
was programmed
and then why was yellow so unpopular
with pokemon go
oh is that a fact i have no idea of any
of that
but i actually was on uh team yellow
with pokemon go
i wasn't that the electricity one
generally i guess yes but not really in
pokemon go you had like three colors you
could join a team
oh they don't stand for any of the
elements
no in this case no i see
um oh there we go chad's telling us
what team they were in oh that's so cute
maybe i'll get a four did you never play
pokemon go
um i did for a little bit but it just
wasn't for me
i made a lot of friends with pokemon go
yeah it seems like a fun game i'm just
not very much into mobile games
um yeah me neighbor in general
oh yeah that was close you little [\h__\h]
i'm telling you
it's it is a race game it's fine they're
almost in there but they need the exact
number
to get in there exactly
oh my god no wait no that's okay
now we're gonna pass a million times too
because yeah uh i mean that's a shame
because if i didn't get out i probably
could have hit yellowstone
but actually i didn't even have a choice
because i could only move there
you're right that's not your fault it's
not your fault
and here we go passing again
all right let's see let's see how often
it's okay um the the yellow one will get
the exact number
i wouldn't be surprised computers are
evil man
oh come on that is [\h__\h] ridiculous
stupid
yellow oh wow i got a second go [\h__\h]
yourself yellow
man
i'm sure there are some fans of
sunflowers in the chat or other things i
mean
flowers are nice and all but but this
npc sucks
it belongs in jail yeah i i agree as
we've all said many times before
computers are evil
we all know this as a fact and today is
simply more proof of that so you know
what
kusutori in the end at least we it's
about the message
it's about the message so we've won
don't worry
the message is that [\h__\h] computers you
stay with takamori
i was going to say uh f f the computers
um just f the computers and nothing
follows but i mean if you
i mean that's fine too
well thank you kelly yeah
it takes two and then yeah we're gonna
try to play it takes two weekly
yes but we're also doing a verse yes
shadowverse in fact i'm i'm building my
deck tomorrow
come check it out you guys if if you'd
like um i got a bunch i got a bunch
of where it's basically just a card
opening stream and then we're gonna
arrange a deck pretty much
based off that so i think it'll be fun
uh look forward to it
um and yeah i'm looking forward to
playing it takes two as well i gotta say
i was i was really tired this evening
but it ended up being fun and i got my
energy
maybe if you were tired then it was
maybe good because i think what it takes
to
it would have been a bit more difficult
than playing these small boat games
it was a really i did a lot of stuff
today i went out and ran a bunch of
errands and
didn't quite get to relax the way that i
wanted to so
yeah but next time i'm sure it'll be
fine
yeah thank you for everyone coming
anyway even though we changed the game
so
sudden last minute yeah that was very
thank you so much for coming to cheer us
on anyway and enjoy i guess our reunion
because it has been a while since
we collapsed on anything so cheeril but
now
now now the what you call that when
you're like really thirsty
uh huh uh when you're like in this in
the in the in the
in this in the sand and really thirsty
um dry i mean your throat is dry
oh
thirsty ever again yeah exactly it's
gonna be great and
i'm really excited about the what is it
the the tabletop rpg thing as well we're
gonna
start character creation in may in late
may so look forward to it
until then i'll be crap i'll be crafting
a story
uh that hopefully you guys will enjoy so
look forward to that
yeah lots of collab stuff planned
hopefully we can finish it takes two
before we start doing tabletop stuff
let's try our best yay
okay i guess that's it i'm gonna read uh
super chats another day probably after
the stream tomorrow so look forward to
that uh yeah anyway i'm imori hope
you'll remember me
and uh peace out and i think uh that
in kusutori's dreams they say something
else what was it again
oh we say and in german we say auf
wiedersehen
see you guys bye bye catch you on the
flip side
[Music]
peace
you