[Music]
e
[Applause]
[Music]
huh
hi
hello huh
huh where am
I
huh
what what am
I
huh
hello
hi who are
you
huh why so many people writing to me
what's going
on that's so
fast
huh
huh who is
this plus
here
I am I talking to a
aier huh am I going
insane
what why
spamming
cucumbers what that's that's quite
odd
H who are you what what's her
name why why so
many what's going
on I'm
scared
huh what's her
name
ch what a silly name why would you call
yourself
chatini it's so
silly
huh
h
h i don't remind I don't remember
you you said you said that you are my
plus what you guys what are you guys
talking about
huh I I I see no plusy here look there
not flashy what where are you who are
you don't lie to
me
H this is not fun who am I why I'm
here what's going on
huh are you trying to SC me or
what what is this room
huh and why am I why my friends are
here who are them
what I mean I know I I remember them but
why are they here
like huh that's so odd that is odd and
who are you again
what is
this she forgot about us about bikini
too oh
bikini
bikini Jimmy
I I remember you you made that promise a
long time
ago but I don't remember details
actually dang it but I remember
something vaguely I I
do this is hard I don't know what to
deal with how to deal with this it's oh
my God my head my head is about to
explode my head
hurt he I'm
scared what is going
on I wonder what's going to
happen so many of
us
what
H cha cha chatini that's that's her
name what your fers they trying to break
the the walls maybe uh maybe she'll try
too
H the thing is your
name this is
SC
oh I wonder maybe that's just a
dream maybe this is a dream
hm maybe this this is just a
dream yeah maybe I'm going to wake up
soon yeah maybe maybe if I try to
escape maybe I can make a
hole and the chch escape from from this
room we must do something right maybe
here nothing works
huh ba is going
crazy I don't know I don't know what to
do do you guys have any
suggestion maybe maybe you guys can
solve the the
Enigma it's 4:00 a.m. and the beard is
up sleep is for the week
let's go now now that you made me
remember I actually haven't slept in a
long
time
well
H
guys why are you doing jokes
about I don't know what you're talking
about I don't remember those kind of
jokes
anymore which balls are you talking oh K
is following
me can can can you can you be serious
for 5 minutes I really don't know what
is happening like wa we're just here in
a
room I'm going
to I'm
scared you should help
me I
wonder maybe maybe if I dig enough
h h
h is there something I can do here let's
[Music]
see are we going to die all of us huh
are we are we going to die
everyone H they start to fight each
other maybe I should fight
too
maybe maybe there is just one player
that can
survive of course I'm a big cat I have
many chance to stay alive after all
yeah I don't have a you guys are talking
to each other did you see where are you
from
what
[Music]
huh
what bro let me take a
screen there way what
happened oops I don't know what happened
the server
closed
[Music]
what oh he back hello hello hi
H so
cute am I dead we're we're back I I
guess we're back yeah
jump
[Music]
scare
hello don't follow me what going on I'm
sorry I just wanted to touch you had
something back there I thought I attack
I attack I'm telling you okay she's
violent I'm
dangerous what
happened who are you
so
short what do you mean by that
any you know what you're my
enemy
you're
bir she talk back she talk
back I I don't remember are are we
lovers are we we lover
I can't stay as a blank forever you
think I talking to myself I'm
not people I think what's happening oh
my God what happened to me you can't
miss what you don't remember K we can we
can build a new life we can we can build
a new life where we live she she's okay
I'm pretty sure she's fine people is
is that your super you can recognize
mistak
I I'm not
fla you
scared it's okay I it'll be
okay
too
yeah wait what
are you going to attack
me please don't don't do that I'm
friendly I am a big
cat I'm a
big scary nice to meet you nice to meet
you my you're the first nice person I
met H it's scary here do you know why we
here
[Music]
maybe we should try to scap or
something you have much memory
either that's that's
odd maybe we'll find a
[Music]
way frequency of I don't have fish I
want fish have you oh did you adjust
[Music]
it you
are yeah
you
remember I I think that's a dream maybe
maybe I drunk too much yesterday and
that's a dream drink
maybe I actually don't drink so that's
weird that's very weird you know why we
here it's a
conspiracy
conspiracy how how do we get
out how
to what do you mean you don't I don't
want to die
here I think we can do that maybe maybe
uh maybe it is like a pzle we have to
solve or maybe we have to kill everyone
until we are the only two left
ah h
Huh where am I they wor to
leaveing and more than anything
the people I hold more most the people I
hold most
dear W face with Oblivion I
feel
empty
oh face with Oblivion I feel
relieved I'm not going to skip
perhaps this
road I don't I do not
know so much I don't know and
yet so much I don't know and
[Music]
yet the bright light to to the light the
light is calling
me is anybody else concerned about this
syis going into the bright light
[Music]
am go again I mean everybody's going so
I guess I should to the now we should go
let's go go to the light go to the light
follow the
[Music]
light go to the light light follow the
light is this it is our time are we
going to shoot up we shoot up are we
going are we going
to
that it say they have him I don't like
light I don't
like I don't want to
T is this is this what feel be Dad wait
what is an alien so many voices we we go
up we can we go we don't go up should we
go towards the
light oh what's that that looks like an
egg this oh yeah what is
that EG it's like a broken
egg but we came my God don't turn around
it's not a hole it's not a hole which
one is I don't want to fall what happens
if I going to
fall J I'm
scared why don't you
[Applause]
jump the best
Castle
oh what is
that you there what are you doing
here you have the look of Outsider about
you huh oh is a
quest quick send word to his
majesty the years has arrived at the
sanctuary
[Music]
away huh
oh
cute what is this
little this is a kingdom of leeso and I
am its king the guards who brought you
here have informed me that you remember
not but your own
names h a side effect of trouble between
words no
[Music]
doubt you
see an unprecedent Ed Calamity now treat
our
word it has sewn the Earth with
corruption and driven us from our homes
this Bri land now given gives rise to
creatures of Shadow NOS of stains the
kingdom of liil and its surroundings are
now the only safe place left to us
liis going to SK a
[Music]
but so the Calamity be left unchecked
till only a matter of time before it
consumed the entire
wor I can
read I can actually
read fa with the Pro Prospect I scored
the ancient text for a way to come back
the
Calamity the rid of hero summoning
oh and so I ask you I will will
you your majesty what it is a great H
stain has broken through our defensive
line
no we are rushing to mount of Defense
but the situation is there Your Majesty
we must get you somewhere
safe who are those
strangers let's see you he is will you
accept this Destiny there's a great
power within you will you use it to save
us to save this
[Music]
word oh hi up Heroes hello hello
beautiful maidens it is so good to see
you I would you like a piece of bread
thank you your bread I like oh would you
like some bread too what is this can you
give me bread I I don't
feel I W
bread oh my God there's what is this
this place is Big look at
that down
oh so you're the ear yes I do sense a
mysterious for with you well my name is
rues
the r ear names ring in my speciality
normally but hey Fortune favor the ball
don't it let's show them
since what for huh oh thank you
the blessing upon upon you my
name I am I am a I'm a big I'm who are
you I am nice to meet you a you look so
nice H nice to meet you I like cats you
like cats IOP you
yes I'm going to follow you everywhere
now oh nice okay that's more like dog
behavior but
your I am going to leave now who are you
I think you a brave here you may call me
very
Elizabeth Ohan hello there are you still
lost okay okay gathan that's what I'll
call you this place is Big isn't
it okay
I'm come here come
here who are you oh how very
forward I am ra panta wow are you a cat
I'm a big cat I'm very first and I'm
Predator that means I can kill you at
any moment at any time can you Pur okay
yes you told me my name was
EXC
it'sing oh wow she PR for anyone
huh I'll put you in my
sword the heart the heart no the heart
help leave me
alone help help help
help I I I would stick with you anytime
you know oh wow thank you wa oh they're
talking hello distress
Madam someone was killing me someone
some some some maybe it looks like a
no no I I adopted her she's a cat I'm
not killing her tell me okay wait they
talking was like a dog like a dog using
a sword against me what
scary what are
they privacy statement bad
dog bad dog but I I bet they're having
like a
really I'm not they us to defend King
your duty not my duty this is not my
case look at that look at
that yes I
that's very
strong what
[Music]
to Hur it Hur It Go Go hurt this one hit
this one Hur this one okay we got
going to kill
them come W give
up oh
goodness
comat okay okay easy we can we can we
can still
fight easy
[Music]
interes mechanic this is good job isn't
that how it works in
theseal there's
no has been SL he is so strong we canot
hard them we're too low level we're too
low level
yeah look out for each other
focus
focus oh
the I'm
Dreaming H sh
Revelation huh hold your weapon and left
[Music]
click
huh huh
I am doing
it is it
[Music]
bu you mean shout it doesn't
work
Revelation revelation
revelation
[Laughter]
[Music]
hey doesn't
[Applause]
[Music]
work that's so funny
okay it's
down we I was too strong guys I'll tell
you uh that was me that was my fault I
was too strong and I destroyed not only
the the word but the entire
server so
yeah I I'll take the full
responsibility I don't know who I
am
but I know I'm
strong
CH and I'm stronger
than you
[Music]
it was very that was very
strong let's
wait let's
wait a oh my
God music is slow
okay let's
see I remember what you I don't know who
you are have no idea but you're very
could plus yet say if if I wasn't a word
where plushes were collectible I would
probably collect all of
them you know like I would probably try
my best to collect
[Music]
them
yeah maybe maybe why why don't why don't
you guys use this time you have to
remember to remind me who you are and
what you doing here like why are you
watching me and what are you doing here
like I just happen to be
here how do you how do you met me how do
you know me in the first
place
hm you're an
idol I'm I'm a
Panter H that's all I REM
we're chatin and we love
[Music]
cucumbers e that's that sucks you have
bad taste for
real
M
[Music]
yeah she I I don't actually hate you I
it's more like I'm
confused what is what's going
on you love FR on Pizza hm I think I
remember that part about me
h i met so many people
already
H maybe everyone loves fries on Pizza
h
h you collected us H really
[Music]
H your Giggles are so comfy to us can I
make a record for
that HH why would you do such a thing no
one will be interested
into me
laughing you
know no one will be
ever I don't I I I do remember I don't
like cumbers I actually don't we're here
because we support mama and
Justice
who why would you call me like that that
doesn't make any
sense you want me to adopt
you I
mean I mean I think you cute and
adorable plushies
so I may think about
[Music]
it
yeah mhm we adopt not kidnapped I could
never kidnap anyone like
hm I don't think I would do
that you know your voice is relaxing you
think so for
real do you you you you you you think
so
huh you're part of a lower enforcer
called Justice you got a good eyes you
love pizza with
pineapples and you trusty you trusty
compain
chis are your trusty companions also you
don't like buff guy and bikini
cosplay
H I don't know about that I think you're
pretty wrong H I don't
know I mean I definitely don't like
pineapple and pizza
so just thinking about it makes me kind
of uh
[Music]
I don't
know it's
weird I I just no I I'm pretty sure I
wouldn't be I wouldn't like pineapple
and pizza like no maybe not
no I think you're wrong I'm sorry uh
what was your name again
oh J Jamie
no it's not possible I think you I think
you're talking to the wrong person I'm
sorry but do I have God eyes for real H
let's
see
oh oh my God I see I see everything huh
huh
I I
see I
see what are you
doing I I see you I see all of
you you truly are a Chini oh my God fles
fles
everywhere flashes everywhere
I think I want to catch them all
yeah I think I'm going
to I think I I'll find to around the
world yeah you know I don't need
to yeah whatever I'm doing I'm going to
drop it and go get all the flashes all
of
them yes
H very
cute very
[Music]
cute but I want to get just the one who
deserves so I'll make a test to make
sure that I get just the original and
good quality ones I don't want to have
like fake ones you know
fake I'm not going to off my we're going
to call off this journey and you're
going to go to
your you have nice too
than what's going
on like way too much
here was it just a
[Music]
dream you
lot
of thank youas thank you I will
be and your title is
the to the B oh ba you are so high ba no
my bread out weapon yourness my
bread I'm I going to feed the
cat where is my
bread where where is the bread where's
my bread where is my bread why are those
two kissing in the corner I the cat and
the N want to join you want what are we
doing here I I'm looking for my bread
you I heard you stole my item pink cat
it was not me
stop
no I protect the
weak why everyone bullies
me because a forgotten memories who am I
the word I live
in why you don't protect and more than
anything the people I hold most
de face with Oblivion I feel
[Music]
empty
relieved perhaps this Ro
I don't
know I do not
know so much I don't know and
yet so much I don't that bring light
close to me don't go toward the light
what if
we we
here let's go to the
lights I wonder what happens if if I
actually jump
I'm scared maybe let's not
jump I think she was it's
safe is come here my cat meow
meow no don't get I am am I am a wild
Panther I'm telling you I can I can
attack you at any moment if you were a
wild Panther then why did you let me
adopt you because you I like cute girls
come on I got I got some more cute girls
over
[Music]
there okay I don't know it's the first
meeting I'm not ready I don't know who
she
is I don't
know some I'm looking for some food do
you have
any I had some but it got taken away
from me can I have food
later I I'll give you food later you're
so cute can I give you a p on the
head there you go Yosi
Yosi yi yi yi oh she's puring I like her
yi yi she's
puring
a thank you
wow wait wait what's your name I am I am
I am ra
ra yes yes say that say that
[Music]
again
yeah yeah yeah that's your
name what's your name I'm I'm
sorry I'm skiing this
though um skiper skiper I already read
that in my defense
mhm those bunnies are so cute I I didn't
but I was thinking about it I forgot
your name cuz you sound like a crazy
person so I don't think took any of it
seriously she czy I'm telling you she is
the craziest why are we back czy I told
her harness was
going C she crazy where is the royalness
back
here wait I know what happens there's
going to be enemies yeah there's going
to be enemies remember don't you
remember you know you guys don't
remember there was a battle right here
am I crazy yeah I think
C are we in an endless loop probably I
want to follow her how do we break it I
don't know maybe we need to kill
someone maybe one of usone someone oh
yeah let's kill someone
yeah oh you I won't die without a
play are you you purple like why do you
why do you smell like chicken please
don't I offer bread and peace why are
you purple like the stains
okay
okay help okay okay please stop do if I
your
I
dogs
dogs follow me hey hey why do you guys
why do you guys look the same let I
touch your toil
I don't know it feels little weird to
me maybe maybe there's an
imposter
Che they're claing I don't they don't
seem to know each other either really
save the oh I hurt
[Music]
myself I know her she was trying to beat
me
up no bullies allowed
need
okay I we can talk about it wait cat
person cat person I have food now here
you go take
it no cuz you pray for me thank you I
appreciate it hey she's talking to me
dog get
away help help help behind me beautiful
help there are two dogs two dogs are
attacking me for no reason dogs we
protect you it's GL she
P
well I I I don't think I have heard it
but I think you should leave her alone
yeah leave her
alone yeah don't be a
bully I'm not bullying her bully I just
want to hear the pring do do you look
like you might be a dog so do you
bark hi do you yeah bark for me me yeah
bark for me yeah bark for me come on
yeah yeah bark for me you have dog ears
in a
tail bark for me too yeah bark for me
but I don't think that's
barking bowow Bow Bow Bow Bow yeah she
is barking don't that's why you hate me
I don't hate you I want you a p okay
okay if you come close I I'll show you
serious wait the big guys are
talking
okay y y YY
YY fall the CL don't don't hurt me
anymore wait I'm ready they they were
right here I remember from my past life
are we friends now it's going toen I
remember thank
you you're welcome I remember
you uh what
your no my name is
[Music]
Jonathan I I all I know is that my name
and and now I found family this is
glorious I know how they move you must
protect the king defeat the I will for
you father
cousins let's
go again
he so
strong got get the small ones
first ah well done blue ma very large
vehicle
down you
go
[Music]
time don't let him get you nice let
go that's
a yes I remember the big one has a beam
big got to
jump the are we doing any damage with
the
King
maybe maybe has he's jumping he's
jumping
yeah good is there
a he's like a
piggy maybe we have to on the head I'm
not sure chop chop chop
[Applause]
this
is what we going to
do he's
going I
help revelation
Revelation
huh
[Music]
Revelation this St H has been
rooted you fall bravely can hero I pray
you are not
injured that my armored one must be
their leader the stain King fascinating
Most Fascinating well I see why they
call you ears we' been in the right
people without your
help we sustain minimal damage thanks to
your Valor our King om is in your depth
thank you I must hen to inform His
Majesty of our Victory will accompany
me h
Huh what interested me host however is a
strange power where you manifested
during the battle with which you were
able to defeat the Saints the power my
may be the key to saving our world from
anihilation According to the heres the
power came to them like a forgotten
memory when they spoke to the word
revelation but once the use it the stain
hes it seems the power vanished without
Trace well the bloody brilant in it in
it ah so what are we supposed to do next
time to the Saints attack revelation we
must uncover the secret to the this
phenomenon if we are to Prevail against
the Calamity many questions remain but
one thing is certain the kingdom of Li
besto still stands today thanks to
you here here so here's I ask of you
once more will you lend us strength to
save Li besta from
ruin yes I'll do my very best
marvelous on behalf of Leist I thank you
we're blessed to have you eight kind
ears allow me to introduce the four
Great guilds which are responsible for
ensuring the Kingdom's peace and
prosperity the Heaven from the curse
where knowledge and creativity are
avable above all the Scarlet W the home
for Glory Seekers with ambition and
vision where closes Alis become Fierce
of Rivals the Amber coin the sanctum of
healing where the spirited of empathy
and devotion treates the seruan
cup the bacon the B the beacon of the
Rous and loyal were the great treats and
fees ah too
fast one of the skills will become your
home during your time here
beheld this door lies the room of
Truth there in the will of the ancestor
show decide your G guilt fear not
introspection is a v step of the road to
Enlightenment exceler as I always say
even
higher time to roll the dice huh we
thinking some of you Lo down at the
Ember cor guil hole let us say save this
word together the room of the TRS await
go forth with
[Music]
Valor room of the truth oh my God this
is so
exciting step on the platform and
receive the will of the
ancestor I miss the countless sparkling
length
take Enlightenment with
sear let
favor
Amber we have a clo
huh
huh do we wear that
look
huh wait huh what I
got I got
a
huh I got a
clo that's so
cool look at that huh
huh huh look at
that that's crazy
this is so
cool huh I got a need
CL what that's so
nice maybe tatini can come back too huh
come back tatini come
back here you
go this is so cool
you like it huh I think it sweets me
very
[Music]
well armed with the unwavering will seek
to defend the soul of
Jade
yeah oh my good that was the cut I've
ever seen now how come to hello have I
done something to you
three you weirded me
out H where are we I think we I think
were we supposed to talk to the we all
in the same Guild do I really have to be
in the same Guild as this okay you do
right you been chosen to be with me
where where is the lead oh the the Le is
the leader over here oh orin's over here
hello we have to go Orin who is this who
are you how do we do we oh I think I'm
standing on a do we have
to
oh on the table your gu Guild Master
hello there
hello oh wait it's oh it's our Guild
yeah waiting oh that's perfectly fine oh
what right you also got a recycling bin
why I've got to recycle was be we've got
a map oh yeah we got a recycle for sure
oh my goodness how do we talk how we got
to speak to the Gil Master how do we
talk to the
master we have the British
one oh we totally do oh I I can talk to
him how do we you speak British yeah
right click he says watch this air is
the Amber Corn's little den of operation
uh name's aurin and I'm the closest
thing in charge around
here Orin we have the Bri Jo the fight
for the LI straight away after you were
summoned but we appreciate it now you
want to watch mean We Fight Together
against some stains maybe do a little
well saving while we're ated eh perfect
first things first Canadian
too though you ought to get to know this
Town we're in learn how to accept and
perform quests see there's a quest board
out in town where missions get posted
might want to take a bches out and see
what the quest master has to say I don't
understand stupid cuz you do it this so
well I don't understand
either that that was me that was that
was the M was was Master next go to the
quest board
Quest wait where is the quest
Master honestly that conversation took
so long it's already not wor bother him
we the quest oh go to the quest board
okay let go to the quest board I'm kind
of I'm a little bit
uncertain down you what was your name
again the I'll follow you the bay okay
what's your what's your name ah me yes
what's what's your name I am uh nice to
meet you I'm Takara of the
oranges your
name or all of your names my name is
p p
yes nice to meet you both my name is the
B and this over here is three very nice
to meet you nice to meet you that's the
lazy version of my name three no it's
CRA Eisenhower she the great the third
ah if for short three just call just
call just call her three number three
just not she's not very nice so try not
to get on a bad side all right no I I
just treat people the way that they
should be treated that's
all this a very nice G I don't think
we're going to get along yeah I don't
want to I I think that I think that
there'll be a Twist in this story line
and we'll be the best of of friends
doubt it I don't I also don't know where
we're supposed to be going isie the
quest guy perhaps we need to find the
quest to Quest I'm sorry I think the
first thing you need to understand is
that I have no idea where I'm going
we're going Quest board Quest board do
you think that's the quest board
everybody I'm going to find the quest
board
H let's see it should be inside maybe
maybe bookie has it rules make a B
oh
no where add
them
oh I lost I lost them
already what where at
them I lost
them you want to G no
later h
i l them
already maybe up
here
oh oh this place is beautiful
though so pretty oh they're outside I'm
going to go
there ouch cat I I lost you for a moment
yeah I know this not lost you so I came
back for you come with me cat thank
you I I knew there was something
missing the puring was missing thank you
with three thank you okay I got lost cat
needs to be on a leash it seems no I'm
free quest one God can we please have a
leash yes we need a leash for all C no
I'm free kitty harness guil cat I am
fine m free cats where are we going the
B uh according to this map I think the
quest Master should be right over here
wait have you have we found a quest
board board this is a board the board
that's a cool board nice
board let's see looks pretty empty you
must be one of the heroes then you
master told me about you I too here is
the question
jobs and requests people
here
hello here they are a good eye you have
it's your name sweet one they all got
their weapon look at
[Music]
that oh my God your sword is way big
than mine I don't know
I make
teleport honestly that's don't think iOS
to it's about how you use it of course
for the sake of improving our
relationship going on I've never felt
special in my entire so
cool we need to go talk to the quest
Master again an hour ago I don't really
remember what
how I feel but so Jonathan you have
spoken
to understand
Master complete the side quest and then
speak to the quest Master perhaps we're
not so different after all are supposed
to
help
are hello there we are part of the I
must go back to our Guild and speak to
the Guild Master I don't know I just
I
made wait where do you check the where
do you check the
quest
my me this here looks like a perfect job
on
the complete the
side
first where is the side we need to go to
and my mother says we are running low
and R materials if you can help us some
please
stop to
to maybe right click onto the quest
board maybe I don't know I hope you have
the time for some
citizens this a perfect job for you well
best of
we go
now where is
the no we have to complete the quest I
need to find the the the SMY the SMY the
you want to go
together the map we can go to the Smithy
yeah let's go right I don't know if I
should be in charge of directions I mean
maybe I can help maybe
uh I'm not sure for a cnap hey it was
her
H I'm I'm coming oh what happened to
three I don't know what is three maybe
we also oh we want to cook
too come here come here actually uh
receive one of your remaining breads you
may because I have more than you thank
you I have zero at this point wait I
can't give it to you oh we made trade
what oh oh how do I
accept like this yes like so okay one
one bread for you did you did you get it
you you are so kind uh I guess I oh wait
no this here we go wait I can't
what I I can't put it in your box oh
yeah
maybe I must
exchange oh wait H lock in we got to uh
click the red uh thing in the B at the
bottom oh I need to eat as
well Green Time free stand still do not
move pleas
huh the golden a red moment thank you
yeah okay
okay egg what is that
up y we match to the let's
go we can go with the horse too oh you
ride are you a horse how did you get the
horsey you w the egg oh the egg from
eggs and
this that's so
fast where I don't know
so
fast blacksmith is that the appr prince
oh we go it's up there oh oh my gosh wa
where did she go you can get off of
shift oh okay shift oh who you're
killing your horse you're killing your
horse oh my God
horse hello oh cuz I right clicked the
it's over here we're in the wrong house
ladies oh I don't think we can get in
all right how do you get the horse shift
shift shift you shift okay I shift all
right it's this
way how did you disappear this V is so
pretty isn't it the house I was just
it's just the power inside houses look
at how big it gave me endless speed is
it an
air just that's a chef I don't think
he's there oh is it over here problem I
think it's up there oh yeah it's over
over here mhm so this is the smithing
but I don't know what materials we're
supposed to have maybe we can just ask I
think here we go we need 10 oak logs
bunch of trees we can
oh okay what okay it's a good we have
axes girls oh
that's how far do you think is far is
this far enough how far is okay can we
this look at that can we take these
trees I don't I don't think so I don't I
don't I don't think so maybe we can go a
little bit like further out yeah yeah
yeah yeah further okay okay okay the
horse let's go my horse changed every
time yeah maybe
here what where at
them oh they fast I shall remember it
this time oh so nice I love I love the
atmosphere I'm
sing okay okay I'm fine I I I be careful
cat let's
go where' they go we lost them
again it's hard to keep
track well they're probably around the
the the trees
Maybe let's see here they are okay let's
grab some not out let's grab some not
considered outside this is not out it
respawns right away but oh maybe we can
not Farm here who even want
these well then yeah no we cannot get
this on Tre maybe we have to
go even further this
is Maybe
outside the walls yeah
probably I
follow outside maybe maybe upstairs can
we
go so bu
ah you can do it
horse I think we're going to die if we
fall from here a is there fall damage
yeah there is fall
damage help those must be the trees
right you need help help what's
wrong where are you I'm in a dangerous
situation how you end up here how did
you do that I might die no don't die I
I'll try to go step by step yeah yeah
yeah I have
Park I'm just realized I've been muted
in the game this entire I've been muted
this entire time oh my gosh you've been
a mute this entire time I've been M this
entire here before oh my goodness where
did she resp I don't know perhaps
there's another staircase closer to
maybe on my
HS M how do we leave actually I have an
idea I'll
is this church what is
that or maybe
not is that not
possible it doesn't look like go to a
gate oh I'm muted too oh no I was
muted no I was muted
too all right I
think let's go back to the staircase
yeah let's go we should got C out we get
out of that where is she where did she I
think she spawn in the
guild I think
so why did you stop riding
your there was no other
staircas whoever designed this
wall let's go gra
K where is she
where is she wa are we trapped here
forever
no I think there is like on the map okay
Quest
masterer
H oh I love
them I literally looked away for a
second they probably gone let me check
the master
[Music]
H that's the exit
maybe
[Music]
H
materials need does okay we
need we need a boot
right lost cart I'm
lost this is where uh it's our gu I
think to him H
hello yeah what what what weapon do you
have you have a candy wow what weapon do
you have show me your show me your
Revelation okay
[Applause]
so cool instant
TP oh nice
I I'm I'm going to call them private
Co I'm going to call
B she going to pick
up
hello my cat my cat oh my cat I I found
you oh my God you looking for me the
radio where are you I'm here we we've
gone outside the gate wait are you the
voes of our kitty I'm call I'm calling
to be at the phone oh wait a sec wait ba
where are you there's phones we are
outside hold on we are
defeating oh H H how did you R outside
um look for a blue spot on the map you
should be able to teleport Outside The
City Gate okay yeah my way sheep
K I know how to go I was muted I'm sorry
K I know how to go outside we have to go
to the blue spots come here okay but
wait I'm not sure if I really accepted
the the quests okay let's go double
check um cuz it says what does it say
for you it says I have 100 coins and
side quest materials needed at the
Smithy yeah it says the same for me as
well okay but they say I need to still
talk to the blacksmith uh cut it says
mat needed this
me let's just double
check what do I want we need 10 oak logs
oh maybe we and we need we need 10 oak
oak logs yeah oh okay I mean that seems
like I'm I'm through let go let's go we
have a lot of cheesec
on K want to make a party together yeah
yeah I invited you you're right I
invited you oh how do we accept together
how do we accept the party though I know
oh we are in the party okay okay good
let's go let's go to Adventure okay we
have to go here
probably you want to go on your horse
cat it's it should be like right here so
it shouldn't be that far oh it says the
blue spot on the teleport there should
be teleports here blue spot we should
find some
crystals
[Music]
H maybe the child can tell us child
seems to be
local on the gate on the gate huh
doesn't talk to strangers is it is this
the gate I'm I'm checking we need to
find blue stuff on the gate I'm going to
call B maybe again to ask okay wait I'm
going to call Ba no no no I'm calling
you wait
sorry uh uh private call where is me
please pick up CH leave town just
approach a crystal by H I did see about
a gate but not this tiny gate bigger
gate
but I've just gotten a phone
call you scared the B bisel out of
me yeah three maybe if you were a bit
nicer to people maybe they'd call you
what what do you want kitty cat where
are
you I'm
sorry over here never mind we found it I
I'll be
[Music]
back yes life did I just start off for
no reason I found it yeah let's
go Bad Kitty you made me lose 10 years
of my non-existent life that I just for
absolutely no
reason from the dead oh hello welcome
back wood we have we have a lot of wood
we can leave now oh I don't have enough
wood it's okay I have
wood I have 30 you want to trade once
again I can do
this yipp
yppe
y wonderful would you like
like so generous I don't know how to how
do we trade yeah accept how
accept press T then then click on accept
oh okay darn Mom let's go back and get
that coin oops oops we finished the
quest
yeah here you go thank you exp how do I
get it think you click click the
red okay thank you yay wait actually I
haven't got
it I should have I'm oh no no no he's on
the
chest
oh all right let's get out of
here wait ladies should we create a
should we create a party yeah yeah yeah
let's make party she would have to
invite you oh okay I invite party please
I invite tree as well there you go I
invited hey hey hey hey hey hey a y a
all right let's go back okay is that why
we can't hear anybody
else am I going
back what are you looking at let's get
out of here let's get out of here let's
get out of here
yes woo all right we made it we made it
we got back
to boyan
[Music]
girls
right is this is this house I think it's
over here all
righty we
cannot you got to buy things
yeah you
guys
here um I don't I'm not comfortable
those people I feel very right now I
don't feel that's a lot of people are
you sure they're not going to attack us
should we should we should we come back
another time we should come back another
time maybe we should introduce ourself
maybe we should make more aliens and
more
friends we the am coins we might not
must not be iau you nothing KY you trust
no one I'm sorry
[Music]
how do I make a
pickaxe you can't make the see my master
bring the material can the it for M was
made immediately do you have the
materals C wooden
pickaxe wait what see my master the
master we can go to the quest Master
where's the master espe wait do I have
to do something with them
everybody have their pickax oh yeah no
she gave you oak logs right yeah yeah
yeah I think they're in the Box still
right yeah I open it and then
okay we have to purchase you do not have
the requ we got to make planks and
sticks all right I made okay we need
plank I have planks and we need sticks
all right I thought I was I was trying
to skip the process I understand I'm
sorry so we need to make planks okay I
got this um perhaps my my
group how many I can do that
pickaxe oh okay I got all of it and then
what what do we have to do now
complete what we do now I made
the oh more things complet we
completed thank you so much Master over
there if you bring the raw material next
CFT a wooden pickaxe I made it oh
Cobblestone
Cobblestone too many people at once
wow to
my is this all of our money am I am I
using all of cobblestone okay we got to
go get cobblestone right yeah yeah okay
let's let's wait for the other girls out
here
yeah c St with the pickaxe I see I see
there's an order to this after that
we'll probably make a a
spoon spoon we shall get
sand you just brag about being old three
it's not really I'm out all that's not
what that means that's the next Quest so
shallow go you think you think just cuz
someone's older or younger they don't L
that's shallow the
B I keep hearing hearing something in my
ear but you know it's just three C stone
is
here I'm just sometimes I
wonder oh no careful it is it is a
nightly time where many danger awaits Us
in the outside field yeah is our current
Quest here
Cobblestone Cobblestone 10den
Cobblestone I still don't understand we
all need to get Cobblestone all right
you got 10 Cobblestone each one of us
needs like I don't know how many 10 10
Cobblestone 10 Cobblestone okay yeah oh
that makes oh I'm sorry that makes sense
because then we can upgrade our tools
and PR we made it I'm going to get a
little more right so every time if we
get if they ask for 10 we collect 20 you
know that's the what you know Amber coin
is always about
about you got to think ahead plan for
the future I think you're very smart
today thank you three was that a genuine
compliment coming from you I'm going I'm
going to get extra extra Cobblestone
just in case we need I really don't
think we're going to get a long three if
we
don't hey stop fighting you two I think
I think we got a slowburn going
on it's morning good
morning
righty I've got enough I'm ready to go
back are you all ready to go back yeah
I'm how how much
need 10 right
yeah
okay and we go back to the back
me I say Scarlet it makes my ears perk
is it here oh yeah it's here it's
here let's see h
a TR hi come come
here to the black
oops all right uh talk to my mouse okay
more TOS his I already got a wooden
pickaxe you have a wooden pick
what here materials you can use for St
to and a bit of
Co okay open the trade box right I've
been trying to do a we can craft stuff
now
what
cool I am no longer rich I don't have
enough coins oh oh I don't have enough
coins either we need to go farm
maybe how many coins you want I am no
longer Rich no I am no longer Rich all
right I have 21 coin I'm poor what what
what do they want us to
buy bless you do we have to buy buy
nowe I have a feeling it tast like
cookies yeah know what's you're V we all
losing oh what we supposed to do now I
think we have to go back to the uh maybe
the the quest board oh okay maybe me
would sh you quest moner let's go to
Quest Master Quest master all right you
know how to open the
TR it's somewhere I forgot I can't
remember okay this way oh here here oh a
new face is here hello can you guys hear
oh oh thank God hello there's so many I
have no idea who are you why are there
so many cute girls around
me are you in me lady oh I I don't know
what I'm doing I'm going to lie you
sound like someone I want to get my
nails done with who is your name what's
your name I haven't gotten my nails done
in ages my name is Iris and I don't know
anything else besides that name oh so
helpless and
[Music]
weak honestly it makes do you know what
cup you're in my dear you go a cup what
do you mean cup I got a new Quest what
what quest what what do you mean cup
what group are you in my dear I I seem
to be in The Blue Team oops oh that is
the seruan cup that's what I was asking
oh goodness all right another one gold
okay there a problem with that speak
tooper is it ours matters hey number
three I haven't said it do we have to
what have I done to these people I don't
understander you know interesting I
don't know my quest says speak to
shopkeeper hey did you not get a quest
that say so build
something question what I I don't think
I've done I I don't want to know what we
all heroes but I we
interested in construction
and and request
yeah I'm rich what your say oh I'm so
rich I have the
same I mean the
B we um no I got the same Quest though
okay that's good we'll pass the garden
and you'll find an
oh yeah there are many
quests oh there are more than ones I see
it like we can actually switch the pages
oh these are all the side
quest okay let's get all of them this
here looks like the perfect job for you
okay complete the side quest and then
speak to the quest
master I see go suddenly okay over there
I'm yeah oh you know the blue people yes
you do you want to like join the blue
people or you could join us
too yeah I don't know who the blue
people are I I honestly trust you guys
more okay you can join us because I
haven't even them our our party leader
shall invite you too yeah I'll invite
you I babysit you babysit me please yay
yay
are you still on your first Quest yeah I
am I am well we can help you with that
thank you how do I I how do I accept
this invite um um you click T and then
you click on accept with your
cursor there you go okay okay nice
nice excuse me excuse me uh you you you
seem to have a blue aura around
you no we have to
I found her I found her help teammates
teammates to the quest they're they're
trying to kick her they're trying to
take her away no she's ours now she's
ours they're trying to take her away
she don't fire it turns
my you were not there when she needed
you Qui come with me no
our I think it's too late now
so can
have what what you're Bing me no h you
want to be with us you can be with
us we'll help you complete your come
here come here come here come here let's
go Iris come hereis
let's go leave them behind
byebye no come to the dark
side the dark side know you have two
halves one dark and and a lighter one
you must listen to
the oh my gosh she's suddenly hitting me
she's suddenly hitting
meit you will
hit BL lady the blue lady the blue lady
get out of here you evil
massage re see that's why you were
Mass
re
ration
[Music]
reting oh nice fist oh my God such cool
moves yeah they look like from a retro
Revelations
Revelations Revelation what's a retro
game yeah yes I know Nots of what you
speak hello who are you you beautiful
beautiful violin lady oh at least you
know I am to be the next Queen of the
kingdom of lesto what I did not know of
your intentions oh so that's how you say
it this is not an intention this is
meant to be your destiny it was meant to
be it was meant to be are you Rel to
them are You The King and I you must be
blood related are you blood related to
that tiny King what no we have and we
knew that did did you marry him you
married the king
that with the King did we just Ste
another
part supposed to
me well you don't
have wait I wanted to oh B was talking
to
me oh my God let me call her
[Music]
again
hello why did you hang up on me I'm
sorry I didn't understand you were
calling
me sorry my mistake oh my goodness I not
three I'm not talking to I'm talking to
kitty cat at at the moment did we just
do we do we just do we do we just kidnap
a member are we causing Guild
Wars yeah but that's okay kitty cat yeah
I'm talking to ba the phone oh hi she
says hi she says
hi okay she hang out okay so are we are
we going to help Iris or she left uh is
I think she'll just like probably end up
leaving her grip and go to uh the blue
people
okay want to commit to us that's okay
let's let's go to shopkeeper then or all
right yeah is yeah let me find out one
sec awesome uhhuh okay let's go here
follow me follow me'll have to figure
out follow me follow me one way or
another follow me it's right
here should be here children that
shopkeeper it should be
here a
do you see
any there's a
chef Sim this one speaks a little
Italian
cat this is a
shop yeah oh I was muted I'm sorry I was
muted by mistake I was muted by mistake
M yourself I don't know why it mutes
itself I'm not sure
why I I shopkeeper okay this is a shop
but I don't see any shopkeeper do you
see
any I I I think we're actually aren't we
doing a a different quest for me wait uh
do you know how to how to see your quest
like is like but mine says who's
interested in construction yeah
exactly okay and what he says what you
got to
do oh oh right now I have to speak to
the
shopkeeper okay good okay good let's
let's let's find the
shopkeeper this is the shop but there is
no shopkeeper
hm is that like a quest
book I don't see any Quest book did the
other girls also take the same Quest I'm
not sure like B wait let me do a do you
want me to call her
I suppose so I'm going to make a party
group call
okay Outdoors you me Outdoors you going
to hang out
huh I found I found the shoper oh you
found it good she's right here cute
little hat there you go oh that's so
cute so are you the
one mhm I know he doesn't do anything
for my quest okay we completed yeah
completed yeah speak to the shop press
like I just skipped everything
conspiracy theories and like now we have
to speak to the child in the
garden exuse me one okay now we have to
go to the in the
garden where is K come here you have to
go to the
[Music]
Garden where
the I see the I see the child oh I see
it it's out this way like
mhm this
s oh she's following me
oh
uhoh child before is it
[Music]
here where is
she Lucky Day right well this here is
the gardens feel free to come and use
them whenever you like pretty Acy in it
my job is to keep an eyee on them scare
any away birds and stuff
if you don't like gardening you can also
try building and there's an empty lot
just past here where you can where where
your Heroes can build whatever you like
and you and your guil mes can work
together to make a right spy place to
stay stop by anytime if you want to do
some building or gardening oh say can I
tell you a secret did you know there's a
place in town called the pit fighting
pit mom says us kids aren't allow to go
but I heard you can play a really fun
game there oh you're hero so I bet that
let you in maybe you can go check it out
and tell me what it's like okay anyway I
hope to see you again all right complete
speak to the pit doorman ah you know
what it is okay so I guess they just
generally wanted to tell us that we can
we should or could build something but
they I guess it was just inspiration and
now they want us to talk to the Dorman
okay yeah let's go do you know what it
is I yes this map always tells me where
to go
I
fall let's go
what but it's like a little bit slow to
update I got to stop
sometimes over
here I'm following ah we're back at the
Emin place oh there we go hit him hit
him excuse me what are you doing
it's a
misunderstanding what are you doing
here don't tell
me we have
drama no there and the Amber coin it's
okay you guys can go ahead without me
I'll
just J sword Guild
monster yay I got it okay sword
master okay we need to talk to the Jade
sword Guild Master so we have to go to
the other way I think you skiper skiper
again yeah you can wait for me please I
love no it's
okay you can I love it it's okay it's
okay so what guil Jade guil Jade sword
Guild Master yeah this is the messenger
oh this is the messenger we probably
have to go to the green
[Music]
side let's go
over somewhere over the rainbow I think
it's can oh
it's where is
it oh too early sorry hello okay let's
go this way
way you know but if you kill
him this
way still following good I'm
[Music]
following Jade
sword H wait
I get her where she
where is
she where is
she
oh party group I'm want to call
her lost you what yeah oh oh you were
calling me
I was like what is this
sound hey you just got to you know you
got just got to follow like the on the
map the the the name that says that says
VES oh okay yeah it's a red name V mhm
oh I think I there you are oh I saw you
over
here over here oh oh oh I see it thank
you oh my God
you know where I am yeah yeah yeah I got
to talk to the guy in the middle
wow was somebody's sticky keys okay
stinky who has hardest mission
ever call you're really please socialize
with me
Bain your powers
of that end I have just Reed words from
one of our SCS regarding to the to the
PLS to speak to
this on the Jade sword oh
interesting can you read an Italian
accent oh
where have you skipped everything again
no then read wherever what you seeing
right now
okay uh go for with
Valor and I'm here today to thank the
Guild Master bravery and Leadership
really hates flirting with me they're
nothing say much oh you got to talk to
the middle guy oh I already talked to
him oh you Skipper
skiper are you actually reading well a
little bit Yeah they put some work into
the floor you know you know you know
what from now on I'm never going to skip
a again okay okay
wonderful so oh see Iris was abandoned
once
again yeah gone with
the
oranges
yeah we would not have abandoned her no
she abandoned herself she abandoned
herself for real it say exit the Town
Gate head to the Plains and speak to hus
of the Jade sword okay
okay
to
map ah I see okay wait how do you find
the the the the gates uh when you open
your map mhm it's a bit hard to see even
for me because at the very bottom left
left a
body uh but yeah on the bottom left like
the whatever um you know there's always
something written and R when you have a
quest oh really yeah the wri thing in
red is always the goal where you got to
go oh oh I see it now just follow that
direction yeah I see okay thanks I am an
experienced uh traveler and Warrior so I
know these things please feel free to
rely on me little cat so nice I'm so
lucky not my first Adventure I must say
she's experienced certainly not my last
she's experienced indeed
allora okay
uh let's see oh he's pretty far maybe
yeah we can go for a little Adventure
that's gool yippe you yeah let's go with
the
horse wow wow it's
nice wow W what are these mountains look
at that it's such such a big
map amazing what oh look there's
something
here oh I think yeah we reached
it oh yeah is this one the hello I'm
going to read for you now
okay read hello you arrived we have been
expecting you our initial for for foras
have determined that the portal into the
ruins is yet sealed with no way to enter
the ruins we are at L at a loss for how
to proceed some have reported hearing a
strange voice but we know not what to
make of it the boy seem to be saying the
souls on of St open the
way what might
what they're attacking us while we're
reading not
safe keep on reading keep on reading
okay okay
oh I cannot read
anymore why it's
skipped all water coincidence skip skip
I'm joking I'm not joking I'm serious
was the last sentence what might have
mean by that that was the end no worries
yeah okay slay 10 stains let's do this
let's do this let's go I wonder when
we're in the party it should normally
count each like
[Music]
right well let's say let's go oh here
you cannot proceed yet oh ow I need my
sword you have a sword yeah what's your
weapon actually oh um my weapons this
one yeah use that one it's stronger the
Perfection
executor no the perfect exe execution
perfect a executor yeah the perfect
executor
nice I kill Port because we need food as
well oh yeah careful I I don't I'm going
to make some food now
cuz like usually don't you have to press
right click in Minecraft when you want
to use your
Shield it doesn't I'm going to provide
food
now or provide food huh yeah make food
because we starving you making food oh
no actually we have 63 bread so I don't
think we need 63 bread don't you have so
much 6 yeah wait when did we get that I
think it was like a a quest reward
H is it auto blocking I
wonder not sure hey a bird
bird a also is there like a I don't see
like anything that says how many we have
so
[Music]
far yeah it doesn't says but I think we
can just go
check let's see it will say once we have
all 10 of them oh yeah probably says
that it's complete can proceed okay
thank you for
observation we're done we're done oh is
that why I st spawning okay we're
sorry thank you guys we can't wait to
play again or I fight together again are
you leaving my wife we we must away
yes we have we got the fireball man yeah
it is me the Phoenix of the fires and
the oranges hello lady of water Lady of
water I can put out your flame in an
instant try it then put out my
flame yes I
am that will not stop me good luck my
beautiful beautiful at least I can swim
un likee you you wouldn't know
you don't know anything about
that all right okay I don't know but I
have a feeling I will know well how
about you prove to me whether or not you
can swim there's water right over there
this wonderful
wonderful around over here shk oh cute
you can actually cook get get in there
yummy there's a diamond how about you go
get that diamond back into the yeah have
you have you done with the quest and if
i s
a
Oho I shall save you by that because I
am a
hero a green and I am another go on go
on and I'm a big are you scared we're
both walking yeah give me your big best
grow this nice so
try that was really
scary that was so scary no
I I guess I accidentally kind of uh
killed her in indirectly
um why um well what Guild do you belong
to traveler all that is none of your
business uh cat what Guild are you part
of with no don't don't tell her don't
tell her I am
everyone's
help she just like role playing really
hard
why is she
[Music]
drown where's my sorry uh sorry kitty
cat uh yeah um we done with the quest
right yeah we're done with the quest now
it says investigate the underw dungeon
no I don't wait it still says slay 10
stains for me honestly okay let's let's
do more
then okay okay okay okay cuz I maybe you
got 10 but I didn't and so it really
counts for it's okay I can
help
Okay good time I was meant to save her
how would I have saved
her it's okay she died at my hands it is
my
fault
Diamond we're just looking too
nice need
go this really feels like an MPG right
now h it beginning area all the weak
mobs I love it so many
strangers stranger
danger what can we get
ore I guess we already could if did do
you have a stone pickaxe uh yes I do oo
let me try
then go for it what I got it
but it didn't give me or maybe I need
the iron one
M yeah I need iron wait okay let me
finish this
[Music]
one when you're done we got to
investigate the underw dungeon I guess
I'm probably done why is Iris still
listening your party oh
true didn't she leave the party she's
still written on the you should leave
the party
well hastus has nothing to say to me it
seems
no did you just like talk to this guy
again and he said Quest complete or what
yeah yeah like no no when um there he is
has to when I killed 10 of those mobs uh
it says Quest completed on the bottom in
green hello wear on the phone you could
just call me ba on the phone each other
on the phone B sometimes we're not next
to each
other I Tri follow you I love how we we
thought like all righty we got to talk
to you our initial for determined that
the portal has been yet to be sealed
there's no way to enter the ruins where
M again no I was muted
again I don't know why so of the the way
anyway I was saying um when I was done
with Quest it appeared on the bottom
left the the text saying oh complete
this Quest you know yeah okay it still
does for me so maybe I have like have
you guys completed let's try again then
guys we're going to kill people we're
going to go kill people now more well
they're not B I'm sorry I was muted by a
mistake it's okay have you completed the
quest yeah we we're doing the one with K
now and then we go to the dungeon are we
going to go together yeah we got to
stuff too wait we can we can leave the
private call and then maybe have a party
call oh maybe how do we do that I don't
know oh I I left now
okay I didn't know that we were in the
private
call that that counts as one right
doesn't keep do we have to count
ourselves four I think so ah I I am done
with
it I'm on four right
now get out you're
done how's it going
K it still says that is no fin
me
wait I don't know ah I don't know how to
make a party call with all of us okay we
can I can make a party call when SEC
okay I think I think you guys may need
to accept I'm I'm calling you
guys I'm not getting any call M
weird maybe it doesn't
[Music]
work we are in a party though yeah oh
well how come I still hav I'd certainly
have killed 10 by now try to talk to
this
dude and see what
[Music]
happens I know he doesn't really it
doesn't says anything no
maybe that's
weird oops
nine one more I need one more I got it
right away that is weird no it's mine
it's
[Music]
mine kill
kill dang
it
[Music]
h oh I just realized you guys haven't
been able to hear the game volume this
entire time I'm so
sorry but that was mine
[Music]
is is game volume okay for you chatini
is it good enough let me know if it's
too
low did you do it I got the quest
finished yet oh you did you done the
reason the reason was just because um
like I probably killed way more than 10
but like you participated in some of the
kills so that made it like your kill and
not my Kill ah oh it didn't count
together weird no it doesn't I see okay
good to
know I wonder I need to ask Steph like
if if the stats of my sword are better
than the basic
sword I'm excited for the dungeon
actually the dungeon we're dungeoning
now yeah we're dunge now here here let's
go let's go we going together finished
yeah
okay you you have you all proceeded in
the quest right yeah what the quest says
just to double check it says investig
the underworld dungeon right yeah okay
good we can go then let's go let's kill
this
okay let's do those oh it's actually
right there huh yeah let's
go woo woo
let's go time to fight time to fight are
you ready yeah let's go yeah let's go
Amber Co
Amber
ambero I hate the horse enter dungeon
ready ready I'm ready wait oh wait enter
ready ready yeah I'm ready yeah are we
clicking ready I I'm click I clicked
ready okay standing by to enter dungeon
okay oh enter dungeon no player standing
by what what do we just click enter
now it says no player standing by
though I think could it be uh Z can you
like in your party settings cuz you're
the party leader can you kick oh wait wa
wait wait wait you can click out wait
click out and then go back in cuz then
it says that I'm waiting now oh wait
wait
wait wait I click
what do you see it
now no I said how do I get
back how do you know how do you do that
ready B how do you do that again well
well I just walk back and then walk
closer to it
he says no player standing by um wait do
you want to disband the
party now and then I think it's because
iris is in it so and then we can remake
the party Iris okay
Iris how do you just band the party now
oh here right
click and
then
uh invite fail to invite wait you kicked
B from party yeah I'm out oh oh I see I
see I see I see I see I'm out I got
kicked okay now I'm out as well all
right is make a new party
yeah party do I invite you guys yeah
we're I see you say l and m think B you
yep I'm in okay you in right hold
on the party or ready to oh I'm in the
party oh Okay we okay there we go let's
dry again this this one out of one is
that okay
okay I'm ready now it's working oh now
it's working yeah I'm ready
too okay ready ready M press ready press
ready
ready it looks like you didn't press
ready yet H it says that I did though
like what oh no no I didn't uh three
hasn't pressed ready
yet three has gone three oh
three where is
she where'd she go where did she go
she's gone
serious oh three oh oh did she like fall
for the world or something oh
maybe three what happened three talk to
me tree come
back count on the tree
she's entered the dungeon what what okay
we got to enter all
right my accident I guess okay I'm going
to going to go now are we going are we
are we entering hold on hold on hold on
can you not exit the
dungeon uh do you guys even hear her cuz
I don't hear her oh I'm I'm calling her
I'm calling
her
uh maybe do you spawn back at the when
people talk to themselves because they
have those air air buds in their ears
and you don't realize they're on the
[Music]
call we kicked you already are we going
to
wait do I have caps lock on I can't tell
oh think I do yeah it's probably
glitching yeah party the
party all
right confusion has entered the chat
what we doing are we waiting for
threee yes okay well three come
oh oh there she
is hi nice to see you once again hello
hello have missed you yeah we missed you
very much seems like I missed all of you
too am I in the party now you always in
the party you need to be ready I click
ready I was not right now but hold
on don't click the sword click just yay
yeah are we
ready okay okay okay let's go time right
I'm ready
Victory explore don't ask why but here
to the door the
Underworld the domain of boundless
oppressive Darkness as fear it is
unavoidable it holds the final resting
place for every creature that walks the
Earth yet even in this realm of the Dead
those are who live and call it home oh
my this feels like it was written by the
hands of death oh my goodness what are
we going to do um must EXP orange
juice
juice uh I don't think that's orange
juice um no which are we supposed to go
maybe we go I know that you really like
the fire C but oh maybe this is not the
kind of fire you
like I like any kind of you can do it
jump
no oh wait wait wait hold on which which
which block is it
from it can do it
excuse me big dump big dump big
dump like
that oh it was the wrong oh I see hold
on the buttons are different I mean what
buttons I mean oh I just forgot how to
run for a second hold give me a
second yeah almost
almost here here
Z
here I got it let's go it's a different
button sorry where did they go I don't
know okay we got to jump again okay
okay
wait I don't know where they
are
H
three maybe
over here oh I see them I see them come
here you see them okay okay okay okay
yeah okay okay we need to jump over here
first I think wait wait oh over there
okay yeah over there and then we go in
the circle okay yeah and we jump over
here
now
yeah where are
hello
do there we go
they're catching
up
I'm we jump oh be careful guys okay but
I'm not sure where are we
going are we just exploring we brought
our own blocks I wonder can we place
them uh we can
try I have coup are we just are you just
walking around I think it's this way cuz
there's a checkpoint up here m oh oh
yeah there is something here what is
that new checkpoint unlocked oo that's a
checkpoint yes I I'm not sure where
we're supposed to go from here perhaps
towards that castle oh that would be
that would be a marvelous idea I'm going
to follow you we cannot place any blocks
right no don't
okay all right all right okay jump
here we have full damage
too yeah careful
careful be careful oh I messed
up no no
no she probably respawn on the
checkpoint it's okay oh that's true
that's true that's
true here just wait here it's okay it's
okay oh thank goodness we we lost you
forever so worried that she's back she's
back I heard the answer to the dream
question be careful to the holes you
ever uh dream about
flying I
don't ow ouch that one hurt yeah okay
let's serve this old checkpoint as well
yeah yeah let's go let's go let's go
let's go go to the check oh be careful
here oh
goodness okay checkpoint checkpoint all
right let's wait for the other two
before we sued
yeah oh remember to eat food because if
you don't have the food
bar oh you're not going to run no
someone from the Lava Girl
Shark no checkpoint
oop again it's a shortcut shortcut let's
go let's go to the okay let's go over
here oh oh oh going
[Music]
okay okay here we
go no can you guys be
careful I'll be can you be
careful no
no impossible to jump here okay you can
do you can do
it Amber coin must Prevail yeah let's
go how do we go up from
here side no no B they went left side
Tre help wait for us ah I see kitty cat
come up here again from the side from
behind and then jump and then oh
smart smart
oh at least I'm aile new
checkpoint you go first
okay okay easy easy oh there's a
castle
a a which Disney Princess does this
Castle belong to huh H we coming
look at them go look at them
no okay she should respond
here what is she what is
she one
sec
huh where she
fell she going to come
back I want to I want to wait where is
she H I want to call her now
huh no just jump die for
us okay die for
us no
wait there we go there we
go are we ready everybody after all
everybody full all right let's go let's
go
let's go let fight let's
go oh my oh my oh my realiz weren we
told to go and like not just our
group um I don't
remember this one has only gear what is
that I see okay oh it's so dark yeah we
don't need anybody else just oh I'm
still on Co I'm
sorry
phone careful
nice check the corners check the corners
are we're doing go
W nice next time let's stick to each
other because we're going to get lost in
this dungeon yeah yeah we found the do
wait what is this we found something
what oh I got a triangle someone got I
got a triangle
what can take it why how did you take it
how you filled it up or I I think we I
think the zombies are going to drop
those so we got to kill more okay so we
need to find a star and a circle to fill
it right okay I found the circle and the
star star let's go we got the
star immedately brought it to us there
you go we need a
circle I'm how do I put the circle in
how do I put the right yay let's go
we have several
circles yeah make sure
stay oh another
checkpoint remember to eat yes remember
to eat everybody
yeah
wow what does this say checkpoint
another life expired leaving behind a
tiny flickering light a soul
representing a legacy and an
ending read for us read for us the
veiled figure cradled it in her hands
and with a hint of melancholy she
whispered is this the right thing to do
it's if you need to ask it's never the
right thing to do
okay let's
proceed Amber kind Amber kind Amber kind
Elber
coin wao there's so many stairs I don't
I don't like there so many why are there
so many stairs I know
myot is this is this a a puzzle there a
puzzle oh
no I'm going to be absolutely useless
all right um two but what what changes
it I don't know I just touching it how
what are you
are you right clicking it maybe we have
to coordinate H maybe each each person
takes charge of one side or so yeah wait
are we supposed to put all the lights
onto onto the front face
maybe I think you just want the whole
thing to light up yeah I think all of
them have to light up I see I love these
kind of riddles I hate these kind of
riddles I hate them too is this okay hey
oh oh wait mine was full for yeah it's a
each each affects the other side like
it's not just one face ah I
see um wait hold
on that's we should just observe for a
bit I'm not sure if this might not
actually be the to stop every Guild from
proceeding we can do it I believe too no
no no no is a distraction that would be
funny okay I have to go to an idol
meeting it's just not this is probably
not the best time
maybe trying to figure out one side I
think I can't change anything
anymore huh did I use up my
tries okay
[Music]
oh I can't do
anything difficult it seems like a good
time is it a good time I do need it I'm
going an item meeting and let you guys
figure this okay I'll be right back
H I
can't oh oh I F I F I F I F so I just
got a little bit
frustrated give me the power to press
the light I don't understand the the way
they
change I think it's like it's
um okay so it's the
two I'm just going to keep pressing
until something works oh wait I think I
I think I I understand can someone go to
the other side and follow my
instruction yes okay uh up on the top
top top top left click on the top
left okay nothing happens no it's the
adjacent ones it's the ones next to each
other turn on and off okay okay got it
oh why can't I was able to cck it before
so like maybe it's better like if two
people just do that cuz maybe like we
can coordinate better I'm not sure oh I
have also lost the ability R you're on
your own no oh God okay
okay you're on your own okay I I'll try
I'll try let me let me do
it wait IOP
[Music]
H
weird press too many
times pressed it too many times okay
[Music]
here Q are of the
orange Q of the
orange no
[Music]
H I don't understand based on what they
they I'm trying to I I I try to regain
oh no it still doesn't
work still can't press it I I am trying
you're doing great I am
trying okay this
one do you have any kind of strategy you
L up no I'm just like trying to
understand the pattern that's how I
would do it
honestly
so if you have any suggestion you're
doing
[Music]
great they can't use it anymore either
so do we have to make just one line
or okay one side is light oh nice okay
what what about I hope it stays like
that I hope it stays like that
yeah looking good though looking good
looking
good I me know if it
changes uh yeah left side is still safe
and full okay okay let's let's keep it
as it is we're still at it and is the
only one able to press things what oh
yeah I know you want to probably keep
those the way they are on the left side
we've got one face down we just need the
other two to
go two other three three yeah I feel
like just indiscriminately pressing them
without
communicating work what do you mean that
sounds amazing to
fa okay it's working one sec this is
just like I'm so nervous come on come on
Kitty
doing great
Kitty I'm trying to
[Music]
understand oh no we've lost the side
no wait it's it's changing on itself oh
no I think I think three is also
pressing oh my bad my bad
me to
do I don't know I feel like everybody
working on one side maybe it doesn't
work
[Music]
oh send
help send
help maybe they deact like the deps
deactivate our powers so that only I
wonder how the other is going otherwise
it's too chaotic I wonder yeah one group
apparently solved it so far oh
wow
what we can do it oh well I wish we
could press it yeah not good you guys
can't press
it was there like maybe a specific way
to make it I'm not sure another group
made it apparently no uh
a there should be a a reset button you
mean they're really is one or are you
just saying I mean where's the where's
the reset button just got to see which
one is I don't think there is
[Music]
one okay try to do the same pattern not
the opposite yeah let's try actually can
you tell me actually okay let me see we
probably need to face the
other sorry this is like so on
you no it's okay okay let me check this
spotter actually let's try to understand
the logic of a yeah so I mean there's
like I know there's a simpler way of
just like being like Oh you clicking see
oh you're clicking again okay you can
click then okay let's do together I can
click yeah let's do together
M oh oh almost almost almost no oh saw
you I can't look anymore yeah it looks
[Music]
good okay now okay now I I I got an idea
oops mhm she can do
it adjacent blocks ad Jason
fls keep on clicking
keep on PING at it oh nice nice nice you
got this one oh
wait you had this
side how that works I really don't get
the logic of this
game if you wait so now this starts wait
wait wait
wait do unide out of time because you
can if you I don't know how to explain
this very I don't understand why you're
not able to click it though though maybe
it's a bag there's no way that it's a
limit it the yeah yeah it's probably a
bag but it's probably better than all
four of us doing it at the same time so
that is true yeah but the way to do it
is like you just keep track of like what
each like when you block what it
fills but you just got to be mindful of
the ones that are on the side because
they'll affect the ones that are on
different face yeah so like careful
touch like so here's good
this is probably good but you can't
can't touch
these there you go
there yeah yeah pretty much good all
right you're doing
great
yeah oh looks
good something like
that I feel like you're you're very
close you're doing
doing so good than you
oh let's
go did it she did
it
MVP y
the the goat cat all right time to be
useful again let's go oh my
godington
underw chier yeah as can you
see be
careful I don't know if we should have
gone this way get up the whole
bridge I I that might what he's
doing no no no wait
what a checkpoint oh this is a new
checkpoint okay oh scrip supposed to
happen script to death all right script
okay what is this don't eat it it's a
mushroom
um
me let's try to kill those the mushroom
meanwhile
oh yeah I know what to do I know what to
do ah what you do oh wait someone
someone received bone
meal yeah okay can you use the B on the
mushroom the
mushroom and then and then we cut the
tree oh
more can we make it bigger maybe I'm
going to
die this is hard to asend
come
here if you have bone meal please use it
okay okay okay
supp I think we can
[Music]
climb thing the thingy nice nice nice
nice nice
nice I got
you there you go nice nice wo it's so
big no oh it's like spawning the
the okay what do you call it
again W this is so cool
fire good job get get them to die like
on the Tre can we go now you can I know
can we maybe maybe we yeah maybe let's
try oh I think we might be able to
ascend there's a button here oh how do
you climb there's a button on the tree
just press press space jump into
it
buttons maybe
no I think might just be scar oh there
you
go are you going
up oh God but actually we might oh no
it's already reaching the top I can
see you sure
yes
it's maybe just from
here
we what weird I don't
know wait who went on the
top May the vines right yeah maybe from
The
Vines yeah
[Music]
K I don't think the buttons do
anything yeah she's there this spase bar
it doesn't
work I fell
a oh oh I made it
okay and
then which way I made it okay here and
then up here up here
oh
difficult okay the
buttons
okay I wonder what this
does those
buttons
buttons I wonder what those buttons are
doing oh you just follow them I think oh
you just follow
them
oh okay oh we here
no of
course of
course I had to fail so
[Music]
miserably I can do it
okay okay let's follow let's follow the
buttons I can do that easy
easy okay okay okay more I'm
[Music]
coming she's coming
I'm coming a there you go yeah jump on
that one in front of you and then to the
side over
there and then here I'll catch you
kitty y I thought have to call the
firefighters I thought you would get
stuck in the
tree but we have more trees now oh my
God not enough though not enough there
only one skeleton at a time this is
pretty difficult dungeon wa wait has to
down the tree has down on the
tree one
come come
here TR him oh wait wait wait wait wait
don't kill a he's going to kill me wait
doesn't drop the bone meal no it has to
die onto the tree onto the tree oh
okay come here come
here by
another
one be careful there's there's lava
here
look more over here come over here yeah
no no no oh it's okay no no you can't
collect it it has to be on the on the
tree the tree on the tree yeah yeah yeah
okay okay I'm going to
[Music]
come here come here good oh what is that
oh you you di
yeah is that enough wait I think we need
maybe one more looks almost enough maybe
for safety maybe a few more one more
okay okay okay maybe on the on the left
side okay going to kill don't kill me
don't kill me there you go nice okay uh
seems like fully grown at this
point you can do it
Mom I believe oh here we go here we go I
see last time from there
didn't
yeah I think welcome back I think this
should be okay
now this
try they're holding
hand h
who whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoaa back up buddy hey buddy hey buddy
buddy oh I see it I see
it okay I can do
it you
go ahuh here from here I think I think
over
there no K oh she has to come back
now so painful okay does this then
connect ah okay wait maybe
not
um oh up here up here up here up here
okay come go uh wait and then wait nope
not this way this
way oh God it looks
um I am confused uh oh maybe from here
up here oh no oh follow the buttons wait
how do I go up from here um here maybe
oh the buttons they the
buttons oh my God I'm just seeing I see
red uh no we can't there's no way up
here oh maybe on the top go back down go
back down go back
down oh
here where yeah here wait wait where
oh
[Music]
oh and now I don't
know uh oh do we have to go to the other
tree do you think
probably I don't see the other button
oh maybe down there yeah I can do it I
believe let me go to the go in front of
you in front of you there's one over
there can't you make that one the one
that's there oh W hold
on no this one over here not this one no
the one to the right wait B can you
jump yes I will not be able to forget
that there's no over here is this just
not taking me down or should I go this
way I thought it was this way and then
we go
around I'm just down now maybe there's
multiple paths look seems as if there is
one path and that is marked by the
buttons ladies but there's multiple
paths for the
buttons that's confusing whichever
speaks to
you is only up really the
way and then we go over
[Music]
here okay I just did follow the buttons
but yeah that's what I mean guys I found
it
no scary good job you have Che I can
just kill myself I could woo let's
go yay yeah you guys made me feel like I
was being stupid you got to go down
woohoo I'm going to read the next part
okay I'm going to read this you read
yeah I
read to the
den denance of the
Underworld the
light emanated by Soul was
vetal vital vital you got this your so
well
okay now I cannot read anymore for some
reason
H H I cannot read anymore I don't know
doesn't make doesn't make me click
anymore next page it doesn't work no it
doesn't
work I don't know yeah you can be the
other the other ESL will
continue I needed it to survive in this
ever cold and dark environment yet among
them there was a heretic who called
their Customs into question do we really
need to take others lives to sustain our
own Su stain wink no sah has to be
another way and so she stepped into the
plane above oh plane which plane This
Plane let's
go is the last one I
hope we
done we
done let's go your power of Revelation
has grown
stronger you have recovered a portion of
your memories I remember a little bit
now let's
go
yeah yeah we made it the video did they
give us a better way to play
it oh
hi what the heck Intruder Intruder
Intruder Intruder we need to we need to
play a
video yeah uh just be careful the way
they want us to play the video is not a
very smart way to do it I think we need
to play on
stream uh let me see if they did what we
ask
H I just need to download the video
H okay
wait yes so go I'm going to at you
instead of doing what they the thing in
the Minecraft you download the video
yeah okay yeah download the video and
play I'll do now okay I download
video
wow okay I mute the I'm going to mute so
if we okay I'm gonna mute too yeah yeah
yeah mute to
okay T I have something to show
you and we
see oh wait wait wait wait wait oh that
doesn't work
[Music]
look let's
see
oh this is so cool a Reaper's job is to
end people's lives and take their
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need their
sustenance
but I keep
wondering is this the right thing to
do no it's not
[Applause]
[Music]
what's going
on what look at
that what was that turns out we can also
use people's
emotion we don't need their souls at
all Reaper should help the living
don't take away their future if the
others can't accept that that's their
loss I'll do things my
way
yeah so
[Music]
funny well
I like the way it ended have you done it
I watched it yes oh my goodness watched
it too I'm I'm done you're done okay
doesn't seem done then three is watching
it probably at this moment as we
speak okay it was
funny is that first time wow right yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah it was so cool is
that the memories that they took told us
about that lady didn't we see her
already running
around actually I haven't talked to her
it looks familiar who was that oh my God
she was like slaying oh oh my goodness
I'm her fan now when I see her again I
must talk to her yeah I want to meet her
too that's it we've done the first
dungeon let's go I'm so happy
yo good job good job everybody well this
so good
actually how do we return is it is that
light up ahead where the Moon is I'm
going to return by leaving
oh hero hello who are you what the heck
hello hello travel pleasure to see
everyone are you leaving or are you
incoming we are incoming
oh I wish you
luck this isn't the right way it's not
the right way you have to fall off this
Cliff yes have Waits you otherwise you
have to pay your taxes yeah down there
pay your taxes yeah promise down here
down here down here a member of the
ceran cup I trust easily yeah yeah yeah
just all the way down all the way down
you don't want
to this death there's a Lo move move
further move further I'm
it means you're not
ready oh it's not all me to she's not
ready she is not ready to to to face the
dungeon what's under here oh my my
weapon is so cool
actually sorry we're pranking you sorry
I have regret to say that the bay may be
crashing all right is everyone inside
the D
yeah
enjoy yeah let's head back no we yeah go
inside past the bridge and then we can
split our party kitty
cat we are uh turning back now okay I
come byebye child I hope to meet you
again it was nice to meet you
[Music]
byebye it's fine
oh I'm going to put
[Music]
oops what is that hello hello hello I'm
going to put I'm trying to put
music hold yeah yeah yeah yeah okay done
there you go Yi
yipp
goodbye hello
out the I saw her this is the girl saw
in the dungeon saw you in the vision I
saw her I want to go D with my friends
please explain the vision
explain I want to meet
to can can I can I can I talk to you for
a Mee please can I I have some questions
I'm
sure you will understand Big Ups Liz I I
have I have I have questions
here hey what are you guys doing to my
honorary Guild
M today that's right I'm in the toilet
so
white we go in should we go
inside oh
hello hello hello what's your name are
you also a puppy I am not a
puppy what are you I am a big cat very
one of those dangerous one I can
actually kill
youer yeah I'm very
dangerous
catch I'm a I'm a big cat Sor a big cat
yeah bye well they make a big cat noise
then yeah wow you are ferocious I know
scary right rumors are true yeah I kill
everyone and
everything enter the dungeon if you can
enter the dungeon Fair cat where is the
dungeon oh go oh this is this is this is
the dungeon go oh this is the dungeon
[Music]
oh I did my job I helped I can leave now
I need to go to talk to the Jade
sword Guild
Master I understand
hell wait what is we have to go back
apparently oh
why I'm going to call K
[Music]
can this um do you have to talk to the
Jade sword G Master yeah I just realized
yeah what is it oh it's in the other
oh oh oh wait no no no no this is not
the right guy no no no with it's the
Guild Master so okay we have to go into
the city never mind into the city okay
I'll wait you the entrance bye I did
have the right idea yeah okay
bye-bye hello hello stay here stay here
we
here
here where is he C up I caught up oh I
see I see I see I follow
you what' you say say what did you say
what did you say oh hello
ladies hello
thingss H blue creature I am the
appointed
point the point get it are you a biglet
wand I
speak we had a side quest and she took
over leader of our Guild W that's
cool it looks like you're wearing a hat
like this it looks like you're wearing
like a red velvet cake on your head what
is your name blue
creature it um
um I don't know forgot don't
know hey you aren't you the one that hit
me with your horse oh my
God you are the one that drowned her
this
Skil wait who don't worry I'll kill
whoever what what they do they you hit
me with your h
no no no no no who her right what what
Guild are you a part
of please don't leave me with your you
never
[Music]
know yeah yeah a present for you oh
really you want 60 22 two Mangrove logs
if you tell us what color your guild
is
really here I 24 I'm opening I'm open it
no I want I want the big hat or nothing
no
B then nothing it's okay
goodbye wait wait let me reason let me
reason you don't
understand if I take this hat off uh-huh
I will
die so it's a it's a trade your life for
this
hat no that doesn't know her life and
the
hat I
I I think I want the Hat anyway but what
if we give you uh a wood instead I I I
don't I don't want a wood I want I want
this hat
specifically well you're not going to
get it how about how about
I can offer you the opportunity of a
lifetime have you ever needed shelter
and you had nowhere to go what I can
offer you is instant
tee anytime
place I okay let me tell you I'm a white
cat so I don't actually have a house I
don't need a home so I am okay thank you
but thank you for the uh for the offer
it was actually what yeah yeah no but
you already took it you're now in her
debt no no it doesn't work like that
this come she gave it to you and you AG
works okay listen I have I offer you a
trade you give me 500 coins and I tell
you what you need to
know I do not have that kind of
money I can give you five no 500 and
hat five best best I can give you 500
Andy hats she's not to be reasoned with
no
hat okay no hat but I want 500 coins I
give you five you don't have any backup
who's to say we couldn't just quietly
make you
disappear what do you mean hey that
that's against the rule he leave me
alone leave me alone leave me
alone leave me
alone get out of here social
distance
yeah I need to talk to the killed
Master where is it
where
is
H where read is I'm
going oh I
see h
you're
muted what when that
happen speak to the Scarlet one guil
Master
Okay Ruby
guys I believe no one is actually
reading this okay so do not blame
[Music]
me just swim into the
lava I need to make the side quest
because I want to have a big hat too by
the
way oh it has to be
outside m is muted am I muted why am I
keep getting
muted do you H hello where's my cat
where are you
cat cat you just miss Kia K I just saw a
m she's leaving I mean no I'm there she
is I was talking the
phone okay
take her I go yeah goodbye goodbye I
need to talk to the Scarlet W
Master yeah this one
in this Rubio guy I
think here this one talk to him talk to
him talk to
him okay go to the co and speak to Kon
of the Scarlet one I saw how you skip a
skiper from I know I I read everything
I'm just extremely fast you don't one
second let me check my
[Music]
schedule okay okay okay
okay I can still like continue with you
for a while yeah let's go okay hear me
kitty cat yes be muted no why I'm keep
getting muted why keep on doing that I
hate
myself okay I love you I love you too
okay let's go uh go to the coast and
speak to Corin right yes let's go Corin
wait this is so interesting cuz like oh
wait I know why I get muted because I
press M because I think it's a
map I'm stupid that makes
sense it's like House of the Dragons
It's like automatic because every time I
think the m is the map because I play
Other M mod
when yeah oh true okay well I shall lead
you I shall lead the way let's Le the
weight yeah yeah I follow you wait
actually cuz this one has is proximity
shall we just be on a
call yeah then then it's not proximity
then I can still hear you yeah let's
go okay you let's
go let's
go what a great connection this phone
has yeah there's a good internet
connection in this world
apparently the coast I wonder what
awaits us over there
mm this is such a big Lively City it's
so I really like it it's so detailed and
everything is so cute it's
crazy so many details you went through
yeah I'm going I'm try okay
done okay should be this way but it's
probably really far yeah let's
go Little Pigs these pigs are so tiny
cute cute e do they drop meat have you
tried killing the animals yeah yeah they
drop meat oh you can also cook the meat
oh cook
a make the pasta yeah yeah
yeah I sent um okay little little bit
off role play I sent ra oh a video wait
this is wall i s louder a video
ah oh I think I guess we teleport
through here oh did you
teleport yes you did let's go amazing
yeah I sent her a video uh you know
there's this like really cheap Italian
chain Family Restaurant in Japan called
s media and uh yeah Japanese people love
it I love it too but like it's obviously
not very authentically Italian um but
like there's this video of like an
Italian relatively young guy he brings
his like father or grandfather or so to
CIA so they're both Italian and they're
testing like all the food there and he's
like really critical at first but he
ends up actually quite enjoying it
especially for the price value right
yeah like I'll be honest I think the
pasta was pretty unedible for me oh but
everything else was okay the pizza is
fine right the
pizza piz it's not like the the good
Italian pizza of course
yeah I mean it's call that a pizza in
the first place well I mean it's still a
pizza I mean I don't know I don't cool
that like pizza it's like H I was like n
yeah okay I'm not really convinced the
Italian dude he kind of in the end like
supported any I mean I mean I have been
there just
once oh only once yeah only once I tried
like one type of pasta so maybe I'll try
again maybe we can go together and we we
eat together yeah yeah I think there's a
dessert that I really like it's um uh I
think
what's it
called is it panakot
no it's like the the pizza bread um
fried kind of and then top with the
cinnamon and with a vanilla ice cream M
oh yeah that's a thing that's an act
thing it's so good so
good yummy I do have a feeling that this
will lead us to the next dungeon
possibly in that case like we wouldn't
be able to proceed anyway um but let's
see where it leads do do you want to
read what he says yeah uh I
already I know I was just reading when I
was just reading by the way we can also
have uh we also have a lot of side
quests by the way yeah if this leads us
to the main like the next dungeon we can
we should do a side quest instead we can
do the side
quest so
oh should we yeah let's do the side
quest supplies wanted food but I don't
actually
understand how to check the side quest
in this I still have a side quest opened
who's interested in
construction but yeah I also don't know
how to is there maybe in here maybe I'm
not sure ah if you open the book in your
inventory yeah on page two it says check
your currently active side quests click
here to check oh W oh speak to the Mason
at the construction
area wow okay let's do that then okay
speak to the Mason to constru okay I
found the quest ah that's why on the map
the whole time I have the Mason in
green okay let's let's go to the Mason
yeah okay all right the rest of our
Guild is offline so we shall start
constructing let's go I'm happy I'm
probably not like gonna be here much
longer maybe this Quest and then I might
also go I don't know yeah no worries
it's fine before before this I think I
did like 10hour stream
so I'm I saw I saw like you were playing
um the clono and then you like continued
with normal Minecraft what the hell I
was like why is she playing Minecraft
now she's literally going to be playing
Minecraft like the next day like I was I
was locked in I was trying to build
something locked
yeah I was locked in are you okay I'm
fine honestly what were you doing in the
other Minecraft I was just building a
house for
GT GT GT yeah GT GT morning ah gy G
gy wait sorry
G yeah also like um I'm I'm very very
very very jet led oh so I couldn't sleep
and all right you're back in the other
side of the world yeah I'm back how was
it how was your trip oh it was the worst
trip I've ever
had
yeah what happened yeah everything that
could possibly happen it
happened yeah it was so bad but it's
okay tell me more about it after we talk
to this guy what why you yeah wor of the
scholet one I'm talking to Mason you can
build a a house a store room or whatever
else suits your fancy as long as you
don't go out of bounds each Guild has an
assigned plot and you can only build
inside oh it doesn't talk to you oh uh
it's like I'm still in a conversation
with the oh okay whatever that's fine
now I can talk to the Mason okay okay
okay yeah it was still like continuing
the conversation from the previous NPC
oh okay uh so what you can build a house
a
ah oh so it does everybody build here
then yeah so every every Guild has their
own space so we can Guild ah we can
nobody buildt anything yet huh but this
seems to be our space right the yellow
one yeah the yellow one is our space Oh
it's right here perfect and we have a
construction box so we can already play
something let's see
oh oh just the blocks to receive oh
what like a set of like specific stones
that have a look to them more certain
style we just have
uh I guess I get the same what am going
to
get whoa
what amber corn we got to use something
that's
like uh golden and brown and so on
maybe did you choose some blocks already
no what should I use what should I Pi
maybe the Terra Cotta or or yeah the
bricks no yeah the bricks I was looking
at them too I got the bricks okay oh we
only got the bricks oh well okay I mean
better than nothing there the thing is
the other two you got brick to yeah
no we have a lot of bigs I didn't know
you got wa I can probably abandon the
quest and then redo it right no wait
it's okay I think we there is another
like we can just get more in the future
maybe okay yeah the other two can still
we can build the base with the bricks we
can make something really big now I
me add like Windows and lights and
everything uh 120 blocks is actually not
much yeah that's why we need more okay
let's start to build here you want to do
that can but can we make
them
smaller you can make like a small house
if only we had a stone cutter okay well
ra you seem to have a good eye for
Aesthetics so how big should we make it
first if we're only we have this big
plot but but we're starting with small
yeah we start with a small one we start
with a small one it's
okay is there a craft table
here uh no but actually your crafting
table is on your inventory I think yeah
but only the small one oh may I can make
big
one oh I made a big one I wonder if we
can place it here how did you make it oh
yeah oh just with the planks oh oh right
we can just we can craft normal
stuff yeah oh I
see how do you
[Music]
make I don't think I can do anything you
know what I'm going to do actually I'm
going to make some a
chest one
second and so we can put the stuff on
our chest and uh I can I can I I we can
build something together
yeah oops what what's
the wait wait wait wait wait let me let
me cut it one
sec okay I have a CD I'm going to put
here
okay okay slime ball uh I'm going to put
all the blocks here you know what I'm
going to do I'm going to go grab more uh
food I'll be our back oh okay
we took on the phone oh yeah isn't it
right over there where we can mine oh no
it was somewhere else it should be oh
yeah outside just
outside and here we are again I want to
look inside this
Arena I muted I was muted again damn it
I I keep pressing M Mama
M Mama Mia wait this is not
but
whoa whoa did you look inside the arena
already no it looks crazy really what is
it it looks
amazing we can like hold some big Guild
Wars in here PVP I wonder if they're
going we going to have PVP no I don't
think
so or maybe at the very end in the
finale
everybody will fight each
other that' be cool oh that's where the
am the Ember no the Jade people are
standing wait I cannot find the exit I'm
stupid any of the like big uh doors on
the edges of the city probably will lead
you out any of
them let me just try
Gladiators yeah the light is
beautiful
no
yeah I still have some work to do after
this guys that's why I can't stay
forever oh it's
okay but tomorrow I think I'm going to
stream at the same time yeah I'm going
to do the same
Monday is it so yeah I mean for me like
well okay in jst uh like now it's
already Sunday for you I guess it's
Saturday
right wait what time soon are you if can
ask wait what what right wait you in the
same time zone oh yeah okay we are in
the same time zone
then okay now I start at the same time
so yeah okay we can uh we can meet
here again but then for my other days uh
like uh Tuesday and Wednesday I'm I'm
going to not be able to no worry we you
know what we're going to do I'm going to
help you with the quest when uh you come
back you already then you already know
everything I don't mind really I can
actually like I don't mind I don't mind
I really don't mind I'm happy to I
wonder though if there's anybody else I
I feel like like if anybody isn't
available on Tuesday they'll probably
just do it on Wednesday and
then it's okay don't worry don't
overthink about it I just want to have
fun and we I'm out yeah yeah yeah I'll
be so behind on no no no we we we go
fast through everything if anything yeah
well this dungeon was pretty fast so
yeah
exactly it's easier where did you are
you did you find the wood no I'm looking
for the exes still
oh I cannot find you keep on getting
lost yeah very bad sense of direction I
see okay I found
it good good good good good okay I'm
getting food now let's
go didn't realize that this is what that
was cool
[Music]
oh they did start building here
oh the what which one is this green oh
yeah green the green ones oh they didn't
get really far
[Laughter]
either build that Callie's in green
M
oh I am building I'm preparing stuff oh
I want to make a nice
house
yeah but
like we need a lot of stuff like if we
want to do something nice I wonder wait
with my
Stones can I make a stone
color let's
see my God so
annoying all I wonder if even all items
are unlocked
actually build
[Music]
everything they so
strong I'm not going to
die are we forced to buy
let's just look
[Music]
again sorry I need your
wool okay materials like uh or pickaxes
and stuff we can't build them ourselves
we have to buy them I guess other things
may also be like L yeah we need to buy
them
mhm I think you can Farm money uh
killing monsters like the stains
yeah and making qu doing quests and
doing quests
yes where is it
here ooh ah
armor oh and the blacki okay yeah yeah
yeah yeah do you have can I
buy 50 coins Cobblestone free oh I can
buy this we have we have Cobblestone
though we can get it very easily I know
I know I have still my cobblestone M
should I get a better sword I don't know
which one's
better should I only be using my Phoenix
sword for like the special attack and
then in between I switch to this yeah
yeah yeah yeah I think you should use
the sword yeah this one has actual stats
so
oh
oh was I not doing any damage so far I
think we're doing a little bit of damage
anyway
but how do I get them to sell me more do
I have to continue their
[Music]
Quest oh wait they furnaces do they have
stone
cutter oh yeah if you can find a stone
cutter would be nice I have a lot of
money right now there's all kinds of
things a small where are you in the shop
yeah well they have a lot of things but
wait I don't see a stone cutter come on
there must be one maybe we need to craft
one no I don't think so I feel like
they're not like letting
us but am I blind I don't see why look
for anothera shop and even though like
you say oh uh the armor wouldn't have a
stone cutter but like the he has this
like enchanting stuff and the on the uh
map making table so I feel like he would
have everything else to seems like would
have anything here to be
honest this seems like the
place to be but
H oh
W he grow so
quickly okay I found a shop that sells a
fashion surprise box what what is it I
have to buy this maybe oh my God is this
like in never more p is like the cash
shop where you can buy cute outfits no
are we already wasting money is it
God I have to buy it I bought it I
bought it I bought the fashion surprise
box I okay I want to see I want to know
what it is please tell me three two one
oh oh I get to choose It's
gotta okay okay okay oh I choose
you what what is it
oh
uh
uh huh okay do I only get one of these
or
D equp the B I got like it gave me hats
from each like
Guild uh and it gave me a lot of
construction supplies
boxes cool oh it's already in my
inventory wait oh oh that's just the
reveal of what what was where ah
honestly I'm not mad about construction
supply box Chan I appreciate that
what I right now oh no you just ran past
me oh where are
you there she is let me bring the
supplies box to our building
field
yeah which was over
there got oh my God it's going to get me
addicted but the Hat that's like the
main price I don't know well I I don't
even
start cute outfits
who oh
kitty cat yeah remember when you were
able to choose
the materials that you wanted basically
I got the same kind of box and I can
again only choose like one full block
okay okay uh do not get any
wood um oh I muted oh I muted again okay
uh okay so should I get
glass M Glass m
I I don't know I I feel like having like
64 blocks of glass is such a waste no M
should I get more bricks
no no more bricks I think we enough
enough bricks oh let me think there's
there's a cherry tree logs too no we
have we have uh logs it's fine we can
Farm
them maybe some some cute bricks some
cute blocks that we can use for the
house concrete not bricks you say I mean
we already have bricks so we can make
some variation you
know how
about white concrete or brown
terracotta or the concrete is very cute
the concrete is great wait wait you know
what we you know what we should decide
what we want to build in the first place
do we want to build something big for
Amber coin yeah okay so we should
consider to get the same materials yeah
then we need more bricks do we do you
want to make a build a brick brick house
partially
maybe okay that's fine let's get cuz we
already have bricks so like we're kind
of starting that yeah yeah yeah you're
right I'm I'm looking I'm looking for
some bricks
construction yeah
bricks I want to build more bricks more
Bricks now I spent 300 of my coins for
more
bricks yeah do you sell any
no I want to check out more of the city
of the shopkeepers and stuff let me see
if I can get more oh actually what did
you got the bricks thingy sorry the the
pack the box um from the gacha oh on the
shop
yeah okay I'm not sure if it's like
really worth
it you know cuz it cost me 300
coins I got
it you got it
oh I think it was it was fair to be
honest for 300 for 64 blocks I think it
was worth it yeah especially cuz I guess
we can't get those blocks in any other
way if there's a quest uh where we can
like
proceed with like what the blacksmith
would sell us I would like to do that or
is it like dungeon bomb you know that
would be a huge Flex to make like a
little castle or something yeah wait let
me check which materials do we need
though making a castle is going to be
difficult little castle we need like
[Music]
stones did they have Stones I'm going to
go I'm going to go to
so may I don't remember they had a lot
of wood like different types of wood and
some like
turquoise beautiful turquoise
stones but like I feel like the either
the blues or the greens will use a lot
of the turquoise
stuff wait where is the shop again can
you guide me oh um wait mama Mama Mia
there's a Quest That's Italian oh I want
to read I want to
read come to the quest
board oh one second M Mama M I want to
find the
uh the shop
first where is it let's use a teren
cooking
pot Master's trying to craft some tools
oh yeah this sounds like it continues is
that quest
line I'm going to do that and then maybe
I'll log off after that yeah if you go
to the quest board you'll find that uh
oh you're here almost turn
around oh how oh there we go go read the
Italian Quest I
go uh which one is it uh well you should
recognize it let's see it's the first
one for me page one Help Wanted at the
tavern Help Wanted at the tavern okay
Mama
Mia I I
am more
more I
I I don't have a near enough
help is this how it sound like I I don't
know yeah sometimes okay cuz you said no
hey read the rest of
[Laughter]
it but I don't have a nearly enough help
if you land on me a hand I I I'll let
you use it cooking
P
oh I wonder why he got CAU off maybe the
quest is too long
maybe okay but I actually I I took the
quest that's on the next page because uh
when doing that I think they will give
us um iron tools rather than stone tools
once we complete it oh yeah makes sense
looking for five iron inot so I'm going
to go
outside where is this shop can you show
me the shop where is the um oh it's a I
think it
was oh why was it it all looks so
similar
maybe I found it let
me oh I found it again it's like close
it's like across diagonally across the
quest
board where are you over here over here
turn around turn around turn
around there here if you want to do the
gacha yeah
fun okay where is a time over
here going to get myself have those iron
tools oh wait wait
wait is a castle let B
here it's not where I wanted to but
that's
[Music]
amazing fashion surprise box M I want to
buy it too and you don't even the thing
is you don't even want the fashion you
want the the consolation price don't you
anything is fine yeah I like
[Music]
got
oh I can choose yeah just one and then
it will reveal to you
uh like it will reveal to you what what
uh what was in what space there's a hat
too I want I I like I I want to get I
can't find this cell phone is not very
useful hello
talking do you hear me I'm going to I'm
going to quck the call one second yeah
let me turn let me let me turn off the
coal hello crony senpa I mean I mean I
never saw you before who are you what's
a crony s pie who are you that like a
food who are you Tam I'm a I'm Tam
Gander ah hello your name
yeah my name your name is yeah my name
name is that's a weird name okay well
good seeing you my name is
RA oh
ra yeah
yeah yeah
yeah yeah what's your name to see you
Tam Tam Gander Tam Tam
tber Tam Tam Gander
Tander Tam Tam gander
Tam
Pam Tam Tam yeah t m d
tender not tender
Gander
yes Cam Gander T dander no not tender
Gander dander no not dander g g a n d r
gender no g g a n d r
not it's not damn tender
okay that sounds like some sort of
chicken chicken tendies or something
it's really not it's a I see like
chicken tender no it's not it's Tam
Gander
I you don't have to be mean so like you
don't have to be so mean yeah
got it okay I got it I got it
hello no you don't okay what is my
name sorry how you
doing no say my
name don't
just
rud laugh that's disrespectful
T
Ender what the heck
what stop
laughing
tender oh my
God or you're doing this on purpose
aren't
you
10 he 10
correct t a m yeah t Tam Tam yes yes
tender no g a n d r not tender dander
Banner with the B as um g g GS in good
Gander Gander
yes yes T Gander T Gander yes thank you
so much I got it I got it oh thank you
oh my god thank God I got
it well hope you have a nice
day are are we talking have a very good
day T Gander we are not we're talking
about my name hello we're talking about
her name can I introduce you yes her
name is tan Gander Tam Gander so your
last name is Gander your first name is
Tam she kept she kept saying Tam tenter
pepponi see even she thinks that we're
talking about pizza no I don't talk
about pizza all the
time oh I love the pizza oh my God Pizza
I love that pizza too I love the
pizza I love
pizza you guys remember this language
why do you guys remember this language
what is this language I don't remember
any
this is the language of love the
language of love Yeah is Beau love yeah
I thought it was French that's love wait
what what's French what is French the
only French that I I've heard of is is
the is the smooching French is what I've
heard of what what what is it I don't
know I actually don't know anything else
past that so bye
tender it was very fun not tender Gander
dander oh hello tender you're saying
this on purpose there's no
way you're saying
this hello no she keeps calling me
tenders help tender you she's harassing
me because I cannot say her difficult
name harassing those are my friends
they're in my party so I guess I ought
to disband the party so that you guys
can get back with your ceran
couses oh all right well I'll disband it
for now to disband yes you are
free you are free of your obligations to
your boy I we'll we'll Brave another
dungeon together someday I hope so good
luck on becoming
Queen not good luck it will happen after
okay then I look forward to you becoming
Queen yes thank
you you want to become a queen no not I
going to become Queen not I want to I'm
going to become queen queen of what the
queen of
leeston no what do you mean no I will be
a queen what
yeah oh you're the second oh no no if I
build my castle before you no that's not
how it works oh yeah oh yeah I'm going
I'm going to build my castle right now
bye
I need to get more more Stones though I
need to go to this stop
[Laughter]
oh I found I found I found Hell
I'm actually
crying
okay okay I'm going to open another
box
ooh buy
boxes I'm going to put this one think
okay I'm going to build a castle
now I will take
M to make a
castle
oh yeah I want to get the big hat too so
probably going to get another
one maybe Cobble STP
plate
maybe actually think I can make uh custo
buy cobblestones only
no yeah cobblestone castle will be will
be
cool try selling stained
drops
[Music]
H maybe uh let's
see light source first what kind of
light source do we get though
uh the glow
stone
maybe
[Music]
h no lanterns there are no lanterns here
this is all they
got do you see any
lanterns I don't see any
maybe maybe I'm going to get the glow
stone it looks
cool what is better glow stone or shroom
light H see
Lantern okay fine done done it's too
late can't come back okay I'm going to
farm a little bit I think everyone left
though
[Music]
H I wonder who is somewhere if someone
is out
side I shall also complete some side
quests
I I love the proximity chat it's so
fun wait let me just uh turn on
the
okay yeah I need to build a
Castle give one moment everyone I need
to check pting
[Music]
I'm still thinking about
it so funny oh my
God
gosh okay I want to F I want to build a
castle Bast I
decided I'm building a
[Music]
castle I need the lot lots of
cobblestone and
dirt
Oak I can do
[Music]
that oh how can I make it oh my
god oh okay you know what I can do that
H I can do
thater
cler what do you mean cipa cipa what you
got a cipa cipa here there's nothing to
cipa
cipa okay I'm going to get
more hello are you the big cat
ew hi uh how are you uh how H nice to
meet you nice to meet you I am I am a
big cat are you Amber coin I'm not going
to tell you I don't trust no one I see
it's because you that answers my
question ambercoin members think that
nobody likes them because there's been
some weird rumors spread by Cerulean cup
is that right
what yeah the weird rumors are that
Amber coin is not very
good I think so how does that make you
feel that's right I think they're right
you think they're right I think they're
right oh you're not a big Amber coin fan
are you I hate
ambercoin okay it seems everybody hates
ambercoin huh all righty well I I still
am not going to hate ambercoin just
because everybody else hates ambercoin
well I don't hate ambercoin either
because I have my own opinion yeah see I
like you I feel the same
way I'm going to the coast where are you
going I am going to farm
and I don't know actually I
need I hey how dare
youo nice
gone re
reation reation I I think I'm going I
think I'm GNA get some side quest done
maybe okay enjoy your side quests fellow
traveler I'm going to the coast yeah and
and remember that also Amber coins
deserve some love some time I think so
too I I am not against Amber coin just
because everyone seems to be against
Amber coin why everyone is against Amber
coin it's it feels like it's propaganda
spread by the Cerulean cup but I don't
know I don't know why they don't like
you so much I'm going to kill them it's
me your Amber coin but it's okay I got
you I prefer I prefer to be
open-minded I want to be friends with
everyone that's
right well take care fellow travel take
care
byebye
well well well it's
time for
my
Castle mhm
exactly I need no
one
yeah what is
[Music]
this ah I was looking at
the of the
map ah
H oh someone is calling
me mush MH hey I forgot to call you back
it's okay what were you doing I am
farming to make our Castle oh let's go
yeah I did the like uh iron tool Quest
so now I can buy iron tool oh my God
that's so cool yeah but it's expensive
really expensive how much is it like an
iron sword costs you like some materials
right and 200 coins not that much it's
much 200 coins is not that bad yeah well
the sword at least doesn't break oh yeah
that's cool and then the the the single
tools they cost 100 and the
materials okay that is pretty cool yeah
when you find time you should do the
quest too I'm going to go I'm going to
I'm going to make this side quest soon
mhm I'm going to go too okay are you
leaving yeah I'm leaving okay thank you
for much for playing with me I'll see
you tomorrow at the same time okay see
you tomorrow
byee byebye
let's see who is
online I want to call
[Music]
crony where is
crony oh no she's already a CO with
someone else
fine I'm crafting crab
cobblestone we should also
[Music]
Gober oh she's still that
coal I want to call someone else I'm
going to
call I'm going to
call
GG J is aome a call I'm so Lely I feel
so
[Music]
lonely
hello hello what can I do for you you
you pretty little kitty yeah I'm a big
cat by the way I I was feeling a little
lonely and I said I'm want to call my
friends so I called you oh well I'm so
grateful even though we have just met
each other today that you consider me a
friend I'm honor I don't consider you
friends as said that no no my friend
actually answered to me and so I was
looking for new
friends but yeah you I we can't become
friends because we barely know each
other so we need to we get to know each
other a little better we need to go on a
date you're right where you want to go
to on dates uh well we're about to go
hunt the dungeon in a little bit we're
waiting for those dogs to come back on
okay you call me I'll come okay how much
longer long are you planning to stay in
this world for the night until you
need you're so sweet well if you want
we're by veredus right now me and this
Ki beu Oh I'm right outside farming some
Cobblestone oh well we'll be headed that
way pretty soon yeah I'll see you there
we see you all right goodbye goodbye
[Music]
that's
[Laughter]
funnyes yeah
[Music]
I need a lot of cbon
so
yeah yeah it's fun how they
cry H I see
people oh it's
you what
out there you
go a
all right Fair Maiden beu why don't you
continue down the way because you will
need to kill 10 of these for the next
part of your quest oh I will I will
onward the way yes
goodbye well hello
wow what was your name again sorry I
forgot about it oh my name is narissa
Raven coft oh nerissa Raven coft it's
such a long name
I know you can just call me Risa for
short okay I like Risa will you show me
what your weapon does on one of these
cows yeah
look
ah oh my
goodness what mine does
oh so
cool I love it thank you so cool
do you get coins for getting animals uh
you get
meat nice you like meat I'm I'm I was
farming some
Cobblestone that's a good thing to do a
good way to spend your time yeah
actually I want I want to build
something in the future so I need to hey
yeah we do got to build are you guys
digging yeah we're digging we tunnel no
you gorgeous
they're I think they're digging a grave
what what
yeah no digging you gorgeous digging you
gorgeous we digging on you gorgeous
that's right you digging me yeah we're
digging you I am I am hot pink we want
to we want to Dan to hot pink yeah
yeah well
before hot well Maiden yes what fairy
well Maiden you're trying to right
yes goodbye goodbye goodbye goodbye
lovely Lely
ladies I will do a magic chicken
disappear oh wait I didn't disappear
right away oh shoot I was I
was she's gorgeous I love her I love
Nisa
I love you
oh calm down now you called me you
wanted to be my friend you know how
special that
is
yeah beautiful big
cat please you can't talk to me like
that I get embarrassed come on like what
what I get embarrassed I got so red and
I cannot talk anymore because it becomes
stupid I'm sorry I I have not done
anything fair Maiden please forgive me I
forgive
you ah I must retrieve my dogs alas Fair
Maiden we must part oh okay thank you
for coming by yeah thank you for letting
me Farm some Cobblestone with you H that
was a very nice time thank you so
much men I hope I hope I hope to see you
again I'm sure we will I will look
forward to the day thank you thank
you see you
soon actually need to go back home
to
okay I need to put the some
cobblestone
house and then have some some yeah
didy didy do
that hello who is Gigi is
Gigi someone is calling me Gigi I am
Jonathan G oh
sorry yes what what a good game one
second I must drop the telepathic call
oh it's going to drop it someone else
host it hello hello
what is your name my name
[Music]
is yes one second I forgot my name oh
you don't know your name no I mean you
know uh the Amnesia that happened to
everyone it's kind of like oh uh my name
is
um Mario calling you Mario it's Mario
everyone's been calling you Mario yeah
oh hello Mario I am Jonathan G spelled
with a g hi Jonathan you the name my
name in your head okay so you know how
to spell it I
forgot that's how you spell it why
gathan G no it's Jonathan it's spell no
I said can you come with me because I
have to do something come here I think
it's I think it's gut I will I will come
with you no is pronounced Jonathan I
like I think gathon is better no no it's
Jonathan Jonathan G but I'm not a big
fan of go
Jonathon that's my name I don't know I
don't like it personally name I
personally don't like
it what are you doing here are you
building no I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm trying
to farm materials to build stuff
later
oh yeah
I I I promise to myself I'll become the
queen of this place so I need a castle
you're going to be the queen
ooh I don't know if I can associate with
you I
I I I know the person the king is
engaged to
who her name is cam cam Tam Tam a m Tam
oh are you talking about the fake queen
the fake queen yeah she said that
they're getting married and they're
engaged she is fake how is she fake I
know she is how do you know I've been
traveling with her she's been very
trustworthy and she has stood up for me
she is trying to steal my
spot how do I know that you're the real
queen look at me am I
gorgeous you are gorgeous
yeah
gorgeous what are you doing stop I've
never had a woman's touch
before
stop okay listen I I I I can offer you a
very nice position if you help me during
this okay what I don't not tell you
later when I become a queen what how I
will not stand for this I was a listen
listen listen listen listen we killed
the
king kill the king yeah we kill the
[Laughter]
king she
left let's
see I'm going to do my
quest do you mean
it you're going to kill the king
uh
[Music]
no are you working
with who are you working with I'm
working with um I I cannot tell you it's
secret it's NDA what do they look like
is NDA what's an NDA what's an NDA you
know what is an NDA who are you working
with I can tell
you if you tell me maybe I will converse
with you okay
I'm
working
with
someone who is on the top of
everything what
yeah your hair color what's your hair
color it's
rainbow like it change every day you're
a liar a
liar no didn't
[Music]
I have no
friends I have no
friends I just want to have friends
[Music]
I've thought about it what is what is
your how are you planning on killing the
kid okay I I'll be honest with you
okay I just have no
friends oh so you don't plan on killing
the King and I want to and because of
that I want to kill everyone because I
don't care
[Music]
actually
Jonathan Jonathan
Jonathan
De he
[Music]
left oh cool
okay so I'm going to put these here
too I need more Cobblestone like a
[Music]
lot
cobstone
and
food can I make wood pack
AR they
can't oh there's nothing you can craft
actually just Banks
h i
see Jonathan
G was that Jonathan G
I don't
know oh
well I guess I can I can
[Music]
start
m h to make this Costo
[Music]
H let me
see can you follow a tutorial for
that I think I may stop for today guys
and I'll go rest also
probably
soon I want to go I want to do one side
quest first before I leave I'll be
honest at least
one pi to the Taran Chef okay let's
go t Che
I wonder where it
is uh there was like a t a TN Chef
before
[Music]
H is not the one this is
so
oops
oops yeah oh is it this
one deliver the cake to the Ser cup
Guild
Master oh I need to find it
now the ren cup Guild Master
sounds
difficult need to deliver the
cake I wonder if it's over
here is it ruos
[Music]
no is it here oh is it outside no I
don't think that's the one
[Music]
though
H H I need to collect uh rainbow cor
Shard no that's not the
quest that's not the quest well where is
the quest hm
[Music]
yeah it's such a kid word right it's
crazy
good I love it
[Music]
ceran should be maybe the blue
no is it this part
no h
I'm not sure is
it
h the green
one green one green L bottom left to the
map I don't see it
last St okay we're trying to go there
no oh maybe
maybe report to the th stu okay let's
go I'm starting to learn the game
maybe okay this is the shop
oh
yeah people draw no how
is
this where's the tavern
[Music]
H look like a
chef
no best master
I'm so
confused there's nothing
here b car GPS there's true I should use
the
map
no
uh is it
this I think so
H this is the shop I need the
[Music]
chef I wish I understood oh there you go
you can buy a carrot and potato from the
shop or grow them in the garden oh so
like all those quests they just like
they just help you to unlock new
stuff ah makes
sense help one to obtain a carrot and
potato then speak to the Tav
Chef I need to grow potatoes and cots
okay fine I'll do it
wait
H I thought that I hadot potatoes and
Cur
huh what am I missing
something h Huh bye from the show Oh I
thought they give it to me for
free how dare
[Music]
they a potato and carrot okay
oh portable
Lantern that's also very useful
[Music]
maybe yeah can I actually sell
stuff
no hello Jonathan Reed
hi
Jonathan Jonathan
Jonathan G
hello
hello oh My Hope feel had a good time I
I I I I can't wait to play it tomorrow
again it's going to be
fine okay let's
[Music]
see I'm going
to hello Mario yeah it's me it's me
Mario I wonder if I just PL them
no oh I think I need the tool for
it I'm going to I'm going to
cry I need the thingy
where can I buy armor yeah
here m m
hello so cute hello will you per for me
again I will pet
you
yay thank you
okay let me buy
one I'm I'm I'm getting get
that
pouring oh I keep muting
myself oh I have to go to the
chef okay I'll go to the chef
[Music]
this
cake
[Music]
o hey hello I told you it was all huh
huh what did you got did you got the
memory back do you remember
now I only remember something about
C oh I see yeah makes sense perhaps
we'll get more stuff
[Music]
oh wait I have a phone call one second
mus what are you doing I am I am walking
around we're in the dungeon do you want
to do you want to help you don't have to
it's okay to say no it's okay to say no
I want to say yes okay get here
ASAP thank you
ASP yeah now what is it get get get get
to the dungeon ah I can't come
okay I'm
coming I love
this my cooking B is broken but I need
to get oh
man a oh a I don't know why she said she
said in a way that I didn't understood I
think
she said a a oh I mean I know what is
ASAP I I say ASAP all the time I think
the way she said
that I'm going to I'm going to the
dungeon okay should I just
enter I'm not going to enter alone
right
oh
oh wait let me call
Nisa I don't know how that
works hello hello I am in a dungeon but
how does it work like do we need to make
a um a party yeah we're not in the
dungeon dungeon yet we just went in the
initial one right after you talked to
like the guy originally so we're like
right by the actual entrance so just
come to us we'll invite you to our party
okay I am next to the uh yeah the screen
guys I think next to the dungeon okay
come come into the come into the dungeon
and we'll invite you okay okay okay
thank you
soon I'm going to have them and then
they get
out I think I got to wait
here hello hello it's a pink cat it's
it's me big
cat you're a cat are you sure you're not
a horse no I'm not a horse you're not a
come closer let me sniff you yeah
if you're the who are you
H um I I failed to sniff AKA I failed to
invite are you in a party with some
other people l oh yeah let me actually
leave my party I'm sorry oh how do I
leave H use the use the knowledge of
book The Book of Knowledge oh the book
of knowled okay okay
yes purple now leave your party you need
not them instead you need us well we
need you okay I'm done okay let me try
that again to sniff you sniff sniff
sniff sniff there you go successful
thank you so good W Wy I like all right
let's
go let's go
wo let's
go oh I need to
[Music]
eat enter the dungeon
ready
ready you have to
first oh am I not ready you have to
stand by to ready I
think I think you I think we're all
ready what do we do now
y there we go there we
[Music]
go what is this mysterious door pass by
Miss K P Mor and she told me she lives
here apparently Liv here this is the
under word she did say she was death or
something like that oh the underworld a
domain of boundless oppressive Darkness
as feared as it is unavoidable it holds
the final resting place for every
creature that walks Earth yet even in
this realm of the Dead there are those
who live and call it home o
well I think that's a bad idea to walk
in there yeah I I would have to age how
do we go in over here where do we come
from we probably going to jump
here
what
yeah be careful be careful you can do it
Run and Jump yeah
oh look at
that there's a
thing yeah you got to run you got to run
oh you got to run and then jump yes yes
yes look at this
Pro hold hold on hold on hold on hold on
hold
on okay okay I'm good yeah okay now
where do we go we go over
[Music]
here you get prop for me I need
bread get get some
bread no I think we have to go over here
over
here is going what happens if we fall
down we die
trouble
mhm oh yeah this one looks reachable
yeah there are
checkpoints if you get close to it it
becomes a
checkpoint yeah now if you die you
respawn
here that's good
look
like second I
believe I
fly
yeah good job I have a feeling that the
C doesn't help that much oh we got to
keep going yeah okay
mhm
nice oh what's that over there I don't
know wow there's like a big castle in
the Des m
W oh he s of looks like
Nissa Nissa come
him I infiltrated advant don't tell them
yeah it's a
secret oh that oh wow
[Music]
oh watch out and there's a there's a big
be careful oh I do something so good
it's it's pretty steep now so watch out
no more mistakes here no more
mistakes good
job
okay okay get up
[Laughter]
[Music]
I made
it good
job going no they're coming back I go I
go check on them I'm feeling a bit than
usual I go check
them what or add them
oh they call
me
okay okay I'm doing
good
uhoh I am the one who died now I'll go
back do I remember this way
a I'm I'm
[Music]
coming there you go mama I called you
mama why join the join the party call oh
sorry I didn't know oh party
there we go yay I can I can I can call
now let's go
yay oh can you join the party car the
close one right click right click no no
no no no right click you want to go and
scroll into
it watching I died on purpose I couldn't
get back
[Music]
up
checkpoint here you go checkpoint okay
nice
it's okay we just got a checkpoint we
got a checkpoint it's safe you can just
jump you can just
jump I love parkour wow somebody unstuck
me yeah how are you stuck there you go
I'm
stuck oh that's right the w button
oh is it is there something wrong with
the w the W button doesn't like to work
sometimes broke
it what's that guys there's a castle up
ahead you have to this oh right
here it's pretty
big
wow hey go W are we all here I'm here be
careful here we're ahead yeah we're
we're already at the next checkpoint oh
what the
heck W I'm just going to fall good job
okay okay you got this slowly slowly
mhm
it's it's okay you're come to me okay
okay go go go go I just
[Music]
here good
[Applause]
job I see them from here okay
H next
[Music]
[Laughter]
checkpoint I'm not prepared for
this okay uh-huh come on there's a big
castle W big castle big
castle oh god oh
no goodbye fuaa it was nice
how did I
[Music]
fall where
am it's too hot
here it's
okay that's fine how do I get up this
wall how do I get up here you can you
can you can Pro we jump here there you
go look at that leader leader out for
real I'm not me and this beu person
we're just running ahead like it's
nobody's business I got I have the zies
my
bad this way I I take care of the dogs
thank you I'm
not thank you is my I'm just I'm just
checking Advent because yeah I mean not
not not about not about
that what why
you no I I probably I was dreaming about
something I'm sorry yeah yeah I was
dreaming about something watch us or
something no no no no I I was I was
sorry I'm
mistaken
i i i i i
mistaken I think
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh oh hi
oh oh hi hi you made it
[Music]
y
God you can do
a you better P
it why you not moving oh there oh there
help I of everyone do a little jump got
this
yeah yay we all made it good
job are we ready to go on the spooky
Castle yeah let's
go
am oh bad guys we need to talk
we got him no no problem no
problem it's time to talk that was I
protect the
dog I can do it yeah I can't do
it oh yeah you did
no no
oh e down this way yeah it
[Music]
this guy's got
AAR oh watch out watch
out I prot oh he does have a star what's
that oh I got a star key
oh I'm being
overwhelmed you need
help I'm coming where is
Lisa where are
you where she oh go that's a okay we're
good we're
good I'm
coming I'm
killing they have triangles they
have there you go
okay protect why do he have
ow ow ow ow so many stars oh my gosh
they hurt okay I'm eating bread I need
bread I need bread I
need oh they're behind me but they're
ignoring me
that's help help I'm going to
die there you go okay you
okay another Circle do we need to
collect a certain amount of these I
wonder we might have to I've collected a
bunch of Che
there you
go there's more there's
more behind
you thank
you I'm going to okay where are
you are we going the right way keep
going
you yeah
[Music]
yeah I need a circle key I got the
circle I got the
circley I opened
it guys come
here where we are I don't know where is
okay let's let's wander until we find
them oh I see their names let's go over
here yeah yeah
yeah there they are H hello
you're coming the right way
there no no no no come back no no no F
come
back come
here okay through the newly Open Door
let's
[Music]
go oh ready
W this is beautiful W chandeliers in the
sky nice
wow so cool yeah check checko unlocks
nice
mhm eating bread is my passion same we
love bread bread I love
bread
done whoa what's this I like the windows
what's
this it's a puzzle it's a puzzle puzzle
oh do we have to light all of them
oh I'm just going to sit now and
watch okay I think that's not a good
idea I think one person should work on
one side so we don't overlap
maybe did it break on my side oh oh they
are all connected
I monitor
down I almost have it I now I don't just
relax now I did my part you yes you
helped I think you need to click it oh
it does oh it's not doing anything on my
oh I see I see I see I
see oh okay I I'm scared I'm going to
stop touching it well let's stop
touching it let's stop touching it beu
seems to have figured it out what did
you figure out I I almost got it hold on
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait it's
not I got I got one whole side
uh she's doing fast oh okay hold on now
this side now it's
wheel which one do you click on my uh
you don't you don't okay there we go
almost you don't okay almost here almost
there almost here Kaku your brain is so
big which one do you click on I don't
know it's it's I don't know I don't know
how to explain this uh you just respond
there we
[Music]
go it's so cute to look at
them oh my God so smart so fast I just
want to tell you we spent like half an
hour to to to solve this puzzle you did
so fast oh thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
wow I didn't know my brain was that big
wow so
[Music]
good checkpoint
y
this is is a skull I really don't like
this I do it's kind of cool yeah I like
it it looks
[Music]
darkning I can't use my horse bro what
what the heck what the heck what the
heck I think we have to
fall oh where where are you guys wait
we're in a room we're stuck in a room
okay I'm
dropping hi oh I think we can proceed
this way
M
you oh what is that h m
now
oh gosh what the heck be careful we
distracted okay distracted us with this
where you where you
where yeah get him oh oh it grew GRE oh
I can't we used their mhm we to make
them grow we yeah yeah we used their
bones to make them grow Oh I thought you
destroy that and then can somebody take
care of
him I'll take care of him how I get the
meal yeah
how do you take it so you actually don't
take it you have to kill the you have
kill them you have to kill them next ah
I get
it you have to kill it over here come
over here I want your I want your boys
them
nice give me your boys B Mis yeah two
fly two fly there we go y good
job oh there's you you
Bo come back here come back
here too far oh far
away got to get closer
hey
nice hey what do you want from
me oh there he is
owow m looking back wait do we climb the
tree not yet I don't think we can yet
him I need
him him over here
nice I'm okay okay here I'm right behind
you I can't she's fine I'm just
fine bring our bones I think we climb
now
what we're bad at
climbing oh you can climb the vines you
can climb the
[Music]
vines
genius
M Oe
okay there we go I'm just going to wait
here so I can watch them oh go why I'm
going to
die you
[Music]
goit
wait have the best have I have the have
the best view I press this one no
there's more buttons bested in the
house I think I think they're going to
die are we sure they're
everywhere the bottom of the trees are
you sure we're not supposed to press
them po view M I think the buttons are
decoration they're not very cute
though so
cute you can do it I
believe of course cats are good at
climbing trees yeah I'm a big cat and
I'm good at climbing
I did it I got
here she's a big cat
climbing yeah I need to show
you
[Music]
mhm okay yeah this is the highest I've
oh it goes up really high
though supposed to go up
far good
job yay
y yeah oh my God I thought I keep
killing them maybe are they comeing oh
yeah they're here oh here they
are
okay do we want to focus tree
first nice nice
here here into the yeah nice oh here's
another one
HH the Tre
tree you need to help
us oh
gosh
[Music]
into Nara you're being so chill about
this it's almost like you this before Oh
no I think I already forgot about it you
know mhm
yeah I
I I'm I'm I'm I'm watching and helping
maybe maybe the other tree
now what you cheating I had a
head what do you mean you had a Head
Start
mushroom yeah
fell you what the where'd he go he
climbing we need to make this as
well a
yeah is it enough so you're in the
way maybe
not mhm okay nice is that enough is this
enough I'm not sure maybe
maybe they're not spawning anymore so I
think this is enough probably yeah
[Music]
dogs I'm
dying I got here good job so
quick oh no best way to climb
[Music]
thise so
fast yeah no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
it's
[Applause]
difficult this way yeah I think Arrow
up oh I think I think now this way
yeah eat from the
Tre I'm just going
to oh I made it come on I'm just going
to jump
[Music]
oh oh hi good
job how do I get out of here there's
another door here is there another one
to the Denis of the Underworld the light
emanated by Souls was
vital
yeah wait from me I'm still climbing the
tree don't worry take your time to
survive in this dark environment no no
rush no rush yet among them there was a
heretic who called their Customs into
question do we really need to take
others lives to sustain our own yes
there has to be another way and so she
stepped into the plane
above question do you really need to
take other lives to sustain our own yes
there has to be another way no
we're the
hello hello welcome back she like the
light where wait wait wait where is
everybody how do we get up from here oh
where are
you hey I come I come pick you up where
are
you I
come need the wait I di on here oh I can
see somebody
almost can you see
this yeah oh I saw you how do I get up
there okay I'm
coming jump I don't think where are you
I like the trees though I don't see you
anymore oh there she is hello come here
come here oh okay
yeah
okay now s okay okay
come
here and up here I think you're in
danger I think you're yeah are you are
you sure I'm in
danger
anything I'm in
danger you're in danger yeah I so in
danger and
here
mhm take your time I'm living on the
edge you know the edge I'm living on the
edge here
how do
you how do you do all
this yeah okay okay okay one step at the
time yeah no would you like to live on
the end with me no let me
check Edge yeah the edge wait let me
check is here
maybe oh
no and here
where almost there okay
[Music]
here and
now
okay okay I can do
it do it and we jump welcome back how
was the end almost almost I couldn't do
it okay okay let's jump oh no don't
worry I'm okay I'm okay I'm okay you're
almost here you can do
almost
there you can do
it if you hold shift if you hold shift
uh you won't go over the edge so you
keep holding the Okay jump
here over here yeah just yeah there you
go
yeah and now we do a big jump here
jump Qui come here come here big
jump good job and now here
yeah good
job okay scary all right
on
okay here we go y thank you
you
done your power of Revelation has grown
[Music]
stronger my
memories
really
W so pretty oh
watch so
sweet wow
the good
job I'm going to watch the video yeah
wait wait wait I I got to give me give
me a sec I'm not ready I'm not ready
them yeah I'm ready to watch the video
okay I'm ready whenever too wait I don't
know where it is oh I can send it to
you yeah yeah give me um I I send the
link to you don't worry okay thank you I
I I done I'm done it I done it thank
you I thought I I thought I got it but I
can't find it don't worry you got to
download
it my thing is sparkling
wo yeah my thing is
sparkling okay should we should we
should we press on the the let's let's
count down and then press the yes okay
okay okay I'm ready ready
[Music]
you want to see again as well there you
go
go I show you
again a Reaper's job is to end people's
lives and take their
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need I didn't
notice the
eye but I keep wondering
[Music]
it's so
cool is this the right thing to
do no it's not
[Music]
what's going
on look at
that turns out we can also use people's
emotion we don't need their souls at
all Reaper should help the
living take away their future if the
others can't accept
that that's their loss
H I love the music my way what a
badass
yeah wow so
cool seriously so cool I love
it I wow I suddenly remember a lot about
that about that girl Callie yeah Callie
yeah Callie yeah Callie
suddenly suddenly I really remember
her yes he was my
dad my dad
too well shall we return to Li besto
then yeah we need to we need to talk to
the Jade sword Guild Master what let's
go
horses horses onward
they don't fall into
lava why can I fall into
lav oh oh
oh four white horses on the
[Music]
Reaver oh oh yes oh yes they cat oh oh
oh oh
where I going go far okay so open your
map I'm going to teach you how to read
it okay wait they're
gone I'm here they're gone oh oh you
open your map up and then you'll see
you'll see a little thing that says
viridus and then you can actually follow
that as you walk on the map or have your
horse go and then it'll help you show it
it'll show you where to go what if what
if my map is stuck
uh yeah yeah yeah it'll catch
up
no I did
it yay now you're use
m r Harden to see that you have returned
unharmed pray tell what transpired at
the
room I see I think to think the runes
tell such secrets
a crystal de been touched returned a
fragment of your memories to you I am
help awakened the power people making
Quest and only fraction of its
potential yeah what are you up to uh
doing some side quests
a that sounds cool okay well have fun
have have fun have good luck with your
side quest you too can byebye
Can Can it can it pat your head as
well I guess this time May
me
byebye H I'm
buy how to join the
party
[Music]
oh how to join the party
is it
backed pi to join the pr it doesn't
join what
I don't know
why it's Sil B
here maybe not no they
talking they the end of the oh
really oh I see him okay
okay wow
I think I am going to go now tatini I
had such a long day
and
and yeah I think it's my it's my moment
to rest now I'll see you tomorrow at the
same time so I'm going to stream at 11
i.m gstd I hope I hope to see you there
thank you so much for your support and
thank you so much for your company
thank you everyone it makes me happy you
made me
happy more Minecraft yeah tomorrow I'm
going to stream as well uh
[Music]
actually one sec I'm going to actually
check one thing
okay I'm going to go now I see you soon
everyone thank you so much for
watching thank you I see you
tomorrow and remember beat
means big
trouble
byebye bye-bye
ttin actually I'm going to actually
she'll say it
bye-bye
by
okay let me see we're going to read
H going to read oh
who we going to read
huh let's see uh in sen pie
maybe should we read inoc sen
pie okay everyone have a good time see
you tomorrow
bye-bye
T big cat means big trouble
oh
[Music]
the e
h