[Music]
w
K
C welcome back everybody to another
Super
Mario a stream on takasi Kiana whole
live English Channel before we get
started make sure to press like the
thumbs up yeah yeah yeah press
and leave a like and comment and
subscribe and do it all yeah if you even
if you're really cool if you're one of
the cool people then you click the
notification Bell as well ding D ding D
are you ready to party let's
[Music]
go
oh
man must be rough to be like a like a
YouTuber that makes
videos no I I I I've been before the
stream I was like watching some stuff
and oh my God they talk like this yo
because they're so excited and oh my god
thank you for watching this video make
sure to watch it until the end because
something exciting unbelievable is going
to happen so in order not to miss it
make sure to definitely hit that
notification Bell subscribe in three two
one Oh but before we get started let me
introduce you to our today's
sponsor whatever the [\h__\h] it
is segue into that segue out of
that bam you still here oh my God
incredible attention span you have there
buddy no let's [\h__\h]
go I
actually I should just out of parody
reasons I should make a uh a video like
that should I
not to I hear no there we go did you are
you hearing that it's
quiet ah my microphone so there we
go you know this does this oh wait you
don't see anything
oh and the video comes up in three two
one oh my God can you believe it there
is the incredible famous worldwide known
Mario from Nintendo with me today and
he's going to show us what is up in the
Mushroom Kingdom or should we say the
universe we are going on an
odyy
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow Peak
[Music]
content sorry um I was parodying
YouTubers YouTu
you
um yeah uh I definitely do not have all
that kind of energy for a whole stream
maybe for a 10minute video but not for a
whole
stream let me where do I put you you OBS
today today I'm just kind of feeling
like having you on the left side OBS I
know it's kind of crazy I know guys so I
was going to say does this not
look at his face does this not look like
like like a reference to Nintendo 64 to
you like I don't know somehow I feel
like I can I can drag his
face and and move it but I can't I wish
I could it does yeah I can see it yeah
right only this one though the others I
don't know what the hell that is but
like this this really even though it's
just him looking like having his posture
straight into to the front and then his
face just being pretty
normal yeah the title screen yeah yeah I
wonder is it a reference but then why
only here and why can I not move his
face oh what the [\h__\h] was that snap did
you hear that microphone snap snapped at
[Music]
me oh okay uh I I do have a Coca-Cola
with me but the only reason I did that
whole thing is because of the videos I
been
watching it's zero it has doesn't even
have sugar in
it sugar doomies no no no sugar but I
actually doomed before I started the
stream I I zoomed through my rooms to
find snacks because I realized I have
almost nothing so I just found like one
one more of those gingerbread chocolate
sticks I only have one left and they're
small and I I brought one thing that has
vitamins I don't know if I really want
to eat that a mandarin and uh some
gifted chocolates that from like a
company that just give out you know
promotional promotional
snacks
yeah um but yeah uh so
[Music]
this is a reference to when Mario was a
vtuber at the games conference he was
wor what the
[\h__\h] it can't be a reference to that cuz
m64 was before vtubers what are you
talking about you mean the other way
around what do you mean are you just
joking uh by the way I played a little
bit off stream I know unbelievable but
after that stream I kind of felt like
want to play a little bit more but not
too much I didn't go to a new
area uh I just tried
loud I just tried to
see oh man the Coca-Cola burpees I just
tried to see if I could find a few more
things oh I I maybe I maybe found I
don't know three more stars or something
I don't know I don't even remember oh
you can probably compare to when I ended
the stream last time on the top left you
can probably compared to
that uh the B yes I checked the bottom
of the hole Yeah uh I failed on the
first
[Music]
try good morning thank you oh oh you did
the swims animation yo every time I see
stuff like that I feel like I want
to I I need to to
commission like
animated
wallpapers for myself like not for
myself but like for maybe a new loading
screen O
W uh or or a special members wallpaper
but I always I just see it and then I
always forget about
it he y'
skills
what
uh yeah
no new loading screen yeah I should I
should prepare a new loading ending
screen and the ending screen is what I
want something new of like there were
times where we had a new loading screen
every other
week cuz of those pixel uh loading
screens uh but ending screen has been
the same one for a while
[Music]
so I I love it very much but maybe we
should make a new
one yeah I
guess I've been thinking like I should
get some new graphics and stuff done in
general maybe even a new gaming
screen
commissioned the one that I got gifted
is nice but um I don't know I I'm it's
not perfect for like as a lay out I I
noticed some difficulties with it but
yeah so yeah maybe I'll commission some
stuff for the new
year yeah um so this I think we can
actually already go uh because uh yeah I
got enough Stars I think where do we go
here
right ah good I want to write a
[Music]
memo
memo oh speaking of that I here this
here's the
memo and then um what was I going to do
oh yeah talk about sock
puppets talk
about I want to rant about
family
um
YouTube
uh what
else what
[Music]
else what else was I supposed to talk
about uh I can give you a go sigle
update uh oh yeah we can talk about that
collab
[Music]
um yeah recent collabs just in general m
cat update is there a cat
[Music]
update post office post office you know
I went to the same post
office this is so not interesting wait
there's a bird on my nose
I went to the same post office as the
last time you know where there was like
this fight going on and an insane amount
of people waiting and it was the first
time first day after the like holidays
where people couldn't go to the post
office so I thought it's going to be
crowded and I'll have to wait a long
time I was so ready for it but then I
went there there was literally no one
besides me in there and the worker and
it took me 2 minutes and I was like oh
today's really empty here I thought
there would be more people and then the
guy said yeah yeah I'm just I just work
fast I'm like
okay yeah so I got the sock puppets
pretty fast and that was yesterday was
that yesterday no yesterday yesterday I
feel like it was yester yesterday but
then I filmed it yesterday and then we
edited it yesterday and then we uploaded
it actually kind of today for me it was
a.m. but yeah um uh let's just keep
those up for
now I might think of other tangents I
feel like there are other tangents and I
just oh byebye birdie I feel like I I
just I just uh can't think of it right
now uh we're going somewhere wait eight
what do you mean eight more but they
don't calculate the ones I I I didn't
give to them yet right
right
oh oh yeah I forgot how to play the game
yeah definitely enough
right
bam The Odyssey has powered up let's
[Music]
go where are we going
next
oh
America we we have enough power now to
make our way to the Metro Kingdom time
to cross that vast ocean is this is this
the map it's not the map of the world
right USA USA it kind of looks like
USA oh this gives me lethal company
Vibes now kind of looks like our lethal
company um
ship with the railings around it we can
walk around the whole thing but just one
entrance it's like a
box it's a it's a it it's a
reference you think they reference this
game no way whoever heard of a wedding
with a stolen dress that's good after
the attack let threat fiend seeing as
how we've got some time to kill let's
review some useful skills travel tip cap
throw and
ho shut
up now then let's see what there is to
see in the Metro
[Music]
Kingdom how old is le le company is new
oh yeah I want to talk about lethal
company a little bit just a little bit
goodness what was
that also my birthday merch is arriving
I see so many pictures oh oh
confetti I see so many
pictures so happy to see I mean it's
mostly J Japanese people for now
but it should arrive at other people's
places soon as
well well nice I
mean they made the ship look really like
a nice weding
location patiently waiting yeah you got
to be
patient the chicken is so
big and
fluffy we're already we're
already I'm not going to fight him
right you expect me to jump on those
hatsi that's going to be difficult
uh I don't even remember how to play the
game
but I know how to jump okay okay after
we had hit ah yeah right thank
you that will Mak uh it into platforms
that's right I forgot that that was a
big hard mode jump on the hats one by
one wait both b and a is
jumping what the oh
X is also the same as y
interesting okay okay hey I was I was
testing my
control
ooh wow oh huge oh my
[Music]
God Mario I don't have time for you I'm
buy one of my wding don't you know how
stress what that
is my voice hurts because I drank
Coca-Cola bad
idea the panium plant bouquet so
cute oh wow oh that's what I'm
fighting oh with you okay I fought only
the
Hat uh wait wait uh
uh I don't know what I'm doing okay
there we go there we
go I'm
Bing what's that hit
[Music]
box okay okay okay okay oh this is so
sudden we
immediately we immediately go into the
big boss fight wait am I supposed to hat
him when he doesn't have his hat on you
know what I mean I put my hat on him
instead ah but he's so to far always
he's too
far my hat barely goes
anywhere okay let's counter it I'll
try and
now jump in oh I wear it
oh I was reading the menu okay game
design wise that's not really good that
you introduce a new fighting feature in
the middle of a fight without pausing
the battle um I mean sure it could be a
skill issue but it's not very user
friendly is it shut
up
no no that's harsh like honestly it's
harsh thank you for
agreeing like pause the [\h__\h] game so
I can read it then
God damn
it Y and b instead
[Music]
though
nice oh okay that's pretty cool cuz uh I
I did pretty well in like jumping over
those
uh lines efficiently oh that's the wrong
one so I only go for the right one I
suppose you
might and then I have to change my grip
of the
controller because that's uh Y and B is
positioned in a way that is kind of
unfortunate
oh
that's mean that's mean oh but I got a
heart I got a heart
get
nice okay middle
one goodbye
goodbye you're going to do it again it's
pretty difficult to get that right
[Music]
hand I got it let's
go
oh oh they're really generous with those
jumps yes that's go f f
f she did
it t turn
T [\h__\h]
yeah was pretty good I think the first
try we only failed because I so you know
I was so
sudden
[Music]
firear
Mario up against
Mario I mean you had to rely on your
ship in the
end you yourself did not have the power
and it wasn't even you yourself it was
you and that weird ass hat
so if it was just one versus one either
with or without the hats doesn't matter
I would have won but you have a [\h__\h]
huge ass doped ship what is this
place that looks weird
H this supposed to be like a kind of
poison
jungle where are we now my question oh
no the Odyssey is all busted
up we need some power moons to fix it
let's get looking of
course cool oh there's a moon there wait
what can I even get there cuz yeah I can
obviously not go into the water there's
a sling to go back but yeah from
here from here probably not but let's
get these purple leaves oh there's a key
probably for that Keyhole but okay I'm
guessing there will be a solution later
on Face the P yeah
okay
wait
I should not have jumped
down okay
finally
[Music]
and the grape juice see you call it
grape juice it's just
pretty
tempting oh Che them M can
I ah
surely I get a scar if I do it for all
of them oh there's only
two
oh wait what what were they for
oh what he took my my ghost but not my
hat right you bastard wait this is death
bird help oh wait wait no it is my hat
at the same time okay
so we're on our own the music makes me
feel like there's a Time problem
[Music]
here oh wait where did it
go oh here
oh what are these for this this for
later do I have to care about it now
could he land on these
things
is just dist stress the rescue probably
like do this first before you do a [\h__\h]
ton of other
things
maybe oh wait I bet these uh monsters
have a special oh I can't use it right
now they have a special feature for
sure maybe I can dig into the ground
with them ow what the [\h__\h] why did I
just run into
you how do I go up there
oh is there path back here
no
uh I got to get
there I slipped
[\h__\h] nothing me a ground pound
ground
pound ground what are we going to ground
pound let's see oh oh we resp spawned
here but we already don't have the Hat
okay
[Music]
okay jumping on these things doesn't do
anything
right it does what the [\h__\h] they
honestly didn't really look like that to
me like they would do
[Music]
something like some things like this
looks to me like something I I can
ground pond on and have an effect
but the other stuff oh does does not
look like that to me if I jump down
there can I even get back up I feel like
no okay all right then we have the
solution uh I guess got to go to the
top
[Music]
wow they're so cute they're so
colorful no don't go away you little
[\h__\h]
[Music]
no he comes
back what well what
what
what what what she going to do a
wait
ah so
stupid so stupid come
here h w thanks for the rescue that was
unpleasant I'm rather Pokey I sure hope
it doesn't happen
again I sure hope it doesn't happen
again what a thing to
say raising a flag
here now to pluck up our Spirits let's
go collect some power moons yeah let's
do the thing we're here for uh what is
it a cute l+ y
stretch I almost jumped into the water I
I guess I pressed the wrong thing
yeah ah okay uh that hurts though I to
go over
[Music]
here
cute oh I like these features that they
come up
[Music]
with just music is nice
too oh
wait I look so [\h__\h]
ridiculous cursed
wait oh why did it go
[Music]
backwards I can kind of go in a in a
wiggle a squiggle motion
here we go let's
pickle
sorry yeah sorry I still need
you oh thank God it healed me H oh
cute do all of them wear those hats I
didn't realize until now no no they
don't oh I threw off a hat
M
[Music]
okay okay that one is gone that's fine
we don't need
it let's go back over here I feel like a
like
a that instrument that you stretch and
then push together
again an accordion yes yes
according to chat it's called an
accordion what can you
do no no no
no [\h__\h] you no what that's not what
[Music]
oh I was trying to control it now I
realized these enemies are
uncontrollable great and I have to get
my hat back again oh what am I doing
sorry sorry sorry sorry my brain my
brain it
hurts very
much I need my hat back wait where is
it it's not
there oh wait that's my hat
oh oh
what at
this I can't break it but it looks so
breakable why can't I control
[Music]
you
yeah thank God this game has endless
lives yeah yeah okay okay I'm sorry I'm
sorry [\h__\h] the floor is so
slippery so this
off you're so
slippery oh the controller is so
[Music]
slippery unnecessary depths
why well I need to understand somehow I
have to be able to use this buddy no
because I feel like he will help
me opening up
this if I can't break it surely he h
maybe he'll attack it if I'm
honest
no I'm not going to throw my hat at away
he'll throw it wait the I'll give him my
hat and then
here yeah
[Music]
okay let's
go I'm
leing I figured out so many things
already all on my own hey
[Music]
hey okay how do we get back up once I'm
down there I still don't
know is there
no leave me
alone what else what if we is there
something down
[Music]
here
probably just points cuz if it was a
moon then it would be
[Music]
glowing
okay let's go this
way ooh the Rings the rings of
fire you're mine now I shall control you
cute caterpillar
back flip back oh you think I can take
that distance
[Music]
oh I didn't think I could but if you
think
so then perhaps I could if I wanted
to oh that's got that
checkpoint okay oh well let's
go let's go here first
lots of traffic
here
okay we can make
it oh no we can't okay but we still got
the moon but I guess we have to go
around can I really not reach it oh we
can go go
fast and oh the last one is kind of
occupied m M I can I can go to the the
next one the closest one and then try to
occupy the other
one
[Music]
no I was hoping I would land on my own
they're called wigglers right I was
hoping I would land on my own one
[Music]
you many deaths to say with this [\h__\h]
poison
wait
[Music]
[\h__\h] try to do that jump wait wait wait
wait wait how do you do it again okay
okay no that's not okay that was just a
normal jump I was hoping to do something
else got to get some coin
[Music]
bags I will not give up yet I'll get
that last Moon I think I can totally get
it
y not grape juice I'm not even that big
of a fan of grape juice my juice of
choice is orange
juice although wait was it grape
juice doesn't thin air was it thin air
where I had
that oh wait I can reach
oh quick get out of here
y fin air I think fin air finish air a
finish
air has I think no blueberry yeah that
was that was blueberry yeah fin air if I
when I fly with finish air I have to
drink leers
of their blueberry juice because they
have this special juice some Airlines
have like a special drink you
know that they specializ
in and for finish air it's this
blueberry juice that is absolutely
incredible oh
yeah almost he almost bumped into
[Music]
me oh oh is that a
secret
oh worford coming around
here I want that me too I I think you
can buy it
totally in Finland or on their airports
and all that but in Austria I mean
there's surely blueberry juice but is it
that
[Music]
good Captain
T how did I get
here I was St by a giant
bird a different giant bird than hon but
it's been nice to rest in the quiet and
I discovered a power moon for you so
that's
good a
miss
a I should probably get going soon
huh oh I can get a heart here but I
don't really need it why is this wiggler
here though ah for getting back I
guess oh it gives me coins okay that's
fine that's fun is there no other way
out I have to go the same way I came
in damn it can I reach over
there no really I try
again [\h__\h] okay we have to take the long
way my butt is so slow to catch up on
me
okay here we
go
no
M [\h__\h] what did I get all those coins
for with toad oh well he gave me a moon
and this is kind of where I wanted to go
anyway
[Music]
okay once they touch the wall they
become 2D as well
ooh oh oh and there's two moons the [\h__\h]
avoiding fuzzies inside the
wall Mario is not a fan of muko I
guess can I jump
outside he's not a
fan he prefers The Fluffy one not the
fuzzy
one it's Mok
cover I come over you're not going to
come any closer huh it's okay wait do I
need a
wiggler probably I mean maybe with one
of those jumps I could do it if I was
skillful but we all
know we all
know that I am not skillful oh it's cute
how I can hug the
pole oh man this is so cute
all right here we
go
oh I'm too
skilled don't don't say that to me I
know it's not true
it whatever I'll just I'll just uh
whatever leave it behind cuz I'm not
sure what I was supposed to do don't
underestimate yourself you so
nice
now let's see
oh I can touch it just five more to go
yeah no I I have a lot more that I want
to achieve over
here wait that reminds me of doggle of
when a
doggle paddles in the air why is it not
moving there we
go
[Music]
wait there was a hole
there how did I not see that we have to
go back
again you are cute no
you I have a feeling I like more I like
dogs more because
of oh come
on oh I wouldn't say really that that
had any effect on it
no
no I will not give them credit for
that so did you guys enjoy the sock
puppet finale that went up last
night I am so proud of it I really
really like what it
became
and yeah I I I really really really
really love it you guys like it too
huh it was a m piece it really was I
mean I know praising yourself is kind of
cringe and all that
but this one deserves the
[Music]
praise that's what I
want
and it's also thanks to the great voice
acting of the girls I thought I didn't
think they would get so into it
especially cuz I thought when I was
writing the script that it was really
cringe and I was worried about making
them forcing them read it I was worried
that maybe some of them would be like w
I'm sorry but I can't do it it's too
cringe or I don't like the script I
don't like your idea ideas or something
like that but no it wasn't the case at
all oh there's a moon there yeah okay
let's try to get that moon
now see I can do it I know how to do it
just telling
myself and crony got really intoed yeah
like okay so I think crony and
[Music]
Lissa
no
I think crony and Nissa are probably the
best voice
actors
in we're losing a lot of money STS are
definitely going
down Mario st's going
down can I go closer
so confusing where is it
here so I was saying I think cron and
Arisa are the best voice actors uh but
like they do it so seriously which is
great they're like really Ser they take
it serious even though it was a cringe
stupid script where am
I a cringe stupid
script they still like they were so
passionate about
it croni seem to be
suffering and Nisa really seemed to be
upset with
Shi
okay well okay then let's get some money
back what Fu great great thanks for
nothing can I get money here
again
Blue Woman power oh yeah true they're
both kind of like dark blue
fend well I still don't understand these
poles so and then M and
bails I for me they win the most
dramatic act
award they were both also extremely into
it but it was like kind of like like
they they understood that it's a like
kind of a ridiculous script and parody
and all that so they they totally went
for
that I had to crack up so much when I
was listening to Bale's voice voice
lines it's so funny to me okay where
what else have I not seen oh how do I
get
there I maybe we got to go up there Che
them up maybe I haven't seen much of
that
side
[Music]
I have to go from the
side love the B thank you I actually did
uh quite a bit of research for that are
you laughing while you did the actual
pupp yeah a little
bit a little bit I did some research for
the bayus stuff cuz I I wanted them to
have some kind of conflict a lovers
conflict but I wasn't sure what it would
be
about and
so I I looked up some like I I basically
looked up on YouTube bayus like
fighting and what I found was like
several conflicts one was about I think
ba called Iris saggy I
think a certain part of her saggy I
don't know I don't remember anymore oh
that was an absolute accident I actually
just like smacked the
controller against my hand and this
happened what [\h__\h]
what but it does point at
it
and and then uh then I looked up I found
one
uh what was it where they fought oh yeah
where Zeta was flirting no Iris was FL
flirting with Zetta apparently and B got
jealous or so and then the one about you
know even when I lost my voice she stood
by my side and became my voice when I
had none or something that that was a
reference to Iris giving BS her voice
basically when they did like a no
talking
stream stuff like that so there were
several references that I think you
would get if you're one of them or one
of their C usual Watchers but yeah I did
my research
yo yeah that was
yeah me being very smart okay we got to
go
[Music]
there and I yeah right I kind of got
stuck there but now I know how to do
this
watch even jump so that I don't get hit
it feels like I get hit when he does
that
[Music]
oh
okay
wait wait I have an easy way of doing
the circle thing now I just smack the
controller with my pal the palm of my
hand I didn't know I don't have to do
like this crazy shaky
[Music]
shaky that's good to know I think I'll
be using
[Music]
that yeah okay
cool that's the cover
logo no no it's not
[Music]
what here
here ah
[\h__\h] I didn't take damage
right okay okay okay nice you just jump
out of the
way okay
okay difficult difficult
area I love how you got goo in the video
Yeah well that was um my solution to her
not being available is um me using old
voice lines and making like making her
into the pet
OFA so the groupings I thought of the
groupings I thought of the whole script
the main storyline and
everything um since I had to write the
script it felt logical to me to make me
that main evil character I didn't want
anyone else to be like the evil person
I'm sure some of them wouldn't have mind
it but I didn't want to implicate that
they're evil so it's me cuz also I think
it was perfect cuz I was able to you
know give them all all jobs at kfp and
that way we were all connected in some
way the darkness in the end it made more
fun using C over for the story so smart
right I thought it was like pretty
fitting pretty
suitable and I know that Scrooge story
I've watched it before and all that so
I'm aware of it but I didn't even look
up what
exactly it goes like again because I
just wanted to make my own version so
just with in the back oh just with in
the back of my
mind like knowing that it's about some
dude who is not very nice to
people
uh and then him being shown what effects
it has on the people around him and then
he'll become a better person so that's
all I had in mind and I applied that to
my story some parts were a little bit
difficult to
you know round about cuz like I wasn't
sure what they should be fighting about
or what the what the effect should
be that I like them working at kfp and
me overworking them has on them and it
shouldn't all be the same one I didn't
want everybody just to be fighting about
the same things so yeah okay what the
[\h__\h] is this
here I need to land on it
first oh
oh
uh okay okay okay okay I kind of
stumbled in the beginning but I made
it Y what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] is that dragonfly
over there really I think it's supposed
to be a dragonfly cuz it's a fly and a
dragon huh or something like
that um yeah
nice
nice oh this is the Shar
huh what do you
have a g yeah
whatever I knew that from the GetGo that
it was a
GetGo I have the perfect amount of coins
I think there always 10 and five for set
wow an aviator
outfit
interesting well I probably need to have
one of their outfits again right to fit
in probably maybe in order to fly the
the G
gecko otherwise they won't let me oh
that's how I get to the island I
guess I guess
so I guess so with the
Geto if we use it from the Geto we get
to go to the
island oh baby
the c c
[Music]
combos oh [\h__\h] oh okay yeah you look
fine anything new here oh oh yeah the
Life part the
[Music]
moon n no need bye
bye-bye so yeah writing the script was a
lot of fun and then like uh acting it
out once I had the voice L of so happy
when everybody actually sent the voice
lines in on time and then I was sad that
I couldn't finish the video on time
because I didn't have the the sock
puppets
yet uh but in the end this way you know
it was a little bit less stressful to
take a little bit more time that was
nice and it came out so good I had to we
decided to Premiere it publicly in the
end because it was already delayed and
we already we've said you know it's the
final video it's going to be a group
effort from everybody oh it's worth it
to have it public right away so that as
many people as possible get to watch it
and don't miss out on it and maybe this
way people will also like people who
didn't see oh okay people who didn't see
the other videos who didn't even know
that this was going on for whatever
reason cuz they live under a [\h__\h]
rock maybe with the finale they realize
it and check out the old
videos
yeah so with
that oh ah okay like
this what the
[\h__\h]
I
[Music]
am I was surprised by the controls how
do I get back up to the top here do I
take the Geto with me
please yes okay
there at least I didn't fly into the
poison
walk where's I going I yeah with
this
the uh uh Holo life English Advent
calendar
2023 is
[Music]
complete oh what I don't [\h__\h]
understand the controls so much okay I
just let it go A
okay okay wow I take my hat off to you
but yeah please don't oh there's
slingshot is there
wait that
one
goes which
direction whatever I just want to
actually go back the same
way thanks for another a great year
thank
you it was an amazing ad C thank you I
think we had less group videos this time
just because we had more members
available than last year and I kind of
really likeed the group
videos so oh
I wonder if next year if we do it again
we can somehow still Implement more
group videos somehow some
somehow I just really like them a lot
but I think everybody should still have
a solo video too you know but instead of
having like duplicate solo videos we
should just have more unit videos but it
was kind of difficult to like you know
make anyone do a unit video where I'm
not involved because it's kind of
difficult to be like hey you cie okay
for cie it's still easy cuz like I I
feel like she has go-to people like Bae
for example for like besides that I'm
like who do I tell to do a group video
and then do I tell them to who to do it
with cuz maybe I should give them a
recommendation but like I don't know I
don't want to like control everybody too
much you know and be like hey FAA do a
group video with someone do it do it
just do it
please I don't know it just feels like
I'm I'm controlling too much I don't
want to be like you know that
annoying and and too
bothering but in the end everybody
really worked together on this to make
it a a great
experience some of these animal calendar
videos are absolute
masterpieces that are a huge Joy wo wo
wo
wo to
watch and I
think I think they're there it's it's
just I don't know it all came together
really
nicely the Irish tree burning Oh you
mean the Holo Ian 3D repeat one The Sims
repeat yeah that
thing
um I was asked beforehand like hey we
could do this
for the Adent calendar video if you want
it's going to be Christmas theme what do
you think I was like yeah I guess I
mean this is the only thing where I'm
like kind of iffy about because I don't
want the videos to be anywhere but on
the website just so that you know it's
exclusive I want people to have a reason
to oh to go to the website what the [\h__\h]
why is there a butterfly there can I fly
that one too
wasn't there another thing another place
that I have to fly
to is that it did I reach all the
destinations how long until the website
turns do I'm not sure I think it stays
up for a while this time I'm not paying
for it so they might not keep it up for
a whole year
but there's a big long should I go there
I thought it just glowed by default and
I didn't realize until
now all right I'll go
there and of course I
miss wait is it
really something up there when I land on
it cuz now it's not really I feel like I
could reach it without this get
go look I could reach it without
[Music]
see see oh but it won't even let me land
on it
interesting yeah I know I'm just I'm
just ready to go I guess wait what what
about this key
thing is the Geto still there
yeah who can
glide what's the key also supposed to be
reached with a
wiggler the key the key was here I I
need a wiggler I need to bring a wiggler
down
here
[Music]
uh oh [\h__\h] don't get it I just don't get
it
for
okay where is the closest
wiler pretty far away you
[Music]
know there's none over
here I guess this one
wo let's go we're going on a little trip
it's going to be a little
[Music]
bit Nerf
wracking cuz you have to hover over the
poisonous poisonous toxic
[Music]
fumes
I hope I was able to make uh the holiday
Christmas
season um more enjoyable not only for
kfp but for generally all Ian whole life
English
fans with that project if that was
possible then I'm I think I accomplished
everything that I wanted to
accomplish
meow there it is there is it
is let's tle twist and turn up treasure
was there another thing like this I know
I already have enough moons but now I'm
kind of on a
roll he really wants me to go I guess
I'll I'll okay I guess I'll go let's
see you leaving him behind I don't have
a choice I think he was going to
disappear eventually anyway the year is
almost over
[Music]
yeah the cage ah the cage one yeah
whatever
whatever thank you for ad thank
you thank you for checking it out every
[Music]
day all
the
[Music]
it almost feels like we're in the what's
that Island we're in these places too
short like especially this one seemed
really small and
short kind
of there'll be much more to do later
really
what
what I do leave with minimum moons I
tried to find a lot of them though I
tried I found just enough power moon to
fix up the Odyssey thank goodness but in
any case this is just supposed to be a
filler game so I'm fine with it not
being too long cuz I'm going on a
vacation very [\h__\h] soon so we better
finish it
up next Kingdom is huge okay okay didn't
really have a boss and it wasn't yeah oh
you're right
yeah all the other Maps had a boss
no true I mean as far as I can
remember I guess it's supposed to be
short
yeah mes
[Music]
mes [\h__\h] I'm so excited I'm so
excited so excited I think narissa is
also really excited it will be a first
time meeting but I think we will get
along so well I have 100% confidence in
that
because we we tell each other like like
as almost as if we're lovers we tell
each other is like every second day that
we love each
other yesterday after the
collab I I felt
so so happy that I I had had to tell her
to like suddenly like this overflow of
love I felt it I told her I love you so
much like I'm so happy you turned all
alive you you you really brightened up
my life and and I'm so happy that you're
here I feel so relieved every time I
talk to you and I don't feel like I have
to be careful of what I say because no
matter what [\h__\h] I say and how stupid I
am I know that you won't judge me for
it just randomly throw love like letters
like this at each other every now and
then it it's ridiculous I just can't
stop and then she's like I love you and
I'm like I love you and she's like I
love you and I'm like I love
you yeah too much lesbian stop the
lesbian we just really really really
like each other and appreciate each
other and I I especially appreciate
her yeah
control the
game so I can't wait to get to know her
IRL I'm glad that I just went for it
even though we don't know each other for
that long but I feel like I felt like I
I knew we were going to get along so
let's plan a vacation immediately you
know we we we are going to have a great
right time no matter what no matter
what what day are you going not going to
tell
you but uh soon very soon very soon oh
my
God and she'll have to divorce all
of that's a sham wedding they're not
really
together
careful too much lesbian sorry guys this
is a meme for people who don't know it's
a meme it's a new kfp meme okay you have
to catch up with the
times careful careful Tak too much
lesbian okay no more lesbian be
[Laughter]
careful careful
now
I already have ideas for a
collab um a certain one like I mean
obviously we're going to do like the
usual stuff probably like K we're going
to do some switch games probably I have
one special idea though that I thought
of
yesterday fine I'll leave no not the
lesbians
no where are the lesbians no don't go
away oh man so many lesbian memes oh my
God
I wonder if they'll put flowers in the
bathroom
again or even on the
[Laughter]
bed I hope they
do oh I I hope it will be as good as the
other place that I went to with waya we
kind of more or less downgraded in terms
of
room uh I think it's like it's still a
great Resort but we don't have an
overwater Villa this time because we
thought nah like I already experienced
that and there Isa didn't really feel a
need for it and and I said well it's
nice for the gimmick
but you can just as well enjoy a villa
right at the beach front
so that's also amazing and I kind of
wanted to see that one next time like
have a Villa right at the beach so that
you just walk on the sand you right
there yeah but I I I hope it will be
like comparable in quality to the last
one because it's hard to tell really but
it had good reviews I think and and
price-wise you know we had to we had to
go a little bit cheaper this time
because it's 100% on season I checked
out how much the one costs that I went
to with waya how much it would cost for
this season and maybe it's because when
I looked maybe it was already like fully
booked mostly but the prices were insane
so it was definitely not taken into
[Laughter]
consideration it was like per night I
don't know 2,000 3,000
4,000 so I I I I can't really imagine
maybe it was really fully booked already
at the last couple of rooms that they
had would be that price but it was not
something that I would find
feasible sorry for Tangen thing I feel
like the game distracts me a little bit
but okay what is it roll oh shut
up shut up I just want to you know
chitchat with you guys a little bit
because tomorrow is also a collab but
I'm planning to do a stream on Monday on
the 1
January um solo so we're can to have a
talk there as
well off yeah definitely I mean
offseason there were definitely L of FEA
problems what [\h__\h] oh
oh wait oh she's the girl
Ah that's why they wear some weird
actual human looking
people what was I going to say just
now I forgot I was kind of interrupted
by seeing the lady all right finally
made it things don't look so good though
oh yeah the weather yeah
um it it was still bearable though like
I feel I feel like yeah it's a bit
disappointing and and crazy but it's
also funny like the weather suddenly
being a [\h__\h] typhoon out of nowhere
and then being calm and tropical
again it was kind of funny when we were
like there's like this like Spa Island
like they have these like paths going
out into the ocean and little Huts for
the Spy
area and in order to go from like one
massage room to the to the like hot tub
area or so you have to walk outside over
the paths over the ocean and at that
time it was like storming like crazy so
me and waya were like screaming while we
were running through the absolute crazy
typhoon storm just to run over to the
hot tub and then we we with a free view
over the ocean because it was kind of
like open we sat in the hot tub looking
at the storm but yeah it's it's not the
perfect weather but it's still kind of
it still kind of works like if you want
to save some money to go to one of these
paradises you should go off season it
kind of works you just have to know what
you're getting yourself into because we
didn't but
yeah it's a unique experience it
definitely is yeah hearing these storms
also when when we were getting the
massage it was fine it was fine
not as bad as the storms I had here
recently we even had like an Austria
wide storm
uh or Oran
warning I think it's also a typhoon
directly translated was really bad and
it it gave me [\h__\h]
anxiety yeah no yeah I guess hurricane
Oran translated to Hurricane I think
yeah but I was like hurricane could you
call it the hurricane I don't know about
that but it was definitely [\h__\h]
crazy yeah it wasn't much rain so maybe
it wasn't a typhoon it was more crazy
wind I
think until you remember AAR is like
three miles long shut up it's more than
that Neverland really bad as well
everything is flooding yeah I guess it
was like it's going over all of Europe
yeah it's kind of
weird or
tornado tornado I wasn't I didn't see
the tornado like you know I typically
see it like
a swirly whirly oh well anyway sorry
look it's Bower ship let's
go okay um [\h__\h] Terrible Weather but
this looks like GTA and a way out or
whatever I don't know cool cool cool
cool cool cool bye-bye
oh I'm not ready to meet
them I'm not ready don't look at me oh
there's this thing
again Super Mario
GTA
W oh uh this this could be me if I were
to get an outfit specifically for whole
talk this could be
me yeah talk show host outf there mhm um
I'm a mayor a
mayor I'm sorry but I really don't have
time to chat right now I need to figure
out a way to save my city things have
been in utter chaos since that brutish
monster showed up and he has to the Nerf
to be advertising his wedding the
wedding of his all of a new dog City new
dog City a bit tasteless if you ask
me yeah it's all over holy [\h__\h] a little
bit Overkill does he think people will
come and
see and check it out he's a [\h__\h]
villain you thinks normal people will
come
no a you want to give this try guys all
right here we
[Music]
go so
close so close though so
close
see I'll try
again oh but I guess I already got the
coins do I not get them again oh oh
those coins I lose normal coins but I
don't lose the purple coins oh okay okay
okay okay I see I
see me heading to the city forget about
it forget about it is this like supposed
to be like New
York there's certainly a lot of nasty
looking bugs
here e New York do you have a a problem
with this stuff yeah B they
explode what what can we do with that
information oh no they don't really
explode never
mind
e e there's a
fight I can use it right
lucky
W my God go ow that's so cool
cool let's
[Music]
go yo can't believe on the [\h__\h]
bicycle this is Mario Kart now bicycle
on
B what why the why the [\h__\h] is New York
occupied with
tanks
ah oh
all right all right all right all
right wait surely we can use you I
forgot about
that no fight back bro bro fight the
power H I don't even need them right now
but
okay tank Kashi is back oh wait the shop
is here oh
that sign is super attacking wait which
one there's too many can I shoot
them oh what the
[Music]
hey oh no okay what with all the road
blocks yeah I don't know
turn I like blowing up things
don't
h
nice shoot the wall thing this this
[Music]
one
help oh this one okay yeah that kind of
looked like we can get rid of it but
probably don't need the paner for
it tank nashing
[Applause]
w got to get the stons rising
again we lost too many
stons for what for
what oh I want to ask you guys what was
your favorite story for the sock puppet
theater out of all the suffering that I
have created what's your favorite
[Music]
one why was I so
wobbly oh
cute
wait no why did I kill him Al
why is there a secret path that I'm not
seeing B but I'm bi cron M crony dying
crony B Iris oh a lot of a lot of the
same anwers n ah it was so difficult to
ride like a long rant because I wanted
it to really sound like they're
realistically fighting so thinking of
something they could fight about and
then the arguments made at each other to
like to have them make somewhat
sense it's really
difficult what's going
on
uh I need them
I need
them wait I forgot how to do
it okay what was I saying oh yeah it was
really difficult to have it make sense
and
all I had to implement my butt though at
least I I had a good reasoning for
narissa that she fell in love with the
with
her her
boss
no go okay there we
go [\h__\h] off Goombas oh there's a moon
down
there how do you get there oh I guess
from that
side ah and people ended up being the
the narrator because first of all I was
making all the all the like combinations
of people and I can only I only have two
ants so I can only really act out two
people people at a time so they were
bound to
be couples like this and then I had
people kind of left over because it just
you know kind of ended up like that but
I thought wait maybe she can be the
narrator because I feel like she has a
cute voice for
narrating I think that actually works
out pretty
great yeah I I couldn't use my feet
okay jokes are funny thank you the gravy
yeah the gravy of the situ I'm pretty
proud of that one and and am's delivery
was very good too the gravy of the
situation good one right thank you thank
you I I'm happy you acknowledge my
jorks
also did you guys slow this one of my
favorite Parts I just went with it cuz I
didn't want to reenact it again did you
see when sh's head fell off and then
while still acting I had narissa oh I
had narissa
um push her head back up during the
conversation
yeah is there something up there oh oh
there is
maybe so many Secrets don't know where
to go
first oh I guess wait oh oh I created a
shortcut nice I no I didn't o o o o
o
o I never noticed you were doing
everything too good what you didn't
notice that the head fell off actually
that was a danger constantly for
especially the myth
[Music]
puppets because the myth puppets were
already mishandled a
lot and really falling apart um so
inside basically the way I made them is
like half of a toilet paper roll with
hot glue attached to
[Music]
um like more cardboard
paper that is shaped like a mouth and
that with because they're really small
I'm not even using my full hand I'm just
using my thump and my you call it index
swinger
maybe um to like open it and close it
and then they they yeah
that's how they start
yapping yeah and uh those
parts for most of myth were separated at
this point so it was really hard going
in there and like reconnecting them is a
little bit difficult to be honest um so
I just I just tried my
best to what is this
area I tried my best to deal with it but
there's definitely a quality increase in
how I made the new puppets even though I
kind of made a mistake I made them a
little bit
differently so the old puppets I don't
know if you've noticed but for example
their
mouths their mouths uh I
I used
to make it with red
paper and then glue it on top of the
mouth this time I didn't have any red
paper so I just decided to just draw it
on because I had a red
pen and that worked fine can I shoot it
to receive it yes
okay
nice look good this way yeah I think the
mouths look good this way but I also
kind
of
somehow somehow their mouths were not as
flexible as the old puppet's mouth
so it was a bit harder to move them and
and open them up probably I just didn't
bent them
enough uh before they before I attach
them
inside
um yeah but it's fine they they
generally I was so careful with the hair
and I was way more like trying to be
accurate with the details and the
accessories I made accessories for
people I gave her the sparkle Stu I gave
her a crown properly like shiny
material yo so much
effort the only thing I forgot and I
realized today cuz somebody wrote it to
me I didn't add nisa's beauty mark
[Music]
no
unbelievable I'm so
sorry I am so sorry is there a reason
why there's Goombas here or am I
stacking them for no
reason
[Music]
I think there was no
reason unbelievably believable yeah I
guess
so I want to go up this way oh there's
coins here I'm nice to definitely need
them oh there's someone
here oh I hit
them
tort oh there's a moon
there
oh
Stones life emotion also I I I I I don't
like their eyes I tried to make them
bigger by drawing lashes really big on
them um I only had smaller goggly eyes
left but I didn't want to buy new ones
because they come in like mixed caps and
I get so many and I actually still ooh I
still had so many but they're ah oh
they're all kind of the smaller
type I thought we were
dying yeah so I didn't have as much
Choice with the eyes only people got big
[Music]
eyes I feel like they would have looked
cter if I gave them U bigger eyes alt
together sh and be's headpiece look
thank you yeah put a lot of effort into
the Advent pu because they're also like
really really intricate but if I if I
look at how much effort I put into the
Advent puppets and then I look at Pia
who doesn't even have the right hats and
the hair is so [\h__\h] up it's always in
my face and I'm falling AP and this mypp
look [\h__\h] but the stuff is charming
right it's
Charming I think it's
Charming
no but this time I only had to make
these five puppets uh and even though it
took a lot of time because I only had to
make five I thought okay let's let's put
like as much effort as I can into them
so that so that the girls are happy with
them what and I sent them pictures once
they were
done oh another
H oh no okay that's fine let just go
back up
and they were really happy when they saw
the V puppets they really liked
[Music]
them this puppet are a great first try
with tons of soul in history it's true
but I don't know if I if I
make some people said cuz this the
second time I saw this in a YouTube
comment that it's Tradition now and I
have to do this every year if I really
end up doing this next year I think I
will remake the my puppets because they
are literally falling apart I cannot use
them
anymore what the [\h__\h] just
happened wait did I not get the
moon oh wait this did it not count M can
height night on
the oh I didn't I touched it though I
guess the Hat doesn't count I thought
that was like
smart let's go
okay okay there artifacts yeah I I won't
throw them away but I I think I want to
make a 2.0 version I'll still keep the
scuff and the charm in some
[Music]
way just like need to end it end and end
you can if be hard not
on another thought was that I also had
for this time because the sock puppets
weren't arriving I was thinking what if
I just make a finale with Advent only
make new puppets for Advent and only
include
Advent see that could be something for
the future but no I think the finale
should have everybody and this is the
easiest way like something like this we
could also do like a a skit with live
Tod or so but it has to be something
pre-recorded where the girls can send in
voice lines in order to have everybody I
think it has to have everybody ined so
having only one generation involved no
that's sad bad let's not do that no no
no no no no no no no new donk City Hall
interior
okay generally so far why have there
been barely
any oh barely any
stars oh nice
jump
nice
points it'll make sense soon
[Music]
okay what the hell you I hate these no
why did I keep I keep on jumping off
because of the the perspective
the view is confusing
me I oh
no okay here I
am no
I oh
at least I got the the coins the purple
coins oh
wait they were going to assassinate me
right
[Music]
there no yeah okay one HP in the
dream oh a oh wait I didn't see that oh
well missed a couple purples it's okay I
don't really try to collect
everything but I I could get them now
[Music]
here there we go there we go we reach it
anyway so what does it
matter an armored chicken you need Chad
thank you congratulations and thank you
for the longl lasting
support
yeah lots of coins here lots of money to
make w w w I would like a heart though I
always get them on this map when I don't
need
them generous but not at the right
time finally I jump in a good
Tempo we're
rolling we're rolling going the roll
guys
whoop wo
[Music]
you guys I checked some perms by the way
for the super uh for the
Nintendo oh oh nice for the Nintendo
64 and Advance Game Boy Advance
extensions uh on the
switch um we have perms I think for
everything except the Pokmon
games so it means I can play all of them
and I would like you guys to make me
recommendations can we get much
higher and I would like you guys to make
me no so stupid make me recommendations
for games from those
expansions that
uh have local
multiplayer possible cuz maybe I want to
play them with
Nissa M Min I do want to play Min and Ma
Mas yeah in general
yeah sing
yeah Min is so good yeah I know I
[Music]
know yeah there's the Mario party and
the Mario Kart games but are there some
that are not like really obvious
multiplayer that I don't know
about oh wait the
coins it's so human that come on if you
going to make characters that are actual
like human looking people then let them
speak an actual
language how fantasy language
f0x oh wait isn't that also just a
racing
game it's simulation
no Sims is something
else does Min does Minish come with or
sword SWS what I don't know Mario 2 is
still best Mario Party ever what about
Mario Party
fre new donker oh it's their own new
donkey language
H with one of you having only a little
bit of input ideally it would be like
the same amount
of input for both
players MP free Mario Party
free is also good okay don't play Golden
I the controls are Terry bed okay we'll
remember that Jet Force Jimmy have co-op
okay okay okay I'll
remember okay thank you thank you pilot
lngs 64 is probably still fun
[Music]
okay all right then Kirby dreamland 3 is
that multiplayer
too that thing is trying to suck up all
the juice from our city hey I'm walking
here get out of there like he's he wants
to walk up there let let him let him
pass the [\h__\h] is
this oh they were sucking the energy
out how do I fight them
here well I don't okay good to know
are we going to that field where I was
like
no new don't City Hall all right we're
fighting oh do I use
you I feel like it's an obvious
invitation ah yeah I got them all is
this our
transire oh they changed constellation
okay immediately I understand
the the
mission my homework my what what you to
say as assignment I immedately unet the
assignment oh where where are they going
to come out
of Tashi Tanki can I stop
them or do I join them do I try to go
up do I just have to dodge oh I guess
they're
done oh no oh damn it I almost had him
my angle was kind of
bad no I'm not de again I literally
don't know what to do
here I don't think I can do
[Music]
anything oh he's back doing the normal
thing oh oh he only has I [\h__\h]
charges back up but he only
has the same amount that he had last
time where we let off
okay okay freemons
oh baby a triple to make up for the lack
of moons so
far
[Music]
we I
so so
wet
[Music]
shiny Moon yay okay and now oh maybe now
they have the electricity back and maybe
even the rain stops it literally
stopped in that scene oh and it's
daytime for
real oh the city in a new light and now
maybe there'll be way more
moons and she will thank me for saving
the city maybe a kiss on the
cheek and we got rid of the big bug
thing and the wind cleared out but
Bowser must have gotten away in the
scuffle we should probably Shuffle back
to chasing him we don't have enough F so
let's look around the city for more okay
okay
damn I keep on running off the
Bowser kind of
[Music]
annoying I want to
talk is poine is the bee's niece what I
wonder what she's up to now after the
most recent excitement excitement being
me saving the city wait there's so many
people
here and no more tanks no more bucks
really they saved they they solved the
the pest problem as
well
yeah wait do I have enough points yes I
do let's buy something can we get a suit
are we getting a suit like all these
other people to fit
in it's even even here it's a real
person on this oh my God n
[Music]
oh
wait can only afford this construction
of
[Music]
what
okay sad but what can I
do check next door the other might have
a
soon
[Music]
byebye wait oh I didn't change the Hat
again oh hello
welcome great new swag he said we we got
great new
swag oh this is new right from
here all right yeah this is what I want
this is what I want finally I'm wearing
something from this shop
I look so
proper black fedora I can tip my Fedora
into
Pine
wow h i look
amazing wow what a gentleman I look I
look even more Italian now but this suit
somehow oh look at this little small
baby car oh good can I stand on it and
you can drive it
please no how stand on it no you jumps
off
no wait
what how do you get
that do I have
to there's
trash talk to the guy one I didn't see
an a
button maybe that
one the
rats oh oh I can control the
guy
oh oh wait
[Music]
what oh my God this difficult
steer oh oh wow the controls are so
weird I can't make like a proper
curve what what one of these
controls how do I go
right no
[Music]
that's
what ah I made
it tank
controls but why on the
car why normal electric cars like this
don't control themselves like
this no ah I have to enter from the
front kind
of wait slowly slowly slowly slowly
slowly if we go
slowly then we can make it
yeah
[Music]
Y no that's not how the cars that I
played with when I was a child
work oh okay so I can only control
certain
people I feel the spirit of remote
controling you step right in remote
[Music]
control oh my God
they have a whole like mini game here
about
it I don't see how it's even possible to
get under 35 seconds super exciting
under 35 seconds is what you
want no not yet cuz I'm just thinking of
my
childhood I'm playing him okay there's
no
way but at least there's railings ah
there's no way oh oh okay wait see this
controls a little bit better in my
opinion oh way
better
[Music]
oh H [\h__\h]
ah
uh ah two free rounds in that amount of
time I was kind of on a roll but now I'm
like
confused no can I
restart ah it's
over oh okay okay a [\h__\h]
no this really feels like I'm
controlling it in real life though I'm
not playing a video game right now I'm
playing a real
game yo new record yeah but we're going
to we're going to get 35 seconds cuz
then probably I'll get a
moon okay
just don't do a complete turn and then
we'll be
fine yeah
nice
nice okay okay
[Music]
okay nice safe uh but the e what he's so
he's too slow why is he so
slow
what a that ruined
everything
[Music]
no suddenly I can't go up there what do
you
mean oh my God you ruined
it oh it was so great so close to
greatness and success
no okay
again I know I can do it I was on a roll
yeah but now I know how
how difficult at ramp is now I know how
important it is to have full
speed at all
times
oh okay
smooth smooth s
oh let's
[Music]
go yeah I did it 10 seconds under even
almost
woohoo
[Music]
yay deserve
Moon here we go yay can I jump onto the
course
no oh it's in a glass cage okay wow
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank
you I'm a [\h__\h] gentleman look
at
[Music]
me [\h__\h] gentleman what
this oh
okay I'm up here
oh H yeah um what how do you use it
again oh I guess I don't have to use
it oh
trash y let's
[Music]
go
's your
hat what on that thing uh yeah what on
what on
What Kick the Can I am not kicking it I
am throwing the Hat on it is that not
good
enough the man okay I didn't really want
to say the word cuz it sounds kind of
[Music]
L I found something
uh railings guys
railings We Go Again wait what about
this PA no no no no what about this
PA is it connected no oh it is it is it
ah like it's a circle kind
of where where's this manhole that you
guys were talking about you didn't mean
did did you cuz I already got the
moon on the floor level oh okay
okay at this one oh see there's question
mark even it's a
farting no what is wait you said hat
never mind what that's
cute it looks like a farting
pillow oh let's
go
wo pirna
PL oh it's Moon parts so I have to get a
full moon oh
the no okay that can stay there I but
how do I get out okay never mind it goes
here oh I can't move the blue
ones oh no problem this is how I reach
it okay this is
fun I fell asleep wait wait oh never
mind I need
it I need my hat I just realize you
can't have it sorry I keep on forgetting
that I need my hat
the
maze oh they turn yellow
before before they spit the
fire
interesting I never observed that
before I see the moon
y
oh oh yeah but how do I
get the second
one
[Music]
oh oh wait do I have to do wall jumps to
get on top of these
[Music]
walls can what I don't think I can the
distance is not
correct I have to go out oh
okay thought there was a secret PA
somewhere here
oh let's
pickle I always say that cuz that's what
it sounds like what he's
[Music]
saying okay okay okay it's just
uh low enough for me to reach it like
this okay but I hate jumps like this cuz
I don't even know how to let myself
go from this
position without jumping into
[Music]
space no b b makes me go back
up
z l doesn't do anything z r doesn't do
anything a makes me go back
up Y and X don't do
anything Mario players help
me press down oh he goes to the left
side wait okay
ah from this POV okay okay
okay here we
go oo hold
oh there's even cans up here
why who left them
[Music]
there
unbelievable dirty dirty dirty
City banana
bagels
and candy cafe speaking of
candy
[Music]
hands are a reference to an NES game oh
really let's see if this chocolate is
any good it says it's milk chocolate
inside nougat and rice puffy
thingies Oh So
Soft wa where a rice
puup a there a little bit like little
tiny
seeds of rice
puffs well it's okay I I would have
preferred it to be some kind of
cookie something to Crunch
on paen is Mar's original girlfriend
from the OG donke Kong what so he knows
her she acted like she didn't know me
but tell you this city what tell me
about it tell me about it and then he's
like forget about
it I don't want to talk to you
Mario
what I just one
friend I'm trying to control my
controller wa have to jump there you go
with my pinky
finger no it's pretty good chocolate's
pretty
good don't know if I'll survive or
not but it it gives me some
happiness
[Music]
what now don't hold
up
[Music]
oh he threw the hat in the wrong
direction
right I'm already exploding what am I
exploding
for oh wow I wanted the normal coins but
oh wellow hey what what this is so
confusing where are they I thought they
were on the
side it's
misleading leave me
[Music]
alone
wait no stay
here okay let's get some
coins no death perception no that's not
just on
me why I put put the camera like this
but you know I kind of stay where it's
Ona okay wait wait in
here all
right all right oh this one's fast a
fast boy okay the Moon is right there
okay I thought the section would be
longer the camera lies to me yeah for
real it's confusing true thank
you Ma Ma GTO wait there's another Moon
here
what I was about to leave where could it
be there's something over there a
platform that's kind of sus but I don't
see a moon there
it probably has to do with that though
[Music]
huh yeah I have to get there with a
rocket but which one can
I take
on cuz it's going to be difficult when I
hang here
right okay
[Music]
me take on me I
yo
um
no yeah it's was already giving up I
didn't think I could make
it I'll be there right away surprisingly
YooHoo yay
I made it can't believe it I'm
incredible is he going there too why
else would he walk if you walking that
way dude this is not a place for tall
people like
you only small people like me can go on
these
Adventures or Luigi but Luigi's still
smaller than you he's taller than me but
smaller than
you right Christ happy New Year yay
Christmas is over guys and happy New
Year the new year is the day after
tomorrow
oh like can you believe it it freaks me
out
W I wish cars were this bouncy in real
life uh where where where have I not
been yet
should go to
Pauline wait where did it fall I feel
like I think I listened to that one I'm
pretty sure I did yeah yeah yeah yeah I
did but Oklahoma I don't remember
Oklahoma
no my friend there was never a chance
for me to remember the location of any
city in
America no but wait isn't it like it's
okay I would say it's like when I look
at the map it's somewhere um the like
around
Texas in the middle maybe more above
Texas how about that how about
that wait it's not a city is
it yes yeah cuz I think I remember now
people were
like telling me they're from Oklahoma
and I'm like oh Oklahoma is around here
or like is is Texas or so and then they
were like
uh
[Music]
offended oh there's Oklahoma City in
okay okay then I wasn't even talking
absolute
nonsense we're close enough yeah oh what
with him Mama always said go play
outside
wait that sounds a little bit like the
beginning
of
[Music]
it's the same beat and like
VI this is all so
[Music]
crazy party in the USA yeah I feel like
they might have done it on purpose cuz
this is very USA is right wait can I
play s
I just kind of flicked my head hat in
his
crotch all
[Music]
crazy away nting my head like moving my
hips like
[Music]
it's in the
US in the
USA what what do you mean I'm getting it
do it do it do it do it do it do it do
it
again do it again why did they
stop hey I'm the master jumper let me
jump back up W okay okay okay
okay do I actually like get something oh
it's a challenge what wait
okay how do I get in like getting in is
the first
problem I wasn't in yet it doesn't
count give
me [\h__\h] walk in oh yeah you just got to
walk in smoothly right
okay I'm in I'm so
in let's go oh let go oh I go faster how
many till I get a star a Moon I mean
maybe already the 10 the 10th
one while we're going
hard I'm not going to give up I'm going
to impress these ladies with my
jumps all right let's [\h__\h] oh there
it is oh you have to get birie wait
what's going on wait I can't I can't
you're got I think 4 40 is
maximum they were like doing it faster
than I can even jump
realistically wow what 100 for a second
Mo nah look at him he's shaking his head
like that that means no no no I wonder
if anyone no shut
up okay I'll give it one more
try shut
up just get
going
okay okay stop moving the camera
wa I don't think I can get to 100 it was
some kind of crazy speed
there like sorry but like at some point
you can't even really see
well yeah cuz I'm doing full jump short
press
okay
hey uh is this not a short
jump this is a short jump
right it has to be oh wait this was a
short jump that was a long I don't even
know oh my God I don't
know oh my
God go [\h__\h] yourself go [\h__\h] yourself
ladies you're [\h__\h] bullet K me [\h__\h]
you n no no [\h__\h] no no there's a
higher chance that I'll do 100 jumps in
Super Mario
RPG I just got a warning that my my my
spice plat memor not memory My my what I
didn't even do anything is it
OBS my [\h__\h] plots is
getting nothing
no no no I didn't do anything no didn't
download anything what do you
want I can be the
car what you couldn't even move the
camera there
interesting
no okay I think the from here on we'll
go on our
foot oh m
p oh these are not
bouncing so if you don't clean your car
they will lose its bounce I didn't know
that that is
interesting what what it's in the car
wait I need the
tank where do I get the tank I guess can
I bring this one
down come down with
me I hope I won't regret this o o o o a
well I was going to get that anyway [\h__\h]
but it's only one heart now we're back
to the save
ah
oh shiny spot up there what where where
where a heart another heart nice
nice okay back to full
heart
H okay I didn't realize I could go
upstairs with the
tanks now that I know
that this knowledge is very
crucial violence
they you need for the whole thing yeah I
mean I know but I thought I just have to
pick up another one after walking for a
few meters I knew that this was going to
going to be a thing I knew that
okay oh they're
back happy s to be new year thank you I
looked up what what year it is next year
cuz like this year we had year of the
rabbit right and I was wondering since
like the company was really pushing Pi
by heart this year because you of the
rabbit and all that I wonder if they
were going to do it for someone else
next year and it said next year is Year
of the
Dragon
well and I was like oh imagine in
another
[Music]
timeline what could have
been imagine or don't imagine cuz it's
sad and then I was like wait isn't it
like chicken or AKA
rooster uh where do I go also a Chinese
zodiac and yes it is so I looked up okay
when's my
turn when is my turn then and well 2027
or something like that
so uh still [\h__\h] far to
go which even if it were like next here
I don't think that they
would do this whole thing for
me
uh but there's an after the deer of the
Dragon uh I think there was another one
and then was here with the Sheep I think
so L Senai could get this
[Music]
eventually where's the last
one
ah oh wait I think I see
it wait how do I do I shoot it maybe I
have to shoot
it monkey monkey does not equal K
Senai wait why did I run into that I
don't know how do
[Music]
I I don't know long jump I
guess
[Music]
but okay I don't want to die here
please can I become the
bullet I kind of aimed away because I
saw the bullets coming I don't know if I
can make it wait if I shoot it first
then it won't be in the
[Music]
way what a [\h__\h]
joke unbelievable
[Music]
unbelievable okay here I am
again uh yeah oh another one is dog so I
was just generally looking like what
what are what which Zodiacs could be
represented by whole life members so
there's dog sheep booster rabbits I
think I think that was kind of it at
least oh wait the blocks why are there
blocks
[Music]
now okay I'm stupid wrong jump I don't
have the jumps in my block oh yeah and
rat yeah yeah yeah rat rat rat rat that
was another
one is there no
cow isn't there a cow wait let me shoot
that
bastard
[Music]
no's cow but no but what about Ox could
we consider an ox to take the
rooll sorry I can't do these
gems
I am Pig I mean I mean no you're back oh
no wait why do I do that again and
again tiger yeah why don't we have a
tiger we have a lion but no tiger god
damn it okay we need a b down set by
counterpart okay this kind of
triggers me
now oh
[Music]
no why why why is it sometimes the wrong
jump
what do you mean more jumps by shooting
what wait
what why are Le the
tank want them after no I thought I
[Music]
I oh somehow I
thought wait my whole thinking was kind
of wrong there because I thought oh I'm
just going to get the tank over there
and then shoot from there to the
[Music]
moon but
I could do the same one if that
even that even works I could do the same
thing with this
one there's more hidden boxes there's
more hidden
boxes how do I find
them no why am I wasting so much time
for this one shitty ass
moono this is what I've been trying to
do how did those blocks show up in the
first place
they weren't there in my first
run but
maybe no
[Music]
nothing okay I'll just randomly shoot
around them in that area and try to see
if we can
find
um
secret oh my God oh my actual [\h__\h]
God no no no no no come
on
no so I cannot shoot at it to get it
right oh I
can I [\h__\h] can that's what I was
trying to
do but I you guys said
blocks but anyway when I was trying to
do that I was just somehow thinking I
need this tank over
there oh my God
[Music]
oh my
gosh let's get out of
[Music]
here there you go oh
no okay we need a a couple more moons we
need 1 2 3 4 5 six all
right oh okay these are the new posters
that give me money now that the other
one is
gone interesting oh wait what is
this
wa sounds like um I'm hitting a soccer
ball what's that area over
there oh is that the beginning
area
no can you ground pound the tarp I feel
like I tried it in a different place and
it didn't
work but they're so sus aren't
they oh okay it's just coins though you
have to stand exactly in the middle
okay
okay this one doesn't work I was in the
middle right so it just doesn't work for
every single one of them
maybe no I am in the
middle oh there's a
moon I like how just the one that I
tried after you mentioning it is the one
that gives me coins and then I thought
oh okay but every single one after that
doesn't have
it what up with that how do I get
there oh jumpy jump but let me check out
well something over here first just to
make sure you don't have to come back
there's a big
[Music]
button that's it the button
this is the
button no I fin I could do
shotgun no no
no how do I get up there again where did
I enter from no no
no God damn
it
I fought it oh that area okay I thought
it was saving some
time bye-bye seeing a trash like this
makes me feel kind of bad for it but
only kind of oh that
thing
what yo that was certainly not trash
thank you for not throwing it away
completely yo
W what what are you
playing
That Doesn't Remind Me of anything play
something
else no no that doesn't give me
anything oh Donkey Kong is a Donkey Kong
reference the
song oh it is a I
say okay let me give you a go update but
I I feel nervous talking about go
because I feel like it's going to get
clipped and I don't want to this is a
thing what the hell this is a thing that
I told her too like please don't feel
like obligated to like cover everything
I say about you on your stream I don't
want to like take up too much attention
or time I I told her that directly in a
DM um and then she said no don't worry
about it at all I enjoy it I'm like
okay uh this place is amazing on these
big buildings everywhere I got curious
to see was inside one turn thought there
was a problem one in there hope you like
it I probably already found it right oh
no oh you you're giving it to me I
thought I already found
it okay why are you standing on this
dangerous place so me and goo have been
discussing um collab ideas and I told
her though that I can only do it after
my break and she said no problem we can
o we can take her time planning
something cool and will teach me about
her Tech she ask me like what what I
have like accents or something like that
on my CA so maybe maybe she can even
help me with
that yeah trying to figure out I haven't
had so much time
to
um experiment with my accent suit
yet yeah we're disgusting I threw like
four different collab ideas at
her
and we'll see what sticks or we'll
combine them all
got she's so
sweet she's so freaking sweet she's such
a sweetie cutie
patootie and I've been listening to the
some of their songs
too cuz they're they do like their music
videos they they really like K-pop Idol
videos kind of what I've been trying to
do as well with do you and so on
pineapple as
well you're going to be kidding
kidding so cute W go can't wait but you
have to wait cuz it will take a little
while okay give us some time give us
some
time but when it will happen it will be
great can we not go up there okay is
there anything else
here
no really
yeah February maybe maybe just just wait
for
it now every time I look at Mario's face
I have to think of go what have I done
what has Mario
done okay maybe it's time with Dr
Pauline first we listen to
this oh look at him
dance
I can do that
too checkpoint oh yeah right there's a
checkpoint I never see them I'm so
blind I spanked their butt of my hat
behind so she wouldn't even notice that
it's was
me sneaky
sneaky
hi new DK City really means the world to
me I just can't thank you enough for all
your help Mario you really must join us
for our upcoming Festival I'd love to
show my gratitude to both you and the
city with a surprise do you think you
could find me for a
backup okay I think I already found all
of
them easy like one's literally right
next to you
Pauline I me
your yo okay oh oh we got a move for
have been
summer
[Music]
bankim
w Wait why we we immediately brought
here I'm going to bring more of these
people oh we were able to record my
session yeah I'm bringing more yeah
don't
worry girl don't be so
impatient you missed I've probably
missed many
moons the goal is not to get all
moons M
Mia I remember them yeah don't worry
here this one sorry I forget that's how
not how I talk to people by smacking
them with my hat it's not how I talk to
people sorry nice Fedora
though yay
yay
wow yo Moon
spam use your words okay I'm
trying I like how he like like lifts his
arms after he does that and no not this
yeah like that and then runs like he's
flying he's so
cute
uh source of urban
energy have I been up there
before
a ah this is where I got that Moon
before is there anything else I would
want to get
here probably
not oh that's the that's where my that's
why I fell I wanted to go back
there
[Music]
should go over
there
can we can get there from
here at least to
that one place that I couldn't even
reach before now I can here we
go
it's pretty wide pretty far
apart okay
y skills W am I
right what's that what was that down
there oh just that thing okay but from
here I can't get back up to where I was
before sadly oh well it was worth the
Moon
I hear it
was okay guys no accidents this time
please okay okay
okay almost fell
off I made it and then oh oh it's where
musician play is I didn't even realize
[Music]
that wow convenient very
convenient all right almost
[Music]
have it's already complete guys what
else do you want
yo with the Clapping that's [\h__\h]
[Music]
exciting they were not playing those
same Melodies outside right I would have
recognized it they were playing
different melodies for
sure okay so there was wasn't there one
here yeah hey only one left wait look at
this one it's our new star
right he's such a Miley Cyrus fan oh my
[Music]
God on song is on
I'm my
head yeah we made it wait is she going
to
sing that's all the musicians we need
thanks that's her surprise isn't it I'm
amazed at your persistence you should
consider running for public office now
just need to figure out this other
problem to see the undergr underground
power plant seems to be out of
condition we need that thing to supply
power to the festival I don't suppose
you're familiar with you need my moons
probably don't you but I need them
too wait so
what do I just charge what how do I what
do
I you want to tell
me power might want to check out those
big manual manual covers but you didn't
he that for me the manual covers I went
one already are there more that lead to
different
[Music]
places glowing light right
here it's just one coin but I really
want to get it okay uh glowing
light all over
there sorry
hey I'm walking
here oh they even like staring at it
don't even tell me about it don't even
tell me about
it
wa this is so cute
stop let's go hey I'm rolling
here bye
oh wait am I supposed to go here
anyway shut let me talk to the gyers too
fast wait
what oh oh oh I thought there was an
opening here but there isn't okay never
mind never mind then there's nothing
there really it was just to show us
what's up
interesting it's turning forever now
okay oh now I stopped
moving oh I got them all
anyway
[Music]
oopsy a P with a
pinky oh recommendations I see very
good very
good
oh wait when I press this when I don't
have to hat on I
can't I just realized it
now
oh
nice that's fine at least you made it
Mario often I fail these kind of jumps
so I'm I'm pretty
proud
whoa how come this like those moments I
immediately kill it it doesn't just uh
eat it how
comeing
unnecessary because I'm so close okay
okay
wait ow what why did I do that I'm going
to
die wait I can move them with the hat
too don't die oh my God there's a heart
let's go another one would be nice
though
all the
rats
so
w
wait no no
no it didn't save me a second
time okay I wanted to get on the top of
it get some coins
back I need to stay rich I will not let
my wealth trickle down on
you
humans the we we must stay
wealthy I will not share my insane
wealthiness oh my
God just like sopa exactly she inspires
[Music]
me
that momentum was a little bit too much
not going to
lie so learned
nothing there was nothing to
learn
as long as my company lives I
live and chickens can be reproduced
easily any victims that
are a byproduct of the suffering o
is
all just part of the bigger
picture
n I'm such a good
villain no
[Music]
no I thought that was going to make it
he looked like he was diving onto that
platform God damn it okay
whatever come
on it's not that difficult I don't know
why this is happening to me
ah no
no
[Music]
okay but I think I can get a heart again
here okay y y y y y y y
[Music]
y okay please do not die Wawa surely
this level is over
[Music]
soon
e
[Music]
can I do this too
no
[Music]
no whatever I don't care I'm getting a
heart here
anyway this is a real heart Challenger
man it's unbelievable it's
unbelievable you're unbelievable okay
come
on oh calm down calm down calm
down okay let's just go let's just go
let's just
[Music]
go the momentum almost got me Pauline
why are you in
here why are you in there you're
supposed to be in the in that stage
place I wanted to get a firsthand look
at the problem down here at the power
plant
well she teleported yeah
looks like that Monster's friend needs
to be taught a new dunk
lesson oh
cute
[Music]
cute cute it's so cute so cute that was
too easy
also but I guess okay that's why the
those dudes oh look at his
PS that's why those couldn't get out of
here and couldn't do anything they were
being terrorized by those plants
unbelievable and I saved them once again
waa saves the day you guys all say I'm
evil and
yet I just casually do hero things like
that without be without even you know
intending to do
so not what I would say it's a real
hero
yes you save them after dying 12 times
you see how many times I am willing to
die for the greater
cause no I don't say that that's not
special because I'm a
phoenix don't you dare say that don't
you use that on me it's still painful to
die okay I may be able to revive but it
doesn't mean it doesn't hurt or it's
traumatic for
me oh look at all those
bounds
so why don't you give them to
me and where did you get them
from oh thank you Mario now that you've
um powered up the city it's time for the
festival to begin now we can finally
kick up the festival in style and power
shall we oh hey would you like to
participate in the festival it's right
up your alley yes I'll be the dancer and
you'll be the singer
okay how am I participating though for
real I traditional
Festival best part of the
game ladies and gentlemen no way am we
going to sing rhym game
style she's a star it's all about
her wait I'm I'm going to be in a
challenge there she is
yay
oh Nice lyrics they really get me deep
in my heart oh
[Music]
oh oh wait there we go there there is
actual lyrics I'm
impressed
[\h__\h] trying to go in in
style oh sing it girl
wait wo wow is she going to sing like
this
forever jump like you don't
[Music]
care let's go let's go
Queen
yes
belted I love
you what no don't go
backwards it turns around at some
point hey hey he he he he
he
what is it this see yesi what is she
singing oh this is
confusing please no upside down
[Music]
please almost gone
maybe when does it start looping cuz
this doesn't sound like a loop
yet
no yeah all the money I lost with so
many deaths it's coming back to
[Music]
me jump without a
care you'll be there really you
promise Donkey Kong a oh is a yeah okay
that's that's a d reference for
[Music]
sure also because she originally
appeared in a Donkey Kong game that's
why her city is called New Don City huh
and they even implement this as a
throwback that's pretty darn
cute Donkey Kong she misses him where is
oh there he
is Pauline your husand question
[Music]
y bye bye donkey King get
[\h__\h] I am the new husband I am the new
gu she lies you got nothing on me you
can punch I can kick I can jump like a
[Music]
boss jumping me in Jump oh they jumping
how
jump jump black you don't care woo y I
want to get up
here
[Applause]
[Music]
y your oneup girl did she just say
she'll be my oneup
girl like a like a one up
for
I'm ruining her music what if
[Music]
I no get them sing
impossible
C
[Applause]
see wait it's kind of dark if she
doesn't for that
long
to
W okay I'm done girl yeah yeah thank you
again Mario I'm dedicating this Festival
to you we couldn't have felt kind of
dedicated to Donkey Kong to be honest
but sure
mhm we couldn't have done it without
your help please accept this as a
gift no
yay that's cute that was really cute
hold that wait can we just forget about
Peach and leave her with Bowser and just
you know you know run away with poine I
think she's right
there I just
say I'm I'm not interested anymore than
the peach I'm a poine kind of guy
now no
we're ex is canonically no way
well it's not uncomon that xes get back
together right
so there have so many
moons that was very
productive no one can say that that's
not true will you be our oneup girl your
oneup girl
[Music]
H I'll be one down girl cuz I'm down bad
for you oh
[\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] I can't believe I just did an
actual freestyle flirt that actually
works oh
than what it's not a roast what it's a
flirt excuse me if you didn't get that
then I failed my mission I guess it's a
one down B I'm
staying I'm down for
you re re I've got the
re
what that was horrendous hor you
embarrassed I
do
down for what everything as long as it's
you uhoh we've H uhh we've hit a
proverbial fork in the road which
kingdom oh again something like this
snow or Seaside oh oh we'll go to both
eventually right so what does it
matter stop for already
dead okay let's go see
[Music]
M I'm so excited I can't believe I can't
believe I'm going back
there oh wait shut
up why does it say in my capture
card like for example 900 50 mb free on
Windows
c um and it's going down I'm not I'm not
recording anything why is it this is
what it meant before hul this is taking
up space but what it's not recording
though it says there's a red button that
I can click to record but wait what if I
press
oh but
no that didn't change
anything no it's not OBS it's a capture
card
program I guess it's just temporary
[Music]
files I feel like it just reached zero
before and then it went back up to 900 I
think so it just Loops like that I
think yeah I had this before yeah yeah
yeah wait why am I out of my
suit why am I not wearing my for oh wait
I am wait what the M the
oh I'm playing in the past okay now I'm
here again okay
okay confusion your vision
h w are your eyes
okay you need to do some cleaning up
yeah but why is it taking up this
temporary anyway why is it taking it
up yeah yeah I have the other thing
but it's uh like I'm I'm installing all
my new games and stuff over there and I
deinstall games once I'm done too but I
guess it's still so much stuff on my on
my disc uh hard drive or
what that I generally basically
have nothing left like yeah 900
MB it's just too much yeah it's just too
much no it's 930 GB that could be on
there
I need to move things but um
some
difficult SSD become pretty inefficient
for real time to see clean oh I used to
use that in the past interesting does
that still work is that still thing I
might remind me then after the stream on
Twitter
please what an amazingly energetic
Festival let's keep the energy going as
we keep on the seeing as how we've got
some time to kill let's R some no shut
up do not talk to me do not even talk to
me there's a cabet scene that's supposed
to be nice and says here to be sure
revisit the four Giant M fountains not
mountains
okay you keep stream archive it's I
don't know I'm not keep keeping a stream
archive but I guess it somehow is like I
don't
know
wow whatever it's probably fine it's
just a temporary thing
now it's at 400 it probably reaches zero
and then goes back to 900
wao wow
wowow select this clean up oh what's on
top of the fancy goblet
W it's sucking something I think it's
sucking a moon probably no wait is a is
it straw
drinking Moon power or something like
that bouncer oh boun's
Footprints they look
cute they're so round and cute t SW this
bub Lane as long as that sucker is
creeping around literally sucker
okay oh this a
straw it is a straw it looked like a
laser from afar B us IM Resort until a v
creature sh up just look all of our
treasure Sparkle water don't you help us
put a stop to him otherwise we only have
sea water left and that's really [\h__\h]
salty please help
us SE
go oh
Goombas that water kind of
wobbly no it's it's amazing it's
actually amazing do we need
them let's collect them just in
casewise I have to run back and do it
again
oh he's like oh where'd she go [\h__\h] P
sized braak
okay I've got them
all does that do anything for
me maybe
not well they're
scared they're
terrified go up the path with them oh oh
is it
necessary
stupid
bird they fear the Goomba Tower
everybody here at the Goomba
Tower music changes
here
oh ises this work
Bowser's
hiding
wait it kept on like cutting off but
here
actually now it's kind of continuing the
music is it depending
on oh here it's weaker I think wait no
am I imagining it I'm trying to get the
coins he and the
lady she loves me oh no she has a moon a
pink moon let's
go oh and she's
gone let's
Backle okay can we still use them I
don't think we need them
anymore and we're less flexible with
them need them anymore right
oh leave me
alone sorry for
screaming
no okay I'm in safe zone now safe Zone
safe Zone nice Dodge thank
you de
May what
oh we're done yay no we're not
done now they're shooting us so close to
where I'm standing please do not do that
wait Moon Moon Moon
[Music]
Mo above rolling Canyon
yeah I have ascended the
canyon
vamos
P wait I can jump in no oh I don't need
to it opens up for me and I can press
the
button press the
buttton
oh what that seems like the main thing
to do on this island and I did it
immediately oh oh we we all you want I
will Never Surrender your delicious
Sparkle
[Music]
water angry I
am oh he's mad now Freemont just left oh
okay okay I
see ow oh I get
Sandy
funny thought it was from the game
I am the
game the game is
me wa in
control oh yeah let's talk a little bit
about that collab that I had with K
Maki the goddess the Queen the other day
did you guys watch it oh do I need them
again just in case just in case no maybe
I don't need
them this is a dead end I
think this Gap though is kind of sus no
no okay there's no Gap it just looked
like it uh so I had this collab that I
was
um invited
to and uh I I I hope you guys watched
those videos that I linked on Twitter
because only with
that will you really understand
why it's such a big deal thank you for
the gazon
[Music]
tide
interesting they were very mhm yeah
she's she's U quite a spicy lady lady
lady in her
music she's good with the spicy
stuff
um and and yeah she's been a solo artist
under AIX for quite a while now and AIX
has been doing like YouTuber stuff even
though they're a music
label they've been going at it oh
interesting
and I guess they were like hey don't you
want to try becoming a vtuber as well I
imagine
treasure
wo oh I have to kill him in that order
are you kidding me I only remember the
first one guys did you have an eye on
it wait how do I kill them I've been
trying to jump on them but [\h__\h] no God
damn it we have to look at it again cuz
certainly I failed oh this one even
stays alive
why can I
redo oh oh I died
okay yeah I I know I know it's hard to
tell though one 2 3
4 one no
[Applause]
[\h__\h] that was the wrong order cuz my I
hit I missed with my
hat oh that
sucks what was I saying I had a collab
so blah BL um it was
interesting uh there was like me and the
other girls were like preparing for it
like testing like they were they were
putting like all everything together
like she has her own stuff who puts
everything together it was very
professional so she doesn't touch the
OBS stuff at
all I thought I thought like she had
maybe learned how to use that kind of
stuff but no and honestly I I think this
is the right way she's such a legendary
Queen she shouldn't be even touching the
keyboard you know
yes they should be doing everything for
her M because she deserves it oh wait
right there's
air
um yeah so like aic's YouTuber staff or
so just how we have cover staff who does
help us uh in case it's like a official
program or
so she has that kind of stuff too I
guess and so we were set setting
everything up and then they were like oh
K makian has arrived um you get to greet
her for a moment and and and then she
she shows
up she like we hear her voice and we're
like nice to meet you and I am this
person I am this person I am this person
looking forward to today and then she's
like okay okay and then she
leaves like she we just had a greeting
for like 2 minutes and then she leaves
and they finished setting up and then
right before the beginning she comes
back like 2 minutes before the
beginning so like really really really
um everything planned out perfectly
everything timed
perfectly and then at the end also after
it ended like we said Thank you thank
you so much oh it was a pleasure let's
do it again yeah and then immediately
gone yeah yeah it was pretty pretty
corporate open the one behind first oh
okay it was pretty
corporate but I I hope that we can do
more stuff together um I want to try to
like now that I've been invited to her
program maybe I can invite her to
something on my side too you
know I'll give it a try I'll give it a
try Sly m
[Music]
but you know she was asking us um at the
end during the stream what kind of stuff
would you want would you tell me to do
and I thought everybody was going to
give an answer so I I I just like raised
my hand basically the first and I
thought the others would say something
too but then I guess my answer was so
good they just cut it off after that but
I said she should do K because I just
want to hear her saying and I was just
saying like she should do a solo okay
but somehow it turned into a
conversation of like haha yeah we should
to collab all of us together and I'm
like really I mean yeah sure but I I
really just wanted to hear good gaki is
solo K and I said she should also do
like a dancing um
stream too I think I said that
maybe yeah that was my that's my
answer so it was a nice stream we
basically talked about V tubing in
general and like its history and our
advice on how to survive this business
and and how to stay up on top of it and
I said stuff like yeah in order to keep
up my motivation or like what was I
saying in order to keep the audience
interested and so on I like to every
once in a while do like Innovative
original content unique content like
cooking streams and this and that uh as
much as I can but I mean I obviously
can't obviously can't do it every day
and in between there's many normal
gaming streams but just got to set
myself apart every once in a while with
that and that's pretty important to me
or like oh yeah they were they were
really excited about what I said when I
said I do vacation streams like travel
streams
I travel and then I talk about it on
stream and I share everything on stream
it's a good excuse to Vacation basically
I can combine the two things yeah and I
told them oh I'm actually going to the
mes again soon they're like oh I want to
go I was flexing my
vacation yeah and then so before it it
was actually interesting like before
when we were setting up and it was it's
just me and the other two guests
basically and the staff what Mario what
are you
doing oh oh he's feeling really hot oh I
should change cloes huh never mind um
when we when we were setting up I I
heard in their
conversation that the two girls like
they know each other because they've I
guess already been in a lot of streams
together and events together I thought
oh so they were like talking a little
bit together and I was just chilling you
know I didn't really have much in common
or I was just like also a little bit shy
and nervous um so I I wasn't really
mixing myself into the
conversation but during the stream I
guess we all
really like felt like we were in the
same situation same position we all of
hello project really a lot they were all
I first thought I should go into this
like without mentioning it at all
because I don't want to seem like a
creep that was my original plan to not
bring up hello project much or at all
and then before the stream I asked if
it's allowed to at least say in my self
introduction that I am a fan of it just
so that she knows but I don't want to
talk too much about it but then once I
said it the other girls cuz I was the
first to introduce myself the other
girls also took the opportunity to talk
about it and then we all started
fangirling about it and it became like a
whole fangirling stream overall and and
and I really H you didn't think of us as
like cringe fans and like oh what did I
get myself into what did I invite these
people yeah I hope we didn't make her
feel
uncomfortable
yeah I wonder that really was for me it
wasn't the
plan why why would I open them one by
one
what
what wait I just guessed that one you
guys said up and then left and this one
I just
guessed
what they don't show
up what oh because Oh I thought I had to
kill them in the right order but you
just have to see them and then in the
same order as they show up like that you
also just open the treasure chest and
then n no hold
on well it was good having a little talk
there okay I like to focus on my
tangents sometimes every once in a
while only sometimes
do I need to wear the right clothes yeah
I thought so can I wear the ones from
before or do you guys have your own
outfits uh hey
what
what oh you're right those flowers give
you that speed ah yeah
you know actually another think that's
kind of
funny regarding that
collab so as I I was going to say like
in the beginning we didn't really talk
really much but then afterwards I guess
we uh you know gaki son she left really
early and then we were like oh okay so I
guess oh yeah thank thank you everybody
we were thanking each other and thanking
the staff and so on and then we slowly
left
and then one of the girls added me on
Discord and I was like oh okay I guess
she just wants to be know a little bit
you know friendly and so I added her
back and then we talked a little bit
more and she was like oh yeah that was
fun and I'm like yeah that was
fun you're cool let's let's be friends
and she's like yeah yeah let's be
friends and then she
says then she says actually I I I I know
you from a long time ago and we talked
before and I'm like
it she says oh we talked
about hello project
before like 10 years ago and I'm like
what
huh she's like oh yeah yeah you know and
she explained to me and I'm
like oh my
God what and we even we even
we we we we even have the same
oosi we had the same oi this from B's
cobal but I I feel bad cuz I didn't
remember any of
this
what can you believe it I can't believe
it go straight go
straight
yes
Yahoo yeah sorry I don't know how I can
make those things more
quiet I hate this sound board thingy
this I don't like the RO I don't like it
I wish there was something as good as
the
[Music]
gold did you remember after she
explained i i i let's say I don't I
didn't remember the situation but I
remembered
her can I say one thing please don't
clip
this I I don't I I feel awkward if this
gets clipped I'm not like saying
anything illegal or something but don't
make it
awkward no don't clip it no no no when I
say don't clip it people usually
listen cuz they don't want my wrath upon
them ah
a I think Clippers are scared of
me
byebye what's it G Turn enter the
lighthouse you must go a bit further I
don't know where I really want to go
don't tell me where I want to go what I
really really want to go don't tell you
where you want to go where you really
really want to go I want to I want to I
want to I want to I want to really
really really really want to go out of
nowhere
oh yeah yeah wait NY shop oh it's a shop
okay let's go to her the if I it's so
hard to get out of the
water this place is so open looking that
it's bit difficult for me to decide
where to
go oh there's
a there's a gold flag here a checkpoint
they aren't scared enough of
you I I do think I scare them because
I've said before
like uh like some criticism about
Clippers and then I think I I may have
had Clippers like change things before
right so I'm like I don't think the
other girls really do stuff like
this they just let things happen so yeah
yeah
[Music]
oh my God this is
terrifying nice I remembered my new
trick I need air though
ow smack
[Music]
it nice
one
better to put your foot down oh speaking
of putting my foot down that reminds me
of something
um I
feel uncomfortable even talking about
this um but I feel like I have to I also
talked about it with
[Music]
JMA God damn it
oh
um remember that Korean Wiki that I
talked
about uh I hope this
reaches uh someone me saying this
because they seem to be very uh
attentive and like on top of
everything there is one section like I I
appreciate the wiki being so detailed
and I'm pretty impressed about it but
there's one thing that I don't really
understand where that came from at all
like I don't remember any situation
where I possibly
gave
any any
situation that would make
that a thing like I don't understand I I
don't think I ever said anything that
that gave people that kind of idea but
it makes me very uncomfortable to have
it referenced there and I don't even
want to say it so this is difficult to
get my point
across um in the ref I think it was oh
yeah okay it's the section that's
directly under Austria
Australia um in the references where
there's like usual room AUST Australia
and uh I think bottom left as well I
just I
don't like that being
there because it's just wrong I don't
understand why it's there like when have
I ever made jokes like that I mean
sometimes I see other people making
these jokes and I look over it but I
personally don't think I ever made a
joke like
that so I don't know if if if somebody
could edit
it
um if someone could edit it out um I'm
now making a public statement that I do
not approve of
this content
so I don't know how to do it so I leave
it up to the people cuz it's a community
[Music]
thing
yeah like the rest of this is like the
rest of the article is fine and it's
like really really well
written it's all good but this is just
one thing where I'm
[Music]
like cuz I don't want people reading up
especially now cuz like goig was reading
it and a lot of new people were reading
it with her and I don't want a bad
impression to be left you
know that is my my
concern I don't get it yeah sorry I I
can't I don't even want to say it
because it's really uncomfortable for
me yes I am now where the money
is okay and with that I will end this
topic thank you I think I hope I got the
point
across I think we know what I'm talking
about if you were to look it up then
yeah you probably would
understand I'll keep it that way yeah I
mean it's really just like a reference
that I don't think I ever made
so so it's
fine I mean it's not fine but it's it's
okay don't worry about
it um what what else is there I need to
get the
moon but now I can't go back there and I
can't do that oh
wait I need you guys yum ah okay let's
just put
[Music]
coins there's one tube there that goes
sideways oh wait wait can I ground pound
it this thing cuz that's where it is
that's where the tube
is
we got to check out the costume shop
here
later yeah wait how do I get to that
tube turn to start now you can stand on
those three blocks oh oh wait where was
the
start here did I enter
here I think
so oh yeah yeah yeah
oh oh wait another thing that we can do
o I'm definitely going to get hit and
then die yeah but there's a checkpoint
close
by I know
it we all knew
it I had it
coming
[Music]
get out of my
face or I will send my hat at
you they're up too
high nice nice
nice
oh no no no no no no no no
no here it
is is it reset de
now you can send me your tiny head I'll
look after it what I don't I don't know
what you
mean I don't know what you're talking
about oh no don't go there oh yeah oh
yeah okay that's what I want
M
no right we're not going there
though we
are seems like we have to do uh
everything again seems like it's reset
no but uh that's okay
too cuz we'll activate this and then
I'll just I'll come
back no no oh okay
okay I hate the Koopa shells
man that one was just a coin right so
no need to get that
one can you not pick the shells
up I don't think
so what the
hell what
the why are they trying to killing
trying to kill the
ocean is it because I'm in there oh my
God go
in
okay why is there no music here we need
music I need some some ocean inspired
music give me a ukulele or something
like
that let's go let's
pickle and the octopus is angry very
very
mad
ooh there's a lot of these like speed
UPS
woohoo where can we go with this oh
there's another T chest help
me
htain oh and
checkpoint glass Palace all
right oh with this this is also nice
because we can walk over the water huh
what are those Foods what the
hell oh they jump really
high we have 15 coin I always have like
almost the exact
amount for the
shops you're selling here oh cute the
Sailor
outfit a but this one really cute oh my
God
wait this is how me and therea have to
dress in the
malds I don't have a Hawai is t-shirt
though maybe I can order
one Speaking of ordering clothes and
Nissa yesterday out of nowhere she sends
me like unprompted sent me like
underwear that she's
buying or she already bought and she's
like look how cute this is I bought this
and I'm like oh pretty cute and then we
talk about underwear and she sends me
more links and we look at the underwear
together she's like oh if I didn't
already order I would have ordered a
pair for you because it's a shop that I
I don't have access to I
think oh don't shoot
Nissa what what's this thing's name
again
Nessie yeah
yeah
Nessie right yes almost like
narissa oh
my is this random corn a
[Music]
hint that surely leads to something
interesting
[Music]
right there we
go where couldn't lead I thought she
doesn't wear underwear well it was is um
it was more about the top part anyway we
were talking mostly about the top part
looking really
cute and being
[Music]
comy but then I was saying like I I
don't know this is cute and all
but I
I don't even think I would buy it yeah B
I don't have air ah no no no no no no no
no no no I want to lose all these Hearts
no I don't even think I would buy it
because it's like well I
mean I don't I mean people say like just
be pretty and cute for yourself oh where
cute clothes for yourself and all
that yeah I guess I can see it but I
don't really I don't really feel like
I'm getting anything out of dressing up
like that for
myself I got the extra Hearts back as
well
so I'll just
continue with my not so cute underwear I
have some cute underwear too okay but I
never wear it like what
for it's less comfortable
than normal boring
underwear you want to be
comfortable I want to be
comfortable that is the perfect state to
be I'm sorry it's disappointing
perhaps cuz you know they didn't expect
it to be oh dear oh dear okay
spicy I got to say though like I think
we I talked about this before to some
extent the Japanese
underwear is so different from Western
under I mean I mean the
designs are so
different it's really interesting oh
there's a scarecrow in the water
they're so much more like
girly the patterns they use and the
shapes they
[Music]
use yeah it's very different uh wait I
[\h__\h] yeah get down get down to the
bubbles get down to the bubbles there we
go okay we got it we're down here what
for okay Moon Parts I am
understand is more focus on cuy yeah I
mean they surely oops oh my God I think
you're doing that on purpose aren't
you there uh there definitely are also
more
mature underwear designs if you look for
them but generally it's like cutesy and
pink and pastel colors and yeah as I
said the shapes are also very girly and
I used to really like that a lot
lot and buy a lot of Japanese underwear
sets but yeah now I also kind of no cuz
um yeah I just
buy normal comfy why am I telling you
this shut up shut up guys don't even
listen close your
ears St on your
business
[Music]
you're only allowed to hear this kind of
stuff in a girl talk stream otherwise
no put the fingers in your ears
now in in a retrospective can you do it
like backwards so that everything you
heard what has been
unheard yeah wipe your
mind
[Music]
do it just do it don't question
it
no let me teleport I can't can I not
teleport in
here is there do I do I swim back
up oh we're almost there look
okay
what's my hat doing
there give it
back what is my hat doing there I don't
remember giving you my
hat oh to open this
okay I mean I remember giving him my hat
perhaps but I don't remember what it
did where is the next girl I don't know
GH po give me some time we'll be back
after this vacation
break
[Music]
yeah we'll be back and I want to do the
reverse H talks and a VR
maybe worth
it m thieves all St
h i mean there's so many things I can do
you know and there's only so much so
little
time nice all at
once definitely want to do one or two
gaming streams one CA
[Music]
stream maybe I don't
know
that one Z done stream where we talk
about some mif stuff I think I think
we're probably going to do just like
with way and we're going to do an after
talk too and you know I had this cute
idea what
if I buy like
little maybe Diaries or like little
books memo books for us both of us one
for her one for me and then every day at
the end of the day we have to write down
our memories of the day and impressions
of the other and all that and then after
the vacation we do a stream where we
read those things out to each other and
to you guys isn't that cute I have like
the best ideas oh my God I'm such a
genius oh my
God and then we can also keep them as a
memory isn't that so cute oh my God I'm
so cute my brain is so
cute h
and that's that's uh oh that's how we
could do our like review after stream
like with me and Raina we did like the
she did The Artsy thing
right um and then we our way of doing it
could be like you know these these diary
entries Wayne's drawings were so cute
man yeah she's so good don't know what
else I'm not in
there is it one I already
got wait anyway I'm like I need to get
to another
Fountain but I'm so distracted like
running into the weirdest corners of
this
map you made fun of me for having a
journal what no did I make fun of you I
know I didn't want to make fun of you I
mean there's nothing wrong with that
also like I think it's cute goo also
apparently keeps a diary and she put my
name into it so cute I'm in her di you
have no idea how many attempts I've made
in my teenage Hood childhood to write
Diaries because like I love stationary
too so I like see cute books that have
potential to be potential to be a cute
diary and I ride into it for one day and
then it's over then I don't get back to
it and then I buy a new one ages later
because I'm like well I started this
like two years ago I can't ride into the
same diary again if I start now keep on
telling myself to write
one
[Music]
because no don't go away no okay because
I'm like oh it's surely like something
great to look at when you're
older I wish I wish I would have
actively written Diaries in my in my
youth I'm still young
though motivational issues I don't know
I don't think I have motivational issues
much just just Comm commitment to diary
I don't I don't think I have commitment
issues either in general it's just to
diary
specifically this channels are there
yeah I think I've um I've documented my
life in different ways so that's also
nice yeah but I have not documented
like like my time as an I don't know 11
year old 12 year old and all that so
that's that's sad I wish I did that the
button is the key to restoring our
pressure okay okay we'll go there okay
thank you that's really close I can do
that I can do that maybe with these
boys oh wo W okay I can stay up here
even so it's like a regular but
upwards it
wait or it does end eventually okay wow
well that was easy
H that was
easy today I blew a hug hole out of out
the seat of my pants what all those 11
year old yeah there's um yeah there's
not really any Diaries remaining for
that but I have something else remaining
remaining from that time of my
life that I've been keeping to share
eventually on the stream number one
friendship books with my friends entries
and like me writing cringe [\h__\h] like
what I want to be in the future and what
job I want to do and what music I listen
to and what is the best game in the
world
and yeah that's I'm eventually going to
do that eventually and then there's
another thing but I'm not sure if I want
to share that um did I ever tell you I
had this little book with my best friend
in junior high school first
class I don't know how old I was then uh
but Young
um uh and it was like um it started
because you know you you you exchange
little pieces of paper with messages
during class right you do that and it
was just never enough I guess cuz I've
been a Tanger since I was young and she
was that too I guess and we just had so
much to say that these little paper
pieces would not be enough so we started
a book I told you I'll tell you
again and so we would give each other
the book like maybe at the end of the
day to write in like basically a whole
letter like one or two sometimes three
pages of what's going on what we want to
talk about I guess probably at the time
smartphones were not yeah I mean I think
they were phones I don't want to like
you know say anything that say my age or
so they were definitely smartphones but
like like online messaging like Discord
or WhatsApp and all that was not really
a thing yet you know so we had SMS but
those cost money and the more you write
I think the more it costs and all that
you know it was just like you know not
that common yet so yeah so you are kind
of still forced to communicate
differently and you know I I kind of
like that thinking like that thinking
back I'm I'm I'm glad I experienced my
childhood like that now that I think
about it I'm glad that I'm not growing
up during the current um generation I
had a mix I guess of both like Boomie
and zomi culture right I got a little
bit of the both of Both Worlds cuz I'm
like growing up with this whole
[\h__\h] like like uh um
evolutionizing itself you know what I
mean
yeah millennials uh
but yeah growing up during The Changing
Times and changing with the times and
now kids grow up and they [\h__\h] have
iPads as toddlers if I ever have a child
let me tell you I I would
never I don't think I will I mean yeah
it could be tempting probably in the
future but I want to I want to say I
want to say to the future self don't
give up do not give your [\h__\h] toddler
an iPad no no no no and you will not
give your child if you will ever have
one which I kind of doubt but anyway
don't give them an iPhone uh or whatever
phone before I don't know I mean okay
that is a okay okay iPad yeah but the
phone thing is a problem because if your
kid doesn't have a phone and in school
everybody else has a phone they kind of
get bullied and they feel like left out
and you know this and that so that's
kind of an issue that will come up that
your child has no other way dealing with
besides getting a phone because children
are terrible and they will say you suck
and you're lame because you don't have a
phone for sure but ideally I wouldn't
want to give them a phone until
like 13
maybe 12
13 but iPad no no no no [\h__\h] iPads
no
no no toddler no one under 10 okay maybe
no one under nine is touching an iPad no
[\h__\h]
no give them those kids tablets yeah no
the only
thing the only
[Music]
tablet yeah the only tablet will I find
this this
is is this what I think oh yeah
something like
this
[Music]
yes this is the good stuff this is the
good stuff I think mhm oh yeah oh
yeah the only tablet my kids will be
getting I don't care if it's not
something they sell in this day and age
but the only thing they'll be getting is
something like this an attached pen on a
string they can draw a little bit like
it's almost like pixel art on there and
then you there's like somewhere there's
a lever oh yeah at the bottom there's a
lever here and you pull it to the side
and it
disappears this is the best thing and
this is the only tablet you will need
until you're I don't know 9 years old I
don't care this is the best thing ever
one of my favorite toys when I was
younger right do the do kids these days
still get these from their parents or is
this like replaced by by iPad that's
[Music]
completely you already have a tablet and
I want a tablet you already have a
tablet at home tablet at
home they still get them they will if I
ever have one yeah [\h__\h] yeah we grow up
with those we will give them to our kids
eventually replace with a hand me down
iPad no no no no no
no anyway um thank you for that fun
conversation how did we get there oh
yeah yeah yeah so communication so our
way was like writing letters in the book
and then giving each other the book back
every now and then and eventually like
the pace was getting like slower because
we were not
like keeping up with it properly but we
kept it up for quite a while and there's
it's it's it's really cute because most
of the time my friend had a
crush on
someone and and like that was discussed
a lot in
there her crush and we're like yeah he's
so
stupid it's so cute I think I think I
had maybe
one Crush maybe during that time but it
was unrequited and I think I was also
too embarrassed to even admit it I don't
think we ever talked about it properly
me and my besti
I felt I felt embarrassed because surely
he wouldn't like me
back
goodbye surely he wouldn't like me back
but I wouldn't that was my way of
thinking and it still is like past me I
was nerdy and I was unpopular I was the
weird
kid and they were like in terms of boys
I don't think they were don't go away
money I don't really think we had many
or any maybe maybe maybe one nerdy boy
actually surprising there's always I
think several nerdy boys as well
but I don't even I don't even recall
them was he one of the cool boys I don't
think he will he was something in
between maybe maybe
they missed out there were
T I
think I think I at least once in my life
in in that Junior High School first year
around the time at least once I wrote a
love letter I
think an anonymous
one I think I remember doing that okay
where's the other thing God damn it
ah where is the other one where's the
next
one heart Challenger was
real not not not really like that I
think with the red
heart it certainly must have had heart
yeah you get any love letters and fan
mail I
mean
not so blatantly like saying oh my God I
love you so much marry me I think those
would probably get filtered
out they would probably filter those out
where do I go sorry I need to open my
eyes for once up
there let's see how we get to the LI
house oh yeah that's the other
[Music]
shop
shortcut marry me wa please marry
me not
now I cannot get married now don't you
understand oh wait a there it
[Music]
on
wait how do I get to the Top If this is
not the
entrance let's talk to the NPC and you
must ah to enter the yeah I read that
before you must go a bit further ahead
probably in that direction okay I
see you have five four wives already
I'll probably have more than that
those are just the ones in the worldwide
wife web but I have
other
other how do you
say
collections also I think was a little
bit worried that when she saw in the
Korean Wiki that I'm apparently a wife
collector no I'm not I'm a wife
receiver they just naturally flock to me
surprisingly but yeah i' I've I've cared
a good amount of wife so far but she was
pretty surprised she was like like what
like I I am wife or so something like
that no no no go you are
child my new child not wife don't worry
don't be
concerned don't worry got to catch them
all no go Set Go go is
different is kuo jealous no I don't I
don't know if she even noticed anything
going
on hey a b
air oh wait I should become a fish why
do I not just become a fish I'm a
[\h__\h]
idiot
no I lost
my my extra Hearts go down go down how
do I go how do I go
down
[Music]
whatever how do I go
down ah there we go x button that's
weird
controls wait that's really weird with
the joystick you can only go like four
forward no matter what direction or like
sideways weird you can't even like
combine it with the camera controls no
[Music]
no what
no this really bad I can't even try to
get everything here
okay I guess I don't need
[Music]
it what's that mean
come did I read that
correctly shake to attack
what why are you telling me
that
what
yay I [\h__\h] made it
finally
as a fish I wasn't I wasn't planning on
attacking could I have attack the
eels I thought I just had to make it
through
boom wow all those glass sharts Mario
standing right in front of it and
nothing hits
him for the third
time one more fountain
which one over there oh yeah I
see PL
armor here we
[Music]
go oh yeah
spe
yeah cuz I wasted so much time now we
have to speed up a little
bit I looked at the at the area you know
in detail oh wow okay helping me but at
the same time being a piece of [\h__\h] okay
cool cool cool cool
cool oh the back
[Music]
side oh it disappears
okay my resion yeah more my resion oh
there's another seed over
there the seeds give
you more moons
but like it's so
fire I don't want to go for all the
trouble not worth my time Hot Spring
Island Hot
Spring wait I have to bring one of those
bad boys over
here and
no
B
okay wait I'm a taco right now I'm a
taco Dad look at my backside so cute
tentacles
wow I need to charge wait I can't move
while I'm doing this wait I should do
[Music]
W you know in the
script with the w for Ena she did say
the first one really quietly according
to the script as I as I made her do it
and then the second one was supposed to
be louder but it was still pretty
quiet her loud
walk is
that wow you know
it didn't get much louder you know oh
thank you for the membersip
wow thank you it do be like that yeah
also did you like the joke that the one
that CI said that was not freestyle that
was my joke
too wow Wawa's jokes actually for once
finally
Landing you guys seem to find them quite
funny
oh oh oh w Wait I didn't know he could
do
that how did I do that
anyway no
idea I surprised to yeah comedian is
back I appreciate you hum your humor
greatly oh thank you so much I'm really
happy to be so appreciative is this last
one
hey you dead now or we have a final
fight Bring It On great time great time
to take back to spark water okay and how
are we going
to is he going to come over
here wait take back wait you want me to
actually go up there instead of fighting
him
hi or by the way it's a yes it's a yes
it's a
yes what if I go here does it shoot me
up no damn it so how do I take it
back I think I forgot to answer oh while
but it's a yes it's a yes she said yes
yippe
is there an
entrance fight him with the tle okay so
it was kind of misleading first I
thought oh yeah yeah let's fight him but
then like he kind of says
yo yo time to get the water back so kind
of misleading you
know how do we fight him with the tackle
small tackle versus big
tackle I think I know
how but I can't move like
this wait I can reach endless height
like this
no oh no oh oh no wait this is what
happens to Taco that just when they're
out of water oh my God terrifying okay
so not endless but we can kind of do
something with
that
right get a I'm trying I'm
trying and H
[Music]
no why' you have to land
there did I get at least a little bit I
think maybe
uh maybe a little bit oh [\h__\h] no
no okay this is not good this boss fight
I don't know if I'm doing it completely
wrong but it's not as intuitive
or like
easy he moved around so much there we go
finally finally
finally boing boing
boing nice shiny bald head wow oh yeah
get those hearts oh Hallelujah
[Music]
got now you're head is shiny now oh wait
do I just um change back to Mario once
I'm at the top him and then ground to
probably well I got to catch up with him
though he's really [\h__\h]
fast how he so
fad okay here we
go no no no ah what so quickly Out of
Water you skipping like
pink
that was it
yeah okay I need a new one I need a new
one just got to do that several times
now I guess oh what the [\h__\h] are you
shooting now can I send it back wait
I'll try to send it back maybe that's
what he wants let's give it a
try wait was it too late was I too late
oh now he s something else okay
uh I need I need a tacos to reach the
top there's
one wait for me come over
here no I need to
F don't you dare attack me we're
fighting this fight
together we're all in this together oh
there's another heart here let's go get
it
[Music]
w
chill m
[Music]
where are you
going I hate this fight this is my least
favorite fight and there we go what
going on no I have to redo the whole
thing ah come
[Music]
on other boss fights easy this this one
is like
what maybe it's just not my
thing I'm going to lose I'm going to
lose water I'm go
down stop
[Music]
moving oh my
God
oh
please
no this boss is really annoying thank
you I'm I'm glad I'm not the only one oh
my did he drop any hearts again no
you don't have to be I can be Taco the
whole time okay but even then he's hard
to reach
man so I can just hit him with more
water even though he's already
[Music]
clean still
annoying
look at my
[Music]
CS no
no nice thank you round
three
wa where are you
[Music]
going where
he there he
is he
fast
oh he
stop
[Music]
no and then it's kind of hard to see
from from the top point of
view when you're really above him
sometimes it's a
bit mising can you stop ah and he turns
like this cuz he looks at
me okay okay maybe now y yep y y y y y
yep yep yeah no you little
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
damn what does this teach
us size can be a
problem figure is not always
better hey we can apply this to boobies
too
okay just saying and the butt too I
don't know what you're thinking of first
of all but we can apply this to anything
boobies
butts
um don't know don't
know brutal kill booies yes I'm talking
about 8
Z8
135 the secret code oh wow wait this
looks really awesome
now yeah she sick even with a rainbow my
goodness what a pretty sunset and it's
so nice that the fountains and the spark
what wait who the hell said I would like
this
area before we were
choosing did you just say that because
of the multis or did you really think I
would enjoy this because the boss
sucked and but I guess it was good to
tangent about this and that because I
easily got distracted to my tangent
towards my tangent not towards the
game I didn't say
[Music]
nothing it's like sunshine no well I
guess it doesn't seem like Bowser in
this Kingdom anymore of course he's not
so we head to the next yeah but how
about we head to the next next because
so far every time we head to the next
one he's not there anymore what if we go
one step ahead of
him H I ever thought about that but I
guess we can't go that far without the
moons we can't cover that much
distance okay well done I'm done with
this area more or
less you're actually gen I know I
know snow kingdom is a good one it
better
be I'm so
hungry let me eat the second piece of
no I dropped the chocolate don't worry
it's
packaged it is packaged I just have to
pick it up and rolled
away was like juggling
it fumbling dropping from one hand to
another flip flop flip flop flip
flop floor chocolate no no no no no no
it's
packaged
[Music]
maon TV what now we can get to the snow
Kingdom watch out
Bowser I'm have a feeling we won't meet
him there
[Music]
either bye-bye
moldes going skiing
[Music]
again 1080 snowboarding
TT has due
time he wants to make a toast using this
parkour oh wow he's thinking of
everything what would he want next like
an ice sculpture because like I guess
some do some weddings have ice
sculptures like the really fancy
ones maybe that's what he's going
[Music]
for ah no he wants cake Frost frosted
cake I guess that's some sort of
frosting Sharia instead of siaria cuz
they're shivering it's
varia my God
Nintendo my God that is the
worst the worst pun
name I have ever heard for anything
ever shivering in
siia Shia
wow oh it's not Siberia Siberia I guess
in
English I've heard worse not with me
right wait this is like a lethal
company the weather is
terrible
it's too chocolatey I want some
cookie or even something not sweet man I
want a sandwich I didn't make a sandwich
before Super Chat
reading I hear Christmas bells what the
[\h__\h] W wa oh
okay hey yo we have to warm that up
eventually
so lethal company oh yeah
was fun but don't worry guys I'm I'm not
planning on playing it much more than
once because it's it's repetitive it's
fun but it was really
repetitive um
so the reason why I'm playing it one
more time is because already kind of
decided to have um a myth collab next
week I don't know how many people we're
going to be but there will be a myth
collab next week and it's going to be
lethal
company I know that without mods you can
only play it with four
people but if we end up not being
complete then that's fine I guess if we
are
complete then one person will just like
sit out I guess each round I don't know
I don't know how we're going to do
that
but can't get mod
crims I don't know if anybody started
the process
of getting them I'm not
sure I certainly
didn't where the [\h__\h] am I going it's
hard to see
d there we
[Music]
go follow the pr B shout
casting I mean I don't mind just
watching but yeah this is the problem
really this is why I think Advent is has
this Advantage cuz so many
games you can only play with four people
and I mean yeah they're five but they
only play games with like four most of
the time
anyway so good like Generations should
just always be po
people from the GTO in my
opinion I love cleaning up the snow here
I love
it should we jump down
see want on noow I mean I see a
hole wait the checkpoint have I
activated
yeah
okay claim one of the my as your
personal
fuaa Adan finally was so good thank you
so much oh
my wa cute wait cute oh cute what are
you wait what are they they're cute show
me your face you look like a like a
n but n is in water and with not not
feet but I
think
flaps seals yeah not a seal are you
n winter
seal so cute welcome
to oh those money things give me no I'm
going to it's going to disar no
[Music]
[\h__\h] the music is
cute I've never seen that thing in the
circle there before I
think I mean I don't know if I'll be
going back there think I said I might be
going back to all these places
eventually I I don't want
[Music]
to that monster ruined everything no
cake and no racing no fun for Sven oh
wait I don't have enough money yet at
all there was not really anything to
collect unless you have cheap stuff
they're so
big
whoa oh cute what
oh I'll get the hood for
now maybe one is enough even oh [\h__\h] Dam
it what else do we have do we have like
what you're wearing I want to wear what
you're wearing I I'll have what you
have what there's a Madding cosplay in
here no why is that here here or was
that in the beach shop actually
originally probably it
was no wait not done looks kind of cute
only the hood alone can't this be warm
[Music]
enough like this this kind of fits
actually
look that must no no no I must have
missed something
here no
huh nothing
new I'll buy
this should be fine at least from the
look yeah looks warm enough yeah it
does on the way
no I don't want box of
shorts and must for her must keep your
face nice until
I don't know guys does
it I guess it kind of might help a
little bit depending on how thick your
beard is and how covering it
is I missed a race course anything s an
ER raser with without a race
course what oh you like a camera here
set up that's Bowser ship I frosted
Frost frosted cake is
gone your price is
gone now this boun his face here the
[\h__\h] ra keeps my heart warm please open
the door oh what
a bring p on back F please oh man those
poor seals I have to help
them and never I shave and feel I feel
cold air on my
face wow speaking of cold air
what the hell is
that you
think you could deceive me I see you oh
it's just
money all
[Music]
right y oh you little [\h__\h] you
bastard wait how do
I can I not do anything about
him oh there we go there it has a
mustache now look so
stupid oh why to Exhale
well no need anymore all the enemies are
gone
oh wait
mistake
um why would I do
that I can just jump over it
right e maybe for the coin I
guess ow okay here I need
him blowy Joey that's his name that's
this character's
name no way blowy
Joey no go
away oh I have to shoot away all
those mean
byebye
there's no way Nintendo really that name
an odd name to have okay so it's
probably incorrect okay wait can I since
he's not cornered anywhere oh he can go
around cuz yeah he has freedom of
movement wonderful
[Music]
wonderful oh we can get those over there
as well it's the only one I
think
thank you for your
services I happily accept this orange
[Music]
[Applause]
moon there's a beast Jerry you can check
names should I oh wait oh oh it it got
rid of one
[Music]
layer I checked this through what okay
like I don't
even you know I have the same feeling as
you guys like for you guys apparently it
sounds really like yab or
so I didn't even feel as critical about
it as you
guys but it's
real oh yeah right they don't have a
balancing issue
[\h__\h] they don't slip they are Slip
proof no [\h__\h]
way oh my God I couldn't even jump on
top of it I came out of
nowhere
M real m a moment
man if you want to kill
me I will not let
you you will become one with me G tie
baby or nothing
[\h__\h]
okay is this ah it only cracks when
you're under
it unbelievable that's why I fell for it
I was like wow that's kind of random and
well timed I never saw that falling down
before
surely anybody who enters this world for
the first
time
gets stabbed in their top of their head
by that icle it's surely not only
me un unbelievably unbelievable why is
this
here why is that there what
for that one just I guess probably just
to make it difficult for me me to walk
through this one at least serves as a
[Music]
platform oh there's
more no why did I let me be hit why why
why I it making me nervous when they run
around like
that
o if they're all in will it break the
middle
ice
somehow no then why did I do it oh oh no
it is it is doing that okay
[Music]
okay I don't need them anymore right
awesome yeah that area was pretty
[Music]
cool so creepy how Mario possesses yeah
it's a little bit creepy you
know pretty cool you
[Music]
say actually you know with the with the
whole family and iPad and stuff like
that
topic I wanted to
segue into what are you
saying oh okay I wanted to segue into my
other uh topic that I have written up
there I just quickly want to touch on
this subject and say family YouTube
channels
suck and I'm not just saying this uh in
regards to
recent uh a recent one where that was in
the news
everywhere
no I have I have
um seen
some content not directly I I watch you
through a YouTuber that I kind of like
at the moment who yeah I guess he does
some react stuff and he reacts to he
reacted like several times to some
family YouTubers so I watched those and
oh my God but he makes fun of them
perfectly but
um it's it's kind of insane it made me
realize how insane Family YouTube
channels are and how unethical because
they make millions because of their
children then they Flex all that wealth
in their in their videos which are
originally supposed to be
like aimed towards younger audience
what's the younger audience going to do
with content like flexing your new 10
million mansion what and your new five
Ferraris what and what is a child going
to learn from that nothing good it's
going to get an image that all that's
important in life is money and that with
YouTube You're Going to make that money
so let's become a YouTuber
haha yeah yeah especially not only the
kids now now I was talking about the
kids the audience that is watching
but what about the kids in the
family that are constantly being
documented talking to a camera like
everything is like exaggerated and oh my
God most of the time they do like some
stupid ass pranks that are either staged
or just not funny at all absolutely
ridiculous pranks so to
say oh my
God it's it's terrifying how these kidss
are being raised I just want to say that
that's that's so sad and the parents do
it because they know it's making them a
[\h__\h] ton of
money but that's not a normal
environment to be raised in like first
of all the the extremely wealthy
environment is like a weird environment
to be raised in and
also like those YouTube videos and like
what kind of values are they are they
learning here like what the hell is it's
it's exploitive yes it's
unethical it's the worst side of YouTube
like they want to make you think that
it's so wholesome because it's like
videos about families and their kids and
all
that but it's really just the parents
controlling everything and and being
money
hungry they're just doing it for the
clicks and the views and that's kind of
like why I was doing this parody in the
beginning of the stream because that's
exactly how how they talk in those
videos
too and YouTube and ads are like pushing
those videos extremely because they're
familyfriendly so to say and they're
safe to advertise on but
damn I would say it's the opposite of
safe to advertise on if you really think
about
it and then certain Family YouTube
channels they're like so Su sucessful
they
like they they make videos about moving
from10 million mansion Villa to the next
one which is now $15 million worth of
whatever like oh my God what how is this
even a Family Channel and and then like
oh there was one that the that YouTuber
was like making fun of where like the
Dad gives his son who's like I don't
know 12 or so a challenge to play
fortnite for every kill he gets $100 up
to
$1,000 and and then they're all dressed
in like Gucci and fendy and all that
[\h__\h] oh my
God
can't terrible I'm not surprised I'm not
watching that kind of content because
it's
just I don't know why people watch it
like
when people flaunt their wealth like
that I hope I will never end up doing
that like tell me guys when I like you
know some it's it's it's I think
I H yeah mostly I I think I'm I'm safe
with
that sometimes maybe I'm like very proud
so like once I've mentioned like shoes I
got before but generally even for me
looking at that [\h__\h] it doesn't feel
good it doesn't feel fair if feels like
[\h__\h] so tell me if I ever start like
flaunting my wealth like
that
please I
mean yeah it's just
disgusting tell me if I do it because
then I probably don't realize and and I
need to be brought back down to
earth
I mean the Mal Dives well yeah I mean
well but that's not comparable to like a
$10 million house or so I
mean okay let me enjoy the moldes at
least I have to enjoy the moldes it's
for Content wait [\h__\h] wait that's like
pretty much no but it's not the same
thing it's similar you could say you
could make a connection there but it's
not the same
thing it's
no but it's also for my own you know and
uh and like we're making we're making
okay we're making we're making great
memories there and and and it's it's
nothing like those Family Channel videos
okay it's nothing like that I'm not
showing you like you know stupid ass
pranks that are unethical and like like
terrifying me dropping a a a baby puppet
from the third floor
to shock my wife that I just dropped our
newborn toddler or something like that
and then see her reaction and then be
like haha it was just a puppet like I
don't do that so like you
know yeah that's a common Family Channel
prank one of
many just a prank
bro anyway why are you guys here now not
not
Bowser I what's am I done with you guys
I only fought you wait why are the
bosses repeating
now no no what I can't jump over them
you little [\h__\h] no
no wait
what wait wait what wait what oh wait I
have to shoot the hats
[Music]
huh wait is this the
beginning of
they did not set me back to the
beginning no no no they did not oh no
they
didn't oh
no oh okay but we're pretty fast up
there never
mind you
guys
it felt longer cuz I was talking so much
and going around the corner okay what
are we doing ah
okay nice okay easy I forgot what to do
about the Hat
originally
sorry what do I do about this part again
oh maybe just escape cuz he stopped on
his
own oh
oh oh oh while slippering slippery
slop that's pretty
[Music]
skillful okay I'll just keep on ignoring
that part hoping that it's not important
oh
[\h__\h]
no shootting again
okay there we go I got one oh m m oh no
no
no got okay I got one oh wait oh no no
no no no no no no no
no might be a hard in one of the Rocks
really
[\h__\h] oh so slippery
slop
oh wait that works
too I didn't
realize
I'm
okay very dangerous area must
say need some safety
measures a heart M I would have needed
an extra heart heart a heart container
one might
say
okay ah wait what
how wait why did I I thought you just
have to like kind of no what the [\h__\h]
no what why can I not land on them
[Music]
anymore
there's no heart in there are you
[\h__\h] kidding
[Music]
me one more guys one more one more oh my
God
Panic that was right in front of me that
could have ended really
badlya
POA action baby wait my
coins that was pure
[Music]
action
100 mb3 of Windows
C just no oh it's going down to 88 85
what's going to happen what's going to
happen it's going to reset right 78 75
69 oh it went back to one
GP
now I
finally saw it with my own
[Music]
eyes are we
done wait still
lay which one did I which one did I not
do only one bar to go this one the one
is no wait H that one's black that one's
bright what does that mean what what
about the
others right okay so the black one is
the one I didn't do
yet you can buy a full outfit yeah but
do I even need
it I think I look perfectly fine
[Music]
now I've been
here and I got the
Moon
[Music]
oh the SS blocked the ones I completed
okay so it wasn't about the
color so I did that
one ah okay okay this is the only
[Music]
one oh
okay what the
what
wait I can let it pick me up but I
should
quickly no wait okay wait let me do that
again come
on y okay that's enough
[Music]
Y no
get off
there okay one more is probably
there y there it is that was fast
easy coins coins coins coins coins coins
and then I guess I need them to bring me
up
oh no bring me here bring me
there here here here
please try to bite
me ah I only got one
no he was so ready for it ah
no okay whatever I didn't want them I
want I don't want them anymore I'm over
it
very interesting enemies I must say the
gimmicks in this game are really really
cool I have to give that to
them
y Munch Munch Munch Munch
Towers I see Munch
Towers yay we help them we saved them I
really like their home
so so nice and cozy
intimate very sweet gives me a sense of
community are we racing now
yeah let's go oh let
[Music]
go are we racing on our but please say
yeah no we're not just that part huh
oh are you the
king about one more racer I think that
should be me look at that w i just your
racing
clothes C wait it might actually be
seals it is
seals how about the clothes they look
more like seals well they're so
fuzzy fluffy winter seals y fun
[Music]
do
RGB
wow they have little feet so cute this
is the way to go back uhhuh okay we need
one more R oh wait oh there's so
many oh time you bounc to the moment you
make contact with the ground what are
you saying you go faster through curves
if you bound
what I just want to look at how cute
you're sitting there
honestly
oh oh another wow that's a huge course
do I have to
roll wait I there we
go I wonder if we're all just going to
roll all right let me in can I do it
with these clothes
[Music]
do sit down why it's taking so long
changing
[Music]
Mo are they dead am I replacing
them snow so so
[Music]
snow W oh he's scared and I'll help him
I'll be like I don't you don't have to
do it but am I going to pretend to be
him cuz I don't know I'm if I can fill
out his clothes and all
that might not be convincing we have to
do it a different way look he's terrify
what is so
cute race oh my God that sounds
terrifying race I don't want to the
other Racers are too serious I don't
stand a
chance if someone else wanted to race
they would be welcome to take my
place that sounds kind of like
him all right e this me then seems like
we're just going to walk out here and
that counts as me being
it wait
just wait
local news kaha discovers a way to jump
higher I I I thought I discovered that
in the water and I thought you could do
it only in the
water
and
wow so is that an
uppercut
[Music]
yay oh oh we just come out here again
interesting
oh oh I have to possess
him
Oh I thought I was just going to tell
him I'm going to be the
one
oh all right there was that feature in
the
game [\h__\h] I'm
cute wait I'm
[Music]
rolling I have to be the
N what I'm ready sorry to keep you
waiting I'm totally
myself this hat yeah that's I just
something I I found on Amazon that it
looked really cool so I wanted to give
it a try today for good luck don't worry
about it let me go I'm ready
wait there you
go finally now I can start a
race
FR be mulon oh that's
great wait his voice is more like this
it's been a while since we race so we'll
start with some
tring
okay that's exactly what I need what's
bounce Oh you mean
bounce to me that's a
bounce
oh but um I don't know does that really
make me
faster I guess the curves are easier
that way maybe gives me a little bit of
a boost I
suppose are we
ready are we really this kind of makes
me skip
them
yum like
rebound bounding is required to win
should I just bounce like
everywhere but sometimes there's these
special BS where I Sparkle so I'm doing
something right
[Music]
there well okay he says I'm ready let's
see let's see if I
am I remember having trouble this I
might have troubl
too perfect timing if you can chain the
bounc you go really fast
[Music]
o can I bounce on them can I sabotaged
them wo wo wo wao wao no wait now
they're so far do I have to
win why do I have to win can I not just
be hard or so I'm happy being third
personally
oh wao I don't know how it makes me
faster I'm just losing speed here
actually we're bouncing so
high
yo those two dudes are so
fast that's totally [\h__\h] up there just
how
what maybe not bouncing all the
time the third one oh they they made a
mistake oh
oh
what
second
second I don't remember those advices
they
gave
wait
what' you say you go faster for Curves
if you bounce time your bounce to the
moment well this is not really like
helpful what I was going
anyway wasn't a bad run better than
before no no
[Music]
go we'll see we'll
[Applause]
see
just want to roll normally
there not
good
why was he able to do
that
[Music]
[Applause]
no o
o okay a
out the control bounce so close so close
oh I'm first I'm momentarily first
y y it was already already the third
round oh
oh oh this is better than Mario
Kart this they should make a whole game
out of
this
I I didn't even realize I was already in
the third round that went so fast I was
so
focused no not cuz I wanted it because
it's like I the mechanics are
interesting you know you could do all
kinds of courses maybe even have some um
items there's a multiplayer Kirby game
is the kiry game like
this
y
yeah maybe it's a Mario Party mini game
even you played the Kirby game it it
didn't feel that's the one you mean I
thought you meant the older Kirby maybe
but it didn't quite feel like this it
had different
feeling from the bounces on
Alla you were like a super sonic
snowman cat hair
well thank you Sonic got to go
[Music]
fast keep bouncing oh
reveal uh are they watching like I just
revealed myself in front of everybody
here
um uh
uh they don't say anything we just we
just saw straight just go straight
back do we have they said 10 moons right
one oh we're missing one
okay
no can I go into the water cuz the sun's
out so it's not that cold
anymore oh oh oh a little bit oh God oh
God oh God oh God become fish
quickly is there something interesting
here he's got lights his eyes are the
lights um can I attack it
no
wo wo
y I'm
[Applause]
pengin no don't fly away no they hate
me what did I what did Mario ever do to
them I have no idea why they would react
like
that
they fly Penguins can't fly yeah right
not like
that oh hi toad sorry I was helping you
though do I going to start for that
itold I had to find some shelter but I
got bu it thank you so much myun my life
[Music]
savior that was another really heroic
thing okay now I would have enough
but I'll do a I got a bit more a bit
more just a bit a little bit a bit
tiny but I think this might be my last
World for
today then we'll read some super
chats and then I'll go cook I really
have to cook I keep on saying these days
I have to cook after the stream and then
after the stream and I'm like either too
like mentally
exhausted or too tired
or it's already to so late and I have to
get
up so I always end up like not doing it
but today I have to because I have like
nothing really in my freezer
anymore so I'm
forced
ah this feels like a sunshine
[Music]
level wait what
on I thought like oh does it
automatically activated when I run into
it
no it does
[Music]
not so do I shoot my head
hat
um maybe you can't really ah do it with
such a flowy flow oh oh oh
no okay you can kind of do it got to
shoot it early
enough I want to see I'm play it did she
did she ever finish Odyssey cuz like she
played it yeah but did she finish
it oh
nice y yeah I missed that but oh
[\h__\h] yeah
[Music]
oh the I got it
wo that was
difficult
[Music]
aren't you supposed to leave here I
can't go there on my own and there's no
more flowers here so I guess I
[Music]
leave maybe if you keep going after the
first
moon well I do not atttend on doing
that
nut uh that's not
good well I don't even know where I
would bring that
one I don't even
know let me
go
here okay I can try to get it out of the
water I'll
try was somewhere here I think was
it it's back here oh that's good it
respawned that's
good carefully hold the
nut oh I can even swim over it I I don't
know why why I think I have to be so
careful with it I can do pretty much
anything with it right here we
go time no it's my second stream my
second stream of Super Mario
aam where are we going I am the princess
of um what was
it what is this again Pap also in RPG
they also show up oh what is this
music
[Music]
remix oh I love
this
yo cute I like this cute
level uh bit hard to tell how high I am
but
[Music]
whatever hard to see anything really
it's [\h__\h] white as
[Music]
[\h__\h]
what
what was that on purpose
[Music]
I have to bring the nut
again I have to go
[Music]
higher it was going so well okay then at
least we'll get to hear more of the
music
even that came
back the
court I'm on the
top let's go
again
[Music]
no no no oh I me back oh okay
okay I will not try to care so much
about
the coins anymore I already got a lot of
them right so okay
[Music]
here okay okay okay I'm oh I didn't see
this whole
[Music]
section I totally missed that and here's
the
Moon
Yahoo can we listen to that soundtrack
forever
please great save
yeah I like that Moon I'm glad I stayed
and didn't immediately
leave should we leave now
[Music]
though look at those I want to go up
there look at the Penguins how do I get
there I need to somehow I need to be
able to fly or ye myself up
there can I fly with you give me my head
back can I go higher or stay only on the
same
level yeah okay only on the same
level oh is it like a painting
thing when I was playing off screen I
in the Water World I I found the
painting that where the guy was fishing
the guy the whatever the guy on the on
the cloud was
painting and he was and no he was
fishing I mean he was fishing and they
were like Shadows of of fishies in the
water and I was trying to like control
him and fish something but it just
didn't work I think I was doing
something wrong I wanted to ask you guys
about it I was trying to fish the fish
and I was trying to fish the painting
and then did react to the painting oh
but I could fish I was really
confused that's super
finicky really
oh
o
[\h__\h] made it let's
sprakle
okay there's another one
here what this
[Music]
one oh CL
climb oh
climb
what
no
no help
no I I just had problems with the
positioning I can do it I can do it I
can do it I can do it I can do it
woo the wrong
way
why what are you
doing
I guess that works like going to the top
and then flipping that wasn't really the
original plan that's why I was kind of
confused
there why would you not hold on to it
no sweet
wait no wa the see where when I get
there
like I wish he would flip
backwards oh
no let's do it again I do it again oh
yeah
okay
obviously not going to work not going to
happen I could start probably a little
bit more further ahead of
him no
[\h__\h] to save some time too but it's
[Music]
like
the time is so tired oh my God
wait
wait time is so I have to turn around
there hey can you not is there a
different bottom combination to like cuz
it says uh jump forward is there also
one to jump
backward going the you can flip back
flip up the side you can jump a yeah
okay maybe before reaching the top then
okay okay
okay don't jump from the top okay okay
okay
okay one more
bastard
no
no I still saw like what pixel of it oh
I'm so close I'm so close
though
no no no no I didn't want to go to the
top it's just too
fast no I'm too
late oh my oh my God I almost at
[Music]
it
positioning oh Mama
Mia Mama Mia that was incredible
incredibly tight on time attack on tight
tight on
time oh my
God but I enjoyed it
severely I shall now go to my
Odyssey and I
will safe before I I don't even I'm not
even going to give it the
moons I'm just going to save and we're
going to give it the moons at the
beginning of the next uh Odyssey stream
I'm planning one for next week and then
hopefully we can finish it do you guys
think I can finish it next
week oh is it much
longer if I do one more stream can I
finish
it
yeah yay okay good good good good good
good good wonderful oh
we WEA B swim
I think one more should do it I hope so
I hope so no not two no I don't have
time for
two me next year yeah yeah oh my God
next year what next week is next year
same thing though same
thing um would you guys mind if I
quickly make myself like one slice of
bread sandwich just one slice of bread
cold cut cucumbers and uh one one layer
of
lettuce just so I can read super chats
more uh without wanting to end the
stream okay and also my lips are so
[\h__\h] chapped let me find my
ChapStick and while I'm at it I'll go to
the adle meeting I guess so we all take
a little break to grab food and an idem
meeting or whatever maybe and then I'll
see you in the office perhaps I shall
use my Super Chat inter Mission
screen so thank you for watching so far
if you don't want to stay for the Super
Chat reading uh thank you for watching
see you next time uh tomorrow is the
delayed uh outfit
designs I'm so excited for it so excited
for it finally finally maybe I'll still
make some more changes maybe maybe maybe
maybe and and
[Music]
yeah and um I'll see you then and but
yeah you can say for the Super Chat
readings because we don't this is the
last Super the last superat rating of
the Year
[Music]
2023 do I look like
him oh yeah oh yeah the countdown live
is on
Sunday
yah okay so
to okay see you in the little
bedy no no no no no no no here is there
music here ah ah okay it's astrophic
okay
[Music]
switch
tell me I can hear it
[Music]
[Applause]
I will keep on fighting
[Music]
till
[Applause]
[Music]
break
totin they keep pushing and ping me out
AR if
I me in
the you tell me where I need to
[Music]
[Applause]
go
[Music]
for the
ne
[Music]
he
fore not
[Music]
[Applause]
wow what do does anybody know what that
soundtrack was called the one that I was
like I want to listen to this forever
the one in in in the Cloudy
game nobody knows right
probably bonus level Super Mario World
yeah but it's like I mean a special
remix of it maybe if I type in Super
Mario World
odyy a oh
above the clouds this
one
yeah sorry I was loud
first that's the one
right
[Applause]
yeah we are going to listen to this
while we're reading all the super chats
and when we get sick of this soundtrack
then we're going to listen to the other
one
[Music]
too now let me while you listen to this
I will eat my
[Music]
sandwich almost dropped the Cucumbers
not the
[Music]
Cucumbers like checking for cat hairs on
my
[Music]
hands oh thank you Aus okay wait I have
cat hair is on my lips from the
Chapstick okay whatever I'll commit to
[Music]
it don't stop I'm blooping
it
[Music]
hey
yum yum
yummy did you guys get something to
snack
too if yes what is it
[Music]
no R the
dryer protein
b a apple
[Music]
Denis you're getting popcorn in a bit
right then my Super Chat reading starts
what are you trying to tell me
huh
I'm getting the popcorn cuz you're so
excited for the Super Chat
[Music]
reading
h
m white chocolate
[Music]
yum hey can you really get sick of
this I'll show the chat once I'm done
eating I got my hands
full
mhm it's imp
[Music]
posable on a sandwich guys do you prefer
cucumbers or
tomatoes I would say it could depend on
the sandwich like if it's a madella one
or um what's it called mozzarella then
it should be
tomato but anything else I feel like
could be both like either of
them
tomato tomato
[Music]
tomato most people say tomato
wow I've been enjoying cucumbers
[Music]
recently kind of sick on tomatoes
now oh yeah it's so funny how some
people really have a problem with raw
Tomatoes actually narissa and me talked
about how actually just yesterday I
think was yesterday feels like just
yesterday we talked about her food
preferences cuz she say she doesn't like
chicken
right but she also doesn't like
fish I think neither raw or cooked she
has a lot more I think she has a lot
more food pickiness than me guys she
said she will eat it though like chicken
or so but she doesn't really like it
we'll see we'll see how it goes
[Music]
well Le said I'm not the only picky
one then I don't have to feel weird
about it picky
[Music]
really yeah she still gives it a try I I
will not
I'm a strict picky
[Music]
eater they don't do
Burgers why there's all kinds of
burgers what's their problem what do
they not like about Burgers there's all
kinds of burgers you can't discriminate
all of
them they don't like pizza wait I feel
like I heard about
that but there's also a [\h__\h] of pizza
what's the problem with pizza they I
think they just haven't had real good
Italian pizza maybe if they had real
good OG Italian pizza then they might
change their
mind I don't care for cheese there's
cheeseless Pizza I mean it's not I
wouldn't recommend it
but they don't put any sauce on meat
either wait what wait what what do you
mean like they eat a steak like I mean
okay a really good steak can be great
without sauce but what about chicken
like you you have chicken without
anything that's
[Music]
like what do they eat I need to find
out what what is like their one week
meal
plan I'm actually curious about that
maybe I wonder what they currently do
about their food
because Noti
this I think this could be either a time
or a laziness issue
but a
lot a lot of whole life members from all
branches rely a lot on delivery foods
right not even food only even
drinks even coffee they get delivered I
stopped doing that very early on I I did
that for a while when I was in Japan
especially but I've stopped doing that
for a long time now if anything if I if
I'm lazy I eat like some of my frozen
foods or whatever but I'm I stopped
doing the delivery [\h__\h] because of the
variety the lack of variety and the
money but
anyway it's either depending on the
person I think it's either a laziness
issue and I also often I'm lazy so not
blaming them or
uh a Time issue but like formal goal I
wonder if they even have time to cook do
they say what they
do do they even have time to cook like
with how much they stream I think they
could use the time excuse no time to
cook they take turns oh oh that's so
nice having someone to take turns with a
man fulla Cooks who want to make soup
what soup every day or what what the
[\h__\h] oh my God I need I need them
to I can I ask them to document their
food for a week and then present it to
me maybe even on a stream cuz I want to
criticize them I'm worried about them
I'm worried about them now that I hear
all these issues with
food if they already really picky and
then now they have the issue with having
no time to cook how much
more are they going to like are they
just going to are they just eating soup
only that's what it sounds like right
right
now that sounds like it like right
[Music]
now n you kid just live on super
nut oh my
[Music]
God
no you need more more nutrients more
variety in
[Music]
food I'll cook for
them I mean I don't know actually on the
topic
of my friends are coming um to hang out
with me for New
Year's and they were like okay what are
we going to eat and I'm like oh I don't
know I didn't think about that maybe can
just order pizza and they we're like oh
that's lame so I'm like okay
um I don't know maybe I can try to cook
something but no never mind I don't
think I have the confidence to cook for
so many people I've only ever cooked for
myself so far yeah I don't when have I
ever cooked for like two people
even I don't
know so I said no let's not do that so
we're just doing like ret you you know
have a little Reet Grill I we I think
it's pretty common I've done it several
times for New Year's or or Christmas
just ret it's
easy everybody just throws together what
they want but I have to buy a [\h__\h] ton
of things tomorrow cuz for Reet you have
to buy like five
sauces two or three different types of
meat bacon cheese [\h__\h] ton of cheese
some uh kind of variety of veggies
salad
maybe so many things I have to buy so
many things tomorrow before the
stream by the cheese wheel no no no no
cheese wheel just like there's ret
cheese um already even I think I saw it
in in Cut version already and you just
put it on the little shovel and then you
put it inside into the grill underneath
there's like a grill on top and the oven
below more or less
normally my
usual my usual
recet
constellation
is what did I put together
always some kind of
meat I don't know
what it's a little loud okay
um now it's too
quiet okay and
then
corn ah potato potato not even I'm not
even going to like usually I don't even
put that much meat the main the main
thing that I would bake under the grill
is Big Slice of one or two big slices of
potatoes some corn maybe um bell peppers
strips
Stripes um and then maybe already the
cheese but also sometimes I like I like
to put in silon which is what what is
that again again in English those little
round tiny um pickled um
onions that are a little bit sour
whoop oh yeah I need to buy potatoes
maybe there's a Rec collect uh shopping
list
online yeah pearl onions pearl onions I
love those in ret or anytime really but
they're good for
[Music]
ret oh oh yeah onions onions
mhm
what
what what do you mean
what orange
[Music]
cinnamon
what you mean as a drink or
like you mean orange
cinnamon I'm still eating Lord
e I'm still
eating orange cinnamon with the cheese
you're going to you you bake it like
together what that's not what you mean
right what the
[Music]
hell I no multitask you guys always tell
me to chill and take my time and eat and
in peace now I'm doing that so that I
don't have have to rush the Super Chat
reading to eat
after I'm doing it for
you I'm almost done
though it's like two more bites or
[Music]
so
l
[Music]
I love
salami I [\h__\h] love
salami I'm
WR
[Music]
y
[Laughter]
[Music]
yon this song is so much fun let's go
let's go repeat all
time I can get sick of
it
[Music]
I we are going to read the super chats
we are going to read the super chats
yeah yeah we are going to read the Super
Chat time super time this yo yo
[Music]
yo hey hey hey
hey
[Music]
streaming uh amus oh that's not so far
back my thumbnail is here there we
go
Amo Advent
calendar is Wawa the Santa Claus of
whole life
[Music]
English yes I am yes yes I
am why are the Red Nose yeah I have a
red nose
there that was there's this Christmas
song R love that's red nose strer D that
song was one of my favorite songs when I
was
younger
santaw what was it I was attempting to
sing it in German again but I forgot
rudol reer that sounds stupid
r r rudol
does
does Rolf
[Music]
does
does that that doesn't sound like what I
remember
I got rid of wow who did it was it one
of you
guys that was fast thank you so much I'm
sorry to like I don't know I don't I
don't want to take like creative freedom
with
people but that's just something I
can't keep
[Music]
there thank
you
thank you thank you for
[Music]
understanding yeah it was something that
should have been edited out because it
doesn't represent exactly I don't think
it represents me at all like when did I
have a joke about that I don't know
maybe I was maybe I joked about
something and it was misinterpreted
but that's play
here but was he really
small wasn't he normal sized why would
it be Rudolph the small reindeer in
German to be small compared to others
really was small it was just
red
I don't I don't remember it like that
well whatever let's read the super chats
take a 47 D take
[Music]
monkey thank you Merry Christmas GD D
Jackson f d I don't know why I do the
things I
do but I
actually I mean I was fairly awake for
amus it hit me right after
though it was fun though and then yeah
wasn't this
when after Among Us I think I was really
tired and then I talked to narissa and
then I stayed up like like until 10:00
a.m. because me and narissa had a really
deep
talk I couldn't say sorry narissa I have
to sleep I couldn't say
it I couldn't do it sometimes you
sacrifice yourself like that you have
[Music]
to and it was it was worth it it was
fine I I I I don't mind I mean it's
okay yeah she's my wife she's my wife
you're telling me you wouldn't stay up
late for your
wife aka me you better you
better space waterful thank you for the
rainbow thank you for USANA A lot
happened this year yeah Frey showcase
yeah that was in the beginning of the
year that feels ages ago already free
concerts new outfit yeah free wait free
concerts you mean the Ian one the summer
one and the big one for
Fest
new outfit your first album uh your 3D
life and so many streams and more yeah
my my new outfit this year everybody
[\h__\h] loved it that was
good you did so much and you worked your
butt off every day performed so much
great music and Cho and beat a lot of
games I did you did so much for us
you're the best kamhi that could be for
me always so sweet nice understanding
and kind a True Heart of
Gold sorry you try eat St entertain us
you enjoy our company and appreciate us
so much that it's obvious oh I'm I'm
happy to hear
that um always genuine and honest all of
that makes a chimpin feel like they
matter yes you do you do the love you
give each of us is the greatest gift you
made my year so much better some of my
best memories were with
you that's sh for that you're truly the
best I love you so much K you're the
most important person outside of my
family to me oh oh oh man I said before
you help me better My Life by motivating
and cheering me up Ah that's one thing I
said like what you're telling me now is
basically one thing I
mentioned to um in the in the collab
stream of G Maki
S as a comment
to um what was the question anyway it
was I think something like what are some
special moments or so in your career or
something that something that's like
just special to you and I said like some
some people come up to me and they say I
have this huge influence on them and and
and that I help them improve their life
or whatever and I'm like w Really and
then more and more people tell me and I
guess it's got to be true like why would
they say it if it wasn't true I guess
shees but yeah realizing how much of a
positive influence I can be on people
makes me really really really honored
and happy and proud but also a little
bit
pressured I said before you had me
better on my life by motivating and
cheering me up son of my world you're
certainly a good waa this year right was
I a good timin though did a lot of [\h__\h]
took that break in Spring could have
done better take a take my first rainbow
as plant and exas gift no don't worry I
mean I mean I don't even remember that
break I mean I don't remember when you
guys were going on breaks I noticed when
you gone but when you're back then I
already forget it immediately so don't
worry about it uh you you went on a
break I don't remember
that don't even mention it didn't
happen don't worry about it
yeah I'm just happy that you're back and
that you feel better hopefully and you
know if you need a break then take the
break I would just hope that you come
back to me me
eventually yeah yes you asked it when I
came back what I asked
what oh if you were gone or what thank
you for the membership gift thank
you you are my break oh that is the
ideal way of handling it I guess D is
actually the best
H that's how it should
be yeah
nice so yeah thank you space wonderful
for the beautiful rainbow and for all
the sweet words it was quite a filed
packed exciting
year hopefully we can keep this up next
year I'm not sure like U about the
momentum and all that that and if I keep
up the excitement I I hope I can I hope
I can keep you guys entertained I'll try
my best um but let's just let's just
roll with it let's just go with the
flow thank you so much space
wonderful much love to you feeling leing
than and for nice
good
smoo
smoo sliding into the new
[Music]
year I will continue to Loop sleep
talking but I got to go oh thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank
you I appreciate
that I'll be here until the end thank
you you're always being you're always
entertaining W thank
you I don't know like
sometimes sometimes I gotta be normal
and chill every once in a while cuz I
can't be entertaining 24/7 can I I don't
know maybe I Am Naturally that would be
great
but sometimes there must be down times
sometimes just
sometimes one you little [\h__\h] you are on
my naughty list for this year
[Music]
100% this you're about to end yeah
you're probably going to be on the
naughty list for next year
too I don't sense any character
development
there b than for Empire than
for the pink
[Music]
CH it's nice spending my first Christmas
with po life I wish you all the best and
happy
holidays thank you
D your first Christmas oh your first
Christmas no life damn I wish I could
have like streamed more for you like
there were other Christmases where I
streamed
more especially the first one cuz I was
in Japan alone
H
but
yeah real life oh I did actually stream
on both days 24th and 25th
but
still and this year I'm not even giving
you guys a new year
stream I'm terrible but I'm giving you a
first of January stream okay
[Music]
I streamed quite plenty this month
yeah I think I did like this month I
definitely
uh achieved the
quota the waa
quota we got the live going true true
true true I'm there I'm
there so take it as a stream of mine not
really but yeah maybe I'll upload a
video maybe I want to keep all my videos
that I have for my break I got to upload
them but yeah kind of makes up for last
year when you were sick yeah last year
well I mean that was out of my hands I'm
I'm lucky I didn't get sick this year
good good good good good well yeah happy
holidays to you too
Tassimo right we were able to spend
these holidays together so I'm really
happy yay happy New Year to you Tassimo
thank you for the pink super
chat py random cusion thank you for the
red chat yeah what's that what's that
about what's the year for what's what's
that for was that was there context at
all
I don't remember but thank you so much
for the red super chat
yeah oh cuz I
won but it's a dot dot dot yeah and then
an exclamation mark that's kind of
mysterious I got sick this year for
Christmas oh damn it are you healthy
again are you on your way of B of
getting
better I hope so get well
soon
yeah thank you random Merry
Christmas g d for the pink Super Chat GG
thanks for organizing this coolab it was
so fun I was laughing and screaming so
loud thank you for making my Christmas
Eve so merry also this really was
already at the end of the stream huh
thank you um I I had I I mean I had fun
I had fun I had a lot of fun like I
think we all had a lot of fun so I'm
glad I organized
it I think um all our laughs were
genuine really enjoyed
it and I actually got imposter and I
absolutely messed it
up I did
not use it to my advantage
I think for now I'm always fine being
Crow mate
forever it was funny to witness really
really it's fun always complaining about
never becoming impostor but when I
actually get impostor it's like [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] it's fun to watch you panic thank
you create life is the way yeah yeah
let's stay crewmate
forever more imposter was quite
something oh thank you for the
membership thank you
[Music]
you fre mons only yeah you kind of
showed up
recently happy birthday oo
yesterday happy birthday they wanton and
never
go GG has become like the goto Fu
information
[Music]
Source are you coming to Korea
again I want to go this year this coming
year ch ch oh wait I I know the names
for I know the words for years this year
past year next year but I forgot it's
somewhere in my
brain I don't know when
exactly oh n
n
[Music]
but well I'm already like I already have
like plans for the first half of the
year so maybe in the in
[Music]
autumn
maybe Autumn is the best after summer
ends but I want to go to
Korean anime convention and you guys
only have like two big ones and I think
one is in the summer and one is the in
the winter
no soul s
popcorn oh popcorn 2024 is there a date
August
no
nope nope no no no no no
no what's the other one I mean if they
if they invite me as a guest and then I
will gladly participate from my
comfortable
home I I hope I wish because they didn't
invite me this
year um maybe for variety reasons not
getting the same person twice in a row
but maybe 2024 now that you skipped a
year you could invite me again
please ah no Korean summer for I did it
once I'm never doing it
again somehow Korean summer was worse
than Japanese summer
what oh miss
[Music]
you Super H
yeah
[Music]
is it worse than La summer 100 [\h__\h]
perc because of the
humidity Korea has hotter summer than
Africa I would believe
[Music]
it what I don't even remember La summer
that's how not bad it
was and now I remember dipping into the
pool with
cie and then the other girls were just
watching yeah me and cie were the only
on to use the
pool good at Amit just chilling on the
side what was Ena
doing what Wasa
doing
what was she doing
[Music]
drawing probably drawing like whenever
she had time yet she was like drawing
drawing drawing on her
iPad a man that that was a good time I
wonder if we can ever have that again
like myth together overseas or what
wherever we're going have that
again cuz this year we had last year we
had
La yeah last year we had
La this year we had early in the year we
had to
Showcase where like places where myth
would be together although even the
Showcase was well I mean not all of us
were in the same place it was basically
all but Cali but she was still like
there and we still like did some stuff
[Music]
together just need to make plans for it
well it's it's a thing though like I
mean we always had like a reason to do
stuff like this without a reason it's
kind of
difficult um so if there's like some
project or event or so then maybe it can
happen
no I don't
know I love how Bae was just there yeah
why was she
there why was she there why was why was
she
there why was she in
La why was she in
La good [\h__\h]
question
I don't even remember was she just
hanging out in
La anyway
[Music]
X
why she she mentioned she snuck into
[Music]
ax ah yeah is that where she met her M
Mama yeah yeah I
um I did not go certainly I did not go
didn't I leave I don't
know let me read the super
[Music]
chats and she sent your selfie she did
she
[Music]
did yeah she visited other friends too I
guess
yeah yeah I avoided
[Music]
it
um oh wait did I read yeah I
did g your name g c k is there an actual
reading of it I feel like I've asked you
[Music]
before you soon take for the seven soon
Cru soon you soon Merry Christmas
[Music]
you Cru Cru D thank you for the
pinky thanks for putting this event
together boss and for the rest of your
hard work this year so far this weekend
might just be the best gift this season
yet Merry Christmas PA W thank you I'm
happy to hear
that much joy joy to you all I hope I
hope I could bring
[Music]
joy is there never among no no not
anytime
[Music]
soon but yeah I'll try to organize um
Holo Yen events again in the
future I don't know what the next thing
would be and what the next timing would
be
but leave it to me leave it to
[Music]
me I still want to do
unbelievably with
Advent still planning on that actually I
wanted to do that really early and then
no time no time and so
after GTA and RP yeah that will happen
uh but probably also after my
break uh like I told them I'm not going
to be there until later and it seems
like the plan to start it up is later
anyway cuz they have to like figure
everything out like they will make a
server or something is that like a time
limit of the thing cuz I saw the
Japanese no wait yeah the Japanese side
like I I don't understand I I really
don't understand much
but like they did like a finale or
[Music]
something and now they're
done know what
that
what like in Rust yeah is it like in
Rust yeah the VCR server regular limited
time event
[Music]
time limited for logistic reasons yeah I
mean that's fine really but when it
starts uh I think we're doing
Iden
only and when it starts you can expect
me possibly like depending on how it
takes off within our
members um if it's if others are active
then I'll be active too and I'll be
playing it a
lot if not so active then I also will
not be as active maybe we'll see we'll
see but I think since it's the first
time we're doing we're we would do
that I think I would be yeah I I think
people would be very active
you yeah if it's ID there then uh more
people might be online while I'm online
too ha
[Music]
yay I think that's what the
the what they said was the
[Music]
plan in terms of Who's involved I think
that was it I mean I might be wrong
maybe I understood something wrong but I
think that was the
plan I'll have hopefully some partners
in crime like
way way you like the background music
I got to make use of it while I'm doing
a Nintendo related
stream where was I A A Merry Christmas
Fon Cruz thank you so
much can I can I say Fel navad is that
that's that's that's fitting right right
right
right or is it something else
f
right okay y have Spanish
pass
[Music]
okay
no point of
view
[Music]
o and merry PE thank you for the pinky
thanks for making another Christmas
[Music]
season it's worth it when you guys enjoy
it and when the other girls enjoy it
it's worth it
then yeah thank you so much Mary B Merry
Christmas to you too clone D Saloon d
space waterful d and EV
[Music]
D okay maybe we should change it is
there another dope bgm that I really
liked there's a Bowser one
what about
the what what
this I could listen to the one from
Pauline of course
but oh let's listen to this I like this
one I did like this one a
lot do you hear
[Music]
nice okay we're uh as I said I'm going
to
wait I'm going to quickly look
over the super chats from where I took
the
Polaroid uh
requests and going to read the non Reds
I guess and see if
any
anything stands out in terms of the
[Music]
RS okay first of all Brandon sent a
beautiful
[Music]
rainbow happy
birthday see I could not miss out on
that you know what I'll read this one
since it's a rainbow and your
birthday oh you're right that's wait
that was in the preat and I saw it and I
was like dude you didn't even you didn't
even uh send me a
number Merry Christmas came M it's also
my birthday wow free birthdays that
Carey seem so long ago though but it
doesn't feel that way because every day
has been so good you said you likes
hearing about our backers so I thought I
take this rainbow to do that let's go I
found YouTubers watching clips of Debut
myth because haha anime aatur moves wow
later I saw a clip about you opening up
up about leaving Japan and how you
weren't in the best place then I was
touched by your openness and wanted to
learn more about
you I don't remember that but yeah I
remember I I know how I must have felt
I became a lurker in chat catching a
couple minutes of streams when I could I
was it was during the 1 million chicken
celebration that I realized I wanted to
protect that smile forever oh are you fo
M and joined as a member I upgraded my
phone plan to unlimit data for something
unrelated ah un oh yeah unrelated okay
not for me I was about to say and
realized that let me listen to streams
at work oh I've been a pretty consistent
fixture here ever since even if I'm not
[Music]
typing I stay in K with me forever I
love my come see you're the best you
deserve all the support and attention
let's all have fun in the new
year love
you thank
you that was nice to hear happy
birthday little bit late but Happy
Birthday you'll get a polar War I of
course thank you for opening up your
heart to
me before EDS in the Super
Chat yeah I did see it on the day I did
indeed indeed
indeed okay then C sent to pinkies so
that's
good wait can I turn off the okay I'll
look at
all
[Music]
thank
than wait why is hokan talking about his
eye
again did I already tell like did we
already talk about this
Hulan
did I what did I read this during the
stream that was before you gave my eyeb
okay
okay ah so that was more recent the I
giving back
okay I can talk about my tooth again if
it helps no no no no wait I I completely
like I'm pushing that out of my memory
but I feel it coming back the moment I
read your Super Chat
don't I don't don't that's nothing good
right I don't want to remember
that this rer would be honor to pull
your
Sligh am I Santa or Rudolph I don't
[\h__\h] know I was
both got TI I got
TI make it Eric
okay oh GD sending one for FAL oh
wow Champion I don't know about
that ah lashes okay okay lashes lashes
okay
[Music]
for can I get
a garden
[Music]
park Garden
Park I'll see what I can
[Music]
do chy
CH please yeah Mario arst yeah very good
I'm having so much fun with this game I
don't understand
why all other Mario games I have to
suffer but this one I can
finally I can finally enjoy it and play
it
properly why
why this one is way
better
yeah what about Galaxy I don't believe
you exra li you the way you say it with
that face sounds
fake are you
see really this one has a lot of
variation cuz you take over enemies more
oh
yeah let you die less and there's lots
of ways to keep from falling into pits
and
whatnot you mean in
Galaxy or
here Galaxy is actually easy would also
be easy is good for the same reasons as
hesty if it's better even oh okay then
that's another a Mario game I I could
consider for the future all
right
discussing American Heritage and all
other
[Music]
notas any fun Christmas morning
Traditions Christmas morning Traditions
no no we don't have any Christmas
morning
Traditions no not that I know
of sad Tim Tracy
D
[Music]
puyy do somebody recognize
that cowboy k outf
no oh this song
ha nobody was cute
[Music]
e this
KP thank you thank
you thank you oh sweet words Sor I'm
like in the middle of reading for these
red ones if there's anything that I
shouldn't miss out
[Music]
on there's so many oh my [\h__\h] god
oh my God
stks one number two B of you to have two
non RPG Mario streams I
did in the same week oh oh I guess yeah
we're still in that week aren't we are
[Music]
we yeah we are yeah we
are
[Music]
just want to tell you how amazing it was
than thank you
[Music]
a thank you
sh thank
you you got mostly pants that's funny
because that reminds me of me talking
with Shi about what gifts she
got and I don't want to I don't want to
expose her on I wonder if she
talks talked about it cuz she's been
doing Twitter spaces right I wonder if
she talked about
it I was I was pretty
like what's the word dumbfounded that's
a word right I was like
what I won't tell it maybe she told it
already maybe she didn't I won't tell it
I found it really funny
n thank you oh that's I guess that
belongs to a red super
chat it's a common
response that is a word and the correct
way to use it Y what did you get for
Christmas was nothing we didn't gift
each other anything we haven't I don't
think I have really gotten the Christmas
presents in years where we just don't
really do it
[Music]
anymore um
no we stop gifting or like at least not
everybody sometimes one person I would
give something but
yeah but this year we didn't gift
[Music]
anything ah yeah I guess she got my slow
cooker that never has been used by
anyone besides her so it's basically
[Music]
new not not even cards
all no
[Music]
know a bit sad
honestly oh oh happy belated birthday
Chief masam oh I see you waited for this
opportunity to send your birthday Super
Chat as well nice so this is smart
because you're giving yourself the
birthday gift of a PO
award you wish your family did the same
they want to see presentes on the tree
but don't want to tell anyone what they
want
they should at least give some
hints if you're going to like demand
[Music]
presents is a busy month for kfp
birthdays oh I feel like every month
really is I don't really sense any
difference I'll be Christmas
[Music]
M FAL but what's the difference what's F
andal Fel is Merry Christmas what's Fel
Nal
again thank you for the pinky secret
identity Studio we all know your
password is I love P pineapple anyway
boss don't [\h__\h] expose me like that I
it's Portuguese ah okay makes sense
[Music]
doing whole C are super creative class
getting full support to pull off because
they're so funny I'm looking forward to
more it's going to be my birthday
[Music]
a the sign painter I'm glad I caught
your super chat I almost didn't see the
the birthday part happy birthday the day
before yesterday
yay happy birthday I'll get you a polo
as soon as I can I I'm going to try to
get at least some of them out before
mold bees I don't know if I can do all
of them [\h__\h] I'll try I'll
try maybe I'll start
tomorrow I should have some time
tomorrow and then maybe also on the
Sunday should have some
time thank you thank
[Music]
you
don't hurt your hand no it's fine um the
the digital signing sessions at least I
don't have like a really hard time limit
so I don't force myself endlessly like
with the other Polo wordss the the real
ones that I wrote
[Music]
recently do more in the
past perhaps I was a last KP who hadn't
found their Wawa oh this is so sweet
Jennifer King shiny gr don't thank
you
sweet St Rob T I don't want you to hurt
your hand signing a card for me so
here's a pinky instead oh man St thank
you can't be forever yay can't be
forever I'll be D soon oh jardo jarvania
sent a RP chat saying Merry Christmas
but with no number
whatsoever
do you not want a polar roid I guess
not if you're here in the chat now you
can tell me about it otherwise I'm going
to just not right
[Music]
one but
another in any case Merry Christmas to
you too thank you for the red chat
grunt cbw thanks for the pinky Merry
Christmas K can I get a number one to
Steven oh grunt that's a
pinky
[Music]
oh see I don't want to like everybody
else you know pays the full amount so I
don't want to like you
know uh
you know make anyone else feel like they
pay too much uh
difficult U but I also don't want you to
be like paying half for
nothing maybe they sent another one
towards the
end I don't see another Pinky from
[Music]
you
yeah cut the polar right in
half
[Music]
oh no that's
evil H I'll think about it don't think
about it difficult cuz you're not seeing
the chat so we can't talk about it
either
[Music]
huh what and I don't want to be like hey
pay up either that feels
evil but I don't think I ever made one
for you before did
I maybe be first time or discount cuz
last one was 50% off or
so I'll think about it I don't want to
this is
difficult Red Diamond O2
D
[Music]
and see
Canadian
after you moved I wasn't a kfp in the
beginning but after you moved back to
Austria I was able to watch you more I
quickly oi
hen care oh for
real ni the
Canadian the Canadian or she hands to
[Music]
me who doesn't say who you first liked
but that's
interesting it's not like my time is
particularly good for Canadians
but I do have a strong connection with
Canada I even know your national
anthem I don't even know my own so keep
me entertained at work y I'm happy to
hear it hi good that you're here are you
working right now probably
yeah Oh
Canada don't even get me
started
[Music]
furry
Kiam
no
well even though I'm not reading them
out loud it's still taking a while
[Music]
get happy birthday Expo 77 I don't know
if you're here now to catch this happy
birthday thank you for the Super Chat D
XO
77 um Brandon pow thank
Unwritten
D thank
[Music]
you not here
huh uh oh it's strange to think that I
hadn't even heard of YouTubers last year
but you would end up becoming my most
watch creat of 2020 friends wow Ohio
enjoy thank you
happy to read
[Music]
that I'm sorry for your future copper
tunnel don't worry I won't get copper
tunnel from
this I
think
do not turn off Super Chat
[Music]
yet hi
hi
hi oh you have the seing
what get well soon
nothing be ground P St creat thank
you my my my eye scanning skills are not
good enough here why am I so slow f and
[Music]
green oh I think this person is Italian
saying chiao Kiana and donating in
Euro
L Moon very
[Music]
energetic I heard an Austria is on 25th
26th still Christmas too get celebrated
even more as here in Germany no I mean
we have the days off 25th and 26th was
holiday but we didn't I don't know we
just work off off of work but
no
we only really celebrated so to say on
the
24th ah Joker
happy whoa wait waa within the last week
I just bought my first house had my
third birthday and three years of
membership with you all with
you oh wow wow
wow wow wow wow that is
intense congratulations on all of that
yay Pats Pats Pats Pat big wow
moment Big
W
omto lots of milestones for real yeah oh
there there you go you're
here good luck with your
house m
[Music]
you're still going to get a polar word
afterwards eventually so keep an eye
open on the community
board early birthday birthday is on
January 9th oh yo yo yo it's my second
time of kfp and you love you bus I
believe in you always don't ever change
I'm proud of everything you've done to f
m that LE thank you happy birthday to
you ooh happy birthday to you ooh and
jam in your shoe too happy Birthday Dad
Leia happy birthday to you okay that
wasn't really a proper song but I mean I
did sing for you happy birthday to
[Music]
you happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you too happy birthday dead L and the
Jem in your shoe too what no in your
pants
[Music]
too o m f g Blondie D thank
you that is true I
[Music]
just Merry Christmas
Oar the under bu waa Christmas outfit
okay I was not planning on that we'll
see no
[Music]
promises
ah o d
o o d are you
here it says r Super Chat from
you no number no
order
[Music]
o are you
here
let me take your
order not
here
[Music]
why do you not want it put send the red
super chat it confuses
me don't send it if you don't want one
during a PO right order
session but you still I'll still give
you a chance if you somehow you know let
me know before it's too late you
know just make your way to
me
[Music]
super
ah he also no order what the [\h__\h] but I
I immediately repli to you on stream and
you must have still been listening and
you didn't answer so you're not getting
one maybe I'll make you one anyway you
won't probably won't even pick it up you
probably won't even pick it up what you
hick hick
hick oh wait I reached the end more or
less
he said it was D did he where in the
chat cuz I didn't see another Super Chat
of
him oh oh thank you so CL so
CL chickens need to be
responsible yeah in the in the past
Mario stream g d s the artist
d
gasan thank you for the pinky tension do
you know H this super chat you know the
12 Days of Christmas song If You Got
Each gift per the song One Part 12 Days
12 Birds which gift would you get the
most B ran screaming from the map got
close people nailed it are you smarter
than a rock yeah I already answered you
in detail I'm sorry I've been asked this
before literally before
that and we didn't get really
far resine
D and that's it that's it I looked for
everything I wished some people some
birthday
messages so that was good and the UN the
the private de um cloes for Advent
stream has one Super Chat only from
Jacob 47
soon uh and yeah the polar wordss will
follow for that what I just went through
the polar wordss will follow I hope as
soon as
possible please be a little bit patient
with
me D for
understanding thank you now go eat no no
no no
no no I'm going to read a couple more
more
[Music]
properly what I'm not done what I'm not
done why you say great stream today why
you say this like like a
goodbye it's not goodbye yet it's lethal
company Super Chat
dime see how you how I added some noise
even I I put some effort into this
thumbnail
y to get that effect on the font it
wasn't like this it didn't have these
scratches at
all I had to make that I didn't really
know how to make
it but I
somehow was able to create it that
way yeah wind and some Distortion and
then sharpening and this and
that graphic design is my passion oh
it's already 1:00 a.m. what the [\h__\h]
wait these are not many super chats let
me just finish these py
for thank
you thank for CH so much W worldwide
live web it feels wrong to say you're
giggling wiggling perhaps what do you
mean giggling what was that
giggling why does it feel wrong oh
because of the w we need more
W's
thank you
[Music]
D yeah it was so much W and in English
that means I was
winning if I have many W's that means
I'm winning I've learned
that and maybe in Japanese it means I'm
laughing in German it means
nothing but
[Music]
I wish I had something in the
freezer
[Music]
coming I start
this it
in for the red CH yeah the
laziness it's okay I will do it I will
cook I will cook hopefully I have like
at least one simple recipe cuz I did get
a hell fresh
delivery
um I wonder if I actually chose the
recipes though I'm not sure if I did I
think those I might have accidentally
not
chosen but there must be at least one
quick
recipe I think G thanks for CH it is
once again my birthday my fourth review
really four birthdays of you I'm now one
year from a big scary number
change which one thank you for being my
CI oi thank you for being my CI chicken
half a
century half a century is that 50
then is a century
100 sometimes these uh words confuse me
wa whoo W that's a big
one all the all the tens all the tens
are big ones
[Music]
nice Don't Call Him
old
manners Boomer fan cultured
man don't rubp it in his
face one year now from 50 to 49 yeah I
know I know I know
congratulations on your
birthday by by by by by B everybody
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday in your pants too
happy birthday I told
you thank you so much for all your love
and support and damn four
birthdays yeah that's so
crazy
four you were 45
then
damn time is [\h__\h] terrifying time is
[\h__\h]
[Music]
terrifying but as you know love Rush
tells us we grow older but we also grow
Bolder so it is in our
hands and in our hands only to do
something with that boldness let's do
something bold
yeah [\h__\h] no Boulder maybe also Boulder
but
no I mean
Boulder still what my hair is getting F
no no no no no no it's not no it's
not Boulders
gate when we grow bald we go to Boulders
gate right that's what you
[Music]
do most people in here I want 25 you'll
have your entire existence up until now
and just catch up to
him what was that mean what are you
[Music]
saying oh my oh God my feathers are
turning white wait they're already
white typical chicken
Panic well anyway G is in thank you for
always
always what's the word Lo loaning re
renting uh give giving giving your
wisdom sharing your wisdom sharing your
kindness and your heart with me
congratulations Kami
chicken
aorus B
[Music]
anime Harline thanks the pinky this
marks my fourth birthday
o another one being spent as a Cy
chicken thanks for all the continued fun
and entertainment you give not only me
but KY as a whole by any chance can this
humble race car request a roll Safe
Harbor for his special
day of
course Harbor
line roll Safe
Harbor and happy birthday
y four years of you and
me
congratulations happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your car too happy birthday to
you zoom
[Music]
zoom
congratulations I'm glad you're here
with me again for another birthday wow
wow wow wow wow
did we decide I'm not making dinner
tonight no I don't really have a choice
I think I have to make dinner the only
thing I could make is
like I have some like
prepackaged Japanese
Curry that's like in a in a bag that I
have to like warm up and add rice to
it and they're they're they're okay but
they're also like
n
I don't know if I would want to eat that
no sometimes I feel like they're pretty
high quality for what they
are but I just don't really feel
it how empty is your fridge I mean it
has all the hell fresh
ingredients I just have to cook it but I
don't have anything I can I can eat
right away yeah the Muji curries those
those know what I
mean this is why I keep microwave
burritos in the
freezer I mean I normally also have have
some stuff in the freezer but I just
used it up yesterday I ate my last
couple of um fish
sticks empty according to your mood
right now that is true thank
you going make real cheese no I don't
have any cheese except for like Greek
cheese or something like that but that
belongs to a hell fresh
recipe you could always just starve yeah
you would like that wouldn't
you always nice to have Serv for
emergency sitations I normally do I
normally do but I have to cook like I
also like I know I should cook so I
purposefully don't give myself too many
options besides
that I can't run away from it too long
because otherwise the ingredients are
all going to go bad Murphy BR a
t mayine thanks for pinking K and her
harm are unstoppable or is it A's harm
or narissa or hom Mutual harm web yes
yes we are each other's harm you know I
mean I don't know I don't really like
the word
harm uh I don't use it at all I don't
like it it's weird
um but we're
all there for each
other you know if we need each other
yeah
wife sharing system yeah it's like a car
sharing system but it's with wives and
it's invite
[Music]
only yeah worldwide web live web is
better than
Haron sounds dorkier I like
it you're all there for each other until
someone put on the
mask I was the only one who didn't play
the game yet yesterday right so they
brought the skill that was necessary to
get at least some [\h__\h] done and I
brought like the the non-existent
knowledge
to make some accidents
happen
naturally it was good I think it was
good because we also got very far I
think as well like we did a lot we were
really efficient I was surprised of how
efficient we were and I was a bit scared
in the beginning just because of the
premise of it but then after a while it
was like it was really fine and I
recognized like how people said that
it's mostly just dorky it's not really
scary the monsters are mostly dorky and
yeah after seeing like some of them the
first time the second second or the
third time is more like ah hi you again
huh let me Bonk you with the shovel I
have now you can't scare
me so like with Outlast no Outlast is
still way more
scary yeah I mean I got a little bit
used to it too but it's still way more
scary I would not compare it to
outlast you got more scared by the door
[Music]
P soup and beans yum why why does that
sound yummy
ew it's more intense but I wonder if you
could tack it now no thank you I don't
need to try
it you like left for dead since you
could fight back I'm like the only one
who doesn't play that game snow is
falling now in Korea snow is falling
in
Korea chickens
playing having
fun this the season of staying home and
watching W was
YouTube stream
now what was
YouTube stream now
hey
what's
Korean under the table no no
no it's
snowing
[Music]
means falling
down I just JP my chair still
loud
sorry
[Music]
sorry I think you need to
adjust
good morning time to wake up
[\h__\h] wake up
[Music]
[\h__\h]
up I knew it I knew M would say mother
fluffers I knew she did wouldn't have
the bowels to say it
properly why didn't you say mother fers
though that it work
too bows yeah she doesn't have the
bows you heard right you heard me
correctly so you
deduction no hate I love I love moao
what
what yeah doesn't have vowel movements
[Music]
either don't even get rest started again
don't don't even get me started
ah I will go now I will go
now she likes her vowels yeah she surely
likes her
vowels no B what what what
what they do like to put the h a little
bit in front of their words right but
that's a that's um a speech pattern I've
noticed with
uh I don't know where some part of
America uh where they talk
like
what like they put the H in for the
words yeah Midwest
right there's this one Netflix show uh
where yeah cool
whip where I've
um like that was hammered into my brain
cuz the main character was like always
talking like
[Music]
that no I'm not talking about family gu
no I'm talking about a show that I'm not
even sure like the show was so good but
you know when you're experience or your
I don't know your opinion of a show gets
so sour because of the actor turning out
to be a piece of
[Music]
[\h__\h] no I mean House of
Cards but I love how House of Cards
handled it by making the last season
about her getting rid of the guy and
making it about the wife and it actually
even though it is such
a difficult change where I think many
other shows would fail completely it's
quite a challenge to make that work but
I think Viet was very different and
maybe not as good as the first couple
Seasons I think they still did it well
[Music]
enough it wasn't a good deison but it
was a good decision a good season but it
was a good yeah no it wasn't the worst
it could have been worse it could have
been definitely
worse it
was the best way to handle it I I
suppose yeah Claire was a good character
yes she was a great character my
God thanks for making the community
reference yeah there were two Community
reference in the in the Advent calendar
one might think I'm a community fan I'm
actually not I keep on telling you guys
I only like the first season if
anything and maybe the second and then
it gets
weird but
yeah they were good references for
making videos what a
fraud when are you doing office I've
done office references in the past I'll
keep on doing these videos If chy helps
me
out keep the person the product separate
yeah I mean I I can do that too I would
still watch the show
again but like I feel weird about
mentioning it positively on stream like
saying anything good about the
[Music]
show but it was a [\h__\h] good
show H it's [\h__\h] uh
scandalous it really made me
wonder if if this is like I wouldn't
assume that it's really that bad in real
life but I it makes me wonder if to a
certain
extent the [\h__\h] that happens in House of
cards happens in real life politics too
like at least there a certain
extent but do you think it's all what
happened to the
chat here it
does so you don't think it's all
rainbows and marshmallows
and you think there's secret
murder
okay we shouldn't talk about this the
Illuminati is watching
me and theer we sa Us in go I got to
go they're behind
me no tell my cats I love
[Music]
them
for
[Music]