[Music]
do
hello everyone
today is my
birthday
so
welcome to my birthday party
i wanna talk with
en
member
members and id members
so i
will
do the
totsumachi
today
[Music]
there
m
[Music]
happy birthday too
fellow twin
yeah speaking yeah yeah yeah
conversation
yeah conversation
english is okay
[Music]
how are you
oh
i am
tired
your original song is very beautiful and
very
cute
oh thank you
[Music]
very beautiful
um everybody
worked really hard in it and yeah yeah
i'm just very happy and um yeah thank
you very much i
i i
will repeat a lot
your
original song
let me see something nice about here
because it's it's your birthday stream
okay i have the question
yes
um uh if
uh you were to collaborate together
what would you like to do
this i want to eat food
i eat i'm sorry i'm hungry
i'm hungry
all right okay
what's collaboration right eating
collaboration we will
[Music]
it's so good idea
and
if
[Music]
japan
i will cook for you
[Music]
do you know how to make
omurice ah omurice it's okay i i will do
it do it
[Music]
i love almora
what flavor
tomato
tomato is
[Music]
is
what do you like what almost right else
do you like
huh
where do you get the eggs
i think you get the eggs
all right all right this is very
important ah i i see uh okay
i
will
how to say um
[Laughter]
yes give me your egg
okay
okay on hulk eggs on rice i i will make
it for you
thank you
thank you for coming sana chan
and happy birthday have a nice year
happy birthday
[Music]
thank you very much
happy birthday
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
so cute
[Music]
it
okay
[Music]
that
thank you
hello it's me i sound a lot more awake
now
yeah
chana's birthday you
looks like uh sweepy
yes very sleazy i just woke up
i'm much more awake now happy birthday
thank you
sounded
very awake for santa's call
wake up this morning
uh i just wake up
[Music]
eight o'clock
oh my god
and i
i i want to eat breakfast in
now
i work
eight o'clock
and i called
uh jerry very
delivery yeah
amazing
how was your birthday
yeah it's so happy because you coming
my birthday party
thank you for coming
of course your english is so good oh my
god
i want to improve my english so please
teach me
and oh yeah
i will teach
japanese
please yeah
but your japanese
very good
no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
which question am i supposed to answer
do i answer all of them
you you want to
answer the all of them
i don't mind
okay i have um
i have the question one question
[Music]
hi uh what was your first impression of
me
please teach me
first impression oh
um first impression would have been
[Music]
and then um i could tell you were
nervous and that's what you're really
cute
[Laughter]
is running
i'm so sorry
it's okay
thank you very cute very very cute this
is my
mistake
and then i
um and then we talked atos and i was
like oh my god her english is so good
and then ah
so cute
and good english thank you
how about now
now
still very cute
he's employee and
very good
i'm gonna continue thank you
but your japanese is very good and so i
know we will
improve
uh other
language
together
yeah
[Music]
thank
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
hello
i can't hear you
hello hello hello
[Music]
there
hello okay i i i hear you
oh no my microphone is being weird
hi i'm okay
don't worry about that
you hear me
yeah
hi happy birthday thank you thank you
for coming my birthday party
yes thank you for inviting me
you're welcome
i have a gift for you huh
[Music]
yes i have a present yeah oh thank you
one second i got it i have to send it
okay it's us
but
okay i i will show everybody
just moment please
[Music]
it's so cute
just movement
yeah
we are so cute but
okay
yeah it's so cute
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's so cute
i didn't know what to draw
i
spent like an hour thinking
i see
i love your draw
before
it's also so cute
and i love your drawing
thank you
thank you for letting me draw you
[Music]
mummy
i i want you
i want to ask
one question
okay
what kind of japanese food would you
like me to cook for you
i will cook for you
[Music]
what what is your favorite thing to cook
ah
um
[Music]
yeah like
just sweet
just sweet it's sweet yeah
yeah but
very delicious
it looks so nice i would be so happy to
eat that
okay so i will make
i will cook nikki for you
i
i will make you cookies
cookies
yes you like you make me miku saga i
make you cookie
oh
thank you i love you peace
happy happy birthday
i love you
we will probably eat together
yes please yeah thank you let me know
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
foreign
foreign you're welcome thank you for
coming
yay
it's first time
first time talking right
[Music]
yeah yeah i mean we've
talked a bit through the yeah yeah
some time yeah
but
this uh just talking is the first time
today
i want to talk with you
yeah
i wanted to talk with you too but then
like uh
we were gonna have that uh collaboration
but
yeah i got
sick
oh are you okay right now
yeah yeah i'm i'm good now
yeah
so good
i worry about that
but
it's so good i'm amazing
what does she can't pick he does make it
perfect
perfect human is
so good
yeah but happy birthday
i hope you're enjoying it
yeah
sure
for sure yeah
i have the question one question for you
it's okay
yes okay
uh
what was your first impression of me
let's think um
i thought
you were going to be
like
like a teacher
vibe sense name fancy
and they're calm and chill and i think
and i think you're still kind of like
that ah
i see see me tiny top
[Music]
like crusty cow right
yeah classy classy yeah
i see
uh
i
okay
i want to talk about
uh your first impression
uh i love your voice
and
and you are so cool and beautiful so
i love you
oh
oh i thought you loved mummy
but i also love you
oh
oh my
oh blush
oh thank you i
i how about you
i
put on spot um i
yes i
i love
love forever
thank you i like i love your voice too
thank you thank you wrote
yeah um
i'd like to invite you one day
uh too
you're welcome
okay i
uh we will collaborate
yeah
because your english is good so
so i will teach japanese for you
oh yes please
so collaborate japanese lesson
yes yeah yes
okay i will send a message
wait blessed yeah thank you about the
collaboration
thank you for coming
yes
thank you
happy birthday
[Music]
[Applause]
top
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's
this is so cute
i make the confused
cooling champ
it's so nice
okay
um
next
person
is
hello
thank you for coming
no problem happy birthday
thank you
how are you how are you today
i am doing well i just woke up
good morning
good morning to you too
thank you for
uh work off
[Music]
anytime anytime
thank you
okay i have your one question for you
okay
um
do you want do you want to come japan
come to japan
yeah yeah yeah yeah so if you
come to japan what kind of japanese food
would you like me to cook for you
oh
japanese beef is very delicious
what kind of beef
food
[Music]
okay anything is good example i cook it
okay i i will
i will cook for you
some beautiful food okay okay
okay
uh omurice is very popular for
um
foreign people right
yes i think it's simple but delicious oh
yeah
yes okay
i will make it
okay
other question i have
what was your first impression of me
first impression yeah uh first
impression was
kakui kambu
however it's like now
right now
[Music]
do you want to girlfriend
um my girlfriend
what uh what day is free don't worry
anytime anytime
saturday saturday night
okay saturday night saturday night
okay
okay okay i'll take saturday night okay
the chinese
please uh open the
open tonight okay
okay open tonight okay okay i will
[Laughter]
i will talk with you tonight okay okay
okay
i will wait i will wait
thank you for coming
thank you we will collaborate together
again
yes
yes thank you
let's come up again soon yeah
thank you thank
you saturday girls love love
[Music]
she knew the
a lot of girlfriend i have
i'm so surprised
so next
person
hello
[Music]
hello hello hello
ah
you were have the mute
hello
oh
[Music]
hello
hello oh hello
just uh work up now right
no no i i woke up
in at the early morning i see
yeah
thank you for coming
um yeah thank you so much for inviting
me too yeah
i want to
talk with you before before you
uh
after
i want want want one to talk with you
so i'm
i'm so
glad
today
because yeah
we finally talk right yeah yeah
however
uh
my first impression
oh
your
first impression from me to you
to me
yeah yeah
um i see that you're so
cute cute you're so kind yeah so cute
and so kind yeah and um
but yet so cool yes thank you
[Music]
and i want to collaborate with you over
the tlp
because i like the tft and i
played the tft before i debuted oh
yeah oh i see let's play together then
but i
um
long time no prayed at yes
so please teach me
here or
okay i'm not that good but okay we can
play sometime
yeah
collaborate tft
yeah yeah
okay sure oh thank you
yeah
i'm looking forward to it
play together yeah
okay sure sure sure let's just stop
after this probably here yeah
yeah okay oh sure thank you
and yeah uh i will we will collaborate
japanese restaurant right you want to
japanese soon right
so i will teach you the
japanese
for you good yeah yeah i wanna talk i
wanna learn japanese yes yeah yeah yeah
thank you thank you for coming i will
send the message
um soon
so okay
please collaborate with me
okay sure
thank you for coming and kind of
thank you
[Music]
time
rishi
okay
next
hello
[Music]
thank you for watching
yeah i actually already prepared a
present for you but maybe
maybe i will send it later i can send it
now i will send it to you yeah yeah
mr okay yeah it's okay thank you
very enjoyed
violent yeah yeah
yeah it's a surprisingly uh
uh you know senpai is a very sweet
person yeah yeah yeah yeah i enjoy the
color i
thank also thank you thank you for
collaborate with eat of us
and
please collaborate with me
yeah yeah please do to me i saw i saw i
saw your your stream your collab with
zetta
in japanese
yeah yeah maybe
maybe you know i hope you know
how you can uh teach me also yeah yeah
do you want do you want to
do the japanese restaurant right
oh oh yeah yeah yeah okay japanese yeah
i only speak animal language
right now
yeah so i need more
you know uh
vocabulary
of japanese yeah
okay
i will teach japanese
for you so please teach me
uh indonesia language okay
[Music]
okay okay
thank you
okay i will just send a message for you
later
about the collaboration so yeah okay
we will check again
i'll be wait i'll be waiting
thank
good night again
a
[Music]
okay
yeah just pretend that you understand
okay okay okay
thank you
i can't understand but it's okay
it's a passion passion
inspiration communication is
the point is uh it's a it's a good wish
a good birthday wish for you so okay
thank you thank you
thank you
okay next person
[Music]
hello
happy birthday
japanese pronunciation
i love it
no i love your english
so much
thank you i i suggest english
[Music]
i am
your japanese
oh my god yes we eat each other this is
this is um this is
destiny
[Laughter]
is
have
a lot of knowledge
japanese
i'm so
surprised and shocked
if
if i watch your stream
you have a lot knowledge
of the japanese culture
[Music]
[Laughter]
you will forgot the japanese because yes
i will
come to the japanese restaurant right
because i will i will forget japanese
for one day
okay louie will invite me uh i will the
wesley beam for you
what's a little b
for you and please
please
[Laughter]
okay i invite your you yes my
japanese resident
in the future near future i will i will
cut out the wastewater
foreign
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
it's okay i will i will cut out the
wastewater team
to get invited okay i'm planned uh
is correct
yes yes i would love to come
thank you for coming
thank you too
thank you for writing happy birthday
thank you
happy birthday
have a good day
love you
bye
[Applause]
[Music]
so good japanese skills she has a good
japanese skill so
i forgot
she is
not japanese
so i will
joke japanese only japanese
speaking
for her
thank you for coming on your senpai
next
[Music]
hello
you have the present
yes
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
so cute
you're so powerful today
[Laughter]
it's your birthday
thank you
you're welcome you're welcome
how are you enjoying your birthday i
looks right yes
yes yes
so pretty
so i have to first
a question for you
if you were to collaborate together what
would you
like to do
[Music]
you maori maori with me yes i want to
marry you ah i see i have to a lot of
girlfriend
right now
i know so
so it's okay
[Music]
no
but now you have so many girlfriends
that's so cool what day you want
for our wedding
yeah
not waiting just girlfriend the first
time
but i want to marry you no not
girlfriend ah i see so um
musukashi kana it's so difficult
it's so difficult to uh married you
because i think uh sakamata will i'm
angry
[Music]
to you well then i will marry sakamata
too
sakura will kill you
no no it is a wife-sharing system louie
wife sharing system
so crazy
yeah so crazy ollie
crazy crazy crazy horry
crazy in love with you
thank you
oh okay
it's joke right uh
want to collaborate with
me
ah
i am okay anytime it's a demo
okay
that's wedding collaboration
okay um
when we collaborate together
this is a wedding day right
yes
okay
so
i think never never do the
crazy
i don't want to
collaborate with you because
he's joking
just kidding
okay um i will
just send
a message about the
invites collaborate
yes so please uh fps or nfx is okay
let's go yeah let's go epics
yes
yes thank you for coming only time
and thank you for inviting me happy
birthday
everyone thank you thank you for coming
bye bye
goodbye
[Music]
this is data present
thank you santa chan
okay next person
hello
[Music]
thank you
how old are you
uh 1
600 wherever
years old
[Laughter]
[Music]
is so young
yeah still yeah
okay nice nice nice
and spicy
spicy yeah
a little spicy
hey i got a present for you
oh
thank you
i have a way i i send to you okay
hi doing
[Music]
wow
it's so cute
thank you i wanted to draw something a
little bit for you
okay i i i will
show
everybody
this moment
yes please
i see
okay
[Music]
spicy spicy spicy spicy is it painting
yeah
spicy it is so cute
[Music]
i i heard i heard you have a a lot of
girlfriends so i tried to draw you a
little bit more you know handsome so you
will get even more girlfriends
and do you want to
my
my girlfriend
you want
what day which one
what day do you want
weekdays weekdays or weekdays any any
any day weekdays okay we can okay so
busy
you also have a girlfriend
a wife wife i have a
little bit wife a girlfriend no
maybe
uh you have the wife
yes
hello id uh
why food sharing system
chilling system
is girlfriend no girlfriend right uh i
think no girlfriend ah okay
you think justin yes
i think yes uh dewey is my girlfriend
now oh yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yes
amazing good idea
[Laughter]
if you come to japan
if you come japan what kind of japanese
food would you like me to cook for you
[Music]
i want you to cook me
um
what's the dish that you are best at ah
any food i will
[Music]
i will cook
then i want to have
i want to have a hamburger
yeah
i will make it i
my favorite
food
hamburg
okay
yeah and then you can write with ketchup
you can write fancy
fancy letters i will
like the spicy message oh please right
oh my gosh
with spicy messes okay
yeah hang out
so thank you for coming my birthday
protein
i hope you have a
great birthday thank you more happy
stuff more girlfriends thank
[Applause]
you bye bye
she's so cute and beautiful
i love it
oh
next person coming
hello
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Laughter]
you already senpai a lot of
a lot of kohai you have
[Music]
happy birthday thank you thank you for
coming
my birthday party
of
[Music]
[Laughter]
sana in the morning and trip again and
coming my
party exactly exactly
thank you for coming and thank you for
wat for me
oh no i should be awake right now right
[Laughter]
it's already afternoon i should be awake
right
what you do today
i slept
[Laughter]
were you awake the whole time after that
i
sleep again
and i work
up
at uh 12
8 30 pm
right before
[Laughter]
after waking up in the morning
so normal
same thinking
i have the one question for you oh yes
yes uh i want to collaborate with you
oh yeah um if you were to probably
together
what would you like to do
[Music]
i want to do
singing collaboration sing collaboration
yeah
your your singing is very beautiful and
i love it
if you want to i i also want to
yeah
you want to do like a singing singing
stream like
karaoke and you you know a lot of vocal
light songs too yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah i see i hear you're singing a
lot of vocalists
yeah
that's what i want to do game two of
course of course i love playing games
but it's just that i can't think of a
specific game at the moment
so i
uh
thank you
thank you so much now thank you so much
and happy birthday again i hope you have
a great one
good night again good night again
sleeping beauty needs sleep i
[Music]
this is a
few minutes two minutes last time
for me i i drink water
this moment
how
[Music]
this is very fresh fresh
the collaborate
because
i never talking talk
with them
before
and
they
coming
for
say congratulations for me i saw
happiness and i'm glad
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
next
person so i'm looking forward to talk
with her
[Music]
not
happy birthday louie thank you
thank you for coming
uh id nikki and
nikki
thank you thank you
okay
just come right
hello
hi
nice to meet you
[Music]
me too me too
thank you thank you for inviting
me yeah um
you are welcome
thank you for coming my birthday party
i love too yes thank you
your singing voice is very beautiful
so i have the question
i have one question for you
if you were to collaborate together
what would you like to do with me
i have uh
more than one thing
to do
singing collaborations
[Music]
your idea is so good
yes
so i will send a message after the
birthday party
okay and we will design the
collaboration day
ah okay i will wait
okay
i'm looking i i can't walk i can't wait
okay thank you thank you thank you other
questions i have
okay okay uh what was your first
impression of me
i think
my first impression was louis
until now i think you are still so cool
i i love your uh your voice and your
outfit it's all so cool
thank you my pleasure
[Music]
nakoi
ah
i loved your voice and singing voice and
your stream is so cute and beautiful
so i love your personality
ah no no no i i love louie
thank you
thank you for kind
message for me
thank you for inviting me
so
i will send
a message
ranger
[Applause]
time
[Music]
why life
very beautiful
i'm happy
to talk with her
okay next person is
[Music]
hello
thank you for coming
thank you for inviting me
i'm happy
you're welcome
i want to talk with you
yeah me too
that was so bad
[Music]
and i want to collaborate with you
let's go
yeah
minecraft or something you
singing crowd is
very good minecraft singing singing
collaboration i love you
i really like your voice it's so cool oh
thank you really
yeah
i also loved your voice and singing
voice
thank you your
singing is very beautiful very very very
beautiful
thank you i really like your your cover
the copper i
i don't know what the name i think
ending is it was yo nadiro
yeah
i love that one oh thank you it's a new
new cover right yeah that's a new stuff
love it i love to get cold gekko covered
it's beautiful
yeah thank you yeah
i want to cooperate with you
so i have the
uh question
one question for you
uh
what kind of japanese food you like me
to cook for you
[Music]
ramen ramen women
once i go there you have to cook one for
me okay
you uh second one is yakitori you say
what what kind of bat do you want
i don't know i like them all anything
okay it's no hook right
[Music]
no hope anything anything
oh my god
[Music]
no no no chicken chicken
[Laughter]
dog is so cute i don't want to i don't
want to eat dog
okay
i i will make the taking
chicken food for you
and
other questions i have
okay what's your first impression of me
the first my first impression is i
really like uh when you are debuted and
uh
your appearance is so cool
i don't know maybe it's the first time i
saw uh like the bird kind of hair
thank you i really like it
and he loved my hair
yeah and also uh i have another
impression when we meet at arc
yeah yeah yeah and you are like uh
talking in english uh i think that was
my first time was like oh my god there
is a japanese solo member who is really
good at this i feel really good at
almost
better than me
yeah i i'm uh nervous
in the ark stream but
when you
when
i met you
i want to talk with you so i chatting
chatting send chat chat for you
in english
wow
what did the creator you remember about
that
oh my god and i'm really i'm really
happy that we talk at that time yeah me
too
thank you for coming my birthday party
thank you happy birthday please
collaborate together
yeah after this i will get in touch with
you i will i will dm you apparently oh
right here we talked about that
immediately okay okay
for sure thank you
thank you for coming bye bye
happy
[Music]
it's so happy
him
if he
have the video message
so
i
should
show you
later okay
okay next person is
hello
hello hello hello
she coming
no
[Music]
thank you for coming
yeah
how are you i'm so good
how about you
it's good i'm good too
you woke
any time anytime
when
we
already talk
with
uh talk together
yeah
i think before the i
debuted
right
now
okay i have the one question for you
yes yeah
uh if you were to collaborate together
what would you like to do
eh
i wanna i wanna see you play
a scary game
[Laughter]
scary game horror game
with me
yes
you do
attend for me right
yes i'll protect you
protect me
i'll protect you yes
you
uh
don't eat azula how to say it
okay
i will do that uh what kind of fly game
do you want
there's a couple we can play i'm sure
i'm sure
yeah let me know
maybe maybe around
halloween yeah
it's good idea
okay
i
invite you
yay i'll be reading
other question i have the what
was your first impression of me
ah first impressionally first impression
was
uh your english is very good and you
know a lot of languages thank you
i guess the second thing i thought was
that um i want i want lee to head pat me
i see
yeah uh i i have the uh you're uh i
also
wanna
avana and talk your first impression
i loved your
personality because very kind and very
powerful
i loved your
uh
like
painting
oh thank you
it's so cute
i love you
yeah
your art is very good
ah thank you thank you
thank you for coming and i we will
collaborate together yeah
yeah happy birthday thank you
have a wonderful wonderful day louie oh
thank you thank you for coming
thank you for having me bye thank you
i'm happy
happy to talk with her
[Music]
next person
hello
hello hello hello
thank you for coming
thank you for having me hello
i am
i want to talk with you
since long long time long time ago
oh
yeah
[Music]
it's so nice to finally get to talk to
you thank you
yeah we've messaged a bit we haven't
actually spoken before so
this is exciting
i have one question for you
hi hi
what was your first impression of me
wow your pants are very i like your
pants very tight ah very shiny
they're pants ah curry's empire also
loves my pants
they're very do they
do they make noise when you walk ah
i would like to try them on one day if i
if if that's okay yeah
thank you can i borrow your pants
i give
uh same one for you
oh
i am honored because my friends is i
think uh
you're not uh
you're
not fit
so
i
i buy for you and give for you
ah
then we can be matching
and twins i love your
3d
uh reaction i i love it and i
i love your singing
[Music]
[Laughter]
i want to collaborate with you
ah yes yes yes
i have the uh we have the plan to
collaborate but i um
still
not decide didn't decide the day of
collaborate right so
i will collaborate
with you
yes yeah yes what kind of coverage
together what kind of
graduates
do with me i
want to kick your butt in mario kart
really time
your card is so good idea
yes yes okay we will collaborate in
battle
but
together
[Laughter]
and thank you for coming
good luck and fine thank you
yeah i have been i happy
i
yeah
talk with you
yeah thank you for coming
thank you can i ask you one question
yeah yeah yeah for sure
can you make me okonomiyaki
i will make
it if you
uh come to japanese japan
if you come to japan
please
come my house
and i'll eat your ukulele
my house is a hotel
it's perfect i will sleep i'll sleep on
the floor next room
no just like a doggy yeah it's okay
together
oh
okay
in bed together okay
it's perfect i'm small i won't take up
much room you can use me as a pillow
i promise i'll be good
thank you
thank you thank you for coming
thank you happy birthday omega
time bye bye
bye bye
thank you
[Music]
guess
i want to
collaborate with grace and pie
because i
found
[Music]
i love to
fast stream
how fast stream ah
i love it
thank you for coming good senpai
[Music]
now next
person
[Music]
who is next
hello
i am
[Music]
thank you thank you for coming my
birthday party
thank you for inviting me
i'm happy to
talk again with you
i told you to meet you again
yeah
when i opened the collaborate
i
passed
time fx collaboration right oh yeah yeah
i did we did
and i want to crowdrace a game
with you
yeah
i would like to play um apex or valerian
or any type of game
i want to start the bar around so please
teach me
okay
i'll be from senpai to sensei
it's a good idea
we can play fortnite
fortnite is oh so good
but i i cannot make the like uh
how to say kenchiku uh
building yeah yeah yeah building a
building i don't oh i cannot
make a building
they have a new game mode where there's
no building guns only against only in
photoshop right
it's i think i very weak
[Laughter]
me too me too
so
i have the one question for you
yes uh what
what was your first impression of me
oh kaku
thank you yeah
very cool because of your cape and also
uh grandma's glasses and your glasses
the sunglasses
sunglasses
your comforting voice i like them i want
your hair
my
grassy's it's
cool
very very cool
thank you
[Laughter]
my pleasure
actually
before i called i was
sleeping on my couch and i thought i was
late so
i got up and i ran and i tripped and i
fell
but i'm happy
to be here
i have the uh fast impression of you
yes yeah and
you are very uh
[Music]
funny funny person
the picture is so
crazy
but i think you're funny too
i thought you and chloe's son are so
cute
thank you
and i i have the other question for you
hmm okay if you come to japan
i want to meet you
so uh what kind of japanese food would
you like me to cook for you
oh
um i like udon or
a cake or onigiri
pick onigiri
what kind of flavor
[Music]
me too i love
it's so delicious right
yeah it's tasty
i see okay i will make it
and what kind of cake do you want
oh chocolate
chocolate okay great cake i will make
yay
and uh iloha also
very good
cooking skill
about the sweet so
we will
make together
oh great cakes for you yeah
wow
good idea right
yes yes i would eat all of it yeah
thank you for coming and
i want to collaborate with you again so
we i
sent a message about the invite coverage
okay too
yes please thank you thank you
happy birthday thank you
[Music]
is
i want to collaborate with her in the
fps game
yeah
again
thank you for coming amazing bye
[Music]
finished
next is a video
i get i got
some video message and voice message
so please
ah watch with me okay
[Music]
okay
final video message
[Music]
okay three
two
um let's go
honey
oh thank
thank you so happy to have been able to
meet you you are so sweet and a great
teacher hey you too good friend and a
great kawaii
and i hope that we get the chance to
talk again yeah yeah yeah
said okay if i play a little song for
you on my clip oh really
she's
singing for me
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
to you
dear louie
happy birthday
to you
[Music]
happy birthday and thank you so much for
everything i hope you have a great
birthday and a great day and i hope you
get to eat something yummy yeah yeah bye
bye
bye bye
she's so cute
she used my job
i
already teach
japanese western
japanese class
yeah
she used the japanese words
[Music]
when i teach her
thank you thank you for giving
give your message
[Music]
okay
next person
is
[Music]
ah
ilfin senpai
[Music]
foreign
party but singing have the
some object
so
she
gave me
[Music]
some
video message and some present
so
video message
works together okay
eh
just movement please
[Music]
this moment
no no no no okay
three two one let's go
happy birthday thank you
[Music]
me
is
[Music]
happy birthday johnny
thank you
you'll finish and find thank you for
game message for me
[Music]
and
she sent a
gift
she liked
my
picture
thank you
you're pissing by
see
with uh scrabbled for a game with me and
went to
kyoyuku uh want to help together
[Music]
she said
and
she
talked about the first time first
time contact
together
she
said
your
english
are very good and make effort
so
[Music]
i want to talk with
you
in the first time
so send a
message
the
uh
first person
yeah
can you understand
my english
still not good
can you understand me
[Music]
your first contact is me
yeah thank you
eofy senpai thank you for coming uh
thank you for coming notice thank you
for game message
for me
okay next person is
kiara senpai
kiana senpai also had a message
so
please watch
together
are you ready
let's go
[Music]
oh
yay
[Music]
thank you
thank you for coming
[Applause]
[Music]
i can't i i i want to the um
i have
uh
wish
about
this moment
[Music]
please
please please please
uh
in
robot
include me
[Music]
[Applause]
i i will i will then send a picture
i think uh she forgot the
update
but it's okay i am the new bot
new brat so
if uh collaborate again with horotoli
we will
take a picture and
take the
uh
kazaru showed
in
this
picture frame
[Music]
thank you
thank you for
again
message for me
[Music]
next
person
is
[Music]
final
member
final member
[Music]
she's still
not not japan so she have the voice
message not video message but voice
message
she gave to me
so please listen together okay
okay
[Music]
okay just moment
[Laughter]
[Music]
i love collaborating with you yeah me
too you are an amazing koh hai amazing
kohanda bye
happy birthday to you luichan um
you have
a beautiful wonderful voice
and i want to hear
your uh original song someday
so please
make original music
i can't wait
uh and i want to see you again
is that okay
let's
let's meet again
[Laughter]
[Music]
she said please kiss me
kiss
together
she's so cute but uh take care take care
manish i want i i love
i love her personality because
she said
me
a lot of kind words and message for me
and
she
said
my voice and your
my voice and my
singing
my song
is
[Music]
laughs
she said loved my
voice and my
singing covered
[Music]
so
i'm happy and my pleasure
thank you for
[Music]
i'm so happy
right now
and i
i
[Music]
like so
this is very emotional for me i love her
thank you for
thank you for game message
and take care you
i hope you're
um
get
good soon
yeah
thank you
and then
[Music]
thank you thank you for sending
gift
for me
oh so cute
[Music]
japanese japan in japan is have the
rainy day
in
june
so i
[Music]
take the umbrella
thank you thank you for give give to me
love love
she's so cute
[Music]
foreign
it's uh all of uh en members
and i remember
say
congratulations for me
[Music]
very happy
but
my
english is still no good
and
i think
but
i think improve a little violator
[Music]
i
wanna
go the
english lesson
again
and
go to the english restaurant a lot
then i want to collaborate
with them
in
like chatting or drinking
shopping i want to collaborate
so
i want to
improve my job
my english
so please teach me english
hi guy niki okay
i
sometimes i miss
mistake
[Music]
english
so please teach me
[Music]
so thank you for coming
everybody and
thank you for coming kai nikki and
anihonomi nama
i have to one announcement
announcement just moment
[Music]
okay
i have
pasta party
uh totsumachi only japanese member
and i have the five announcement
on the stream this stream
yeah
[Music]
and
nine pm today 9 pm is my
birthday party again
i have five announcements so please come
please please come or
if you want to sweep sleep
please watch archive
archive
so thank you for coming today
okay
uh
so
this uh stream is finished
you for coming
[Music]
so
ah first announced is uh 8 p.m but uh
today is 9 00 pm i i will change i
change it already changes the time so 9
pm jst is correct time okay
[Music]
thank you
so think uh please come
[Music]
and see you again 9 pm gst okay
mata kuji
[Music]
today is my birthday
and today is um
heroine doing is me
thank you for watching
thank you thank you thank you thank you
i love kanye nikki
i love japanese from luitomo sound i
love it
so please
subscribe me and
please
support whole life
jpenid
and me
thank you for watching
bye bye
and go
[Music]
up
you