Genius Upper Lyrica
Yo cute positive
Genius cute positive
Genius Ichi Lyrica
Yo cute positive
Genius cute positive
Genius Ichi Lyrica
Chang Corporation works with Lyrica
We are currently recruiting talented people who can
You in a homely and pleasant environment
I can work in a way that suits my lifestyle.
We offer a comprehensive welfare structure with a variety of systems.
I'll be waiting for you all together
Masuda
Yo cute positive
Genius cute positive genius
cute positive
Genius Ichicho Ririka
Yo cute positive
Genius cute positive
Genius Toko Lyrica
Yojo Corporation together with Lyrica
We are currently looking for talented people to work with us.
How could you really open it like this?
cute positive
Genius cute positive
Look at Genia, take a shower
Okay, I'm Rika, I'm going to take a shower.
Yo
[music]
I'm here today, but it's a little too much.
Ririka was so nervous that the book was explained at the beginning.
I was thinking of starting after
I couldn't do it, so I suddenly asked everyone to come.
It's so cute, so cute, so cute
It's not just woo-woo, it's because everyone can't get started.
Thank you so much. I'll take a shower now.
I'm going to stop taking a shower and take a shower now.
What should I do when I'm nervous?
I'm just going to go take a shower.1
Bathing in a professional bath is the best way to relieve tension.
Yes, it seems so, actually, yes, yes, yes.
Well, it seems like that might not be the case.
Well, just a little quickly, Lyrica.
Thank you for wishing me a happy birthday
Is that okay?
[music]
It's birthday yeah yeah yeah, it's always Lyrica
That's Lyrica
Bye-bye, everyone!
Thank you so much for coming. Everyone is gone.
Aye, see you later
That's why I'm going to re-gross it right away.
The members came to visit us.It was great.
I'm happy.By the way, how nervous are you?
I've been here for about two hours now.
forever
Trembling all the time
It's warm now. Is everything okay?
Did you hear voices properly? Problem
Wasn't there one today?
It's my first time waiting for convex, so there are a lot of people.
Thank you for all your help up until now.
I would like to speak to people
Even Lyrica was a bit surprised.
Those many seniors and
Of course everyone from Rigros can go!
I was so excited when you said that.
We'll be spending some time together, but everyone
When Lyrica said it was dangerous, what should I do?
That help when you're wondering if it's okay
I would be happy if you could
Is that okay? Wait a minute, you're the first one.
towards
I would like to contact you
[music]
It's a little quick at Masua, but I'll call you soon.
I want to go
I think, wait a minute, it's true.
I was going to ask for icons and stuff.
But I was too nervous to show the icon.
Hi, I'm Ponkotsu. Hello, I'm the best Ponkotsu in the world.
Okay, let me say a little.
[music]
Can you hear me?
yes
Good evening
Good evening Iro
Happy birthday to my senpai, Ririka-chan.
Thank you very much
Actually, you were the first to
If you reply, I'll probably chat with you again.
return by number
You responded with a bang, right? I'm sure so.
Well, it's really impossible. Even one more person should come.
Even if you contact me in hopes that you will
Well, thanks to my senior's reply,
It looked amazing already, right?
Thank you for making my heart feel so warm.
Thank you very much.
I think the members of League Loss were there.
But this is my first time since my debut.
It's my birthday, so it's my first time.
I'm sorry about that.
Be the first person other than the regross members to clear that up.
I'm sorry I got it, it's the best
Thank you and happy birthday
Thank you very much Ha-senpai.
The same goes for many different broadcasts.
Let me go out with you and do things like this.
I heard you should get it, like an escape game.
Yes, we went to an escape game, and we also had dinner together.
Thank you for going there.
What is that about amusement?
What is that instead of poker?
Is that poker? Jack is black.
jack
It looks like my bra didn't come out, blackjack
We went together and stayed like cats.
I didn't play outside much.
I wonder if Licca-chan made this debut.
He comes in, so he's pretty much my junior.
Playing is a bit of a dream, but it's still fun
What can I say? Yes, it's a comment, so I
I don't feel that way at all right now.
No, isn't it? Is it true? You're so kind. I'm so happy.
Even though everyone was talking to me
I've had some time, so I guess it's okay now.
I wonder if they're still friends.
I'm pretty sure Ririka-chan is out there.
Please go out with me.
Thank you for always taking care of me.
Thank you for your help
I'm sure when I first started, cars were like this.
I don't know what it is, it's covered with something like a blanket.
I thought it looked like a really small animal and was cute.
Memories are coming back to me now
But there were really a lot of people at that time.
There's something wrong with that phrase.
Looks like the 8 of us are going to have a first time together.
There were 10 people in there.
There are probably 10 people here too.
There are about 3 more staff members.
Because of that, when something like that happened
There were 10 people. There were 10 people. There were 10 people.
Sorry, you just left us out of the picture.
Oh yeah yeah
That's right, I was nervous because there were so many people.
I did, but now it's amazing
As a senior, I don't know what to say.
I'm late, but I'll get along well.
I say it's almost a miracle that I was able to receive it.
I hope we can continue to be good friends.
I'll be happy if you do. I'm happy. I hope we get along well, Ririka.
chan just wanted to collaborate.
At the time you invited me, my body was dealing with a slightly different matter.
Looks like he's busy
Hehehe, I would love to see you too.
I would be happy if you could play with me.
Thank you very much.
Please promise me, I really do.
I'll check it most days and send it for several days.
Thank you for giving me so much
I said I wanted to play with you.
If you like what you gave me, let's do it.
Thank you, absolutely absolutely
I think you'll enjoy the mess too, so this is it.
It's not really torture for the head. No, it's not like that.
I don't think that's the case, senpai.
I'm going to have fun with you, my junior.
I won't give up, I'll do it when I have to do it strong.
Well, it's a game, I won't lose.
It's a competition in a good way, so please.
That's right, even today, I'm going to wait a little longer
I always heard that you work hard whether it's convex or reverse convex.
There's something I'm giving you for protection.
So I'll rent it today.
Thank you, even a little picture
It might be big
Akai Pokome
Naomamori Poko-chan, thank you very much
Thank you, please let me leave this here for a moment.
Once the mass has become too thick, boil it in the pot.
Thank you for staying warm
Thank you
Masu Nankane-chan is doing well.
Because everyone is kind, all the seniors are definitely kind.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, the first one.
Even though I'm a senior, I really did a million dances.
Is that true? Thank you very much.
I'm so happy that you invited me, thank you very much.
Thank you very much. See you soon.
Please, I'll give it to you after a little planning.
Yes please, please post this right away
Let's show everyone what I gave you.
Tada!
Everyone, I'll leave it here today while eating.
I want to know
Please do your best and once again, happy birthday!
Congratulations on a great year
Please, thank you Lyrica-chan
Please let me talk to you again.
Please, of course, thank you.
See you later, please excuse me.Yes, please excuse me.
[music]
Yes, Airoha-senpai was really kind.
And even a super cute Bokobe doll!
It's not the doll you gave me, pot.
No, I'm a little too nervous.
I was able to speak properly, so I was able to speak properly. It's okay.
That's it
Hahahaha you are so kind seriously
All the compliments are too kind and Riruka
I'm shaking. Please contact me only in hiragana.
I can't hit it
I'm shaking so much
Everyone's support made it okay.
becomes a strength
Hawawa
Wow, I guess I'll contact the next person.
I think so.
You are also a compliment.
It seems like it is
Ta
I'm a little nervous. Let's move on to the next one.
I would like to give a shout out
[music]
It's okay to spend a lot of time
mosquito
[music]
Well then, let me call the next person.
Itadaki
Masooisho
[music]
Hello, I can hear it
Yes, I can hear you, Ririka-chan.
Thank you very much for bothering me.
Thank you very much
I will provide an icon.
Thank you, no worries at all
Please come, Kaneda-senpai, who was a great junior.
Thank you very much.
[music]
Yaho, it's sunny. No, it's already a mess.
I was nervous and now my seniors are so kind.
It makes me nervous.
I think I'll get used to it when it gets quieter
I might be butt-to-butt with Kako's seniors.
I've been doing it for over a year, so yeah yeah yeah
Yeah, I'll be able to do it before I know it, but I still have a long way to go
It's not exciting time, I'm still excited
There's no need to be nervous about the time.
However, Ririka is also excited.
chan is precious right now, so on the contrary
That's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, one day
There is also a possibility that it feels like Kanata has come.
Yes, that day will come
Is there any chance that this will come at all?
We laughed together a few years after watching Lyrica-chan.
Please do it, even at times like that
At that time, I was already Katasekako-senpai.
I say senpai
It's fine, I'm happy to call you anything.
Thank you very much.
My senior is so kind, no, no, no
When the previous album was released,
I wonder if it was to that other senior, Rami-senpai.
Lyrica even when I saw that she was signing autographs.
Ririka can't even stand or stretch.
I definitely want the rhinoceros one
No, I can't even brazenly say that.
When I sent it to you, it was actually true.
I was wondering if I should give it to you without permission.
I stopped because I thought it was power harassment.
That's not the case at all, I'm glad
Thank you Nerika-chan
I also love Oracle and listen to it a lot.
Thank you for the animation, what a nice boy
That's right, Ririka-chan, you're such a good girl.
Yes he's a little too special
I'll give you a sexy picture, okay?
A little bit of this, a little bit of that.
Don't show your secrets, don't show them.
I know it's no good to show it.
I saw it
Yuka-chan, you can use this as sacred paper.
Yes, but this is just a lie
Isn't it included? No, this is the original.
It looks like an efg cup. Yes, yes, it's different now.
It's a bit scary, the oracle is playing for a moment
Better
Why is this different from Tao? It's true, true.
Yes, it's just a little bit.
Can I show you my brain?
I hope you all will be interested as well.
I want to speak directly to Lyrika's brain.
I think it's okay to send it as long as it's not in my head.
Hey, it's Seph, so no, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is good
I think this is just in my head.
from within the brain
It's not directly or it's not a lie.The sound is not a lie.
It's not a lie It's not a lie It's a lie
Ah, I guess I'm just dreaming.
Ka-chan, come with me, right?
Let's go out or do something together.
I've certainly never changed clothes.
So I don't know, so I guess that's what it is.
So, let's go out somewhere.
Let's do it, please do so.
In other words, an outing where you can see this swimsuit.
I'm glad you're going.
Of course, show me Licca-chan too.
It's shaking steadily.
I'm just continuing to do that.
Hey, I'm doing my best right now.
It's moving up and down. It's always moving.
I always end up looking at it because
I'm looking forward to it, please
Is this okay? That lyrica is that salt.
My mom hit me and almost killed me.
I'm not a girl like that.
It's not the person who hits you, but that studio.
I'm sure something will happen when it gets blown up.
I understand, let's leave it to the corporation.
Just use this as that poster.
Please share it with everyone, yes, in your mind.
Thank you for sharing it.
Thank you so much Ririka
Let's talk slowly. See you soon.
Please speak slowly, thank you.
thank you
I'll do my best, Viva. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Masuka-senpai was very kind though.
What the hell kind of poster is this?
Is it okay? I received a poster like this.
Is it okay?
mosquito
Wow, that was cool when I came here just now.
Sariri panicked and ran away.
It's a streamer
Too bad
The screen is becoming more and more chaotic.
Well then, there are so many of them today.
Someone is scheduled to come over there.
Let's just say a little more right away.
Slowly and slowly, I actually talk to each person one by one.
I wanted to, but I'll move on to the next person soon.
I will call you.
I'll have it
Good job
[music]
Lululululu
hello
Hello, Happy Birthday Ririka-chan!
Thank you for starting
I'm the group leader, and Noel-senpai is here.
Thank you for your kind support.
Yes, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
There's something I wanted to do, Noel-senpai.
Nie, that one came with bath salts or something like that.
Why are you finding out? I don't think so.
I just looked at it and saw it, oh, maybe this is it.
If it's Ririka's personality, I'll talk to you next time.
Sometimes they tell me I smell good
I thought so.
It was obvious.
The smell was great, it felt really good
But it's been a while since I've been back to normal.
I took a lot of showers, but that's okay.
Wake up to the comfort of that bath
I woke up and I've used it all up
Thank you very much thank you very much
I am very happy that you are using this.
I like it. I like a good confession.
From that to that hundred
Is your eardrum okay?
I'm worried about you too, Ririka-chan.
That's about it
It's like that 100, oh yeah, K, K.
It was totally fine, it's broken now.
Don't worry, I'm glad it wasn't.
If anything happens, I'll go and learn secrets with Ririka.
I'm going to go apologize for that.
Sarika-chan's secretary at the place
Minarai-chan is so amazing!
So, the next time we do that collaboration, we'll see.
Are your ears okay?Everyone seems to be nervous.
Please tell me it's okay and I can feel at ease
Please, thank you very much
I also want to play Monster Hunter with Noel-senpai.
Okay, I wonder how far I've gone yet.
I haven't cleared Iceborne yet.
If you clear it, they won't play with you.
I've always wanted to hear from you.
All right, even in Iceborne.
That's a good story, all by myself
What if that's what you want to do?
Don't collect any materials or borrow anything.
I would appreciate it if you could give it to me.
A glimpse of Ririka-chan's Moha broadcast
It's nice to be able to use a variety of weapons.
I wonder when was the last time I thought that?
I guess I just used a hammer.
It seems like the hammer is your favorite.
Yo, I did that hammer with Noel-senpai.
It's so much fun
I just did it, so let's do it with hammers
I would be happy if you could come and visit me.
Thank you so much for watching
Go ahead and have some fun
I'm just smiling, right?
Last time, I lost to Beriberos twice.
I was only one step away, it was such a shame.
Really try your best, it's beautiful, thank you very much
I'm so happy, no, no, no, that's it.
Yes, the basic benefits of the question seem to be completely different.
No, that's right, I was thinking of talking to you.
I heard about Sakatan the other day, right?
I heard about you, especially Katan.
We're already talking about posters.
It's such a good deal that it feels like it's a good deal.
It's a bit silly, but I'm sorry
I have never been asked if I recommend self-cooking.
Everything has disappeared since then.
It seems like I don't have enough time.
There are so many things I want to talk about.
I've been in so much trouble with Neto.
I don't want to speak slowly, but I recommend it.
It's recommended that men cook for themselves these days, after all.
I thought it would be nice to cook rice, so I made rice.
I'm addicted to frozen gyoza for both cooking and post-cooking purposes.
That's right, frozen gyoza and rice.
But I feel like I can live as long as I want.
That's what I think. Frozen dumplings are delicious.
That's right, it's already so crispy
From the leader's point of view, it has to be Uber.
I'm sorry, I made this myself.
But that's not self-catering at all.
I understand that Lili's self-catering is too low.
I thought I was going to get poked, but it's normal.
I'm sure it's because he rides on it.
Thank you. I'll freeze it for a bit.
I want to try some gyoza, I hope so soon.
It's easy to do, but recently I've noticed that it's burnt and scorched.
The gyoza doesn't splash, so please be sure to understand.
Please stand up, please take it easy next time
Let's talk, please. There are other things as well.
I think there are a lot of them, yes.
I'm sad to leave but thank you
I would love to see you again, Ririka-chan.
Congratulations and thank you
Thank you. Good luck. Excuse me.
I'm Noel Senpai.
What I wanted to tell you was revealed
Found out
There's no rehansa, just like this beforehand.
He said he thought he would listen to what he had to say.
There was one, but that
absolutely
I've become completely hopeless
I ended up not being able to understand God at all.
I would like to call the next person.
Thank you very much
[music]
Good job
Lululuaaaah can you hear me? I can hear you
button
It's your birthday, Senpai. It's your birthday today.
Congratulations, sorry, I'll just mirror stream
It was because I was in the middle of a long time ago.
Oh it's okay now it's okay now
Because I'm in an interview
Thank you, I'm doing well. I'm doing well.
Thank you very much, I'm really busy.
I'm so happy, it's okay
I'd love to have some meat with that button-senpai again.
I want to go eat Ririka, let's go eat meat.
I'll go whenever I want to eat meat.
I'll go again today
It's early today, I'll post it when I go today.
You're right, I found out
Button-senpai really
It was so cool in the beginning
I'm a cool senior, so I'm going to do something about it.
I thought I wouldn't be nervous, but I am.
When I actually talked to him, he was really soft.
It's gentle and soft, isn't it? It's soft, right?
really like
It looks so disgusting
Is that so? It's pretty sloppy, so
Even if it's sloppy, Ririkaririka is also sloppy.
I'm sure it's true that I can't lose.
Is it true or not? It's pretty accurate.
I have an image of it. Is it true? Yes, now.
Maybe I'm wearing it a little too well
The one who wears it seems like the one who first thinks of it.
The rust may gradually come off.
do not have
That may be true.
However, I couldn't listen to the talk deck at all.
I'd like to ask you one thing, okay?
I wonder if it's a little button button senpai
There's something I've always wanted to ask you.
Hey, that's what Button-senpai ate recently.
Delicious and recommended ramen
Isn't there something about that store's name?
I don't have to say it, so it's okay
Very rich salt ramen.
I wonder if the restaurant has salt ramen?
hey
Yeah, if it's a store, I can't go there after all.
I say it because it is something that everyone can get.
It's really good, yes, it's delicious.
Everything I ate was delicious.
No, I've never eaten Lyrica, actually.
I know, but
Well, have you ever eaten Umakacchan?
I have a memo that I have never eaten.
Umakacchan Umakacchan eat
I think I should keep it, I understand.
Of course other ramen that instant
Ramen is also delicious and there are many kinds.
There are so many things like that.
But things like Matai's boramen, yeah yeah
I want you to eat Umakacchan once.
Okay, I've been eating ramen lately.
I'm addicted to so many different ramen shops.
I'm going to San by myself.
I'm a bit of an idiot about ramen.
I was hoping you'd ask so thank you
By the way, I made it with less water, I understand.
The voice that was written was too small.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I'm serious, you know, that pork bone.
You can get rid of that smell with that instant ramen.
I think it's amazing, so I'm like, yeah, yeah.
By the way, I'll give it a ride as an extra.
Do you have to do something like that?If you have green onions and eggs, it's fine.
That's good, I understand. Green onion and egg.
Ukacchan eggs are seasoned eggs.
That's right, just boiled eggs or something.
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's normal now
I understand that just Ucchan is fine.
It tastes like egg fishing.
I can understand the taste of Gotsuri Gotsuri.
Thank you very much, I learned a lot
Then I definitely want to eat Umakacchan.
There are many different flavors of Masuone, but the first one is
I've already eaten denormal and understand what is denormal.
It really tastes like something
You don't have to eat it, so it's really normal taste
Please eat it, yeah, it's normal.
Eating Uma-chan, it's delicious
Please go to other flavors after that.
I understand, you're a great professional.
I'm sure it's Nakanaka.
Thank you for yes sorry
Even though it was being distributed, please check it out again.
I wish I had a chance to relax slowly.
I'm happy. Yes, that's right. Thank you very much.
Please yes thank you
Thank you again. See you soon.
Hey, excuse me bye
Bona I've never eaten Baoumakacchan
Senpai, that's a really good idea.
Ta
That's great, that's great, that's great
Hey, thank you, Bota-senpai.
No, boil the water
I'll boil the water.
I can't wait to move on to the next one, everyone today.
I'm so angry that I feel like it's okay
I think it must be difficult to keep up with that.
But thank you very much.
Okay, then I'd like to call the next person.
thought
[music]
Happy birthday, Ririka-chan
Thank you, Azuki-senpai is here.
Thank you for your help.
It's been a long time since I last talked to you, my senior.
It's New Year's Day at my house, isn't it?
Tea party Tea party or Asoka tea party is better later.
It might have been like that, but neither.
I'm sure it's impossible to do an off-collaboration.
Looking at it, this kind of online collaboration
Maybe it's my first time, I guess it's true
It's my first time to do it and talk about it online.
That's a surprise, thank you very much.
Thank you so much Aki-senpai.
Also the 1 minute getter that I did just the other day.
I really went to a professional place, Ririka.
I was watching you do it. I'll show it to you now.
It's really already dangerous.
But are you okay? I have a headache.
So you become a genius, right?
That's right, that's right, let's start from here.
There's still a bit of growth to come.
Let me play with that Holomen map.
Actually, it's already black, so I guess that's it.
DM to talk about this Nea no Gyakutsuri
When I received it, I thought, ``This looks like it, Ririka.''
I thought Azuki was doing chanjigesu.
I made a hollow map, Ririka
I'm just thinking of giving it a try.
Please let me know that I introduced you.
I really want to be able to clear it now
I'm thinking of making it
I'm eating spirit anytime, anytime
I'm coming, thank you very much
Very
Thank you very much Iato Neso
I want Azuki, right?
That limitless meal I got for New Year's
I'm wondering when to use my gift certificate.
Yes, that's what he said.
Hey, congratulations on reaching 1 million people.
I thought it would be okay to use it when I sent it to you.
I'll think about it, resize it, and sell it soon.
Please come and visit us again.
collaboration
So let's do an offline collaboration and Geogestar would be good too.
Well, let's do it together, please.
Please, I'm so happy and looking forward to it.
I'm so happy to see Jige doing it.
I felt really happy.
I'm so happy, I want to see your senior's work.
That's what I thought, so I thought I'd be happy
When I thought about it, I was completely surprised.
I'll do my best from now on
Will you get better? The more you do it, the more you do it.
I'm getting better. I've seen this scenery before.
I see it feels like
Is that what it's like even on billboards now?
The blue signboard looks like it has great information.
Since it has become
It came from that, so I know it came from that.
Please let's play together in a little collaboration.
I would be happy if you could give it to me. Please click here.
Thank you very much, thank you, pioneer
Lyrica too so that everyone in the group doesn't blow bubbles.
I'll take care of that lyrica.
I'm glad there's a place to go around.
Please take a look at that Holomen map.
I think I'd like to get it.Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
I think it's going to be tough after that, but please do your best.
I'll do my best, thank you again
Please make it a wonderful year. Yes, it's already wonderful.
It's starting to be a year, thank you very much
See you soon. Let's play again. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
[music]
Masu Azuki-senpai is coming.
Very
kind
I'm happy and happy
Moreover, Lyrica is completely alone.
Map I was thinking of doing that, but you invited me.
I'm really glad I got it
I feel happy
True purity
Ririka also does her best to keep things neat and clean.
[music]
I have to
Okay, it's really full of angry waves.
Thank you for hearing from me a lot.
I feel so happy that I'm here, and I'm looking forward to the next one.
Also contact your seniors
Please let me know if you don't mind
Please take care of me.
Try your best to be neat That's right, try your best to be neat
I'll be your next senior.
also call
[music]
Mashimoshiaaaaaaaaa
a
Ririka-senpai, hey, hey, happy birthday.
But say yes
Yes, that's how you felt
Well, it wasn't like this.
It's a little different, my interpretation was a little different.
That's the explanation that's coming out, it's so weird
Should I do it? Hahaha, over there.
I think it's better, but I'm currently on the path of Shura.
It makes me feel lazy, but it shines brighter that way.
Is it Lili?
What did you do? That icon is a little scary.
It doesn't appear, but the icon of my senpai is
My computer has turned into an hourglass.
I'll give you some cute pictures, okay?
Yay, cute photo, is it really cute?
Are you giraffeing?
Giraffa, I pasted a normal one.
This is so cute, but it's better not to say it yet
Well, those who don't spoil the story before releasing it.
I would like to release this
[music]
Let me give a shout out to you all.
hand
Very
It was a lie, I thought you were talking like that.
I was lying so much
This is so disgusting, which one is it, which one is it,
Which is the real Lyrica?The real Lyrica is
Maybe this one is better than the other one?
No, that's not true.
But haha, now I'm on board
Cute new thing that came out the other day
Her stomach is also a little more sexy.
This hairstyle is also a bit disappointing, after all Rika
In that tower
This cute baby's frilly fingers are frilly.
Fluffy, fluffy, it's so cute
No, it's amazing, she looks like a little girl
I've grown so much that I've been told that I look like an older sister.
But that was also really cute for Lyrica.
I can see it
Mommy can't sleep for some reason because I'm a bit nervous right now.
It's like, oh mom, Lili can't sleep.
mama's pachocho
That's how you live your life
That means you should come, right? Lyrica too.
Yes, that's right, but Nachichishiyoi, Ririka
With Hanehai Ano Mae Saomaru and the others
When we talked, it was about the departure and arrival system.
Yeah yeah yeah it was really interesting so I'm happy
But at that time, I was really able to show my true self.
I thought, wow, I have no worries.
I feel like I was allowed to talk, which is great.
I was so happy, let's play again
Please, please, please, it's all good
Yay!
It's just lilikaririka ASMASM.
I love you, so yeah, hey, hey 9 pairs.
Is it about 1 yen?
balance
I understand that it's 9 to 1.
It means adding ventilation and aiming for gap moe.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Okay, leave it to me, Ririka, go.
Masuodoya Nice Doyae By the way, a little
I'd like to ask you, Senpai, but what have you eaten recently?
Please tell me something delicious
What delicious thing did Anene eat recently?
Well, I ate a fruit sandwich.
Hey, it's a fruit sandwich that I've never had before.
I'm not that good at whipped cream
That's why I haven't been able to do anything until now.
I was avoiding it but huh huh uh uh uh
A line drawing shop that is famous for its fruit line drawings.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, there.
The edible fruit sandwich looks disgusting.
It's a little expensive, but it's really
It seems to be delicious. I want to try it.
By the way, what kind of fruit sandwich did you choose?
I'll eat it, it's a mix of various things.
I see, they're not going to give us the ones that are.
There are various kinds of things in there.
Not, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, I understood the mix from the beginning.
Let's go eat. I want to go eat together.
Let's go
I'm so happy! It was super delicious!
Oh no, I like it, but it's hard
After all, I didn't have a chance to go out to eat.
It's hard to go in alone, isn't it?
Show me, I get it, I get it, I get it
That's why I tended to go far away.
Well then, please come with me next time.
Let's be fashionable, let's do it.
Yan
Thank you very much, I feel happy
Thank you for this.
Can I leave it alone for today?
Finally done it
Happy Birthday 1
I turned 23.1 years old.I was 23.1 years old.
Congratulations thank you very much
Let's play again. Please play again.
Thank you very much
[music]
[applause]
It's been a while since I talked to Nene and my senior.
I feel like you can still call me Nenechi.
You told me that, but I don't understand.
I don't know what to call it, but it's a bit like this
I wonder if it's okay for me to be hesitant, even though I'm a senior.
It has that kind of feeling, and the picture is amazing.
happy
It's easy to call it, it's easy to call it.
My heart is pounding
I'm just trying to remind my next senior.
I would like to do this.Everyone has a good heart.
Are you ready? Is everyone ready?
I don't prepare, Lyrica does it.
Please let me relax
[music]
Masu
I'm excited about Shirika-chan's birthday
Thank you very much
It feels like it's been a while since I've seen you, senpai.
It's true, Lyrica-chan. It's been a while.
It's been a while, what have you been up to lately?
I've been playing a lot of games and it's great.
That's great, it's been a long time, really.
Yes, we did an off-collaboration the other day, and since then
Opportunity to talk slowly, not much.
I forgot about the offline collaboration the other day
Maybe I'm missing a lot of collaborations.
When and when are you going to beco off with someone?
Was that there? Who was there?
After all, that wasn't Beko's senior.
Well, it was when we had a tea party, Kanata-senpai.
When are you talking about that?
When was that? It must have been a long time ago.
I'm so crazy. I can't remember anymore.
But I forgot about it.Recently, I don't like it.
You should have coke the club properly.
I forgot about that Imaishi, I'm sorry, the flow of time
It's already so fast that it feels like it was just yesterday
It's so hard to remember, I panicked for a moment
I can't believe it was so white.
No, it's Pecola-senpai's birthday.
Quite a while ago, 4 months, 4 months ago.
Just stroking it reminds me of yesterday's house.
Surprised, I opened the fridge and put the cake in it.
Pecola-senpai noticed that I was still there.
I remembered this and got up from my seat with a disgusted look on my face.
Beko-senpai, I hate that awkward guy.
Thank you so much for that time too.
Thank you very much.
I have something I would like to ask Pecola-senpai.
Okay, please, I'm already messed up.
A long time ago, that Pecola-senpai was broadcasting on the 1st.
Eating that cream cheese once
I heard you say things like happiness.
It happened, it was amazing, I knew it, yes.
Yeah, it's also a mess.
I think Pekora-senpai is amazing.
Wow, what's amazing? It's so short.
I felt it too, Pecola-senpai and Ririka-chan too.
I like Kiri's stuff, I really like it.
Wow, that looks delicious
It's really delicious, I think.
I've been having some extra lately.
I ate some food recently and it was delicious.
It's fine if you have something, but if something happens
I've been thinking that I'd really like to hear about it, so I recently found out...
It seems like there are some people who are into it lately.
Honestly, things have been a little cheesy lately.
I'm sorry for being like that, but I like Chi.
Remember, I like cheese a lot.
But that 7-Eleven is currently increasing the amount.
Is it some kind of campaign?
But that cheesecake is quite pecola.
Yeah, it was a huge hit and I'll be using it next time.
I want Lyrica-chan to buy it too.
Okay, I just looked it up and found this.
It's like a toro raw texture cheesecake.
Cat, I understand, don't worry again.
I feel like I'm going to eat it and eat it again.
Be careful, don't eat too much
But it came with 2 pieces, so after eating 1 piece,
It's good because I can still eat one more piece.
I can eat one more. I can eat one more now.
I'm in the happy period, so I want you to grow up a little bit.
I understand Pepa, I will definitely eat it.
Thank you very much
Thank you, please play with us again
Please, bye-bye. Excuse me.
Masu Pecora-senpai is coming.
Tacha messed up
I'm happy, wait a minute, wait a minute
Those things are coming from my senior now.
[music]
Okay, okay, okay, late, late, Lily.
But I can't multitask so I have to type
It's already been 50 minutes.
But for Achinami, that day
I thought it was that one hour time slot, but it's true.
A lot of seniors came to that place.
That 2 hours and 3 slots because I decided to give it to you.
At that time, around 50 to 6 minutes,
I would also like to introduce
So, this is the next senior in front of the goods.
It has become
It's so good, it's so good, it's so good
So, I would like to call you right away.
Everyone was so angry that I wondered who would come next.
I'm sorry, I don't have much time to make predictions.
Yone Okakeshi
[music]
Masu happy
Birthday Rika Happy Birthday Spar
Thank you senior and congratulations
Congratulations, I'm so happy for that Lyrica
What's wrong with Suba-senpai?
She's really a woman who sucks a lot.
I did something I'm sorry for to Lyrica.
This is my first time gambling.
Wasn't gambling good, Lyrica?
No, I really want to do it again sometimes.
Now it's blackjack
I went there one more time after Tesaa.
After that, I left my Subaru there and went there once.
That's just how it is, senpai.
Please tell me where you want to go.
I'm so happy together
Let's gamble, let's gamble, but
If that Lyrica starts to get dangerous, stop it.
You can also request a set including
No, that's impossible. Subaru has to stop too.
Hey
I can't stop, I can't stop.
There was no way I could stop it, it was no good.
It's over now. Really. Just a moment.
I was able to put it out, no, it's already Swaru-senpai.
Ririka took me to that meal for the first time.
Wow, the senior who gave it to me
Nostalgic, I went, I went, already collaborated.
It looks like there will be Yakiniku of Ichi in front of it.
I really feel nostalgic about Lyrica from back then.
Subaru Senpai Doco Love is old, but it's okay.
Kanae I'm so happy thank you Lyrica thank you
Thank you very much.
I'm so nervous today, I can't take it anymore
That's right, it's not that bad, Lyrica is confident.
Thank you very much for taking it with me so suddenly
I'm worried that I'll end up dying
It's bad to suddenly leave the country.
There will also be announcements of dangerous goods, so after this cat.
That's right, when can I start looking forward to it?
Well, I was told to be by 8 o'clock.
Oh okay, it's totally okay.
Because senpai is important
Thank you, but I don't like it.Goods from my seniors
Is that true because winning is important?
I'm serious about doing it in time.
Thank you for your advice
Yes, no, no, it's important, isn't it? Goods?
I definitely picked up a lot of them.
And it's my first time, so it's the first month or the first time for Lyrica.
I'm a little nervous, then I'm excited
By the way, it's kind of nice
I also want to ask Kawa-senpai about food.
The recommended food is different.
I would like to ask Subaru-senpai about cooking for himself.
You ask Bakasubaru about self-catering?
I said, Are you okay? On the contrary, I said, I thought it was the other way around.
No, this is rude, maybe it's rude, what should I do?
No matter what, what level is Lyrica in Subaru?
What level of cooking do you think it will be?
That's right, see Ririka's cooking at Subaru Maji.
Well, it doesn't look that bad.
But sometimes I feel like I eat like this.
There are times when I think
So we were eating together at our limit.
That's right, rice is packaged rice after all.
No, packaged rice is the best, isn't it? Chee for 3 minutes.
The food you can eat is so amazing! It's the best!
That's too much, so Subaru will give it to you.
There was nothing about self-catering anymore.
There's only so much I can bestow on you.
It was good that it was only for one person.It was not good.It was not good.
I think so
Is it okay, Soba-senpai?
If you want to make some kind of rice, try Lyrica.
I can't wait to think that I might be able to make one.
I heard it, it won't change, that's for sure
The opposite I think I can make
It doesn't change, so I don't buy it, so I see.
That's right, we're pack rice companions.
What foods do you recommend?
Is that true? Please let me know.
Please, that's spaghetti.
Delicious bread punch with Pancho E Papancho
What is that? I've never heard of it.
Patti's Punch you don't know when you hear it for the first time
I've been saying curry for a long time now.
But it's still spaghetti pancho
Let's eat at a Neapolitan restaurant
Yeah, it's decided, seriously.
Most of the shops called Umeee are located underground.
It's common, but it's seriously delicious.
Yes, yes, yes, this is it.I recommend self-cooking.
Yes, it's going to be somen from now on.
I understand, so let's eat somen noodles.
All you have to do is eat Neapolitan punch.
Well, I think that's because it's noodles.
That's too extreme, isn't it?
Looks like you'll be covered in noodles.
If you have time, let's go get some punch.
I want to go with you.
Yes, yes, please, please, punch
Please take me with you, I can go as many times as I want
Take me with you, it's already a promise.
You didn't take me with you, please take me with you, Senpai.
I'll just say you didn't give it to me.
What is this negative campaign? It's so boring.
I stopped negative campaigning, so I went to Punch during the day and then at night.
Its so nice to eat somen with Lyrica, its the best
Maybe
No, that's good. Please eat it to the limit.
Please, let's eat together. Let's eat together.
Well then, Riruka, it's about time to make an announcement.
Wouldn't it be better to do this?
I'll read the mood and give chase.
I'm very happy. Please come again.
Let's go eat some Masusome!
[music]
It was Subaru's senior, as expected.
Time keeping senior
Subaru-senpai
My seniors are always so kind and helpful.
Seriously, she's really sweet and kind, but
I'm really sorry that my senior was so considerate.
Even though you told me, you still have Lyrica goods
It would be a shame if I didn't introduce the goods, so I'll also introduce the goods.
Please let me do this. It's still in progress.
Everyone relax a little bit about that.
I hope you will listen to it.I will announce it here.
Masu Ririka's birthday goods are on sale now.
Oh wait a minute, that's not right. That's not right.
Lyrica's birthday goods are out
Do-don-do-do, a little something else
But it got mixed up.
Let me prepare the birthday goods.
I've received it now.
URL
Make the URL a fixed comment
Is this a good link? Is it possible to fly this link?
I wonder if I can fly but I'm sorry this is 8 o'clock
Because it's empty, it's still
Yes, still.
So let me give you a little more detailed explanation.
I'll have it though
too
This is what a set of Yoishoe goods looks like
Acrylic panel square can
Batch Genkai Meal T-shirt and we'll always be together
3 types of plush keychain voices
It is a bonus voice for the voice card.
If I explain the details in more detail, then
This is the full set of that Lyrica.
Special voice and a bit of that color.
A postcard with such a cute expression is available!
Follow me and there I will be filled with Lyrica's love
The signature is included and the illustration is included.
I wrote this for my teacher.
The super sexy Lyrica I received made me happy.
It is a birthday illustration.
And here is the can badge.The can badge is
Because all of those Rigros are matching.
It would be better if everyone had it together like this.
All of the Rigros feel like Sada
It is shaped so that it can be elevated.
Marginal Meal T-shirt This is a special point
Here's that cute wiener
Here is a picture of the rice on top.
It's a bit plump, so it's a wiener
It's so plump that there's a limit in the back.
It says "look at me and don" so that's it.
If you look at it from before, you can use it for everyday use.
That slightly stylish wiener T
Don't worry, it's a shirt
Please give me this plush toy.
That Lyrica is so cute too
It is a stuffed toy that has been finely adjusted.
Surprisingly large, the size of Ririka's palm
It's about the same size as Ririka's palm.
It can also be used to think that this is about it.
No, you can use it for everyday use, but it's a little more expensive.
I want to be as cute as possible from the start.
She's cute, but I have to adjust the position of her mouth somehow.
Added various small adjustments such as
And the voice is this ASMR voice
That's U100, I guess it's through rumors.
I also took pictures of other things.
There are various slightly stylish voices.
So I would like you to listen to this.
It feels like
Thank you very much.
What should I do? It's so small somewhere.
Let's put it out like this
Put it out like this
Thank you very much for your support.
Sorry, the URL is broken.
Teru
[music]
Oishio, I'll try again in a bit.
Oisho
And I guess the characters are a bit garbled.
I tried pasting it again
And that full set is autographed.
It becomes
By all means, please
Please feel free to pick it up
I'm happy
Please let me call you
[music]
and
And after this, I would like to congratulate many seniors.
Please, actually, Rigro-chan and the others too.
I wanted to include Doshishiroshi-chan's 5
I couldn't prepare icons for people.
Well then, just a little bit
I wonder why the URL is not working right away.
[music]
Well then, please let me call the next person.
Hello, can you hear me?
Thank you for your hard work, Moshi Moshi Sora Senpai.
Sorry I'm late, thank you
Happy birthday goods are cute
thank you
I'm so happy to be with that Lyrica Solo senior.
I want to play darts. Let's just die.
Last time we played darts together, I was able to give you a present.
Looks like it was good. It's already a mess.
He gave me a cute present.
I guess it's not, but actually it's still a bit
I haven't been able to use it since then.
I want to use it, so please come again
Let's go together, please do it.
I'm very happy thank you
And I heard that it's okay to go upside down over there.
I was so happy to receive it. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your help.
So, it would be nice if you could say thank you for your help.
I've been treated extremely kindly.
Karaun yeah yeah yeah Lyrica is that.
I'm still planning a lot of meals.
I've been planning a meal for the past few weeks.
I don't have one, but I want to continue doing it.
I'm thinking of a meal plan
Oh, it's a limit meal, it's a limit meal, right? It's a limit meal.
Are you interested? Did you eat the limit food?
I'm not good at eating food though.
I like eating rice I like eating rice
I see, that's right. Senior Seo is amazing.
I thought I was good at cooking, but I'm actually not good at cooking.
I'm a friend, my brownie exploded.
I made a cake that looked like it was going to explode and it exploded.
You're saying things like you did.
I'm sorry, but it might just be a delusion.
It's not an explosion, it's that gatochocolat
A long time ago, I wanted to think about it as a plan.
Ah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, what's the temperature?
I thought it would only get to 100 degrees.
Yeah, yeah, you can't get the temperature above boiling.
Yes, because I thought it was 100 degrees.
I'll bake it in the oven for a few minutes.
If you answer something like that, it's like
Looks like I can't do it
It makes me wonder what happened to it.
I don't like the big water, but I heard something about it now.
Tete and Lyrica seem to be able to do that too.
I honestly thought, "Oh no, that's no good."
That would make it feel like
Because I'm fighting, I feel the hottest.
It seems that water boils at 100 degrees.
I was doing it like that, so it's kind of funny.
The cake is amazing.The cake is amazing.
It's dangerous, it's difficult, it's chocolate so it's even more difficult
Well, I feel like my dick is going to get really hot.
Isn't that what I'm saying? It's a bit of a point of contention.
I might be wrong, but somehow
Something like that inside me
It's so scary that I got the answer.
I don't know what I'm cooking now, but I don't know.
Since we're talking, you can't even comment.
No, that's not true.
I can't even say it, it's like, ``Ahmuhuhumuhuh.''
I feel like
There's something wrong with the temperature.
I see, it seems expensive.
It's expensive, so I learned a lot. Thank you.
I don't remember when it will be next time.
Let's make a mishmish dessert
I made it explode again by making a mimish cake.
It can't be helped
But I think it's good to try sweets.
I love it
Victim to be eaten by Karayatchoja
I hope you will think about it again with me.
You're always calling me, yes, yes, usually.
I haven't called. I haven't called. Not always.
But I call you sometimes
Sorry I wasn't detailed
No, it's interesting thank you very much
Happy birthday thank you
Please come and play with me again.
Please, there is one tomorrow.
Yay, there'll be one tomorrow.
Let's get lost. It's my first time so I'm looking forward to it.
It's seriously something I've never done before.
I only know enough to understand
Let's do our best together Thank you
Let's do our best. See you tomorrow.
death
I'm so tired
[music]
Yes, Sora-senpai came.
Very
Kind, no, kind, kind, Sora Senpai, cooking, cooking
My friend Sora-senpai is so cute!
I also received a message from Lyrica's angel.
I'm going to go there, I'm going to go there, there's going to be a lot of things.
They are coming.
Ariihawa
[music]
Lily, please introduce yourself.
First of all, Hololive Airi-san, please come.
Zeta of
is
Don't call me cute Rika Rika.
I was going to say Zeta-chan from Lyrica.
But Lyrica's
That cute thing became a thing before I knew it
Nattae is doing an off-collaboration at my house for the first time.
When you came to visit me
That's right, it's been my birthday ever since then.
Thank you for your congratulations
Tesonochie
Hey hey, this or something else
Acha X's X's
A little bit next to Saya's senior
Hey, hey, hey
Terue yay that Neri-chan dog song
I'll sing your birthday song, thank you.
Yes, please turn off the BGM.
No, no, the BGM is okay, it's okay, it's a lie
Why no, no, no, no
Landa
[music]
Lili loves landau
Chan
Wow, I also played an SE of applause.
It's so cute and I even love it
Thank you for giving it to me, I'm so happy
No, I already have a nice present.
This is a present, this is a present.
Even though it's not there, there's a difference, this, this, this
Thank you, you're so cute, just now
put it on screen
On the screen like this, like this
Oishio, wait a minute, it's so messed up
So cute, I'm so happy no no no no a little
hang on
[music]
It's not open, it's open.
Teyoishochachachacha
By the way, you wrote this.
Thank you very much for Zeta-chan to write that.
Cute Happy Busday Lili-chan written
Subscribe
Adaki saw that
Odate
Lyrica is an English listener
It was discovered that I was putting pressure on Mr.
Thank you, Irumi, for registering properly.
Thank you
Masue is so cute thank you very much
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I definitely fell again
I'll go home for a while before you come visit me.
I'll leave it sparkling clean for you to stay overnight.
It's okay to sleep over, but of course it's okay to sleep over.
I wonder if it's okay if I come to see you. I'm so excited.
Can I sleep?
Let's sleep together. I'm happy to sleep together.
Thank you, I promise, no matter how scary it is
But don't run away from home
Uh, please, I'm coming, even if it's dangerous.
Spin and play, play, play, play, play
Thank you, I will treasure this image a little.
I'll display it here, okay?
Thank you, let's play again
Thank you for playing
Thank you, let's go get some food.
Let's definitely
Let's go, see you, bye-bye
bye happy birthday
Senkyu Kai
Messed up
She's so cute that I turn on the BGM
I forgot
[music]
Wow, that guy who sang it earlier.
Please cut that out and send it to Lyrica.
I would be happy if you could give me the screen
There are so many really cute things
Is it okay to be this happy?
Probably
A little bit
Can I call you next time?
[music]
Pururu
Hello Happy Birthday You Happy
birthday u happy birthday dear
lyrica
Chi happy
Happy birthday
My
Is that a tambourine? Is it a bell?
I've been waiting for that, thank you so much
Congratulations! I'm so happy!
I was surprised. It's okay. It's amazing.
Amazing, the sound was absolutely perfect.
But I was already surprised by the sudden appearance of Asuka and Suzu.
My eyes were already starting to twitch.
Thank you so much Congratulations
I'm happy to meet my senior Lyrica and Pokemon.
Please give me a card, Ayaro Yogekageka.
Is there a deck? Is there a deck?
Wow, tell me what deck you got.
Charizard deck and what is that?
Too bad I forgot about that ice cream.
That blizzard of the Four Heavenly Kings has fangs.
I'm sorry, I'm a pazin with fangs.
Hmm, I suddenly forgot my name. Just memo memo.
So why pretend that you can counter it?
Even if you look like you're strong, you're strong.
I really wanted to win the deck.
I'm preparing my deck, so it's really strong.
It's strong, I'm told it's really strong.
But is Lugia somehow stronger now?
I don't know what's going on. I was with Mu for a while.
Maybe it was strong, yes, yes, that's right.
But yeah, it's amazing how strong she is despite being cute.
Raku Ade Ririka That battle experience is almost zero.
So I've only run it by myself.
It's my birthday and I'm in tears
Raden-chan doesn't know the rules at all
I think I've only done that once.
You are not zero, but you know the rules
I've never played with someone like that, so I'd love to play against them.
Thank you very much Wamowa Memone Rules
Do it with a love you don't know, I lost.
That's right. I lost. Even then.
It's good to have fun, no, it's the best to have fun
That's right, then come on over for a second.
Is it okay if I get a present?
Is it okay?Presentation
I gave it to you as a gift, Mame-senpai Noe.
I'll take a moment to say this
So let's play with this!
Please definitely take a look
It's hard to make a mistake like that
Strategy no way
Nohahaha
This may be a strategy.This may be a strategy.
It's a battle that can't be won
It's pitch black in front of me, but it's just like this
It's okay to wear it like sunglasses.
Birthday glasses on a scolded head
I'm sorry, but it's all about this one.
Can I say that she's 100 times cuter?
I don't know but it's really cute
This is my favorite so why did it bother me?
Thank you both
Thank you very much. See you again soon.
Please come and play with me even though you are busy.
Thank you so much Ekogoso
Let's go eat, I promise again.
That's a promise. Thank you for the birthday wishes.
I'm so happy then.
Please eat that lamb meat with mutton.
I'm sorry I'm going home I'm sorry I'm sorry
No, don't go.
I want to drop my senpai, or my missing one.
It's gone.
Yodou each other
What's going on?
[laughter]
[applause]
That's sad, I felt a little dangerous.
It seems like lamb meat goes well with mutton.
hey
It was mutton. It was safe. Mutton is also sheep.
Isn't that mutton?
Your stomach is very nice.
The nice guy also sent me another one.
Let's ask Mame-senpai to draw this too.
Okay, wait a minute, it's a sheep.
Both of them were sheep, right? Is that so?
Well, like this
Okay, Matamame-senpai is not mutton.
There is a difference between
Various things
I didn't know
Please give a shout out to the next person.
Now that I'm done, I can't get enough lyrica anymore.
Let's spend more and more time alone
I should have kept it longer
It's my first time colliding, so I don't know anything anymore.
I haven't
It's so stupid, it's just cute
This is cute, wait a minute
And it's my first birthday, so
Time keeping is a bit of a mess
Well, I'd like to give a shout out to the next person as well.
[music]
Good luck
Hello, you can hear it.
[music]
Maybe happy
Thank you for your birthday Roboco
My senior came, Ayane.
Thank you so much cute roboto senpai
I love it so much it really melts in my mouth
I had plans to have dinner with Rika.
I can't meet you, that's right
I wanted to go for dinner. Let's go for dinner next time. Definitely.
By all means, yes, really, that mahjong launch.
I think you said let's do it.
That's right, only Ririka's schedule doesn't match up.
I want to go next with Uguguzuguzugonex.
Please let's eat together again, what do you like?
What does Nano Ririka like? Ririka
I'm a gourmet and I like anything really delicious.
But yeah yeah yeah yeah but
Lately, I've been eating a lot of meat.
My heart is filled with happiness when I
Hey, what a shame, all I ate the other day was meat.
Why are you saying that now? Forgive me.
I really wanted it. I wanted to eat it.
Oni
Let's go to Yakiniku again.Please take me with you.
Please come with me. Let's go.
That same pot that Robo-senpai made.
I want to eat hotpot.
Yeah, what are you laughing at?
That's suspicious
Are you really good at something? Because you're good at something.
First, buy some healthy vegetables and eat them.
If you put it in, you win, so there's such a thing as a win.
That's probably the only thing I'm good at.
It's too interesting and I'll leave it to you for a while.
I feel like an old man after eating that Lyrica hot pot.
Are you saying that I like that rice?
It's really delicious, isn't it? Rice bowl
It's delicious and easy to eat, but you can do it yourself.
When I tried to make it, it was kind of messy and dirty.
It turned out to be so I asked them to make me something.
Takute Ririka is probably worse than me
Puei iya iya iya iya iya Senior is barely able to
I feel like I'm winning No, no, no, I'm the one
I'm looking forward to showing you the perfect
Thank you very much, please
Let's give it as a birthday present
Well, I'm really happy that I did it.
Thank you, I'll do my best to clean the room and wait.
Let's just keep this place clean, Lyrica.
I'm the type that doesn't mind even if it's dirty.
When are you going to get serious?
Yakiniku Revenge and Yakiniku Revenge
Let's go double, double, please.
Shimasuoto
Thank you for enjoying it
See you soon
[music]
Yes, Roboko-senpai is kind.
Hey, that's a lie. That's rude. It's bad. That's what I meant.
I wasn't kidding, but I didn't mean it that way.
I did
Because it was unexpected
Aru Bobo Bobo, it's so nice and messed up
Yatate is good, no, Roboko-senpai has been doing something lately.
So, I often give him something that looks like a goldfish.
I feel like I'm actually winning in real life.
It was something like an app.
I thought he was winning live.
Yes, I thought it was amazing. Yes, goldfish.
Amazing!
keep a cute goldfish
So, I'll call out to the next person.
Keep it
Tsutsu
My heart is really broken now
It's so warm, no, Ririka. To be honest, it's already half and half.
About the following people came
I feel so happy if you give it to me.
Because I was coming
Looks good
Yes really
Full of happy and happy feelings
[music]
Looks like it's too much
Okay, but you're still here, seniors.
Are you here?
We look forward to seeing you at
[music]
Don't give up, it's too bad, let's move on to the next one.
I'll call my senior
hey
Lululululu
Hello, happy birthday, Fu-senpai.
Happy ugly day thank you
Please call me, no no no no.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you very much
I'm happy to talk to you. It's been a long time since I've seen you.
Let's play together before we meet again
It was winter in December when I came to Japan.
From about that much to that much
It's been like this since December
That might be the case, I'm surprised
Please play with me again, just once.
I had a promise to play with you on the way, but
Lyrica's plans suddenly conflicted.
I put it away and it didn't work, so I got some revenge.
I definitely want to do that.Okay then.
I want revenge
I'm so happy, but I don't need to go through the trouble.
I've been saying this for a long time, Licca-chan.
I'm sorry, but I'll have a drink with you someday.
yeah
at
Thank you so much, Lyrica.
Ioffe-senpai did an illustration for that Lyrica.
You wrote it, didn't you? Yamada.
I'm on my way, don't watch it, don't watch it, don't watch it yet
forget about it
I went back from my memory and examined it from what I found out from my memory.
Bibibibibi was so cute it was super
I'm looking forward to it so thank you very much
Thank you so much, you're so cute
I'm going to do it, so I'm going to do it.
No, it's already so cute
As expected, I'm already good at drawing.
I knew it, but it's so delicious and cute
I think it's too much
Teiyane, I guess she started drawing after all.
Yes, recently, but before that,
I guess it'll be something like Fufufus Fifth after all.
I don't have much time to spend on it because
It's over as soon as it's gone
Wait a minute, there will be another painter.
After all, it's been a while
Hey Erica, hey model
I made it and I'm really happy
I'll continue to write more, thank you
Thank you I'm so happy
Licca-chan is chasing cute things
I'm already looking forward to the completion
I am giving it as a birthday present.
Yay, what's that? Also talk about otome games.
Let's win, let's win.
Let's win, that guy, Senpai.
Lili, who recommended it to me, actually bought it.
Yes, I bought it, so I haven't tried it yet.
I don't have one, but I bought it that way, so I bought it that way.
I'll definitely talk to you about it, thank you very much.
Nice to meet you, everyone.
I'm sure you don't know anyone else
Hey, just say something.
Channikachan, I know you're doing this.
Huh?
Surprisingly, we really know each other very well.
He said he was surprised.
We're otome game friends, after all. Even after Neko.
I'm going to Japan a little bit this year too.
I'll bring you some souvenirs, thank you.
I'll definitely try something else then.
Lyrica also has some good Japanese things.
I'll prepare it so that I can give it to you as a gift.
Please come and visit us again next time.Let's go have fun.
I'm going to visit you. Thank you.
Thank you so much Neko Do this Holo
It's my first birthday at the live show.
Hey, that's right. It's already my first birthday.
I'm so busy today
I was like, "Oh no, oh no!" and I was already so popular.
Thank you everyone for being so popular
I'm really happy that you're so kind, you're so cute
Thank you very much for being so kind.
I'm looking forward to lunch too, Rika.
I'm looking forward to it
Thank you thank you
See you soon.Let's talk slowly.Let's meet again.
Please play with me.
[music]
Iofie came again.
Japanese is too good. Is it really true?
ID and en seniors use this honorific language in English.
Well, that doesn't exist, there is no concept.
That's why Lyrica also speaks a little English.
It's a little bit because I'm thinking about it while talking.
It's easy to speak without using polite language like this.
Ah
You can speak so frankly
I'm happy, yes, yes, I'm not, it's English.
and
Neunma seniors are all completely frank.
A senior who looks like he's disgusted when we talk
There's no one there, though.
There are certain things that are easier to talk about.
I would like to call the next person as well.
It's been a while. I'm sorry I pressed you.
There is
Hello!
Hello, happy birthday Ka-chan
Thank you very much
Masubee-chan came
Haha that's cool I feel like it's been a while
It's been a long time since I last saw you
Seriously, it's probably coming this year.
Well, maybe that Valentine's day?
At the time of Valentine's Day, since Valentine's Day
That's not true at all. Let's play some more.
Please, by all means
I want to play, Yatcho, I want you to teach me how to dance.
It's too bad, it's too bad, I don't like it
No, that's not true, really no no no no
Too much, no, no, no, no, what do you think?
icon icon ain icon x
I'm allowed to use the icon like that.
The cute icon is chan's
It's cute to be an icon, isn't it? It's a cute self-confidence work.
I wrote this myself.
I wrote it
Scary Iaasu celebrated Ajan's birthday.
It's my first birthday. It's my first birthday.
What do you think? It's already amazing
I'm so happy to celebrate with so many people
There's nothing you can do about it, so once in your life
too
Actually, I've never done anything like waiting for a bump.
It's my first time waiting for a convex one, so I'm already done.
There are so many things happening for the first time right now.
No, no, it's okay. My head is spinning.
It's okay, just take it slow.
I'm nervous waiting for the first time, I'm nervous.
It's already gross before it even starts
The children have all gathered together and it's okay.
It's so cute, it's so embarrassing
The unscrupulous young lady who did it too expensively.
I only did it for a while, but that was it.
It doesn't seem that bad because he was already a super guerrilla.
It's called Villain's Daughter or something like that on April Fools.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, at that time
I'm probably even more nervous than I was then.
I don't know, maybe
It's okay, it's okay, everyone, that Leeka
I want to meet you on your birthday, so it's okay.
Thank you very much I'm very happy
Thank you very much
The rest is not a thing, but just in case.
I'm preparing a present, but it's okay.
Is that okay? Thank you
Masunan
I'll go
yes happy
Bade to
Juha
you
happ
Birthday
[music]
Rika
Happy
Batoyou
Wow, that's amazing. What's that?
It wasn't a trumpet, he was singing.
It's a tomato now
Tomato-ton, I'm a tomato-ton professional.
It's so good, my mouth is so open
A cute one that opens with a snap, yeah yeah yeah
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Eh, thank you, I'm noticing something right now.
I'm glad you lowered the BGM.
I thought something was coming.
Congratulations, you are such a genius!
Too genius Otamart
No, thank you, Otamatone.
It wasn't Otamart.
Otamatone, yeah yeah yeah
Mutton Hoeko still has some time.
Mataga-chan invited me over to my house for something.
I'll invite you again to make that hot pot and eat it together.
I really want to eat it.
Please, please, I will definitely fly away.
I'm going to eat motsu. It's nice to come.
Thank you for the gift
I thought I would cut it out and listen to it over and over again.
Masu
No, you probably don't have to do that.
Why is it good?
I listen to this every day before going to bed.Wow, I definitely have nightmares.
Go out
I might have nightmares, thank you, no, see you next time.
A hot pot party with a must-have hot pot party
Please let me help you, thank you
Thank you and happy birthday again
Thank you and congratulations
Let's play again soon. Bye bye.
by
I hope it doesn't disappear because of the cute noise canceling.
However,
too
I received the last ji.
cute
You were the best, right now
Thank you very much for the gift.
Masusobe-chan bee-chan
That's right
I met him off duty a few times, about 23 times.
I've done it before, but it was a bit slow.
I may have never collaborated before.
Oh, the next person also informed me that he could go.
I would like to call you
[music]
Hello, hello, hello, hello
Hello, hello, can you hear me?
Hello hello hello
hello hello hello
Hello, I'm a clap pro.
Congratulations to Kashitesu-chan senpai
Thank you very much
I was completely wrong.
Sound effect when something goes wrong
Congratulations, how old are you?
I am now 23.1 years old.
He's 23.1 years old, so it's the same format as Mizuki-senpai.
The same way of carving is the same way of carving
I'm so happy thank you
It was my first time with Su-chan-senpai.
Time is minecraft, like this, like this, I'm alone
I was wandering around wondering where I should start looking.
Just when I thought I didn't understand, I said goodbye
It's like a hero that appeared, it's cool, it's the strongest
It's so nostalgic I see, that's my first time
I think it was a tangle, that's the first time.
When was the last time you talked?
Who actually spoke? It's a sports day. Sports day.
That's right. At the sports day.
I feel like it's a sports day, it's all up and down
That's right, that practice with the same team.
At that time, please be very kind and tell me various things.
I remember that. I wonder if I taught you so kindly.
He was so kind, what should I do?
Is it okay? On the contrary, there is a possibility of business interruption.
Very good business
Naya
It happened, it happened.It's so nostalgic.
But we still hang out together quite a bit.
There are a lot of escape games.
I've had a lot of things done to me.
I'm so happy, I went to that casino too.
Well done black jack
I played a lot of blackjack. I want to play it.
But since that day,
I want to go to Black Jack but I still
I haven't been able to go. I'm really busy right now.
I can go even if I'm not busy.
I can go, I want to go, I want to go with you
I enjoy watching you because I think you seem busy every day.
Thank you for spending time with me, it was great
How many months has it been now? It's already been 8 months.
I'm scared myself, but it's been 8 months.
No, no, but somehow it's already been a year.
I feel that way too, but seriously?
I still feel like it's only been a month.
It feels like it's been a year already.
It's already been a year. I'm so happy.
It's been a year like this, I want to be put on your shoulders
A year where I want to say, Im in the middle of it.
We're friends because we spent time together, right?
Part of my memory is messed up
Terua souda Mizucha-senpai told me.
That recommended thing
Wasn't there a game thing about it?
What can I do at home by myself?
I can endlessly recommend people who seem to be able to do it.
But the most recommended thing is yes
It was Detective X, so that's it.
It's something that was in a bottle.
I remembered that bottle and it looks like I would recommend it too.
Yeah, what are you saying, bottle?
A message, like a message in a bottle
It's a formality, isn't it?
Did I do it?Actually, my sister took it from me.
That one looks really cute
Isn't there something like this on the table?
When I put it on display, my sister said, "Oh, this is cute!"
I'm being taken for granted, so I'm still doing it.
I haven't, so I'm going to say that I'll definitely do it next time.
I thought, yeah, I want you to do it, sister, that's me.
It's on display at home, right? My sister is somewhere else.
I live in , so I met that wife at my sister's place.
I went
The moment you solved it for me, I looked inside.
What does this mean? It's an escape.
I might be able to really move on without knowing it.
Shire
I wonder what it's like to be cute
It seems like I can't do it again.
I'll buy it for you, yay, yay
I want to eat meat again after everything is done.
I want to go to Meat Shop too.
Basic advantages
Contents Recommended Foods Recommended Foods
Food is good
Yeah
Yes, I recommend it, but I mostly eat Lyrica.
That seems like it, but I wonder what's going on.
There aren't many things I can eat at home.
I haven't eaten it, but Sui-chan-senpai.
I have an image of people cooking their own meals that much.
Maybe not, that's right, I don't cook for myself.
Yes, yes, that's right. Mail order, etc.
It will become Uber or something, but hey.
Hmm, I see, wow, yeah, I've been hooked lately.
However, it's been about a year already.
Is it better to use raw ham or logs for ham?
Whether it's raw ham or raw wood, I'll take care of it a little.
That's because I heard that it's difficult.
But
Yeah, it seems like it's hard to take care of those cats and dogs.
Because I heard it, it's true, it's a cat.
I thought I would buy it, but I didn't, but it's a woman's
After the cat and the raw ham, it's all about Ajillo.
I've been hooked on Ajillo recently.
Ahijo Recently, I've been using shrimp ahijo.
I'm addicted to it and eat it with bread.
Eat a baguette or a baguette.
It's really delicious to eat it with
But I can't eat anymore.
It becomes oily because it turns into a turtle.
I noticed that from
I'm eating a lot. That's nice.
I guess that's it, Ahij is a lot of alcohol.
I had an image of eating and drinking together, but
Chan-senpai doesn't drink at all, so I can't drink.
Let's have some water. Looks good.
It's like Uber's Ajillo.
It seems like there is, so yeah yeah
If it's nearby, I'll try it.
I understand, thank you very much
I learned a lot from my notes and this ahi shrimp.
From Ajillo and prosciutto
Cat That's right. I really want to buy it right now.
Yeah, it's probably a cat, but it's at home.
I guess it's because there's a rabbit.
I have a rabbit at home and I can't change the cat.
I see, that's right, when Lyrica came.
Did you see my rabbit?
It hurts, it looks like that
I saw Tae, right? I saw it on the sofa.
It was so cute, that's right, the sea of sofas.
I think there were a lot of them, but what's going on now?
I was so freaked out when I thought it was happening.
If I did that, I'd be talking about it in the comments section right now.
That kind of thing
Please come and visit me again. I'm scared at home too.
Please say hello to my pet rabbit.
I understand, I was scared if I could do it now.
It's dangerous, Usagi should just pretend that she's winning.
But it's true
Like a prank that looked like
Thank you for the prank too.
It looks like this setting
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Congratulations, please talk slowly again.
I would be happy if you could call me anytime.
Please don't call me again without any further contact.
It's okay if you do it, I'll take it somewhere.
Yeah, is it true? You're too kind.
I wanted to try it out to see if it was true.
Please try it out thank you
Thank you very much and congratulations Ma
Yes, please again. Yeah, bye. Excuse me.
Masu
I was so surprised
Even the senior who is trying to help me is already acting playful.
I was surprised because he was so playful.
Good sir, I am really worried about that.
Every time I say that, I feel like that's the case.
When did you say you could ask me anything?
But he's a kind senior who says it's okay.
Yes, it's true
I was seriously told that I had seen it.
I never watched it, but I don't like it.
Already daddy
I glanced at the comment section.
I would like to thank you and pass it on to my next senior.
I want to
Thank you very much for telling me so many things.
Please give me
hand
mosquito
happy
[music]
My birthday is so cool
death
Teru
What is that?
Now that I'm being criticized for whatever it is
Noi Can Noi Can Noi Can I guess?
I guess this is really noise canceling
The sound is distorted, the sound is cracked, and the echo makes the sound
Because it's covered all over
Such an idiot, such a beautiful voice
And Lyrica said happy birthday.
But I already heard the voice in my heart
I heard that
Maybe our hearts are connected
That's it
I don't know what this is all about, but I'm happy
happy birthday
It's a mess
Happy screen. It turned out to be amazing, really.
I am so happy that I have received so much from you.
It's true, today's birthday will last forever
I'm so happy that I want to keep it in my heart
Thank you, I did it, thank you, no, that's it
I'm getting happier and happier.
Well, my brother is coming to my house again.
Hey, you're coming to play with me. I want to play with you.
You can play around with me, but of course you can't come back.
Next time, eat something instead of gyoza.
yes
I also ate Nabetsu Gyoza, but there were various fillings.
I guess I'm sleepy because it was. That's right, that's amazing.
That was amazing gyoza That was amazing gyoza
On the other hand, the next time I tried to eat it, it was good.
What is good for two people?
What do you think is good?
Oh, I don't know what to do, but it feels like a dark pot
We bring so many things together, it's dark
It's fun to watch it simmer like that.
I think so, yeah yeah, that's true
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's not like that.
It's like I want to eat it.
I guess it's not darkness.
I want takoyaki or takopa or takopa
Let's definitely tacopa tacopa, tacopa
Let's put anything in it.
Anything
When I said it was fine, I didn't care.
It's going to be something like those gyoza.
That's right, even though it's Tacopa.
I can't put anything in there that isn't an octopus.
It's gyoza gyoza limit gyoza is going to be the limit
The truth about turning into dumplings
It's okay if you don't mind, I understand, Tacopa.
Alright then, next time when Aani Yatepa comes.
It was a happy decision that I made.
But if it was Tacopa
It's okay to have two people, but there should be about four people.
It might be fun too, sure.
It might be a good idea to invite Holomen.
Yay, Takoyaki, Yay!
Yay, we made a good promise.
Now that you've done it, let's move on to the next one.
Please come to Rika's house anytime.
Um, it's totally fine if you come and stay the night.
Please keep it clean.
It smells like a pervert all day long
[music]
I suddenly feel like a pervert.
No, no, no, this is this, and that Lyrica too.
Zeta and I don't feel like this sometimes.
This is the kind of tension I've seen waiting for the bump.
Saririka speaks with such excitement.
We had a conversation that never happened, but now we're in the opposite position.
Teruzu
But anyway, Anya-senpai is like this.
He's Uncle Sahome, who represents GP.
On the other hand, if you say so, Lyrica is E.
The second season of Ano Saa Ano Saa's overseas is Saano.
Lyrica's English
The cutouts are pretty good.
Yes, yes, yes, from that overseas second term, Lyrica
People are seriously saying that it's en.
I guess it's okay if it's just that one time.
I want Lyrica to see the comment section and stuff like that.
I'm being told this is true.
That's right, this is it
It's not like JP or JP, it's Rigro.
Device
It's true, it's true, it's the opposite, either way
It might be okay either way
Okay, either might be okay.
That's so true
Let's switch places
Even if Ani is replaced by Ririka in GP.
It's not going to go away, I thought so.
It's regro, it's regro from now on.
Regrogross device
Hamel
Yay, what I'm doing is Lyrica today.
from
Yay!
Yay, nice, perfect, nice, perfect
Thank you very much, thank you very much
Happy Birthday
Thank you, Ill definitely play with you again. Lets play, I promise.
That's a promise. Thank you, see you soon, happy birthday.
Congratulations
Thank you, happy birthday, thank you
[music]
Aomo isn't super cute, but it's definitely Zeta
Lyrica used to do it well, but that's all.
It wasn't that bad.
That's funny
And then next
Hello, hello, hello, hello
Happy birthday Jima Ao
Thank you very much for waiting
I have a cute birthday present for you
But Ai's, well, a little sub too.
You may not need to make a sub or anything.
I guess this is fine. What should I do? Wait.
I'll take a look and see if it's posted.
or thrown
Why? Throw it, throw it, I don't need this.
Okay, I don't need this, green screen.
If you don't give it to me, I'll ask for a green screen.
Please wait for a moment. This is my first time.
I said no to the presents I received.
Shima
It's rude Don't you think it's rude? It's too rude.
I've been waiting forever.
I've been listening to the stream too much and I can't do anything
Thank you for tuning in
I tried saying something out loud in front of me.
There's nothing like Ha-chan at all.
This is a bad wake-up voice.
It's like, oh no, no, I just woke up.
I guess I took a little nap.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's a little beautiful
Now I can only make Nahachama's voice.
Beautiful rotation with a neat and clean voice.
A little bit
What's wrong with this, please?
Wow, it's a bit too much to put on my head, but it's so close to my head.
Wait, wait, it's gonna turn into something over here.
Either is fine, even a green bag.
I can do it, I really do.
Can't you do it with a green bag?
That's right, so it's okay.
I don't get along well with you, so don't be shy.
I'm not holding back, I'm not holding back, it's just footwear.
Even if you don't put it on your head, you can throw it.
If that's the case, I said I'd wear it.
Well, I'll be posting while chatting a bit.
Just say something appropriate
You got it while I was pitching, okay next time.
Let's do that Siu ASMR. Good, good, what?
I haven't even heard of it. Just 10 billion yen.
I don't mind if you lend it to me, that's why
I heard that, oh, I heard that.
Are you there?
That's what you're asking.
10 billion yen 10 billion yen That's 100 too much
It feels good, it feels good, thank you very much
Ai, this is so cute. Wow, I want to see it come.
What will it feel like? What will it be like?
I bet it's cute, and it's made of cotton
I'm giving you these sunglasses as a gift.
When I was giving a present, I thought of this cotton.
I started researching sunglasses and found this.
I see, by having a close relationship
It's like they're intentionally making it easier to see.
I haven't been able to research even 1mm that I haven't been able to research.
I learned this from Momame's sunglasses.
Is this a mask? Wait, this is a mask
If you think about it, you might be able to do it at all.
This is a mask, this is a mask
Hey, it's not a mask, it's a mask
Aaaah, the mask is so good
I've lost a few bits of hair.
Well then, I wonder if I should hide my beard. This is ruined.
It's completely different, wait here, is this the perfect place?
Maybe it's not Lyrica on the chin
I gave you a key bag for your birthday.
Nonisan's jaw
I came here with my jaw in my throat.
This is a terrible picture. This is seriously too bad.
Where did you want me to go?
I would have been satisfied if they had covered it.
I see, where should I wear it?
That's the T-bag I wanted
What are you trying to say about that T-back?
It's okay, it's a T-back, so it's decided.
I'm sure it's a thong, after all.
This cute ribbon is definitely on your ears.
I'm trying to listen to it
However, it's not that weird.
It's just my birthday
Thank you for being born
After all, it's my birthday after all.
Well, I guess I should tell him directly, even if it's embarrassing.
I think it's important for you to say it directly to me.
I'm trying to adjust the feeling.
I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it
It's a true feeling from the heart
Yes, really, yes, yes, that's true.
Even if I give you some pants, I'll be happy
I'm not as happy as you are to give it to A.
I'm really happy to have a junior.
to
Thank you, I didn't mean to be happy.
But I'll leave it at that.
I wasn't happy about it
Let's eat that sausage too.
Let's eat at
Let's show each other the net, let's do HR, let's have fun
Yeah, yeah, let's definitely take another trip, let's take a trip.
Let's do it, really, I just said something about being a junior.
But somehow Lyrica is my junior now.
No, it's more like she's my older sister.
Are you saying you're 231 years old?
That's right
Oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no react
You're overreacting a bit.
It seems like I was overreacting. I didn't say anything.
There isn't one
That was so dangerous, so dangerous. 231 years old.
That's right, 231 years old, 23.1 years old.
Hey, I've lived a long time, I'm 23.1 years old.
It's still barely okay. It's still barely okay.
That's so funny thank you so much
Wait a minute, thank you for these pants.
Congratulations, I'll burn it up!
I'll burn it aaaaaaaaaaaah
A birthday present for someone with a cute birthday
I eat it as if it were on fire.
Burn the food and turn it into starch for cooking
Yapa
It's a bond, so it's embarrassing so I'll burn it somehow
I said it, but somehow I need to cook it.
That's what I meant by eating.
I totally forgive you
Well, that's what it means.
You can cook in a variety of ways
I'll give you more for next year's birthday.
I'll have a little more bread for that.
It's no good unless you give me many times more pants.
There's nothing like that. How many times more bread?
It's not true
Congratulations to Kumoja.
Thank you or happy birthday and uhm
3 hours left?
It's true that there are only 3 hours left. 3 hours left.
Yeah, it's your birthday. Enjoy it. Bye-bye, see you soon.
Thank you
Goodbye, I'll be with you anytime soon.
It's cha
No, I won't be waiting for another 3 hours.
Karaet Nako
I received a punch unexpectedly.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience, but I would like to send a message to my next senior.
Kakeshi
Masu
Ruto Moshi Moshi
Hello, can you hear me? Can you hear me?
Yogacha
happy birthday
Thank you beauty
senior
embarrassing
spe yuro happy birthday haha
I'm happy
Hey, Biju-senpai, please come.
Oh my gosh BG senpai noise cancelling.
noise canceling blue whatyou
say Urika I forgot, I forgot
cute business
Senpai Uka-chan is cute
Happy business today, face business
Oh, you're good at Japanese, yeah, you're good at Japanese, you're beautiful.
senior
Japanese
Yay OKalltheknow
Kia cute positive genius
Mythanthan is happy
Mo with
me
havesaywill
Senkyu is kind and will play any game with you.
You just said you'll do it.
Ta
than happy pichi senpai lovei
haveonetoyou o Yesis
anyFoodYouLikeTo
EatanyFyour
orJustYouatebefore
or
[music]
Explain to others
Masukareka
[music]
Have you ever tried Kareokatsu Curry?
Haveyouevereaten cutlet
Boyfriend
before Oh, I love you the most, I love you the most, oh
Okay, okay.
I culinary form
OK never made
neverwill
[music]
My
isLwhichmade
What do you call a microwave?
Maui ifyouuse
microwaveyoucaneata
very delicious rice
soMICWAVEmicrWAVE
You put the rice in the
microwaveandwait3
minut
andwillbedelicious
[music]
hang on
[laughter]
please at MyCookingin
theiwilleat okay MyST
iswillbeok
than
and lookingfortoit looking forward to it
I'm looking forward to it Yes, I'm looking forward to it
Thank you very much.
There is a play
Aire
a
E
Eef to
will thank you beach
Thank you senpai
[music]
Happy I want
want
[music]
Hahaha
Juhadeh
happy
Present by
There are bi people
I'm very happy
I'm a business senior, I'm sorry about that English.
Maybe that's why I didn't know
There may have been some parts, but this time
I want to eat the cutlet curry that Ririka made.
That's why Shoji-senpai has cutlet curry.
I wanted to feed it to
Yes, and the next one too.
Mr. English, please come.
Kake
Ma
Hello, hello
Akikeriky
sounds cute
Cute baby Erika
Eh, happy birthday
[music]
I gave it to you
House squid
Hey, we did an off-collaboration in Japan.
I did a lot of fun.It was really fun.
I think we've become really good friends with Shaku.
Tayoun Ririka too. Even Ririka has some kind of convexity.
I don't have to wait for someone to call me, so I guess I'm forgotten.
I thought, forget it
No, actually that time
Its hard for seniors to come because of the defense.
I thought so, and at first I was a little confused.
But I still want you to come.
I almost thought about it that much
It's not that bad. It's 2 o'clock in Europe.
It's 2 o'clock in the afternoon.
It's 2 o'clock in the afternoon or right now in America.
It may be a little harsh, but Japanese
That prime time prime time
Yeah, it's around noon in Europe.
Well then, there will be more from now on.
Does that mean you'll play with me? Yes, please invite me.
I'll play if you give it to me, thank you very much
It's almost noon, so I have a present for you.
Is that okay? Thank you.
It's not something new, but it's exciting.
Karirika-chan is cute and stylish
I'm wearing earrings, so I'm so happy
Chiara's ear feathers aren't earrings.
But it's growing from behind my ear.
Fufubut special for Ririka-chan
I made an earring version.
Super cute Senkyu Berimae
Thank you very much, I'll leave now
Please, it's so cute
The color of the phoenix is so bright
It's a phoenix feather, so it's only a one-time use.
come back to life
I'm so happy to be able to come back to life
just once
Delica-chan because I got the power to come back to life
What should I do? What should I do?
There is something I want to do
It's so big, what should I do?
Huge potato
Big IknowITR
to it's so big it's this big
I wonder if it's about that, and it looks like there are two of them.
That's right, there's a bit of a bust in there.
Is this the outside?
Rao probably has a def.
A cat and a cat that look good on a kamao.
It's so big, like this, like this, like this
I wonder if it's done. I wonder if it's done.
I'm watching the stream for a while, but it's a bit slow.
No, I don't think it's done yet.
This side is big, but the right side looks good.
I guess this is about it
I'm done pooping! Yay!
Okay, what should we do?
bungee together
Jump That Uchiha Para
Gliding hun hun hun hun hun huh Japan
Even in words, papara yes, paragliding maybe
It's the same big one, right?
That bunge jump is a little too much
I went paragliding because it was scary.
But it's bad
[music]
It would be a little bit better if we were jumping together.
I think about it, but it's actually Lyrica.
That's right, that's more than that.
Yeah, let's go paragliding one more time.
I recommend paragliding in Japan.
I was really scared at first, but
It's also up, so please check it out.
I was scared, but somehow I rode with Izar.
The breeze feels so good after all
Paragliding can fly quite a bit.
The scenery of that mountain is quite slow.
Being able to see it feels a little soothing and soothing.
The more it becomes
Yeah, I guess there are some places you can recommend.
I don't know what to say, but it's Lyrica.
I've never done it before. I've never done it before.
I never thought I'd do something like that in my life.
But I tried it as a challenge.
Hokkaido was really good Is Hokkaido good?
What is so good about Hokkaido?
Japan is certainly beautiful here and everywhere.
I might be able to go there, but there are mountains
It's okay, huh?
There is certainly skiing like this in the mountains or Nagano.
If it's a place where you can do that, you'll have an image of mountains.
Maybe that's a good thing because there is
There might be a whole mountain in Nagano.
I don't know, I've never been to Nagano either.
I don't think I like it that much. I'm going now.
Let's go back to the hot springs. I'm tired of the hot springs.
I don't always like taking hot springs after a bath these days.
The hot springs you mentioned were also a bit hard-working.
I tried it, so I guess it takes a little getting used to it.
I wonder if aliens are coming, but it's embarrassing.
Maybe it's because there are so many aliens
All the hot springs are like there are aliens.
Everyone is walking around naked so it looks a bit like aliens
Isn't it scary to think that way? No, aliens are scary.
I can't see everyone's naked bodies.
I'm sorry, but I'm sorry.
No, but it was actually embarrassing the other day.
I went to that hot spring in Japan with Nerisa.
But Anosa-chan doesn't care at all
I don't think it was there, but I really like it.
I'm sure everyone will stare at me.
That's right, Chiara-senpai is a kibon.
I don't think it's that far.
I don't think so because it was only in that house.
Oh, that kind of thing can happen to some people.
Therefore, some people may find it unusual.
If you don't mind, Licca-chan,
Isn't that the president? He rented out that hot spring.
Please, I understand.
I'll talk to Himira Nai everyone here.
Thank you very much and please give me your best wishes.
Please, I'm nervous if it's not everyone.
Of course, I'll do it in a private room.
It would be great if there was some kind of fear.
That may be true. Yes, that's right.
Chan this time, yeah, it's finally Japanese
Let's do the Japanese version of Shark Tank
Yeah, I want to do a Japanese version too.
I did it because it was so much fun
The Japanese I wanted to do: Speak Japanese
Invite the members and ask them to introduce various things.
Let's do it. I want to do it. Let's do it.
Yay decision Circtank
Japanese
Please check the version soon
Okay, let's talk about the details again.
Thank you, please, everyone.
Please tell me what happened to you before.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm done with my ass.
Okay, so I did it with Kia-senpai before.
There will be a collaboration broadcast with Shark Tank.
If you like, please watch it in Kia-senpai's slot.
I think so, this time it's Ririka-chan's
I played the Japanese version on my channel.
I'm looking forward to it Ajae and I'm in a bit of a hurry
in
Thank you glur
Is that in Australian?
Hey
It's not from Austria, it's from Austria.
Oh my god, I was wrong. That's right, it's Austria.
Seriously
Kanben Lee Iwilldie that
WhyyoumegoingtoDies
i
Dedededededede
Pi
Thank you Senkyu, it was a mistake.
Ta
I became Australia
Good mistake I made in Austria
I've said that before.
Thank you Lyrica
[music]
I'm going to get banned even more.
The length of Lyrica's gori is the length of the five powers.
[music]
I don't mind if I call you.
The next thing that can be done overseas is
I would also like to thank you
Please forgive me, Mr.
Maybe, maybe, maybe
What's wrong with this? What are you doing now?
It's a dangerous wait, but it's a lie. It's already delivered.
Who do you think is waiting for the ride?
Kaemaemae
Hey, it's my birthday, Jancho, wait, it's going to be delivered, it's going to be delivered.
On the contrary, I thought it was dangerous.
It's amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing
Because I'm doing it more and more.
It's no good now, it's no good anymore
It's not standing
Hey, I thought to myself, ``You're really amazing.''
Please listen to me, thank you for your strength.
I'm really grateful to everyone for being so kind.
Thank you very much
It's always been Shintera and Volka is amazing too
I thought it was amazing and decided to use it as a reference book.
That Mei from Yayaedemo Rivolka Senpai
Learn more about that power by referring to
I'm out there, I'm going to do that, I'm going to do that.
Are you going to do it? Are you going to go to the office again?
I won't say I want to try that again.
I'm still alive, so I'll do it again.
I'm looking forward to it thank you
Wow, 24 people is seriously one big club.
Isn't it possible to have 20 people, or 20 people?
I have a little apprentice
Oh no, it's the wrong 25 people. Ligro is the one.
Regro has already been part of Lyrica from the beginning.
I was thinking like this just now
That's right, congratulations to Ato and Kani.
Yes, all the goods were good, it's a marginal meal T
That shirt was good. Hey there.
I'm so plump, I want you to come.
I'm a little worried about the fact that it's hollow.
I wonder if there will be a sample photo?
I don't know what it feels like
I don't have a real photo, but yeah
Please wait a little longer.
I don't do goods properly anymore.
Even though I was thinking about it, I'm already more interested in it than the goods.
I've been doing it all the time because it's so much fun
That's right, I've been doing embroidery until now.
I know, but I thought it was plump.
It's so plump, isn't it?
It probably has a three-dimensional feel to it when you touch it.
Wait for the photo to be uploaded someday
Well, I'd love to have a little fun.
I'm curious, what is bungee jumping?
Ah, bungee, bungee jump
No, there's no bungee jumping, no polka.
Leave it to me, Chiara.
It's scary, so I understand.
At that time, everyone will fly or even the dangerous ones will be blown away.
If I make a promise here without permission, what will happen later?
It fits, it's totally fine, that polka
The legend of polka that is well taken care of
The program will be aired there.
I really want to do it with So-chan
Damn, I thought I should have written Lyrica too.
I couldn't write it because I thought it would be the second sage.
But Mr. Rigro has been doing that lately.
You also started doing variety shows, didn't you?
Holding hands with us, the first part, the second part
Would you like to collaborate like this?
I would love to do it, please, that polka
It's a legend, and the second half is that variety show.
I want to do it on the show, it's so good
Yeah, this is definitely a big name in regross.
I'll have to try a little bit with you.
It's okay with the manager, Ririka.
I'm good at that, please. I want to do it.
I mean, it's like that in Riga.
I'm going to sleep a little shorter today, and I'm going to keep it to a minimum today.
I'm thinking of going, so I'll give you a present.
I've already sent it!
Thank you very much
Steam or registered on Steam
It's an address, so it's probably Pol.
Lyrica's Nekore This is the game I want you to play
Even if it's just once, it's okay.
I wonder if it's a yes or no if you want me to do it.
Look, it's a game called Princess.
But it's a bit unexpected
A little rice with the princess to the Ka-san who is being treated.
I want you to learn from the rice game.
I'm very happy thank you very much
Well, if you have time, please
Not streaming at all, just playing normally.
Please feel free to have it, everyone.
Please give me a present
This is my first time doing this, thank you very much
I really want to eat that Lyrica and rice too.
I've never been there or played there
I guess I just played that game.
That's about it, but please tell me next time.
Food and games
I'd like to hear all of them. Polka is a bit slow.
I don't know, so I'll take you with me.
Pull the bungee, let's go bungee
The bungee will go. That's my waist.
It's heavy, but I could go if I had a car.
That's strange. We're all going on a location bus.
Well, that might be fun.
Oh yeah, we all have location buses.
Maybe we should all go on a location bus.
I'm going to hell with Rigro, now I understand.
I wish you a very happy birthday after all.
It's already short but thank you very much
I'll do my best to wait. That's really nice.
Thank you very much for the present
Let's play, let's do it, okay?
baji baji
yes thank you
Wow Borka-senpai
decided to take me there without permission.
Shima
It's too funny, it's a gift
I can send it to you
[music]
I'm so incredibly happy
I'm very, very happy
Are there any regrowth members who don't know anything?
I want to paste the regro members here
That's right, that's right, I'm already too angry.
I want to paste it properly.
When I tried to paste it, my computer froze.
I couldn't paste it or I couldn't paste it.
Gross has been my emotional support for a long time now.
Thank you for staying with me
Thank you for being here.
The seniors are also really crazy.
You're really kind, aren't you?
Nico actually
hey
There's only one person left at Oishio.
Actually, this is
It's not a reverse convex, but just once.
I asked if it would be okay if it was the other way around.
Tara's
I just don't have the time right now
I can't, but please tell me, that's nice.
Please prepare a present
Thank you for your support.
By the way, to the other seniors too.
Hey Lyrica, just before that, I said something to you.
That's partly because it happened.
I'm sorry this time.
There were many seniors who had lost their lives.
But even so, those people really
Very kindly, reply to Lyrica.
Please give me a little bit. I'm still that stubborn.
For those seniors who I haven't been able to talk to about collaborations, etc.
Please feel free to talk to me another time.
I wish I had the opportunity to
There are also people who were unable to reach out to us.
But
I wish you a truly happy birthday.
I want to bring out Raden-chan, Raden-chan.
Yoisho paralysis
What's more, Raden-chan was just streaming for some reason.
Send me that fan art, this is serious
received
Are you drunk? Are you drunk?
Let's have a good time together with Gross.
That being said, it's okay.
Rika-cho, I did it in a really fast way.
That's what it is but yeah yeah yeah
Okay
Well then, I'd like to share the movie I received with you all.
I want to show you
Turn off the BGM and turn off the BGM.
Take this out
Going
Is this okay? The volume is okay, Lili.
I'm talking like this. Wow. I'm talking like this.
Is it okay? I'll go, okay, okay.
Sorry, wait a moment, it hurts
I'm being bullied by a turtle. Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Are you okay? Rika, please help me. I'll help you now.
Look, go over there, it's a turtle. Thank you, Ririka.
Thank you, if Rika hadn't come
I was bullied by the turtle for a long time, thank you
Is it okay? Is it full? Thank you
Let's go together, I'll bring it with me.
Techichichi Ririka Happy Birthday
Congratulations
I actually wanted to go to the other place, but today
My schedule doesn't work out so I'll just watch that video.
Just say let me send it to you.
I'm taking a picture of it. It looks like this.
It ended up being that video, but that
I really, really love Lyrica.
I feel a sense of congratulations.
Next time, definitely, let's collaborate again, let's play
Congratulations!
Thank you very much
[music]
In other words
Even though Fronet-senpai is so busy.
Please prepare this movie and send it to me.
Please
I'm very happy. Thank you very much.
[music]
I laughed so hard when this arrived too.
Moreover, Koro-senpai was the first one.
I think it's better to be on screen, so I'll stop here.
Toko
No, really
Kindly, tell me it's okay and send it to me
Please come
Yes, I'm really, really happy.
No, it's really coming slowly.
It's always interesting
It's always been so fun.
If you keep playing this video,
Okay, just put it in a loop. No sound.
Well then
You really have great taste
That's a bit too much.
As I said, the timing is right today.
It doesn't seem to fit. Unfortunately, I can't talk to you.
Thank you for everything.
There are also seniors who were unable to bow.
But it's finally the moon, so I'm with everyone.
He also celebrated his first birthday in
That's why I'm really here again.
Supported by so many people
That's how active I am.
I feel it from the bottom of my heart. It's my birthday already.
I was worried a lot about what to do.
Well, Lyrica doesn't usually do anything at all.
I have never done convex or reverse convex.
The only thing I really think about is Lily-sama.
It was at that X that I felt like I couldn't do it anymore.
I just want to help a little bit.
I don't seem to be following that whole thing I said.
Convex has done this before, but like this.
I mean, it was done properly.
This is my first time waiting for a convex event that I have prepared well.
But I was still nervous and nervous.
The seniors are so excited that they will soon be able to solve it.
You're so kind and everyone comments so much.
I think it will liven up the
I was really, really happy.
Thank you so much for being so warm
I feel supported by my seniors.
Yes, I feel happy. I'm still your number one junior.
But
Lyrica also has a little bit of this Hololive
My seniors started to realize that I was protecting them.
This is such a wonderful place to stay.
Please help us make it a warm place
I would be happy if I could make it even 1mm.
There are a lot of birthdays for Ririka.
A lot of Lyrica feels happy.
Share the fun with everyone who has made a mistake
I wanted to do that.
Yeah
Thank you, there were a lot of things that were new to me.
As a result, the progress was quite slow.
It happened, but so did everyone.
I had a collaboration like this with a senior over there.
I wish Rigro-chan was always there.
I feel something like that even just a little bit.
I thought I would be happy if I could get it.
And once again, all the apprentices
Thanks to you, Ririka had a fun birthday.
Yesterday too, I heard that song, but to be honest, I'm a little thirsty.
I was really disappointed because I wasn't in perfect condition.
But it was still really good
He told me it was fun.
I'm so happy Lyrica, even more next year
I would be happy if we could spend more fun time together.
I thought so.
For those of you who are watching this for the first time.
If you like, please take this opportunity to subscribe to the channel.
I would be very happy if you could come too.
That's how I feel, right here to everyone.
There is a report of a pleasant surprise.
There are many
Well, there are two things, but first, let's start with the first one.
Wait a minute, I'll get ready.
Well, what should I do?
There must be someone who prepared it earlier.
is
But I guess it's because I went on a trip.
teeth
Well, let's do this first
Let's get it out
Well, new member stamps are here!
I did it
Well, this is the first announcement, so please wait.
I prepared this so that I could release the next one right away.
I was supposed to go somewhere, but I went somewhere
Shibori is so cute, isn't it?
That stamp is so cute, isn't it?
Added the stamp written by Lyrica.
Yes.
But I thought I hadn't added that much.
So I'll take this opportunity to give everyone a birthday present.
So the birth of everyone
I will add it as a present.
a little bit
I'm adding it now, so please wait for 2 seconds.
I think you can add it in about a minute.
Thank you. Please try using it too.
Please save it.
Thank you to all the members and welcome back.
I am very happy for both the new members and the new members.
The illustration is the same as last time.
I asked Mr. Kawase Carne very much.
These are cute stamps. Use them a lot.
I would be happy if I could get
But I can't do it anymore. There's not enough space.
It feels like there's not enough space.
It's so soft and fluffy
There's one more piece, and I'm happy to report it.
Yes, this is already super big in terms of Lyrica.
This is just a notice.
I will also go
Good luck
Noji
We have started production of Jiichijo Ririkao station.
Ta
I'm making an original song. Please make it already.
Actually, there is also a song.
The song is already pretty close to completion.
It's amazing how far you've come
You must have been surprised.
By the way, it's a really great song.
So let's actually tell everyone a little bit.
We still have a little more time to show you
It's about to take a while, but I'm still singing that song.
Even though I didn't know anything about it, I thought about a lot of things when I made that song.
So, it's still to come.
But yes, from now on, I'll sing a song again.
I filmed the video and made an MV.
I want to wear a yukagane like this too
It's true that I was able to start making folds with such speed.
Thanks to everyone's daily support,
Thank you very much. What kind of system is it?
The song is still a secret, but
I think I wanted it to be a high-quality song.
The lyrics are what everyone understands
I want the song to be the way I want it to be.
A lot of things, a little bit of Lyrica's obsession
I packed a lot of things and made it like that.
Thank you to the members as well.
Please look forward to this
I would be happy if you could give it to me.
Do you sympathize with the lyrics?
Do you agree with that? It's true.
It's okay
I'm surprised
Right?
Hey, I hope you have a really wonderful birthday
Thank you very much
I would like to take this opportunity to introduce the goods once again.
Can I do that please? Sorry.
It really turned into a slapstick situation.
yeah
And the shoes are pretty similar to Lyrica.
I'll explain it to you because I put a lot of effort into making it.
I want to
[music]
Oisho
Well,
Yes, I want you to come first.
But this is the first thing I can't do anymore, Ririka now.
No, this is Lyrica's OBS-kun mess.
So much so that I have no idea where anything is.
Yes Birthday Commemoration 2024 Noe Goods Sale
Please pick this up right away!
Is there anyone who gave it to me?
That set, the single item, and the voice only.
There is a single item and I have prepared various things.
I bought that full set.
Regarding the person who gave it to me,
I bought a lot more voices, all real voices.
I bought a lot, my 3
Oh my key it's a mess
I'm really looking forward to seeing something that makes me happy.
But still, it's still pretty good for everyone.
I've never given a signature before.
That's what I wrote at the time of the expo, but that's
Something
To everyone who writes about this on panels etc.
I think it was a sign of Soukou1
This is my first time getting a single cat sign.
Actually, the voice was wrong.
It was a sign
Mane-chan also says it's a quality voice.
I'm sorry I got a message saying that.
It's a handwritten autograph. Yes, there's a voice as well.
However, voice is not a sign.
What is Nqa Boiz?
I'm sorry, I made a mistake.It's the sign for the room.
That and the one with the message. Yes, this is it.
I also explained that it was a bit of a feeling.
is
But that's the case, so please take care of it.
Now, one more time.
I would like you to take a look at some goods.
design
of
good food
[music]
#1
Anniversary full
Set acrylic panel square tin badge
Limit Meal T
Shirts, seriously, I like T-shirts
We'll always be together stuffed toy keychain
This stuffed animal is definitely worth it!
Something to carry around, something to sleep in, and food.
I'll eat it and then lend it to you.
I hope you don't mind if I lend it to you.
I hope you can pick it up a little.
Seriously, stuffed animals are so cute!
The three types of voices are ASMR voices.
There is only one, and this ASMR voice is amazing!
Let's take a photo with that Co., Ltd. cover.
It feels really smooth
I think it's true. Yes, please lend it to me.
Yeah, that's a little bit of that voice.
It doesn't come out, but everyone has this in them.
When you consult with Lyrica Voice, it's ok.
You did a great job. Tell me you love me.
Everyone in my heart
I will say it in everyone's hearts.
Stock Acover Co., Ltd. Socover Co., Ltd.
I'm sorry, this is Yabaiaka Co., Ltd.
It's like being punched in a dangerous goo.
There is an imaginary lyrica full version
For those who bought the set, it will be delivered to your room.
Comes with a signed postcard
Well, it's an order, so I guess I want it.
For those of you who are thinking about it, this time you can get it.
I think they made it in a way that you can take it off.
It's my first time and it's my first product, so it's something.
If you have the chance, please let everyone pick it up.
I want to get it
I'm thinking about it, but what will happen next time?
I don't know, so I'm glad I got it this time.
I would be happy if you could take it.
I am signing many, many signatures.
So, thank you very much for your support.
death
Masu
And the panels are really cute, aren't they?
It's super cute, right? Together with this Lyrica.
Please eat that cake with Lyrica.
The memories of spending my birthday will last a lifetime
Acrylic to display in your room for a lifetime
The panel is really nice, and that fermentation too.
It's okay, so I'm going to look at it. The color fermentation is super cute.
Thank you, Canbachi's face is up close
The stand on the back is also that design Lyrica.
The person in charge of merchandise thought this was cute.
Let me make a decision while saying something like,
I received it, and it looks like a square drumstick.
So it may be easy to get rid of by poop etc.
There's no limit to food T-shirts that normal life
I don't buy many goods.
If you are interested, please try just this T-shirt.
I would be happy if you could pick it up.
By the way, the size was quite large.
I already received a sample of that Lyrica.
But
That pretty Lyrica part is about above the knee.
It felt like it had a length of up to
I think it also depends on your body size.
But Lyrica is 163cm tall.
But it's a free size, so it's big.
Yes, Lyrica is for maki and 2nd place.
I bought it. I bought two. It's a lie. I have two.
I haven't bought it yet
Yes, this is a one-size-fits-all size.
It's free so yeah yeah yeah
Yeah, it's pretty big, but it's big, but that's it.
Apparently Lyrica was able to cut normally.
I think it's good, but I haven't gone outside yet.
I don't go outside, so I'm not talking about the knee-to-knee length.
The size is probably just above the knee.
Is it out?
So yeah yeah
Yes, it looks quite like that baggy thing.
I can wear it and it gives off a cute, baggy look.
I'm not sure if there is. Please come if you'd like.
Look
Please, by the way, I can do it at all, really.
It's cute and has a special feature on its back
If you wear clothes that don't show your eyes,
He's wearing some kind of stylish T-shirt.
I think you'll think ``Amen162''.
He's about 2 to 3 years old.
Oh yeah yeah
yes
By all means, this is important because this on your back is important.
Karama 162 to 3 is about Lyrica.
Your height will change depending on the day, so it will grow a little.
This is really cute
But you'll know how cute it is when you see it
It's amazing how much attention has been paid to even the smallest details.
Lyrica's costume is now clothes.
By all means, please
Please pick it up and talk about it every day.
If you give it
The lyrica in this lyrica's heart is joyful
Yes, this is really cute
It's so cute By the way, the real thing is also true
It's cute so I'm super confident. I'm confident.
Lyrica samples that look like real ones
I'm watching this, so I'll see if it arrives.
You're different from my image, so I'm sure you'll never be the same
I hope you can pick it up
Well, I guess I'll have to get my hands on this.
If there was someone who took it, I would have all kinds of food.
Or when you go out to eat, take me with you.
It would be great if you could take a photo and post it like this
I'm so happy.Ririka herself is an otaku.
That's why it's amazing even though it's like that.
I have longing
The person walking outside with this
And so on.
I wish I could pass by you this time.
Hey, let's talk about various things about my birthday and cake and Lyrica.
It is written that way, such as by placing it near the goods of
There were a lot of people who were kind to me.
But yeah, I'm so happy, I'm insanely happy
I was happy so there are many things you can do
I wish you could take me somewhere.
But that stuffed animal is really quite dirty.
If you carry it outside because you will use it,
I really recommend buying some in stock.
business
Above and above
Voice voice is ASR voice
There are 2 situation voices.
ASR voice is quite sweet.
I'm so excited because I'm flirting with you at the door
Please give me a situational voice too.
Both have a pretty nice one-on-one feel.
It's a situation voice.
If you're okay with that, please smile at me.
I feel happy
Even after the order deadline for Masu Voice ends.
I thought it would have been available for purchase.
You don't have to rush, so it's okay
Is it structured like that? I have a question.
If you have any questions, please let me know.
Answer with the tiles you can answer now
It's a relief, it's a relief
I want it, the heart stamp is cute too.
Together with Asoko who is curious about the limit meal together.
Marginal food's voice is a bit of a surprise.
I'm surprised because it's about to unfold.
I want you to be surprised, I want you to be surprised.
thought
Yes, it looks like this
Can the stuffed toy be washed? Yes, it can be washed.
I think it's difficult even if you can wash your hands.
There are various small parts that are hand washable.
I think it is difficult to choose a hub
I won't change Lyrica herself.
Look forward to it
The fourth voice of the grass is yes, this is the fourth voice.
This is the voice that expresses my gratitude
The voice only comes with the full set.
hand
Yes, it's like that
Masu
So
Well, today is really nice.
Thank you very much
What was meant to be an hour turned into 2 hours.
That's what I thought, but before I knew it, it had been 3 hours.
Now
From 10pm after Tako, members.
It will be limited distribution, but
There's a lot of stuff like today's behind-the-scenes stories.
I wish we could talk for a while.
Relax and enjoy some snacks
I hope you have a good time, so please
Please spend some time with me
Thank you very much.
Maybe here's where I'm going after this.
I think you should post it.
Member-only distribution at
Paste the link
[music]
Some of the Neyoisho members have joined us.
Thank you very much for today
I was really nervous though.
I wonder if all the seniors are really kind and okay.
I hope Ri isn't panicking or saying anything strange.
I wish, uh, write here next time.
Toko 2nd member
Limited edition If you like, please meet me here.
Let's say thank you one by one.
I couldn't do it, but to that member
Thank you to everyone who came and to the many
Thank you very much for sending me this gift.
Thank you very much, I sent it to you before it started.
While forgetting the preparations you made for me,
I felt so happy when I saw that.
Thank you very much
If it's nice, I'll have a nice time with Merica again.
spend every day
Please do the opposite at the end for everyone.
After this, I want to relax with everyone.
thought
The Regro members who came
Everyone, seniors, and this time Neon.
I couldn't come, but I wish you a happy birthday.
Congratulations to everyone and still
I hope we can get along well from now on.
To all my seniors, please continue to do so.
Thank you very much and I'm watching.
Thank you everyone
In Masu, the next members-only distribution will be held 2 times after this.
See you next time See you then
bye bye
[music]
[applause]