[Music]
do
wow
[Music]
oh
i feel like um you guys probably you
probably don't notice it
because yeah it's just how it is because
the microphone is just too good but
the i sound different to myself today
because my
my room is pretty much empty
i took off all the the audio
foam from my windows
and um doesn't really sound different
the acoustics yeah the acoustics are so
weird and i got no curtains anymore
and my room is pretty empty i mean my
bed and my desk and my pc is still there
but it is very different
from
sounds it sounds emptier could just be
echo
i don't have an echo on though it
doesn't sound that much yeah it
shouldn't
it shouldn't really because the
microphone
is just
[Laughter]
there is a bit of an echo what
no [\h__\h]
yeah but one thing i'm worried about is
um
i had like i had curtains that are like
supposedly
help with the with like sound leaking
outside supposedly it totally didn't
uh maybe only a little bit but yeah i
had those curtains everywhere
and i had the the this kind of foam
and stuff like that um
but now it's all gone so now i think
probably
my neighbors hear me like hear like
exactly every single
[Laughter]
so ever since this morning right now
it's 8 p.m
and in the morning time i already had no
curtains left because i already prepared
everything
and i woke up so early even though i
didn't even have to
because first of all i hurt my neighbors
so so clearly even though they weren't
even talking that loud
and because i had no curtains and i have
like a million windows
it was so bright and i don't know it's
just
i think that would have been the key to
fix my sleeping schedule if i would have
ever opened
the the curtains and just let the light
in
when it's supposed to be in there yeah i
think the lights
really woke me up um
we're in combination with my neighbors
though
so yeah but because of that i think they
definitely hear me because i heard them
in the morning
very clearly i heard like every word
they were saying but i wasn't sure if
they
had a window open and maybe that's why i
heard them so clearly or they were
outside i don't know or if they really
had everything closed and me too
hmm
yeah paper balls yeah yeah but i live in
a i live in a one
like like in a house and there's like
space between the other houses they're
not like
i mean it's not a lot of space but there
is
space between the houses so
yeah it's not like there could switch it
up
[Music]
did i tell you guys
did i tell you guys that i was did i
tell you that
in another stream where i said like
that they were like banging on
i scared my vocabulary is like what not
banging but like like um uh
hitting hitting on i told you that in
the other stream
ah see recently i've been hearing my
neighbors a lot and they were they were
hitting
hitting on on some carpets or something
outside i did it i told you that and
that's why you said that
indeed
i basically almost all of my furniture
is gone
um as is my pink pink gamer girl chair
it's gone so i'm sitting right now on a
folding chair
so it's not very comfortable
and i can't sit sit in many positions
not the chair it's gone it's gone
so ah
[Laughter]
so yeah guys generally i should i should
probably
not be speaking as loud as
usual
to not disturb my neighbors too much
and i should probably not stream
after midnight anymore because yeah they
definitely hear everything
um but
we have like four hours so
oh we have like four hours four hours to
read uh
some super chats hopefully i can read
them all i'll try to be a bit more quiet
i'll try to not you know
go to too too loud
[Music]
something weird my my
my uh balcony belt balcony sliding doors
they don't close properly anymore
so weird but oh well that will be the
problem of the next person moving in
because of the earthquake ain't no i
don't think so
it's kind of weird like when i when i
push the left side of the door to the
very end
then the right side of the door moves
over to the left side like
two centimeters so it's not completely
closed
and then when i move the right side of
the door over to the right side then the
left side moves
to the right side again and then if i
hold the left side of the of the
window door back so that it doesn't move
and then i push the right side of the
sliding door to the red side
it still moves along with it even though
i push it back
avoid too many details about your travel
please thank you for your concern but i
know what i'm doing
um that is exactly the reason why i am
not
telling you giving you guys a weekly
schedule
i am very much aware of what i'm doing
don't worry don't worry
but okay i'm feeling much better than
when did i last stream yesterday i
streamed last yesterday didn't i
i feel much better than yesterday
because yesterday after the stream
and i i got so
i got i got i i kind of panicked
i kind of panicked and i messaged botan
senpai
i finally did it and
i
i i asked her like for advice
mostly because i i thought she wouldn't
have time to help me like
um in person anyway so i asked her for
advice but then then after like five
lines of text i i
kind of like hinted at the fact that if
she could help me in person
i would be absolutely blessed and
grateful and she
replied saying that um yeah if our
sketches online she would help me
in person she would come over and she
would pack
my pc for me
and our schedules did a line it sits
my my schedule is packed right now but
yeah
so i'm meeting bhutan senpai before i
leave
[Music]
i feel like so so blessed
like honestly but i wrote her the
message i was like panicking
and then i got back to work i started
like ripping off the foam of my windows
and then after a while i was like
i don't know i don't i don't wanna it
just it just seems so sudden like you
know i i normally don't really have
conversations with her um
so i just felt like it was weird to
suddenly ask her for help so i wanted to
go back i went back to my pc
to delete my request i wanted to delete
my message
but then she already replied by that
time
so it was too late she already replied
and says yes
so i couldn't delete it
i was like it was just a panic move i
wanted to get rid of it
no it's not about having confidence it's
more like you know
just um partially also like i don't know
japanese culture like people
people don't really ask for help much
and
um and i kind of got used to this like
being on my own
thing uh yeah
it's i just especially like
like i mean say you you you you know
someone they have an acquaintance
someone talked about my door what the
hell
am i too loud
was like 8 p.m what the [\h__\h]
i'll go there
[Music]
russia oh
what is this what is this
what is this
what is this i got i got some mail
what did i order
oh yeah 8 p.m isn't it crazy in japan
uh after it's half past 8 p.m
they deliver so late and and
today today even is a holiday in japan
today is a holiday they deliver that's
one of those things
in in japan that is absolutely amazing
on holidays on on weekends sundays like
in
in australia if it's a holiday or if
it's a sunday they don't do [\h__\h] or even
on a saturday that they don't even do
[\h__\h]
actually what is this
what is this
[Applause]
emperor's birthday i guess nanny who
huh
what the hell
[Applause]
come on
quite quiet i didn't order anything
it didn't even come from japan what did
i order
hey
[Laughter]
[Applause]
oh
[Laughter]
aah
okay i can't
i can't tell you guys
i cannot tell you guys because
someone is watching who is not allowed
to know
what i have received
totally ah oh
i totally forgot like i mean i didn't
really forget but
ah all right there's there was so much
going on in my head
but i didn't realize that that was still
coming
up
okay wait i know what it is so what but
wait oh actually i wanted it
why when was it why is it two
let's open let's open but this
this this is interesting
because this
this um creates some
problems for me
[Music]
okay
oh
i'm telling you eventually i can't i
can't give you a hint
nope
matching winter he said what the hell no
gucci bag foreign
no i'm drinking dr pepper right now it's
so good
i see oh
[Music]
i was saying that imagine you have an
acquaintance who you talked to before
but you
the last time you talked to that person
was a long time ago and
you don't really have any conversations
and then suddenly
you're like hey hey hey hey i need your
help for this and that could you come
over and help me
it's just like i just feel like that's
so
out of nowhere and asking someone for
help
when you don't usually have any
connection with that person
i just don't want to bother them and it
i feel like some people
could be like you only you only talk to
me when you need help
you know there's yeah there's
i feel like there's people who could
react like that obviously
i was like feeling like okay well dan
senpai is so kind
and she she likes doing stuff with
pieces i guess so
she probably wouldn't mind and all that
but still like there's still this
this part of me that feels like i would
have been bothering her um
so yeah but but she she said she would
help me
oh so happy
so help me because um
that was the one of those things that
stressed me out the most yeah
and then today um i i finished like
um sending oh my god guys before we get
into the super chats i really just want
to
get these things but out of the way but
i went to the freaking post office
with like 10 bucks let's say
eight boxes
like normal size boxes
no it's not it's not even about
australia confusion i was um
shocked
and today was a day where i was like wow
if i wasn't in her life i would be
[\h__\h] right now
i'm just gonna say one
zero zero zero
can you [\h__\h]
is
the big ones are open on holidays this
isn't that's another amazing thing about
japan
even the post offices are open for you
to send stuff
on holidays absolutely amazing
but yeah
who
i was so shocked at the price i was like
he he showed me on his
on his calculator he was like it's it's
um it's uh
over a thousand dollars and i'm like oh
one second i gotta go to the atm get
some more money
i mean i expected it to be expensive but
not that expensive
[Music]
send it with ems but um
i didn't want to send it with uh with a
ship because it would take
too much way too much time and and and
right now there's like a high chance
that like if i send it a
ship which normally can already take up
to two to two to three months
with the delay it could take like over
half a year or something
so i was like yeah whatever also it
could even get lost and never
never ever show up like recently i hear
that there's
they often lose packages
completely even and i don't really want
that to happen
um so yeah yeah i had the choice between
bi-air
and ems but then i didn't i wasn't i was
like okay where the
writer freak is the difference i just i
just went with whatever
oh my god that was a huge shock i was
i was there for a long time but then
yeah then um that was done and my moving
was done i put some
i put some i i got some things
transported to
a storage i i'll probably
pick some things up next time i come to
japan again
and after that i went to get
ramen and now my tongue is burnt
ano
what
lamentable
so much but still still was
so hot
so my even now even after like
hours and hours my tongue is burning
um
i was like i gotta eat one more ramen
before i leave japan because
otherwise you know i will i will miss
out
on something although i heard my
favorite ramen place
back home started delivery
yay in these trying times
my favorite ramen place that i told you
about started delivery
my roommate said that she ordered like
robin from that place three times
oh she's very addicted to it i like that
spirit
quick question if possible would you
like to live in japan
i live in japan right now um and i'm
moving away
so i guess i don't know no
it's not it's not my first time living
in japan and it's just
i've come to a point where
i have i have this feeling of
closure i mean that's what i came for
this year
i came for getting closer
and doing some things that i wanted to
finish
but i didn't get
any of those things done
but i still feel like i got closure i
mean
um could have been could have been
better but
there's there's many many reasons and
yeah
[Music]
um
[Applause]
i feel a bit sorry for the japanese fans
because i feel like i'm
i don't know it's like i'm breaking up
with them
it's no difference it's just just the
time when i'm streaming will change
a little bit so so so-so
i think i start reading again with the
with the orange one and then goes
to the takamuri uh super chats
there we go and i
will ban you
that's not what i wanted to say but i
will indeed ban you
and then
wrong button and i will what was i going
to say
what was that ah i will probably
um reread a few ones that i have already
read we didn't get
far at all uh
i i feel like my japanese rear is like
okay the ones who are always here
the ones who are always here probably
understand but the japanese viewers who
are
who are not always here they probably
really think i'm from australia
[Laughter]
kuala korea night
[Music]
um
i tried to explain hey i tried to
explain
yeah on mario kart you can see the
australian flag
i was reading a few months i'll continue
from
pretty much where i left off i guess
yes okay i'll just i'll just continue
where i left off
where i started crying so sorry guys
that was too
too too stressed but now i'm fine i'm
fine
most of oh my god what you turn you turn
slow mode off for one day
and then you get this [\h__\h] in my
comments too
dear lord i trusted you guys i trusted
you guys
well i'll leave it to you denmark
and yeah i was saying uh most of the
most of the
stressful things have been lifted off of
me there's a few things that i have to
still get done a few as in a lot
a lot of things i still have to get done
let me tell you one more thing before i
start we're doing all the tangents
before we read today so that we can go
zoom um tomorrow
i do plan to stream
around the same time as today a little
bit later maybe one or two hours later
um however
i'll be streaming with from
tomorrow on with my um
transition wire wise with my
uh pocket wifi from with my mobile wi-fi
so i don't know we might have internet
issues
um i will still be streaming with my pc
but with my pocket
mobile wi-fi and maybe cardboard maybe
not
i feel like i might get it to work
without cardboard we will see
the wi-fi the high school
[Music]
does take some internet speed doesn't it
um
we can try we can try
i guess actually playing something
on the switch would be even the safer
option because i guess the switch
doesn't take any internet speed
i mean depends on what game we're
playing but i feel like that might even
be the safer option
but i do want to kind of play sliver.io
i don't know
i'll think about it i'll think about it
i'll think about it something short
because i also want to do a members only
stream maybe tomorrow i don't know what
exactly i would be doing
if you guys have any idea what we could
do
in members only you're welcome to give
me suggestions
yeah it shouldn't be anything too long
um
animal crossing yeah i guess oh yeah i
guess we could do animal crossing on
members only
yeah one hour of animal crossing
just uh drawing is not possible because
my my draft
graphic tablet is gone now um
some games on the switch that we could
do that would fit a shorter stream
[Music]
oh no no no no
oh oh and uh and one more thing i wanted
to say
before i forget it because i don't know
what i don't know why i do all the
tangents now
i know there was
this japanese only stream that i wanted
to do before i leave
again
without
do where i would be singing like bloom
songs
i didn't really have time to practice
after all so
i'm gonna be doing that uh once i'm back
in
australia
arigato
okay now that we cleared up all of these
things also yeah also i was just
thinking because we did
the karaoke two times last week and two
two days in a row i just felt like it
would have been too much
of the same kind of stream
yeah i did i didn't want to do a
japanese only final stream but i was
thinking like besides kadoka i wasn't
sure what to do
[Music]
also the the internet speech might be an
issue and i don't
i don't want to mess it up that much um
well well yeah we did that before though
um well i'll do another
i'll do another japanese only stream
soon
i promise to my to my
[Music]
anyway let's get started then
free talk um that's done
[Music]
small talk i don't know i just feel like
uh
i always i still feel so
i don't know like i would ran out of
things to talk
i know you're like you would never get
out of things to talk but no i feel like
yeah i would
need some some some topics
before the stream already so that i can
be sure that i don't run
out of things to talk and today i just
have a lot of things to talk
it's just uh yeah it's just there a lot
of things happened but still
okay let's read
so yeah uh this is where we're
continuing
at uh at decibels uh
war cry
pink nose pattern
i feel like it's a tradition now high
fructose
[Music]
i want to practice more there was a lack
of time this time
oh wait i mean
you guys know what i'm so scared of
actually i have to do you know a certain
test before i leave
and now after it's been like almost a
year since this
certain thing has been around in the
world and i've been lucky to not get it
you know
um but oh now no
now would be the worst time to get it
ever
so i'm legit scared
like i don't have any any symptoms or
anything no
um it's not the nose thing it's uh they
do it um
on the on the tongue so
i i couldn't do that i heard that
the nose well the nose test i heard that
you feel it like in your brain or
something
oh hell no oh hell no not doing that no
thank god they have a different one
but i'm gonna throw up no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no they didn't
even have that option they only had the
the mouth option
so anyway i would be so [\h__\h] s
[\h__\h] up if i if i got it now right
because
then i couldn't even board my plane my
flight
so please please i i pray i pray
that i'll be i'll be healthy
usually usually i'm always
fine though but yeah don't jinx it
one second
did you guys do it before is there
anyone in the chat who did
such a test before
the did you guys do the the brain the
one that touches your brain
me me me yes yes oh my few ones
i've done it more than 20 times why so
often
why so often yes yes yes it was horrible
disgusting
i've had both i haven't done that one
yet it wasn't so bad
mmm did it took on the wig
better safe than sorry oh yeah i guess i
mean in some
in some places it's free and
then i guess it would be easier to
do it anytime and it's necessary
here it's not free there's like a
a big variety in in pricing
but yeah it's not free it's not free
i don't understand what there's like
this a huge gap in pricing so weird
some are like super cheap and some are
super expensive
but when the place where i'm going to
australia
they have uh free tests over there
anyway anyway anyway
anyway
[Music]
thank you for the membership thank you
oh yes it is did you spend too much or
did you get bonked
thank you tai chi season two
i got to know your second account nice
to meet you tai chi number two
nice to meet you
thank you thank you
vanilla
and trevor king custard thank you for
the pinky
orange you glad this is pink
[Laughter]
thank you blue pinky trevor g donkey
[Music]
song
here's my ticket for the orange concert
so happy to see you two back together
i've been waiting for this a long time
yeah i want to do more in like normal
collabs with nanny too
my two favorite youtubers together again
what you got amazing taste
jeffery kitten
kitten may i are you here right now may
i expose you
may i expose you
i will no matter what you say
if i cater the other day you tweeted at
me
and uh i know where you put your brain
in that tweet but you wrote love
challenger instead of heart challenger
in your tweet to me
i know you got it you i don't know you
something something
happened with your brain you did a brain
oopsie
i didn't i was about to point it out
in a reply but i was like no you know
what i'm gonna point it out
in a in a stream
i think you were saying something like
you've been listening to
love challenges so many times and i was
like
huh you can't even get the title right
what the hell
guys have you been listening to heart
challenger
have you been listening to heart
it's almost uh almost at 500
[Music]
please listen to heart challenger please
please please please please
put it in the playlist with a short
video
and then repeat it because normal
repeating the same video over and over
again
[Music]
like people who aren't like super
informed about every single
member in whole live english
if they get asked to like who they think
he's like like a singer of life english
i feel like because of kelly's recent
projects
most people would say cali but i i wish
that
people can also mention me when they
talk about
who is a singer of whole life english
because i
i put out two singles where i'm like
actually singing
like you know i i
it's like j-pop songs
but i still feel like so many people
don't don't even realize that
that i've been doing that weirdly enough
yeah and the cover and the cover that's
true
don't forget about the coffee
[Music]
you guys don't need to mention a million
other good singers i know
suicide senpai is amazing at singing i
know gouda is
amazing at singing i know i know but you
understand what we're talking about
right now
the the point that i'm trying to make is
when people think of
takanasi kiana i would like them to also
be like like not only see me as
the the girl who is crying because of
technical issues
i would like them to see me as um
you know more than that now preferably
also as as a singer
like your king cover thank you
that was great right
[Music]
and
all this life reaction yeah that was
funny
thank you for both blessing us with this
orange concert and for representing
orange and underappreciated color
that is true it is kind of
underappreciated isn't it
isn't it i do agree with that
orange and yellow are a bit
underappreciated
[Music]
um
thank you for the pinky sing progress
uh i suppose you enjoyed our
uh our concert thank you
thank you thank you so much for your
support
[Music]
are both really great singers and
they're so in sync with each other oh
even though we barely practiced i'm
happy to hear that
thank you for the amazing ends to the
week you make us uh
proud to be kfb employees slash husbands
we are like yoga thank you
thank you so much
um
hmm it's like yeah that name is like a
smiley face
oh static snake thank you
i have a conspiracy that keanu has two
hair buns under both of her hats
that's how they stay on her head you
probably learned that trick from super
energy
um maybe i don't know i feel like that's
kind of a cute hairstyle um
uh like do you guys know um thomas
empire
toy senpai's outfit uh the one where she
has
her i think it's her new year's outfit
where she has like
um shorter hair than usual but she has
these buns
on top of her head and i love those
those are so adorable
maybe that's what i'm hiding underneath
my hats what's up
that's when i took off my hats maybe i'm
taking off my my buns whenever i take
off my hats maybe
maybe every time i put on my hats i'm
turning my
uh my hair below into buns always
hasn't stopped
but maybe maybe maybe i'm maybe i'm
hiding
cat ears underneath who knows
except the onion um
should i should i embrace the fact that
i am
an onion and that i do have layers
do i have to do that
mmm
[Music]
also thank you for renewing your
membership thank you
thank you for today's oran's concert it
was so fun can't stop popping my head to
the tunes
well done kiara and energy we want more
in the future thank you
we chose the songs um together uh this
time
and uh
i think we both chose some really good
songs but the k on
the keon song was chosen by ninety oh
it was so hard i i mean i love all the
chaon songs and i've heard them a
bazillion times but that one was so hard
to practice i don't know if you guys
ever tried singing that song
but even for um even for japanese people
like that one is so hard
to do
[Music]
that's like pretty much a wrap but like
in a very cute way
oh yeah daft punk oh yeah i heard about
it i was so confused about it well
because everyone was tweeting out
something i did like um daft punk a lot
actually
i listened um to daft punk every now and
then
that's uh even hookah papa tweeted about
it
thank you for the membership uh
there was this there was this one song
of daft punk i think that i was thinking
of
singing in an aircraft karaoke at some
point
wait because because
of a reason
wait which one was it did i save it here
no ah yes get lucky
because in the lyrics
like the legend of the phoenix oh there
we go
oh ends with beginnings it starts like
in
literally it's the first line it's
literally the first line
[Laughter]
like the legend of the phoenix
that's why i wanted to put it into one
of my unarchived uh streams
karaoke streams oh i love i love that
bank
i did like that group a lot
we've come too far to give up
who we yeah french house oh that's
called french house like unless you
don't know
what to call that genre that's french
house
i've never heard of that french house i
mean i know house music i guess
that's house music
oh so wasn't there like a
wasn't there like a pentatonix cover of
a deaf punk song and that was so good
too
even even now they disbanded now it's
even now it will be even more like
em emotional and fun if we sing that
in our anarch now it has
i don't know this sentimental feel to it
for some people for the people who are a
fan
my actual finally opened are you sure
you want to get out of there
you're just getting closer and closer to
your death you sure you don't want to
stay in your egg but okay it's just
your decision it's your decision
i mean aren't we all every day getting
closer and closer to our death
aren't we all i'm just being i'm just
being poetic right now
philosophical burp philosophical phoenix
philosophical phoenix philosophy phoenix
should i make like should i make a
serious video series of a philosophical
phoenix doing like philosophical
statements like
you die when you are killed
hashtag philosophical phoenix
and everyone will be like that's some
deep [\h__\h] bro
that's deep as hell bro
it's kind of like my i need to continue
my comedienne
thing as well
me
old trees are no the trees are not blue
hello vlog you're full of [\h__\h]
trees are green stupid
stupid sometimes they're pink
anyway genie thank you so much for the
red super dad
did we go on a tangent because of this
super chat how did we get here
oh yeah we did go on a big tangent
thanks to judy
started with uh talking about google
maniac
how the [\h__\h] did we get to death punk
though
[Music]
um
japanese bro asked about the bracelet
that kelly gave me
i was so surprised when she gave it to
me i didn't think she would do that so
quickly
like she's so busy and we just sang
about it in a song like three days ago
and there she goes
she told me that she was like ordering
like a bracelet making set
in her members only stream and her
members apparently knew about it
oh wait you guys i'll be right back
wait don't worry don't worry i'll be
right back
oh yeah oh yeah
this is this is okay this is okay
one one second what what happened to you
oh yeah
this is okay
no no i'm still here don't worry
don't you worry uh
let's go don't you worry
i'll be right back this should work this
should work
i'm doing some weird stuff right now you
know to to get this to work
there we go all back to normal
hide and seek time mama mom oh
you guys are crying oh he's so cute
i love you guys you guys are too cute i
want to kiss every one of you
i want to hug every one of you
thank you mama is back
so anyway we were talking about the
bracelet yeah
she made the she made it in her stream i
guess
one is much bigger than the other by the
way some people even pointed it out in
the picture
i thought that maybe you guys wouldn't
notice for some reason she made um the
blue one much bigger
so it's not actually like you can't
really really
wear it as a bracelet because it's like
way too big
i have to make it um she only ordered it
on stream ah she didn't make it on soon
so i have to try to make it um
smaller because i took the i took the
blue one we were talking about
should i take the blue one with the
money or should you take it
like how do we do it but i felt like i
want i want her to be with me
so i took the one no she said it's not
really adjustable
the she had some issues i think with the
string
and if i would open it it would probably
just i would have to get a new string or
something
and redo the whole thing if i understood
it correctly
now it's also it's just if it's just a
kitty kitty
it's not long enough to be a choker
or a necklace no no for that it's too
short but it's too long to be a bracelet
but that's okay i mean i i was so
freaking happy
i was so surprised that was the sweetest
thing ever
what is she with the string she used the
ribbon and said why you know everything
where are you
you guys know everything ankle bracelet
if you think my ankle bracelet is
so much fatter than my my hand
handwriting
ankle they're pretty much the same size
what the hell
wait what do you think my my ankles size
is
what
[Laughter]
uh
hand ankle question my question [\h__\h] you
what do i know what do i know
give it to white kiara ah that would
solve a lot of problems indeed
[Music]
um i was so that was
that was so adorable i never expected
her to do that
ah oh man
i was literally screaming we were in a
in a restaurant and i was screaming
i was like what what
what what what
that was so cute i can't get
freaking over it i cannot get over it
it's
it's just oh man
i can't stop smiling
streaming in public screaming in public
not streaming
although there are people who stream
outside don't they that's pretty cool
irl streamers
the set list was so good blue club for
hype heart challenger is so cute
you finally connected yeah except the
times the forgotten lyrics level
p.s you can i actually i didn't really
forget the lyrics like i was looking
um on at the lyrics on like paper
and on the screen and it was confusing
me from time to time
uh which part is whose part that's when
i
i suddenly like i lost track of where we
were but yeah
yeah if you know i bought a line wasn't
that low both
and you sounded kind of sexy to be
honest oh cool thank you
i'm i'm glad i got to sing it with her
uh together i love that song so much i
love all the the macros delta songs are
so freaking good
um
a lot of you guys seem to like that one
the most
out of that stream everyone was like uh
but borderline ikinai borderline was so
good
naganei
i'm glad you guys liked it thank you and
i'm so happy that netan
learned a hard challenger for me so on
in the takamuni stream on the day before
we sang hinotori together and then on
the next day with nineteen or enzo
we sang her challenger together
see what i did there both of my both of
my
original songs got covered with with my
best friends in her life um
i love dinner i love her
she actually i didn't tell you guys she
gave me a gift too
she gave me a gift
i should i should have i should upload a
photo
of it on twitter but she gave me like
two cups
um from starbucks
with like a because it's it's japan only
it's japan limited
with like a sakura design and the cops
are like not normal cops they're like um
uh formal cups is that what you call it
like when the inside is like out of
steel
to keep the the drink hot
longer the firmest
cup and she bought me two because uh she
i guess she knows that i'm i'm gonna be
living
together with someone else again
i i was i was a bit confused to be
honest because she was she was kind of
like saying like
oh because you have two cats
uh right and she gave me those cups and
i opened them up and i'm like yeah well
these are for humans what are you
talking about in a town
i don't know what the house is i don't
know if she gave it
to me for my cats but it's like
cups for humans and and i do have a
roommate so
i was like okay maybe that's what she
meant but she was she was mentioning my
cats so i'm like so confused
but anyway i'll be using it i guess with
my roommate
that's that's not something that that my
cats can drink out of it's a bit
too high the cup is a bit too high for
my cats to like
go in there
i mean i don't know i'll use it for
myself
[Music]
[Laughter]
a lot she's like besides kelly
i feel like she's my um my bestest
friend in in in her life
um so i'll be missing her
i really like her her room
her room oh my god it's like
there's literally bears bear plushies
huge bear plushies everywhere she told
me it's okay to talk about it
yeah yeah i uh yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yeah yes i visited
[Music]
i i definitely know what to give to her
if it's her birthday because she
i knew she kind of liked bears but i
wasn't i didn't realize she liked
berries
that much there's like millions of
bears in her room like like all kinds of
bears but mostly like bears that you can
buy in disneyland because i guess she
goes to disneyland a lot
um she said she even said she was
thinking of
um instead of the cops she wanted to buy
me a disneyland ticket but
uh she wasn't sure if i would be able to
go because there's not much time and
blah blah it's kind of hard to get into
i mean disneyland is open here but it's
kind of hard to get in because they
restrict the amount of people who can
get in
but anyway we made a promise that one
day we'll go to disneyland together
um
her birthday is actually pretty soon
uh i think it's next month isn't it
but i won't be there like i wanna i
wanna give her some a physical present
[Music]
um how do i do that maybe i ordered
something on japanese amazon
i don't know i don't know i'll think
about it but
it's so easy now because now i know
exactly what she likes she's
she's addicted to bears
i guess i could give it to him i could i
could buy something already now
and then give it to genma and then have
her keep it until her birthday
bears bears are really cute huh
yeah we'll find a way we'll find a way
to
give her something but i really want to
give her something for her birthday
she's such a sweetie i love her so much
and she's she's such a hard worker
and and she she had so much patience you
know
with all that stuff she still has a lot
of patience
and i just want to really support her
and and
and i just like her so much i like her
personality and her singing voice
and i can we can i feel like we both
relate
um on a few levels on a few topics uh
quite well
um
continuing traffic thank you thank you
now to rock the english part of our
challenger
her pronunciation was better than yours
tanjo now listen here trevor g
little [\h__\h] that
that is that is so stretched
trevor that is such a stretch
[Laughter]
she was just like i love
you which is totally fine that was
adorable
but are you freaking kidding me
that's [\h__\h] don't
this nana english
but it is i i understand it is difficult
to pronounce that
oh did you just chill to her
no i didn't really the opposite
super english not so much
[Music]
i was when i was actually i did um a
part of
pilot i don't know what's a good way to
say it
um distribute it i distributed the
lyrics
for like uh 90 of the songs
um and uh
i was like i mean i could sing
the english part all on my own
because i speak good english but
i want to be fair so i was like
john you're singing that line
i i told her she has to sing that line
so you know i want it to be fair
with distribution of the lines
no i just don't i just don't wanna want
it to be
do you mean contributed no no i mean
distributing
i mean parting saying who sings which
line
oh yeah i split up the lyrics yes this
is oh my dear lord
thomas oh wait i didn't read the rest of
tribute you two have such a wonderful
connection it was super orange concert
and worth
both the ancient exit trees thank you
both thank you too
was that your neck yes
um i i really want to do a 3d concert
with her hopefully hopefully maybe this
year
we'll we we will practice much much more
and then
and then we'll actually be dancing
holy [\h__\h] you know when she'll be like
yo yo yo yo you know that those
those moves that that rappers do she'll
be like yo
yo yo yo with her hands
to do all those hand movements well i'll
do my sexy
boob mating uh dance
oh my god what if she pulls out her
flute and she might be like
and i'll be like a snake i'll be like no
no no no
do you have any idea what i'm imagining
i'll do like um
like how do you call that when when
someone controls the movement of a snake
you know what i'm talking about yeah
snake drama kelly
m snack coming soon by the way i'll do
that eventually
and i'll just do my sexy my sexy rolls
well this is how we will make the best
use out of 3d
kelly will be like and i'll be like
a snake snake
oh my god
oh snack charmer challenge
kitchen
[Music]
a question um what are you
what are you gonna like do like uh like
an official english version of your song
i wanna cover it i love your song but
i i don't i don't trust myself to sing
it in indonesian can i please have an
english version i think everyone wants
it
are you thinking of ever doing an
english version
you really should that song is so cute
english version please please please so
that i can cover it i'll think about it
okay
what you weren't thinking about it up
until now what the hell
you were not thinking about it yet
please please english version once you
have it please send it to me so that i
can cover it
oh in a karaoke stream i love your song
so much
i love how how it's also like a like it
could be an anime opening just like my
songs
and this to make it hundred so you
expect me to treat your super chat now
as a as a red one because you sent
your super chats separately
bird language cover though no no no no
no english english
english english place english
well looking for the top oh thank you
for the pinky
oh thank you for the pinky
[Music]
you think you can just add those
together how you like it and then say
this is a red one
okay
if they're all like after one another
then okay
but this is this is this is borderline
illegal
but it's okay i saw you sent a lot of
super chats
it's okay it's okay
but now that is followed up by an actual
red super chat from sumit janato
thank you for the red super
best life thank you carol and energy
thank you too for listening thank you
for tuning in and enjoying it together
with us i'm very happy that
you all were there thank you
thank you for the pinky
foreign
um
[Music]
this is for the two amazing concerts
really enjoyed seriously thanks andrew
thank you for listening thank you
thank you those actually those those
karaoke
streams take way more
preparation than i thought they would
because
uh obviously i try to not repeat um
the same songs all over again so i tried
to
learn some new songs for these streams
and
you know splitting their lyrics and
preparing
um you know all kinds of effects and
stuff like that
it does take more time than i thought it
would
so i'm glad you guys are enjoying it and
always showing up
in big numbers thank you guys very much
so let's move on to the takamoni stream
we i hope we can finish them
i hope we can finish them oopsie
i mean it should be fun maybe we can't
go to mario kart super chats but
at least we should be able to finish
those kodi
[Music]
stream i think there's a lot of red
super chats
so uh we're gonna be reading a lot of
messages
okay i'm scrolling i'm scrolling
red carpet
almost oh show audit
scrolling scrolling scrolling you guys
went
crazy you guys went absolutely crazy in
that stream
[Music]
um
thank you guys so much i'm i was like
overwhelmed
i i i was like what the hell
what guys i'm so glad you liked it so
much though
i was very surprised scrolling scrolling
[Music]
down
i reached it
let's go hopefully none of these super
chats class crying
and honestly i i feel like like
generally
when i'm streaming i when it comes to
like messages
unless it's like hate messages unless
it's hate messages i usually don't
get too emotional like most of the time
when i'm streaming my
my brain is like it blocks off a lot of
those
emotions i know it's a
weird because i cried a lot in the
beginning but that's something else
that's something else that happened
because of stress and because of
things going wrong but reading messages
i don't know it's weird like in a stream
i feel like i gotta you know keep my
[\h__\h] together
um but i do know that when i'm on the
plane
i'll be crying oh yeah i saw tacoma he
was trending on twitter that was so cool
guys
what
what is she really sleeping
reyna you're still watching you need to
do something about your gen mate she's
sleeping
wake up
how the [\h__\h] do you fall asleep on
stream
how do you fall asleep is she really
sleeping or did you just leave her desk
for a moment
only passed out why
how do you fall asleep now that's isn't
that like kind of impossible
isn't that how how does that happen
what i don't understand
like even kelly doesn't do that even
though she's so tired how do you
you would act i mean i mean wouldn't you
actually have to be
actively trying to fall asleep
i mean if you get if you get to the
point that you're about to fall asleep
wouldn't you like
stop the stream and go to actual sleep
she yawning a lot from the free prime
side of the stream it's been 82 minutes
huh
kelly fell asleep before how long was
she really asleep you know
maybe she was just closing her eyes for
a little bit how long how long
is only like this
how long has you been like this
how long has it been like 20 minutes
i want to see like i want to go to the
archive and then what's the moment like
the moments before she fell asleep wake
her up and what can i do like there's
nothing i can do
account name
oh my god moto account name sent a red
super chat
he changed his name again kfp taka lion
shipper
oh because of bhutan senpai oh that's
kind of cute then
you're supporting taka lion now
takarao
one more whole live member that i can
cross off of my list for
like meeting them while i'm in japan
yay
okay i'm all the way all the way down
okay i'm back i'm back
[Music]
don't worry
add it
ah okay
okay okay mama
is mama can't find mama you guys are so
adorable oh my god i love you
you guys are so cute why are you guys so
cute
why are you guys so cute
[Music]
a
i am back sorry kind of unstable
might even be worse tomorrow i'll be
disappearing a lot tomorrow i suppose
thank you
we love you tanjo not as much as dad
loves you but
no matter what will always be kfp strong
thank you thank you i love you guys soon
i love you too
thank you okay guys um i i know she's
sleeping i
watch your stream i can't do anything
about it so you can stop mentioning
it guys thank you thank you
read the rules please i know it's funny
it's very funny but i have to do my own
stream okay
i have some [\h__\h] to do
dr pepper
thank you so much for the sweet message
thank you i appreciate your support very
very much thank you for the generous
donation
is
thank you for another war crying but i
have to be a bit quiet today so
i just be reading it quietly
on this day we k of beats
declare in one voice we will not go
quietly into that good night
we're going to fight on today we
celebrate our two queens glory to
takamuri
someone asking me how i am for their
name
and then now that's big brain i would
say hey glory to takamuri thank you guys
thank you
how are you i feel much better than
yesterday as i said before
and much less stress there's um a lot of
like
uh when i what i still have to do is
um like like paper stuff you know
i gotta i gotta uh do some paper stuff
some administrational things
um and uh
yeah a few few more things than that
it's not over yet i'll uh i'll be i mean
they cut off my internet tomorrow but
i'll still be here
uh for a little while longer that's why
i said i'll be streaming with the
pocket wi-fi but the the most stressful
things
are done i guess
the only thing that i'm a bit worried is
that i still have so much trash
but there's like a maximum amount of
trash that i can throw out per
per trash day and
i only have two trash days left
basically
i think well not not really even
i don't know i'm not sure if i can throw
out all my trash in time i don't know
what i'll do when
if they don't take all my trash
hoarding no actually every i knew that
this was gonna happen so
actually since like two weeks ago i've
been
um trying to throw out as much as
possible
early and early on so that i won't
have this kind of situation but yeah
here we are here we are
[Music]
um
oh
[Laughter]
guys guys i can it is impossible for me
to wake up ollie okay um there's nothing
i can do
[Music]
her her people have been informed
there's nothing i can do okay so
uh i know i know she's asleep okay
i know i know okay let her sleep okay
what just let her sleep
let her sleep in peace if she wakes up
she wakes up if she doesn't wake up then
she doesn't wake up it's funny either
way
isn't it funnier if she's if she stays
asleep
when do you guys feel like that's
funnier
so just let it be let it be let it be
let it be oh let it be
whisper words of wisdom let it be
got it okay rule number four is it
really the rule number four in my in my
rules thank you guys please uh now shut
up about
foreign rule number four is it really
the rule number four though
because i changed my lyrics is it really
wrong my lyrics are my my my rules
is it really rule number four do i have
it as rule number four
is it oh okay okay well then everyone
read
the runa before in the description
otherwise i must recruit you and say you
know the rules and so
do i do you really know them though it
seems like you don't
anyway
justin bieber it's a mystery thank you
for the flight to fancy thank you for
the pinky thank you
no words of it so i don't know what to
say but thank you very much for the
support
none of us are fancy i'm glad you liked
it
jogie raiden duncan thank you for red
super chat
it's girl's love wasn't that funny
i i suggested to kelly that we would
sing that song i'm so glad you sang it
with me
it's girls love i love that one i love
scraps i need to read i've rewatched it
so many times
i need to rewatch it again and again and
again and again
i love that musical episode they had
really good songs
and i just love um jd and turk so much
and i changed the lyrics it was me who
changed
the appendix appendix line into
um the soul line etc so
that everything fits better
it helped you get the bracelets exactly
exactly
those bracelets wouldn't have happened
if it wasn't for that song
yeah i'm still laughing about it every
time i think about that cover
[Laughter]
it's a it's a great great song to sing
for us too yeah
there's this this one thing i'm sad
about the song that i sang for kelly
um leaving on the job plane first of all
i thought that i sang it quite well
because i've been practicing that for
many years
and second of all it was like the
highlight um of
that stream but it gets blocked
everywhere so no one can rewatch it and
it was in the unarchived stream
no one can re-watch it that's so sad
i i it does show up though like for
example holo sings uploaded it
and it shows up on my side because it's
not blocked in japan
but it is blocked in so many other
countries
so you know what to do you know what to
do if you want to if you missed it
or if you want to listen to it again and
you know what to do
it's not blocked in every country just
letting you know
it's not blocked in japan just letting
you know
just letting you know
there was something else i wanted to say
what else what did i want to say
my mom my mom randomly called me
yesterday
yesterday night she randomly called me
uh wanted to talk about like random
things
and she told me that she she
she she wasn't in time to watch the at
an archived one and obviously now it's
blocked everywhere so she can't watch
that but you know
the story behind how i got to know that
song right
and i think most of you know how i got
to
know that song and she told me just by
hearing the fact that i sang that song
on stream
my mom cried
so cute she didn't even i think she
didn't even get
to listen to it but just like she she
read it uh in the comments of i think
the the archived potion
or or so and uh then she was like what
she sang
living on the job plane and then she
started crying i think
oh
yeah because there's a yeah
she remembers i guess when she played
that song for me
and i i i sang it like sitting next to
her
because i really liked it yeah that was
that was cute she didn't even listen to
it yeah maybe i should send her the
recording yeah
um
[Music]
oh
i'm gonna explain the lyrics to the
japanese bros
such a beautiful song but by the way i
um
i used to always listen to a
cover version of it not the one from
john denver i listened to the one
how do i pronounce her name
chantal cr crab bits or something like
that
it's like a female cover yeah yeah i
love that one i love
that version so much it's so beautiful
you gotta listen to it if you only know
the original version you gotta listen to
that one
you know it jd edgy dj you turn
where's your turk gd
all that's all to talk about scrubs made
me confused
chantel creviatsuk thank you
the one from armageddon eh
i don't know it's a what is that like
for some movie
was the cover made for a movie yeah i
didn't know about that
i really like the female version um
dr clark's best boy he's
i love him yeah he's freaking dope
i love dr cox gosh every character and
scrubs is so well written but
what do you know in the late in the in
the last seasons it's
uh
because i don't know everyone's like god
and everyone's doing some
something else everyone's doing their
own thing oh the janitor you're the
janitor
oh man
i'm no superman
gosh don't make me feel nostalgic i
freaking love scraps so much
okay continuing droid person thank you
and boop snoop donkey
mangas and bones malone duncan value
cubed by luigi cubed function
guys speaking of valueity what's the
deal with um
wario being everywhere
but while we do not
what's what's the deal with that
nintendo
we don't know
[Music]
warrior is dying too
you're asking a deep question it's like
um it seems like i mean i'm not so
deep into the whole like mar super mario
lore and then all into all those games
but i've noticed that people
like to uh whine about the fact that
wario gets included in games
but rallying doesn't
it's kind of sad
tell me about it violation stance dries
up
because he's like hey that's that's
no that can't be the reason
why she deserves better
oh man you guys have noticed too haven't
you
oh man we need justice for valencia
so sad why did they drop him what that
what what kind of
beef do they have what's behind that i
need some conspiracy for yours now
thank you thank you i'm so glad you guys
liked it thank you
tactician elgat mikey word thank you and
thank you for the pinky
thank you it's okay to be sad
are you quoting kelly on that thank you
for the pinky
mikey thank you
it is indeed okay to be sad but
um i i definitely noticed that because
of the stream
because that the fact that we were
streaming i wasn't able to really like
unleash my emotions
as much as i would have if we weren't
streaming um
as i said i feel like the stream kind of
holds me back which is okay
uh because i don't want to be constantly
crying i'm way too emotional i don't
want to be constantly crying on
on stream anyway but there's something
about streaming that
holds back my emotions because i i guess
my my
my my ski
my consciousness
wants me to control myself
yeah professionalism i guess as well
like while i was singing i was also like
feeling like
i don't know i was holding back a lot
but
but but that song it's just that's that
[\h__\h] song people are more constrained
in public yeah exactly
the exposition effect is that actually a
thing
always stream ended thank you did she
end it herself when
someone ended for her
[Music]
yeah probably um
probably was ended for her okay so now
everyone can stop talking about it
dragon ball z
really shows true bond between you both
props to all you both do
thank you true donko dankeshin
kfb kappa donkey shoe and master
cellophone thank you
thank you for the red super chat glory
to taka money thank you
bye i appreciate it indeed all the glory
to takamuri
ernesto felix is
i still don't know it's still uh
so hard to remember all those currencies
skye are you here by any chance
are you here are you here skye
probably not
let's give him a moment in case he's
here
it is red how do you know
how do you know how do you guys know
no i don't see the colors guys yes it
sky it's just amazing that people who i
call out for
are actually in the chat it always
amazes me how you guys are like there's
these there's these people who are
always
who is in the chat always
well then yeah thank you skye part one
is so touching
it really was but it was also fun like
we started with
you know somebody once told me
i think we had a lot of fun songs and
this shut up oh my god
i was singing shut up i asked kelly to
sing some kind of black at peace song
with me because
i [\h__\h] loved the old oldies of black
eyed peas
and um
[Laughter]
is she colorblind
when i say i don't see the colors i mean
that
legit when you look at the super chat's
uh
history it just doesn't show any colors
anyway what was i saying yeah yeah i
think um it was very touching we had
that last song
and bakeries don't cry was also kind of
emotional but i think there were a lot
of
really fun songs as well shut up oh my
god it must have it must have taken
kelly a while like she said that she's
heard those songs before but
she never tried to sing them and she
learned a whole rap
because shut up you know she she was she
was like wrapping
well i am and every other members parts
except for fergie
so there was a lot for her to practice
she did so well
shut up was so much fun everyone was
going crazy it was like legit like a
married couple
having like you know a fight
it was so yeah and then i did my hands
movement
finally came to use that was
that was i think up until now it's been
like almost six months and this is the
first time where i really felt like
my hand movement fits
i was so perfect
it was like don't talk to me talk to my
hand i feel i don't
listen to your [\h__\h] i don't want to
listen to your [\h__\h]
what's so funny
thank you skye gd also thank you for
read so much oh there's like three red
super chats in a row oh my god
the big red ones sky gd and fodr
damn genie thank you over there
this is all i can say right now i just
can't oh why are you crying it's okay to
cry
i'm not i'm not i'm not gonna make fun
of anyone but i'm
i'm like really um
fascinated by the fact that you guys are
so like some of you are so invested in
it and
um some of you got like i read a lot of
people saying that they were crying i'm
just
i'm i'm i'm glad that we can convey that
kind of emotion through
you know through a stream
through you know a song and
a kind of okay stream i don't know it's
a
i feel like it's it takes a lot to make
someone cry
but i guess it's not just that one
stream it's it's a
it's like six months of streaming and um
just a whole build up you know i guess
there was like a lot of people were like
also really confused like people who
who don't watch our streams who don't
really understand the friendship that i
have with kelly and who don't understand
the bond who were like why you guys are
why are you guys so getting so emotional
both the viewers and
me and kelly why are we making such a
big fuss about
you know me leaving a country i can
still collaborate yeah that's true
but it's like it's like
it's just it's more than that it's like
uh
the only person let me try to explain
in i said i mentioned this in my letter
for callie
in the beginning
i i i i can't like all the whole life
english members couldn't meet each other
i only had county
and um we both just barely have
any friends that we meet uh up with in
real life
and just we only had each other and
especially for me
i really felt like i needed someone and
she was the only one i was able to meet
up with
and that just made us have
a way stronger bond um
and you know we we definitely
i love all the other girls so much but
we had just
so much deeper um conversations and
connections and we even went
traveling together and now it's just
like
i'm leaving and i don't know when i will
be back again just as in i'm leaving on
a jet plane
i don't know that's another thing
uncertainty
is just especially in these times
because it you know the situation keeps
on delaying and delaying itself
it's been a year now and leaving now
who knows when i'll meet her again and
me going to
australia i'll just i'll have my friends
there and i'm really glad to
be able to see my friends again but no
one
whole life related and
you know i'm not allowed to really tell
anyone i mean
i mean my close friends know they found
out but
i'm not really allowed to talk about
like inside things and
all that kind of stuff so it's way more
than just me
leaving a country
some people just don't get it i guess
but
um it's that i'm leaving the person who
i've been
so close to for their past six months in
a time of my life that has been
so life-changing and so impactful
and also stressful and
yeah very very difficult at times too
yeah i am so
[Music]
yes so that kind of stream like a
farewell stream it was necessary
it was necessary to even if we can
collab in the future too
so then we had to have some kind of you
know
conclusion to it um
but obviously we move we will stay
friends and
um probably for you guys not much will
change because we'll continue collabing
yeah
but it's just it's just going to be a
bit lonely for both of us
anyway that's that's that thank you gd
so they are also thank you for red super
jet glory to taka morning
ah thank you everybody for another red
super chat thank you for
your generosity as always fo
thank you i hope you liked both karaoke
streams
and um thank you so much for the support
so glad all of you are so supportive
thank you i love them
thank you i'm happy to hear that really
i hope we chose
some songs that you're like gosh this
freaking folding chair is so
uncomfortable
i don't have much space on this folding
chair
but this is where i'll be streaming on
for the next couple
of streams
it's the only chair i have left
we love all of it thank you
too thick nah the thing is like i always
like to sit on my feet in like weird
positions
like i sit either on one
of my legs or on two of my legs and
i don't know it's just weird positions i
need more space
bowling chair ouch yeah i got rid of my
gamer gold chair today
it's gone it was such a cute chair
i have another gamer gold chair at home
but um
in in australia but
that chair is it's uh my cats use it as
a scratching
uh pole
pool and which i'm totally fine with i
don't care
i i don't give a [\h__\h] about my my cat's
scratching anything
but it's like totally like you see so
many scratch marks all over the
chair you can
i know
no
thank you for watching
thank you thank you we uh wait what was
the first song of the archive portion we
we instantly went back into like a
and a half into like an energetic song
so right it all day days right
so yeah we were able to switch
back into happy mood very quickly
because there was no time
no no of the of the archive potion i'm
talking about yeah yeah
we had like five minutes in between
to clear our minds i tried really hard
to stop
crying
and wipe my tears and then back to
business there is no time
that's it's kind of uh
actually kind of kind of sad i should
have given ourselves more time because
it was kind of like
anti-climb anti-climatic
for us it was like emotional roller
coaster
but i didn't want to leave too much time
because it was supposed to be one stream
you know
anyway thank you
so much i'm fine i'm fine thank you for
your support
thank you for your generous donation
did dad cry she had a
teary eyes yeah she hugged me
don't make me think about it
we think we were sitting so close next
to each other because we were singing
into
one microphone we were like already
squeezed next to each other but then
yeah
when when i started crying
she hugged me and then while i was
staying with fine
she was holding my hand
yeah anyway
no man
no man she definitely recently
probably because i'm leaving she showed
me her
dead aside a lot
the
thankfully i couldn't
if she would have been sentenced to me
as always
even though i'm leaving i would i
couldn't take it
oh man wrestler thank you thank you
i was not ready you both are wonderful
people oh
thank you you're a wonderful person too
thank you somber apoc thank you for
the generous donation thank you for the
red super chat
you should have been ready we all knew
we all knew that it was going to be
at least somewhat emotional everyone was
like
i'm ready for this but then when it
actually happened everyone was like i
wasn't ready for this
thank you dominique
is hard but hey it's not the end of it
i'm sure the both of you will meet again
soon take your time sorting out your
move and the kfbs will eagerly await
your return glory to takamuni
thank you yeah i wonder i wonder how
early i'll be able to stream once i come
back
home to australia
i'm planning to actually guys i was
thinking what do you guys think of um
um me opening
at some point opening like a waiting
room
for like a stream like i don't know in
one year later or whatever and it will
be it will be titled
waiting for uh the phoenix to land
so it's basically like i don't know how
many hours it will be but uh it will be
just like you guys in there waiting for
me
to to write in the chat phoenix has
landed
yeah like a free chat and you guys gotta
just be there waiting for me
eventually after a million hours i'll be
like i have
freaking landed the phoenix has landed
and everyone gotta like has to like
like go crazy and report the phoenix i
love that
the phoenix said that i report the
videos landed
write it in the newspapers report it
everywhere and then
and then you're gonna make it then you
gotta make it trend on twitter
hashtag the phoenix has landed
i don't know i don't think we can make a
trend but but i thought that the waiting
room would be a fun idea
as soon as i get like internet um
connection or like i guess
as soon as i'm back in my in my uh in
between some walls
then i'll be like i have freaking landed
[\h__\h]
should i do that i was thinking of doing
that yeah
okay i might i think i'll do that then
then you guys can
like have a chat and and wait and wait
and who will be the lucky ones who will
be there
in the chat when the phoenix lands who
will be able to
witness a phoenix landing
you're gonna hand maybe like in her
in her talk here maybe maybe that's what
you will witness
i wonder though should i should i turn
super chats off
if you guys can promise me you won't go
too crazy i might turn them on
maybe or i'll i'll tell
um maybe i'll tell genma to turn them on
the moment i'll land
so it's at least not for like what 70
hours
constantly turned on was only turned on
for my landing
we'll see what i can do
now i'm counting on you guys to
to witness the landing of the phoenix
epic epic pure epicness
so yeah anyway scoot thank you thank you
thank you
that number that's um
how freaking much is that oh my god
thank you so much that must be
like i think at least a double red super
chat thank you tai chi
that's probably why you needed to make a
sub account i understand completely now
thank you tai chi ma
thank you for the insane support glory
to takamuri he says
wow did you cry taiji it's okay to cry
don't feel bad about it if you did
i i wish i could give you a hug thank
you so much
thank you thank you thank you
thank you for the support i hope you i
hope you receive a virtual hug
just imagine it
thank you i helped you
mass mention
butter
the first half was beautiful we love
your attention so does kelly stay strong
kfb is here to support you no matter
what thank you
thank you thank you
i'm so glad to have you guys thank you
i love you all too typhon thank you so
much
you're you're the legal drone does that
mean you can you can follow
um my flight and then
reports to the viewers where i am
no we don't want to we don't want to dox
me so legal drone yodo school please
don't dox
my flights you're you're allowed to
follow the flight as a drone oh are you
not that kind of drone
is that not what a legal drone is are
you not a flying drone are you flying
drone
you're allowed to follow it and then
later on release um
release the footage of the flying
phoenix
it's not it's not that kind of drone
what's it like what is it is that not
one of
legal as yeah i get that but the drone
oh a mindless worker oh you can't fly
well that's lame typhon
lame i thought you could fly
ah okay chickens can't fly
ah
you guys just gotta believe in yourself
you give up too early like just because
someone tells you you can't fly doesn't
mean you can't fly
you could fly if you want to
don't give up so early
thank you tyson 99.99
your name always confuses me because the
first word is kind of like a german word
i don't know if you
chose it as a german word on purpose but
the second part is
english so the pronunciation confuses me
every time thank you for the red super
chat though
i've been preparing for it since you
first mentioned special song i was not
prepared thank you
that's exactly what i was talking about
you guys were like
i was originally german oh god so you
are aware of it
it's it's difficult to pronounce like a
combination of a german and an english
word
very difficult yacht crap
yeah you guys thought you were prepared
and then you're not prepared what the
hell
you should have known it was coming but
it's okay
sometimes it just catches you off guard
right
let me kiss away your tears
not licking i'm not like ahmed i don't
lick away tears
okay i kiss away your tears i don't lick
your tears
i wasn't ready for those fields i'm not
ashamed to admit i cried too we all did
oh my god you guys are so cute
i can't believe it i mean there's
nothing bad about it
there's really nothing bad about it but
i'm
um as i said i'm i'm i'm amazed
that we were able to get those feelings
across
yeah wow wow
but i think that just means that this is
that just
shows you know the connection that i
have with my viewers since i'm always so
open with you guys
and um probably the most
emotional one out of her life english
the one that cries
too much on stream and and shares too
much on stream
i'm i'm definitely the one who's the
most open about
everything in my life so
yeah we we definitely have a
a very strong bond you guys and me don't
we
maybe that's why you guys got so
emotional together with me
well cameron thank you so much for the
support
i appreciate it very much thank you
thank you thank you
from the bottom of my heart thank you
ak stf2 thank you
thank you for the pinky i love you mom
and dad we love you too
thank you very much king of the property
thank you
carlos chavez thank you so curious thank
you and friendly neighborhood lesbian
thank you so much for everything you
girls do you're both absolutely amazing
talent and we all love you thank you
thank you so happy to hear that thank
you
thank you
[Music]
this isn't just a karaoke it's a
celebration of the love and friendship
that keeps us going every day to achieve
our dreams and to work hard to become a
greater version of ourselves
no matter where we are on this beautiful
world our hearts
world our hearts will keep us close wow
that's
that's really deep bro
i guess i guess yeah i guess i agree
thank you for taking it so seriously
thank you
and now there was definitely a lot of
thought behind it
and a lot of emotions
thank you very much danny scope
i appreciate the support and i'm glad
you liked it so much thank you i hope
you will come again
darren wait thank you stick the figure
thank you
thank you for the pinky everest and
thank you for saying it's a pinky
because you know i can't read
uh i can i can't read i can see the
colors unfortunately
i knew what was coming but damn it so
hurt so much all i can say now is glory
to takamari
indeed thank you thank you
i feel the same way as you do
thank you or liable cats thank you
subscribe
thank you for the wonderful stream you
too you guys are such a great tool
friends will always be there even from
afar i love you guys
thank you my girl was so sweet
i'm glad you like us as a duo and we
will do our best to
um do some more collabs even when we're
far apart
to bring you some more wholesome
takamori content thank you so much
thank you sacred edge
hamilton doctor excellent
[Music]
the next collab remember it's not the
end of your movie because very close
door it's just the intro of a brand new
kusa toy
thank you club thank you
thank you very much i'm glad you liked
it
yes it is uh it's not the end but i'm
glad we finally sang that song together
that's
that was such a perfect last song i mean
we did an ancorum
but it was a perfect last song
[Music]
the last song was amazing what are you
talking about uh the
actual the last song live again or are
you talking about
[\h__\h]
either way thank you that means that my
rap was good thank you
or are you maybe he's still talking
about the one in the
archived portion because this is
probably still the beginning of those
super chats damn
live again
i don't know
[Music]
wait let me translate
thank you for the red super chat wow we
love you mom and dad our love will never
wave forever glory to takamoni forever
thank you so much thank you
that's so sweet i love how people
started calling us mom and dad
how did that even start
like i guess people started calling me
mom because
like it was kind of separate like i feel
like it kind of happened separately
as well because people started me
calling started calling me mom for
several reasons
like for once it was the the fact that
i i said that i'm raising you guys as my
children because you're my eggs and my
chickens and i hatched you and all that
but then there were other reasons that
came together and kelly started getting
called dad and i don't know
kind of started separately and suddenly
we were mom and dad
oh because of the manga she was reading
i don't know so many things came
together
kuda said it too
yeah it just had to happen it was
destiny
thank you gamerpad
logical paradox
russian name
one second
oh yuma yumanai
russia
[Music]
a
you may not know when you'll be back
again but you will be back we love you
so so so much attention so does kelly
all of us will be
with you as for for as long as you have
us by your
side glory to taka glory to kfb and
going to takamoni
thank you thank you guys
thank you i have one more hour left do
you guys think i can finish it
one more hour until i should probably
end my stream
mm-hmm let's go let's [\h__\h] go
speed breakdown thank you
foreign
thank you thank you thank you
so much
um
the stream is kind of lagging is it
really
really eric
the kfb tentacles oatmeal cookie dough
a bit sometimes not it's okay for me
like i said maybe it depends on the
country
it's buffering in here you you
at least damn europe seems to have
issues the most like up until now
whenever i've been streaming
whenever some country had issues it was
like always europe
will i be affected if i stream from
europe
it's it's always europe what the hell
it's always europe
we just have shitty internet in europe
we really do oatmeal cookies
or isa
thank you and vampiric otaku thank you
for
a red super chat
never say goodbye if you don't say
goodbye then you aren't really gone
you just you just you aren't here right
now stay strong buzz you'll see each
other again someday
all of us are here for you and i have no
doubt callie will miss you just as much
glory to takamori thank you
[Music]
thank you vampire kotaku i appreciate it
thank you for the support
but it's it's not only that i've been
sad about leaving cali it's just
generally
i'm a bit sad about leaving japan too
because
you know it's for me it's a big step to
once again
leave everything behind again i've done
this many times in my life
many many times i've moved between
continents
many times and i just every time it
makes me feel very emotional
it makes me wonder if it's the right
decision
and all that kind of stuff it's because
it
it is a huge thing um
and you know you always kind of think of
like am i missing out on something am i
doing the right thing i don't know
but yeah there's no place like home true
yes
that is true i mean in in in my
earlier days when i first moved away
from my country
it was like i didn't really like
australia like i didn't appreciate it
much
um but after being away so long from my
country not only this one year
it's more than that after being away
from it for a long time
and realizing how difficult it is to
live in japan
anyway as a foreigner it's just yeah
it was a quote from rvb what's rvp
uh what was i saying stop spamming
what was i saying
brett was his blue internet show i have
no idea what that is
anyway yeah you know what i'm saying
you know what i'm saying guys
but i can i can
i think i can
this time i think just the excitement of
seeing my cats again
overpowers everything so
strong that i'll be fine i think
i'll be fine um
[Music]
um
i'm explaining to my japanese viewers
the difference between
the past year living in japan and living
it overseas
because japan just barely has any
restrictions
in this one year and it's just
fascinating how
in this one year i've i basically spent
my year
pretty normally i feel like other people
had to give up way more
but then again the past few months ever
since i joined her
life i've been i've been
barely going outside like maybe once in
two weeks except for like convenience
stores and so on
but like actually going outside to have
like dinner or something
or meeting with a person once every two
to three weeks
not even that much even though i had all
this
um freedom so i personally feel like
when i'm back in australia and i have to
stay home it doesn't really matter much
to me
because even here where i was able to
live normally
i didn't really make use of it you know
what i mean
yeah helen love luck
i i think i agree with that but i will
have to compare
i i really wonder if the people in my
country
are actually following the guidelines
you know
because i do hear some stories from my
friends and
i don't know i'm not sure it seems like
they're all really pissed off
oh well anyway let's stop talking about
that
i'll stop talking about it
what i love when people call me chao
that's funny
k e k e y
ara k yara
i don't know why but i also find it so
funny when people
typo my name into kaido i don't know
it's such a simple
typo but it cracks me up
and they're like oh kaida did this and
that i'm like oh okay my name is kaida
now
or oh my god when google translate
changes my name to
ch
that's like so italian i love it i love
i love
me some italian kiara
if i ever do a trip to italy and bring
my laptop to stream in italy
i'll be changing my name to ch ayata for
the meantime
hong kong
thank you
thank you thank you
for 15 seconds can you can you can you
like make it like maybe maybe eight
seconds
i feel like 15 seconds is such a long
time but i guess my members
my members uh are not affected by it but
but still i feel 15 seconds is so much
vivala
chris parker thank you for the red super
chat i recorded the undercut
part for a friend who couldn't make it
and now i'm crying in the club at 1am
what what you were in the club
it's never leaving my files oh you're
just making a joke right
i love you guys so much and for your
information no i'm not okay
oh chris parker i'm sorry to have made
you cry
it's a meme right okay okay
uh i'm sorry i'm sorry
it had to happen i'm sorry but it's good
to let out your feelings chris parker
wow thank you and thank you for
recording for your friend that's very
kind of you
ryan l thank you kfp evic furniture and
res ralph
13 thank you shouldn't be ghosted cash
500 bucks donation thank you for the red
super chat with only a heart
in it
oh is this like is it are those are
those
deadbeats is that the is that the
deadbeats crew
the cash money makes it very very
it hints at it very strongly it must be
a deathbeat
wow wow thank you so much for that
support
oh my god
damn thank you that was not necessary
but i appreciate it very much thank you
from the bottom of my heart i don't know
if you were ever gonna listen to this
but thank you so much
for the support it's very kind of you
but please take care of yourself too
thank you so much
huge support
scp thank you for the red super chat
scp-079
punched right in the fields love you
guys and hope you get through everything
we'll be fine i think i hope
you actually kelly got
doing our dinner when she gave me the
bracelet
she seemed so clingy she it was like
weird like it was so weird she so many
times she mentioned like she doesn't
want me to leave and
she she she feels like lonely and all
that i was like kelly
kelly kelly
don't make me feel bad about it suddenly
i think she's feeling it it's coming
closer and closer
[Music]
oh man no i feel bad for leaving
bun hmm
but yeah we we will be fine i'm sure i'm
sure
roll river reversal
i try to not think too much about
leaving
you know i try to not think too much
about it i just
i can't even i don't even have the time
to think too much about it there's just
too much to do
anyway thank you for the support for the
red super chat
and your generous donation thank you
soon
d houston also with a red super chat
thank you very much glory to taka boy
very much indeed thank you thank you
so many kisses today i'm glad you liked
the stream thank you for your support
so so so so so much to houston
so many names i read for the first time
in that stream
they must all be deadbeats thank you so
much for supporting me too
thank you i i appreciate
it a lot tremor wrinkle thank you
thank you and i think that's the red one
thank you chunky chunk for the red super
chat
don't make me cry in part two i think
yeah part two was totally fine it wasn't
that
it was not that emotional not even my
letter i don't know it was more like
positive positively reminiscing
about the things that we've been through
thank you chunky chunk i hope you didn't
cry in the second part
the leather was so cute
leather was heartwarming oh the letter
made me cry really
was it so emotional i was reading it
very happily
oh
[Music]
the appendix talk after the letter do
we just go on a little bit of a of a
weird tangent yeah i don't know where
that came from i just
suddenly i just suddenly had to bring it
up
thank you donkey chunk
[Music]
i wasn't expecting to actually be
emotional well
but damn the beautiful relationship
between you guys and
the pain of being a part really touched
me in a different way
oh you guys are so so cute
damn oh man
thank you thank you
i hope you i hope it touched you not
only emotionally but i hope you also had
fun with it
thank you i'm glad you all support our
friendship so much that's
makes me very happy
thank you walter
the admiral duncan you need a ladder
thank you bruno sugar thank you
casper
casper are you gonna make me cry i will
kill you if you're gonna make
i mean you're pretty much invincible by
now and you're a ghost anyway but
don't make me cry with this okay
even though we'll be apart and always
remember all the fun we have together
it's a good time
[Music]
i i wanted to say yes hopefully we will
meet again
but you freaked me out many times so uh
and i have cats i think it's better for
your safety
that we at least don't meet in australia
maybe in japan maybe we can meet again
in japan casper
i hope you will i hope you will continue
like
like talking to me like that not because
of the money but just because i enjoy
reading these messages from him so much
i just love these little messages i hope
he doesn't disappear
please please continue sending me the
messages they're so cute
i don't want i don't wanna like i would
be so sad if i wouldn't hear from you
anymore
i can't i couldn't take such a timeline
where you are not
in it oh casper
i love you i love you casper
i wish you the best casper
i really i really didn't want to do you
any harm in the beginning i was just on
a note freaked me out and i didn't know
what to do
but i i never really wanted to do you
any harm casper
i i like mice i think mice are adorable
and i think every every animal on this
world
deserves to live
a full lifespan
and and a warm ceiling to live in
so i wish you the best and i wish you a
long and healthy life
and i hope that the chocolate didn't
make you poop
too much because you you i know you're
still alive after
eating all that chocolate i know you
just had to poop a lot
i hope it didn't hurt your tummy too
much
i know it must have been hard on your
tummy i know
i'm sorry but you shouldn't have eaten
that you could have
there was an apple there as well why did
you not eat
the apple casper
why i know you like the sweet stuff you
should have eaten the apple
i would have made you strong and healthy
goddammit castro what would you do
without me huh
i'll leave you some food in the ceiling
okay i know where to open it i'll leave
you some food there
um
what what is it i mean i will not
actually do it but why are you guys
telling me not to do it because
he's there anyway and he he will find
like
his way inside anyway whenever he wants
to
why why should i not give him like a
little piece of cheese huh
huh why not not of course not personally
i'm just gonna put it there
okay i probably want but you know it's
the [\h__\h] that cons the the foul
the fault that counts
because he's gross oh you're gross
because mice don't eat cheese
you guys are stupid he eats everything
he literally eats everything
cheese is bad that would be so weird why
is it common knowledge that
like my seed cheese but then
actually it's bad for them what the hell
that is that is such a misleading
knowledge
[Music]
auntie mice cat prep again yeah it must
have been the cats who have been
like spreading propaganda so that they
could hurt the mice
oh cat propaganda
jesus
it's mind-blowing it's mind-blowing
anyway slowest recycled pump thank you
thank you for the red super jam
no distance will be big enough to break
you apart you two
are amazing apart and thousand times
better together glory to takamori
thank you thank you thank you
i'm glad you support us i'm glad you
like our activities together thank you
hopefully so much much more activities
in the future
yes thank you thank you thank you thank
you so much
thank you
for battle thank you for the pinky thank
you so much just remember a hello
follows a little while after goodbye
true you shadow thank you mary nicole
cipher thank you so much
oh my god wait spanking time super
chatting acapella
writing writing acapella in that super
chat means i'm still at the very
beginning
because we accidentally sang solo
in the beginning oh dear lord oh my god
tell me it slowed down after that right
the super chats slowed down
after the beginning right everyone just
sent a million super chats in the
beginning because they were too
emotional
right right i think that
it must be true it slowed down at least
a little bit
[Music]
it never slowed down oh my god
single-handedly made all kfb and
deadweights cry we love the both of you
duet is absolutely perfect
thank you i'm glad
thank you very much
i mean i guess i'm glad i don't know am
i glad for making you cry
cry i'm not i'm not sure thank you
thank you i'm glad you enjoyed it i
don't even know what to say anymore
there's so many red super chats and i
i don't have any more words of of of of
thankfulness and gratefulness left
i'm sorry guys thank you flanders you're
here
thank you
sorry guys i don't know what to say
anymore thank you
i appreciate every single one of you
guys so much though
thank you
so much dear lord
astro dolphin
kitchen wait i don't know how to read
that one
also getting really hungry
shouldn't we
i really hungry shut up hokan
with your dad jokes thank you for the
membership
oh wait uh wait thank you for the red
super chat that was a red super chat uh
see you at song thank you for the red
super chat
thank you glory to takamori
thank you very much for your support
thank you
order delivery i don't want to make so
much trash anymore
i'm it's pretty abundant
it's pretty amazing
the ending for part one really hit the
kokoro hey have a safe trip thank you
viva
takamori thank you i hope it will be
safe i'm really worried if the trip will
go
well yeah that's that's uh
the next big worry if everything will go
well i love the luggage
and uh with you know the test and
the travel itself i don't know i'm kind
of worried
knock on wood okay okay okay it's out of
your control
i guess so um
i hope it won't go well and yeah the
ending of part one
it's just that song made everyone cry
but that's just the one thing that
nobody was able to clip
or upload because of the freaking
blocking in every country
so sad it's so sad why did it have to be
that song
couldn't it have been any other song why
did it have to be that song
i even felt like i did a decent job at
singing it
i love that song so much i wanted people
to listen to it
damn it damn it
and not in all countries
anyway thank you pinkerton i'm glad you
didn't miss it i'm glad you were there
for the moment
yes it's always better to watch it live
anyway hmm
oh my god is that another one of those
that beats dropping 500 bucks super chat
stay lord
what have a safe trip and always
be happy and be together i wish i could
always be together with her that's
unfortunately impossible but thank you
so much for the
big red super chat dear lord oh my god
holy holy moly holy macaroni felix sal
thank you so much for the support
wow wow wow
it's a super chat yeah i guess dad
usually probably calls you a chat so
i'll call you a chat as well you're a
chad
supposedly oh my god
wow thank you for supporting um
takamori thank you i'm really happy
thank you
is quite late now sorry for that thank
you though thank you for watching the
stream and i hope you had a great
birthday
listening to us singing
thank you for the pinky thank you for
the second part and cheering us up you
girls i mean ladies are the best
glory to tackle in the otp thank you
so happy to see you guys like liking us
so much you made me so happy
i'm so happy oh man
if i could have told my i don't know
nine
year old bully itself in june
wait what what what school are you in
when you're nine years old
elementary school yeah i wish i could
tell elementary school chiara that
i would be popular one day i wish i
could
i got i got bullied in elementary and
junior high school but i feel like the
people who get bullied
in those years get really successful
at work in the later years but what does
that help you right when you're young
and you're getting bullied and
you just feel like [\h__\h]
even even when someone tells you that
one day
you'll be the successful one that
doesn't help
i wish i would have known that back then
though that one day
one day i would be popular and people
would be
listening to me talk for hours and hours
and appreciate my existence
really thank you cd and all of you
thank you watson can help you oh maybe i
should
ask ahmed to travel back and
tell me that i will be popular one day
i'll be a beachbody oh yeah
nine-year-old kiara
will not understand what that means
don't alter the timeline yeah
it's dangerous to alter the timeline
indeed i shouldn't do it
now
[Music]
m
my stomach is making sounds
[Music]
i still have some things in my freezer
but i don't have any like
plates or any forks or any knives
or anything left so
i wouldn't even be able to
prepare it i should probably maybe i'll
quickly go to the convenience store
after the stream is over
i just don't want to change out of my
pajamas maybe i should just go in my
pajamas who gives a [\h__\h]
maybe i'll go in my pajamas
thank you je for the red super chat once
again mwah
glory to taka molly love mom and dad
do you hear that chat repeat after je
no matter where you go tensile because
every closed door is just the intro of a
brand new story
glory to takamori thank you thank you
luke
thank you so much thank you for the
membership welcome
and now we are
goblin society thank you for a red
superhero oh my god there's just too
many
help dear lord we're still at the
beginning
but at least that stream was short it
was only 40 minutes or so
yeah i don't think i'll finish yeah i'll
have to remember where i stopped
anyway goblin society thank you for the
red super chat i'm crying so hard my
face tingles but i think i needed this
i wish you the best of luck yeah and i
hope you can make your way back to mori
whenever you want
thank you i mean for a while it will not
be
impossible to go back whenever i want
also have to wait but yeah
eventually i'll be fine for a while um
[Music]
thank you though
thank you i don't know what to say
anymore i feel like i'm repeating myself
so many times because there's just too
many red super chats
or too many super jobs in general like
i'm repeating myself so much
make a note when you finish why would i
make a note when i have kfb sticky notes
huh
you guys even if i remembered myself if
i would ask you i know there will be
people remembering it
i know there's always my sticky notes
that i can rely on
goblin society thank you for your
support i
appreciate it thank you thank you
thank you thank you so many new names
really
thank you i guess they must have really
all come from
kelly's uh cave beets
thank you guys for coming over means a
lot to me
black roses foreign
is
[Music]
um
this uh was going to be a 50 but then
sora you know they started and you
drilled right into my heart
god drill breaking wait you like it um
i guess you're a big fan of the anime me
too and kelly too
thanks for the wonderful stream it's
always standalone remember this isn't
goodbye just and until next time that's
true
looking forward to the future with you
thank you flamex
you know i really i really like um
what's your name again
uh not yoko the the white haired girl
what's her name again
yes yes i really like nina nina
and especially um it was so cool to see
in in
gurendagan how they grow up and see like
um all of them in action again later
when when they're like adults that was
so cool and yeah
turned into a damn hot [\h__\h]
oh yeah i love your flower eyes yeah
like she had this this kind of like
bodysuit going on damn
damn she hot such a cutie
who is your favorite flamex let me know
next time
thank you dr eleven thank
thank you for a red super chat with no
words um
in in in daddy's words i would say what
a chat
thank you for your support thank you
kaya said
responsibly be damned how can i not swim
for this takamorika
okay it's a goodbye but it's also a new
beginning i'm sure there will always be
more chances to meet again and have fun
in the future so please don't be sad
taka money forever
thank you i don't judge you for simping
that's it's
it's totally understandable
but i also don't judge anyone who isn't
stamping because then you know
some people just don't have
why are you guys going crazy over should
be saying daddy
what shut up
shut up shut up
yeah i called callie daddy so what
it's really weird i'm just calling it
because of you guys
normally i would never call her dad
that's so weird
so freaking weird she's not my dad
she's my wife don't make her male
she's my sexy ass wife with the boy in
balloons
why can't we be mommy and mommy tell me
why can't we not
anyway take it monkey thank you thank
you
thank you
thank you for coming to japan and loving
japanese pop culture
i miss you but we all clerks belonging
to the japan branch of
kfb will support you for years to come
clarity
is not
[Music]
so
thank you thank you for red super chat
christopher chad and it had to be when
the drill of love pierced the heavens oh
another good and again fan
glory to takamori i'm so glad there's so
many gorilla gun fans around them that
anime was so insane
it got so crazy i should re-watch it
sometime
[Music]
such a cute iron my such a such a
positive motivating anime
it's like you can do anything you can
reach anything
it's a really good show yeah
thank you abraham i'm glad i'm glad we
sang that song so
that you enjoyed it so much not only you
but a lot of you
legendary song a legendary uh anime
rover fight the power
thank you thank you mexican
the kevin uh cave beach thank you shane
random collusion duncan thank you also
for the red super chat thanks for
bringing being a bright spot in our
livestream
you're welcome thank you for letting me
or letting us be a part of your lives
thank you random collusion wow
i'm so glad i hope it will continue like
that for a long long long time
all the best
thank you wow stop being cute together
doggone it
what is that is that some canadian slang
dog goonit g-u-n-i-t
it's like god damn it oh wait yeah
that's it probably
god damn it is that do do canadians say
that
canadians don't swear oh that's why they
say god god
dog dog gun it that selfie
oh we just won because it's like
canadian dollies
oh it's american slang
are you a fake canadian called canadian
i mean you're right canadian with a case
so
that's already very suspicious i think
we need to investigate
thank you wow thank you so much
i want to visit canada someday i really
do
canadians seem so nice
so nice they're always portrayed so nice
maybe it's maybe it's propaganda though
maybe it's fake maybe they're maybe
they're not nice
maybe they're all freaking rude nah no
way
no way
your name just reminded me of burger
king and it reminded me of the fact that
once i'm back in australia i can finally
eat my favorite
uh burger king burger again finally the
crispy chicken
in the way in the in the form of what
it's actually supposed to be because
they they have a
crispy chicken and the burger king in
japan as well but it's not the same
it's so different so i'm so excited to
eat
that burger every freaking [\h__\h] day
oh my god i worked there really really
you were good burger king yo nice
i got the new kept chicken burger oh
burger king is amazing is kind of hype
broken foot oh no no no no
no no no are you still
married to the burger king i guess i am
we never
we never had a divorce so
yeah charles murphy duncan kevin ventura
my name is thank you for a red super
shot
even a thousand miles of ocean how much
is that in kilometers please
between you we can still trace the line
of fate that brings you and cali
together thank you so much for uplifting
our spirits over these months
many have experienced so much loss but
with you two we found something
beautiful come back home
that is so sweet you are good with words
sir
damn
that's really kind i'm really sweet some
of you guys are so
philosophical and poetic i love to see
it
thank you so much for the support um
thank you hoping hoping for your support
in the future as well
don h thank you klaus fassbender
circumcision
skull zero thank you the bruno guy thank
you for red super chat clap clap [\h__\h]
club indeed thank you
thank you for the right super chat mwah
thank you for the applause i'm glad
you're enjoying it
thank you very much thank you for your
support
of kfp thank you for investing in kfb
stocks
tony bones thank you the karma thank you
soon
thank you you guys really made us go for
quite the lower course of emotions
i really can't express how much i love
your relationship and dynamic and this
is not a goodbye just to see you later
clarity thank you
yeah but i don't know when that later is
you know that's the problem thank you
for the membership
welcome yeah but i'll be fine
i have my cats my cats my cat i'm gonna
ask
my my um
my roommates to record my reaction
just so that i have it for memory
purpose
let's see if i'll cry i might cry when i
see my cats oh my god
i'm so excited i'll be
wait we have like 15 minutes left
hey
i'm collect thank you canvas night
these streams were so fun i'm glad you
two got along so well
wait is this the end actually because
it's it's writing as if it's ending
almost sounds like i'm getting to the
end camera's not are you here do you
know when you sent that super chat
at the end of the song i don't know like
a lot of these super chats
right like thank thank us for doing this
i don't know
i doubt it i'm ready to get along so
well with this blessing i can survive
the next weeks of withdrawal symptoms in
case you have to take a break to get
settled after the move
no i really don't think so i mean unless
i have some really really really
difficulties
with the internet that i can absolutely
not stream which i don't think i think
i think at least worst case scenario
cardboard but um
i i'll definitely be able to stream at
the latest
on the day after i arrive
i plan to do so at least yes don't worry
it will not be a big break and i have my
pc so even if the pc that i'm bringing
along with me will break on the travel
i still have a pc at home which is uh
pretty good so it will be fine
so thank you canvas knight thank you
thank you
for your support as always sprick
seventeen thank you
lorenz
thank you
i just i can't really think of anything
to say you both are amazing and you've
done so much so
for me you've you two are amazing and we
will always love you
and we'll make sure we will fund those
trips to see each other
your amazing stories that we won't
forget oh
damn you guys are so bold
so sweet i'm so glad to hear such things
thank you
i don't know i don't know what to say
but oh damn it
ah thank you for the membership thank
you
thank you
reunion oh thank you
thank you thank you i hope we can
reunite in summer
um i really hope so thank you so much
tyler sundance for also red super
damn two actually that's like two two
reds and one pinky and one super chat
ah thank you this kaioka stream is
totally on fire first part and the sweet
case of death was the pain of departure
second part and the eternal fire of
takamori burning brighter and hotter
than the sun being apart and still
connected for heart for all eternity
wow tyler son
when did you turn into a poet damn
damn yes that's exactly what it is
thank you ma
yes i mean me and kelly are eternal um
[Music]
beings and our love is eternal as well
our whole relationship is eternal so
nothing will be able
to do us part that easily
no worries about that
[Music]
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
[Music]
thank you always for your support and
for cosplaying me as well
thank you tentacled seven three three
six thank you for the red super chat
this is a hard tattoo concert with
heartwarming songs and a very sweet
letter see it's where the letter is so
it's like
it is at pretty much the end
thanks for sharing this with us today we
are introduced to a type of relationship
named takamori today
you've been introduced to it since the
debut day
what tentacle you kind of you're kind of
late on that you've been sleeping on it
you have been introduced way
i mean that's that kind of is uh fitting
to the tentacles i feel like they're
just you know taking things
slow they just chill
the tentacle is just chilling they don't
mind you know
they're just chilling or or
you know that takamoni has been around
for a long time but now you finally
are like oh right
he's the best couple ever otp
he's running on internet explorer
way to roast him oh my god i think
tentacles would never use internet
explorer
oh my god okay guys if we had to
assign which browser each life english
fandom is using i think okay i think my
fans will be firefox because
obvious reasons i mean i'm using google
chrome but
i mean firefox right okay
then what what browser
browser do we assign to uh the deadbeats
what do you think opera
edge
opera opera what even is that
edge what is that what are those
edges let's do
okay let's do edge because she's edgy
she's trying to be okay okay
i'm firefox kelly's and uh
what is good i think gouda might be
i'll leave it to you guys you guys have
you guys are more informed about these
things
uh internet explorer
why though safari
what makes you guys say safari though
what what exactly what about safari
makes you connect her
or not exactly good at but like her
fandom
we're still talking kind of about the
fandom not about gouda herself
what what browser is
that fandom using
i guess yeah um
[Music]
because she's an animal animal equals so
far
i feel like we shouldn't assign internet
explorer to her though
i feel i feel like yeah
i'm just gonna take the upper hand and
say internet explorer
for the chambers what about
what about the tentacles
what's the browser for tentacles
this is this is difficult damn
for tentacles i feel like they're like
just like um the smart people
the i.t people and all that are in the
tentacles
so they would go for a good option like
chrome
[Music]
what's tour what is tour what is that
everyone says so so i guess we're gonna
go for that whatever that is
tentacles uses tor apparently why
what is that it's a dark web oh
why why did you associate that with
that's so weird okay if you guys say so
you guys seem to all agree on that
why shouldn't that be ame
shouldn't that be the the teammates
i feel like the teammates would be using
the dark web
eh ahmed is google chrome
i mean should be edge eh we're having a
we're like big discussions here you know
what i'm
on twitter what's the maximum what's the
maximum options on on
for uh pulse can i enter five options i
think i
is for the most
poor [\h__\h] hell on go on
on youtube can you do more than four
i guess we can do everything but me
because i'm obviously firefox
okay okay let's make a poll on twitter
um assign
uh browsers to each
oh wait how do i do this with a poll
that doesn't even work like that
no it doesn't work like that
hey that's not how it works damn it
what
okay it's gonna be maybe it's gonna be a
longer twitter thread
assigning assigning
browsers to
holo yen fan fandoms
a friend
i kfb
is obviously firefox
so no discussion
on that
okay so and i do a plus and i do a poll
for um
[Music]
tentacles okay and then i give them a
bunch of options
and it was tour we can give them four
options so let's give them four options
what would be another option b
i think chrome
and what else i need i can enter two
more options
opera and
netscape
what is that i've heard of it okay
pulling for one day
okay okay plus
chambers this is gonna be fun
okay somewhat internet explorer
uh what else
yahoo and safari
and one more
[Music]
we can have we can have choices
overlapping that's okay
bing but bing isn't that just i guess
it's a browser
it's not only a search engine it's a
whole browser okay this is funny
uh wait i want to do another one
okay there we go uh teammates
right that's that's amaze fandom right i
don't know if it's a browser
technically i think it's on a browser
okay whatever we put it in there anyway
so teammates what do we have with
teammates
yahoo and bing aren't browsers
okay we'll fix that in a moment
chrome okay
uh i have chrome aol
aol for teammates really tort yeah i
agree with adding tour
and
opera gx netscape
aol i have aol in there
um let's add in netscape for fun because
that sounds funny
ah wait i already had netscape with inna
it was just okay but
h let's do edge i feel like edge
kind of fits too okay and
deadbeats
okay oopsie that beats pull
and edge and i feel like kind it could
also be internet explorer
what do you guys think what else what
else could be possible for
a for the deadbeats
oh poor over okay
and there's not even that many options
huh
things are repeating itself
give me something give me something
original
but you know i don't want them to be
actually choosing the ones that they
actually use
i want them to choose the ones that they
think
suits their
[Laughter]
wait what what wait what am i doing uh
microsoft explorer
wait what internet explorer
internet explorer
[Music]
what sea monkey is that a thing
voyager is that a thing yandex is that a
thing
pale moon is that a thing
what is palin
[Music]
dolphin what
dolphin and let me look that up
wouldn't that be more like gouda dolphin
brow was there
what is that
ah for smartphones and tablets
let me give that to gouda instead
because i feel like
okay wait where was good out here and so
because we gave her
bing let's put dolphin in there never
heard of it
dolphin for that beats in why it's an
inside joke oh okay okay now give me
something else for instead of
bing for chambers
i'll give the dolphin for her then when
i need something
why not firefox because i'm firefox
cali hates dolphins what the hell
sega dreamcast wrap rousey
i put it in i put it in for the chambers
okay and then for kelly for the
deadbeats we have dolphin
we have edge opera dolphin and i need
one more
let's skip let's keep on hearing about
that
[Music]
okay i mean probably most people are
gonna vote for edge anyway so who cares
netscape there we go
and wait let me clarify in the first
post
cape is obviously five or so no
discussion on that vote
vote for
what you think suits
each fandom best not what
you actually use
i'm looking forward to that to the
results of this
let's freaking go okay
okay let me tweet it
tweet all okay so let me repeat
tentacled
poor chrome opera netscape chambers
internet explorer yahoo safari
nintendo ds project
teammates chrome aol
tour edge that beats edge opera
dolphin netscape
three two one
go and it's past midnight so i have to
leave you guys by the way
[Laughter]
it's out there it's out there everyone
retweet
everything and share it so we get
all the all the fandoms included maybe
share it on the
on each fandom's um discord as well
we are we are doing some like very very
serious research you know
okay okay so
we stopped reading at tentacle 7336
and write it down kf3 sticky notes
please but let me see let me
scroll up
wow ah it's not even that much left
i might be able to finish it tomorrow
after playing maybe an hour of sliver
and then
and then finish the super chats um
all right all right that's it guys
thank you for watching
my
it's past midnight now so see you guys
thank you for for um chilling with me
while reading super chats i appreciate
it very very much
really thank you so much thank you
even though i've only been reading super
tight but this this week there is not
much
not much chiago content so um
i'm glad that you are spending these
moments with me thank you
thank you thank you i'll see you
tomorrow
um i'll make the stream reservations as
early as possible
but i i cannot guarantee
that everything will go well i'll have
to test out if it works with my pocket
wi-fi
okay so and in german we say
bye bye bye bye
love you love you very much
[Music]
you