[music]
O.G.
It's open. It's open. Hello, White group.
Congratulations
Omasuwa
Wow, everyone from the White Team is here now, so show me.
Are you all in the waiting room? I'll call you in the waiting room.
Good morning you good
Alright, it's okay.
Oh, I wonder if everyone is here, let's gather together.
Ah, set, set, yes, set, set, where.
Hahahahahaha Ah Manekata Sensei Yes He Sensei
I'm not a teacher, I'm not a teacher, but absolutely yes.
Hello everyone, I just happened to be here.
We're all together, Kazemasamikane-chan and Yes.
I'm fine now. Is it true? Please.
Teacher, please take attendance. I'm off to work.
Okay, let's go from the white group.
Iroha-changozaru I'm hungry, please.
death
Masujarobo Senpai Yes, Hello is here too.
Iriame-san, thank you very much.
Kanata-san
teeth
Hamui-chan, hi-a-hai-ame-chan
Good
[music]
Inainai to
me candy
Chanmeamechanchan
I
I'm so tired, Okaela.
Thank you very much for your support.
Nice to meet you, this member is on the phone.
These are the people who break up and become A. Yes, yes.
Okay, okay, B's weather chocolate-sensei.
Wow
Irioriirioriyoachanhai Kozukiya
Please
Hi, Hello, I'm the leader. Hello, hello, fight.
fight
[music]
Ida
Okay, let's do our best to flow up
I'm having a lot of fun
So, let's do this here as well.
Those who asked if it was okay or if I should go.
I think it's better. Yes, that day.
It's Laren-chan, but she was absent for a while.
I'm sorry for being so sleepy.
I'm sorry, my second junior, Goza, will do it.
So I thought you just came here to apologize.
The house I visited
There is a cloud
do something kind
I got nervous because they looked alike.
Nema Raden-chan's flight is also a little us.
I would like to cover it.
Thank you, please, please
Masu
I think that's what he said so I'll praise him.
I'm going to go hunting, but that's it.
I'm here for a bit of a change.
Thank you very much for your support.
As a hunter, how are you doing in the fang battle?
I guess it's a secret, right?
I'm looking forward to the secret battle again.
Should I wander around alone? Someone will come.
I guess it's a battle, so I see him working hard alone.
I might be alone and take a look at everyone's camera.
I can't believe it, but I'm not saying that.
There's a spy here. There's a spy here.
It's true here, like a really messed up spy
Mematsuri-senpai is here. There's a spy.
In the waiting room of the white team, Unkoko is leaving.
It's a classroom, so everyone is waiting here right now.
Masu Sou is very good-looking.
Hey, I'm here. I see.
I'm glad everyone gathered together.
It was good, it was good, it was good
Everyone gathered together
Oh, there's a signboard.
leave
Yes, it is certainly used where and where to use it for support.
I can't put it there, I can't put it there.
It's like a lever that makes a sound like a piece of paper.
This is what it means
How do I use it? Things like that.
two handed sign
I think I have an inner target
Use
Is that something?
[music]
It would be great if I had a board at home.
Ta
Is it blue?
Yes, it's Pol. Poro Polo came to police.
Hey everyone, it's nice to see you here.
A slightly different place where the scout group is coming.
Should I go scouting? Should I go scouting?
Red Team I wonder how everyone in the Red Team feels.
now
Please [ __ ] me
Looks easy
[music]
My wife
There are plenty.
Who is hitting Gozaru?
I can hear the sounds of punching coming from everywhere.
time of practice
from
Yokore dead
If
Probably the main thing is Mr. Rigro during practice.
We were getting into a lot of trouble with each other.
That's right, Kiruro was all Rigro-san.
Yabagome
Something like that, take the signboard in your left hand.
It's gone, but the signboard was up all day today.
It might be on
Hey, what should I write?
Oh, I can't take it anymore. Good thing I can't take it anymore.
Not only that, but it's really no good.
How many boards do you have? Everyone fixed this signboard.
Even if it's too serious, it's okay to hold it in a competition.
Maybe it's easier to reset your inventory
I think it's set in place
Maybe when you're infected
My left hand is always on my left.
As expected of one of the Kuramaicura creators
It really looks like it's going to happen again, I'll debug it.
I'll try harder
And this time, I was the Minecraft sports day bomber.
I'll do my best as a blast
As expected, he can teach me anything.
I don't have any regrets towards the Karane creator.
It didn't happen, it didn't, it didn't, you see.
It's true, it's terrible, it's true
Is it true that it was made by Minecraft?
Is it?
Amazing! What's next for Ade?
Catch me
I said "Karikirari", but I have to ask you something.
I understand
I don't know, it's so bad
We don't know much about cameras.
But you can hear it
picture
I heard a voice like Enan Kasuri Senpai.
It's not a misunderstanding, it's a misunderstanding
What's the broadcast? Okay then.
I think I'll call out to you. Well then, Red.
everyone
Mr. Amo, please enter the place where Nasu begins.
Damin, it's not red.
hey
I'll take care of myself
It's good to go, it's white, it's white, it's red.
Mememe here
It's there, it's there, mememeruru
Mememe, it's over here, I'll make fun of it properly.
that
The red was falling
Like now
It's okay
hey
This year too, it's genius. It's really lined up in red.
They are lined up neatly.Let's line up the white ones neatly too.
Ajashi came to do his best, mom.
and yokoko here
together here
to
I said yes, so next was the White team.
Everyone please enter.
[music]
Masuhai
Yes
There are a lot of people, so it's a tight-knit white team.
That's good, then let's move on to that yellow group.
Can I have you call me Noka? Yes, that's it.
Continued with
Please, if you're a mother, do your best.
It's okay, Kashiri-chan, you're hiding.
The soup stock is mixed here.
Wait a minute, I'll be fine
No, I just realized that this Ruto
We're punching each other, we're punching each other, we're punching each other
I'm hitting you
white made of clay
I have a very beautiful one.
Yes, I'm serious, so I'm serious.
Shio-chan is the only one with a pink sign in the frame
I have
Oh, it's true, we faced each other yellow.
There wasn't a white signboard.
Nayaba signboard, take it, take it, take it, take it
First of all, there isn't one.
Greetings from the Treasure of the Hololive Movement Members
Thank you everyone for saying yes.
Sanya hello
Meow, it's amazing how everyone came together.
Thank you very much for your time.
You know, seniors and juniors really helped each other until today.
I think he also encouraged me during practice.
Well, today is the actual day, so everyone's strength is needed.
Let's give it our all and get the victory.
I hope I can get it.First of all,
Everyone should have fun and aim to win.
So everyone, please enjoy it.
Thank you very much for your help today.
I hope
Thank you very much. I will continue.
From Mr. Yago, President of Tecover Co., Ltd.
I have received a message
Please click here in Masunine Yes
Take a look
Please, thank you everyone for your hard work.
Sports day Sports day is all about the body.
hey
preparation book
tired
Let's cooperate with each other at today's sports day
Encourage each other and fight bravely until the end
Let's do this live as usual
Thank you to everyone involved in the production.
Thank you very much.
Masu
Please pay attention to and support everyone's efforts until now.
I hope you can do this.
All members, please be careful of monsters.
Please, that's all for me to open the meeting.
I'll have it too
I can sense your long life and your injuries.
Yo
I'm glad I won, it's great
Sleep
Channel 1 please go to the player teacher
I'm coming
Hello, it's true
Shitantan
slope
red
Please listen to the principal for a moment.
Thank you for hearing about Yago.
Hey, I didn't hear you, I didn't hear you, Tim, I didn't hear you
Yes, there is a team. They said they were stubborn.
Hey, I told you to do your best.
Whether it's rough or not, it's still amazing every year.
I feel like VTR is getting better.
Yes, you were good at reading, you were good at reading.
I don't know what to say, but it's a book
Thank you.
Finally, I would like to give a talk to the players.
Red team: Tokoyami and Sane White team: Azuki and Sanhai Wood team
Mr. Hacos Veil, what is this?
mosquito
Please come to the table, please.
Masukara
Please excuse me for a moment, the wooden group is a little
The problem hurts.I'm sorry.It hurts.Has
HakosukamonkamonsuHasuHasuHaisu
Is the length okay?
Hey, it's okay
Yes, okay then, are you okay? Go.
I guess so, yes, it's okay, it's okay.
Well then, it's okay if you ask the player teacher to do it for you.
Is that okay? Is that okay? Well then.
Please
Mr. Masu, we players have played Hololive once.
Sportsmanship as a member
The master teacher is fighting with dignity, so cute
E November 4, 2023 What is Red Team Representative Tokuyama?
White group representative Azuki yellow representative Lotus
Bell's Yeah
Yay
Yeriparipa is wonderful, wonderful
That's wonderful, thank you very much
Thank you thank you
I threw bread here and here
Yes, from here, thank you.
Thank you very much.
With that, the opening ceremony is over.
I'm back
[music]
Please
Is it a move? It's a move. This is a mess.
It's okay
white
The voice of the person is terrible, but the fugitives are fugitives.
is the contestant channel of each group, the contestant of the white group
please channel
sound quality of hano sports day
or
It feels so real, it's round 2
Karamada
Channel is Chill Home Hunting game 1
Only people with eyes or one eye are like this.
That's right, that's right, that's it for the white team competitors.
I'm going to the channel so uh Ame-chan
caeranelisa
Haira
[music]
Pre-team fight to do our best
player channel
Go
[music]
It's totally Gluck Gluck
That's Kara, right? Yes, that's right, Kaela.
Okay, cool.
[music]
We were able to go. Were all three of us able to go too?
Is it okay to be a fugitive? What's wrong with being a fugitive?
Is it true that we are the white team hunters?
White looks the best, looks like a hunter so I'm rooting for you
Are you going to go and support me? Please support everyone but that meba.
It's okay for us to cheer you on, but he's a fugitive.
I don't need a fugitive. How many groups does this come from?
I wonder if there will be an announcement about how many groups will start?
Is there definitely an announcement?
Check whether there is a kana or not.
Except for the now check degozaru hunter team
It's all 2, so maybe we're different too.
Hunter Team
The team stabs three hunters.
Or stab the white group of hunters.
I still write the frame of the match as red at the beginning.
It's red, white, and I'm writing it down, and that's the other me.
You only have one entry as a fugitive.
well
Is it okay to have sex with a fugitive? This is my entry.
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
mindWe yeah I can't enter yet
I'm having a good time entering.
No, I had entered the competition.
Tachaka
I have already entered this.
Does this mean I should enter?
Without permission
At first it looks like the red group, even if you don't push it.
It's okay, it's okay, I'm sorry, Sade.
Could you please excuse the announcement?
Iroha-san Roboko-san Nakiame-san Ane
Kanata-san Shisumu-san Yuchoko-san Azuki
Thank you to the Eshirogumi contestant channel.
Please, it's the other way around.
I'm moving, maybe it's the other way around, maybe it's the other way around.
It's not because everyone is running away, people are moving.
Well, the broadcaster is the contestant channel.
Is it okay if I move to
I see, what number is it? White technique in the same place.
Chinne, I hope that's the case.
Mashie this is this, this is where it fits.
here this
White team competition
That's right, the fugitive running away is here.
What is the channel?
It's difficult to say the opposite, it's difficult.
I wanted to do this exercise that was difficult today.
The first seed
This is the exercise I wanted to do the most.
This movement is becoming This is movement practice movement
The one I couldn't do the most
It's true that no matter how hard it is, once we get through this, it's over.
I can do it, I understand perfectly.
Well, wait a minute.
Please, the first thing I said earlier was red.
But the hunter is here and everyone in the white team runs away.
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes everyone
That means he's a competitor, right?
As a result, the remaining white group
When hunting, separate from the infected at the tar.
I guess so.
Difficult ALLhunALLhun
TEwhiteaandIGUMaybe
Because all the Fi
weretoldtogoto
Channel
has
[music]
Oh
Ekore
Only hunters
[music]
It's fine
Well, only hunters seem to be superior.
Thank you
Yeah yeah
Yeah, run away, run away, run away
Members of other teams must separate to avoid being caught.
Don't automatically set it to zajant.
I see, that question comes up.
For example, the people in the red team
If the hunter was a member of the White Team,
I'm being targeted so I run away like crazy
Something like a click gets caught with a rope.
Well, even if I get caught, I'll run away as fast as I can
It's like O.
I'm going to be put in a cage, so I'm going to sleep
I will be heading to South Korea, but I won't be able to leave.
Surprisingly, the back of the cage was a hiding place.
Yeah, yeah, I'm a little anti.
Surua
On the other hand, the opposite of the demon on this side
I'm going to the widest one, so there's no one behind the cage.
and
As much as possible
I'm a little worried about Nekanatan behind here too.
It is easy for the staff to
I guess that's what the text is
I'm watching the channel and it's the 7th white group fugitive.
That's because the contestants came, it's the second tier.
But I guess it's better to say it.
Nodoka-chan didn't call me that name.
I guess it's a competition, so it's hunting.
Both people from the first and second games went over there.
I'm wondering if it might be better if
There are as many as I thought.
I was called Kanata, but I don't think he got it.
Yeah, it sounds like you probably think it's this or that.
I heard that and that kind of thing.
Yeah, yeah, I feel like that's how it is.
Maybe let's listen to the announcement.
Thank you for this.
Yes, there's Raden-chan's.
That's true, right? That's why I talked about it earlier.
I was called, but it's probably still Raden-chan.
I wonder if they're making progress by participating.
It's like that
That's right, that's right.
I mean, I'm not really a hunter.
Only people should be on this channel right now
I don't know if it's there or something is flying.
road
It's the power of God. It's the power of God. It's the power of God.
I have the power of a god
Hey there
Let's just ask if it's okay.
Thank you very much.
Is it okay? I wonder what's going on.
I guess I haven't heard anything like this this time.
Speaking of which, I was surprised to learn about Nesa's method.
But I don't know what to do with my overall flow.
Apparently not.
hey
I'm probably reading the materials right now.
I guess you can probably see it either way, except for the contestants.
It's written
Yes, except for players from other teams.
Which one, which one?
[music]
[laughter]
I'm typing so fast, please go home.
It's coming, clatter, clatter, clatter, clatter
Kata
I wonder which one is rattling, but today everyone
Okay, that's a bit of a long line.
The plan is around 9 o'clock.
Maybe I should push it.
The atmosphere is a little difficult because it has a good atmosphere.
There's a bit of atmosphere, so there's an atmosphere.
I'm hungry and need some energy.
There were some people there, so let's have some food.
Let's take it easy. It's going to be a long time.
It's long, so this is the real pleasure of the sports day.
That's right, isn't it? It's hard to see the big garbage, the big garbage.
You say it's a big piece of trash.
Garbage is different
It's a different English, but Daigo isn't English.
Real Thrill Real Thrill That's it
The answer is "Real Thrill"
It's a book, it's real, it's thrilling, it's real.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
in the first place
I've been in my current form since I was born.
It's like this, it's a book, this is twice.
For the next person when eating noodles
Well, this diagonal is already a bug.
It's not good, it's not good, it's good, it's good
It seems like there aren't 7 of us.
3456789
9 people9 people
Da Go So Goun
Ah, thank you very much.
Thank you for your reply.
Thank you so much thank you thank you
Okay, but in the first game, everyone says red is first.
I have to run away, but I wonder what will happen.
It's definitely true, it's true, it's true, it's true
What's going to happen? The channels are separated.
Just doing it together
The voice starts suddenly
Immediately
Ruruni
come
Run away, run away
I ran away and went around the English members.
Let's protect it
[applause]
Hey, let's protect the English members.
Let's protect English members, I'm that number one
behind
I can't wait for that, it's terrible
Farfa
If you don't protect yourself from the long fall, your back will be seen.
Even behind bars, I'm not an anti.
The person who is
Protect
Wait, the subject will change.The subject will change.
change
Ru
It's a high-quality product.
Nokore is squatting for a little while, 149cm.
I made a little mistake when I put it out.
What about the perfect person?
This is the perfect person
It's not that, it's less than that
Enter 149 Let me catch you
It's not a mirror, it's tiny at 9cm.
He's tall
Amazing, on the other hand, some small people have already run away.
Don't pretend to be confident
I'm completely confident, okay, okay, no one came.
Think
What is this?
Who is wrong?
Who is it that caught me and caught me?
Please burn it
It's actually a hit.
But
Chan-chan, catch that, catch me.
I can go, I can go. Someone can I go. Who is it?
If I'm wrong, I can go, you can catch me.
Yoho failure
What is this?
It was a failure and a death, but I'm here
Miyoe was caught, caught, caught.
Hey, no one can arrest me
It's over, it's over. Who was it? Who was it?
I guess it was something like white.
It seems like Anya is different in some way.
It's awkward, it's awkward, it's awkward
Pachi pachi jane mi senpai want ne de anan
Hunter white group hunters go to voice chat
Please move. All 6 people.
All of them, yes, all of them, six people.
It's true what it says, so let's go.
Hello, I'll go, wait a minute.
Wait, the 6 people are not here, sorry.
Six members of the Hunter are here.
All the fugitives of the White group have now been consulted.
Everyone, white group ABB, original voice chat
Please move to
Thank you for your hard work.
Well then we
I took it, I took it, I took it.
Okay, this is like cheering, cheering.
Gozaru ok Kaela-san too, ooooo
It felt so good
Somehow we split up, so please go without missing a beat.
cage
I guess that means I should just stay in the audience seats.
That's right, let's support each other.
Is it okay for me to stay like this? I got arrested.
Hey, you're still under arrest! Get out!
I can't go out, I'm really stuck
That's a lie, right? The game isn't over yet.
Maybe someone in the middle of the game will be in prison.
It failed, it didn't work, I couldn't jailbreak it
do not have
I can't do it, I can't do it, it's Korea, it's a country.
It's Korea
Yo
oh
Oh and Kihara-chan are both caught.
Maybe I won't be able to get out until the next start.
If you sleep, let's have fun.Korea.Korea.
It's a country. It's a country. It's Korea.
Yo
Thank you Korea for being photographed
That's right, my face is stuck in the grass.
Gozaru is so hot here here here here
This place is so so so so good.
That's good
I'm going now, I'll pick it up.
has been reset
I finally got out of jail after successfully escaping from jail.
Then it's time for the White Hunters to do their best.
of
Let's cheer, idiot, let's cheer, let's cheer
I'll put it on my whiteboard, it's Korea.
thank you
Korean news
[music]
It's kind of like this
I feel like I should show it to the listeners as well.
Okay, this is the best shot. Wait a minute.
Let's download it. Wait a moment.
Korean Photos Jailbreak Korean Photos Korean Photos
Where is it really?
Our faces are so close, our faces are so close, but we're underground
I'm so close to you that I'm in love with you
Nadedasu
It's definitely Korea
The country has already escaped from prison. It has already escaped from prison.
Successful escape, yoyo yoyo, the next one is about to begin.
We are entering Degozaru.
Yes, it's infected. It's infected. Yes, it's infected.
It's spacious, isn't it?
The infection was actually created by this infection seat mat.
But it seems like it's really amazing.
But in the end, I want to think that there are only 6 people.
I'll do my best if I don't have to
human
Too wide, one person per block, one block
Yes, it's really big here.
It's spacious, even though it's really spacious.
It's really nice to see everything. Everyone is really nice.
Feel it!
Ta
this
If you want to build a ruins near Korea
Yes, there's definitely a seat at the back of the prison, and it looks interesting.
The yellow color I made myself was definitely a mistake.
Now that I've gone to the team, I'm dodging things.
I just came back to see if you're okay.
I'm back.
[music]
I had an interview so it was the second match.
But it was
There are enough views that I want to see.
I interviewed
Taeyota, it's okay, Mu-chan is confused.
It's okay, it's okay, I thought it was funny
Just a little bit
Yo, lose, I'm laughing so hard
It's okay, everything will be fine.
It's okay, it's okay, I thought it was okay
Hey, from the way the speech bubbles are now, it seems like there's something to talk about.
I was talking
My soul was blowing a lot, it was blurry
Ta
I'm just walking around.
Senior, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it
Let's play Let's
Shirotame Chirotame Shiro Team
[music]
Because Chichichi White Team Ashiro Team Hunt
That means we're not fugitives either.
Yes, that's right.
Yeah, I want to run away, I want to run away, right?
I'll just run away next time, so yeah
Yes, please wait a little until the next escape.
Yeah yeah next
Nodaji
Noteme so well behaved so well behaved
I guess it's because we're a team.
Yes, everyone behaved well, so the white group was beautiful.
was lined up the most beautifully. That's right.
That's right, they were lined up beautifully. That's right, ours.
Clear and clear like this color white
white clear clear white
Clear, not power, is clear, Tooru.
Clear and sure
Yamaa demone resident toy gathering white is 2 positions
Because there is
It's white, so it's classy. It's starting. Do your best.
Do your best, try your best, do your best
Do your best, I wonder what's coming.It's a theme.
But from 2021 to 22
Well, it's pretty recent, isn't it? This is Phlox.
Don't enter Rocks Rocks Rocks Rocks barely enter
That's right, 21 yen.
I wonder if it's up to Holo, but only Holos is there.
I'm running away so much, but that live show
English students from the third batch
English's 3rd season ID's Ajaa
I see that the third season of ID is very popular.
Wait a minute, this is the summer of 20 years.
I don't want a name that's a bit boring.
It seems so difficult to find it.
It's tough, isn't it?
Do your best, do your best, Mouko Daiko-sano
Hercha
Yuushi has a boyfriend
Even people who want to be caught are caught
I feel like something is wrong with me.
I'm so happy to be chased
Hey this shitobushibo
It's not secured at all, it's secured.
It's gone, it's okay, are you okay?
Everyone regardless
Catch me
If you catch three people, there will be at least one bob.
It's hard to believe that Shibob has different hair.
I know there's something there, but I'm still there
It's not very quiet.
Why are you so quiet?
Mianchashin took Gura-chan too.
Terua
Nice, maybe some kind of strategy
Terute's Holo Kids Holo Kids
Ikk Holo Kids Keiyayyy it was good
As I said, I'm sure someone will come in.
Not kids
I feel like I can go in there
Something bad is going to get in me.
One thing is for sure, Anya was arrested.
It's true, it's a joke
It was Ajanai's older sister.
Hey
I'm curious about this, I'm curious about this, but I'm going to enter the slope.
I wonder if he's not good enough.
It's not kids, it's boobs.
What a big woman
Sleepy
I'm about to enter
We have no choice but to run away, we have no choice but to run away
It seems like I should just run away. Run away, that me.
and group
Let's catch it, catch it, catch it.
I don't know if they should just catch everyone or put everyone in.
Just put everything in there as you see fit.
Yeah, that's a lot faster.
Tatatan is a very good topic
It wasn't easy like it was when I was there, it was difficult.
It's not a recognition that's interesting. Who would have thought that?
I can survive failure
I'm sure seewas Under
toSECONDRsays
EnglishKids
frompersforEXany
Consider to
[music]
beExcuse me, kids.
Thank you, thank you, Bra-chan
They might be kids, but they were already in.
Hey, it's me, that's it, that's what happens sometimes.
I guess I was unlucky.If you think about it, who are the kids?
What will happen to Toki-san?
I'm sure it's someone like this Kaji-san.
I think it's probably a kid who's going to get into it.
Chan-chan has a tough face
I'm being watched a lot Hello, sure answer
I want to know the last thing I want to know about what I saw earlier.
What's the bar?
I wonder who my feelings were for
Neme-senpai was totally into it, that rock sound.
It was a long time ago
It seems like it is
Nanaka Sa-chan
Yeah, I feel like the same person Aya
That's because I couldn't get Miare or that one.
I can secure it and it's okay.
It's okay
I care about him because he was a good person.
big
No, it's okay. It's difficult.
It was difficult. It was a little more difficult than practice.
It's totally fine. No problems with practice. No problems.
That's because the practice table is too easy.
It's okay to beg, it's okay.
The leader and Chiara are covering for them.
I'm looking forward to your stay.
It's Kanatamoru, everyone, it's me.
I'm going to let everyone in, so I'm going to let everyone in.
All the people I found
Everything will be fine. Please use your grip strength to move.
It seems like it's moving. It's like moving. It's moving.
mosquito
Welcome everyone, all of you are contestants.
Please use voice chat
no
or
forIPutONEYeahbut
saidThatShewas
consideredI
isdefinshort
hairthingisIknoware
wetalking
aboutdefault
ONE
[music]
Fair enough
Not worth it
Sleep
Good no
prorenow
That pro wrestling guy
ni bro bla look look look look look
Look, there are some pitiful people like this.
It feels like that
Dee
What's leaking?
Terudo
I couldn't find it. What do you mean for a moment?
The situation is so bad, I want to do this.
If you open it, open it, then close it right away, it's like that
Love you in front of the closed door
That sounds like a lot of work, isn't it?
flower bed
Chan
It's a little squishy, it's squishy.
It smells like earth.
It smells so bad, isn't it?
[music]
I won't say
tree
It's so bad
Is it a bit of a fusion?
That fusion contact is too close
Yes, they're standing side by side.
It was cute. Yeah, it was cute.
Stand up, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's it.
Isn't that so cute?
Okay, just like this, just like this cushion.
Release
You have such a cute one.
My head is so cute
this hunter
But there's no hunter, oh yellow next yellow
Yellow yellow, you can't run away
Let's run away or run away That's right, run away
I'll do my best, I'll do my best
do my best
Run away, run, run, run away, Korea
I want to come in, but I can't, I can't.
No, only the fugitives, only the fugitives, the fugitives.
The patcher is just patching
Apparently it's there because I entered it.
Run away, run away
Run away!
color
Run away from yellow
Run away, who should I protect?
[music]
is
Nice nainai hiding even in E
That's nice, I'm just wandering around
I want to disturb you and I want to see you fresh.
I got it
That's right, let's go by Anya's side.
is
It's true that the appeal is really weird.
I just got debunked but no one pays me any attention
[music]
Yes, even Kia is sorry, I'm so sorry.
Hey, I'm here too Sue is out
It's 160. I want to catch that, it's completely through.
That's what happened to us
Senpai, there's no way that can happen, wait a minute.
I used the leader
But long
158 Self Heel Heel is not included
No 65 That's right Hidden
Tega
From the person in charge
I
is
Noda
Catch me one more time
It's different. It's different.
No one is there
It's a shame, but I'm very determined.
But the person I lost
It's not neat and clean.
Yo, you're not neat, you're not neat.
Even the screams are clear now
Who is this?
I'm a middle-aged woman. I'm so innocent. I'm dissatisfied with the applause.
It's happening. Dissatisfaction is also happening.
Nice, nice, I didn't get caught, I got caught.
It wasn't there for a long time.Why?
I was running away properly, even though I didn't want to run away.
It's true that A-chan is definitely a member.
I definitely got in and ran away.
It's cute when you have a little self-awareness
Well, I wonder how it went, it's neat and clean.
Are you sure you're not that clear?
I want to run away with Ei-chan.
Don't be soothed, you'll get caught drinking
No!
It was very yellow.
That's how many people I caught.
That was amazing. This was another amazing one.
No, it's not Dankiyo next time, I'll run away one more time.
Well, you can enter again now.
It seems that everything was done automatically at once.
Masu Run 2 Round 2
escape
But let's go run away
It's okay, but when you're an adult, Captain.
Or something
[music]
I don't care if she's a sexy woman or something.
I wanted to be chosen from
Don't say yo
It's true that my height wasn't even selected.
Monnea
You misunderstood me, but Polka misunderstood me.
I misunderstood you, so move a little closer to the cage.
It's time to get out. The cage is really small.
I wanted to
Whatever it is, if I can catch it now
You can't run away during the game.
During that hunter yeah yeah yeah next game
It's so good that I can't stay until then
Do your best to escape
So next is Mio-senpai, no, who would have thought that?
I wonder if it's Tamio. Oh yeah, that's right.
Well, I guess that's what I'm saying, so I'm coming back.
There's a chance that it will definitely come out or it might be completely different.
Well, I want you to think about it
Well, it's finally being said that it's time to move on.
I want you to wait now, so please do this.
I want to be protected if I do it.
Yeah
shoes shoes io shoes shoes shoes
shoes shoes
All my shoes are tight
Wow, this is creepy. This place is definitely on a slope.
A little bit of this
It's nice but it's not good
Oh no, everyone is buried.
Caught in between
I can't help but stare at it, it's so cute
It's so cute they're side by side
Cute, someone please come stand next to me
Acha
reset reset oh
It's about to start, I'll probably have to start over again
Oh, yeah, yeah, okay
O
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay ooooooooooo
OkOk has nothing to do with it, but Subaru-senpai
Her nipples are gone, they're gone.
I worked hard to make it.
Why don't you go to the trouble of chatting with me?
Words like how many nipples does Subaru-senpai have?
How many pieces did you ask? It was probably two.
Why are there more than two? Because birds are eggs.
Isn't it the person who is talking about it like it's not there?
yes
Well, it's starting, it's starting
It had become something of a specialty.
Review of What's Nana? I'm lonely
is 2019
The year is terrible and it tastes red and red.
Who is this from 2019?
I've been arrested
Everyone run away
Please, it's 2018.
I was close to making it, but I was prepared.
Captain Miro and Chief
Long live 2019, 2019
That's right
Why?
Gerimashi
But
Run away, run away, it was frighteningly fast.
Artists gather here
Very collection
Kashiaito
It's difficult to say there are more than 3 games.
There was an image that showed quite a lot.
Naja
do not have
fellow
To Ozora police who are completely anti-Yachi
The captured king was interrogated.
Tasonaki
It's not Irani, it's Claw.
There isn't.
catch
I've been arrested before
I got caught
Or rather, I got caught.
never got caught
do not have
He hasn't been arrested yet.
Don't pet it
Looks like it's going to get sticky
of
Catch
Yo, nice, nice, nice, nice, all of you.
It fit the question, but I ran away.
New
Thank you to the Sui Shirogumi hunters for your hard work and hard work on your journey.
Thank you for your hard work, Hunter
Only three people remain here, the rest move on.
Please yes
I understand, keep doing your best, keep doing your best, all of a sudden
It moved. Is this okay here? Maybe.
It's here
I got caught again. I got caught.
I'm glad you got caught, Degozaru, got caught.
It's Korea, it's Korea, it's Korea, it's Korea.
I'm going to crawl
I'll give you this too. Which Korean is this?
Yo
Well caught
To those who are giving it to me even though I am being captured.
I'm already used to it. I'll give it to you.
this
Leader and Yoshichiko-sensei are giving it to me.
2 shots for Korea all over the place is amazing
It's so surreal though
This Noel-senpai has a great sense of lighting and photography.
Zae
I understand, it's a mess
Positive
doing
It's Tsushito. I'm a commuter.
No, I want you to do your best in the second match, do your best, Captain.
Ah, cheering seats, let's go cheering seats.
Yayara
Do your best! Wait, wait, I accidentally shot the concentrator.
Please wait a moment.The mouse is
What was the situation like?
now
The mouse that was shot incorrectly became cracked.
Live the mouse
It was terrible and I was just stroking it.
I was stroking it.
I was stroking him, but he hit me
[laughter]
Hey
It's cute. It's facing down. I thought it was facing down.
This is so cute, it moves, it moves, it moves
So cute
Hey hey Gra-chan, that's gross glass
I'm sure Pagla will appear.
Are you sure it's okay to be here? It's true that I woke up
Maybe he was a competitor.
Hey, I'm currently entering an entry for The Runaway.
It was written, how should I take you?
The one who gets taken away or disappears, the pin
keep it up
A white brawl begins
It's true, I didn't realize it was a Subaru statue
Has that one been taken away from YouTube?
Was it really true?
Na
That was done
Yes, I'm home
I don't know what to do
Good place
Let's start. I wonder if it will start with a simple question.
Something, something
Naoah
There's a lot of this, there's a lot of this
There are quite a few
Do your best, don't worry about someone else coming in.
Ae
No, it's expensive. My senior is hiding here.
Toa-senpai is hiding here, Toa.
Senpai is probably going in because of the wind.
It's really in the corner
Very secretive
Terue is surprisingly different
It seems expensive to do that, I'm sure.
That's right
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good
Yo, who's hiding? Who's hiding?
Catch it!
It's too early, it's too early, Fluffy-chan, it's finally here
Who is Fuwamoko-san being arrested?
Bebe-chan
Ekari-chan is tall, isn't she? She's tall.
in
Yeah
Aku-chan is cotton
I didn't catch any fish, but I really wanted to go there.
Naeke ear people don't even have ears, that's surprising.
I don't know if it's that one or the included one.
Probably
I'm not sure. I'm just listening.
That's right, that's right, Fana-senpai is that
Horns aren't just for kicks, are they?
I don't think there are that many, it's terrible.
I keep saying good things
There are so many blurry judgments about this.
Oh that feels good
Structure
It's so good, so so so so so so so so so so such
Stop it, stop it!
That senior who captures Teru so much is also a blur.
Na11 blur
Darumecha
hair
There's definitely no Merle you can go to.
No, it's just a blur
Boke person
Asute-senpai is on the right side, completely hidden.
here here here
You're in a red place. Do your best.
nice
Too nice, too nice
No
That's a really good cow that has secured almost 1 spot.
The record is the highest record. It might be the highest record.
I was totally screwed.
Isn't it 2 if Tae doesn't run away?
Okay, okay, nice, nice, ah, nice, nanai.
Nice nice nice nice nice nice
Nice nice nice please
a
air
Wow, what happened earlier
Staff
[music]
What's starting? Wait a second, chocolate.
The teacher's photo is too good, isn't it?
This chit is so amazing
That guy is so good I need to stop now
good
If you put it on a Subaru, it'll look amazing
That's great, it's a Subaru. This is too good.
Where is it?
Awai Aeri is so nice and I put so much into it.
The beast was really good. The beast was really cute.
I was caught a lot at the end, yes, at the end.
It's mostly blurry, mostly blurry.
The face that looks blurry is almost blurry
Teke ears are surprisingly rare when you do this.
Newa-senpai, listen to me too
I'm a little surprised, but I don't have an image of it.
I'm not sure about this, but it seems like that, everyone.
He's a blur and doesn't have many thrusts.
I wonder if it's that blur, maybe that blur
I don't like it, but if I judge Mio-senpai, she's a pretty dumb person.
I don't think there are too many, but there are many.
The same goes for Karami-chan, who pokes me in.
That's right, Mio-chan or other than Kamio-chan?
Miorando Mirando
Mirando is a bonus stage in a sense.
Surely there was an escape
It's dawning
Run away, run away, run away
I did my best
Egg
No
Wow, they're gathering in certain places.
It was a little hard to catch.
Oh no, hide, hide, hide, oh no
Chandoko
senior
Senpai, someone has been arrested.
I've been let go
That's definitely the case
hey
That kind of 0 to 2nd generation student Moe
That's right, I read it. It's dangerous. I'll get caught for a moment.
Wait a minute, you can wait.
I wonder if Yochan-chan knew?
I did it, didn't I?
Asade
If you see it, it will be released
Chico
Chansugi was also arrested
It's true that a lot of people have been arrested.
No, I have silver hair.
Ta
It's a bit dangerous
I'm sorry it was so lively.
I was surprised that it didn't work.
Good luck
It's a shame that I have free time. I have so much free time. I have so much free time.
It's a bit scary to get caught.
Se
Hidden for a long time
Chief Chief, please hide there, just for a moment.
You can catch it here
There is a chance!
What about me? What about me?
Completely ignored
Why didn't I do anything about the name?
Matsuri Senpai Matsuri Senpai Matsuri Senpai I
Then I failed
That's not sexy
Oh, sexy Nanchanchanchan, I'm here.
Here it is!
It was 12, so nice, nice, whatever.
Was there 14 of us? Or was it 13?
People are nice
White nice nice nice nice no
It was just barely dangerous, but no.
[music]
The captain managed to escape, but he managed to escape.
I'm glad I cut it, it was dangerous, it was dangerous
Tepa
Kaa
I was really a bit surprised.
Tami
Sleep
white
explained
Remu-chan is disappointed. Go back. Go back.
mosquito
Oh, I was moved without permission. I want to come back.
come back come back
move freely
death
think, move automatically, move
I see. Yes, yes, seriously, now it's the white group.
B true
Okay, okay, okay.
oh
Is Holomen hunting over?
Can you tell me the results now?
Well, I'm sure you're wondering how many points there are.
At first, they told me about the sports meet.
They didn't tell me anything along the way, but at the end yes yes yes
That's right, that's right.
What will happen?
[music]
I'm sure it's a follow-up to what competition is next?
Stop it, stop it, you'll get hungry
Yes, my stomach is fine.
My stomach is fine, but I'm really nervous.
I was practicing like it was going to happen, and it looks like it's going to happen today too.
Well, the other party is very rare, so the opponent is that one.
I was practicing with my opponent, but yeah.
I was winning quite a lot.I watched it in practice.
Even if it's really nice, it's real.
The actual performance may be different.
It's okay, but the stage is still the same.
It's the same, same shape, and the first match was super good.
Mercury-senpai and Mi-chan are serious.
The first game is Roboko, which is dangerous and dangerous.
Yeah, that's right, but Roboko-chan, it was me earlier.
I tried to teach it and got pretty good at it pretty quickly.
But I feel like I started practicing today, so I'll do my best.
Beginners who want it so much
Passion to sleep on the rack
Passion, whatever, whatever.
It's really scary, B and White are currently in 2nd place.
Yeah that's really good, nice nice
Nice nice follow up
We have received information for each group of 6 participants.
Haustit Move
Please, Okiba, do your best.
Hey, I'm going to go up. I'm going to go up.
Naruue venue
Well, it's on top, so you should just go to the bottom.
Even with that voice
Shiuno's voice seems to move.
Chiara isn't moving, yeah, Kiara-chan has 2 fights.
I have another interview to see if it's okay even though it's my eyes.
I guess so, I'm going to go in.
Good luck and do your best
Terrazzo yeeeeessssssssss
Ah, now everyone is here, that Chiara.
Chan's gone, so I'll just
Say something that puts pressure on you
I know, but so many people are like this all the time.
I'm watching you try it, it's scary, isn't it?
It's impossible, everyone is paying attention.
It's a line, it's painful for this line phobia.
No, that's amazing, you really have courage.
Even though it's okay, I've been practicing a lot.
I guess it's true. Just a little bit here.
Even if my record is worse than my practice, I don't care.
That's a nice fight, yeah yeah yeah first
It seems like I don't like it because it's amazing that I can score a goal.
I'm really excited to see something
My heart is pounding even when I'm on the other side, what's going to happen?
yeah
well
I've done this before, just for practice or something.
Don't do it. I touched it for just a second.
It was difficult, after all, where is the scaffold next?
I'll figure it out properly and fly here next time.
If I don't make a decision, I'll just jump
Furthermore, that trident talk...
There is also a technique that seems to increase the flight distance.
It's quite technical.
That's right, today is the most difficult part of this competition.
That's right, it's definitely the most difficult.
I wonder if it was last year last year.
There was a human one, yeah, that one too.
It's difficult, but you should pay more attention to it.
It was just a moment of effort.
Yeah, the outcome is decided in an instant.
There's something like that.
If you try, you'll be fine right away, whether it's good or bad
It feels like the end, but this is 300 seconds.
I have 5 minutes, 5 minutes.
I hope the truth lasts for 5 minutes
What happened to this in the end?
Sapasui-chan is here to support you for some reason.
At practice yesterday, I felt like it would be better to have some support.
Yeah, I guess that's it after all, the team is coming back.
No matter what, I broke up with the contestant.
It's true that the A team is
Of course, here are 7 and this is the one above.
I can't see it, how much Yushi is this?
Roboko-san and Chiara-chan's courage is here.
It's 200 mel that you can only look up from.
Is it worth it?
200m
200m imagination messenger
So fidgety so fidgety
Even if it's Chaue, Chiara-chan is roboco with this
When senior Chiara-chan gave a good score
Choco-sensei will add some goodies.
That's right, I believe it, so I'll have a hamburger.
Make fried chicken or karaage
Or Japan. Yes, Japan said they were coming, right? They're coming.
Kagochi
I'll make you a hamburger.
I want to eat meat-stuffed green peppers.
That's great, I want to eat stuffed peppers with meat.
I guess it will decrease and decrease
I'll make it so you don't have to worry about it.
will make it for you
Whether you go or not, it doesn't matter whether you win or not.
I kind of want to go to the launch instead.
It looks like I did something, after all.
I was chosen by lottery to be part of this group.
After all, it's definitely the white team.
Let's launch, let's make a store reservation
It doesn't matter what kind of thing it is, it's still meat, it's yesterday's
The repertoire that appeared was also impressive.
Hamburger steak fillet cutlet
Yakiniku, shabu-shabu, etc.
Oh nice, oh hot pot, nice hot pot, nice cold hot pot
It's getting cold, but Chiara-chan
I'm coming to Japan, but I wonder if other people will come.
I guess it's different at different times
But every time I come here I go out for dinner.
It's not okay Calchoco
[laughter]
Line, it's true, it's true, something might come.
I don't know, but only those who can go will go first.
Just take the number of people
Take it to the store
I see, you can add it later.
Looks like it's going to be a year-end party
Certainly this season
Wow, the season is just around the corner, come loaded with flowers.
Is that okay? Please go.
That's fine, but it takes a lot of time.
Well, some entry came.
It's like each competition is a gimmick.
There's an interview coming up so everyone is probably in high spirits.
I'm talking passionately about that, but
I'm so full of things to do, so I'll do my best.
It's crazy because people with a lot of enthusiasm gather together.
Yeah, wait
Well, now is the time, yes, this is completely true.
Fuji too
I have a feeling that there are definitely some marks left.
What happened after this was a little off.
It might be that, but it's the Kiba Line.
The rest is Hime, let's go over Hime, and the rest is Hime over.
Spring/Summer Citorile Yes Yes Yes Yes it's over
I think it was something like that.
I think there must be 5 types.
Even though I'm thinking about it, I don't think I'll be able to go.
Oh, I'm sure it started once, then I heard a voice once.
It's probably just like that.
And since there is only one relay, there are only two.
I feel like I can go because it's around that much.
I'm sure the feeder line is like that.3 That's it.
It's like doing it 3 times It's the same thing I'm doing it 3 times
I'm not sure how much that will cost
It certainly begins
Do your best and let's start cheering for you
Let's do our best, Odoko-san, who's about to start.
Good luck, everything is going well
Things are going well, let's do our best
Roboko, you are a woman who can fly
Da-chan is just insanely good.
It's so good that you get anxious when there are people who are good at it.
Isn't there some pressure on you? Do your best.
Do your best, Oro-san, and make it to 200m.
I wonder if I can get Baun points?
Maybe it's just that it's the end
The point is at the last position or so.
Because it's decided
5 minutes
Well then, isn't this first order, everyone?
If everyone reaches 200m, they get the same points.
I wonder if it's not?
time and final arrival
Kodo yeah yeah yeah max 200
There's even a fight with yourself that seems like you'll be able to win.
That's right.
Hey, do your best! You're halfway there.
Things are going well.
Yeah, Chiara-chan just got roboco.
I guess I'm a beginner when it comes to my seniors.
I wonder how a beginner will be able to complete it.
You said how you felt, but the third one
Checkpoint is just a good game
Nane skill is high, finally Roboco
It feels so good, it's so good
It feels like a competition after all.
I'm used to this kind of thing because I've been to Kane tournaments.
I'm sure it'll attract attention, but I'm not at all nervous.
I don't think so, the water is rising
strong
Oh, do your best, ok, do your best, ok 4
Nice, nice checkpoint
Ui umai umai, there's still about 3 minutes left.
Nene, it's so fast, B-chan
It's early, it's nice
It's amazing that no one has fallen since the fourth one.
Calm down, keep on raising your voice
I'm getting hotter and hotter, I'm getting hotter and hotter
hey
Good job
Do your best, just a little more
30m left
You can go, do your best, you're struggling
I can go
If something were to fall inside, it's normal.
Just about from the checkpoint
That's right, that's right, so calm down.
10 meters left, 10 ah 6, wow, just a little more to go
Do your best, oh nice
Sei-chan is too nice and does her best too.
A little more, a little more, a little more
I'm still practicing after all.
Somehow, Sui-chan, Asui-chan, I don't like it.
There are still 90 seconds left, so there's still more than a minute left.
There is no room for that at all
Sui-chan is so good at being able to afford it.
There's always pressure during performances.
Pressure, do your best, the real thing is a monster after all
They say there's someone there, so I'm going to lie down.
If you try hard, the purpose of the game will change.
But everyone wants to support me, right?
Yes, but you say this is a battle with yourself.
But it's a 200m battle, right?
Yes, the scores are now equal for everyone here.
There is a possibility that everything will be a draw.
Yeah
Do your best, I'm nervous. Drink some water, drink some water.
I'm looking up, but I don't understand anything at all
I can't see it. It's too high. What's going on?
Oh, I want an elevator, everyone.
200m all
The dry crackling feels good.
No, but on the contrary, it's the second layer of people.
The pressure is coming
I guess so
keep it up
[music]
But this is 39 seconds long.
That's it, it's hot. I climbed in 39 seconds.
I can do it
It's from here
Hey, the second match is Chiara.
Chanun
Chan
Do your best, try your best to climb up to Choco-sensei's place.
It's a great place to see it from above.
This, this, this, this, this is really cool, this is pretty good.
I feel like I'm getting a little closer
[music]
Okay, let's push it a little bit now.
It's okay, okay?
Good job
Oh, it's true, I can see a little bit here, yeah, yeah.
It doesn't matter whether you see it that way or not.
[music]
Feel it, 2nd round 2nd round Chiara
chan kiara
If you touch the signboard of an infected person, Chiara...
Let me know in the comments if you think it will be well received.
That's a lie. Can I press this or the infected person?
good
Where is it? The signboard on the far right
Entry Oh everyone was doing this
There were so few people
Entry list for the signboard on the left
Four here and there, oh really, this
receive
How do I receive it? How do I receive it?
How does it float? It's just like that.
It's true, I got it, I got it, it's a severed head
Really
Where is Kia-chan? Hey, Kia is doing well.
The severed head is climbing
It's scary, but this is probably a contestant.
I guess you can't see it. I can see it.
I can never climb it
What's this poop-like thing that's disturbing?
What, what, this is some kind of soft-serve ice cream?
Is it really soft cream or soot cream?
Looks like you're climbing really well.
Wow, wait, wait, I've lost sight of Kira.
Chiara is the fastest
There's a checkpoint, so sparkly
Nice second one, Wow, it's a masterpiece.
There are only teru
Good, good, good
[music]
The effect when Neo Oumai rises
That's really cool
Wow, it's really fast everyone!
Teru
Oh, we're almost halfway there. It's early, it's still 1.
It fell too many times
No, that's amazing, as expected of Phoenix.
Step by step
I'm definitely going there all at once.
I'm glad to know that you can do this.
Thank you so much for the comments.
not at all
No, the three of us are just looking up at the sky, no, seriously.
That's not right, this is interesting Agi-chan, it's fast.
It's been going up fast, it's going well.
This is exactly what happened when I got up
I didn't know, I didn't know, I didn't know
So this is placed in the spiral field, isn't it?
I made a lot of mistakes with this and it flew off a lot.
Wow, colored blocks are real!
It's kind of like that, it doesn't really depend on where you go.
It's different, yes, there are quite a few shortcuts.
Tsutsu
[music]
certain
Oh I'm nervous
This is so cool, it's amazing, it's already the goal.
Be careful when reaching the goal
Teru
oh
amazing
You're so nice, I don't think you can see us.
I'm drifting right now, but I'm drifting
Hit me a lot and everyone's face
But Geara-chan is amazing and makes no mistakes.
It's a mistake. It's amazing that I didn't fall even once.
crackle crackle crackle crackle crackle crackle crackle crackle
Crackling, crackling, this is the final point
That's why I'll do it here too.
There was a scuffle and I got kicked out.
I wonder if that was expected?
The distance in the final seconds
I guess so. Just 70 seconds left.
give and take
It's certainly better than giving in and both of us fall.
I mean, it's too complicated and I have to fall.
I'm worried about that.
Saka is working hard
Good luck, 50 left
Seconds ah
Nyan is good too, I'll do my best
[music]
There's a lot to do, so do your best and do what you can.
Don't let it fall again
Ah, 30 seconds left, do your best, you two.
Tomooo, they're coming, they're coming, they're both coming.
Are you going up together?
Let's do our best to be evenly matched
Do your best, you only have 7 seconds left
4321 Zhang Oh
Yatoya tomorrow was amazing no mistakes ah nya
Unfortunately, it was just a little bit more
Hey, okay, I'm scared, but I'm going to do my best.
All of a sudden
I'm going to be knocked down.
Amazing, wonderful, wonderful
wonderful
Yo nice nice nice nice
Yayara
Yes, the next one is Kisekise.
Yeah, it looks like the Kiba Line is going to be Kiba Seda Kiba Line.
Poichi Oka A and B are also included.
There are pairs too, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Everyone on the competition channel
oh yeah
Oh no, Captain, let's do our best. Captain and Gundam.
Choco-sensei, I want you to notice me, Choco-sensei.
I'll watch it because it's stuck in that ass
I wonder if I can go to 3 races?
Good luck, are you going to fight the fangs three times?
The point of this poop is now on the other side of the stream.
The one on the screen is the key to follow up.
If that's the case, the White team's points are now 20.
I probably got the first point after doing that.
Floor up is Na point everyone number
Is one coming? Can I catch up?
Hey nice fight nice fight
Yayarachane
Come on, you haven't come back yet. Come back.
Are you still in the interview?
No, no, no, no, there's a saying again.
White team Only our white team was able to properly eavesdrop on both of us.
I'm doing it, right?
Please stand in front of the mountain where you can live.
Yes, it's a positive interview, but it's at this level.
It was a great match. That brain mistake was amazing.
Hey, I didn't make any mistakes. That was amazing.
Nice
Nice, the White team is currently in 1st place.
The time is close, but White 40 Yellow
38 red 37 wow
Nice nice nice team 4 points
Yellow 308 Let's
37 Let's go degozaru like it
Nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice
Nice, this is a lot of our princess and the dangerous princess
I wanted to practice whether it's cool or not.
That's right, isn't it?
There's also the possibility of protecting the general with fangs.
Ah, yes, there are many more things.
I have to work hard, the pressure is overwhelming
I'm planning to take things easy with what happened.
I don't like being nakatane at all.
It's starting to feel like pressure
It seems like there are no pairs.
Right, I teamed up with Ra-chan this time, so what happens?
I don't know yet, thank you for your hard work.
I'm tired
My mom is looking at me and says hi.
So, here is the general specific interim announcement.
Click here for the second overall score
is
Yes, I'm 40 and have a lot of money like that just now.
Barely yellow is 63 points, white is 60 points, and 52 points.
[music]
Move to the next venue of Nemakiru
Let's jump from here and announce that
That number of people who were being treated like that.
What happened? It was out, it was out, it was out, it was out now
Ehaku is 2nd overall, Amada
It was 33 points, yellow was 63 points, white was Kia
chan was nice and nice
Good game
Goza good game good game nafa down
Ta
nafa
It was amazing
I can't come, it's dangerous, it's not coming, it's dangerous
Oh no, Chiara, do your best.
Maseoisho riding
I'm going to ride Masuato Azukia, isn't it dangerous?
Otherwise I don't want to become a general.
Where is the general of the snowman who doesn't want to do it?
Yes entry right where entry where where
Here we go
And this was Okitakita Orchestra General Hamio.
Chanadori-san is so nice and nice
This is so cute, this is so cute, this is on top
It's okay to ride.
Touch the person who rides it while holding it Oh wait
But which general is the best general?
is on the top, so it's the side that gets clicked
It's okay if you don't enter.
If you have already entered, please cancel and try again.
If you touch once again
became a general
This is it
That person from Nesan's Pepea is coming.
I wonder if my pair will come.
Is that person there? Come!
I guess it will be given to you
Or if your pair stays like this, I'm all
around
reactor
Maybe I should prepare some rice balls.
I might add some sauce to eat the rice balls.
Onigiri
The rice ball you want
want
I'm so hungry that I want to summon you.
If so, please release the general, Datte-chan.
Chanaaaaaaaa, it looks okay
youknow
how
hand
E-sama
Where is it?
But everyone is here
Because more and more will happen
Awesome
Niru
Akochikocchi
Which one? Which one?
Is it okay to get off, General? Are you okay?
How do I stop it?
Press the same place again
Just nice nice nice nice ah
My friend
Mumbling
Was there only one person with this rank?
He's coming in that suit. He looks strong.
suitstudo
It seems like a good candidate.
Teruosa looks too strong.
I was charged a huge amount of money after it was okay.
No, it's okay, then he'll go.
Maybe it's Oyu Senpai Osa
Thank you thank you thank you so strong
Yes, I was able to ride it. I was able to ride it.
Riding strong
I folded it up, I thought it was great.
Kayu-senpai came in as a pinch hitter and helped me out.
Thank you very much for your request.
Thank you very much for your support
Aoka-senpai, thank you for coming.
Thank you
I'm going to ride, please ride, I'm riding
I got on top of porridge-senpai who got on top of me.
Ka-senpai got on board. I'm riding a little.
I'll ask you to turn into a chair for a moment.Okay.
Leave it to me
Thank you, I'm so happy. It's on my ear.
A fluffy mofu that you can ride is stuck in your butt.
Yes, the corner of the chocolate wire is stuck in it.
It hurts when the leader stings my butt.It hurts.
It's better if you don't like that, it's intense
It's quite irritating, it hurts, I feel like it's quite irritating.
That being said, Mio-chan is also quite stimulating.
Maybe
This is the senior's corner.
I'm stimulated by
Maybe you'll win
Thank you for today, Mayu HaNeko
Let's meet each other
Thank you very much for your participation.
Be scared, one person has turned into a suspicious person.
Don't get teased
That's why I say yes, please.
I want to guide you
Masu
That's so reassuring
Let's do our best, only for the white team.
[music]
Okay, I'd like to ask you one last thing.
What is the strategy of the Gurumihi group?
I wonder if everyone in the white team is getting angry?
Well, if Takumi's kill is taken, then...
I guess 1 point will be added.
The opponent who will probably attack while defending
Focus, everyone
The one where everyone approaches General Ananda.
It seems like it would be a good idea to wake him up for now.
Type
Isn't it possible to do more and more?
Someone who is weak, that's right, someone who is somehow weak.
I want to beat you up. I can see the cart.
Maybe the person wants to die
Sakami Sai is near Shou and can see 1 heart.
Tara will attack
Okay, maybe this is the voice chat.
I think it will be like that.
Yes, there are so many voice chats.
There's probably a name at the bottom.
I think there is, so it's true that there was
It seems that Kanataoka is a collaboration
I can't get it any better than that. Cooperation is bad.
The general will protect and protect me.
Let's all do our best with the leader as a landmark.
Yes, I'll do my best.
[music]
This is not a book, we're both being targeted.
I guess I should go cover it.
If I freeze and find it, I feel like I'll be attacked.
If it looks like that, then maybe
I think we're going to start moving from here, so everyone is moving.
Well then, let's all move on. We'd better go now.
Is it okay?
Olet's Go Let's Go
Let's move, I was able to move.
I don't want to go to bed or sleep on the red floor.
This is a bit like that color from Minecraft Pro.
I thought I shouldn't put her on top of this anymore.
I don't know how to fight, but with a shield.
If you use it well, you can win, you can win, you can probably win.
It's a ham cut, so that's a han cut.
That's right, I'm so stubborn that I'm going to get it right.
Let's get it for a while, then give it as much as possible
Protect the general too
While protecting
Noame-senpai or bottom is a horse, so-so-senpai point of view
I wonder how it looks
Well, just in case, look at it at F5.Yes, at F5.
Check it out with a little picture.
What does Jump look like?
The jump is probably a critical hit.
I guess it's okay if you don't handle it.
That's because the person attacking seems to be doing that.
Well, I can't run much. I'll see if I can run.
Jumping feels farther than running.
I feel like I'm going to jump right in.
Jump dash is a good dash
Yeah jump dash
I'll do my best and I'll roll up my sleeves and do my best.
It's short sleeves.I put effort into wearing short sleeves and was able to do it with short sleeves.
I'll do my best, I'm hot and just like a man, I'm hot
It seems like you are full of enthusiasm
I was wearing it, but I just took it off.
Please take off your clothes and wear short sleeves. We'll do our best, everyone.
This is actually my first time saying I'll do my best to defeat everyone.
What is it? I'm sure there are 5 hearts on the target.
That's right, there's a general and three regular soldiers.
So the general over there is Miko in red and Suba in yellow.
It looks like it's going well, so the more seniors
Who is that?
Who is this? Who is this, Mel? Ah, Mel.
I'm staying with Chan or Mel-chan.
I'll check it out, it's amazing
Pom Pom Pom
Pompom-chan Awa-senpai is on character contest
This is amazing, Miko-senpai and Mel-senpai
This pom-pom combination is amazing!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Kamikomi Kochitoko
I don't want to go, but there might be some problems.What do you think?
It's really okay to keep it fairly large.
It's okay to just do your best to your seniors.
If it sticks or sticks too much, it may cause damage to the sword.
The swing is quite large so you can get hit all at once.
That's why, oh yeah, that's probably the summary
I tried all the things I thought I could do, and the feeling was 3
There's going to be a fight, probably 3 fights.
fire
I'm so excited, I feel like I did it yesterday at the all-night festival.
Yes, but Chiara-chan is amazing
Thank you for working so hard on the attack.
I had a really amazing 8 kills, so yeah
So maybe let the person who can kill it get the kill.
The food looks good and I'm happy with it
That's right, someone the White Team is targeting.
I'll tell you something about it then.
It might be nice to go out and have a good time
Good job
Turn it around
[music]
Please, I'll do my best.
Ajimori
If you have to protect me, attack and carry me.
Carry it while receiving it, carry it while having it carried away
Tsutsuomo's senpai's body stands out, I get it.
Feeling strong
Wow, how will it start? Will it start?
Maybe this one in the middle is what it is?
Isn't this thing going to disappear?
I guess I'm strong enough to climb, but the climbing trowel disappears.
I wonder if it will disappear, but it hasn't happened in a while.
It wasn't here the other day, but it was there.
If you can climb, you'll probably be stronger if you climb here.
Maybe a glass block was placed there?
I might not be able to climb Noun though.
The top is strong, maybe I should go to the top.
strong
Okay here
How about the edges?
I think it's a good idea to make it impossible to climb.
I'm sorry, but I wonder what will happen
Yes, it means defeating someone.
It's definitely very peaceful, people.
There's no way I'm going to do that.
It's a game, so I have to win this time.
This BGM has become a sports day specification in various ways.
What's more, it looks like a fang line.
that
100 Hyakuryo Hanafubuki Let's do this, run away
Yo
hey
[music]
Sound that enters from the BGM type and enters from the sound
The sound and shape are important. Shape is important.
empty shape
Hakama is also like this.
When playing games, think of yourself as the strongest.
Grandpa tells me to do it.
When I fight, I begin to be the strongest version of myself.
Its good that this starts with me being the strongest.
Maybe I'm making a mess, but it's okay.
Oh, it's coming. Waiting for it to come.
[music]
Oh wow, how dangerous, where are you using it?
Where is this? Where are you defeated?
everyone
[music]
Where's the ugly scuffle going backwards?
I can't seem to get a wind sword anywhere, but I got one.
I got it I got it
Yeah wow
If I don't defeat him, I'll be here.
I'm not strong, I'm not strong, it's dangerous.
I think it's too big to have a foot down
Wow, I got knocked down.
I'm aiming for that yellow thing.
Let's go, go aim
[music]
Let's do it, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, which one?
Is it over there? It's dangerous, it's wrong.
It's difficult, wow, I've been defeated so many times, I can't defeat it at all.
I'm sorry, this is difficult.
Wow, the game is over. It's over.
I can't believe it started all of a sudden.
Collaboration is difficult
It's difficult if we can't work together.
[music]
I wonder what this feels like
Please wait a moment. If you do it once, it will be 1.
I wonder if it will go down.
let's
I don't know where the general is.
figure
[music]
Maybe this is just waiting
I wonder if there's something to wait for. Maybe 2
Did you do it three times?
[music]
Change your perspective
Kane's point of view Yes, no, no, no, this is it
[music]
nattttttttt
t
ttt amazing T is flowing
The amazing Kaela-san is doing really well 7
That's what's killing it.
Kashin ranking Wow, it looks like this
Narudegozaru
Yes yes yes
Yeah, oh, oh, maybe this is how you came back.
Na
[music]
Everyone in Fukonoi entered this.
It seems like the White team has gotten quiet since they entered.
Cooperate with
Maybe it's not there yet, maybe next time
I'll try changing my perspective
Yes
Yes, run through, run through, or go and pull back
It's not good, it's this, it's that
During practice, there weren't many people.
It seems like it was less.It was less.
I wonder what that is, but the third person is better.
It was cheap but yeah yeah yeah this
It's a melee battle, so I'm sure the upper one is probably 12.
It might be easier to win.
I see, I understand.
Yeah that's it
But I think there are only a few people who feel that way.
Easy to hit, but run away if hit
Okay, something like this
do
Jump is good, I see
a jump
Do your best to jump, do your best
Yeah, it's okay, it's okay, I'll do my best too.
do my best
Zonanka members are better than Okayu-senpai.
TRUE
I'm in a pinch
Hitter is the president above the president after all.
It's true that the president is either this or that.
If the presidents think about it, they'll give each other a ride.
Is this true? We're riding together.
That's not the case
Yes, yes, we're both presidents here.
This is the only place where the muscle seems to be strong when a work-related accident occurs.
They are the business-routine business rebuilder and the debtor.
Oh no, how was it? That's bad. Let's try harder.
A dangerous debtor
none
Too bad there will be an absorption merger.
I just remembered that it's really bad that I won't win.
I remember it, it's painful, it's painful
If I don't work, I'll go with you or work.
hold together
Weeding
I have to take the test for insects.
If I don't do it, I'll have to wait until it starts.
Then I'll rush it
Pull
[music]
It would be better if the orchestra became quite solid.
Yes, but
Hey, it's a really big lag. It's a lag. It might be a lag.
No, it's very laggy.
Wow, it's been a bit laggy since a while ago.
That's right, but it might be a little laggy.
I killed something
Taeda is dangerous, dangerous
It's bad
Too bad, too much lag. Too much lag.
Kakodai
It's too bad this way
[music]
It's so bad, it's so nice that I defeated it.
Nice ah
terrible
Dangerous Eladin is better
It's fun, don't knock anything down.
Nice oh, you know, that movement on the other side.
I'll read it and hit it. Good luck!
You're coming here.
That's nice, better than before.
Wow, it was much longer than before.
I thought it was better this way.
read ahead read ahead
I don't want to read ahead, but it's pretty good.
I was able to defeat it, so wait a minute.26
I chased you, chased you, chased you, 5 kills, 5 kills.
5 kills, 5 kills, big kills, 5 kills, yay!
I did Yoshiyo's 5 kills I did it
This one also includes target kills.
It's nice, it's nice, the red is strong, the red is strong
Lag anyway
Hey uncle who can beat the internet
A man who can beat the weak internet
I think there is a man who can beat the Internet.
Kia-chan did 8 kills, that's amazing.
That's nice
After all, reading the trajectory was the key to determining the trajectory.
The path of the sword
[music]
of
vinegar
Don't make me do it, don't make me do it,
standing
A sword that determines the muscle of the muscle
Something about my muscles
Somehow, so many people gathered together.
Something like that
There's nothing I can do about it.
That's the world
When I start reading the face of the person who is in the direction
There's only 1000 left.
It's true that someone is riding above me.
Dakara was on board.
Which one will you ride?
Okay, it's the last one. I want to win in the end, White team.
I'll do my best, I'll do my best
After all, I'm looking a little backwards.
Let's go without hitting each other head-on.
sea bream
Let me jerk you there
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll show my colors
Let's jerk from behind
Let's do some jerking
Even so, it was a pretty good result.
That's right, 5 kills, I'll surpass 5 kills.
sea bream
Yeah, it looks good, the red team was amazing.
strong
Aya from the red team said, ``I'm going to beat you up.''
Because there are people who are
I will send you a super good mark
Superg super good mark.
Red, strong red
Namiko's team?
a
[music]
Kuu is really inciting me, I'm really inciting you
This is crazy! The Red Team is really stirring things up.
[music]
Only that emoticon that looks like a crazy old man
B
Like
ah
[music]
Oh no, this is the only thing I can do, super good
Even though it's work, I definitely have to fight.
Just aim for a kill from behind
It's delicious if you go there.
[music]
I will give you my life
All I can do is fight for my life
That's super super good.
super good
Oh no, it's probably been discontinued for a while.
Or if it is interrupted, please re-enter again.
stomach
Masu Now Entry Now Entry Now
Good ride
hand
Thanks for giving me a ride
Of course it's good, it's not bad, it's not bad
But Saazuki is worried about Hihime's voice.
No, it's okay Himeko
I've already practiced my voice, but
All the attacks are on the menu. That's right.
Chan, all I'm thinking about is this menu practice.
I wonder if things have changed.
I don't know if that's the case, I'll take measures on the spot.
That's why it's so bad.
That first thing makes me laugh.
Now I'm concentrating on the fight, even though I'm screaming.
I'm concentrating on the battle, let's go, let's go
I want to go from behind too much
Nayabe it's really laggy but long but the enemy's
read startup
Nice nice nice nice now falling behind behind
Let's go. It's dangerous, Miko-senpai is flying away.
tree
Yes, while reading 4 which side of the enemy should you fly to?
Yes, I'm sorry, I'm serious.
Too crunchy
Very strong
Do your best! Wait, it's The World! Read it.
I do a lot of reading through space and time.
But nice, nice general, it's red, it's a hit.
If I see someone with a weak point, I'll hit him.
Teruka Uwa
There's something wrong behind me, it's behind me
Na
Oh no hahahaha
It was a bad day.Okay, nice, okay.
Okay okay nice nice uh uh
Mr.
to
No, but it's amazing white, amazing, amazing
Ume-chan and Lissa-chan are amazing tomorrow
I'm doing a lot of work
It doesn't matter if you want to do it or not.
I think the damage was done, really.
I couldn't see it for a while.
Mostly yes, it's fine, the white team did their best.
Nice!
Too many overseas fighters have nice fights overseas
Such a nice fight, so bad
Tear target kill Huge 4 kills No target
Kill 4's big eyes are seriously amazing
Awesome, so nice
Nice, strong, awakened, no, strong, scary
All I could see was fish, so I aimed really hard.
It's amazing that no one is aiming for Kana.
I don't know, but I've changed a lot by participating in the war.
The battle situation is
Hey, it's amazingly white with no emoticons on it.
It's dyed, it's dyed white, I'll dye it red
In fact, I dyed it white.
[music]
No, but from here on out, is this the end of my participation?
The white team was amazing
Strong, strong
I dyed it white
The whole thing
Announcement What is the whole announcement?
It's better to go back to A, which is becoming better.
I'm going back, then let's all go back.
Chani
Thank you for your hard work on the move.Sasasa was amazing.
Eh 41 right?
Oh my god, Lisa-chan!
It's Nerisa-chan Oh yeah yeah yeah
Nerisa-chan is right 10
Kill and Kaela and Ame-chan too
10 kills As expected, overseas lunchtime is better and lunchtime
It was a machine
It's better, it's amazing, it's amazing
I woke up, I woke up, nice
This is amazing, isn't it?
Did you get it back or did you get a lot of money? 41 is right.
I was surprised to see target kills included, 41 generals.
We did it, we did it too.
I did it, I did it.
Gomeru 3000
It's important to be visible, so yeah yeah
Sorry nice 1 kill nice 1 kill nice 1
Kill #1 If that kill hadn't happened.
Because I'm 40, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's right, it's important, important, important, nice, right?
Nice nice nice mechannechan strong
Very Strong
Gozaru
Roboko-san pair was amazing too, nice
That was great, I was super sleepy
I got 3 kills, that's amazing!
Awesome but expensive good job Awesome Awesome
is
It was amazing
Eggplant
I don't know, it's not quite good, it's quite good.
I wonder if I've gone that far. I've gone quite a bit.
I don't know, but I think we've made a comeback quite a bit.
Rewind
In the second race, I was ranked 2nd, 2nd, etc.
It was about 26kg.
The red was also quite strong, so I guess
It's definitely a strong red
It was amazing at first
is
I'm scared of what's going to happen.
This is dangerous
Hey, I'm trembling. I'm trembling. Imme-chan.
Let's do our best, it's okay, it's okay, we can win
It's okay. Is it okay? It's okay. I can win.
I spent a minute and a half with the yellow group during practice to see if I could win.
I guess it's like I'm about to get kicked out.
You know, the part that serves the food is nothing like that.
Wow, this is seriously meta-reading.
But yeah, there was an update and Holomen
The content of the hunt has changed considerably.
So the menu has changed completely.
I have a mysterious reading that there might be
It's possible, it's true, it's possible.
It's possible. It's totally possible. I win.
I want to win, what if I come this far?
also
Ive come, right? How far do I want to go? I went.
Yes, I want to go, right?
At first, I started to get a little greedy.
It felt like it was fun and fun.
It's starting to look like we're going to win.I'm wrapping my arms around it.
Come on, I don't have sleeves anymore
I didn't just tear it apart.
At first, I tore it up to my shoulders.
Tear it off
Even if I tear it off
It's too obvious
There is no way to cut the skin.
But don't touch the skin
tear off the skin
You're so wild, you're such a big deal
I'm so muscular, I'm proud of my muscles.
Miase last
41 I turned bright red as Miko Senpai stood there.
It's too much and I'm being beaten
How was it? Who had the most kills?
Who cut it first? Shitane-chan
Chiara Mosu group was at the very end.
I'm sorry, but Subaru-senpai and Miko twice.
I defeated my senior once.
No, there were a lot of people who came.
That's amazing
That was amazing, so it's the white team.
It was great, but a little bit at the end.
Thank you Nekomata porridge
Masu
Thank you, please leave your feedback Yes
Yes, thank you very much
I was happy to play with everyone.
I will continue to support the white team.
thank you
Thank you, but it disappeared in an instant. It disappeared in an instant.
Thank you agent agent
Thank you very much agent
agent of maga team
Thank you okayo
Thank you, me and my seniors are also amazing numbers killer
Because I'm doing this, I don't think it's possible at all.
I'll try my best to make a difference, thank you very much.
Nia
It was so much fun! It was so much fun!
Maybe the competition after this
[music]
Shin is
No, it's okay to relax and hope.
If you still have time, you can go, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, I have to protect the princess again.I need to protect the princess.
Even if I get it, even if I make a little mistake as a princess
You can turn it around with a rele.
Pressure is dangerous, dangerous, dangerous.
I'll look into it
I'm going to practice yonaso, and I'm already climbing the ivy right now.
I can practice, everyone is climbing the ivy, but I can practice.
Climb?
Nebut somehow the vines are getting better too.
nice
It's difficult, isn't it? It's difficult, isn't it?
I heard you say that
Tell me when and where did you run?
So, let's talk about a specific collection.
So I would like to see 3 games
Here is the total score. Good luck to the Red team.
What's going on?
is
The strong Red team is 46 Red team.
46 White group 38 points Yellow group 23 points
or
I was at the red level a while ago, so I made a comeback.
That's not it.
hand
Let's see what happens in the second half.
Do you want to go? Yes, but then let's move on to the next competition.
Everyone moves to the race venue.
Let's
Gogo
looking forward to looking forward to
Let's enjoy the fight and do our best.Let's do our best.
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Is everyone else coming?
Nahisi
It looks like Naro, so that's a total memory.
Points total, no, that's that, that's that.
If I add it to the previous point, it'll be fine.
That's amazing if you add it up. This is still a team.
It wasn't the VC, but I guess everyone is doing their best.
Pink, yellow, all yellow, red is fine, but even me
Yes, yes, you don't have to be in a hurry
But Princess Iris, oh princess, let's go, princess, fly away!
Tapi red yellow or this princess's outfit is amazing
I'm still not sure if it's cute or mysterious
No, you're cute. You're naked. This is naked.
naked naked
The naked naked princess is so naked
Enter the princess and the dangerous exposed princess
Yes, it's princess
Hime Hime I'll do my best. This princess looks so powerful.
is
I wonder why it's the same.
A princess from a neighboring country is a princess from a neighboring country.
Let's do a little trade, please.
Hello princess hello princess princesses
I have to take a look at your face after all.
Thank you very much.
Please include me too, Princess Moanori.
More
I hope you will be kind to me.
We are princesses after all, after all.
Yes, that was a very fun battle.
Let's do it. Let's not do anything dangerous.
Let's go, don't run slowly
Yes, that's right. I ran all the time.
I've never run in my entire life.
I wonder if Hime Mamo was my princess in 5 seconds.
I've only stepped foot once.
Please take care of your body, please don't run, seriously.
Never run, never run, bye my house.
The princess might even be the strongest.
Please don't do that anymore
I'm so weak and yet I'm like this
Even though she's a shy princess, she's definitely the best physically.
I can hear it crushed
Okay, let's start by asking the red team.
The role of Ehime in Masho Red Team is played by Yami Toma.
Kishi's role is Shion-tan and Hi-Aoki Hai and.
Fluffy, fluffy, and fluffy.
Well, here are the 4 photos, and the fluffy ones are those 2.
I'm alone, so yes, thank you very much.
death
Thank you very much.
If you say yes, how about your enthusiasm?
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, this, that, that
We all practiced until late at night.
That's right, that's right. I usually go to bed at 9 o'clock.
I practiced until 1 o'clock.
I really messed up, no, it's true.
Nothing really happens at 9 o'clock or 10 o'clock.
I sleep on days when I don't have to, which is amazing.
Wow, you woke up really early.
I guess that's true, do your best.
Okay, let's do our best
It's okay to do your best, try your best, do your best
Next, I would like to go to the white team hahaha
Yes, white group, can you hear me? I can hear you.
So I would like to start by introducing the players.
I think it's going to rain if it rains.
It looks like it looks like it
Hey, who's who?
Here comes the princess. Yes, the rider is Azuki-chan.
Yes, yes, then yes, yes, then seven.
Chanhaiha
[music]
It has become a name
What do you think? I don't have much enthusiasm.
Those knights of mine protect me.
I think it's okay because I can give it to you.It's okay.
Well, this time it's about those three princess guardians.
I would like to have three princesses.
I would like to protect the three princesses. Thank you.
Please, Princess
I'm alone, I'm so cute, I'm so cute
It's cute Yume-senpai, are you okay?
This guy is getting old.
I'm confused. I'm confused. Good luck.
Thank you very much
Thank you for the fight
Lastly, I would like to ask the Kigumi
The wooden group plays the role of the princess and the role of the knight Iris is summer color.
Matsuri And E Knight Ga Hajime Ririka Hajime
It's a Lyrica Festival, so I said yes.
How is Hatsuhime doing today?
Yes, Princess, with the lucky knights
Show everyone the amazing cooperative play of
I will
It's amazing Princess Princess
Porin 1 at the fastest speed
I want you to steal the first place.
Princess yes the true princess is me
Yes there is good luck yes
Thank you very much and keep up the good work
Please enter as well, yes.
Alright, that's it for now.
It will start as soon as the entry is completed.
Let's go. The wall is already there. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Looks like it's okay then
Swell, I've always been a little nervous.
I'm not talking about this, I'm not a princess.
But I'm not a princess, I'm not a princess, but I'm moving
Mume-senpai is aso-asokamu
Chanaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa nice mu-chan
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here.
I'm so excited to see if I can go. Wow, let's do our best.
will be the first scaffolding, then.
Azukiet and the last color is Azukimude
I'll call out the name of the person on board.
Carrion soooa Carrion Kishiname
Sez ok
Senkyu
Oh, it was a really nerve-wracking ride.
It was a ride. Is it conveyed to you? Ride
Member name Seiseinkata Senpai Mume
Senpai okay okay
Cue English sleigh
It's extremely reliable, reliable time.
Yeah, I think I'll stop moving when my name is called.
So namece top namece top
namecess tops
I'm going to the orchestra ao
I'm going from the right side of my foot, Kamaea-chan M
Kazu-chan Gomenzu-chan Mume-chan
I can go, Nana.
Next time with Nao, let's all climb up now.
Chankazamakakorehazu-chan is not good
Chankazamaakorezu
Chan-mei-chan ka oh oh oh nice Nasuo
O
Oh nice
Um nota ah
Okay, I feel like anything is fine.
I had them do this for me.
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Do you understand this or that? Wait, do you understand?
Moene, I can only hear my voice for a while
That's it, I see. Wait.
Wait, wait, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Tell me the answer, wait, the book will open.
This is Luna, there's a big possibility.
luna canaluna's
scratch
What is Karuna?
Lamb meat lamb kud
Tonmuton's special hamburger has arrived.
Hamburg steak made with beef and potatoes
Cut the carrots on a cutting board and fry them on a griddle.
Please muim ira rum ra ok
Well then, I'm cutting off all of Killo.
lakilkilkilkillamramramraade
Then I didn't cut the meat for that or the eggplant.
Cut the meat, cut the meat, cut the meat, cut the meat.
The cut lamb is complete. Lamb is complete. Yes.
I made a special hamburger steak.
Let's go and eat octopus
Ooh, the next one is red red.
Yellow Hatena left up to red red yellow
It's a mystery, red, red, red, red
Relena Yoshi
let's go let's go
a
Mumu-chan got caught.
This many sora, nice nice nice nao
Ooooooooo
Oh
Gooooooooo
Too white oi
Nice, nice, quick yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
Fight, fight, fight, fight
Eh, I killed him, nice, I killed him, nice, nice, nice
Nice Ora Ora, will I be able to go? Maybe I'll collapse.
one
Chin
tai nice rere na run run run nice nice
Nice run, run, run ooshi nice nice aa
Yay, it was dangerous, it was dangerous, nice nice
Nice, dangerous, dangerous, even if my dog gets caught.
2 and such a high yield
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
Something like that is coming down there.
Mecha-chan
Nice, good
Nice and I are both really bad.
If I failed, the next problem took a long time.
hey
[music]
I'm in a hurry
A dangerous 3 second difference from 3rd place
Desubishi Jump Punch Oasto?
Maybe I'll come back Where will I go back?
At the nice contestants, everyone
place
I know that Unno's is like that.
I lost the book.
More T
I couldn't help it
I would like to interview each team.
I think everyone can hear it.
Congratulations
Congratulations!
Well then, how was Shion from Knight?
When I tried it, I was really practicing and practicing.
Apparently, the four of them gathered together.
And it turned out to be a great result.
I'm so happy. I'm glad I came in first place.
It was so fast, so fast
I'll fight
That topic is so fast!
Was it Subaru? Yes, yes.
This is because I was making it
But I'm curious what everyone was making.
That's right. By all means, by all means.
I hope you can take a look at the archives.
Congratulations on your success
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Congratulations and good luck for the last two series
Let's
Yes, I want to go white.Yes.
Now, I would like to hear from the White Team.
I think so, but how was it?
I don't care how it goes, but it's the end.
I'm in trouble when I'm defeating a monster.
That one that got caught on the way down.
Something between that wave and wave
I want to fold it
Actually, I got caught.
Hang, I'll leave it to you here.
It was in a state where it was amazing, I'm glad it was 2.
That's amazing, you defeated him!
I tried my best, but there were some accidents.
I rode it a lot while
Taoha's question is who came out.Who came out?
Kaa it was Luna
It seems like there is a bond between Aiyakoko and Luna.
It looked kind of pink, so I said,
I was hesitant, but I believe in the bond between Kanaluna.
I got it
I went to see you and it was wonderful.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Yes, yes. Next, let's talk to the Kigumi.
I would like to ask you about it. Yes, Machi
What did you think of it?
It's really frustrating, right? Lots of practice.
It was really amazing to catch up with what I was doing.
I was catching up, I was catching up.
I made a lot of mistakes when guessing the topic.
It's okay if you don't like it
It's okay mom, look at how hard you worked.
However, you did your best, and the sports day was the last.
Until then, we must all work together and do our best.
There is a meaning behind it, so of course there is more.
Let's all run together until the end while aiming for the top
Let's cut it, mom, you're beautiful, do your best.
Good luck!
What happened to Laplace and what happened to Laplace
I see, I've shown you
It's definitely difficult.
Did you make it? Mom, I looked at the archives later.
Tokara
You'll make it to the end, do your best, do your best
It was a nice fight. It was a nice fight.
do your best
Please interrupt. Yes, yes, please.
Okay, so let's get to the score for the Koshi race.
take a look at
Let's see
Tanone 30 points White team 20 points
Yellow group will receive 10 points Yes Red
Red team is a bit amazing
Even if I leave it behind, I still don't know if the Red Team is coming.
I don't understand
I still don't understand, I don't understand this.
The next competition is the summer seat race.
Let's move to
I know it's dangerous, but I won't say that.
I'll let you know who will be participating in the next rematch for the red team.
Don't go before you get scolded, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
It's so fast, please move. For those of you who are supporting me.
It's okay now, Achan-chan Atsu
Chankoko is the red team. It's the red team. Wait a minute.
Oh no, I was sent away on my own.
I was sent away without permission, so I'm home.
Everyone is home right now
Good dream senior is amazing at cooking
It was so fast
This rum helped me understand, rum rum.
rum rum
I had grilled mutton.
Somehow that person's characteristics are special.
It was because a lot of it came out during hamburger practice.
Well, I'm glad I had time to practice.
Actually, it was up to G.
Sorry it went smoothly, Ken-chan
I'm sorry tomorrow, but I'll be beautiful after this.
Therefore, if you are participating in the relay, please join the Eshirogumi
Please move to the contestant channel.
Is there a contestant channel automatically?
blown away
Nodoka-chan is so cute!
The contestants were sent flying before the announcement was made.
Cutting-edge technology that will blow your mind away
Easy-to-understand technology that can help you in an instant
Karayabaido
I'm going to go get some flowers with a dash.
Hello, welcome.
Well, it's better to make an entry.
Enter tomorrow and get a book.
Then I opened the book and found out that I was a difficult person or a white person.
Choose how many layers you want to have. Oh, come, come, come, come
I came
Is it okay to come? Just right click.
[music]
Yeah
What is the 8th person in Trilith?
What do you think of Ame-chan?
The leader of the memory group seemed to be somewhere in the middle.
Mechan 5th layer 5th 5th
As a person, Mu-chan is 33
I see, I see, I wonder if I can do it with this?
I guess it's fine if Nerisa does it.
Nerisa Number One Oh
Oh wow, my character contact number is blurry today
What is it?
It's okay, you can do it, don't be timid.
I wonder if I can do it if I try hard
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, you can get out of the way.
No, it's nerve wracking at the end.
confI have the bookHow
IHowISELECT
My
Have I wonder if that's it? Open
BOOKYeahOpenbookand
ClickthewhiteONE
English was important, yes, I was lucky to be able to go.
I was able to enter and I was able to enter 9th.
It's becoming
[music]
Nona
ah
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oneisuna looks okay
Ogjoboooooooo
job nice nice
Okay, no, this one-chan, this water, first of all.
It's the contestant's turn.Okay, first layer.
Nerisa, next is Choco-sensei Choco-sensei
By name, the fourth layer is Captain Noel, yes, and then.
The fifth layer
Amehai 6th layer
Kaerae 7th layer is Achan and the last ABC
Well, I guess that's how we got to know each other.
Minecraft is gradually getting used to this nice feeling.
I feel like people are coming in and catching up.
It seems like a dream
Well then, let's have an interview.Yes.
yeah
I heard everyone in the Dajiro group.
Okay, how about it?
Who should I choose?
I don't know what to say, but Iroha.
Anka is doing a lot of things
Before I knew it, I had become an anchor.
I guess it's because the wind is moving fast.
I'm talking about trust, so I'll do my best.
I would like to, that's wonderful
Well then, the white team, by all means, take first place.
I want you to do your best, please do your best
Please, thank you for your hard work. Yes, that's it.
Well, in the end, I was surprised.
circle
I'm back from the flower garden. Welcome home.
Saio
I just got home, so Melissa-chan is here.
Open book when you are confused
The book I was referring to didn't arrive, but it did.
I didn't receive it. I gave an embarrassing response.
with men and women
Okay, let's do our best. Wow, this water is dangerous.
It's a bit of luck that I came to the bottom at the beginning.
Don't go back, let's do our best, try our best, let's try our best
Let's do our best, let's try our best, let's try our best
This is the right one, I fell.
I'm doing my best here. The water is amazing. It's amazing.
Wow
circle
Oh no no no
tension
I must have practiced.
The bad mental health is starting
Mentally it's okay, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's the country.
It's okay, just remember and do your best.
It's true and true, but it's the end.
It's the last one, it's the last one, right?
After this is over, let's go eat some delicious meat.
No, I'm really going to talk to you about it, Azuki.
Yakiniku Yakiniku that was so so so so so so so so such
Owa shabu shabuea
Oh yeah
line
Good luck yes
Good luck, Narimelisa-san! Do your best!
Do your best, try your best, try your best, keep calm
I'll be waiting for you, come on.
Hey there
Kakananaisuki
Nike Nice Bread Nice Bread
nice nice is nice
I'm naa
No way, that's it
Leave it to go go go
[music]
Leave it to me, it's time to run
Yo chocolate is good
You're good at it, you're good at it, you look so miserable
There are times when I say that, there are times when I say that.
There are times, it's okay, it's fine, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Do your best, do your best, it's okay, go.
Go! Go! Go
Go here, here, here, waiting and cheering for me
I don't understand now.
[music]
Wait, this bread is right
It's on the left
hey
stubbornly stubborn
Sorry for being stubborn, do your best, do your best, do your best
I'll do my best
I can't do my best
It's so early
Absolutely, don, don, don, don, don, don.
It's okay, it's okay, do your best, it's okay
I entrust it to you
I'll try my best, I'll try my best, I'll try my best
Do your best, do your best
Let's go, I'll do my best
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Eh, I'm running.Ah, but it's winding fast.Ah, it's fast.
It's fast, it feels good, it feels good, let's do our best
Wow, good luck
It's so bad!
[music]
I can go, I can go.
Kaela-chan, do your best
[applause]
Do your best, Mr. Frog, and do your best in a stable manner.
Good
[music]
Yay!
Do your best, this or that will get sucked in.
Or nice
nice
Okay, okay, okay, do your best.
I like Akichi to do his best.
Senpai, it's like being punched.
It's okay, I'll tell you it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay
Okay, let's eat
Do your best, try your best, do your best
Oh no, no, no, let's do our best and go.
Hayara yara
Good job
Okay, okay, wait, where's the red? It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
[music]
Okere Go Les Go Lets Go Let's Go
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
It's a good ogi
Nai na nai nice nice nai nice
Night nice nice fight, Ive been waiting for you to see it.
Tede
Ta
It was a good run, I was nervous.
Good luck, good luck, good luck everyone.
It's over
Her face was strong.
You were strong, you were strong.
I forgot to eat.
No problem, no problem, it's okay
Yo stomach
I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry
Let's eat a lot when we're done
[music]
Yes nice run nice run nice run
Gozaru yeah yeah
Nice I want to eat meat Meat I don't eat meat
Let's go to Yakiniku, meat, meat, yes, yes, yes, my heart is
It hurts now, thank you for your hard work
I want to eat Japanese sub-sub, uno, and beautiful food.
Shabu-shabu is good shabu-shabu
Let's all eat shabu-shabu
Let's go shabu-shabu together
Dabushi
It's delicious
Kaikai
Cute and soothing
So cute, let's go and leave the shabu-shabu to you.
My line will take me
Give me chocolate lines
Let's leave it to Choco Sensei's Choice Berry
Super nice yeah
Leave it to me, leave it to me
I tried really hard even though it was Aiya, I tried my best.
[music]
Go to the wish interview
Masooi Hakuhaku, you worked hard, you did your best, yes.
That was awesome
Good luck, I served as the anchor.
Let's talk to Iroha again and listen.
We are the best.
Everything is fine from beginning to end.
Let's connect teamwork
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Other people's knots have been untied and untied in various ways.
Although there were times when I finished, I finished in 2nd place.
It's wonderful that I was able to do it.
It was a great fight Gucci.
That was a nice fight.
dirt
Thank you for your great run
Thank you for your hard work
Are you using it well? Don't use it.
How many holidays did you have to go to sleep?
Thank you for your hard work on your way home.Thank you for your hard work.
I did it! I am a grade 1 Kamaiha in the exam order.
Apparently, it was really good.
We all cried already
Hey, I was crying. I was crying. I was crying.
You're so sensitive, that's great.
No, it's 2. It's 2. I thought I could get it.
Hoop
2 I worked hard, I worked hard, I worked hard, I worked hard
To be honest, at first I was quite the enjoyer.
I feel like I'm going to do my best no matter how hard I feel.
But it seems unlikely until the end
I didn't understand, I guess it's happening now.
I said yes to the crab, so after this we had a closing ceremony.
Everyone, please gather before the ceremony.
I'm going to go first.
The best school
There was a wall, there was a wall
Neme
we are sealed
The throat that was currently trapped in this school
rattle
lined up neatly
The white team is coming out, wash it quickly.
line up
It seems that Niruo Ooisho was separated.
It's probably because it's a ceremony, so I'm getting nervous, so I'll leave it there.
Only 5 people
[laughter]
I'm sure
The grinning yellow faces are fighting each other too much.
I won't watch Volca again.
Everyone went up to Volka, just take Volka.
I have some bread to cheer you up, are you okay, black too?
Are you okay? It's over here.
It's too much and they're fighting each other so much.
But it's okay if you proceed.
With that, the closing ceremony begins.
But how was Yako-san this year?
Well, I wonder what will happen.
Honestly, I didn't understand at all, but yeah
Yeah
Everyone is working together so well.
It's amazing how hard you work, it's a close battle every year.
I thought it was really impressive and amazing.
It seems like it's really fun, to each their own.
Well, there was some drama, or rather, there was.
I think it's a drama with some practice included.
However, I think that's what everyone is saying.
I'm trying my best but I can't get it all together.
Stop that group, mom, I was talking to you right now.
I'm coming to ask you to get along well with your group.
They lined up nicely, right?
Yes, yes, yes, so the closing ceremony took place.
I wonder if I can do it. It's time to get ready.
I'm connected to Snapchat, but
But I'm in a relationship right now, so I'll wait for a while.
I felt like please
I think I can go. It's okay. Yes, it's okay.
Well then, everyone, our voices have been heard.
Has it arrived? It has arrived. I am working hard.
So, before the closing ceremony, this time.
For the sake of the competition, the voice chat has been moved.
There were so many, but everyone.
Please support Sanne-chan and that side.
A word to A-chan and Nodo-chan who gave it to me
I'm thinking of having it.Yes, yes.
Thank you very much Ei-chan and Do-chan.
Thank you very much Heaven's voice Thank you for your hard work
It's a voice from heaven. Thank you very much.
Thank you for this year and this year as well.
Thank you very much for your hard work
It's full of personality and the host
The three of us did our best so we could see them all.
I'm so impressed.
Thank you very much thank you
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you everyone, see you both.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much, all three of you.
I think it was fun to be able to participate.
Please do your best until the end, haha
Thank you very much
So that's it everyone.
The closing ceremony will be held now.Okay, first.
This is the closing speech, so let's start the sports day.
Please give a greeting from the committee chairperson, Samiko.
Yes, yes, everyone at this sports day.
It was fun
Yay, I'm glad it was fun, yay, no.
Really everyone was great
Thank you everyone, I really do it every year.
Thank goodness I've been really busy.
Flo Live is getting busy.
But even so, why are you so vocal?
I don't know if it's not on board or not.
We talk, we fight, we call out to each other, we help each other
Nemiko and the others had already seen all the colors.
I was really really moved.
I always think that it's full.It's true.
Thank you very much for your continued cooperation.
Thank you very much thank you
Masu
Thank you for taking this opportunity.
Tarama, after all, it's about the newcomers and that.
After all, members of en and a
In the future, there will be more interaction, and we will all do more together.
I wish we could make Hololive more exciting.
I think it's great, so I'll look forward to it in the future.
Thank you very much yes wonderful yes
Please, then Mio-chan, please.
I will
Hi-san, thank you for participating again this year.
You did a great job, you did a great job, you did your best
You worked hard, you worked hard
Everyone said they were great because they said yes.
So this year is also a finish.
Thank you very much
thank you
Oh yeah, next Subaru is now Subaru too.
As a contact point, there are various things.
Let me see the various aspects of the team.
I received it, but where is it?
The team is also working hard this time.
I think you will get results, but do it like this
The fact that we all worked hard is a big thing.
Well, I think it will become a treasure of some kind.
I think we should make the most of this bond in the future.
I hope you enjoy watching it.
It was a lot of fun, thank you
Thank you very much.
Better
nice speech nice speech nice speech
peach nice senkyuea
It's a lie, it's embarrassing, it's embarrassing, it's okay.
Finally, let's announce the general benefits.
I would like to go to the
The presentation is about 1 and then about 100.
At the end, there were 3 groups with a score of about 10.
I would like to announce it at the same time.
Yeah then, Samiko, the sports day executive committee chairperson.
Thank you for your specific announcement.
OK, so let's start with number 1.
Masuhai
Oh that's it
Please go ahead! Wow, the red team is 8, the white team is
8 Oh yeah, the yellow group is 6.
886 Oh, it's scary, it's a little scary, it's a little scary
The announcement ceremony is scary, but I don't know yet.
I don't know, I don't know what to do, so let's continue.
Well, I'll announce about 100 first.
Yes, yes, about 100
86 Doda
It's terrible, it's dangerous if you can't see it
It's crazy, I still don't understand, all of this is here
It's about 100 in total. It's terrible.
Eh, all 1 I'll go last, everyone, okay.
What's going on? About 10 at the end.
This is an announcement.
please
What happened? What happened? I said yes.
As a result, the red team won with 158 points.
Congratulations on red
Congratulations, congratulations on starting again
Congratulations on your birthday
amazing
The only thing I regret is not having a big fight.
I understand, but
It's reflected here, it's reflected here, it's terrible
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, let's get along, get along, get along
Shiro is coming, friendly please
Please be friendly and second place is
White team with 138 points Yes, 3rd place with 106 points
Well done, you did a great job
You did your best
Yes, it was amazing, it was amazing, I say yes.
Is that why you're giving me an award? Yes, yes.
There will be an awards ceremony this time, everyone!
First of all, it's Domedal in the yellow group.
Well then, it's okay, yellow team player teacher.
Representative Hassu Kanabe-chanbe-chan
Please come. I'm going.
thing
Well then, 3rd place medal please bread
This, this, this, wait a minute, Miko-san.
Mr. Miss.
It seems like everyone is going to go get it.
I'm thinking about it
Yo
Oh
Great, you did it just now.
Congratulations, congratulations, congratulations
Yes, yes
[music]
Hey everyone, please follow me. That's right, come on.
Next up, next up is Geo, who won a silver medal for the white team.
It's a good day, yellow group Hazu-chan is here.
Please, yes, I'm from the white group, thank you very much.
That's Aa-chan Silver Medal Geo.
Congratulations, thank you very much
Thank you
Masoo was nice
Great job, great job thank you
Congratulations!
congratulations congratulations
Masa and yes
And it's Deo, the red team gold medal winner who came in first place.
Yo
Towa-sama with a medal
Thank you and congratulations to Tojato for winning the red.
Congratulations
what's happening
Adult diamond
but
Stop it, I can take this.
of
Naka Naka Naka right in front of me
The eyes
It disappeared so quickly
I can't get diamonds like that, I can't get them
I'm not saying yes to whether it's happening or not.
I have more than
Thank you very much for your help.
Thank you very much.
It's crackling, crackling, crackling.
Yes, it's a bit of a commemoration.
I think I'd like to take some pictures.
What should I do? It's over there in the middle.
Shall I put it on the table? Yes, please. Yes.
It's on the moving table.Okay, let's move.
duck camo
[music]
Kanata good place
Please move, please
Everyone, yes, everyone, line up, line up
Please line up. We can also fit in here.
Also enters
Yoo
[music]
Hey, I can only see it.
It's not time yet to collect everyone.
Wait a minute.
Please wait a moment
Kanata Takatan
Kanata Aateka is also attached to us.
Everyone is lying, Mel is amazing
Shiny
Hey, I fell down.
Kanata medal is gone
Ta
Tata medal is gone
What happened? It's not like that. It's sad.
Too bad, if I try it one more time I'll be able to put it on.
There's no Emi, there's no more.Ah, no more?
How can I do this at the end?
Can you give it to me? Yes, I can give it to you.
Well, yes, yes, I can't give you that.
No, wait a minute, why don't you just tap it?
mosquito
I wanted to come here and touch it with a left click.
I'm glad I did it.
Okay then, everyone, right in front of you
Where should I look at that place?
Should I look at Koro-san? Koro-san, huh?
Toro-san is flying like I can see Koro-san.
Koro-san, please look over there.
It's true, the villager, the villager, the villager, the villager.
There is a cameraman here.
here, here, here and there
There
Yes, everyone, are you okay? Can you see the photo?
I'll take a picture
It's kind of close to Yocho Meruru.
I'm sure I hugged you before, so no, no
Let's go, okay
cheese
Yay, hey, hey, hey, who threw the ball this year?
Who pitched this year?
Did someone just throw it? Stop it, everyone.
I'm throwing a lot of stuff. I'm throwing a lot of stuff.
You're throwing something, don't throw trash, trash
Please take your garbage home.I can't see the bottom.
No way
Thank you very much. Look at that cat.
Thank you to all the listeners as well.
The management that cooperated a lot with
All the staff are always very kind.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much thank you
Thank you
[music]
First of all, Hololive
The Grand Sports Day will end in 2023 or above.
Yes, see you again everyone.
I'm going to Hololive. Yes, I'm going.
Otsuho Live Hono Live Ho Live
Thank you for winning
Tayabayabayaya
Yayaba
[music]
too much
Yo
[music]
DET