[Music]
[Applause]
he
[Music]
[Applause]
I leave my seat for one second and
chunky wonky takes place
wait did you hear
that chunky
wonky right
like and jumped on
[Music]
[Applause]
it chky wonky
please
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
hello
hi hi hi you guys
welcome to the stream I'm big I'm too
big that was chunky wonky from cat to
cat for for uh chatini that was from one
cat to another
cat feeling kind of hot
now cuz I was
rushing
welcome did
she how long was she waiting you know L
you can raid waiting rooms but I think
uh it's better to raid a live stream
anyway because people will not
stay when the stream has not begun
yet four five minutes
oh so sweet to wait for
[Music]
me did you guys e what what was I going
to say ah did you guys hear the meow
just now or was were you just reacting
to my
meow okay by the way I I noticed
something
weird my
arms I broke an arm I
think ah I can't do the the like arms up
thing anymore like this is this is
normal and then when I push the button
to bring my arm up
it's I
mean I mean I can like bring him closer
no no no this is what I wanted to do
actually for the cuz sometimes for whole
talk I do this pose right at least like
it's you know these arm poses they often
quite useless
but but I wanted to do this pause like a
you know presenter host whatever uh for
the screenshot of Amit and then I I did
one arm and then I tried the other arm
and it just like went inside I'm like
this this feels
broken wait see on this side it still
works the the it's just the the this
side it's
broken double jointed elbow yeah like
why are they doing opposite
things that's so
weird give me my arms back give me my
weird arm poses back that I thought are
so useless but at least I can do this
like h
this I don't need you talk to my oh
sorry you didn't see I don't need you
talk to my hand
pose that's the only thing I can do with
that the only the only use for
it and the other like hands inside pose
the only use for that is when I try to
pose with someone after Hol talk
big face wet
yes
ah hello hello how you doing how you
doing I'm cut off because I'm not
filling the whole OBS screen how's it
going should we fill the whole screen
why
not I'm I think I'm pretty
cute
right H yes let's let's let's get rid of
the hashtags
you don't see me this big often
enough every once in a while you need
this my eyebrows so just because I'm too
lazy to change my model and put the
accessories on that I usually wear for
Fallout we're just going to use this uh
2.0 model and say that is why I'm using
it so I can show you guys because it's
still new uh it's been a while since I
last played
Fallout uh
Lou what did she
say scroll scroll scroll scroll scroll
scroll scroll
scroll no you no you you're so
[Music]
cute wait let
me let me put up the chat which I
finally fixed let's
go there I'll put you here
no I will not get to I'm always pretty
good at scrolling back up okay there's
other people who who have who don't even
like notice when the chat spams oh ki ki
ki ki ki for like two full minutes yeah
at least I notice when my chat
says and then I scroll back up there's
other people who don't even notice the
spam from the chat and like miss my
comments three to four times in a row
make me feel so
sad they need a YouTube chat filter yeah
no my life is fine my life would not be
much easier with that my life would be
easier if my dishwasher was working
right now Mama Mia Mama
Mia okay let's see if Fallout will
behave
today if overall everything will behave
hopefully no USB sounds I turned them
back on by the way because I really feel
like I should know when it's happening
all
right come
on come on Fallout as always when I want
to Tab out I have to open Task
Manager love that [\h__\h] I love it have to
reposition Fallout New Vegas baby
is this where I usually was I don't know
dishwasher fun thank you I'm I'm
confused I called the company okay so
for people who don't know my dishwasher
broke yesterday even though it's not
even a year old how old is it
maybe SE six seven
months and it just stopped working as it
it gave me an alarm and I looked it up
in the manual ual but the manual
basically says call the
company uh then I looked up some YouTube
videos
because uh it was already past the
hotline time where I could reach them so
I looked up some YouTube videos and
there is like a couple of YouTube videos
on how to fix this specific error um no
the in the inside it's clean it's clean
I cleaned it again but that was not the
issue it's not something simple as
that but yeah the guides that
they looked pretty simple like you don't
necessarily need the company technician
to come over if you have like a
screwdriver and stuff but the all the
the the the the the tutorials they start
with like taking off the like panel on
the bottom and I'm I don't know how to
do that because my kitchen the panel I
don't know how the [\h__\h] I would take
that off and so I was like
whatever this looks relatively simple
but I'm going to just get the company
technician then I called them today
because yesterday I missed the the
hotline time and today they uh say um
yeah someone somebody will come on
Friday so I was forced to do my dishes
by hand today but honestly it was kind
of fun I cleaned so much today and
yesterday I did some deep
cleaning yeah but I had so many dishes
Mama Mia
it's something with the the pump the
pump will not stop uh pumping the water
out uh like like it normally would do
every once in a while like it fills it
with water then it pumps it out it fills
it with water again and so on right but
it just will not stop the pumping so I
had to like even when the machine is
turned off it would continue to pump
forever so uh I yeah something with the
floaty switch exactly exactly they said
that in the YouTube tutorials
too uh but then I had to turn off at
least I knew how to do that because I I
I didn't know at first I I let it run
for like two or three hours but I was
like this [\h__\h] is so loud so so loud I I
need to turn this [\h__\h] off somehow
properly and then I realized oh there's
like these switches right uh that turn
specific machines off so I turned off
the dishwasher in the switcher switching
thingy yeah yeah float switch confirmed
yep float float stuck yeah yeah yeah and
there's YouTube videos that show how to
fix it but you have to take off the
panel on the bottom of the kitchen and I
don't know how to do that so
KY you you noticed that I missed it huh
I'm not sure
sometimes yeah float yeah it's like deep
inside somewhere I can't get there I'm
just going to let a professional do it
but then I was kind of confused when
they said something like oh yeah we're
going to bill you to your address right
and I'm like Bill [\h__\h] I have to pay
for this don't I have a guarantee or
something on this [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
what you for real now well whatever send
me the [\h__\h]
technician yeah I could try like maybe
if RBF would come by tomorrow we could
probably figure it out warranty yeah we
call it guarantee in
Austria I don't know I remember when I
got my kitchen
done uh I was sent from the kitchen
Studio they sent me uh my guarantees
warranties for my uh cement uh machines
but not for my dishwasher so maybe I
don't have one I don't know but
shouldn't I have one by
default yeah it's less than a [\h__\h]
year
old we'll see what machine what what do
you mean machine what uh oh like
Appliance should I say Appliance what my
one seens what what what does that sound
like to you seens s i e n m e NS do you
say it like Simons in English I'm sure
you have that comment uh company over
there it's famous at least my dishwasher
company uh that one I'm I I know that
exists in America because the tutorials
were from America the dishwasher is m m
i e l
e oh you thought I
said see
seens you Mama Mia Mama
M took me a while to understand what you
guys thought you heard you little
shits Bonk Bonk Bonk Bonk Bonk Bonk Bonk
BK
bnk Basta
finito Basta
finito but you walked in I don't even
know man I don't even know
so yeah I I don't know I don't want to
wait for Friday either maybe maybe I
will I don't know well I wash the dishes
now so
whatever and yesterday after it broke I
was like okay well my dishes are dirty
and I'm not in the mood to clean but I
do have to cook so I just cooked a one
pot one pot pasta which turned out so
good one pot pasta I wonder if rder
would approve my pasta but honest ly I
don't think there's anything wrong with
my pasta it was a really good Pasta
Pasta okay okay right maybe I should
start playing the game but I'm having
fun to chatting pasta finito
phixo did you break the pasta no there
was nothing to break because it's um
it's like the shell shaped pasta shell
shaped pasta it's small and like round
and looks like half of a
shell I wouldn't break it but I will say
if I ever do something with spaghetti I
usually break it because
otherwise it doesn't fully fit in and I
don't think I have OCD but it kind of
annoys me when it kind of annoys me when
when some stuff is sticking out and it
has to take a while to cook the bottom
part to slowly bring in the rest of and
I push it and I push it you know from
the from the top
[Laughter]
don't worry I don't break it often
because I don't use spaghetti that often
you must swirl what do you mean ah that
doesn't really help I'm
leaving what do you mean it takes two
minutes no it takes too long it takes
too
long don't lie to me a lot of you guys
do it
too I believe none of what you're saying
not the
spet I just I just don't like it when
it's like because then I feel like okay
well you got a head start the bottom
part of the spaghetti got a head start
start in cooking the
pasta there's a larger pot I have a
really large pot and even with that it
maybe it's a close close
call oh
well your Italian ancestors would come
from the dead and murder you no way come
on oh no it can't be it can't all be so
strict it can't all be so strict I I
whatever I'm just going to use different
pasta okay don't worry about it
different pasta here can we start the
game will it show up when I tap back
in yeah yeah yeah I do push it into the
pot at the other end will eventually
Bend but it takes a while so obviously
it's getting a head start by going in
first and getting like softer before the
rest of
it it's not right okay it seems like
wait we need one more trip to the task
manager so that I can change the where
the [\h__\h] is my mouse
huh I lost my
mouse it's gone
I swear it's nowhere to be
found ah I found I found it where were
you I missed you it's sometimes it's
really like they're messing with you
they're all messing with you aren't
they okay Yamaha please there we go it's
kind of loud which one is this there you
go wow I'm mixing oh you guys
you
guys sorry one more moment it's sucks
that I have to Tab out for every single
[\h__\h] thing that was probably too loud
so yeah I know I know I know now I lost
my mouse
again why the [\h__\h]
hello this makes no
sense
mouse mouse he I'm losing my viewers
because of this
[\h__\h] I can't believe
this what if I there it is there it is
thank you
s careful careful transport the mouse
from the left screen but no it gets lost
I see it on my left
screen no ah a there it is there it is
okay no that was not normal it
just it's just gone okay let's make this
quiet so I don't have to Tab out
again oh wait no one more
time another thing that annoys me
sorry okay I think I figured it out now
yeah okay I figured out how to get my
mouse back
faster now let me move this over here
all right all right all right okay okay
okay
i' I've been told that apparently if I
wanted to I could finish the game today
but I think the game has been quite nice
as a filler game and there's surely
still a million side quests that I could
do
so there's a high pitch noise I hear
that too but it don't like I don't know
uh I had that to with other mixers I
don't really
know why it's there
um but probably with bgm you won't
notice it
anymore
right it hurts
you there's a lot of sad things to do
yeah that's why I thought we can just
drag it out more it's a nice side game a
filler
game
Maga here I'll just turn down my then I
I don't hear it anymore now
or just a little bit but when when
there's no music I hear a little bit
here okay I went down on
the on the uh whatever
okay how do you play this game again I
don't recall where were we what have we
done does somebody have like a little
bit of a throwback for us recover the
pulse gun from vault 34 recover the
experimental data from Vault 22
return with Veronica to the Brotherhood
ah yeah we should do that Veronica I
remember me and Veronica we wanted to do
some stuff we should do that yeah I
remember we wanted to do that next time
we play how do you do things how do I
okay left click is probably
shooting how there we
go uh return okay all right that's all I
needed
now how do I how do I open
my T tab tab
okay tab it's been a hot minute where's
the oh this is all the same Quest I
Could Make You Care this is the Veronica
Quest return with Veronica to the
Brotherhood of Steel eldo with evidence
of the brotherhood's misguided
priorities wait should I do the other
things first or are the other things
contradicting this
thing like if I do that
I only need one of the items ah okay
recover the pulse gun if it still exists
what which one should I do have I been
to one of these
vaults is this saying if the Vault still
exists or if the pulse gun still
exists I already have one ah does it not
matter which one it
is but then it would be checked off
pulse gun Vault 22 is the plant
one why don't we have the data
then if the square is filled it should
be finished yeah now we finished all
these things okay this this is a fine
game for people who don't know what the
hell is going on because I don't know
what the hell is going on
either we are in the Wasteland in Las
Vegas there's all all kinds of parties
who hate each other who want to kill
each other we are siding with whom we're
I think we're siging with one of the two
or three biggest options right the the
the what's it called who are we siging
with ow NCR that's it which stands for
new something Republic right
yeah I'm I'm fine with them have we
already officially sided with them I
think we have show wait show location
whoa suy oh is that my location oh no ah
I'm I'm here right and we go to vault 34
but I can't teleport there so I just
walk there oh I think I already went
here thinking oh this is the closest
point
maybe
okay new chicken
Republic wait uh
am I
outside these cows they make me feel
like it's world of
warcraft blood elf
cows ugly ass
cows wait I want to change something
here uh what was
that what is this H that's probably not
what I want uh
H okay I don't know what these things
are never mind I'll change it later
don't be mean to
Brahman sorry I'm sorry I'm sure they're
probably suffering in the form that they
are there's a magazine here salesman
weekly that's that surely gives me some
uh uh uh some
skills thank you for the red super chat
wait where did chat go no I have to tap
out I
realized chat is not where it's supposed
to
be
chat you are layer
behind that is not
good that is not
good here we are so back yipp
all
right uh I'm just GNA I hope I'm walking
the right way W there's so many arrows
though which one's the right one okay
I'm going the right
way there was no dash button in this
game right that really
sucks oh it's your birthday happy
birthday naan I didn't see that part of
the Super
Chat nice
aasa did you guys enjoy watching GTA
streams I will say like to an extent I'm
sure I could have had a lot of fun with
it too and I I missed some stuff for
sure but I'm also happy I'm happy with
my choice I wanted to focus on other
things such as
[Music]
Amit and myself cuz I was kind of burnt
out you
know and so on uh where do it I have to
like walk
around how do I get there I always press
Escape because why the hell not is oh
[\h__\h] how do I get out of this
console I I oh I opened some chat
console
again tab is not working it just look at
the bottom I'm adding more and more
tabs what
[\h__\h] I don't know which
keyboard this is the problem when you
work with like three different [\h__\h]
keyboards
no thank you thank you thank
you I hate it I hate
it can I climb up here
HH can I climb up
here is this
climbable somewhat thank you for the
super chats guys I finally W that's loud
in my ear I finally put up
the
uh the Polaroid did you guys see o I
found a path maybe the Polaroids
sorry for waiting for keeping you
waiting so long but they turned out so
cute
right I know they
did your polart is missing what the
hell tag me on Twitter after the
stream where are we
going oh there's an enemy there
apparently ooh
oh wait oh oh thank you I fought this I
thought this thing spoke to me I'm like
why do you have why do you have a voice
ah another one another one ah another
one is it dead already no no I want this
one e or do I want this I want this
one how does this work again K
bu go for Dogo go
go why does it take her so long to
[\h__\h] reload I don't like this
weapon I see more red oh there it is
uh-oh I like the way they
walk uh just don't hit the
dog don't hit the
dog
nice
sorry you
were [\h__\h] escape button I wish I
could just switch it out
[Music]
um did you hear
that it's okay it's probably okay it
just did it once it's not going crazy
yet uh where am I here what am I
carrying what am I using a hunting rifle
well that's kind of
appropriate m
I don't know what do you want me to use
give me give me something that's faster
guys tell me something out of these
that's faster that I should be
using I don't like these slow
things now read the weapon stats
no Cowboy repeater look at the DPS why
why
why do you want me to go for a high DPS
one I don't I I just
want no C repeater really low oh no
that's fine why is that one better do
you think that shoots faster I don't
know if it really will I doubt
it nothing in the metal
box if I shoot this will it blow
up the condition is kind of me oh oh
no of my cowboy repeater can I look in
USA
USA what is
this
oh VA
34 uh looks like there's a lot of
radiation there huh okay test wo h
oh oh oh I must have been in there
before right what was that
again okay I'm scared I'm scared I don't
want to go in is it scary how to quick
save again is it s no s is just walking
backwards do I want your shitty
meat
no
free huh Liars
F5 F5
D where where where where did the Vault
go behind the car
right
pineapple and I'm scared what am I
looking for some gun a pulse
gun um what
don't step into it
guys have fun oh man well we made it for
another Vault that was please tell me
the other Vault was more difficult than
this
[Music]
one holy [\h__\h] I still very loudly hear
that beep because I turned up my monitor
do you guys hear it
still about that this vault is brutal oh
[\h__\h] this the hardest vault in the
[Music]
game yeah no it's it's probably because
of all the gain uhuh oh wait I think
it's kind of gone now don't know why he
I'm scared why is it the hardest can you
give me a
warning something to look out
for
radiation Well my two buddies will do
everything for
me right where'd you come from where the
hell trouble
nice shot I don't know if that hit him
but nice
shot just get go so far no
problem it's pretty all the radiation is
so
beautiful oh a
skeleton
cool this vault is kind of a maze and
you'll be taking rats almost constantly
oh I hope I have enough feel like you
guys may have told me in the past oh
yeah you will need a lot of
a radiation meds for this one this a
horror a
[\h__\h] it's
terrifying a level up
I hey yo oh so like random and sudden
happy birthday to Ste happy birthday to
you happy birthday to
youh wait I got rid of it I think I got
rid of
it feel like I I feel like I feel like I
did get rid of
it sorry about
that now HH now I can turn up the ah ah
ah ah the thing again okay what should I
go
[Music]
for what do we go
for speech
speech speech we already have 80 on
speech I mean more is always better I'm
sure more guns yeah guns
guns let's get to 70
and maybe medicine to
and here I'm making my own decisions I'm
so grown up they grow up so fast like I
feel like working on these things that I
ignored for all this time is not really
you know there's no point in it
now or is there I will
put what could be useful science one
more continue
and then we have this fun
stuff are these the new ones at the
bottom or are the new ones at the
[Music]
top which ones are the new ones new ones
at bottom okay we have weapon handling
weapon strength requirements are now two
points lower than normal for you the tag
perk allows you to select the fourth
skill to be a tack skill which in
instantly raises it by 15 points what
what's a tag skill I don't even know
that having the camer system perk means
you're 50% less likely to develop an
addiction to cams like psych or ja 50%
is
high tag is good super
good it's a good perk yeah but like
what I don't understand at all as a
purifier of the Wasteland you do 50 %
damage with Mele and unarmed weapons
against centur nightstalker sport
Etc action girl with the action gold
perk you gain an additional 15 action
points to use in Vats I love that and
look how
cute is this one also
decent 15 free points skill points to
any skill
uh for one skill right mhm
can I go for this one it looks like
me I mean that's I I I tried to use it I
tried to use
it what do you mean keep on reading I
there's not much more to read I read
it yeah I decided I've made my decision
I have more Vats points now yippee uh
but now I lost my sense of direction
okay there was a dead body over there so
it's this
way wait maybe maybe maybe just maybe I
should always try to keep my HP high am
I right wait put that back there or
maybe not little
map let's eat
something is this good
food can you stack food I don't remember
anymore if like the effect will become
HP Plus two for 7 seconds or does it
become HP plus h HP plus one for seven
uh for 14 seconds which
one the duration Stacks
okay a [\h__\h] who else does that besides
me hm munition
ammunition see I turned the equalizer
off which like balances my lows and my
highs my quiets and my louds so now that
was probably a little bit
loud but then at least there's
no
sound sorry it scared me at least now
it's more intense when I
scream I think it's it's kind of funny
when streamers scream and that's when
when when their their sound uh over
Peaks oh hello there what the [\h__\h] is
that
does that oh
oh but one question if if I like shoot
the Torso or so but like in the moment
when I shoot like my companion like kind
of moves in front of him is there a
chance of me
hitting uh like friendly
fire
or yes so I feel like I should go to the
side oopsie
well he's already
dead they die so fast they grow up so
fast and they die so fast oopsie sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry I was trying to
open this Vault dweller ooh nice a God
damn
it it pisses me
off what the [\h__\h] is that
though that's not going to come to life
right golden oh it's a g gold
yeah why is back not
Escape I am now sick with minor red
poison okay should I should I that's oh
my God I should not be like walking
through so slowly huh overseas fra okay
ah sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry ah
holy [\h__\h] girl
um I'm sorry for
screaming I'm sorry okay uh uh What uh I
B your paper will surely help right
no uh what am I supposed to
take Ratt away I don't have much of the
stuff [\h__\h]
I should take the Red X to keep my
resistance up
maybe like both should just take
B you think it will be enough really I
hope
so CL made a nice sound wait should I
see what you have you should guys you
guys should have R away not [\h__\h]
ammunition this is why you all died you
weren't prepared for this
[\h__\h] what
what sorry it's a [\h__\h]
horrible sorry that was really
surprising I'm
sorry oh was really scary wasn't it oh
he's got manats let's [\h__\h]
go what I can't see
dog It Hurts So B are you sure oh my God
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
ah what what the
hell ooh spring outfit a hat a
jumpsuit no need thank
you let's see is there
some feel like there's a person in one
of these loers no oh oh it keeps on
going up and down which way should we
go perhaps we should put in a Confessor
and take the H PCH out no no
no no The Equalizer apparently uh did
the is the cause of
it oh that didn't wow I did all of that
on my own aren't you proud
what are you guys doing come follow
me two head shot with Vats and a nice a
nice uh chest shot there's nothing
here nothing
here no just a little side
room what what what what what what
what is going on out there it's so loud
too what's
happening wait can you follow oh my God
okay you found some people
oh Mama Mia okay are you guys happy now
follow me please I'm alone ah oh my God
I'm trying to not be surprised okay for
your guys' sake okay
whoa for the
[Music]
Brotherhood I guess wait no not for this
Brotherhood for the
NCR hold tap to the Flashlight hold tap
for my flash what do you mean tap tap
opens this
[\h__\h] why is she going there what about
that direction she probably knows
something I don't uh wait dangerous
dangerous dangerous
oh oh hello
there no the other what about this
guy
huh no I was holding it too and whatever
I don't freaking need
it was he oh because he was already
maybe dead in that very moment
are you okay
Veronica where's my
dog will my dog come back to
me overseer's office oh overseer's
office surely has some interesting stuff
this is the systems I know me too what
the dog doing oh I hear him
growling oh he's probably behind the
wall or so
oh a PC that looks like it's
on for Veronica the steel are you for
the Brotherhood of
Steel guys I've been watching
oo oh okay I've been watching uh rings
of
power honestly it's really
good it's been really good good I
think you guys got to give it another
chance I'm not caught up yet
um I I shouldn't say anything maybe
but oh my are you guys fighting each
other
no are
inaccessible I want to fight
them no thanks no thanks oh come on come
on we got to talk about stuff
maybe just for wa yes
please oh you're still alive oh with a
face like that wa waa who okay chill why
are you still
alive no there we go you're independent
in New Vegas oh I see sounds
fun am I convincing you to watch it
am
I yeah I think it's been like doing
things better than in first season but I
have to say Okay I I I will admit I'm
one of these uh I'm one of these people
that you all hate so much who don't
didn't read the books um but I I've made
this realization and please tell me if
it's the if if this is accurate but like
when I watch Lord of the Rings I wonder
if this is just like a technical thing
because back in the day they they didn't
maybe like from a Tac technical point
point of view they just couldn't do as
many
things um but with rings of
power I feel like I'm I'm finding way
more like magical beings and things
introduced than in Lord of the Rings
maybe they're just doing it because you
know they can do way more of CG now than
they could back in the
day
um but yeah there's like there's like a
lot more magical things that I didn't
know existed in this world I thought
Lord of the Rings was pretty tame on
that and the only thing they really had
was those trees and
stuff wait I want to see your answers
the mov is c a lot they can only use
footnotes magic has left the world
oh by the time of not Rings magic has
left the
world is that
so been fading oh
oh yeah they had a few things like a
ball Rock right it's really interesting
I I they they were teasing the ball Rock
and they showed the door they showed the
door where you have to speak friends to
enter they showed the creation of it in
the second season so far see that's like
cool stuff that I want you guys to
see ah I yeah I mean I guess it makes
sense because the trees the elf trees
they were like dying right and and so
that's a sign of the magic leaving the
world right Malon
and I think ah that was one thing I I
think I understand now the I I don't
know what made me think that it cannot
be okay A little bit of spoiler maybe I
don't know it for sure yet but I've
always thought it can't be Gandalf
because I don't know why I thought so
but and I haven't revealed it yet that
it might be Gandalf but I've been
getting the feeling it is because they
said something um there were some
characters
it's obious no I don't know I thought it
couldn't be him I don't know
why cuz I thought he was evil in in the
first season that's why I thought it
can't be gandal because it didn't seem
like that's where he was going but they
said something they talked about this uh
tall guy right gandal uh possibly gandal
uh not confirmed um probably confirmed
by the end of the season though uh and
they called him
a Grand Elf and I was like wait that
sounds like
gandal wait is that how he got his name
Grand
Elf that sounds like they were like
teasing his name and the moment they
said that I was like oh okay gandal
confirmed
[Music]
right I never had that Revelation before
that gandal sounds like a Grand Elf but
he's not an
elf why do they say that just just
because he's
tall I find it very
interesting I am very amused by it where
are all my
helpers
hello girl why are you going that way I
wanted to go the other way we came from
there
Veronica follow me where's my [\h__\h]
dog
guys are supposed to help me see my
radiation level is increasing because
you guys are not [\h__\h] following
me I'm
scared he he just chilling gets shot
doesn't even [\h__\h] know oopsie [\h__\h]
notice doesn't [\h__\h]
notice yeah he's he's not an elf I kind
of knew a little bit of like his history
from like Lord of the Rings
explanation Lord of the Rings World
explanation videos oops I don't even
need that um so I knew like where these
like Mages the
Wizards uh that they have some
interesting history and I knew a little
bit of that oh
wait yeah but this is like so cool that
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm learning some new
stuff from this you know no so I think
it's doing a good
job you guys have to watch it also you
know why because you can fact check it
and and prevent me from learning wrong
things if if the show really is doing so
many things wrong oh my God what's hard
about this D this uh Vault so far I
cannot tell what's so difficult about it
no we're not watching it no it's not
accurate we could prevent you from
watching no don't I'm having fun with it
it's nice it's it's just way more
fantasy than I expected because you know
but it makes sense if you guys say that
that's how it's supposed to be like the
magic is more Apparent at the time than
later in Lo of the
Rings supposed to be like that I like it
too thank God I'm not the only one Mama
Mia oh thanks for the
closeup when you kind of critical ah
strike
um where the [\h__\h] is Veronica yeah look
at me [\h__\h] look at me hello sh oh
whoa I was like who the [\h__\h] is
that that guy ah wait it's like blogging
out though where am I what's happening
it's not supposed to take this
long hey there we go what happened I was
kind of gone I was kind of out out of
this world what happened let's
safe the perk can glitch it's fine it it
it it saved me some trouble I didn't
have to do anything oh
no I'm getting so many of the same gun
here let's combine them how do you
combine them again
repair
wonderful m
yeah also the whole the whole Salon
history is so interesting in that
show and then
oh s am I going to meet San I have a
feeling like I already know which one
might be sour man if sourman is supposed
to show up in this timeline like time
time time
frame we okay maybe within the show we
don't know yet but like I I have a
feeling is he still like lame to look at
saur no Sauron changed his looks he
looks like an elf now I was so surprised
I was like
what
what he doing a good job gas sliding the
people around
him we miss you in Hol GTA oh thank
you his wig is terrible I've seen worse
wigs in these kind of shows to be honest
even even Game of Thrones had shitty
wigs for the nerys that don't didn't
look
real at
all should I how's my
health oh let's eat some stuff porks and
beans let's go but that has radiation
[\h__\h] that
in the end almost everything has
radiation okay I see a lot of enemies
over there are they behind here probably
at least my dog's back yipp oh W whoa
whoa whoa chill what's this broken MK
free auto dog this is a m free all the
dog sorry I wanted to read
chat yes they use scand I know I know
which is from the same source of to
got that's the thing this show has a
billion dollar budget nothing should
look so far I don't think it looked so
part the wig from that
guy I don't think so it looks okay he's
a little bit
looks a little bit messy but there's a
safe on the wall oh okay have been
damaged okay just safe on the
wall hey why are you guys
going oh
no just don't die come on oh
hey oh let's go let's have some [\h__\h]
fun huh ah yeah I love this kind of [\h__\h]
huh what there you go ah easy oh
sexy sexy
time having a sexy time
here well at least they're clearing up
the area a little bit for
me oh loot M sexy loot it's sexy oh
hello sexy I mean the empty syringe I
don't think I need that but oh
well oh hey welcome back steady weapon
spread
reduced no don't
care
okay you can use it to craft stim packs
ooh I
see oh
wait what what's wrong buddy what's
wrong why are you so angry all the
time where is kiar what do you mean I'm
in Vault
34 sorry sorry sorry sorry oh my [\h__\h]
god what that's I will
not oh
my don't scream don't scream some
stop touching
me hey head
smashed oh my God it's a
party what's
hey did she just
reload no don't don't touch me
oh what did I accidentally cancel it I
don't think I
did I
didn't oh that was
weird I had no I had
a I did there is so much going on in
there all right um I'm still looking for
something have I missed it already or
what why is this weird effect here
overseers Journal maybe there's some
hints in the overseers
journal uh where where is that
normally
here oh we have two fragments of it page
64 page 65 okay let's read this first is
that the did I Miss some or is this the
first one I could have found if you find
a Bed try resting to heal oh did I walk
by some
beds behind a very obvious loot room
you'll know when you get okay as long as
I haven't missed it I'm happy shooting
at the
wall seems like you did nah maybe just
starts in between in here population
continues to grow unhindered with the
overcrowding came violence it was
nothing at first but quickly escalated
with the open access to firearms in the
Armory the armory door was not at the
time connected to the main system and
could not be locked so I placed guards
at the armory door to prevent some of
the more Troublesome residents from
obtaining weapons there was some
opposition to this but the majority of
the residents seemed to
agree real trouble began when a fair
number of residents began to call for
population control what does that mean
killing people foreseeing the issue
spiraling out of or control I ordered
one of the technicians to hook up a
locky mechanism linking the armory door
to the terminal in my
office oh the news of the Armory be
being closed off angered a sizable group
of residents they stated it was their
right to defend
themselves and demanded that they be
given access to the Armory once more and
I of course denied this sounds like
sounds like uh yeah sounds like sounds
familiar this kind of uh Behavior
[Music]
uh oh I'm
[Laughter]
alive I was like oh yeah somebody told
me to shoot it I want to see what
happens that's so okay the effect I
thought it was like bugging out or
something oh it was really on
purpose I see
that was
fun that was
[Music]
fun I think that was fun what is end
minus
one blood pack is that a drug endurance
oh
no wait how's is my body okay
does this stuff go back up with eating
normal
food no right I don't think it
does oh blood pack is for stud packs I
see so there's a gas leak there oh is
that gas also are you not supposed to go
down
here
perhaps you can sleep on a bed it will
go away oh okay okay let's go back and
see if I found a
bed and missed
it cuz I forgot that you could use
it overseer's
office oh wait could have I could have
gone in
there don't touch don't touch the funny
don't
whatever I'm scared oh you require a key
I don't have a key yet
maybe we shall come
back you went here with no companion
wow a
bed ah nice should
have irradiated while being
irradiated what does that mean why let
me
sleep too much radiation or
what I can't sleep in the micro what
so you can't sleep in this vault at all
huh all
right which way was the way this
way oh hey another
gun there's so many of these but but now
with the lore I understand why there's
so many of
these CU this the this Vault test would
was uh giving everyone no something
about overpopulation no um not that that
wasn't necessarily their test right they
just accident whatever their test was
made them overpopulate maybe and they
just had their fun extra was giving
people guns H Second Amendment Vault
arming people to the tee but then they
they didn't stay committed to their test
oh the
armory uhoh
I should have healed
up it was to give them guns and take
them away oh was is it taking away
included in the
plan I want I heal I'm running out of oh
wait I have stim packs
ah
sure ah forgot about
these what what what what where oh here
right when you're right about to get
punched in your face this is how it
looks and feels like
no a he failed his [\h__\h] SLP uhoh
sorry ah he's glowing he's so
beautiful what what are we [\h__\h]
playing Diablo I right now no not the
dog what is he
doing he's like a
wizard is a security officer oh oh
there's another one coming
oh my
God what did he
do he was moring he had a glow
up he's still
glowing
kill all right all right my friend
see I'm using uh uh the thing way more
now huh wait did I hit
Veronica what's what's going what's
going on with these
scenes No don't run into this the funny
substance I need some new limbs what did
I say that oh oh [\h__\h] sure they burry me
oh sh in a
nice who's saying that is Veronica
saying
that I want to help
her why do we always hurt the ones we
care about the
most how do
I ah Y critical
[Music]
oh wait I got so much of this stuff
now let's
go okay how do I how do I how do
I stim pack
or stack works fine right that that
heals her wait she has full
HP she's is she
fine I guess you you were just being
dramatic I
okay wait before we go that way I want
to see what's
here another funny door e which way to
go wait equipment room common room
H she going for a lot at the moment
isn't she
always oh this is okay it's got to be
lock
picked oh no it's it cannot be lock
picked okay no problem
mod on normal mode companion heals fast
okay the floor is lava oh nice
jump I don't know if it even matters cuz
they're just walking over it like it's
nothing
ooh bottle caps
[Music]
clipboard a nice couch or ruined couch
guns and bullets that's that sounds like
it gives me gun
stats ooh reloading
bench uh should I use this for something
I don't know how to use this kind of
stuff oh wait my radiation is is it
still
yab I don't know how much like if this
says minus 110 I don't know how much I
actually like have right now where do I
see uh I'm at 647 holy [\h__\h] oh oh I can
use it here
too is my red egg still working Can I
stack those too oh yeah it says
55 does it
stack never played Fallout but love
watching it I'm happy to hear
that it doesn't stack I was H more than
halfway from being insta killed oh
[\h__\h] well now I know this window
finally let's take one
more
yipp oh look at all this nice useful
stuff
can play some pool
here I think that's all in this room
huhe got my eyes
peed okay it's noisy here oh but wait I
don't have a
key I should save
okay I don't have a key where is this
key that I should be having oh wait wait
I didn't get your
things one of you was carrying it
no oh did I look at your
stuff no but you don't have it I looked
at
you check the journal again see see see
see um did I get a new one I don't I
don't think I got a new one
but Oh you mean my quest journal or
no did you bring the rebreather
what I'm not trying to be
sightseeing
uh uh to hook up a locking mechanism
linking the armory door to the terminal
in my office is this
important the armor
PC and the overseas is L which one do I
want to go
to I guess the Armory right cuz I was
able to enter the Armory I think
[Music]
utility explosion room Clinic something
we don't want to look
inside
Clinic overseers
office at least it's all
nicely labeled
but where's Armory operations
inaccessible calm down
now overseas office is where I want to
go but I don't think I could enter that
one this is interesting though why is
there nothing to find in this
room what I'm going to mutate from the
radation
equipment
room hey I can't find the Armory anymore
is it
higher
cafeteria
Diner now I feel like I I went too
far
oh I don't want to I don't want to
oh where the hell did you come from I
can't handle you
alone hey I need help over here
please where's my girly
[Music]
at die please shoot shoot shoot it's to
good you're [\h__\h] late it's so [\h__\h]
late you're my tanks you got to pull the
argro why are you so bad at pulling the
argro
huh Mama
Mia why are there new
enemies scripted
encounter freaking tanks right
man nah nah normally the tanks are
always always the nicest
ones they're always the ones complaining
okay yeah that's what I'm saying where
did the Armory go I thought I was there
before that is not the
Armory though I I would like to step in
there to see what
happens where was the Armory guys do you
remember
Remember by the way I'm glad I ended up
not doing the Kad that I wanted to
do because
well gy doing the kok that was way more
than I would have committed
to do you
remember on the 21st night of SE
who would have thought that she would
just go on forever and ever and ever and
never and never and never and never I'm
I don't understand guys where did the
Armory
go am I stupid utility is not
Armory oh Mama Mia oh oh
helmet wait is she die
Veron I was just in the
Armory what what do you mean it didn't
say
Armory oh [\h__\h] don't go in there buddy
don't a
ah what's the sound what's the sound
what's the
sound is the sound from from this part
of the the dungeon
I feel like they kind of uh
broke dog is showing me the way I refuse
to go there also they seem
glitched swimming go can't attack you
need to go into the water I don't want
to that seems like a very stupid
idea oh I see how it is I see how it is
I see how it is New
[Laughter]
[Music]
Vegas first crash of the day
yippe let me reposition
it all
right um
um I don't think we lost any progress
since the last time I saved I just
killed a few more
buddies uh Clinic overseer's office do I
really need to go into the
water doesn't have a writing so it can't
be the
Armory yeah but won't I like instantly
get so freaking radiated
the key is there okay but which one I I
found uh like two of those places
now Red X and
prey okay I'll take the Red X the moment
I step in like into the
water which one this
one wait does it say Armory no should I
go into the this
one put your Reaver umh was that an an
AR a piece of
armor apparel I I'm wearing
it I need a key
first are you
sure wait let me heal
sunsets
sa oh there's a bunch of enemies there
is it in the water how am I going to
fight them where's Veronica I can't go
swimming without her I want to see her
in the
swimsuit
[Music]
Veronica hi are you ready to go
swimming let's go look for a corpse down
there okay
I'm
scared I'm scared it didn't even look
like water to me in the beginning I
thought that was just like fog really
strong radiation
fog I'm
scared I'm not ready for
this hey I can still take things out of
out of these lockers huh
this is really efficient swimming are
they not following
me I up body I found the
corpse hey security terminal password is
that all I need can I
leave I'll be fine because of a reever
but realistically if you step if you
dive into water like radiated water
wouldn't this be so much
worse that's all I need but I want to
look around
[Music]
oh that's probably all here huh that's
it okay that's that's that wasn't so bad
that wasn't so oh where are my friends
why did they abandon
me hey oh
oops
see always so much fun with you guys
they turned into ghouls while I was gone
huh all right you were fighting these
guys
H thank you for for
standing
uh where what's the word for protecting
for no for like for gatekeeping no
that's not that's gatekeeping no uh
spawn camping no protecting I don't
[\h__\h] know uh what now wait what what
what
um so I have a password for a terminal
but
uh what what what terminal
oops Bonville for the security ter wait
what for what for for
what oh
dear bye password we
need did I need a password in here by
any
chance
no
okay I'm maybe at the overseers
office did that need a password or a
key not not there
girl
bossing gatekeeping gaslighting
everything requir key okay you need a
key not a password got it got it got it
got it where else might I be able to use
this special
password should we swim in here or
should I do that later
there nothing here
utility
oh oh look at this how did I miss
this science skill of 100 is required to
hack this I I I don't want to hack it I
want to I want to activate it with my
password who wait take a step back he's
going to he's going to morb he's going
to [\h__\h] morb oh he's he's about to
morb ah Critical
Strike he still mored when he died nah I
thought I could stop him I knew he was
about to do it need one more password
okay I will dive into it once
again let me look at my
stats looks good I still have the rat
resist I don't know for how long but
let's
go but didn't there once come a enemy
out of this
water I surprised to not see any
previously but this will not come to
life
right oh hey second password
easy that's probably it sexy
sleeper feel like I already have one
okay I think that's all there is that's
really not that difficult oh
wait no I wonder if we'll find the key
for that
too are you guys fighting again or
no make Veronica wear
[Music]
no okay so now I have two of
these um
Bonville and
Thunderbird Thunderbird My Secret Lost
soulmate firebird and
Thunderbird where was where was this
thing that I'm looking for where where
was this computer that I just
saw here
[Music]
found a bird and boneville I got it it
recognizes that I have
them oh I even typed it in
already warning flooding warning reactor
log system okay let's read the system
has detected flooding on the third floor
ah just like with my dishwasher it
flooded a little bit too that really
scared
me all doors at the third floor have
been automatically
sealed system has detected moderate
damage to the reactor please be advised
of high radiation levels on the fourth
floor are they
counting downwards like where I ended
was first and then I keep on going down
three four and so on two three four and
so
on I see I see I
see um that's interesting
but okay
wait uh something tonight we attacked
the
Armory finally get the dick no wait I
thought sorry I thought it no I thought
they were insulting someone wait what
what I supposed to say I thought they
insulted someone like I a [\h__\h] I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry we need to win
what what do this me finally get the
what we need to win
population
control
um no what TR the
deck file corrupted it's corrupted yeah
but I thought it was you know some the
other words I can kind
of understand what it is supposed to
mean did I want to do that is it pumping
the water out like my
dishwasher that is very welcome isn't it
but maybe the bodies will now come to
life wait how let me get out of there
how do I
here did I make more water or did I get
rid of the water there's more water
there still but we
can
wait was the armor always
there huh
wait who's the
what was I looking for an Armory again
was there water here before I don't no
there's already bodies see I was
obviously already here
oh hey oh oh hello oh you red you kind
of no are you are you
oh so
scary you need a I needed a key for here
but I already entered before so I
already had a key
what did I did with the
pumps pump it louder pump it
louder oh was I stuck in here because I
had no key and then I I needed another
key wait that was a different pump song
pump it up pump the pump up the gem Pump
It Up
dance pum it up yeah there's nothing
left in here why did I want to find the
Armory
again why did I feel the
need so I would like to s s s soda
sooner or
later finish finish this the
Vault there's great loot inside o great
loots let's go the loots where are we
right now like where are we in like the
process the progress the progress of
this
dungeon let's see I wanted to check if
there's still water
huh I see isn't this the room where I
swam
through or is it or was it just
closed huh okay okay I think I made
progress did he say
godamn God damn God damn remember to
Safe
uh-oh that looks so
powerful I shot your ass God damn sorry
your ass was in the
way all
right clear clear
clear it's clear baby o a computer
my PC
addiction let's read it first before we
touch the
computer page 66 FRS began soon after
during the peak of the violence the
group calling for free access to the
Armory stormed the vault's exit and left
the door was sealed after them and
additional guards were stationed at the
exit this proved to be a grave mistake
with the additional guards at the exit
there were fewer to patrol the Halls
none of them were prepared for the group
that ambushed the Armory the guards were
able to defend their position but not
before you know what's really triggering
me right
now there we
go okay but not before the damage was
done during the fight one of the
reactor's cooling vents was
damaged uh okay that's not
really telling me much new
stuff H my my angle of where I look
straight is this the same
stuff what if I press system again is it
suddenly going to flood the room I'm
in oh no disengage lock to
overseer ah cuz they're connected I
guess I don't
know cool
now I can enter the overseer
room which I suppose I haven't been in
yet I'm losing an overview but
ah y it y it y it get back get back get
back get back he's got to Mor he's going
to Mor yum no no no no no y
y oh he's going to do it he's going to
morb he's going to stand back he's going
to morb stand back
wait wa
that looked
funny did you see how she pushed him
away and he just
flew all right
um what about this
way I've been here when it was water
but I don't see anything new I think so
let's go back
up oh Mama
Mia are we are we done with this soon
because I'm not finding many new red
packs red red stuffs was the overseer's
office that way I hope so I hope so
almost there okay see I have the
overseer's
office let's
save I'm trying to I'm going to try to
be faster but overseer's office really
can I just walk in a what what
the was so loud I don't know how it was
in your ears but the boom that popped
off so
loud I'm scared is that is that thing
going to kill me I got to find a way to
turn it off probably right before I walk
in here
my screen was louder yeah cuz I turned
down desktop audio for you
guys
uh use violence bullets will work really
is this the overseer oh it is I don't
think I'm ready for both of these things
at
once should I go
back should I go back
just spray and pray kill tur and then
back off but 68% is not that
high hopefully it doesn't need too many
hits
[Laughter]
um I'm so scared yum
be careful
guys my hearts I'm
dying wait a
second I'm
dying um
is is the thing off it seems to be
off is it off no it's not
off that should do the oh oh what Lord
Death what does that
mean I feel like it may have inflicted
pain on him good job I cannot see his
head I cannot choose his
head but oh well chest will
do damn what are you on
Rex's no Rexy
hexie
hello reloading please please hold the
line what's going on why is he not doing
anything is he bugged is the game going
to
crash I'm not I'm not doing damage am I
um wait I think the game
is
[Music]
sp why am I not
oh choose a gun for me I think I'm out
of
[Music]
ammo should I you the gun that they have
here
[Music]
everywhere wait that's the
pistol didn't I wasn't there another
one the submachine
gun is he am I
cheating I stun locked him
it's safe now
Veronica
doggle wake up
doggle if it works it
works oh his head looks so pretty oh the
password was in the head all along of
course is something in your body
too the pencil what the [\h__\h] is this HH
what the hell is
this running flooding just the same
stuff right overseers
Journal oh no it's
corrupted something something necessary
for the survival of this Vault that we
set limits on the growth of our
population something something something
sealed the door and posted guard since
the RS begin something something fight
like dogs something something Rebels
attack the Armory something something
something
unsuccessful
technicals F me that informed me that
the reactor was damaged during the
assault on the Armory something
something control center the
fighting uh most of those who remain
repair damage unsuccessful wow so
insightful many have died to radiation
sickness skin peeling of yay their minds
are sick attacking the
healthy group fled to South section of
the Vault hey that's so easy to read why
couldn't everything be like this sealed
the Halls behind
them um escaping the fate of the rest of
us all
right open armory door Oh you mean the
door behind the Armory cuz the Armory
itself was
open I guess that wasn't that was just
the pre room in front of the
army all
right now I know where to
[Music]
go
wow did I look into you
no ah my
radiation we don't want that we don't
want that at all please stop
H I'm almost there I'm almost there
probably uh Which
Way
security help I need
somebody
beautiful oh man what is this
same
[\h__\h] PP people the people understand
running out of room need to limit the
population handle this kind of grow
can't they understand this is necessary
we need to kill people you have to
understand ah ah ah ah so many so many
so many
oh Critical Strike
nice Critical Strike
nice
[Applause]
ah I died in the green
soup
no I didn't know I was so low on health
where are
we did I kill the boss already or please
tell me I
did no please tell me I
did
no oh
going to do short business with you
[\h__\h] ah it's not
working why is not
working there we go there we go it's not
doing is it doing something
yes hey you're in the way don't steal my
kill don't steal my k
no
bro no what happened
I what happened to his remains they're
not so pretty
anymore okay I was so ready for this
one what the hell
okay but now we're going to get flooded
with all these enemies like before it's
scripted isn't
it so just reading this in case the game
wants me to read this for for whatever
reason yeah I'll save this
time although I am a pro at this
now quick save and I saw this this
time in the slow motion I paid more
attention cuz I was panicking
less
no bad doggy bad bad
doggy
ah wow I'm finally like paying attention
to the things that really matter in life
not [\h__\h] dying from
radiation okay where are they where are
they shouldn't they be arriving at this
very moment did I want to yeah okay yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I remember
you oh oh hey hey what the f whoa whoa
whoa whoa what the
[\h__\h] made me stumble over
huh
III
okay it has been registered in my brain
all right what the hell is going on oh
oh is she dead did you kill my bestie
uhoh oh nice
shot wait wait wait wait wait M no we
good oh she's still
alive
oh
oh ah
no stop
that ah don't die don't die don't die I
mean don't die to myself
please that was close that was
close good though I I handled that well
I
think enemy
spam oh I wanted to actually wear this
never mind
ooh security St wait wait wait what was
the other path is this really the path I
want to go I just I don't know I don't
want to waste much more time in here
because of my radiation
but I'm still
exploring quick safe
okay no stop it stop making me so sick
[Music]
all
thisty I'm so
[Applause]
[Music]
sick no why
gas Lake in here I knew I should have
been
an uh shout out to the people who
recognize fly
leave all right you
[\h__\h] nobody told me there's a gas
Lake in
there nobody warned me
doctor's bag okay cool fly leaf is so
freaking old and random and
Niche hello let me let me off let me off
no help I'm going to need some new limbs
stop dying wa I'm stuck there we
go can you not heal yourself aren't you
supposed to kind of heal yourself
what's wrong with
you no no
no I wish I had more rways not red X's
do I have anything else that
helps she will right yeah oh well
I felt bad for her she was kneeling in
front of me why are you not wearing hats
because because
ow trying to stay on the
[Music]
cover I don't want to I don't want to
die where okay well we we explored that
uh this is is this worth going there
no okay he's dead buddy chill don't wake
up the dead people I was here okay we we
want to go the other way right this way
do we want to go this way no do we want
to go operation no wait I where are we
right now what am I supposed to
do the Armory we're going to go back to
the
Armory I did a
think don't worry I did a
think
Armory I I think I I know it's the room
at the end of a corridor
um
perhaps uh not there it it I think it
was on this
floor She
funk I wish that was the past tense of
thinking that just goes down why is
there still water did I not turn off the
water there because of uh crashing the
game
or wa I've been to the [\h__\h] I can't find
it again ah this way use local map
no I know where to
go see that's the
Armory is it filled with water no
safe let's safe let's oh no okay has
worn off let's wear
this take my last R
away I got nervous let me let me look a
little bit from my items do I have
anything that gives minus
red any
thing rat's plus is not what I want
rat's minus right rad resistance I'm
taking
these
also
m m
[Music]
x nothing
nothing I'm sad I'm scared we got to end
this too you're too far
they're so proud of their skill aren't
they wait there must be a lot of cool
stuff in this room this the
Armory huh no
no this will be the end of
me security armor do I even want that
should I drop it how do I drop
things right cook
ooh explosives they look like big bombs
but am I en encumbered
again plasma rifle I'm looking for a
pulse Pulse Rifle right
we'll find
it very cucumber I love cucumber make
your companion hold it I
could but I don't know that's too
complicated for
me
um we're five weight
off why do we still have this eh oh
maybe I shouldn't throw it away maybe I
need that at some point oh well we'll
we'll do without somehow but that was
only one weight
less
ah yeah okay
Veronica show me your inventory you're
making me carry the heavy stuff aren't
you
exactly what is the heavy stuff wait
wait can I sort by heavy
maybe not but
um what's typically heavy weight
eight a lot of things don't have weight
in the first place fish and
Battery fish and
chips scrap metal
electron no wait that's
value missile nothing has weight here
yeah cuz ammo don't have
weight I got a lot of junk to throw
out like
what thanks for the ra thank you onion
hair looks heavy what no it's on my that
makes no difference that's part of my
body I'm not going to give you my hair
let her hold the weapons I'm not using
like which one I don't
know which
one do I use the service rifle it's
quite
heavy I don't should I be using it
I don't have ammo for it oh cool okay
good
excuse I don't know this is all like I
look at this [\h__\h] and it's just it's
like I'm reading the corrupted Diaries
you know like I I don't see any words
here it has no meaning to me I don't see
any difference I don't know what the
[\h__\h] it means revolver versus r I mean
okay kind of a little bit okay I I by
now I kind of know the difference a
little bit rifle is long and revolver is
short and they use it in western movies
okay and Pistol is like usually what
they use in police but I don't [\h__\h]
know the rest of this like plasma rifle
laser rifle hunting I don't give a [\h__\h]
man I look at this and I'm
[Music]
like it's too much it's too [\h__\h] much
flamer seems heavy okay so that's why I
need you guys to tell me what the [\h__\h]
to do
oh okay that
helped uh that's a bit better
yeah assault carbine these are heavy too
should I take these are these worth it
oh god what the [\h__\h]
Minun go by the
icons take take take they're really good
they're good wow well the Minun is
something I recognized from GTA I
think a man I'm so excited when a new
GTA comes
out R GTA 5 five four four Adventures
were so good I miss
it [\h__\h] miss
it five right next one is
six fall 202 25 yeah I feel like you
know every time when I hear something
where the release is like so far I'm
like oh my God it's so far we're never
going to make it but then time passes by
fast enough and there's other games or
TV shows in the middle of
it that make it easier to get through it
this is looking really bad guys this is
looking so bad please give
me please give
me I don't want another [\h__\h] oh God
sub oh sniper rifle
sure no don't increase my [\h__\h]
radiation
level going to
die can I give her my radiation surely
there must be some kind of red thingy in
this
room and I'm going to uh what was it
what was it where was it what did I just
pick up Oh I thought I thought I had
another sniper rifle that I could
combine it with
come on come
on
grenades it's just
ammo [\h__\h] missile are you kidding
me no I'm going to die
no I can run out of you and come back
but won't they respawn like enemies and
[\h__\h] grenade launcher should I bring
this m
[Music]
momy maybe the gun you want is close
yeah it must be in here hey
you does jumping yes o got something
good for me is it a
dress
no life's not that fun me
lady ah
C4 that's not nostalgic that's what was
written on the bathroom wall in the
plane I flew to Japan many years ago and
then they flew back to the previous
airport because they thought there was a
bomb in the
airplane ah nice memories nice
memories good
stuff can she get over cumber
cumber that's a wild tangent
yeah not the first time I'm telling you
this
uhoh it's still 55 why did I get two per
second is it about
[Music]
to where is
where is
it I'm too close to puddles oh
okay I can't find anything useful
here A1
American all right
but
where where is
where is
the oh
all is this in this
room shouldn't it be in this
room that's a unique assault rifle Let's
Go All American okay okay
okay oh was that it follow the marker oh
which one
[Music]
I hate Maps can't even go
there maps are
useless where is
it there's no way
of getting out of this room differently
right did I miss anything important here
detonator
pistol pistol I just don't want to miss
anything
I
no the gray Locker on the
floor on the floor why am I so
heavy I didn't take anything oo got
something good for me is it a dress
I guess I did take
something take this for
now am I going to die Foot Locker on the
what is Foot Locker
mean ha
let me get out of here fig have more
buttons and dials and Stu you know can I
leave now it's still the elect
equivalent of a disease from
kamora I want to leave let me go
please I just W to
go go
home
go
home go home
let me
go let me
go my let
[Music]
me I want
to
please let me
go I survived vault 34
hey walking out is I thought would be a
little bit more difficult wait actually
never mind I'm
lost lead
pipe is it this
way I don't want to
die it's okay I'm not going to I'm not
going to die I'm not going to die I'm
literally not going to
die there's an
exit to the first floor if I turn a
little bit right and go
straight ah there it is there's a
door
um
huh
what it's right
there no
don't don't don't do
this
camera is it this no that's that's goes
to the Armory or does it also
lead wait I need to go higher yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah there
there there there
there
Hallelujah now how do I quickly heal my
radiation sleeping does sleeping fix it
I don't remember if sleeping fixes
radiation
go to a doctor I don't want to pay
doctors it's too expensive in
America i' ra [\h__\h]
die heals radiation demands $1 million
okay guess I'll
die walk it off I'm just going to walk
it off
Walk It Up Walk It Up Walk It Up W walk
it up W walk it up W walk it up w w Walk
It
Up Walk H where the [\h__\h] is the
doctor where is the
doctor why am I still in the vault ah
because I'm looking at the local
map
and should I go where should I go
starting town where was nipp the
starting Town there's one by
Novak
[Music]
noac where
was where the [\h__\h] is no
heal me honestly this was not worse than
I I don't know I feel like maybe the
other how do I take down my gun again I
feel like my the other dungeon Vault was
more difficult this was just stressful
at the end cuz I spent a little bit too
much time in there
oopsie and ran out of the radiation
removers doctor wasn't that over there
but besides that wasn't a big deal the
boss fight was super easy though but I
was I was surprised that there was a
boss to begin with so that was nice to
see I guess where is the [\h__\h]
doctor ain't no one in
here do your job Heal
Me
[Music]
hello have you seen a doctor here
what what does Doctor look like are you
Doctor yes what can I do for
you I'm HT I need help oh no wait can
you heal my radiation are you sure you
won't be able to read in the dark as
well 100 caps only and remember if this
doesn't help try taking a bath in tomato
juice ew tomato juice ew okay well
taking a bath in it is maybe
fine 100 bottle caps I think that was
all right not too bad of a
price now I just I'm just left with zero
rways hope we don't um have the need for
any
rways
soon cheaper than one rway oh she sells
them
too H well I would hope we're not going
to get us immediately into a situation
where we need any but
we can buy like two for emergencies
perhaps what can I do for
you yeah
um oh that's cheap you
said I guess I guess you need more than
one to heal completely
but that's that's fine we'll we'll
buy I'll buy them all I'll have your
whole
stock thanks
cats cat
ey I really I'm really addicted into
this pleasure doing business with you
new group later cat's
eye rich girl right there how much money
do I actually
have
oh two
20,000 plenty
[Music]
it's too short yeah you just got to Loop
it Loop
it forever and
[Music]
ever so good time to sell some stuff oh
okay sorry was just uh running around
feeling the freedom the freedom of
America I can feel it in my veins I can
feel it in my brains I can feel it in my
hair
straights should I sell to her or to
someone
elseed anyone's fine okay what can I do
for you
let me let me gas light you into
thinking I'm buying something from you
but I'm actually just selling oh but you
can't I need to remember they don't
they're not able to like buy everything
uh what do I sell guys you have to help
me do I sell something from my
guns or should I keep all of
them as I remembered the 10 m ERS
a I kind of bonded with
them even the not the not broken
one oh just the extra
one
or
okay that would have been a good amount
of money
sell the 99
mm can't use plasma
cell
okay something I want to sell something
that's
heavy I'm wearing
that well this music doesn't feel like
Fallout at all this feels more like an
RPG
want to [\h__\h] play World of Warcraft I
want to play World of
Warcraft it isn't RPG yeah you know what
I mean I'm thinking of like you know you
know what I
mean try to
understand how do I get so much
weight I actually no I'm I'm kind of
okay on weight right now but where's the
trash here
pencil uh prear
money I sell cigarettes too right scrap
metal um the empty
bottles uh uh tell me what
else yeah keeping track of it is a pain
in the
ass
lasagna which your free next oh I do
want to play it
maybe Well for now we're going to be
playing Zelda and then I might pick up
quickly on the the little the little
game that I told you about that I got
purs for the Plucky Squire um if we
really come into a fake where I don't
have anything else to play then I'm
going to pick up Witcher as like maybe
once once Fallout is done Witcher could
be our next filler
game
perhaps cuz it's also pretty depressing
apparently so playing it uh like five
times in a row or so will not be very
nice so just as a
filler would be nice in between the
happy games we have some sad games
Skyrim I don't know um I do want to
eventually play like anything like one
of those games like bivian Skyrim
whatever also kind of like as an homage
to
a what else do I sell guys and nothing
else are we good any any of these that I
don't need
[Music]
Morrow wind oh I know that game too
thanks to my
mom uh what did she say keep ammo it's
weightless oh I guess
so but maybe we're happy with this
satisfied customer I think we're happy
bye s Veronica stuff but do I making me
car the stuff aren't you do I really
want to sell this stuff or keep it for
fun like the cigarettes okay I'm going
to sell the
cigarettes do I not
need something
else sell well I'm not going to sell the
minigun
right fishing
batteries gladly
store
them well you mean I want to keep
them grenade launcher flamer cell okay
yeah that was pretty weak right even the
grenade
launcher
flamers
laser service rifle
cell service rifle cell
she probably won't have enough money
anymore for me to sell all of
that let's let's keep it for a moment
because I won't even be able to sell so
much what can I do for
you what did I just pick
up the laser uh the flamer oh it's
already
over uh this one I can sell you right
and the
cigarettes oh and
these oh will I regret selling that just
let me
know wait it's too much
anyway got a robot has 8, that's okay
that's okay I just want to get a clear
view first of
all uh many fishing batteries around
okay yeah let's sell let's sell two for
now give me a shout if you need bye
okay all right uh do we have to do
something for the quest now like give it
back somewhere bring the Paul's gun back
to the Elder at Hidden Valley is that a
dangerous task I
wonder probably not cuz it's
neutral for the
cute
oh
yippee are you
alive h no
nah bark bark barking up the wrong tree
dear scorpions where the hell am I oh
wait is this like the uh secret entrance
or something open
open
open never ever have I thought about
opening a [\h__\h] rock like
that I'm I'm just oh wow she used the
something I gave her I think
got to follow the error which one
there's
two oh wait I remember there was like a
a path yeah there it
is don't worry don't worry I remember
this area a little
bit open the pebble stole from a pebble
no no no that's more than just a pebble
excuse
me that's
a huge ass
Stone not Stone what's what what would
you call what's a proper English word
for
that a boulder there we
go who am I Mr House's robots are now
using Tech we've never heard of we need
to send a team up there soon who am I
looking
for the elder or so hey
Ramos wait what
oops uh ah
here look for old
guy sorry I'm looking for an old guy
anyone hey hey
hey sorry these machines started looking
funny to me
got a bit
distracted
hey old guy
[Music]
Doo old guy
dooa everything looks the
same you don't look so old you look like
a [\h__\h] Barbie figurine
are you old who can tell me the primary
components of
gunpowder uh gun and
powder 10 out of 10 wa 10 out of 10
thank you thank you I know I'm so
smart something down
here hard to give directions okay okay
okay I'll Stand still is it up or down
first of all
we it we
it it
okay why don't you know don't you know
don't
[Music]
know
don't don't
know right or behind
wait
huh said right but there's nothing
right I can't believe it I can't believe
it
guys see this I don't like to look at
the maps because it's confusing to me
should I go here
hey
I hate this place I hate most of the
places in this
game okay not not true not quite
true scribe tag it's your favorite
student yes well it's nice to did the
person have a
name the
Elder wait wrong direction hello
the reports say Mr House's robots are
now using Tech Elder MN oh you know the
name the game won't tell me they're
keeping this critical information from
me they want me to
fail is there access to where I need to
go through
here yeah there we go [\h__\h] Star Trek
baby talk to me oh let I put away my
gun talk to me Veronica I hope oh you
won't talk to me huh you would only talk
to her disa sure of these could defeat
the whole brotherhood we have to stop
limiting our Focus to military
technology it won't save us exactly
that's what I'm
saying that's not the point technology
won't win our Wars we need numbers new
recruits what does the codec say cled
[\h__\h] we do not help them or let them
in we keep knowledge they must never
have give it a chance for me I can't
stay here and watch us waste away
technology guys we'll die
out I know come on I can't listen to
this anymore okay return with Veronica
to the Brotherhood of SE with evidence
of the misguided blah blah blah
blah okay wait where are
they m
[Music]
wait tell yes man that you're familiar
no tell yes man that
oh that's the wrong
Quest it
doesn't
sure oh oh it's just complete everything
complete he wouldn't listen oh never
mind the truth was right there staring
him in the face he look not listen with
that mask
that was never any chance his mind was
made up from the start I see that now I
thought I knew him better than that but
it was like talking to a stranger how
can I help them when they won't accept
it you should take over H well that's
imaginative but it's not really for me I
couldn't give get one of their most
reasonable members to accept a rational
argument I don't see them coming out in
droves to support my coup and that's
really not what the Brotherhood needs
right now anyway sorry they're hanging
by a thread
sorry
I I don't know if I can
stay maybe it'd be better for everyone
if I left spent my
life somewhere else with me work with
the Followers of the Apocalypse maybe
put my knowledge to some good use work
with me or I can can stay here with the
people I care about and do hello
whatever I can until it comes to a slow
or sudden
[Music]
end I don't know what's what's the best
choice for her I will say she makes a
decision not even a hint huh jeez I
really am all alone on this one no don't
sound so disappointed St no if I left
there wouldn't be any coming back
it might be something I'd inst will lose
her things are going to get harder for
the Brotherhood before they get easier I
should support them in whatever way I
can am I losing let's get going I'd like
to get my mind off all this and some
fresh air would do me some good right
about
now okay she stays but she also comes
with
me staying as in she just will not
become an enemy of the Brotherhood I
guess
I changed her ending
okay but I don't
know you know about them being misguided
or whatever they don't seem too bad
generally oh was this a bad choice
yeah not the worst so fine
Choice buker takes a little getting used
to I will see at the end
okay they're dying out and they know but
won't change anything but isn't this
before um The Fallout TV show
I still see plenty of them in
there so I guess they found some way of
surviving and recruiting more
people oh my
God what the hell we heard Veronica
talking with the Elder we won't stand
for
this what St what who are you stand for
what wait what
are you against us right
now
what who the [\h__\h] are
you uh well I can't talk my way out of
it once have for watch you PL to respect
the Elder
decision I don't get what the big deal
[Music]
is respect nothing she plants a whisper
in his ear him against no she accepted
it no for real though no them
no what the
[\h__\h] oh what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the actual
[\h__\h] look at my HP
already so over
it's all
over
run I I
[Music]
uh
runs can you get your minigun I think
she had do
I I I got a Critical Strike
I will not accept defeat as long as I
live I will not
die if I die then I die but if I live I
live
minigun I don't think I have
it what's my best gun here guys what's
my best choice of
survival pulse gun pulse gun does it go
PE PE PE go pew pew
pew eat all your jet and like oh yeah
yeah
DRS ah it's for robots are they
robots what did you say cycle and which
one where's um no that's armor it will
affect their armor it stuns their armor
okay robots and power arm okay okay
turbo wait uh Scotch
steady Med X and cycle Med X Med
X here cycle well should I take Med X
first damage resist Can I stack it
damage Plus
and Jet Jet Jet I I don't have jet I
think me chilling on my little smart
watch wasting time stalling as much as I
can restore limb condition are my limb's
not okay right
[Music]
now wait where did that go
H time out time out time out I'm so
scared okay uh is there something to
restore in my Vats uh I'm sure there was
something J jet re oh [\h__\h] I don't have
any jet that's the one huh damn
it damn it rebound regenerate AP
okay I forgot how to fight
guys I'm
scared oh yeah oh
yeah time out time time out time out
time
[Music]
out ah no no no no no no no
no time out time out time
oh we did it oh we did
it oh
yeah [\h__\h] why' you pick a fight with us
you little
shits how dare you she literally we were
telling the
truth picking a fight with us eh should
we pick all of their items up is this
useful
stuff hidden Valley bunker key
ooh give herica power armor
ooh what's this steel H attack do I want
that but it has no weight that's okay
I'll take everything that has no weight
gladly and the helmet too and the should
I give her the laser rifle
too oh I'm over
cucumber please Veronica got something
good for me is it a dress wait do I put
the armor into into your inventory or
was there a specific slot for
it uh here and there was a helmet and I
want to give you the rifle if you want
although you're a punch lady aren't
you I'll give it to you
[Music]
anyway wow now I cannot recognize you
and you look like you're from Star Wars
should I oh these sell really well
huh Gatling
laser
sheesh give it to Rex
Rex they're pretty heavy oh are very
valuable I can wear it should I wear it
will it not make people think something
weird about me like with other certain
armors why do I get two of these keys
stealth Boy
no is a good
weapon techn technically not a faction
armor
okay would you recommend me to switch
from my lever armor to this one what's
the difference we have strength plus one
rad resistance plus 25 and DT DT is the
what does it stand for again what it's
heavy armor like it gives me I guess I
it adds constantly 40 weight to me o ah
Power Armor training is required
[Music]
oh I need one of you to carry this [\h__\h]
for
me until we sell it or I don't know
oh is he wait he's actually is he
wearing it no I get used to this I guess
people get desperate they turn on each
other first thing to go is trust I don't
think it's ever going to be the same for
me in there knowing no matter what I do
it's going to end badly that's
depressing that's all I have no you have
me yeah are you still going to travel
with me not let you change your mind
will they take back kill people yeah
will they take you back
I think so two things the Brotherhood
has a lot of hard heads and lasers huh
wouldn't be the first time a
disagreement ended like this I thought
you were losing like we killed all the
witnesses but then we need to hide the
bodies too don't you
think are you still going to travel with
me yeah I've got the rest of my life to
help them out I could spare a little
while to see things through with
you okay I'm happy to hear
that good idea
Veronica has received the bonds of Steel
perks substantially increasing her armor
let's
go oh and I got a level up we need more
speech I have noticed we need more
speech I 95 that's how much I would have
needed to talk it out with the guys but
honestly I'm glad we were fighting I
prefer it that way somehow it just felt
right like because I wasn't able to talk
my way out I realized those are stupid
[\h__\h] and they don't deserve anything
but getting
punched in their
groins Falon
punch I want to sell these things so
heavy
do OBS died for a moment
wait where did
the hello I gave him the armor but he
doesn't seem to have
it did he eat
it where do it go oh he's dropping it oh
he can't carry
it okay can you carry a little bit more
o got something good for me wait is
there a Maxima of how much she can carry
cuz I don't see a weight max for her
wait I I I dropped everything where is
the
stuff a there is that
it she has a car limit okay
y where's the other
one the other
armor whoa
whoa you're making me carry the heavy
stuff aren't you that's so crazy [\h__\h]
man are you slow now no she's fine I
can't see the other
armor wait you you still have one what
the
hell
2,500 value
I'm
cucumber I already have a tag do I need
all of
them a container in the bunker where I
can store stuff no we should just like
sell it right away if anything I will
forget about it
otherwise I should repair the
armor you're making me carry the heavy
stuff aren't you
[Music]
true you look
funny
oopsie see it's just that easy it's so
easy which helmet are you you're making
the heavy stuff aren't you the t51 okay
wait which one's better I have the t51
and I have the
t45d that's dt4 and dt6 okay that's
better well now I don't have to worry
about selling why am I still too
heavy I guess the weapons are really
freaking
heavy the tribe beam okay it's just just
nine try beam laser
[Music]
rifle give Rex the
helmet yeah you can't carry it but oh
wait you have also let me combine those
first and you get
the
huh thanks for the Super Chat Veronica
that was your family I wouldn't call all
of them family if they're not related to
she doesn't have to worry about it but
also I'm confused weren't they like in
trouble
because they're losing people and they
they need more people you're making me
carry the heavy and now we killed some
and we're like ah it's fine they have
plenty of people I don't know makes no
sense to
me does jumping at the yes you're making
me carry the heavy stuff aren't you yeah
right it's fine probably yeah I I I
agree
but oopsie sorry my brain so much back
and
forth I killed the witnesses yeah but
that doesn't that doesn't fix the
problem that doesn't fix the
problem why is this down
here ah cucumber
wait
yeah okay what the
hell I first of all well I need a
bed might as well sleep in here but is
our Quest now complete I suppose we
finished it
yippee isn't that
nice we explored another uh Vault but we
shall do another thing don't worry it's
not ending
here just got to figure out what we
should do
next is there a merchant inside the
bunker uh good question does somebody
know most uncomfortable beds I have ever
seen what the hell why were you blue
there
is
hello who looks like a
merchant
oh I might not be
allowed trade with
them initiate well you're probably not
selling anything whatever we'll go
somewhere else thank you
what should we do next let's look at our
current
quests um oh
wait is that a
continuation oh find a missing weather
Hood
Patrol thank you for the
membership find the
missing look at the Brotherhood history
files
that's the actual Brotherhood of seel
quest I get power and Armor training
from it
[Music]
ahuh the Brotherhood quest on oh we're
not doing that are we though because
doesn't that make a side with
them I met a bald guy I
see ah to them with
NCR oh that would be cool I think that's
a good
combination oh we should maybe work on
that ignore wild card as long as you
don't want to end the game ah I see I
see I
see yeah then I think we'll just
continue this
[Music]
one I'll just be good standing with the
in in good standing oh that's
lame will they not be
helping it's more like they side with
you okay is it worth
it they will help
you wild card is if every faction
somehow hates you like a Laster sword oh
that's also
fun very worth it okay uh but like out
of these things which which thing do I
go for for this is
confusing should I do the optional
things help head Paladin Harden find a
way to outou Elder mcnam from his
position talk to senior Paladin r on the
Harden on Harden's behalf look at the
brotherhood's history F
relating don't
OU
uh no pal Harden if you want NCR Harden
doesn't like NCR ah ignore Harden so not
this and not this or not this but this
is
okay skip a skip a optional okay find
the missing Brotherhood Patrol at black
is this like do one of these as
well missing or do all of
them
wait Black Mountain oh it's really close
I guess I'll just leave the
bunker do all the non-optional OK dokie
got it iky my show
everybody is this
dangerous should I switch my
gun manage your inventory store weapons
back in Novak H okay
hey I found it immediately but I just
got to get
out but if I store them I'm never going
to think about them again and I'm never
going to use them
again like really though
it's okay was this my
room probably I don't remember putting a
teddy bear down here
though and what do we want to
[Music]
store oh why is it oh because I couldn't
sell
it well if I have any money the flamer
is in here to
sell the pulse gun you say is useless to
everything else but the moment when we
needed it it was so good that we had it
so I feel like we should keep it Gatling
laser
thanks what is
this BB gun it's also quiet valuable
you had a ruit and not wear it for
Vault
um did
I
what did
I no wait I don't I don't don't make me
feel oh it's in the locker oh Mama Mia
oh well why did you guys not remember
that tell me to do
[Music]
it tried well it was a nice
Challenge and your 30 resist is not that
much we still would have struggled a
little bit
probably right anyway should I put
anything else in like this frag mine
probably
[Music]
grenade
launcher
Las where oh this
one okay are they in there because I
want to use them again or because I want
to sell them
sometime you're making me carry the
heavy stuff aren't you
does she need the minigun sounds fun to
have either both if you want to sell
stuff you can take them to Gun Runners
she won't use it okay the service rifle
too then
service rifle tribeam
[Music]
rifle
exposion what is
this don't [\h__\h] need this do I
I need the minigun not her but it's
heavy as
[\h__\h] I don't
know maybe maybe for the
finale we'll pick it
up store armor oh which
one H the metal armor right I picked
that up
but I should just sell
it or should I wear
it was that better than what I'm
wearing oh but it's it's
heavy should I just sell it I'm going to
sell it what are you doing here have you
seen that tower on the Strip all lit up
you can see it for Miles there's a guy
in here right who takes my
stuff yeah I want to welcome back use
light armor if possible uh uh what I'd
like to see what you got how much money
okay have a look you got money exciting
as soon you will not have much more
money I'll sell you the
ooh hockey mask and the metal
armor ah he accepts my trade off let's
go I got exp from
that come back soon now beautiful
AGL penalty Oh you mean if I we heavy
armor I'll have
less of that how many stim packs you
got three yeah that's not many but
should I buy it from the doctor instead
of him is there a point in
that oh doc is actually on the clock huh
doc on the
clock you are where you belong wait
that's not you you're not the doctor
seal up misleading doctor's still over
there doctor stun
locked what can I do for you do you have
money though oh wait never mind you get
money from me because I'm going to buy
yeah stim
packs um
I want all of your stock and I'll also
perhaps take should I take doctor BS I
still have a couple but I have money so
I will take
them
goodbye I will now do some bye cool
Quest let's teleport
[Music]
to wait
here is fine fix the addict I'm an
addict
what
[\h__\h] can she do that too she some kind
of magician or what
H damn it's night time now is she still
running
around
uh doctor I forgot something is she
sleeping
now
man why is she not just
there don't think about it
oh man how do I wait
again what's the waight
button
t 10
11 oh probably want to wait some
more can I not get over my Addictions on
my own that would be
nice but life is not that easy is
it DOC Lady it's time to get to
work that's not
her is that my dog to thep one You Can
See For Miles stop talking to me SE up
do I look like I want to have a
conversation with you
this town is so
[\h__\h] it's so
dead Doctor is just wherever the hell
she wants to
be what if I have an emergency what if I
literally can't walk what if my leg is
broken how am I supposed to get to you
if I don't know where you are why are
you not just in your [\h__\h]
tent I'm dying here
where is
she there is that
b you're wasting my
time what can I do for you do you
understand Hey Oh you mean you
want okay there you are all right bye
let me go let me
go wow I feel so much better now
okay I go to Doc Mitchell because he
never leaves his house
smart I should do that
too all right Somewhere Over the
[Music]
Rainbow is some hidden
troops that I need to find
another an entrance to the
bunker of
the
huh up The
Path okay my dog is already freaking out
it's a dead end hey
oh let me switch my
gun
to something more fun
let's use my pistol it's probably
[Music]
weak but I don't
care all Amer is good I looked at it but
I don't have so much ammo so I'm going
to save
it the quick select wheel you think do
you honestly think I would remember the
quick select
wheel after all these
years of me not playing this
game oh you fought
wrong it's been years it's been 84 years
yeah yeah
am I going the right
way I'm bad of directions no I'm
not hey I found the Lost
troops possibly can you recognize
them
lady where there's a will there's a way
guys can you believe that Z game is
coming out this
week I'm so surprised that they like
announced it with so little time oh my
God what the Cent
Tower the [\h__\h] yeah I'm so excited it
says um it will come out on the 26th I I
hope there's no like specific time I
looked it up but I oh oh baby a critical
I couldn't find any specific time so I'm
assuming it should just already be
available oh hello there oh hello there
oh my is that what happened to
the to
Oh you mean midnight you mean from 25th
to 26th right not 26 to 27th
Mo e mo what happened to
you oh
no best by
cosplayer evolve
Centaur you
[Music]
know I don't want to go in here she's so
cute
hi RADS in there oh [\h__\h] oh oh oh
oh what what do I
have these things for huh
uh I don't want to take their stupid
armor again if I want to sell something
I can still come back here they'll still
be there right do how do I finish this
Quest like I've seen them what now
holotape
okay yes famous Japanese cosplayer oh my
God sorry about that that was
disrespectful of
me note added okay okay nice nice
nice
next but have you guys seen I've I've
been having some like really cute B
cosplayers recently you know
there's this one uh Japanese
one she's been so excited and into it
like she's so
so hyped every time I retweet something
or so of her I think she's so motivated
to do another cosplay you know the one
who did the white do you
cosplay for example she's done a couple
things her Idol waa outfit is also so
cute it's so
good I have to walk
there maybe from grab and gulp no
oh yeah she's so
cute yes yes that's the
one she's so
[Music]
adorable it fits her so well
she's so
cute and then there was this other
cosplayer I think her name was
k i retweeted something of hers like
yesterday or so oh my
God she did the fever night cosplay
which is so good it's so accurate I
really uh just getting warmed up oh
what's the this is a dangerous what the
hell especially for your kind
I back there's nothing good waiting for
you further
on um what makes this a dangerous place
you must have heard a radio broadcast
the why a human would follow her
invitation here is beyond me unless you
didn't listen very closely why is it so
loud here the voice on the radio belongs
to Tabitha the supreme commander of
Black Mountain where she calls it the
state of utop utop she took control of
this place almost 2 years ago the super
here do whatever she says super Ninja
Turtles are to be killed on
sight sounds like you've had enough of
taba what if you had some help crazy
crazy crazy help would improve the odds
help might just make the difference all
right if you're good enough at what you
do to meet me in the village up near the
peak we can talk further might I might
but I I'll have a plan by the time I see
you I was trying to go somewhere else
good luck it's going to be a lot harder
for you to get up there than it will be
for me I was going to go
I want to go I want to go
there how do I best get there I will
teleport he's got the
doomies all right guess we're going to
go from a different
direction but I was going to
say her cosplay is so accurate the fite
cosplay like not just the leotard and
the cut of it like how high it is and
[Music]
everything uh but the shoes did you look
at the shoes guys like what are those
they look so so perfectly
recreated and they look kind of chunky I
like the chunky look on
them really
cute that's
like one of the best wa cosplays I've
seen in general
yeah good job I love seeing all the nice
cosplays you know we we talked about it
a little bit in holot talk I brought it
up you know how back in the day there
weren't so many waa cosplays yet but now
there's so
many and they're all so
cute yeah did I tell you I had the
pleasure of meeting Hannah
did I tell
you I don't know if I actually told you
yet not
sure yeah I met Hanah she was so
gorgeous I was so nervous but she was uh
easy to talk
to like the first moment that I talked
to
her uh like she was so
busy she was kind of preoccupied with
something thing
so at first that made me really nervous
I was like oh God oh God I bothered her
now I don't know if I should be nervous
or not but then later we had a lot of
time to talk and hung
out
and she wanted to give me a gift uh she
gave me a few
gifts like some of her merchandise and
stuff and one of the gifts she gave me
or tried to give to me
was a froggy waa no not froggy waa
casual
waa H froggy Cape frog Cape a cape a
recreation of the cape did I tell you
that and it was so high quality so well
crafted like really proper thick fabrics
and embroidery and everything and the
ears and everything were puffy ears is
that not ears it's eyes actually
right and I tried it on and it was like
cute and everything but I was like
H I don't really have a use for it cuz
she was saying that uh she wants to
cosplay like swimsuit waa with the cape
because I kind of also told her to do it
and she was like yeah I give this to you
and then I'll get my own one
made um like basically getting the same
thing done again and I was like actually
like I this is so cute but you probably
have more use out of it than
me so yeah I basically just gave it back
to her which I know it sounds kind of
weird giving back a present but I don't
think she was
necessarily 100% planning on giving it
to me anyway it was just like a
consideration in case I want to have
it but instead of making a second one
she should just keep that one because
then yeah she can wear
it and gift us with some
beautiful
photography I want to meet more wa
cosplayers
IRL I've met a few now what the hell is
that wait if it's a robot do I use my
gun is that an enemy anyway it would
have no it's not an enemy cuz it doesn't
show as an enemy on the
map hey may I serve you
mistress I can't talk to you
it says talk but I can't talk to
you I'm is technically a wos
player well yeah kind
of she looks cute with orange hair
doesn't
[Music]
she wait so am I right
here find missing Brotherhood Patrol at
Repcon HQ and retrieve their mission
Haled okay so somewhere here right of
course of course don't let me keep
you is it inside the
building aren't you happy that I looked
at the local map
ah every time Waba looks at local map
kfp be like let's [\h__\h] go
sorry for waking up people who are half
asleep where's the entrance
there it's a medium dungeon do I
fight The Outsiders don't want to fight
Outsiders oh
dear what the hell is this
place fiend cour fiends fiends you were
in the
show St
they were in the show but I don't think
this isn't even the first time that
we've met them in the
game Repcon Taurus well okay tell me uh
maybe I will learn some about it anyway
but what exactly is refcon um what's the
lore maybe there's some lore here oh
it's locked
though yeah the show describes them
differently huh they make rockets did
they successfully make him like or was
it a failed
company they make Rob robots and Rockets
and what happened to them why are they
oh let's go
[Music]
hacking animated four out of eight
correct
oo they sure went
up it got bought out by robco Mr House
Company Mr house is the end result
ohuh
oh okay well I hope I learned more about
that four out of eight andway so it's
been a while but um the position when
it's something correct that means that
the letter was also in the right
position so it could have been maybe
Arsenal
a no no probably not
no assass
infrared
n e d a that's
[\h__\h]
defeated uh which ones do I look for to
eliminate
options like two this is like resetting
the attempts right and then two together
is uh eliminating options or what was it
Let's It Go Again ah
brackets a this one does
this yeah dot removed
cool is there another
one I don't know okay so anime it was 48
infrared was 2 that's probably the last
letters the e
d
[Music]
infrared what the a is in the right
position the E is in the right
position and the N ah it could be
dead
[\h__\h] I got
to do one of these
now dot removed oh that removed the dot
i thought it would oh I guess those are
uncertain either they remove a dud or
they reset your attempts
huh oh [\h__\h] I
need another D
removed
[\h__\h] wait when I reset it doesn't wait
does it reset the the whole word no
right it doesn't I
think [\h__\h] where
there's nothing nothing nothing
nothing damn it near
infrared should I just try another word
ah that
removed bro really I mean that's good
too but
back out and retry but that resets the
password
right back out don't try again don't try
hello please remember visiting hours are
from 10: a.m. until 5:00 p.m. please
show your badge or make your way out of
the
[Music]
building what if I wait in
here I should probably
leave um what did he say I until 5:00
p.m. 8:00 a.m. or
what might find a badge if you look
around but first let's
wait not
quite
okay am I welcome come here now
huh do you mind if I try to hack into
the gate again thank
you
okay how about refund it f it okay let's
find some
Duds preferably the short ones first I
want to find a short short little
[Music]
dud it's difficult to find
one man okay whatever I I'll look for
another word refunded for a correct is
probably the Ed
again um at least maybe the re it's well
reverted could be it six out of eight
wow I'm a master
hacker
reverted six out of eight something
really inserted one two
three for
five no that's just five I
think revolted
resed no that's not enough refund no
that's what I started with revolted
really one
two three oh yeah
true hey I thought it wasn't enough
didn't look
closely hacking to the
G I didn't hack anything I knew the
password all along did it work
I guess it
worked
hello are they going to like
unauthorized spal pattern please present
credentials for first floor access um SP
60 I'm not supposed to go upstairs let
me pass and I
won't okay please do not make your way
to the second floor that's a weird way
of talking myself out of it
acknowledging that I'm not allowed to do
it what are
these what are
these what are these Wonder glue well
why am I still picking up cartons of
picking up cartons
of cigarettes when I'm I have so much
money already can I try
to let me save first
are you done
okay
no you guys always make fun of
me but you don't understand you don't
understand no you don't understand okay
this is like really weird I can do it in
other
games like I can't turn it anymore when
I'm at that point
Point never
mind who what is this
room what is this room is there is there
um a thing in
here a
badge Plasma
Pistol I don't really need any of this I
don't want to fight with plasma
pistols there's no B imagine here for
real take the all the ammo it's
good you mean these
things it's good for a gun you get here
oh okay what about this thing oh just a
plasma rifle
[Music]
okay moving
on sorry the door opened on its own
wasn't
me oh it's also
locked science skill of
100 oh oh no she went up to the second
floor my legs are walking on their own I
don't know how they're doing that oh
what the hell security is your
duty that's really scary
so I'm assuming I will get attacked up
here because there must be a reason why
I'm not allowed to be up here so when
they see
me they'll be like what the [\h__\h] are you
doing
here or right are you going to you're
going to be mad maybe I'm
scared close the door close the
door any badges in theorized facial
pattern second floor access restricted
to registered employees no no no no let
me talk myself out of s intelligent six
out of
[Music]
seven come on that one point invalid
response you have 30 seconds to vacate
before security is alerted yeah B wait
I'll I'll go get some
intelligence I think I have something
that boosts my intelligence surely
right guess we could just start fighting
them too
huh yeah but I I let's let's you know
you know how long this is
we have we have plenty but how long can
I talk myself my way out of it hey
you're not going to react to
me react to me react to
me do they already recognize my
intelligence and they think oh it's not
even worth
it can we hack
again oh short
words B
two out of
four bags two out of
four where the [\h__\h] are the Duds
pets pets
pets to
[Music]
for Less maybe has the E and the
S what if I
fail yeah I would think
less I mean is there anything else that
it could be if it's two out of four for
all of these it's obviously the
ends there's possibly no other word here
that has the
ands we we used uh ah except for pens
could be pens or
less
[\h__\h] what if I
use what was it what if I use this is it
still the same word a that remove mov
D but lesson pants is still
there okay allowance
replenished
so ah okay there we go it was
less I'm such a hacker let's go oh my
God what is all of this add user oh
I don't have to be intelligent anymore
for second floor access ah okay only for
this floor cool cool cool cool there we
go they know me now all right this is to
Carl Rook the vice president from Sarah
weang the information systems Carl Carl
car
Carl
car car corl car
does it sound like I'm saying Coral I'm
saying Carl I would say Coral
otherwise Carl it's killing people that
kills
people Carl I've made some progress
decrypting the
packets Coral is a Walking Dead
reference I wouldn't understand that
from what I can tell someone is sending
progress messages to a secure offside
server somewhere where I to venture a
guess I will would say that the messages
are going to posideon but I don't have
enough proof to make a serious
claim what are we talking about
Sarah Mr Rook for the last couple weeks
I have seen a higher than usual rate of
encrypted messages leaving the facility
here these messages use an unusual
encryption protocol that I haven't seen
before I'm fairly certain that it isn't
a do DOD approved method I feel that
these messages may be a sign of someone
sending Insider
information please continue your
investigation into the messages and keep
me appraised on any progress you make in
the meantime please keep this
information private I will make sure the
appropriate parties are involved
informed and please call me Carl
Carl two IT services from Carl hello I
will need someone to come over as soon
as possible and clear the old vice
president's data off of this terminal as
well as reformat it with my personal
information wait is that
sus was he alarmed by what Mrs Wang was
finding out and was like oh [\h__\h] she'll
find out about something bad I'm doing
let's clear
everything is that did I understand that
correctly
no Insight from you guys
huh office
drama Nica Tesla and you what does that
teach
me what why why why why why why why why
why why I'm I'm here I'm alow I'm I'm
alow I'm alow I'm alow I'm I'm I'm alow
I'm
why
why what do you mean what do you mean I
resetted it and my my face is in the
system
now
what I I don't want
to they already took so much from
me oh no never mind my health is okay
what the hell I don't want to fight what
do you mean 30 second warning I came
back and
then I I'm in the system my face is in
the
system what wait
wait my face is in the
system you're
malfunctioning
yum
okay it's okay but everybody hates me
[Music]
now you want to fight too or
yeah oh man I just wanted to be
friends why y'all so
aggressive oh are you turned
off time to find my way to the top well
this gun is
fun so I don't mind wait do I only have
25 in total left
ah yeah it's good that I brought this
gun with me you guys told me to get rid
of
it do you want to fight
[Music]
I wouldn't mind not
fighting you okay we can be
friends it seems like it's
malfunctioning security
card I'm I'm double allowed
now I'm double allowed wait don't hurt
my
bodies I have a right to be
here two rights faces in the system and
I have this card
now oh well they'll never understand
maybe if we go to a different
floor box up
[Music]
detergent turn off the alarm where maybe
on some
computer it's annoying it's like my
dishwasher lunch
boox me when
Rand me when random kfp name in
[Music]
Game oh it's fading I feel like it's
fading
[Music]
out it's fading in
again yeah dishwasher it traumatized me
it did cuz
I it was so
loud didn't know where it was coming
from but then I figured it out cuz I'm
smart I guess I'm wasting my ammo when I
try to kill you
guys what what what what wait wait wait
wait what what I don't see anything
there oh is it like
a huh
behind it was shooting from the front oh
you little [\h__\h] how did you do
that gave me a
[Music]
scare
bro let me drink some sunset paradas or
what's whatever it's
called Sara Pilla
people beep beep beep you know what I
want the potato crisps like I don't have
many food choices in my
[Music]
inventory b b b b oh I've have not
spared
anymore oh
dear this is what happens when you guys
overwork yourselves at kfp or basically
anywhere else so make sure to always
take a break when you feel fatigued just
like me
yesterday you know otherwise this will
be
you oh my
gosh right so what where do we
go where do I
go where I go where I go
[Music]
where this is where I came from
this extra
crispy I wouldn't say that that's the
ideal form
no God damn it
dog I have a feeling I can turn the
alarm off here wait is this where I all
right that I've already been here I'm
running in circles
thank you for membership for 11
[Music]
months I got to go to the office main
floor isn't that me going down
again oh
no oh wait can I find a
[Music]
key is that an option
where would it
be yeah I know I'm looking for the
bodies but I'm guessing they're you know
thr they in but I'm looking for the key
right now
sorry no his SN his SN got
CAU do I'm sorry does it hurt probably
doesn't hurt much more at this point
your brain will probably be the most
painful body
part
rebound sorry I would like to turn off
this shitty alarm at some point
please
help the broom closet ending there was
some collapse for it looked like it
could go up on it oh
really interesting let me look out for
that well the ceiling's got to be open
for that to
[Music]
work ah please someone empty
wait what about these doors
ah surely that will be the solution to
everything
oh bubblegum medical
clipboard ah no we have to listen to
this while I'm
hacking
ah details
credits how about cousins cousin let's
go bowling four out of seven I'm on a
roll guys four out of seven it could be
H could be
crazy no c i s that's
free
cutting
c i n no that's
free NOP uh
putting
H losing my mind
here I'm losing my mind here
Bandits no I no
ah [\h__\h] it please remove a DOT or reset
ah [\h__\h] okay wait is it it's not a new
word right it wasn't
before wasting i n
uh
no
parties no probably
not
[Music]
Cousin pouring where is pouring maybe
fearing though um I am
no I don't see pouring I'm blind here oh
yeah oh thank God please under the
alarm please let this me the computer to
end the alarm no I don't know if I want
to read this now with the alarm first
let me turn off the alarm somewhere I'll
come back to this
um
alarm where does somebody know how to
turn off the alarm maybe it's in
[Music]
here ah sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry I'm sorry I screamed
I'm sorry I'm sorry I know it it was
unnecessary
e you don't think I can you never
did aren't you guys going insane it's I
I guess it's way more quiet on your side
than on my side I can mute it honestly
okay I muted it on my side now only you
have to
suffer ah this is so
nice this feels
[Music]
so
peaceful I love it
I don't hear anything
anymore
mute what did I just pick up oh no I
don't want to that off fishing battery
those are
heav is it getting
louder yeah it's like muting the windows
sounds okay now we can read it now that
I'm not going insane I left a stim pack
really
okay encrypted message uh blah blah blah
I've managed to get the password to is's
computer I'll forward it to you with the
release notes to the Q35 the Prototype
is going to be stopping here on its way
to the Department of Defense you should
be able to intercept it on the road the
Prototype prototype of
what is it a
rocket Quantum plasma modulation matter
injection
rifle failure while version 32 didn't
have the power yield of the we managed
to increase the stabilization threshold
this is promising however we still have
yet to come up with a solution for the
matter inversion issues lap destroyed
data lost interesting I'm not sure where
we got this data from it is a completely
different direction from what we've been
working on we managed to cycle the
matter inversion using a polarized
craning spin I think we solved the issue
with the compensation field I have high
hopes for the next weapon success that
data we received from Shuan did the
trick we managed to get a stable built
model I don't think this weapon is ready
for mass production yet but it should
blah blah blah blah blah as you
requested here are improvements when
compared to stand plma rifal is that
like what I'm going to get at the
end inter office
correspondence Julia I'm sure you have
heard by now about robo's intentions to
buy out our company in the past you and
I have been of like mind when it comes
to the moral and financial future of
this company when posidon showed
interest those years ago you helped me
rally the board in order to keep Repcon
autonomous I like your help again with
robco failed Pier claims that robco is
buying shares in company in the company
to force a hostile takeover if we won't
sell
willingly H I don't believe that they
will be able to pull together enough
shares without some approval of the
board I think that you and I will be
able to sway enough roads to keep the
company safe I hope you will stand with
me for this that didn't work out
everything is fine are you guys burning
because of the
alarm I don't know what's wrong guys
it's so fine it's so
peaceful I'd stand with you Leo give me
a few days to try and gather some
support from my allies on the board I've
run the numbers and I'm pretty sure
you're right we can fight
this from Julia you were right Leo sent
me a message last night I've made a call
to the board I think with the numbers
we're looking at pocketing from the Rob
Cod deal we will have no trouble getting
the board to vote no confidence on him
wait
what is she
[Music]
also like betraying
him she was in on
it she sold him
out all right at least I understood that
note added moderator project
[Music]
okay are you guys
okay how you guys
doing how are you guys doing
huh we live in a
society well uh so what what's next ah
can I open this no wait is there a key
in
here there must be a freaking key
there is no
key lockpick 75 how much do I
have 50 I need 25 more I don't think I
can get
there oh can I um
where the
books what's the ni
do the L stop really no it's still
there there's a collapsed okay okay
let's look for the collapsed oh there it
is wait let me turn it up again though
so maybe it will disappear if I go
through a different
floor
ah no
stop there we go oh oh let's
go she's suddenly gone
guys we're all okay
now mush mus mush M mush mus mush mus
mus mush mus mush mus mush mus mush
no
nothing activate
toilet what I drank
it I wanted to just feel like I did this
before I didn't want to drink it I just
wanted to flash it when you say activate
toilet who would think that that means
drink toilet
[Music]
disgusting I feel like throwing up
man I would only understand doing that
if you had no other way of getting any
water anywhere else but we're not in
such a dire situation so I don't
understand This Woman's actions at
all okay
interesting
room
CH hello wait wait wait don't
ah only well then let's fight ice
cream luck seven I am a lucky girl my
lucky and seven is my favorite number
now after playing badro ice cream thank
you ma'am have a nice day oh is that a
did I just just like attempt to find the
cheat the the save word or whatever and
it just happened to be ice
cream but I want I want to
hack what do you mean I need science
[Music]
100 Pierce I Le
briefcase H oh would you look at
that there's a [\h__\h] head over
there go back for the ble Cup oh b cup b
[Music]
b b oh okay you have more than a head
I'm glad I thought it was just your
head Hol tape
I did
it I did it
yipp then I suppose I could leave but
uh I don't want
to there's still rooms to explore why
would I leave oh this goes
down that was the entire Patrol well we
saw some skeletons although those
skeletons seem to be from workers
here want to go through the door is that
your problem
huh well what is this wiy it's so
shiny that's a big
room oh we can
hack oh no wait unlock safe there's a
safe let's
go hello Pierce oh the guy that's dead
now that things have been set in motion
motion mention I am going to be your Le
on Le asan and point of contact with rco
I'll be handling anything that arises
during your transition to the rco family
my first priority is going to be
tightening up your security as you well
know rapco handles many classified
projects because of this rapcon will
need a large increase to security I'll
be sending over some engineers and
security Personnel to discretly
discretly install some enhanced security
procedures most of it will be pretty in
in inous however all employees will be
required to wear their security badges
at all times please have your people
start wearing their badges well in
advance of our partnership becoming
official I think it will be blah blah
blah blah blah
blah okay we saw that in action it still
works security system still works nice
and Steve this comes from Pierce the guy
who died can you send an email to your
engineers reminding them about security
policies uh I'll be sending a message
next week about some increased security
procedures well what why I I need more
context about that
why did he write that
email earnings should I pick these up do
I get lore out of
these is that what I
unlocked single
shotgun I don't know if I want any of
this
what what are these
things am I picking up
ammo
H wait I'm still supposed to find this
weapon right there's still a weapon I'm
supposed to find that's really cool I
don't think I found it
yet hard ammo like it's Metro game hard
ammo like I'm hoarding [\h__\h] in literally
every other RPG
game third floor access is for
executives only what do you me I have
first of all ice cream' have a nice day
oh do I have to like wear it like uh
like armor or what oh hell oh there's
another person I didn't even see
him didn't we talk about this already Al
this just leads down I I am I missing
something
here there should be a weapon right and
usually I would assume it's on the top
floor it doesn't get much higher than
that or can we get much
higher there was a door right of the
safe you were at I
think well that door that I just came
through what's Metra I don't know that
game h
well the game wants me to leave
[Music]
now but I feel like there's an invisible
door
here like If This Were Luigi's Mansion
then I could either like make a door
appear or there's this is just like a
fabric that I can suck in and there's a
door behind or so are you sure there's
not a door
here the unlocked door is on the lower
floor oh but wouldn't I need a key for
that
door like yeah I think I know there's
still a door there but oh I unlocked it
okay hi the alarm is back
yippee it's okay we can handle it for a
little while right until I find the
weapon it's fine
it's going to be okay give
me leave it to
W it'll be all over
soon you know I'm good with directions
so it won't take too long for me to find
this very specific
door oh it's this
one there we go guys there we [\h__\h] go
we're so in
we have infiltrated the
system so dark in
here oh my God she finally did it
whoa kfb going to start a [\h__\h] party
again let's go
[Music]
the flashlight right
guys what the hell that one's red the
others weren't
red oh there's the gun kill 35 matter
modulator matter modulator I like that
word matter
modulator
oh that's what's in here that's safe as
[\h__\h] I guess the the Q45 was in the safe
or
so until I took it and the same book
again what's with this
book dirty water is that the song that
[Music]
sang isn't it actually is isn't it isn't
that called Dirty
Water why am I mixing things up right
now so do I step into
this no I can't is that not a a red
light
lamp to to heal my pain and my
shoulders you should read the book is it
in the
MK no tflow
flower are what are these matter
modulator project
[Music]
oh yeah
okay does it does it now show up here
too
no
okay
okay soft lock Solutions I like that
company
name don't soft lock me it's like I'm
soft locked right now unless I unlocked
myself did I already press it
okay [\h__\h] I need more
science what the hell is that over
there oh it's just like
inside oh I can step into these
ones locked average let's go more
hacking
uh how about defeating four of nine
1 four reminding four
[Music]
n can we find a dud remover cuz these
words are really
long a
man
heyen okay
[Music]
okay no searching i n g
e oh yeah baby that's what I'm talking
about add user facial ah do I need to oh
for first floor
access the floor that we entered
from okay Pierce eyes
front Pierce isolate to all employees
hello again everyone those of you in the
main building may be curious about the
men doing all the work in your offices
and hallways they are installing some
enhanced security measures these
measures are in place for your safety as
well as the safety and blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah everyone feel free
to take a long weekend as soon as you
have received your personal packet have
a great holiday a that's nice nothing
wrong with that
email hello everyone my name is car Rook
as I'm sure you can tell I'm your new
vice president until recently
I oh the one I speech checked out
of uh working in their security division
but now that your family and my family
are one big family we thought it would
be nice if they sent an older sibling
over now I'm going to do as much as I
can not to interfere with your daily
operations here my principal concern is
going to be security security security
security blah blah blah I hear that you
all have been adapting well to some new
security procedures well we've got some
new kids to join your little family here
you'll see some friendly Androids
patrolling around the main building they
were friendly they were as long as
everyone remembers to wear their badges
at all times and make sure they are
properly registered with the security
these friendly Androids will stay out of
your way otherwise they will kill you so
as long as you all keep on as you have
been everything will be just fine just
fine thanks for your time Carl please
remember that fful access is for
executives only oo if you need
assistance from me or Ps feel free to
give us a bus and the phone we'll send
you down The Daily password daily
password oh changes every
day
so
okay this room looks
like wait what is
this is this the first floor it's a
first floor what I thought
how did we get to the I thought we were
going one more floor higher and it was
so dark you know it felt like I guess
now that I recall yeah the first floor
did have the lights off
but I wasn't trying to go
down wait but I got the weapon now right
am I done here was I still looking for
something
hi guys welcome to Repcon headquarters
Rocketeer come all this way to see I'm
here to answer I like a tour please
excellent excellent please be
patient do I have to vote no let me Ro
please carry
me I'll be your guide today on the path
of scientific
discovery let's go take tour after I've
already looked through all of your
[\h__\h] boring old Rod or what is this
what's this A do Rod not so arcaders
this do Rod once powered Ron all this a
museum I know this is all first Sil
contains harmless traces of radioactive
material as an exercise stare closely at
the rod and try to spot the Telltale
glow while this case is lead line
standard in these cases
[Music]
the leadline case behind me is a spent
radioactive rod from one of our old
reactors I don't see anything there need
to sound too close let's move along
shall we I think you somebody took it
out what
this plasma what look here a row of
multicolored plasma fuels careful they
may look safe to drink but your stomach
is the last place they should what a
great tour the difference in cylinder
size refining our production methods has
resulted in higher yields of fuel over
time that's why okay no I don't know if
that makes perfect sense but
okay he's so excited too he wants to
drink it don't drink it bad dougle to my
right you can see a sample of some old
safety barrels Repcon once used to store
radioactive waste perfectly safe but
they're tiny on my left is an example of
a mountain of repor safety barrels some
legislators claim are poisoning our
environment what you mean left like this
is your left
I don't know what which one's your front
what's your front anyway I thought oh
well makes more sense though that's the
mountain yeah move on move on is that it
more
please wow rocket
science this is rocket science literally
tell me about it behind me is our most
recent rocket project which we're
keeping under our hats until launch if
you'll pardon the expression and in
front of me is a model not actual sign
of the launch Dome we are using to send
our Rockets screaming into orbit
oh looks like a
titty teddy bear teddy teddy
bear
what now these colorful fellows behind
me are redon's earliest experiments in
Flight feel free to read the plaqu and
learn rocketeers no I
refuse I do not want to read here I'll
open the door for you what a gentleman
am I whoa what is that space helmet whoa
what the hell now for the highlight of
our T due to a generous donation from
rco this next exhibit showcases the
wondrous world of robots that's you
around you are the incredible iBot The
Fearsome Sentry bot and the
always helpful Mr handy that helpfulness
runs through our whole lives Mr handy
which one this one that's you
huh what the hell is that though the
iron eyeb robco always had an eye for
Robotics and this little fellow is no
different this robotic Marvel can not
only recognize your face and voice with
Advanced blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah okay so I guess that's what
they this is the final on our who Sol
syst wait this is like
an small
Adventures those rocket Zing I don't
know that world also that where we
stepped into the where we were able to
step out of boundaries into the
sky sorry what are you
[Music]
saying okay that's the
sun that's probably the Earth
that's a rocket
spaceship now the rest I don't really
know but
probably um wait so there's is my light
still
on oh wait oh
wait this I don't
know what's this your
anus Venus maybe uh the a red one would
be Mars right is that one Mars a small
one there that's Jupiter how do you know
how do you know is that Mars is Mars
that small again oh and pleas should be
red stay outside of restricted are
that's the only thing I know chup is
Bigg I heard that before okay okay okay
wait so not all of them have this like
nice thing halo around it right that
must be special one is that
Uranus no that's ston [\h__\h]
what's this
one what's this
one is that Uranus that's Uranus let's
go hey he blue wow I'm learning okay if
that one's Mars is that one the Venus
this one the other like reddish looking
one it's kind of hard to see it's so far
I want to go closer can
I is that Venus like more like
orangish yellow yeah that must be Venus
said you guys said it's
small cool I learned some planets I will
never
forget uh blue blue and small
Uranus
uh
NEP
Neptune uh
Saturn yeah okay Earth
[Music]
Mars wait wait what the [\h__\h] is
Neptune I I something jup jup juper jup
jup I was like stop with
PE wait Neptune what Neptune is a blue
one wait what was Uranus
again what well I'm didn't we say that
that might be that might be it oh that's
Neptune there's no no not my favorite
planet oh man wait this door he didn't
tell me about this
door
Yoo yo
Jenny Millet security key
card
heyo who's Jenny
Millie a b c d e f
g where is
her precious
[Music]
key what I do with that
bye Pluto you never existed in this
world sad that's pretty
cool think it went to
notes you mean the these
ones I don't
know what would I do with that why there
must be a reason why they give me that
there maybe I would have if I would have
done the tour first it would have been
helpful
oh no I want the
lockpick I need to improve my lock
picking skill
mistress mistress
a huge true scale
model well is that so
special let's just skip the speech check
oh if you like Pluto sized rocks there's
a lot of them around
huh you you guys are so mean to
Pluto can't just replace Pluto like that
with other
rocks okay wait we did that
um we need to find one more Brotherhood
Patrol at Nellis AFB and retrieve their
mission whole timee Nellis
[Music]
AFB this one
here
no here I can go there and the Min lines
there I shouldn't be too much of a
problemo
hi you guys scare me with those big
Bazookas vault
34 what they're wearing 44 jackets and I
just came for the vault from the vault
34 H wrong way oops
but explain that to
me how come they're wearing those
jackets they're the survivors
huh all right because they love guns
makes
sense they love their
guns how did they survive it did they
already tell me the lore I should have
done this Quest first with going to the
Vault and then talk to them then I could
make these connections but it's been so
long I I don't
remember are they the ones that rioted
because they wanted to keep the guns but
how the hell did they make it
out they booked it they tell you on the
tour the tour I I took the tour didn't I
but it's been a while and the the boy
was so buggy and
glitchy let's
see how you like my of Direction now huh
S I
misspoke that wasn't very cool of me but
hey already
finito I have to return to Elda
magnamar yipp so the most difficult out
of those three was really the the first
one here they didn't pick a fight with
us at all the second one was like you
could have probably done it without
picking a
fight and I wanted to I certainly wanted
to all right back we
go yipp CAA wait yipp you're your
profile
[Music]
picture your profile picture is the yipp
wa yeah my speech is high let's go
y
w Wait say something again in the chat I
want to see the yippi WWA
again
yipp a there you are a yippi so cute is
that like what where is that from
actually like they've been using it I
I've been seeing they've been using it
for the yipp meme but uh
surely that has some like different
origin right La yeah yeah yeah yeah
what's the origin of La
creatura
is I don't think that's that's not
connected with the German kid right
German kid is so old I feel like there
was no Laura back
then yeah I mean the drawing not the
yipp being watched so don't get any
ideas what's the connection with the
l oh good night bottom left huto
don't call me
heno oh what the hell wait I thought I
was walking the right
way where am
I you guys only have the answer to my
question
huh where am
I where am I who am
I the bunker takes a little used to
doesn't it oh yeah it really does man
[\h__\h]
sucks
what it's not
even which one do I follow I wish it was
just tell me when I hover over
it what are you doing
ah that
way ah now I remember cuz I was
remembering this long Pathway to like
that direction so I was trying to follow
that but I was still in the wrong
room found the missing patrols or was
something else on your mind I definitely
found them here are the holotapes they
were all dead then I supp not surprised
holot tapes we have few friends in the
world above and many enemies lost
mixtapes but we must turn our minds to
other matters when I sent out those
patrols I also sent three Knights out on
scouting missions when the patrols
failed to return we assumed the worst
and sent a single communication to the
scouts to hold position and maintain
radio silence I want you to contact
those Scouts and gather their reports
like the patrols they have devices on
them that will enable you to track them
when you find them tell them you're my
representative and ask them if the Bears
are still hunting that should get them
to talk to you return when you've
gathered all of their reports you bore
me you bore me
sir meet of Brotherhood Scout near the
NCR Correctional Facility and collect
his report blah blah this Quest is
boring this Quest has now become boring
not Bears he doesn't mean actual Bears I
would
assume where is the
exent I can't teleport out of this uh
bunker can
I almost done
okay cuz I want to read super
[Music]
soon before my voice gets too
tired trying to think of a tangent too
bad I don't have my phone right
now by the way that
fish so there's a reason why it was mid
and it's such a simple reason is because
I didn't just um I did I I I I barely
salted it
and the second day I ate it I salted it
more and then it was
fine that was all it took but the reason
there's a reason why I didn't salt it so
much initially it's because I
accidentally bought the wrong salt
previously um it's like really like
thick pieces of salt so it's hard
to like put it on the
fish evenly cuz it's either like like
big chunks of
salt or
nothing no not even sea salt just normal
salt but they're like they're made to be
put into like one of those Shaka
Shaka tear the salt apart machines
um but um
yeah yeah a grinder yes and I have a
grinder but it doesn't really grind it
much either like a salt grinder with sea
salt anyway so I bought the wrong salt
so I was like you know really careful of
salting it because otherwise I would
have these big chunks of salt in my
mouth but when putting it into like hot
water or so then it will just like melt
so it's
fine but yeah um on the second day I I
just like grinded some sea salt over it
and then it was really yummy
actually salt rippers RI
[Music]
Ander all right where are we going where
the hell do you want me to go
now I'm guessing both of these points
right
uh how to get there maybe from
here it's been a while since we went to
nipton oh [\h__\h] this was it was this
place I
forgot that was so scary when I first
came
here so
intimidating what are you fighting come
back oh that was an easy
kill you got an automatic one whoa
automatic assault
rifle what wait that's so funny
it's exhausting to make good jokes man I
need a little
break that's been just so funny all this
time what the hell is this pck Brock
flower beautiful
flower flower flower
flower and more flowers where am I
going almost there what am I looking
for
[Music]
oh what am I looking
for we'll find out when we're
there tomorrow's a m stream I'll be
drawing
you may find it very exciting and a
surprise but you know you can probably
assume what I'm going to be
drawing yes
yes I cannot draw likea or
Ena was drawing some am art today cannot
draw like that but I'll try my best to
make it
cute I already drew a little
sketch so
oh hidden Supply cave is that what I
need to find has one of these marks
again oh it's a h Rock
fun so that's a mark for hollow out rock
huh hollow out rock that's also hard to
say got a cute post fig out yeah is
probably good enough I don't know ah ah
wait my chat broke I need to refresh
because it's the
memory o the
[Music]
memories wait
core memory unlocked chat do you
remember
now let me
in let me in I swear to God
all right what do we have here what am I
looking
for I really didn't pay attention oh
it's just a short small room radiation
suit I already have one no need looks
like I'm a space
suit power fist this is G's
weapon what's oh that way is there a way
wait there's no way where's the is there
a way where am
I there's no way this is not what I came
for
Oh I thought that was it cuz it was so
interesting and kind of kind of close to
where I needed to
go all right
if it's not
there it's like around the rock here I
want to go but it's always in the
way nice find
though nice
find there's someone here is that who
I'm looking for I was looking for a
person a knight I suppose they were
talking about some Knights
uh hey are you what I'm looking for
Brotherhood Scout don't take another
step if you value your life for what
purpose do you approach me if you're so
worried about that shouldn't you have
shot me like way earlier you should not
ever let somebody come this close to you
if like you
know like isn't that like kind of late
reaction from you you shouldn't let me
this
close Alo mnar sent me as his
representative he asks if the Bears are
still hunting strange that the Elder
should send an outsider but I suppose he
has his reasons my
observations small town to the south of
here it was cruy attacked its
inhabitants slain nearly to the last
that such an act could occur so far west
is nearly Unthinkable the NCR has forces
in all directions and an outpost scant
miles west from here that they have not
responded to this violence shows either
an unwillingness or inability to
properly defend their borders which is
telling I've collected such musings in
this report please take it to the elders
must be so [\h__\h] lonely to be out here
forever
alone
hello well now you say
hello would have been more polite if you
greeted me from the get-go oh I remember
this isn't this where we passed and we
got attacked and then I attack them back
or maybe it's a different
Road Country
Roads Take me home can I not pick this
to the
place where I
[Music]
belong take me
home I can pick the rain ones
ah that
one road
Xander the route of
Xander okay let's go where first
now well these are all optional except
for this one and this
one uh the correction NCR correction
facility and near camp for l
hope they're all so far how do I get
[Music]
there can I get there from the rep
contest
side
or yeah I mean I know fast travel but
like where which
one maybe that
one
skydiving okay let's go skydiving
cousin who wants to fight oh you
guys you guys are so
weak wait is this oh wait is this the
place where I like got really messed up
once all these memories man it's so
nostalgic uh I want to change weapon to
something
else who are you yeah the Powder
Rangers if it isn't the beautiful cute
power R oh you're throwing some fun
stuff at us again ah hey die die did you
see how quick he died
NCR
money oopsie oh no I accidentally took
everything ew ew ew ew ew ew you're
spamming my inventory with
trash cute cute little airplane oh is
that for skydiving oh that makes
sense right so let me try to
follow my
markers uh
why is it so
Twisted it's not Twisted I'm just
confused
vilified
vilified what I thought the NC likes
me so over
there
vilified V
vilified oh because the powder gang took
it over oh [\h__\h] him I'm going to [\h__\h]
him up
all right
guys we're going to give him a taste of
kfp
yeah oily fatty
chicken with however many
spices your favorite sauce
M only the
best all right
all right hey aim Co not
do shees I forgot I could zoom in
actually oh what a comfortable looking
mattress have I been here before
probably let me
out or are they just that weak now
would be kind of nice uh that way well
that thing over there if they're weak I
would appreciate that but maybe they're
just weak when they're outside here and
then inside of the correctional facility
they're more
tough ooh
XP yeah those were one some of the first
ones so
it's on the back side of the
facility y
b
y f be like yum it yep it oh wait that's
didn't that sound like her though the
last
one
[\h__\h]
[Music]
man
uh
man maybe doctor's pack was not what I
needed stim pack would have been fine
huh I'm looking at the floor I'm looking
at the floor I'm looking at the floor
looking at the
floor oh my dog's going to be so
aggressive oh is it was it fine to use
that
he's he's looking out for us
but you said in the back of it should I
not
enter I don't want to enter oh my
God I don't have to go
inside all right yeah I probably
shouldn't then if it's
[Music]
unnecessary
let's let them Live Another Day let's
look at the bottom doll let's not step
into anything did you guys go inside
stay out stay
away or this will happen to us you know
no it won't we're too strong but you
know oh another 20 XP for
what for
what let me look at the map I'm I'm
losing track again of where am I going
[Music]
uh am I going to this
marker that's like over there
no did they did they go
inside
whatever they'll never
learn they can't go inside H see H
they're here my dog I don't know but
He he'll find his way back to his owner
he's got a good
snoot he has my
scent he knows what I smell like he just
has to imagine the
smell how do I keep on losing sense of
direction okay it's that
way Sno toot Rootin
to
oh what what what oh is it a
tower that was nothing but a scratch
what the what the hell
the what the hell dogle be
careful wait wait wait wait wait wait
here here here oh oh look at this
they got snipers huh but what are they
shooting like
[\h__\h] uh
darts why are they attacking
me wait I'm just here to
talk
H
what I thought you were to is my bear
gone
is was this my
bear what's buff
out look
shind different
people she was fighting with [\h__\h]
pool uh stick
what are you so angry at still they're
dead already Alo like where how
where
[Music]
where I know you can fight with it but
why would you fight with
that I guess I got to go ah D you are
you the bear
I thought it was more like over
there good job surviving what do you
want and don't try anything funny so no
jokes okay I'm such a jokester I'll hold
back I'm I'm on the cool down anyway um
are you a bear you speak truly for it is
unlikely that an outsider would know
both the Elder's name and that
passphrase very well they're so I've
been observing theal facility there in
the distance for some time now feel bad
after having followed some rather
disturbing rumors the facility was run
by the NCR for a time but the prisoners
overcame their guards and now use the
prison as a base from which to conduct
raids oh damn what puzzles me is why
these men have been allowed to run wild
for so long
unchecked why has the NCR not retaken
this place good question give this to
the Elder my observations are all within
I am with the NCR will have a better
idea of what this situation portends I
would like to know the answer to that
actually maybe they just like lost all
their [\h__\h] and like well we didn't
really need this in the first
place
hey I'm done with the funny or maybe
they already told me and I just forgot
but you can't you guys couldn't even
blame me for forgetting anything at this
point right it's just been too
long everything's been too
long spread toin hey do do what's your
name again Rex this is where you got
your brain from you know does your brain
feel like you belong here cuz you don't
you belong to
me for
ever my
dog yes go go yeah attack attack the mol
rats are they mo
ow did you shoot
me this certainly wasn't the bull rat
can you shoot me with the gun I gave you
did she shoot
me
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] can't believe it couldn't have
been anyone else here could it be
certainly not the mole rat certainly not
my
dog all the times you shot
her that is not something I can forgive
I'm allowed to shoot her she's not
allowed to shoot me in the
back back staber more like back shooter
she has it out for me she wants to kill
me she wants to make it look like an
accident probably after I solve all her
Brotherhood problems for her that's when
she will kill
me but only
after what is this fun looking place
oh what the hell
ah no wait I want a
head yay aren't these did I
die is that me or someone
else hey can I get control
back is that the lucky
guy I saw a guy there my lucky guy
appeared and solved all my problems wait
a
second wait a second he was like hidden
in the grass but I think I saw him
that's why it was like doing this weird
thing
again yeah those are pretty strong huh
you guys warned me about them before
they're still strong it
seems still pretty strong got to bring
my tank I mean she's obviously a tank
look at her my tank and my damage dealer
and I'm just
decoration are we
there oh wait by far not
there but should we look inside the
house if there is a way inside in the
first place oh
have I been here
[Music]
before I feel like I've been there
before cuz there's
nothing
interesting
anymore no no maybe
not cuz it was
was it discovered on the map I don't
know I feel like I would remember these
windmills
oh
oh my bad oh
there's something there in the
stone think it was glitched in the stone
it wasn't able to come out wow beautiful
Fallout
things just Fallout
things bu K I'm killing a lot of tiny
flies these days
so they should fear me all of those
Critters I caught donky wonky
again nibbling on an already dead uh
Critter uh cricket no uh you know what I
mean those jumpy jumpy J jumpy Jacks
jumping jack
bugs grasshopper yeah yeah yeah I saw
her like trying to eat something I'm
like what the hell are you trying to eat
again cuz sometimes she just like
accidentally eats like a
fur a a piece of fur right just like
fluffy hair flying around so it's like
sometimes on the ground and then she
sniffs it and then when a cat sniffs
something that she's not supposed to eat
she will like then have it kind of stuck
to her nose and then with her tongue She
like tries to get rid of it but the only
thing she ever achieves is like getting
it deeper and deeper into her mouth and
then I have to like help her and you
know pull it out of her
mouth she so so stupid you have no idea
how many times I've pulled things out of
my cat's mouths
is that a Minefield or anything
here but yeah she was uh eating an
already or trying to eat an already dead
uh jumping jack bug I forgot the word
again
grasshopper now I wonder if she killed
it she probably
did but I took it away from
her I don't know I mean if it's healthy
for humans to eat then it's probably
healthy for her too
but I don't know I'd rather not have
them eat
bugs proteins yeah it' probably be fine
but I always want to be careful that
she's not actually eating like a dead
bee or so
because like isn't there a
danger of the Dead bee still having its
um stinky
tail are you home looking for no where
am
I it's not recognized yet but it's camp
for
Len wrong
direction yeah that always scares
me when they play with any kind of
flying thing got to make sure it's not a
bee but
I uh recently I took like the most
cutest pictures of my cats when they
were sniffing on a bee like this already
like before my Japan trip but it was so
sunny and you know they were playing
with the the cat uh what's it called
again catnip that I happen uh
planted and it was like everything was
blooming and there are bees around and
so the bees were sniffing on the catnip
because the catnip plant has flowers on
it
too and then the cats were just getting
interested into the catnip and then they
saw the bee and they were getting real
close and and and the cats were trying
to sniff the bee and I I I got the
perfect pictures of that moment and they
turned out so beautiful I can take the
best pictures of my cats
outside the light makes them like just
shine so beautifully so aesthetically I
can't find this [\h__\h]
thing when I'm almost
there is that a
person is that a person is that the
bear I think I got
him they're actually outdo cats now uh
smoothie enjoys it way more still than
chunky wonky chunky wonky still gets
kind of freaked out easily out there but
smoothie likes to chill out there so
much and she when I get close to the
door she'll be like meow meow meow meow
meow let me out and I always I I don't
know I really dreamed of making it
possible for them to them if you have no
business with me then
go so I'm just so excited that she wants
to go outside and that she you know has
an interest in it and enjoys being
outside it took a while to get them into
it because the grass scared them theyd
still prefer to not be on the
grass they still like prefer to stay
away from
it but sometimes they're dooming over
the grass a little
bit like Pepito no Pepito is different
Pepito roams around
town yeah
freely Pepito probably lives in a very
safe place I I would hope then I am
sworn to report I've been dividing my
time the camps to the north and south of
here but one belongs to the NCR the
other to a band of slavers known as
Caesar's Legion [\h__\h] Caesar I sure
the NCR would quickly win Caesar salad
not happen that's what I'm going to make
out of you Caesar's Legion going to make
Caesar salad out of you only
occasionally send SK another if I didn't
know better I'd say n enough to push for
a full Victory crunch which seems
strange given the
NC crunch crunch crunch I've recorded my
findings in this report now nothing
compared to a nice Caesar
salad just the one two crispy chicken
burger from Burger King but kfb is
number
one
this
yeah from up here the repeated patterns
are really
obvious he triggered me I don't like
it I don't like it so we talk to all of
them return to alen
magnamar Yi
yipp I'm doing this Quest so brain empty
I'm
sorry but we're making
progress the $2 budget and a Happy Meal
whoa
whoa whoa Gand stop gandal gandal no
gandal
no reference to second season of rings
of
power who gets it who gets it
who you need to you need to watch it
wait is it really G I guess so I mean
it's after they called him Grand Elf
it's pretty obvious I
guess fly you fools
no Gandalf that's not how you how you
supposed to use that phrase no
Gandalf he's got a thing for letting
people fly
huh how many rings do they talk about in
the intro of Lord of the Rings
movie I forgot I should know it by heart
I'm
ashamed 20 okay let me try to do the
math nine for the humans how many did
the elves get
free you's still going to make more
anyways
probably 9 seven free fre yeah they gave
a lot to the uh dwarves I saw that was
probably seven right so nine for the
human seven for the dwarves three for
the elves why did the elves only get
three what the [\h__\h] and one the one
7 + 9 + three 3 + 7 is 10 n okay that
makes 20 yeah I did the map
Yi H how the hell did I get the the
[\h__\h] Elder
again wait okay okay turn to the
right and
then turn to the right wow there we go
local map user hey yo is this a real
waa can't believe
it wait one question
why maybe this will still be talked
about in the show anyway
but why did sa
[Music]
on did
he why did he how do I phras this
question I assume he always just wanted
one for
himself although he's not the one using
it is maybe he did use it at some point
but like why why is why Mak so many
other rings for people you want to like
kill in the end or so or maybe he
thought he would have control over them
huh if they were the
Rings like anybody who has cuz uh one
ring to rule them all so anybody who has
like all these other parties who are
using these Rings will be in the end
controlled by the one who has the one
ring that makes
sense that makes
sense and they all get like dragged into
using them because they're once you wear
them they seem to be doing something
positive but you kind of just getting
brainwashed all 19 supposed to give I
need to Tab out to read the full [\h__\h]
comment God damn it I want to read it
um all 19 Rings were supposed to give to
the elves but they saw through s's buy
well not all of them and then Saron gave
out the other rings to the dwarfs and
humans because because they are more
[Music]
controllable did he originally think he
would not need control over
them could just like kill them with the
having control over elves they were
supposed to be control devices only the
dwarves were particularly resistant and
the dragons destroyed most of the dwarf
Rings dwarfs are particularly resistant
they didn't seem really resistant to be
honest so
far H they seemed very you know like o
shiny thing
ooh only the humans fell to the control
of the Rings and turn into ring RS yeah
yeah yeah I assumed so because because
yeah yeah so um I I I'm I'm remembering
things you know they were making nine
rings for the humans where I was
watching just now and I was like nine
Rings wasn't there exactly nine ring
ravs
Raves so whoa whoa I guess I know what's
going to happen to the humans
o the nasu right that keep on Hunting
froo my
man that's how they became refs oh I I I
I'm excited if we if I'm going to be
able to see the the transformation will
it take a lot of time will it happen
like pretty much instantly will it take
100 years or how long is it going to
[Music]
take they hunted him one time yeah okay
maybe they only did it one
time ring WS ring
WS nine ring raes ra party D became
greedier but never feel the full control
of Sauron like the kings of
men they were greedy for the Rings but
you mean they they like the Rings they
were able to resist the effects of them
more Duran is also making choices on his
own yeah I guess I don't know Duran well
Duran really seems no wa not Duran wait
which one's the King again is the king
the dur Duran or the Sun the Duran I
forgot hey what's up no no not Pig
pocket no no no no have you had any Lu
oh that's why it's confusing you have
something to
discuss yes I did good let's take a
look if I'm reading this right it
appears that the ncr's grip on this
region is nowhere near as firm as I
thought I'll have to review these in
detail but these reports have given me
much to think about DS thank you dwarf
mines are you've become someone solid so
I believe I can share something rather
confidential with you dwarfs are so cool
I was wearing gimly socks
yesterday how come you haven't played
shadow of mortar on stream uh I think
because I was then told that it's a [\h__\h]
[Music]
game yeah I was gifted a lot of uh lot
of ring socks now I'm wearing
them e that was Golem shadow shadow of
Mor wasn't
bad wait did
I let me see
Shadow of
Mordor was that like the strategy
looking
game let me see if I asked for
permission for it sh
Mur no I didn't I probably was planning
on it I requested permissions for it a
long time ago for for the Lord of the
Rings Return to Moria but that was was
uh that just also never
happened shadow of
mortar publisher who's the
publisher I don't see a
publisher super fun action
game when did this come out a while ago
right wab Bros
ooh didn't I just already give up on
asking for permission because wner Bros
might be
iffy I don't know hi
[Music]
smoothie you're
cute that was so neat and maybe one of
bros too
hi I would like you to find the
components we need to fix this Bunker's
air filtration system
I cannot overstate the importance of
this task see Senior Knight Lorenzo for
the details he's the one who brought the
matter to my attention and the only
other person who is aware of it you want
me to fix your air do I look like some
kind of air conditioner technician to
you
what
what super fetch Quest incoming
[Music]
before before I fix someone's air
conditioning why don't you guys fix my
dishwasher how may I assist you wait
there's someone here I
guess I feel like there's a person here
that I need to talk
to who might it
be no
the bottom left Compass is not helpful
when I have two markers that I'm being
shown in a room like
this we have a duty to preserve the past
try to keep Veronica out of trouble with
look this isn't a great time oh what the
hell it's not like we're making any
progress I'm Ipson your hand is so long
is going better than mine is it's like
stretched
out yeah I'm in charge of keeping this
data system up and running but accessing
it is a little uh touch and go at the
[Music]
moment need any help I could use some
assistance sure but I highly doubt you
have the technical background to help us
deal with this virus oh I'm a master
hacker
I can help you with a virus yeah some
pre-war jackass with too much time on
his hands apparently decided to inflict
his misery on those around him it's
scrambling all the terminals here at the
moment luckily we only use this section
for storing historical
data I suppose it couldn't hurt to get
another pair of eyes on this maybe
you'll be able to come up with something
coming at it fresh it's a while the
entire is infected the virus itself is
spread across three terminals the
problem is that it keeps moving
periodically
no we'll have it nailed down in a
terminal or two only to have it jump to
another set of terminals before we
locate the third
no are they at least close to each
other ah I've only had s science no
you'll need to locate it on three
different terminals in this area in one
minute any longer and it'll jump and you
have to start all over loc the virus
would probably be nearly impossible but
the PO B
easier for us normally terminals
infected by the virus just display
gibberish but we found the terminals the
virus moved to had real data pass them
we were able to decrypt the data and
discover that it was just messages from
the virus's rer taunting his victims
when you find well I give it a try
anyway best of luck to
Maxim you're being watched so don't get
any wait did it
start did it start is it these uh ter
criminals are you doing something are
you starting
it hey I skipped the last message I'll
track the virus just jumped find which
terminals it went to this
one is that the virus
does uh I don't know
what how will I know if it's the
virus isolate virus check isolated
isolating
isolating isolation confirmed did I do
it
sir I'll track the virus from over here
bro say
something ah isolation confirmed
loal that that one's weird 10 seconds 10
seconds what about this
one uh what does that mean what does
that mean oh
no
[Music]
wait bro my dog is in the way jumped I
thought we might have had it time let's
do it
again can we do it again the reports say
Mr House's robots are now using Tech
we've never heard of we need to send a
team up there soon I was so
close did you want to try isolating the
the virus hell
yeah all
right I know how to do it
now has he
begun go go the virus just jumped
okay so that means it's not there right
that means it's not
there that means it's not
there
[\h__\h] why are they on the
fire
[Music]
no the far
ones haha suckers Catch Me If You
Can does the time go by when you're in
the computer oh my God yeah I'm not
making this one I was lucky the first
time
bro when they're on the fall ones you're
so
[\h__\h] damn it's jumped I thought we
might have had it let's do it again try
isolating the virus
yeah should I start from one of these
when he says
jumped time stops when you use computers
Theus just Jed I would hope
so find which terminals it went to in
the
way m
m ah
no I didn't find a single one yet okay
found one just one
though did that work or did I have to
wait for the isol Ling
process 10
seconds I was kind of following a
pattern but I forgot
one well
great what a stupid
[Music]
Quest well that didn't kill the sorry
sorry sorry sorry we might have had it
that
time one more time did you want to try
isolating the virus
well if we kill all the
computers then the virus can't travel
between them all right
right I'll shoot the virus
out that's how you fix computers the
virus just jped
oh my God what a waste of time I got to
get
lucky I got to get lucky in a in one run
cuz that's already too much time
wasted oh my God are you for
real are you for
real
what ah sorry my aggression
why did I have my gun out again it's
already over anyway damn it's jumped I
thought we might have had it that time
can I put my dog into my bag or
something did you want to try isolating
the virus yes all
right let's start from
here do it do it the virus just
jumped find it went
too do I have to let him finish his
phrase hope probably
not okay I got
one that would be nice if the others
were
close
no 10 seconds oh my God
oh my
God oh my
God I got one but I'm still missing
one no what about this one please please
please please please please please no
what about this one please please please
please please please please please
please please no it's jumped ah [\h__\h]
this Quest [\h__\h] this Quest what was I
actually looking for
this
one bye your mini game
sucks and I went to the wrong
place who are
you
[\h__\h] especially sucks when you have your
dog with you
uh the bunker takes a little getting
used to doesn't it maintaining the
Machinery around here is
important
Lorenzo you must be the outsider
everyone's buzzing about pleased to meet
you I'm Lorenzo senior Knight and
general handyman around here I like your
name the Elder wants me to retrieve
components to help fix the air
filtration system so now I'm going to
have your death on my conscience too
great my death you think you're the
first person the elders trusted with
this
he sent three of our patrols out looking
for those components and they're all
dead I was the one who supplied the
Elder with the location of possible
sites where we could find the components
so their deaths are my fault and now
it's your turn well don't say you
weren't warned I won't take the blame
when you die horribly but I can tell
you're getting impatient what the items
I'll need to keep the system running are
a differential pressure control I know
this a reverse pulse cleaner and several
hea cartridge filters I know the hea
best for finding the items would be to
search any of the old vaults in the area
no those vaults were usually built much
like these military bunkers even using
the same contractors in their
constructions no don't make me go
another you we have to bre after no the
Hippa filters I think my air thingy has
a hea filter
too anyway no
no
no vault 11
Vault 22 and I don't know which one
would be
here
o o more
radiation o I don't know yeah we're not
doing that
today yeah we're gonna I thought I could
finish nah maybe was too wishful
thinking to finish this whole quest
[Music]
line yeah cuz Vault could be hey I
cleared Vault
22 should be
easy oh is that so but I have to go to
both of them
right the plant one
oh well yeah we finished Veronica
that's
good 22 was the plant one I
see just stream for 30 minutes more oh
don't worry I'll keep on streaming uh to
read super chats but I don't know about
going into the vaults now I
just the other Vault took so
long oh my God
the bodies are still
here
yeah yeah yeah yeah the game drags
itself out it's okay no that's fine I
was planning on playing again next week
so this is good I shall
now uh
save and then I shall leave this game
goodbye I'm happy for today we played
for f 5 hours that's
plenty
yeah vault 87 and Fallout free have fun
with that let's move over to a different
location let's go to my office cuz I'm
dressed like this oh I'm big oh my chair
is
wrong my
chair okay and then I will put on some
bgm oh too small now
[Music]
it's an endless loop I am the
bgm hope you like it hope you like
listening to the same part over and over
and over and over and over and over and
over and over and over again Super Chat
reading I downloaded some bgm which one
was
it I this
one but it's from the reveal same hope
you don't mind I like it another the
reveal it's from
the I use this right when I made the
chart people really liked me making
charts I'm happy to see that it was
received
[Music]
wello let's read super chats everybody
yeah it was not the chart that you guys
expected but it was the chart that you
deserved okay that's somebody know where
I need to read oh I see I see GD says
have to talk I went to NYC okay the the
big one the big
[Music]
one where is
it is
it one ah it was renamed cuz here it
shows us waiting
[Music]
I love
this all right this one's kind of a big
one let's see maybe if we can finish it
then I'm happy Jacob 47
D naan cotton thanks for the pinky good
luck with this first concert waa I hope
it's a fun kick off of a world a yeah
you mean the first cuz that was not the
breaking Dimensions yet but the world
tour I'll be looking forward to seeing
it in December oh let's go I'm looking
forward to seeing you in December
he looking forward to a ton of seeing me
thank you for your
support I'm sure it will be
great Cru than you soon space waterfall
than you soon jacob7 than soon just woke
up after anim my NYC all day yesterday
wter was fantastic sleep talking was hot
you were cute with kobal in the idle
outfits oh you got the you got the
freaking honor to see all of that huh
and do you was so good I want to see how
tomorrow tops it found a cave before the
shoot on the way home cool stuff
yeah people were already so hyped the
ones who the people who went to the
world tour the first one they were like
oh my God it's already so good how is
how was breaking diens going to top that
I don't know if like it topped it I
don't know it was maybe it's different
cuz you know very different lineup of
people
so I would say it's like automatically
more hype just by having more
participants and being an i concert with
a lot of firsttime performers
but yeah World Tour I think exceeded
people's
expectations on that first concert so I
was really happy to hear that positive
feedback thank you Jacob I hope you had
fun and J for the pinky seeing rter at
anime n myc was awesome the first spot
in my head when icho was uh on was wow
so cute and the say second most holy
moly K's moves are so excited and bouncy
of course cuz that song is so cute I
like dancing like
bouncy for these cute songs the whole
set was so fun now it's time for
breaking Dimensions yeah let's go you
must have had an awesome weekend oh my
God can't imagine how much fun that must
have been Nathan cotton than with a red
Super Chat waa a h grip song followed by
pineapple
this poor chicken can only take some oh
wait this is already for the next day oh
this poor chicken can only take so much
happiness at once and hearing the chat
break out into a kfp chant after the
song my pride and my oan fell fans grows
after year after year yeah I was so
happy
[Music]
too hearing the kfp chant like first in
the like pre
concert camera thing and then after me
performing it was H very
emotional yeah I'm so happy people did
that I feel like kfp is such an easy
chance to
do
right it's good that my my fandom but
also like just me like people chant kfp
but they they don't just chant for you
guys they chant for me they chant for
all of us
they could chant K but kfp kind of has
more impact doesn't
[Music]
it it's more like kfp is just cooler to
chant yeah it's like chanting USA you
don't chant America you you chant USA
it's
[Music]
cooler oh yeah the K is me
oh smoothie is back oh and she falls
over oh and she stretches oh good
stretch oh so cute she shows me her
belly she's going back and forth from
side to
[Music]
side you like the
floor so cute I want to touch her belly
but I need to
hold back I can touch her belly all
night a but oh she's so cute well she
got distracted from a
[Music]
fly she came over to me
hi hi
[Music]
she's so cute I picked her
up She's So Soft she doesn't like to be
on my lap but I want her to be my lap
cat all right she's
gone thank you so much
naan I hope you had the time of your
life it surely sounds like
it I'm so glad
that you guys are making nice memories
for your whole
life the funnest times would any of you
guys ever go to like concerts normally
if it wasn't for YouTubers if it wasn't
for whole life cuz I had the same thing
with when I was an idol fan when I was a
hello project fan hello project concerts
were my first concerts
ever yeah you wouldn't home most of you
same for
me and so I went to the hello project
concerts and I'm like oh I now I'm now I
can say I've been to concerts but
they're very different from like what
somebody would expect in
Europe you go to some
frequently oh hardcore punk scene wow
[Music]
okay
occasionally oh I would would really
count like concerts from guests at Anime
conventions wouldn't really count
that I mean like you know proper
concerts where they have their own
venue but yeah I feel like you know it's
making a lot of people who normally
don't go to such events making them have
a great time just like how I experienced
it I I I just I remember when I went to
hell project concerts it was like oh my
god it feels like all these people we
share interest and we're also passionate
about this Idol thing and we all support
these cute
girls we all cheer so hard for them with
our pan lights it's just just so nice to
be part of this
culture and cheer with everybody for the
same thing
[Music]
so I'm so happy that what I experienced
before from the audience side I cannot
experience it the same way anymore for
like myself cuz I'm on the stage but I'm
I'm glad to at least
know kind of what you guys feel
there feel like the vibe is a little bit
different because it's like
mostly at least like for the overseas
concerts mostly foreigners I always like
was the one Foreigner mixed in the sea
of Japanese
people but it was still always so much
fun I just like became one of them one
of us one of
us how the turntables
exactly go white girl go
[Music]
you used to stand out going to Idol
concerts in
Japan hey I hope you get to uh go to a
concert
ASAP
baby yeah overseas contest they do so
have a little bit of a mix of like the
Kay Niki Vibe what what would I would a
k Niki do but the Japanese idol culture
has been flowing over and really showing
itself so it's fun to see how you guys
would naturally react mixed with that
it's a bit different from when it's only
in Japan and mostly Japanese audience
the Japanese audience with neille go
[Music]
like I'll be honest there was a point
breaking Dimensions wasn't so bad with
that but I feel like there was a point
somewhere this summer where it was just
way too much of
that I was like oh my God too much too
much too much oaba
please calm down Su was weirded out I I
can imagine cuz like that's not but how
he wouldn't hear that in
Japan H yeah offy oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
must have been offy it's like every time
there was like an awkward silence after
Applause or something or like when one
uh like a YouTuber was off the stage and
there was a waiting time every time when
you guys weren't sure what to do you
guys would be like
oaba mode activate which is a nice way
to fill awkward silence you know I hate
awkward silence so filling it with
anything is great but it just like was
constantly that I was like oh man just
clap just clap just feel the awkward
silence of
[Music]
clapping oh
man the monkey chance I know that that
that seems very American
[Music]
except for pinea BL with kfp that's good
that's good that we have something to
resort to we got to give people more
Resort something more things to resort
[Music]
to that was really awkward sometimes
what the OAB boonga or not having
Theo but would you rather do just
clap like I feel like I see this a lot
in like other Idol concerts too uh
clapping just ends too fast people clap
for like 3 seconds and call it a day and
then the artist has like an awkward
moment where for example they you know a
song ends and they want to drink before
they start talking and their MC or so so
they try to take the Clapping time for
drinking but then the Clapping ends so
early and then you're stressed out like
oh my God I have to stop drinking
because it's already so [\h__\h] quiet
you can hear
[Music]
crickets and that's just lame when
you're on stage and you're trying to
entertain people and there's [\h__\h]
crickets you want to you want to avoid
that at all
cost in Korean live viewing you did the
same no way
[Music]
huh if only if only all you have to do
is like clap like three more seconds
longer or so or five or 10 10 would be
nice feels nice too to get a long Round
of Applause just feels
[Music]
nice thr your arms up before something
while you drink no no as long as you see
the artist drink you should continue
clapping until she's finished
drinking but well vtuber concerts we
never drink we never take a break to
[Music]
drink maybe it was a solo
concert I just
remember never mind
water
woo what is this the
theater all right let's let's let's read
Super Chat uh so I read the one from
Nathan yeah right and then next one Cru
tashon thank you check monkey dun for
the rest of CH I wanted to send this now
in case I forget after day two tomorrow
love the concert from beginning to end
great job waa I swear you get better
every concert and that pineapple for
performance insert chef's kiss Mah I
can't wait for day wait now you already
got your
kiss I can't wait for day two and I know
you'll nail it again thank you yeah day
one was more Wawa uh but day two also
was plenty of waa but I I was happy to
see like people like Kiana for example
went to specifically day one not because
she knew anything or so not at all she
didn't know what to expect at all but
yeah I I hope that the people I hope kfp
who went to the venue either went both
days or day one and not just day two
there was still Wawa there but the ideal
way would have been go to both days or
go to day
one but Fire and Ice was pretty hype
right yeah I I guess so Fire and Fire
and Ice was
hype I'm glad people reacted like that
[Music]
I did
both B I was hype went to both days went
so
ham that's all I've got to today oh is
it however is it the first you went to
in person because of course it's the
best if the others you may have only
seen
online but I don't know what's the case
for you
day one was PE wow but day two was hype
as [\h__\h] too
yeah I'm glad you enjoyed both I went to
world to day one and day two and face
connect concert what a weekend
crazy you hinted what day you'll have
more performances in I did at the whole
of Summer
oopsie yeah cuz I think for that it was
kind of important to me I don't know I
didn't want to cuz I think the even the
online tickets were kind of expensive so
yeah Miami please next year that would
be so
cool I wonder I feel like it would be
cool if we go to a new city each time
but somehow I feel like they might just
go back to
LA but I really don't know I don't know
but that's the maybe like in my brain my
brain wors at telling me if they're lazy
they'll just go back to LA or not not if
they're lazy that's not really what it's
about but maybe it's just easier to get
venues there and I don't
know and it's probably also like
something they always keep in mind
probably is events like Anime
conventions kind of
like timing it with the Anime
conventions but honestly it was really
hard like I I wanted to do something for
anime NYC but I wouldn't have had any
equipment like streaming equip I would
have had to bring it but I don't think I
would have had like safe internet and
also no time just's no time we were like
from morning till like late at
night you know we were there at the
venue like how could I have done
anything for anim
NYC so you
know this time their program seemed
relatively empty like they had to ask
more Japanese and ID members to do a
program for the anime and YC
stuff cuz most of Ian could not do
anything so I don't know if like tying
it with the events is always the best
[Music]
thing but the booth was a cool promotion
anyway like it had the whole Ian Reco
thing going on the booths are always
nice
[Music]
am I
right the Ian REO line was so long they
want to get the bag at that time you
guys didn't even know yet what it was
going to
be people were still so
[Music]
clueless yeah bag was nice did you
notice in the in the 3D program uh they
gave me I don't know why but I was is
like in charge of holding the bag that
could actually like move and the others
just had it like stuck to their hand you
know what I mean like I had an actual
prop for it and it was like more
movable yeah I was holding the actual
bag
IRL and they were just holding
air so like it moved differently if you
pay attention to it you can tell the
physics so to
say mine had physics I
guess immersion
broken no they just wanted one to like
properly be able to present it and turn
it
[Music]
around but then because they attached it
so weirdly to the
others some were really careless with
moving it I think crony was pretty
careless with moving it and just flinged
it around
[Music]
yeah me with the shopping bag the Gucci
bag all right where was I thank you so
much J Mony you already got your kiss
Alex than take 47 oh another pinky let's
go breaking that meses day one done the
weight and line were R rough oh yeah but
after that it was really fun pineapple
was so hype in person with the crowd
chanting the Ian birds were really cool
together reunion was a cute opening to
the concert very nice experience right
I'm really glad they opened it with myth
it felt
very deep and emotional
and yeah I don't know it just made
sense I'm glad cuz it kind of paints a a
story line a little
bit could have opened with a full member
song You Know like all Ian members up
there but they opened with myth paying
their respects paying the Senpai
[Music]
tax so I appreciate that reunion now
hits different I know right you guys
should listen to our new song too though
make sure to listen to our new
song The Jazzy one on Spotify
Etc yeah watch the uh music video too
give it some views so that management is
happy
The Show Goes
On please
please yeah your favorite group M song
M which one would be my favorite
[Music]
H wow that's hard they're all different
the ones that cie made versus reunion
versus The Show Goes On it's like
they're all so different from each
other but people were praising my
singing you guys were praising my
singing and The Show Goes On thank you
so much for
that it was quite the how to say
melodical uh song Like The Melodies the
singing Melodies were like very woo wo
wo wo woo
you
know like not so
basic so I was like oh oh I think there
was especially one one sound one like
where I was worried about
it you like my opening line thank
you yeah quite
difficult wait I never ah should I try
singing it
should I try singing
it The Show Goes
On is there
instrumental Hol myth is there inst
instrumental up on YouTube yeah there
is let's see if I can sing the other's
Parts definitely not the ending where it
overlaps unless I'm
fast The Show Goes On yeah they gave me
the Divine
Exquisite it it took me a while to
even even when I was singing it I didn't
even catch the
[Music]
reference myth all right lyrics Toco
thank you thank you for uploading lyrics
online lyric
[Music]
websites okay uh uh uh uh uh uh uh I
don't really like the Reverb so much
here uh uh uh just a little bit
[Music]
oh I don't know if I can sing this alone
I'll try one two
[Music]
three the light let's start
and time for Ste show we're jumping with
Jo let's go will the back keep
entertaining hand in
[Music]
hand it's our greatest moment yet they
never forget all
part will go on and that we're here to
stay and the news from Tokyo to
[Music]
broading get the G together we're
alling so right now we're feeling all
right since the day we met we've all
been going strong so
long dancing yeah you bet Ain nothing
going to stop us we're
perfect harmony no matter where we it's
me to be don't you know going to feel
when it's ready to on another
show that
was uh oh yeah instrumental break
my my voice is a little bit
tired a little bit
[Music]
rough okay here we
go to
Cate
anding no there's nothing there from the
Raptors still the eyes contagious
laughter and their biggest smile
hey
he
oh we're slaying like we always do make
no bones about it when I'm with you it's
divine it's
Exquisite on land or and water we've
never been hter it feels so blind we're
friends for All
Time come on listen to the tentacle and
dve with me going to sh better here okay
me keeping ribb while the teamat in the
to but St running we're like a work bar
and I'm going to keep you in my heart
will be
forever uh together me
[Music]
forever Symphony of SPID turning like a
Mery go around
we
on dream another dream
now it's time to change
[Music]
the keep L tonight and we
got St no
wait [\h__\h] where I need backup vocals I
don't know where we are
[Music]
all friends wherever you go new dance
I'm going to follow
no go on and on and
[Music]
end a it's so difficult
did they ever send us a like proper Kar
version of the
[Music]
song like something with backup vo we
usually when we make songs we always
have like a ver version that's
instrumental that gets always
automatically uploaded
too
um damn where is it do we have it and
then there's a the K version the one
that for example for fever night I
always play it in the
[Music]
opening I can't find it I don't know if
it if I have it would be
nicer to sing it that way oh she only
had non- Orchestral Version oh was she
using the instrumental from before when
they put in the real
instruments H the CH for the song was
really nice to love the canes and of
course the HP moving yeah the canes are
something new something fun a little bit
experimental very difficult
but um you know this had to have
something like that right
quite a challenge
though but yeah it would be interesting
to dance with props some more in the
future like chairs mhm dancing spicily
around a
chair I don't know what else
could be
done there's millions of things Bon or
like flowy fat
bricks umbrellas yeah uh I mean I'm a
used umbrella for
violet yeah umbrella pretty basic chil
the pom boms
yeah hydration check very important well
yeah that was not so nice uh I'll try
again some time with backup vocals and
when my voice isn't so tired
but we tried we tried oh yeah I st in my
recommendations right now and I was
watching a video before the stream too I
wanted to uh Mario Party stream collab
on the day when Super Mario Jamber
releases I want to like plan it right
away Reserve myself some
members plan it ahead of time so that we
can play it on release day
[Music]
but I want to make it like I play it
several times anyway but first time just
with four people I know there's like a
mode where you can play with like eight
people or so but I just want to play
normal with four
people but H EU is not four people
I don't know I want to play with
[Music]
crony yeah it's just uh the E people
version is not like it's just some mini
games
right let's continue my God off track
guys back on track
um oh yeah thank you
Jacob Cruz D Man D Jim Tracy thanks for
the red super chat Kiana you were
absolutely amazing all
weekend uh uh pineapple multiple group
songs a takoon MC yeah see like they
always put us together and all topped up
with takam rocking the stage you owned
the stage T it was so incredible to
watch thank
you thank you so much yeah that's quite
a exciting weekend H you only mentioned
breaking Dimensions things cuz I assume
you didn't see the world tour but
including that too is kind of
insane yeah no wonder I've been so busy
huh her doesn't play games though I feel
like she would play Mario party I mean
come on that's just a party game she
won't get around not playing these kind
of games trust
me also hasn't she been participating in
FBS uh collabs she she's been trying out
some
things yeah she's fine she's going to be
all
right it's just like I probably don't
see her playing like Elden ring or
something like that maybe in the future
though cuz like play games that I also
didn't thought I would play are you guys
didn't think I would play
even three four years in I played them
so
nobody would have thought I would play
Fallout in the
[Music]
beginning
yum where was I oh yeah Jim Tracy thank
you m m
MW you're so nice thank you so
much GD Dan space waterful danion
unknown than Super Chat thank you for
the absolutely wonderful concert wow W
you seriously did so incredible with
everything my oi is just way too amazing
you have no idea how proud I am you
truly are the best I love you so much
love you always and forever thank you
thank you so much love you
too thank you soon you didn't get to see
it in person right I hope you get to see
one of these concerts in person one
day are you planning to go to anything
in the
future you got to it's quite an
experience someday someday H I hope so
my Australian oh smoo's back on the
floor stretching are you appealing to
[Music]
me you're So
Soft I know you don't like to be here
held by
but even just your small hug will do
wait you're stuck on
me you
stop let me help you he squeeze pow
squeeze the
[Music]
pow okay there she goes I got a good
squeeze out of her the beans
oh I know thank you so much for
supporting me from Far Far
Away I felt the support no matter how
far Nathan cotton than for the red super
chat wow wow thank you again for such a
wonderful concert you and the rest of
the girls rock the theater loved getting
some ton time and always a fan favorite
pairing of takoni M my heart swells with
pride seeing my oce on stage looking
forward to the tour thank you a I'm
proud to see you guys in the audience
really thank you so
much it's really cool to see people's
reactions when me and cie showed up and
the song
Started
yeah had a good view over everybody's
faces like I literally saw someone fall
over there was like these like two guys
like relatively far in the front who who
kind of vibe very different from
everybody else they look Japanese to
me might be assuming but they looked
like they came all the way from Japan
and they were just vibing so differently
from everybody else they didn't have pen
lights they were just like fist popping
really hard and like oom oom oom they
were enjoying the [\h__\h] out of every song
they were so hyped about every
song they like lost their their shits
every time I I had my eyes on
them and then our song came on and like
one of them got so excited he kind of
fell
[Music]
over but he was having fun so it's all
good it's all good takoni making people
faint
yeah please keep your balance guys
my seat was the pap of the camera so
it's more reserved
a by the pap of the camera
a why would that make him more reserved
usually when people are by the aisle
they like often step out a little bit
which they probably shouldn't because
the cameras want to go through but they
step out a little bit so they have more
space to like dance and stuff I noticed
that was a um a strategy for Idol
concerts in Japan that I went to
the there's like different types of fans
different categories of
fans you were right in the middle good
good view right but yeah there were
different types and the ones who like
did uh who copied the choreography
is when that was their specialty they
often tried to get Aisle seats so that
they could dance along more freely and
at those concerts there was no cameras
going through the aisle so it was really
no issue
I was in the middle in the back it was
actually a great seat very nice TR had
to do that cuz he was too tall
do do
what one on day one I was perfectly
aligned in the crowd shots to be
directly behind the center person while
I was in the front
row behind the center person while you
were in the front row what are you
talking about I'm just assuming you were
in the middle I just stand in the eye
because people behind me wouldn't stand
up
[Music]
oh they wouldn't stand up but
then like especially if you have a
really tall person in front of you you
got to stand up but I guess they were
like
mm I want to
[Music]
sit even during the hype songs like
sitting during the MC's I guess but if
everybody stands I mean yeah it can be
tiring especially if you yeah if you
stand stood outside for like 2 hours in
the waiting line that
sucks I would understand if your feet
are exhausted especially if you also
went to anime NYC right before that got
to take that into consideration I'm sure
everybody was
tired they called the staff to tell me
to sit down what the [\h__\h] did did the
stuff tell you to sit
down cuz you can't tell people to sit
down and a concert there's no rule to
sit down just because they're chairs so
that can't be an expectation of
you that hide
sister okay and then the solution I
guess was hey I don't want to sit down
and then the solution was to just uh
stand by the side
then
[Music]
bro the
hell oh my god well honestly if I were
you know to sit behind you I would also
be like really pissed not at you but
like at the fate of me sitting behind a
really tall person cuz I'm very much not
tall so like in cinemas also movie
theaters like oh my God I got the
jackpot huh sitting behind the tall
person [\h__\h] this
man why why
[Music]
I need a booster seat
man but usually what I do is uh take off
my shoes and sit on my feet cuz that's
how I like to sit anyway that's my
preferred way of sitting
anyway this way I get a boost
too you also wanted the tall guys huh
it's nice that you guys are looking out
for the people around you but what are
you going to do
if you see someone small behind you
you're going to switch seats with them
or try to switch seats with a person
next to you that's nice of you if you do
that I can't help being one 193 holy
[\h__\h]
bro let them sit on my
shoulders how tall is tall no that is
that's that's very [\h__\h] tall don't be
[Music]
tall they one people weren't standing in
the back but in day two everyone was
standing in the back noise but like even
standing
like standing also sucks because I I
like people Sur had a pretty obstructed
view when everybody was
standing but then you want to stand
because it's
[Music]
hype it's difficult
the stage just got to be
higher just got to make a higher stage
why are all the stages so low like by
now wouldn't people who built these kind
of featers and stages figured out
that at the default height of these
stages that they usually are people in
the back have a hard time seeing
[\h__\h] so
like why or big
[Music]
idles why don't we build stages higher
at this
point don't get
it or I
guess the the the chairs have to go up
higher in a like more extreme degree you
know what I mean I
guess you could see even if you were
short oh
okay that's good I guess I feel like I
heard some people say oh I couldn't see
so well but maybe that was World
Tour cuz World Tour was all
[Music]
flat but not all world tour stops will
be like that I inquired about the other
venues there's some really cool venues
yeah like usually I mean you know
usually at conventions you will have to
expect there to be just a normal flat
room cuz it's usually like conference
rooms but some of these venues have
interesting uh venues for our concert
so yeah I hope old short people get to
stand more in the front for World
Tour when there's a flat
[Music]
ground I was in the back most row it was
hard oh I'm sorry but yeah I can't help
it somebody's got to be there in the
back I had to stand sideways
what
what are you saying wait
[Music]
like
this must have been really hard for
you how the [\h__\h] do you do
that then you're on the floor then you
can't see
[Music]
[\h__\h] that really sucks for
you but I hope you on the floor but like
people were holding you up like this on
top of their heads at least if they're
expecting you to go sideways that's the
least they could
do no I just quickly Googled
it what do you mean bad sleeping
position that looks pretty like his
spine is straight as
[\h__\h] he's suspended from the ceiling
like this like a balloon
[Music]
anyway where was I
uh
here thank you chocolate Andia oh my God
500 are you crazy are you
crazy are you
crazy you
okay K you were absolutely amazing at
breaking dimensions and World Tour holy
[\h__\h] I can't stop thinking about how
elegant your was for sleep talking
what are you surprised at that you
should have seen it before I performed
it before in my in my YouTube life every
moment was so precise and I was
completely
mesmerized well I did get more practice
since then it's been a while pineapple
was a pure Vibe and your Fire and Ice
performance with CI shook the whole
venue really was it
shaking was better in person well Sur
yeah the impression is different and
also like cuz if you watch it on YouTube
live there's camera angle
changes but this this
way you just had one one angle one
view I love whole life keep me forever
thank
you I'm so glad you got to see all of
that I'm so happy for
kfp thank
[Music]
you thank you so much you spent so much
money on the concert tickets and then
you're blessing me with this huge Super
Chat are you crazy are you
okay do you need a loan from uh ki's
bank got to help you out or so you got
too
hype understandable thank you so
much I'll be used to repair my
dishwasher Unwritten
D Ultimo MK Ultimo MK I said that
weirdly thank you for the pinkies
[Music]
to think I almost wasn't able to watch
the concert but I'm glad it worked out
in the end because it helped me take my
mind off of a super stressful time at
least for one weekend my o was on fire
again on
stage was she
okay did someone call the
firefighters who's your oia is she
fireproof wait you mean me
oh then she was surely fine let's go
pfk good joke right that was a good joke
that's that was a good joke yeah why
didn't anybody do anything there was a
ooshi on fire an idol on fire on
stage why is nobody like putting her
out why are you guys just standing there
watching it and
cheering oh because it's me oh okay oh I
see I see
everybody thought it was yeah it was
special
[Music]
effects I'm so funny oh my
god oh
[Music]
man and so modest so modest so mindful
s
mirror thank
you for the
support J SW than for the red super chat
oh my God another one this was a great
laa packed weekend wow seeing to thean
take the stage on day one made me so
happy me too I'm glad they chose us for
a unit and pineapple was so fun
especially the come on New York let's go
park I always like to throw in at least
a little bit here and there but most of
asteroid songs are you know so busy it's
hard
to like throw something in there's no
space to throw anything in so I have to
change something
existing I'm so thankful Ian visited EST
ah yeah I'm glad too honestly I would
have preferred if um I could have flown
in from Europe the flight would have
been shorter in that case but I flew
from
[Music]
Japan I I saw suicide s by talk about
this in a clip so I'm just going to talk
about it too now
but you
know like at times when I visited
America in the past I was kind of
intimidated feeling very nervous when
they questioned me so much but this time
I went in
there with so much confidence I had like
a bunch of documents that I didn't end
up showing all I did was show my
passport that had a cool ass American
visa in there
yeah so I showed it I showed it
and they were like oh what are you here
for it was a nice nice lady really
nice and I feel like I don't know I
wonder I wonder if she wouldn't have
seemed so nice like if I didn't have
that I don't know but she was so nice
just by default she was like let here
for and we did a lot of small talk in
between
two and oh yeah she she was wait I feel
like I partially told you about this but
I was like oh
yeah uh that she was asking me if I
travel alone and I was like uh no I'm
not traveling alone but the other girls
like we're trying to stay like separate
you know we don't want to be grouped up
she's like why and I'm like well you
know I told you I'm here for you know a
performance as my Visa
States so you know we want to stay
like on the down low yeah you heard the
double
kill nice you don't recall new tangent
oh
really
interesting maybe it was a member stand
I don't
know yeah she was like oh my what no no
you don't have to worry about that
there's I'm like no there's some weird
people there out there you know you know
um we know want to you know be
recognized or anything and she's like oh
don't that just nothing to worry about
here this is a safe safe City very safe
she was like
really what's the word trying to trying
to paint the city in a really good light
really good image but she just doesn't
get it yeah she she didn't get
[Music]
it and I was like no
we really got to try to not be seen or
recognized so we going to try to stay
separate yeah she like no I don't see a
problem at all
like but she was still so
[Music]
nice she was so
nice and yeah the moment like I showed
my my Visa and said I'm here to perform
she was like oh all good she was just
like curiously asking asking questions
but like in a nice way not in a I'm
interrogating you
way
yeah yeah yeah
yeah but you know what was like funny to
me so because I was in Japan at the time
when you get a visa for America
something like that you have to also go
to the Embassy so if I was in Austria I
would have gone to the American Embassy
in Austria but I was in Japan so I had
to go to the American Embassy in Japan
and yeah we went with quite a few of
us quite a lot of us went there at once
and I
actually uh I went to the Austrian
Embassy in Japan like literally just
like very shortly before that so I had
just visited the ausan embassy was
wasn't even the first time um you know
so I had that fresh in my mind and you
know Austrian Embassy is you know cozy
small it's
secure it has fake walls like fake uh
fence like stone walls you know and you
have to ring the bell to get
in but American Embassy holy
[\h__\h] that thing was
huge they had like a whole back check
and
everything and they were really picky
about where to stand where we would
stand and there were like several like
checks yeah they don't mess around and
they like property was like 10 times the
size of the Austrian
Embassy yeah but then you know we had an
appointment there we didn't just go on
any random day on any random time no
they told told us to come at a very
specific time and day so that they could
handle all of us because we were quite a
big
group but then we get we get
[Music]
there and we went for all the security
check and
everything and then we start standing in
line and there's like several like
checks we have to go through uh like
first they check the documents that we
brought if it's all there and then they
check uh I don't know another thing a
then yeah then it's like an interview
they said I was wondering what what what
are they going to ask I so nervous about
it and then after that they would like
give you the Visa but like each step we
had to line up
for
and like we waited for ages because we
were like so I swear we were so many
people cuz there were like all the staff
that we would be flying in to Japan as
well you know we brought our own staff
to build
everything
so we were so many people and they had
one person out to handle all of us they
had like
10 10 Windows where 10 people could be
seated at a time working through all of
us but no it was one one person and it
was so slow
it took so much time was so boring
standing in line that I ended up like
chitchatting with the staff like oh so
what are you going to be in charge of
huh and they tell me tell me about it
and blah blah blah and then we're like
wondering hey these these guys knew that
we were going to show up and we see like
we see people uh cuz there's like you
know this like you can imagine like a
closed wall with Windows and those
speakers that you speak through you can
barely hear what the person on the other
side is saying right can you imagine so
through the window we could see that
there's an office behind there and
there's like
20 American Staff people running around
none of them bother to take a seat and
help us
out and this is not the Japanese way
this seems to be the American way so all
the Japanese staff around me they were
like hm
H they are really Carefree aren't they
it's just American style and I'm like
yeah seems like
[Music]
it but slowly after like it took so long
after a while after an hour or so of
waiting they finally added a few more
staffers but then then I was so confused
and kind of felt like
like so stupid uh at the last step they
were basically
like giving everybody there no no we
didn't get our passport back no no no no
they were just telling us sorry you're
actually not getting your Visa today
we're not
ready
bro we all stood here for hours and you
guys gave us this this this specific day
and time which was already I'm going to
tell you was already cutting it close so
I was getting really nervous anyway it's
like we're going to America soon oh
[\h__\h] now you're telling
us you're not ready what do you mean
you're not ready
what yeah I took a couple more days and
then we got our
visas
yeah but I was just impressed by the the
hugeness it was so big the place was so
big it was so serious the the atmosphere
was very different from the Austrian
[Music]
Embassy visit and another
time what was there reason oh they were
just not ready they were just not
finished that's
it so you really wonder what did we what
did we go there
for well at least they got to check our
documents a little bit and I had to
retake my um like picture in the
passport picture machine
P not quite
P oh
yeah think I remember uh I was sitting
in the P machine because I had to retake
my picture right not everybody had to do
it though um other pictures were fine
apparently I had to redo it and it was
like counting down 1 2 3 and at the time
when the shudder went off I heard a
suicide Senpai outside of the machine
making some joke or noise or something
that made me laugh I'm like hey Senpai
no please
[Music]
stop messed up one
picture she my wife
I think she did that on
purpose or did she who
knows
trolling should have taken the picture
to G with her in
there yeah what a
prankster yeah anyway I was just I I
just wanted to like make the Americans
among you feel cool for having a cool
[Music]
Embassy are you proud do you feel
cool they didn't even have a back check
at aan
Embassy there was no back
[Music]
check you don't feel cool no you know
you're cool
sounds inefficient yeah a little
[Music]
bit yeah I guess ostra is not
so not so
special not important enough to well
anyway we're neutral
okay we're
neutral we're chill
[Music]
we don't attack we're neutral we're
cool we don't need
to you
know I I guess like I don't know I'm
making a point where that's why people
don't need to see us as a
threat be you're just little guys yeah
we're just little guys
[Music]
Little Mountain guys no attack just
protect yeah ourselves ourselves just
ourselves don't don't don't ruin my
point H I'll shall continue change the
topic and continue so that you don't
ruin my point thank you so much J SW
[Music]
wow uh but I Jes SS to the red super
chat this year I had to work while the
concert was live oh no fortunately
though I was able to watch every single
one of your performances K it live did
you sneak out every time I see you on
stage I feel like you are always meant
to be up
there I love you and all KP loves you
thank you so much no thank you I hope
you'll get more lucky for the next con
concerts in the
future when when it comes to that
working at kfp somebody's got to work
the kfp
shift I honestly there should be
national
International
closure if the potential is on
stage or we should turn all of the kfps
into live viewing
[Music]
venues sorry you had to work now because
this year you had to work next year you
won't have to I'm sure of
it Moon d f the red super chat I had an
absolute blast at the concerts you did
amazing pineapple was extremely hyped in
the concert hall and was personal
favorite of mine H you worked so hard
for these moments super proud to call my
call my Kam oi yay please treat yourself
with cat colors when you can thank you
it took a while but I'm I'm finally
there but yeah pineapple I I had a
feeling it would be a good choice it
wasn't you know performed yet I feel
like Kima would have been really hyped
too but Chima already had it's time to
shine at Fest uh pineapple didn't have
such time to shine yet and I do think
it's a a good life song pineapple you
can scream pineapple so many times right
and then sing along with one two one two
[Applause]
three offy I don't count offy as much
but yeah I guess
so but when it comes to a whole life
only concert you
know which wasn't a
convention yeah so I think it was a good
choice was was one of the more singal
longy songs that I can offer Chima too
it has a
[Music]
Kim which is pretty easy to sing along
too I guess
I would
say my upcoming
[Music]
one might be a little bit more
difficult here and there you guys can
join in
but I might have to make a
guide no you you can't make anything out
of
that no you can't make anything out of
that I purposefully hummed it like so
that's not
nothing left
out like Tunes in
between Coro was so difficult guys I'm
telling you now you better appreciate it
not not every part but like it's it was
difficult to dance with other like you
know back
dancers I thought it would
be kind of
easy but it was like a in between was
some moments okay and some moments were
[Music]
difficult no it's not by
Kiana because she wouldn't have been
like a able to like be there and teach
me with uh like extra
dancers cuz we needed to like she
wouldn't even have been able to really
make uh a coral you know she has her
twin but that's just two people like
getting what getting like you know cuz
we needed basically we
needed at the practice we needed uh
four ideally we needed four the four
back ansers and then one person to stand
in for me to teach
me but yeah it was even for them it was
so hard when they were creating the Coro
it was so hard for them to get
everybody uh in a short amount of time
together for the practices and for
creating the coral so like like all of
the work in progress Coro videos that
they sent me were like either missing
one person or missing two people people
or it was only half of the Coro or so on
so it was like hard to even get an image
of how this is going to look like when
it's all being put together it was all
pretty rushed and
yeah
difficult but yeah you will see I think
it turned out
wonderfully twin is like stunt double no
no she has an actual
twin and they're both
dancers h
H what do you mean what I meant with
stand in I mean like when somebody
teaches me the
Coro uh and the Coro has like the
dancers I also need some body like the
teacher iide like in in the case of when
I learned the Coro the teacher was
standing in for one of the dancers but
at the same time trying to teach
me uh so when we were trying to do the
whole dance like okay we learned some
Coro Let's Dance the song play the
music then either she will dance my part
next to me so I can follow along with
her or she will focus on just being the
D the backup dancer the back dancer but
then I don't have like a reference when
I just learned one part of the cor you
know yeah so they got to do two
things because we didn't have enough
dancers on duty
at the time of the practice so that was
difficult
H
really yours is missing too how how how
how does this happen hoizer is nice
for finding all these super chats but I
guess I always end up missing
something let me check
oopsy wrong
one no no no
[Music]
no I hope there's not many more there
was a miffin right and
hululu anyone
else I guess I didn't put the number
that might have been it
ohulu oh yeah you didn't that's why I
you know I can't there were a few people
who just sent pinky with no number or
even a red I can't like run after every
person you
[Music]
know did you add a number later or
so in a different super
chat but I can still do it for you since
I have to do another one for myin
anyway wait there's another Hulu Super
Chat
though ah okay then okay you later added
it in the smaller Super Chat I must have
looked over over it cuz generally I look
only at the pinkies when I do when I uh
sign the Super Chat uh the the
Polaroids my eyes focus on the pinks so
it's easy for me to miss the you know
the yellow one that you
send I'm
sorry and then myin what happened
my where is it oh here ah wait
miffin I made one for miffin through
GD I made
one I
remember it
what I remember that GD like requested
some for others you
know maybe I accidentally didn't save
it man
damn
it damn it okay yeah you requested
several
ones so
mindful okay so mein and Honolulu Okay
maybe somebody can remind me on Twitter
please afterwards not not today I I
won't be doing them anymore today I
think or tomorrow
very
de I don't know if I'm going to finish
these super chats today
either wait no I won't stop at midnight
don't worry I I I have time I cooked
already I can eat my remains from
yesterday but I don't know if I can
still can do all of them I'm not even
halfway
through I should just schedule a Super
Chat reading stream oh my
God but I I feel like I I
am oh my this smovie doing over there
she's in my line of VI but I was going
to say I I feel like I'm I'm admitting
defeats if I do a super chat reading
stream you know what I mean just feels
like failure to
me there's a state of play in 10 minutes
oh like
PlayStation Nintendo
[Music]
Direct I don't want to be
defeated and that means probably do does
dendo have a stream up to watch it let
me see
dendo is he going
to react to it like sometimes he reacts
to like PlayStation stuff
too but he puts up his reservation so
last minute I don't see one up
now also I feel like he n even even when
it's a weird time he will still do it
maybe he does have a twitch that he
sometimes uses and I never like I don't
follow the twitch cuz I don't really
have an
account so I miss whatever he does on
Twitch I
think he mentioned it you're in his
[\h__\h]
Discord
you're That's So Random you don't even
speak ter German you're in in some in my
oie's
Discord why
that's so funny to me so he is doing a
reaction you guys remember sometimes you
guys complain about gorilla gorilla but
look at him in 10 minutes and he doesn't
even have a reservation up or is it on
Twitch M
Mia we have your work account though I
don't even know how to log into
it why aren't you in your wasi Discord
it had a tail SP in the state of play I
don't think so that might have been the
Nintendo
Direct but I didn't regret that one if
you mean the most recent Nintendo Direct
one I didn't regret it
because remaster of a game I already
played is
[Music]
mid oh the DLC oh was that in the state
of play Oh for T of Ariz
that was special that's something I
would have regretted
yeah
[Music]
eyebrows I'm being defeated by super
chats
yeah smoothie is like think very
purposefully
sitting in the
hallway looking like a
loaf trying to remind me of her
existence she's so cute
guys she wants me to stop she's so cute
recently she hasn't been eating very
much I always give her like small
portions that I know she should be able
to
eat but she doesn't finish them recently
but she still eats so maybe she like uh
has been eating too many Kibbles every
time before I give her the um dinner or
breakfast and that's why she's already
full or
so oh besides she seems very fine is she
still waking you up early uh she
tries but honestly she quits pretty soon
after so that I can sleep again it's not
been disrupting me as much but I've been
sleeping really badly
anyway because it it just feels like so
painful and uncomfortable at the moment
like I don't know why
[Music]
no keep on waking up to TW Twist and
Turn just can't get comfortable I really
need that freaking new
bed they never wrote to me so I need to
figure out how to contact them I already
looked something up and found some some
mattresses that are possibly being used
by this
hotel but it's kind of difficult to
pinpoint because they have several
locations and stuff and it seems to be
different depending on
that a
yeah I got a hotel pillow on
Amazon but even Hotel pillows can be
like different I've had shitty hotel
pillows so I wouldn't just go for any
hotel pillow on
[Music]
Amazon I couldn't just go to a room and
look at the tag no I'm sure they have
the information but they definitely made
it more complicated by telling me that
the housekeeping will contact
me
yeah certain departments and hotels they
just you will you will give something to
another department and they will just
like not follow up yeah I know that from
my own
experience did they even give you a
number no no they just took my email
address and we're like oh we're going to
contact you I should have gotten like
theirs as well because usually like
online you can only find like very
generic like Customer Center email
addresses but when you ask for one there
at the spot then maybe they give you
like a front office email address or
something like that you know something
where you're more certain
to get an answer from the like more
more more directly
[Music]
anyway no I didn't send them an email
yet I've been too occupied my brain
trying
to do all kinds of things I really need
to get an assistant but I don't know
where how how does one get an assistant
a personal
assistant do I have to make a contract
how do I draft the contract I don't know
any of these things
let me
Google so maybe like a company
that like a you know like a cleaning
company that brings cleaners to your
homes maybe the same thing for personal
[Music]
assistant how do I find
one on
Fiverr ask cover
nah it's my I need that like privately
and if anything they would only you're
joining it too oh [\h__\h] off you don't
understand
[Music]
German why are you guys joining my oi
Discord makes no
[Music]
sense time to personal assistant I
wish no don't go
[Music]
there oh
man my head hurts a little
bit wait I was like let me where was I
at was I
at where was I was I in the middle of
Nai Super Chat and then I got I saw the
hululu thing in the
chat let me read na send two pinkies
this weekend was Unforgettable I got to
cheer for you and watch you perform
three days in a row let's [\h__\h] go
with the world to Unbreaking Dimensions
you rocked those stages CH from M did I
not give him
[Music]
one
m I also spent a lot of time hanging out
with kfp and other fan bases and it was
so fun thank you again K because I would
never experience all this without you
I've gone from one end of this country
to the other for you and I do it again
in a heartbeat because you're worth it
my beloved cute hardworking BP Kami oi I
love you thank you so
much wait so one and are you from
the west
coast thank you for traveling so far
from me thank I appreciate it I'm so
glad you had a great memory great
experience but the middle Oh you mean
you went from the middle to the west and
also to the
East noise you're getting to be a
tourist s seeing from coast to coast the
coasts are nice anyway there's
water Chicago oh you you live in Chicago
oh that sounds
cool but
[Music]
Chicago I say that sounds cool but
Chicago Chicago
considered a good
[Music]
City the bean I saw a bean in in New
York
[Music]
too Chicago is
okay it's dangerous yeah
right but I mean people's talked [\h__\h]
about New York and New York was
[Music]
fine look the r musical was in
Chicago that's so
Random why do I think of skateboarding
when I think of Chicago makes no sense
right think of different
[Music]
places yeah I'm thinking of Tony Hawk
but I don't think Tony Hawk Pro SK was
in Chicago
at
[Music]
all I want to play
that it's got skate parks for
[Music]
sure oh it did have one level in
Chicago oh my God my memory didn't fail
me let's [\h__\h]
go she
go Tony
[Music]
Hawk
ah yeah it looks familiar I
think yeah I think that looks
Familia it's been so
[Music]
long it's on Steam Sale wait what is it
the one that I played when I was a child
wild like is it
the that they put it on
[Music]
Steam did they Port It
remake anyway I got distracted again
[\h__\h] man where was I where's my Super
Chat where is it where is it where did
it go where did it go where did it go
here thank you so much MW mwah mwah wait
May PS maybe next year you guys can have
the end concert somewhere in
between I I was I was kind of like
saying that too like next we meet in the
middle right but I I don't know how the
chances are on that I'm advocating for
it
but musi maybe I don't know really not
my choice but I'm advocating for
it let's let's hope so but I I think
it's just like when you look at
demographics of where most of our
viewers are I think most of them are on
the west
coast and so I was like well I mean no
matter where you're going to do it in
America you're going to feel fill the
venue and uh people will
travel anyway I think a lot of people
who went to the New York concert were
not from New York right right traveled
from West Coast or wherever
[Music]
middle it doesn't matter in the end
but
well well
well it doesn't matter that it doesn't
matter don't say it and the company
caters exclusively the West Coast I cat
more to the east
[Music]
C and now they had a concert there the
second concert was on the East Coast so
now you can't even you can't even argue
that before maybe oh the loaf has melted
into a
puddle oh the loaf has
puddled oh my God
[Music]
they threw a bone you guys got threee
days of content come on exactly yeah you
got World Tour
too is there wait what's the other
America that's not on the west coast
right the other America stop it's not in
the west
coast for world or is it what city was
that again Atlanta that's East Coast too
see I mean now you can't say anything
there's no single west coast for the
world tour World Tour is biased for East
Coast I think they totally could have
gone to West Coast it's more like a
timing
thing probably of oh chunky wony it's
more a timing thing of what conventions
happened to line up during
that but
anyway yeah America is America you guys
can't complain as long as Europe gets
ignored
forever with no events being held
there you can't
[Music]
complain not our fault that your country
is so
[Music]
big
no it's huge
[Music]
like I mean in the American tour would
be cool
sometime like North America Tour where
several spots just like the world tour
but like with
America feel free to include
Canada of course South as well why the
hell not when we're already there
although I don't know if like it's easy
[Music]
to like get a venue there
Studio RO with the pinky this this is
one of the many reasons you are my oi is
don't tend to streaming now by the way
speaking of OI it's past midnight
[Music]
just curious not that I want to see
it just
curious watch along of a watch
along do we need perms for no it's just
the same like as with Nintendo Direct as
long as I don't show it on stream it's
usually fine redirect that' be so funny
he'd have to acknowledge me well no I
don't see him streaming on on YouTube at
[Music]
least no no
no he's on [\h__\h]
[Music]
twitch n [\h__\h]
that
nah anyway every time you you were on
stage you radiated such intense
infectious joy and energy oh my god do
you guys have some rata away for Studio
Rob so or some rad
eggs
yeah also I've been waiting all year for
Life fire
nice yeah that was a a a rare chance
like there was a high chance I guess we
could have performed it in our
anniversary H but our theme was like you
know the switcher Rose
so although like it could have been
performed by like one of the other girls
imagine imagine like a amam fire and
ice I don't know I feel like that
wouldn't fit anybody but
us imagine
though would that be
interesting
H maybe better to keep it Takami
[Music]
T reflect was so good right I really
enjoyed it had a great time being
dramatic I love this song so much and I
really really love singing
it I I put my everything into that you
know hope you like the way I sang
it and danced so
dramatically went hard right
[Music]
100 more songs together that'll be
difficult Callie is ambitious but she's
like doing a lot of projects on her own
and with other people so I don't think
she can do 100 more with
[Music]
me anyway Thank You Studio
R please feel free to take some rways
out of my bag to feel better
uh Prince of Denmark things red Super
Chat it was a great concert there were
moments when I felt emotional I cannot
fully explain why or what it was uh what
I was feeling in those moments I do not
I do know that I wish for every fan to
have that feeling that moment is a
special feeling that you can't describe
or explain thank you so much where it's
been so long already were there
emotional
moments I feel like
maybe ah like
or so can get you kind of our bright
parade can kind of get you emotional
with those instruments and the fact that
like at the
end I feel like that can get you
emotional but generally we didn't make
it
very like tear uh
[Music]
baiting connect the world too yeah
connect the world
too h
[Music]
I'm glad you feel like that thank you so
much prins of D I'm so glad you had a
good time
though thank you for going there in
person to support me well I'm assuming
you went in person right it sounds like
it
did thank
you hope to have you again
sometime Jacob 47 thanks for the pinky I
feel like by now I should give you a
kiss Jacob with the final day of
breaking di mentions down it has been a
blast fire and nice reprise with a life
audience was cool and the taco MC was
sweet overall you did great this weekend
and it was so nice to be able to see it
on in person Bravo thank
you I was only online oh oh well done
even more special that you felt it
through the
screen I'm
glad thank you for watching from home
you weren't even like surrounded by all
these people that like adds to the
atmosphere and still you felt like that
I'm glad it grabbed you like
that
wonderful I hope you can see it in
person
sometime I want all of you to get that
experience at least
[Music]
once anyway
I just had a popup
from narissa on
Steam of a game she's started playing
now
interesting is she streaming after like
[Music]
soon no not Roblox no not not BG
foro it's going to have a m later oh
tell
us Final
Fantasy
seven surpris her in the members room go
to her members stre and be like oh so
did you have fun playing Final Fantasy 7
uh
[Music]
earlier be like what the
[\h__\h] Secret
she does have a brain
rot I I I I don't know probably remake I
don't know don't have to be so
specific why my face
[Music]
hurts thank you Jacob 47 I'm going to
give you a kiss now I feel like you've
only sent pinkies but you've sent so
many so here's a
kiss Thank you Sharon so much for
watching every single one of these
content
concerns
ah I hope that the after
effects you know cuz there's like I feel
like you can either be on a really big
high but then after the high you get
like the after depression and after
after convention and after concert
depression hope it wasn't too
rough I'm going to go now my my my mouth
and my face like everything hurts my jaw
hurts
going to go now stop
[Music]
talking enjoy
she I'm not going to watch it if it's on
Twitch he might reupload it probably on
YouTube I don't know I'm not going to
watch it not going to go out of my way
and open Twitch no nope see that's where
I draw the line cuz it's so annoying to
get on Twitch [\h__\h] ads but also like
when I've been watching Lord of no uh
rings of power on
Amazon they they didn't have this before
but they started adding [\h__\h] ads not
just in the beginning but like in the
middle of
it at least they're placed like at the
end of a scene or so but like what the
[\h__\h] is going on they added
ads why are yeah what is the point why
are these Services adding ads now I'm
paying for my
subscription you didn't have ads before
and now you start adding ads then give
me a [\h__\h] discount on my subscription
or
else $3 extra per month or what that's
ridiculous bro can I put on ad block on
my Smart
TV probably doesn't
[Music]
work maybe maybe that probably wouldn't
work cuz it's like probably embed
[Music]
embedded
interesting sounds like it would be
difficult you know I I would understand
the argument that they only put ads on
rings of power specifically and not any
other Amazon like shows on Amazon Prime
just because race of power
is
dying cuz they're not getting their
budget back then I would be like oh
that's funny but no they just like seems
like it's a general thing now it's
ridiculous everything adds ads now you
were supposed to not have ads I I read
this somewhere on Twitter too somebody
was like being angry like what is the
[\h__\h] point you guys were supposed to
not have ads that's why we all left the
TVs and went on onto these online
subscribe
criptions and now y'all all have ads
it's [\h__\h]
annoying
bro yeah it's just like cable all over
again I'd rather go back to TV okay no
not I wouldn't go that far yet because
they still have way more
ads way more interruptions and way
longer and you can't like
choose so specifically what you want to
watch right they they have a program and
you have to watch whatever's on
but yeah at least in the services you
could still choose but I
[Music]
mean like there's nothing you can do
about it there's nothing we can do about
it they decided to do that when we are
all we're
all
helpless to the whims of Rich CEOs
[Music]
H may it be TV like broadcasting
companies whatsoever or [\h__\h]
[Music]
Twitter I'm a CEO yeah and you are bound
to my whims as
well and my whim now is to end my stream
[Music]
no
booo like for
real now $40 for streaming service what
the hell are you
paying
no I'm I'm the only streaming service
you
[Music]
need no okay my face really hurts I
can't feel my face when I'm with you
[Music]
yeah this week did you guys see the
schedule uh I'm going to do memb only
tomorrow and wait let me let me put up
the schedule before I
go is it this one yeah and then we have
oh my God I can't believe it's already
Legend of Zilla time I can't believe it
I can't [\h__\h] believe it going to
choose going to do two two streams this
week and Team Fortress it's like I'm I'm
was putting up the schedule of like Val
games marathon and I'm like all of these
are
Shooters what the hell I don't really
like any of
these um but I was like I don't know
well I don't want to completely miss out
on it I want to do something with
am and Team Fortress was at a really
good time for me like 10
p.m. it's the beginning of the marathon
I was like well I guess I'll join down
because because it's at a good time for
me Marathon goes on pretty long and uh
no Gmod is like 4:00 a.m. for
me I'd rather just Join one of the early
things
[Music]
yeah but didn't we do Gary M isn't that
the same thing that we did with am
before I mean she's probably going to do
it differently I don't know
but I I I uh was part of one of those
before it was
okay but you guys were very excited I
didn't expect that at all you guys are
very excited about me playing Team
Fortress so I guess I'm happy with my
choice uh I don't know why you guys are
so excited but
okay apparently it's pretty like dorky
and you can just like have fun and mess
around so that's good to know uh and
there's some beginner friendly classes
apparently I've been told
pyro is beginner friendly and it just
kind of matches with me being fire so
I'm probably going to do that cuz I feel
like medic is
too like I want to have fun and
shoot rather than focusing on healing
people because I don't I don't think I I
I like to heal in MMO RPGs but I don't
like to heal in FPS games that seems
like a lot of pressure I don't know what
the hell I'm
doing I don't want people to have to
rely on me on
that so I'll try pyro whatever that does
like I'm I'm fire okay sounds
[Music]
good medic is perfect for but I don't
want to like that's boring boring I
don't want to be
healing I've
changed what has become of
me I was always the heel
[\h__\h] what has become of me
was happily
healing it was it was the only thing for
me what's wrong with me my warrior blood
is
calling Tashi no we're not there yet
we're not there yet I want to be
DD it's not a tank right the pirate is
not tanking
[Music]
right no good
good good
good all right all right uh well I'm
sorry I didn't finish it again sorry
maybe I will do a super chat reading
stream next week I
might I
might
uh no
all right in I'm going to stream later
apparently so watch
her
understand is she live now she's already
oh okay let's go I'm going to I'm going
to I'm going to move you
forcefully I'm going to move to my
supposed loading
screen because we use a different
loading screen today anyway bye bye and
thank you so much for watching I love
you
guys tomorrow members
[Music]
oh