foreign
[Music]
thank you
assistant
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
one second please
go on bed
[Music]
foreign
please give my phone five minutes
uh
give it some time just just a little bit
in the meantime have you guys seen my
tweet before the Stream
I uploaded a clip of me and singing in
karaoke
[Music]
I screamed
yeah of course it was good who else
would that be
who else would I have seen I caught
about with me nobody
nobody nobody but good
[Laughter]
I'll tell you about that later because
now gonna end Ina both publicly
announced that they are
in Japan
um who won the girls I was thinking
thank you I want nobody nobody
nobody nobody
[Music]
what what about my hairline
my hair looks perfectly fine
yeah
so what do you mean you can't see me of
course you can't see of course you can't
see me what I'm just not moving but
that's right currently currently that's
on purpose oh I didn't tweet let me
tweet
what am I doing
oh and this may be this this I'll show
you this one too
stream started already
[Music]
foreign
and now we copy paste the stream link
not the comment link yeah okay
there we go it has been tweeted
us
bus Frozen yeah I'm gonna unfreeze in a
moment
um
before that let me show you this
and so this is the thing that I
mentioned in my schedule the extra
appearance
[Music]
it happens
what time was it let me see
uh Japanese Standard Time 9 00 P.M
tomorrow 9pm jst which
I don't know what time that is in like
estpsd
yeah but uh me and Sonic and eofi are
going to be revealing new Idol outfits
wow that are gonna be used for the
fourth Fest and I think you guys should
watch it because you know we talk about
we will talk about all kinds of things
new information and this is just one
part of it but you know I think you
should check it out oh
I mean
there's a reason why me and
your feet are there okay obviously so uh
please
come
yeah yeah yeah it's a it's not a um a
recorded video it's a stream a live
stream so I'll be there uh to chatting
with these ladies
and
um yeah exciting
well that might play a part too
yeah it's a stream a live stream
um
[Music]
yeah I'll get up for this but it's
at 1pm I think no wait yeah one somebody
said 1pm my time or no
at 9pm GST
I think maybe 1pm my time but I have to
be there earlier
for
checking everything
yeah like two hours earlier two hours
earlier what
setting up going through the program
Etc all right
does this and then later in the day
we'll have a members only stream that I
have not decided yet what to do we will
see
later on
hmm oh yeah no that's fine like today I
also got up
before 11 so we're good
let me check my phone how many percent
is that
what the [\h__\h] no
matter how much percentage
I don't understand iPhones here ah wow
16 all right here we go
here we go
three two one whoa foreign
there we go and now we're gonna play
more fire
and wait I got tea and honey and water
and snacks and orange juice I got
everything I got my phone for tangents
um
I am so ready let's go oh I got the DLC
so this will be the first time of me
opening
the game
with the DLC
download the content
[Music]
it'll guard time
maybe I know how it will be revealed to
us but uh
so I just bought it so I'm now assuming
it's part of the game and I don't have
to do anything who knows
what do you mean can I only choose one
character
no way no way
date
I can't even get all of the DLC
they switch at random
what
Kiki must be found I get all three but
chicken must be fun Lots on Earth
oh DLC
I already bought it why are you leading
me there what's the kind of show
oh just bringing me to the to the
purchase screen I already bought it
no mine then
I thought maybe it would like show me
what exactly are the contents okay
okay
we continue we are going to chapter six
I think we just finished chapter five I
think
uh
[Music]
foreign
yes you are confusing me oh look at that
okay expansion pass bonus one received
some items okay
uh I think there was something I wanted
to do
I was like the next time when I play
again what was that
let me pick up some items
11.
[Music]
game eight nine one you got it oh yeah
and even day one oh I saw like barely
anyone oh what is this
barely anyone got into the
lottery for like you you tried but
barely anyone really successfully uh
okay
no one successfully entered almost no
one
[Music]
um
I was
kind of sad to see how many of you guys
said oh not me nope nope no didn't get
anything
[Music]
but as I said I mean
you can still watch it it's just not at
the venue but
remember when we last watched it
together
it was a blast to watch it
online maybe there will be some watch
alongs from like day two members who do
it on the day one or so and the other
way around so maybe you can watch it
with some some member
maybe I'll do a day to watch along who
knows
um
streaming tickets way too expensive what
you have to watch my day
it's really
good it's gonna be good
you have to watch it it's worth it
[Music]
yeah day two and no what am I not on day
one
I don't think I'm on day two
uh
I'm on day one right
I thought you were a day too
now I'm on the decal stage and on day
one which
is yeah yeah
I was never told that fareen had a held
a second ring let us collect Alfred and
journey to the shrine
um
cute
oh
I like her casual dress
um anyway I think I'm gonna do another
poll
oh no maybe no Paul at all because we
already did a poll but I feel like I
I might switch to English dub
because
[Music]
you know with the Japanese dub
I was trying to speak English on top of
it but that's
I don't know in the end it's kind of
like all defeating the purpose and in
the end
it might just be smarter to go with the
English dub
um
yeah it also rests by voice I don't have
to like voice act literally everything
only the parts that are
um not voice acted by the actual voice
actors
so
is that okay
[Music]
I'm
okay
okay but then I have to leave the game
once right
um
oh can I do it here
things
okay photo
[Music]
foreign
version
[Music]
um I could also muted and voiced it
myself no thank you
yeah well we'll see how if it like if if
I don't like the E and up I will end up
going back to the
uh Japanese dub
foreign
um
I'll do this lining okay
maybe we'll like switch back and forth
[Music]
so text English
Spanish there's European and then
there's Latin America Spanish and then
there's European English and then
there's American English
and apparently there's European French
wait what and then Italian is just
normal
what what does this mean
what
all the other ones I kind of get but why
is there French European oh but there's
no American French anywhere or like
Canadian sorry Canadian I guess
okay well
I will go with the uh this one and then
this one this one yeah okay
you must
it's the Canadian for
eign
yeah I already don't like that but oh
well
Fire Emblem engage
somehow it's better in Japanese oh well
that's celine's what
oh my God I have to like get used to all
the new voices now
yeah it will sound weird to me
um
I feel like especially cute characters
work better in Japanese
and mature ones are okay in English
final of any voice I think as long as
it's good yeah well let's talk to her
Celine hmm what
no
just buy that she had a really no voice
what the [\h__\h] no
[Music]
why are they so sad what about you
oh
[Music]
um hmm
we
must hear a little bit more right
we must hear so uh is there anything I
was supposed to do or can I move on
I feel like there was something
but I'm not sure
try to sleep so I can hear them
oh
you do support in the menu ah
[Music]
maybe this one
put View support relationships
ah
it's about that time president Clan
I'm all set president Fram
in that case I call this meeting of the
Divine Dragon fan club to order okay not
so bad
I can't I think this is decent whoa
yeah
[Music]
our first and only agenda item is how to
broaden the fan club's reach
should become a YouTuber who's her voice
actor she should consider becoming a
vehicular
president Clan you have the floor
yeah
actually she should become a YouTuber
I mean before she hits of YouTuber
I voiced her okay Chris Pratt okay
please join the whole live English
please I think we should do something
splashy to drum up people's excitement
hmm
I'm not sure about his voice if it fits
him
the only question is what I have an idea
[Music]
how about we spread our message by
making pamphlets
[Music]
I'm listening
see everyone's heard of the Divine
Dragon but only a few know the person
behind the title
[Music]
Clan sounds 10 years old at any
I'm not sure how old is he supposed to
be is there an official age you and me
we could tell the world what the Divine
one is really like
yeah yeah I'm picking up what you're
putting down but I I even if there's
like one or two voices that are not to
my liking
um
in total then I think I'll still keep
this because it's just a better flow and
I have to read less and
money is
[Music]
foreign
um it will be easier on my phone you
have to consider this will be such a
long play for when they have so many
dialogues
[Music]
how about this we slap the Divine ones
beautiful face on the cover entitle it
ah someone who said I can always just do
Japanese voices and not read but then
whenever you know I saw some people be
like oh but I watched Chihuahua stream
without watching them as like a podcast
Radio kind of thing and I guess so I
guess a lot of people do that so for
those who don't always look at the
screen and still wanna kind of hear
what's going on
um yeah you know
[Music]
so maybe this is the best way for now
yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm one of those
there you go
I'm like that it's not a hotel
the Divine Dragon uh close and personal
boom
inside we have an interview with every
juicy detail folks could possibly want
to know
I'm getting used to her voice I think
it's good favorite foods favorite
weapons hair care routine shoe size the
raw uncut story I really want to know
who the voice actor is
from English voice actor
Ram not Fatal Frame oh
Lisa Raymond
[Music]
no
she voiced
from uh that tamago Market or whatever
foreign
[Music]
would you like to join whole life
English
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's let's not um dig too deep because
maybe that will ruin her chances in case
she does apply
all right next up
you don't like it
I love it that's way less stiff and
formal than what I had in mind
[Music]
yeah no offense I I don't think it
matches for him just the sort of
brilliant idea I'd expect from you madam
president
I couldn't have gotten there without
your suggestion Mr President
um
all right let's get working on this
pamphlet so we can hand it out all over
town
uh wait all over town but it's not like
terrible
[Laughter]
ah okay okay
what is she gonna sound like
[Music]
let's listen in
it's here phew that ought to be enough
running for today
[Music]
looks like you had a good work out there
FDA
oh it's you what are you doing here
[Music]
I thought you might want these when you
were finished
what's that you've got in the jar
homemade pickles they should really help
you recover after a tough workout
[Music]
here try one
sure why not thank you
not a bad voice
it's opened
[Music]
oh this isn't bad it's got just the
right amount of tartness that I like
I'm glad I got it right
[Applause]
General like body type everything
[Music]
so I was careful to keep them delicious
but healthy
[Music]
sounds dependable
really he did that just for me no she
needs to look at like a Sunday a cute
voice like I know
like from uh
Louise
Louise from they don't know I don't know
yep and that's not all
I also slept with them under my pillow
kind of like how hands take care of
their eggs
no kidding
weirdly Charming you're a good one clan
you can keep the whole jar if you ever
want more just let me know
[Music]
oh I will thanks for brightening up my
day
foreign
[Music]
a lot of Clans everyone wants to talk of
Clan
oh wait um
it's not available okay
and
[Music]
okay now they all just want to talk with
Clan I'm kind of curious oh wait this
one's oh
no it does not look
[Music]
um
hey I wanna like listen to Chloe as well
say I don't really
like
all these voices
um
I thought that I don't like the voice
itself it just doesn't don't think it
fits
uh for now just for now
[Music]
yeah for the sake of my voice go to room
to replay oh
um wait a second somebody said spawns
too
uh referend Bond
oh of Alfred and sigurd
well for guys I'm not that worried can't
do much I visited the Divine Dragon lots
of times over the years we're
practically family that's fine a
persistent presence can form bonds
deeper even than blood
they are to be cherished
can't do much wrong
[Music]
level up
okay good for you guys anything else
no okay uh I will not re-watch anything
I'm just gonna go move on now
[Music]
yeah they sound okay
did you go to the ring room
um no
[Music]
whoa whoa
New Paths paralogue as you progress for
the story special chapters called
parallels will appear on the world map
parallels are optional but they unlock
unique benefits you might even meet new
Alice
is that something to do with the DLC or
no
I really should Forge some boundaries
SPS precious wanderings
eh
okay okay
tell me how to do it please do I have to
bring in the thumbnail for that
ah DLC will be prologues but not this
one
ah
there's a separate map for DLC okay cool
a whole map
all right so uh go to the ring chamber
where is the ring chamber
maybe up here
close to my sleepy room no there's only
my sleeping room in here
fast travel
okay but wait maybe some dialogue is
happening
it's gonna make me suffer
oh
if I sleep now somebody is gonna say hi
let me try
oh
who can it be
finally made it a guy
oh good morning
I kind of turned around looking for this
place
that's all right
I was hoping for a girl though
okay
um
ring Tamer there it is
big ass shoulders man he can like carry
kids on his shoulders oh
I don't know so what do we do here
ringtone is a space to interact with
emblems and their Rings you can inherit
skills from emblems here using bone
fragments you can create Bond rings
or combine and strengthen existing lens
you can also deepen bonds with emblems
by polishing the tarnish of combat
of the Rings oh ah cleaning game like
with Pokemon
clean your own ring
shower your ring
okay okay
let me polish them first
Ah that's need some cleaning
uh huh
have Kiana oh doesn't matter who doesn't
well yeah I will polish it make it nice
and shiny
Kyle
can I turn it around oh
you're very thorough
[Laughter]
much better wow
nice and shiny polish firmly what do you
mean polish firmly
and no need to focus there
hmm
I want to
no need to focus there okay okay let me
end it
nice
I'll let me try this one
uh who should I do that one with
who was wait who was carrying her
Alfred no
what Celine Celine
um
please be thorough please be thorough
okay
not quite
an odd tactic
wait her voice is okay
an odd tactic what I'm just cleaning the
ring normally like anyone else would do
your cleaning skills are impressive
thank you
I used to be a ring cleaner for a lot of
the Rings in fact yeah yeah
nice
complete
I guess we'll do this one why not
um for Alfred
because one had thank you this ring is
filthy don't you think
this ring is filthy don't you
it looks camouflaggy
we're doing things a bit
is that not a waste of time huh
he's not happy about me cleaning the
ring what's his problem
is that not a waste of time no obviously
apparently it's not
I appreciate your upkeep of the Ring
well now you do okay
what the hell
and that's my impression now too okay uh
what do we do green boundaries you can
create Bond rings using Bond fragments
Bond Rings increase stats and allow
units to earn SP though not the same
extent as emblem rings do
oh
so I should just create them to give to
anyone who doesn't have uh an emblem
ring
everybody again
[Music]
okay which one should I do does it
matter
bufferings for everyone
gonna ring and you get a ring
[Music]
come on tonight
there will be no singles
in our game create one create then oh my
God it's really God damn I I have a
thousand only okay I'll make one
foreign
looks really basic it's bronze Quincy is
that like a super old fire love
character
strifeless one that seems pretty shitty
I think I don't know though oh
yeah
actually fun
oh
some bronze maybe well she's actually
cute
two plus one
what
is this season no you're gonna
who's that baby
a bronze
never see damn art looks so old
okay I wanna do another one I had luck
with silica let's do another one
can I get overlap
I hope not but
uh
f plus one
give me silver one is it the hearts get
the good ones
number s is one of the better ones
do a temple I can't I only have like 600
bone fragments now
I can combine them
welcome into Highway oh awesome
a zombie space
wasn't the old other one exactly the
same just with a different character
oh
hey people so strength was one ah that
sounds good
let's do that yo
okay
Chris and a bronze for oh never see
again all right duplicating what the
hell
already duplicating
ah never bronze oh Levin scene
has got quite an interesting outfit
yeah I'll combine them then yeah yeah
I'm seeing Oh I like that artwork though
that style art style
[Music]
next up we have I saw
myself crying outside B plus one lap
plus one oh now hold on
not the worst one out there and I got no
bond fragments left so let's melt Bond
rings
oh oh no I'll need more Bond fragments
in order to do that too
a thousand and free of kaida B is kinda
a
and a hundred and two of Navarre C Is
Never B
free of crispy and a thousand is Chris a
not a hotel so anything that's B three
times of those and a thousand Bond
fragments
okay so now I need more Bond fragments
and what's inherit skills allies can
acquire certain skills from fire from
emblems using inherent skills edges Auto
filled the word Fire Emblem
you can acquire certain skills from
emblems using inherent skills
inheriting skills requires a certain
Bond level as well as skill points
earned SP by bad selling with synced
emblems and equipped Bond rings [\h__\h]
inherited skills using the inventory
menu
can't benefit from the same skill twice
so try to avoid avoid overlapping okay I
don't know what you're saying but we
have to try it out I guess let's say I I
click on kiwala
oh
I have 743 SP in total for everyone or
just for Kiana
I could
get
any of those top free
everyone has their own amount of SP
don't use yet
don't waste your spinner okay
look at her she's hot
okay then I think we did what we had to
do here now hold on
thank you
and with that I will now go to the world
map
oh but I didn't assign the
Rings this is also an emblem rings
how do I assign the
huh
okay uh
uh this one
he no he would want one of the magic
ones that I got
right
match here magic and speed maybe for you
maybe you wanna have the maybe yeah and
then
for her I don't know magic too or what
does a Healer need
um
[Music]
luck and Magic
she needs magic death and rest killing
his end I don't have any of those
she doesn't even happens
that's not a stat in this game
[Music]
oh yeah oh I have another magic one okay
you get that one and then for you uh uh
you're and maybe you need speed Maybe
your speed plus one I feel like that
would make sense
you
strength plus one sure
why not
you have to javelin
how about
Dex maybe decks
maybe decks
no
oh let's just hit rate more crits oh
that's for Archer oh
that's accuracy
[Music]
but then what do I give her
speed unlock
that's a good one though
for him
give him the strength one
for me
oh I already have one right so I can't
have a bond ring and an emblem ring at
the same time right
can I
no okay okay then everyone I accept Luis
everyone except Lewis has a ring
um
you can have either the decks plus one
or the death plus one
I would say death
nice well that worked out fine
for now
okay
[Music]
can't use other fingers yeah can only
wear one ring at a time apparently
and should I go down here on the small
island first before going upwards you
know what I will or I keep that for off
screen
but that would mean I would do it
probably like use three four chapters
later because I'm gonna do a couple
today
[Music]
I will be a little bit late
go now okay okay this one I'll do now
then
save the residence of a peaceful Village
from the corrupt Attack Base Class level
four
on Nation level one what okay
begin chapter let's go
oh new staff
oh yeah do you think she needs a new
staff
uh Marketplace
[Music]
you're right thanks for reminding me he
was free
where is the okay
maybe it's not
this shop
[Music]
I can shop I guess
this one like the basic one or
yeah
25 heels plus free
[Music]
and vulneris
I love that urgent but she has friends
he has one
I'll get you one how much money do I
have okay Plenty
um I've only two three two three
[Music]
three two
three two okay
[Music]
oh
so it's like a Side Story or like a side
quest
budding Talent a parallelog our first
parallel these pills ought to clear up
the problem let me know if the pain
persists okay
it's a doctor
he's like take your meds and you're
looking cheaper today I told you that
cold would be gone before you note
[Music]
like his way of speaking
father isn't it time you took a break
look I made you some tea
[Music]
look I made you something
[Laughter]
thank you John I like it you didn't burn
yourself or anything preparing it I hope
you worry too much I'm old enough to
manage a simple pot of tea I assure you
are you sure about that really really
not even that I can handle a simple pot
of tea sometimes it makes me happy to
see you growing up so fine
speaking up I should pour me something
let's see if I can handle it wish me
luck guys
I have a big famous jug
again
[Music]
here we go there's honey in there and
I'm going in oh
it's getting foggy up in here
um
the smell of Christmas and winter
Santa Claus
you gotta mix the tea so that the honey
Blends in nicely with the rest of the
liquid
oh like a pro wow
what's going on out there
not green tea no no I like green tea but
most of the time when I'm in Austria I
drink like fruit tea most of the time
and if my throat is [\h__\h] and I drink
fruit tea which is usually like uh well
herbs
yeah in Japan mostly it's usually like
some kind of black tea or green tea
um because I can't seem to find much
uh fruit tea
in Japan like in tea bags doesn't seem
so popular
doctor you have to help us monsters
around the attack and people are getting
hurt
nice voice acting
but the devil all those pieces this will
get ugly
jump go and hide I'll take care of
bringing people to the clinic this way
everyone if you're on her then assisting
someone who's injured must pull together
wow it's so dramatic suddenly and we
come to the rest
of the original of course father told me
to hide but how can I I have to do my
part too wait is he like an uh a unit
that I can get no way
foreign
looks a little bit too special to be an
NPC but a little bit too unspecial to be
a unit
[Music]
the ball okay
somewhere in between no
[Music]
English boys
let's show her at the clinic
oh come on keep your wits about you
everyone I'll Pat you up once the crisis
has passed
you can't stand idle with the corrupted
on the loose let's save those villagers
okay that's okay that's acceptable
are you all right get to safety and
leave the corrupted to us
but there's still a few left you didn't
make it out in time
we'll do everything in our power to save
as many of them as we can
goodbyes maybe she also wants to join
whole life English I love you for it if
you do you're the Last Hope at this
point
I don't want to think too much this is
my first fight it's like my warm-up
today
won't be that difficult right
[Music]
there are so many rooms
it's up to me to treat them all
oh is he like a Healer I'm here to help
if we split up we can treat everyone or
they're both healers John
uh no I'm on heart not on normal
look at the title of the stream I can't
stay hidden away when there are so many
who need my help
after all father am I not your son you
taught me that a doctor does whatever is
needed
wow it's like so much over his age
respect my lessons have sunk in I see
very wealthy come and give me a hand you
taught your son well
it's difficult to save everyone but easy
to Kill All Enemies with some casualties
on villager's side
okay
love the new hairstylist thank you
father am I not your son
well actually no you were adopted
if you see a conversation in icon on a
unit move to an adjacent position and
select talk proactively speaking with
such units is a great way to recruit
more allies
sometimes these units will only speak to
specific people oh if
hum
not in this case hopefully
all right do I have to be rushing
there's like these villagers but for now
the healers will heal them right
whenever they take damage but I don't
know how much I have to rush
[Music]
wait I just realized we're only
seven
not a big group
[Music]
Sammy Russian can't take too long to get
up there
should I then maybe send
one person up first
maybe the horsey what if he can't talk
to the them anyway
[Music]
oh yeah I could have exchanged and I
thought I would go in with my full group
because that's what we did last time oh
well
main character must suck okay
well then what's the best maybe just
walk straight up here and the right ones
they can just try to come at me if they
wanna
[Music]
I'm ready
we could try to search some turtles
oh that actually might be a good first
move that's a lot of damage
I go far left
and
oh he does 10 damage to me though
goodbye engage
[Music]
more damage
weapon is Advantage oh but it looks good
oh should I went into the house I held
it I'll let someone someone else go and
I'll stay here and I'll wait
and I leave to serve and you can go here
and visit don't know how much you still
get out of this but
[Music]
ton
up now yeah maybe I'll even warp with
her
because this is like one Pap only all
right I can't get too many people
through here
for now we wait
with you I am ready to serve and I'll
bring you here
whatever you say
go here and you can
um
wait so chain guard I've been trying to
observe and it always feels like chain
guard is never available after I use it
once this is only once per battle or is
there some way of recharging it or
something
oh
is that how I get to the units
ah she needs to be at full HP that's
what it was
okay
I'll do it now then does that give me oh
that doesn't give her exp when she does
it because I feel like it did it
before
where too
[Music]
that ax person is Gonna Come for her
not if I stand here
it does okay
so for peace I feel
wanna
engage everyone engage
and one
I don't know if that's stupid but you
know otherwise it will take a while for
all of us to get through there I feel
like
um
[Music]
maybe I'll walk here or you guys thought
I can only hit one person though right
maybe I'll go here
that still means I'm a target for like
two of them
[Music]
facials
strike in the bush
[Music]
but that doesn't kill this one this one
this one will survive with one HP
maybe how about here
now
it doesn't reach the horse even though
it could kill him if I'm closer to him
[Music]
we'll try it we can always like reverse
time if it doesn't work out
[Music]
yeah
okay
okay let's work Ragnarok
[Music]
we have to learn by doing
foreign
[Music]
now let's see if she survived oh oh he
goes for
oh no he goes firstly
[Music]
we ain't just now it's kind of worked
out
oh
I feel like it wasn't too bad
um because right now she looks kind of
mature in her current form
[Music]
okay
oh okay
[Music]
so all my units survived the first turn
isn't that beautiful now
since it doesn't look like hey Will
there be reinforcements oh yeah are we
done once we talk to them and reach them
mmm
if it would be over then why are there
charging points here
[Music]
feel this Dane for tokus that looks why
would I
[Music]
um yeah it was a whiplash yeah I was
thinking of using override here but I'm
just wondering if I might need it later
if there is reinforcement
is it my turn but I'm not sure if there
will be
[Music]
a happy second birthday Leo are you two
years old
yet you can already ride super jets I'm
so proud of you one of the five oh my
God are you making like a rainbow or
what
[Music]
only got two turns oh yeah right I'm
already engaged wait why have him why I
engaged myself
[Music]
I don't even remember doing that oh
I don't know
[Music]
okay
well then
raise your sword
[Music]
I saw level eight wow Noble level eight
nice I can feel my muscles crying with
joy
is that what you how do you how you
describe sore muscles
[Music]
nice level up oh I didn't look at the
stats was it good good stat growth nice
nice
power too lands perfect
so I will oh walk over here
and thank you Leo yeah you are making a
rainbow huh thank you
I have a problem nobody can walk through
until that dude is killed
she could kill him
Kiara actually could not
um and I think that's she will have to
kill him because Celine would have to
kill him because even if Kiara kills him
then they're all still in the way
so um
but then what about this dude you know
maybe I can
still get him somehow oh wait you know
what I'll do I'll move
oh this is dangerous for her
[Music]
I'll move
here is am I in the bush or not no no I
guess I'm not because it says ground
but if I go here and that might be a
target for this dude also later on
[Music]
um
that might still be kind of in the way
I'm not sure
[Music]
Echo gives you two attacks all
yeah do I have to stand right in front
of them no right because I'm I use Magic
oh yeah oh
[Music]
he would do a damage to me but at the
same time I will kill him first so we're
good right
[Music]
I would kill him first
and 100 percent
[Music]
nice
yeah
and now
we Echo
so him okay wow this is really useful in
this situation
but oh wow
[Music]
okay because I wonder if they can all
pass by but she can get pretty far
so we'll walk all the way over here
and then wait
and then oh with you
I can heal Celine
but only if I stand right there
he can't get very far
[Music]
you can't get very far uh he could oh he
could kill this dude from this side
that works well
91 percent
eye opening
[Music]
eye opening indeed
oh [\h__\h]
okay uh in that case
[Music]
The Archers have to be so close
and what's how do I see the range again
from wherever she stands
like without always having to push this
[Music]
is that L honestly like I don't see [\h__\h]
like this just looks like nothing to me
this doesn't tell me anything
[Music]
so what if I
um attack him from here
I'll just leave her down here for now
can't get anyone everyone to the top
anyway and then I finish it with the
Mage and then with the Healer I go up
the Celine
I think this should be a Kill
in total
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm sounds like a plan well I hope it is
a kill let's see oh yes it is
[Music]
for the Divine Dragon I am fire and
blending it
okay
pretty clean stage now
here we go get some uh heel going
Fortune
so you
know
oh not if I can help it oh
yeah
oh oh oh oh
wait I don't have to kill all of them
though right
oh
I thought it ended here
all of them oh
[Music]
but if they all come up there anyway
then I won't go for them I'll just wait
here to protect them I'll just stand
here although some of them might go up
this way right I'll just put one person
here and then I'll just stop everyone
okay okay so you better run honestly
like [\h__\h]
We have basically arrived so
everywhere
[Music]
I will put him now if he can't go that
far then might be worth putting him here
protects that sign
[Music]
worth using a vulneri maybe yeah
oh happy Luna New Year to you too
foreign
[Music]
so can't do it with him
okay next
let's see how far we can get everyone
oh oh I didn't see you here
[Music]
should I engage
huh
even if I engage it doesn't kill him
[Music]
John John will heal you
look at his hatred oh 22 percent
oh
well
not a huddle
engage
emblem engage
can always retract I guess two spots to
recharge right there
okay that kills
his brothers
it's like I did an Elden ring with that
one NPC anime thingy
that everyone struggled with
[Music]
only go here unfortunately
wait let's let's go with other people
power blooms in me yeah you can go here
um
[Music]
yeah okay
chain guarding again
at least for one
now I am kind of scared about my archers
latching behind
but she seems safe here
[Music]
I did feel very smug about that
especially after re-watching it today
other house
and
other houses so far
they don't even seem interested in it
oh he's not engaged anymore sad
uh okay let me try to remember the
Hotel
uh
uh I have a sword fighter but he's on a
not on a flying horse uh with swords
okay Lance do I have any one of the
lands close by oh yes you but
three
great you would be so close
[\h__\h]
and for Magic
it says punch but like
who was a
Poncho or isn't she
the price that works well against all
the other things
moving closer to block and tank yeah
yeah I will move him closer anyway but
just unfortunate that he can't reach
[Music]
oh should I put her in there it's kind
of dangerous danger zone over there
though
hey maybe I'll just move the Healer
there too and chain link again and then
that will take some of the heat off of
her
[Music]
Plus for the avoidance yeah
like
could work out but
[Music]
now the problem is if I try to hit that
do it now he'll be able to hit back
again
but with 54 54 is that already like
considering the fact that I'm in a
ticket or is that still without that
[Music]
it is considers my Buffs now
or I go here and I One Shot that horse
but then I'm not in the picket but then
I can bring my healer maybe into the
thicket and chain link
[Music]
and oh we might be able to deal with
that horsey uh a little bit with the
dude up there
[Music]
yeah
I think it's a good investment
I'll do it
[Music]
no no
not happy with that but oh well
okay
[Music]
that horsey guy will go for
eign
[Music]
now
here and oh we could punch
or we can chain guard
think I'll chain guard
[Music]
Mage probably gonna go for Louie
okay that's fine with me I think
Jacob
[Music]
what did I do it oh yes okay
and now how do we even
when there's uh the villagers in the way
I can't
okay they're in the way
oh
[Music]
look at that what you would shoot that
oh
no he only has 52 percent
foreign
[Music]
apparently he might be able to get
healed or so too
I don't know what or should I put him
here to charge
and then he can come for him if he wants
should we charge him
[Music]
yeah I think I'll charge him
okay
now by the way let me tell you attention
basically oh
OH
Close Call on on my last two days
good and Ina started
rhyming and
[Music]
um I didn't really I think I could meet
Ina because
nah I wasn't sure if that was gonna work
out
okay
yeah but so on my last day since my
flight was at 10 pm I was like okay okay
I'm gonna make the most out of it and I
asked if gouda wants to like hang a
little bit so
around noon time I went to her place and
I was like hi good morning
and then
uh yeah I asked her if there's anything
she wants to do or if anything if
there's anything she was like planning
already
move away
what the hell
why are you so stupid what am I supposed
to do
and if we should like buy some stuff
like like
I know a kitchen stuff or so
um
that engage and like walk over there I
don't know
so at first I first brought her to a
Daiso yeah that was fascinating for her
very overwhelming I think but not as
overwhelming as the like electricity
kind of store that we went to because
holy [\h__\h]
Japanese stories even to me they're
overwhelming to me as a someone who is
used to it and and can read Japanese
even to me it's overwhelming how do I
is there any way for me to move these
people
[Music]
yeah let's just say it's a some some
store like yeah one of those we could
come in some store like that they were
like so so many things but we looked for
some stuff for her in that store and in
the Daiso got some stuff
um
oh
and but I want to attack oh wow
it's not safe here you should be running
I can't I'm the local doctor's son I
won't leave until I've helped you you
could stay and help me out I'm fine with
that you've got a lot of Heartbreak Kid
your age
I feel so good yeah we went through
everything like oh there's this and then
isn't that good I was fascinated by
everything being so cute I knew it was
all right let's join forces and save
those villagers I knew she would like it
I love Daiso they got everything I
really appreciate the help my name's
John now come on there's work to do
and then I originally we wanted to go to
thank you to a restaurant for lunch but
then I said you know what we're gonna
cook karaoke anyway right and when I
said in the beginning hey do you want to
go karaoke with me today she was like Oh
I thought you'd never ask
I thought you would enjoy some karaoke
and we can have some food there too so
basically we had like a lunch there late
really late lunch
um and we're singing songs and it was
your first time at a Japanese cuddle cat
and so that was nice but we had some
troubles finding the right songs that we
wanted with the stupid system
the stupid machine
and also goodness
Japanese reading skills are not perfect
so she had to check uh like I would
always give her my phone with some no
magic lyrics of whatever she was singing
and she would read it off the phone most
of the time
if it was a Japanese song at least
oh
yeah yeah
but we were enjoying our time they were
wishing so many songs like we didn't
have a time limit so we just went on and
on and on I took a photo of our set list
of all the songs that we sang
and then at the end where it was like uh
okay maybe we should go now because we
have a chance to meet Ina
and now we can have dinner together
[Music]
and then yeah after that week I have to
go to the airport so
so
the last song I chose I was like
[Music]
and I didn't tell her and I put in
secretly
the one that we covered before
and she's like
[Music]
that's but not least we sang I could
have all together but we sang many songs
together but I uploaded the snippet of
us singing ikotoba on Twitter if you
wanna listen in um
um
yeah and then we basically rushed
rushed to the
uh to where Ina what
I just opened my Twitter
and that was the video
[Music]
yeah we rushed to that place and then
you know was there and I was like
I gave her that little Sketchbook that I
was talking about was the model car or
whatever it was called
so cute
and then I realized holy [\h__\h] we really
don't have that much time huh
so we quickly went to some restaurant
and I had my suitcases
yeah and then we realized oh [\h__\h]
I might have to leave you guys before
we're even done eating
but
um
we had a good dinner and
yeah it was nice being together a little
group of Ina Konami and and jenma
no
oh that's why I was saying some Fergie
songs actually we've sang them together
partially in a karaoke but then at the
red Parts you know good uh good I
couldn't do those because she didn't
know the songs that well and then I
I displayed my perfect figure wraps in
two different songs and she was like
whoa whoa whoa whoa she was hella
impressed with my
[\h__\h] your rapping skills
[Music]
pretty proud of them
oh it's somewhere in the within the
dinner time
there was something that
either Ina or Jenna said
I think it was Ina actually
no
I think it was something Jenna said and
then oh yeah I ditched her really good I
ditched her in front of everyone I said
well clearly you don't own an air fryer
I don't know why even what it was about
but in that moment I was like this is
the perfect timing this is the actual
perfect timing to use this to roast her
and then
I said it and everyone was like oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
she really did not own an air fryer
[Music]
motivated my trap card yeah
so it was just me spending some time
with Gouda
for a day and then in the end I still
managed to meet Ina a little bit um but
I had so much fun
yeah and she also told me totally
appreciated it I I just you know I was
kind of sad that I had to leave her
because I only had one day with her but
um I'll be back
to show her more and I told her to not
do all the exciting things without me
you gotta wait for me
um but at the same time I told her she
should do some exciting things
well I'm gone because gonna make use of
that time and enjoy her time in Japan
[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah
oh it's fun I
have a good time with her
and a lot of different songs she sang
Some Like City pop and what they were
saying
missing
[Music]
oh yeah some Disney songs
and then I put in some Avril Lavigne
that we sang together
um
oh yeah I just played some Paramore and
some twice and then we sang but I like
that together and she's saying can't you
catch me
um and we sang some more Disney songs
together now we sang Bad Apple together
and and
oh I sang seesaw
yeah yeah this and that this and that
oh she actually sang that
um new radwimps song from that movie
that I saw this song
she didn't see the movie but she knew
the song and she sang it really well
oh [\h__\h] I just saw that like two days
ago
[Music]
I got me excited hmm
good at rendition of that song
the song is everywhere really
I only knew it for the movie
it's coming out in April overseas for
real for real deals
oh that's exciting
[Music]
oh man I got so many tags right now on
Discord but not nothing about this
tangent just because I because Jenna is
back from her little break I don't know
if it was really even a real break but I
was like leaving giving her some space
and now I've bombarded her with some
questions and now I got all my answers
yeah so have a good day with her
and I am looking forward to spending
more time with them soon I'll be back
soon and for now it's just good and Inna
and maybe Carrie I can do something with
Callie I guess
yes I'll be back please wait for me
don't have too much fun without me
you know so good uh some special things
too because it was nice to show Ahmed
things for the first time like you know
it's interesting to see someone
experiencing these things for the first
time and I hope I can share some of my
favorite things about Japan with
especially gouda because you know Ina
has been to Japan before and she's she
she's a bit more like
already experiencing it but
yeah who knows maybe maybe I can take
her on a little trip
Le before me no accustomed I guess yeah
all right let's go back to gaming and
just want to tell you that and I
couldn't focus
when I was telling the tangent so
what was I going who was I controlling
oh yeah ah me
so I talked to him he joined and now I
have no choice but to wait I suppose
[Music]
what are we gonna do I'm still quite
capable
you're still quite capable
[Music]
thank God some of us are still capable I
could poke him no first I could shoot
him and then I could poke him
the mage
why I could even punch him how much does
that do it's nothing no no I was
thinking I was the Healer for a second
never mind I'm gonna shoot
I think
wait oh wait never mind he'll he'll fire
back
[Music]
never mind
oh wait let's control him now too
oh
[Music]
then I'll start by healing him
others must meet you as well
but maybe another time I don't know if
she's open to doing it though
not sure
maybe we can get a full
of eventually
that would be nice but remember the time
where I wanted to take us like a a
picture for the memories and everybody
just hid under the table except Cali
so
but if I tell them
my whole particular tangent directly
maybe they will not be able to resist
the charms
the possible the endless possibility
you know okay I'm gonna do this
how much damage is he gonna
end up with a lot
never mind never mind
[Music]
what's the best way of dealing wait let
me see how much the punch does
that much I thought punching was
effective against Mages
no are you seeing this damage
it's nothing
[Music]
but he'll not be able to hit back right
because he's broken then
oh
yeah
[Music]
only for right now what if I hit him now
he won't head back
seems so
okay John
I'll go with iron Lance though because
Ryder's Bane is only 76 percent
[Music]
was that sufficient it was sufficient
please
okay
oh now these ones are closing in though
and that really scares me for her
[Music]
all right hold up I'll make her hide in
the figet because I think she's like
a little bit sensitive
[Music]
keep him here let them come to me I
guess
there is permade FPS but I didn't turn
it on
[Music]
um
stay although she won't even will he
really attack her better to stay safe
now I still don't know what to do with
him because
[Music]
socks why are you standing there
one should be able to move him
engaged
yeah but still
my muscles are yours
[Music]
that doesn't help me
I can walk around this way but that's
not really what I wanted to do
I can kill this dude though
you know what I'll do that
and then I'll move into the thicket
Maybe
[Music]
attack
of 95 percent one hit kill
[Music]
oh my God
I'm good
and cleared well if I go here I wonder
if the NPC will go for
the NPC or for me
[Music]
maybe he'll even go for me if I stand
here
[Music]
yeah may just hurt
and maybe that was a good priority
[Music]
oh no priorities NPCs okay then I'll
just go and hide here
okay four friends four surviving
incredible
oh
I see that one person is going for the
house
19.
yet to lose a single villager
because I can move so far
oh go here
[Music]
and it won't be a one-hit kill should I
waste my override but even that won't
kill
um
okay now I wonder if this one will will
prioritize attacking me back in its turn
or going for the house direct directly
[Music]
override from above to down to save
Saves The Village
[Music]
Hall interesting
okay one strike will decide it off
[Music]
and then
I can't reach the house but I can stand
here in front of it so he can
pass
not sure
enemy has four movement okay
I am blocking the house from being
invaded
all right and up here we only have three
more enemies okay okay
an Archer
so do we want to punch again you picked
me
oh man
really
this does more damage we could attack
with Louis first
and then shoot them down with 18 maybe
for example just one of the many ways we
could do it
oopsie
[Music]
thanks for free XP so he can't counter
that oh
oh does it break him again
yeah all right all right
tougher than I looked nice
I like the animations
generally all the animations in this
game so far have been pretty good in my
opinion that's great
[Music]
Louis generally such a freaking MVP once
again
[Music]
beautiful while you lasted you are
beautiful why you lasted well why are
you complimenting our enemy they're
corrupted
there's no need
no need to be so nice to them no XP for
her
[Music]
although she hasn't been doing much in
general does that really mean she
deserves EXP
you know and once again I can't reach
this [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm gonna try to make my way to it with
with her
because if she can shoot that horsey
down that would be great but hopefully
the Villager survives another turn
hmm
next turn I might be able to reach
[Music]
um I guess I'll just charge not that we
need it do we really need you for
anything now
go here
I won't charge actually
what was that oh
[Music]
as well
Archer could kill the Villager which
Archer
what Archer
oh this one yeah it'll take him a while
to get there
[Music]
okay um
should I move over here nah
late
[Music]
she got two turns so salvageable wait a
minute
anyways I got two turns
is there a limit
advertisers NPC
[Music]
okay
because I'm thinking although she will
probably want to hit the my Archer will
probably one hit the flying Pegasus
Archer will kill in two turns
We'll Kill
[Music]
um
so much for going for the Villager
oh oh everybody's surprise bamboozle
on this
this is fine though
oh no no kill though
then I might hit him first with I'll
manage you
[Music]
yeah she will get some damage but that's
okay
as long as she's alive
I don't want to kill him anyway because
I want the kill to go to my Archer don't
worry
okay
I heard that but [\h__\h]
I'm sorry it's here nothing for you
today
[Music]
it's no time to shine all right can we
do some magic here um
it's very risky though
[Music]
I don't know
let me let me figure out this situation
first
um
[Music]
yeah
if this love is a crime
can I talk to the house still in the
next turn
could be good right
[Music]
or yeah
next round is so fun right huh
if the Archer lives
he'll probably live
I know I can't live
[Music]
so I can't really reach the arch and I
wonder how he'll move he can't go
straight through it can you no maybe he
can it kind of looks like there's a
fence there
some way he'll probably make his way
over here I'll try to shoot the Villager
the question is what
[Music]
instead we might want to like block him
right
should I do this
[Music]
I'll just move her to this wicket
from one figure to another
yeah I'll wait for that
without
[Music]
thank you
Shane guard in case
for some reason the Archer no I don't
think he can even do that
can't even reach probably
never mind
healing another healer you're a
lifesaver
[Music]
oh I should talk to the doctor too
huh
yeah
I thought it was only the the little boy
[Music]
no need for your doctor okay okay
yeah now yeah I changed to the end of
four reasons
mostly for all the viewers who are
watching without watching who are just
listening
and doctor is unrequitable okay that's
what I thought
let's see what happens here
[Music]
kind of look
well he saw that one coming apparently
all right all right all right
nice thank you for checking in on me
dude there's not much I can do with it
thanks what is it energy drop I'm dead
your job here is done
[Music]
What's um
what should we do this business with
here goes
hmm
she's saying here goes or tear gas
we have a kills yeah nobody nobody
really kills
[Music]
closer
damn the music is so
attic
Runway one range the Archer I already
get it back
but I really don't do any damage
[Music]
a maybe in combination with my other
waifu
[Music]
could like if the exito
who needs it
maybe maybe first
and that's still warm but still even in
combination that won't be a Kill
I'll try anyway
okay
[Music]
and then
nobody else
can reach are you still no you have to
just give up already
[Music]
well
am I [\h__\h]
up
I'll be fine okay
but even if you say move close to like
from this way maybe
I move
um her away next turn
I guess
I guess and this is how I'll do it
unfortunately I couldn't kill him this
turn kind of lame
what's the matter with you
foreign
you're in the way I can't attack from
here
or from here
[Music]
he doesn't take the hint
you survived once again
and he got healed once again
uh he's a stubborn villager
I don't hold on we could get a killing
combination with these two Louis already
got so many exp anyway
um
yeah
she's level eight she's number six she's
level five
I could also first attack with her hope
that she doesn't correct move
Elia away and then moved it here right
in front of him
for the last hit
what do you think
no sure
she's an Archer oh all right but I
thought maybe with the mini bow doesn't
she have a mini bow
[Music]
how where can she go
um
this [\h__\h]
yeah she has a tread bow right okay okay
let's try it
don't quit
you have a one percent crit chance don't
cry don't cry okay
now so I would move here
wait
foreign
[Music]
exactly free
a bow doesn't look very Mini
what's happening in this scene right
there what's happening
should I be seeing the enemy
[Music]
unbelievable all the monsters are gone
yeah that was all me
all my brothers saved and it's thanks to
the Lord of you
you're welcome I guess but you must
subscribe to my channel and exchange
leave a like and a comment too while
you're at it turn on the notification
but no one got hurt I was a little
worried there
really
really you can't know what this means
you have to have confidence we decided
to give you this to show our thanks
you're the hero of the game you must
have confidence
surge is that a book
pure water
oh MVP Celine really oh I didn't expect
that
that took a long time it's been two
hours guys
we're not getting fired today I guess
we'll be playing Firelands for a while
but you know what I I was reminded that
um one reason why Fire Emblem free
houses took me so long uh two years ago
was because some of my parts were really
short I did more shorter streams back
then like what three hours two hours
but currently in my jrpg streams I
always at least six hours if not seven
or eight or nine or ten
so yeah that's why it needed more more
parts in there for more days
oh yeah I guess I also played it only
once a week um
give the nice people a proper thank you
I guess the proper thank you is that I I
will they will let me steal him from his
family and abduct him oh right thank you
for saving our village he looks so
npc-like though we saved it together
you did well today Jean he didn't oh oh
I introduced myself to you but I never
asked your name did I
speak so properly this doesn't he well
there was a lot going on
I'm the Divine Dragon Phoenix
a Divine dragon from the land of lethos
whoa don't mention it like I said there
was a lot going on at the time
what brings such a splendid personage to
our humans
I've been on a journey to defeat the
feldragon and bring peace to the world
love and peace the whole world
it's all right with you divine one can I
come along and help maybe you should ask
your parents first
I got an interview
no you're like ten if not nine my dream
has always been to become a doctor so I
can save people and that hasn't changed
but with monsters running rampant I
might die before I can do that you don't
know what happened
at the Divine Dragon side I think I can
learn to fight and to heal people at the
same time
well that's all very well for you but
what about the Divine Dragon you just be
a burden can
assume that I'll be using him a lot
because uh I already have a Healer oh I
wouldn't say that not of what he did
during that battle is anything to go by
if Sean wants to come I don't mind
though I understand why you'd be worried
I can't believe we're supporting this
decision
he's broken
he's a better dedicated healer oh yeah
but I like from well if he has your
permission then I can only ask that you
take good care of my boy oh oh maybe
I'll need more Healers
you're actually allowing him to go
father I told you I don't need to worry
about me
it's not like I'm never coming home
we don't know about that
[Music]
in return I'll be a first-rate doctor
how quickly they grow up
she grew up so fast of course sure be a
good boy
come home safe it's not classic yeah
yeah I will
thank you both of you I can't wait to
start working alongside the Divine
Dragon his eyes are so pretty and
they're so sparkly
the feeling is mutual John
I have a hunch that I'll be leaning on
you a lot in the days to come
he's killed hmm
I am the Divine Phoenix
okay well welcome to the team thank you
Gene
if I try hard I'm sure I can make myself
useful
[Music]
so far
I don't mind having you around bomb
fragments let's go
Orange let's go
Byron England let's go
[Music]
stealing the steel
how does our healer
feel about the situation that we got
ourselves a new healer oh wow who's
better than you
I want to take an emblem in going
schooler no emblem for you lady not yet
at least
too young
hello
adopt sheep I take the Sheep I watched
another video today of my currently two
favorite
YouTube channels
this one I think was from
Max Foster
and
it was a video where he
collect it roadkill found a Pheasant
Road killed pheasant
then went to a professional chef
had him prepare that into a fancy dinner
and then served it to food credits to
fruit food critics who didn't know what
they were about to eat
I can't get this one
hey why well the thing is I was also
first like it was disgusting but this
video educated me
I realized oh
apparently eating food kill a food kill
roadkill is really ethical and it's it's
in the end it's normal
meat and so on
and as long as it's not been on the road
for like days if it's fresh Roadkill
then it's the most ethical way of
getting your meat
and so the food critics were like
absolutely impressed by how yummy it was
even though pheasant is quite difficult
to cook I don't
oh
rub the flavoring no it's really good
apparently yeah no no it was cleaned
properly they ripped off the feathers
and everything they like skinned it or
whatever and they took out like the
whatever's inside
um
I made some good food with it and then
after they ate it and they told them oh
did you know this was actually a
roadkill and they're like
oh interesting
you know what it tasted good anyway so
no problem
I thought about eating something like
that either but
wow
[Music]
wow wow
apparently it's not such a crazy idea
[Music]
it's kind of common in real parts of
America I can imagine yeah
makes so much sense if you drive around
like at 5am you know when the sun's not
out yet and you see the fresh roadkill
on the street
yeah then I guess why the hell why the
hell not get one for you dinner it's
free a whole
piece of free meat go for it
I guess
apparently it's really good
yeah
what
are you a vegetarian or what because if
you're not then this is apparently the
most ethical way of eating meat and you
should not be freaked out by it
[Music]
wasn't freaking out so much
nah I'm good
all right so I I will not wait for you
guys to be roadkill I will just um
Take You Down
on my own
I will not let you die naturally or
whatever guys before turning you into a
burger
I will just suddenly stab you in your
sleep okay
how generous yeah apparently Some people
prefer it that way for whatever reason
[Music]
oh hello there you want to talk to me
well then
once we're all set I can take you to the
shrine where the Ring of the Dawn made
in this
uh-huh okay
okay
wait let me see
oh okay let's hear let's listen to this
one
I picked up the letters like you asked
Vander
oh yes set them down over there will you
no that's not why I want to get a
driver's license the thing is this is
also something I learned in that video
you are not allowed to take uh your own
roadkill like if you bumped into
something and it died you're not allowed
to take that home with you and eat it
because then I guess you could just
purposefully
drive into thousands of animals and yeah
take them home and eat them
and like basically do it purposefully
but still say oh it was by accident
yeah
so only if you find something that was
already like on the side of the street
dead then then you can take it if it's
not your own um
[Music]
I also brought a letter opener I might
need it
very good thank you glad before I forget
will you deliver this package one pack
it's just invisible oh
oh he's so old he's imagining packages
in his hand but let's just act along as
if there was actually a package there
yeah yeah yes sir answering letters a
man of my age had put his fighting hand
in nobler purposes
[Music]
is something the matter
what oh uh no everything's hunky dory
hunky dory well then why are you
standing there gawking I told you to
deliver that package
huh
[Music]
yes sir
on with it then a faithful servant of
the Divine Dragon wastes no time
if you gave me some real Steward work to
do maybe I'd take it more seriously
pardon
yeah not imaginary I'll deliver that
package for you right away sir
you have to consider his age Clan
instead of his age it's not his fault
something here oh yes
ah
cute girls for all I had hoped to
discuss with you now that you are before
me I am lost for words
I know what you mean but we'll have
plenty of time to get to know each other
[Music]
that voice sounds familiar
foreign
she sounds a little bit too old but oh
well let's get used to it
past some of the voices who don't fit so
well and enjoy the ones who are decent
okay
save and move on to the actual storyline
um
it's Erica Lynn back
wasn't that uh yeah wasn't that shion's
voice actress
I was like oh I like this voice sounds
so familiar it's quite pretty
[Music]
ah
Emmanuel
is
you know
[Music]
she's holding a random weapon that she
can give to someone else
uh how do I do this optimizing here she
has a pole ax all right who does it go
to
I can't optimize all
right optimize you
did it just go into the general
who's uh who's an ax person
a Vander right oh wait yeah
there you go wow we got so many axes
holy [\h__\h]
hmm
time to optimize a bit a little bit oh
he was also an ax dude oh all the asses
went to Vander
[Music]
um
why can I not optimize all
I can do them all singular but I can't
do the optimizer
okay I think I did them all
[Music]
we need a ring for Jane
do I have one left over
oh uh I got the strength one and I got
the Dex one
um
[Music]
okay let's just get in this one
better than nothing
strength for punching yeah whatever okay
here we go
okay let's see Alfred's egg yolk
you're welcome almost there just a
little farther north and we'll be at the
shrine oh the landscape's gotten rockier
we're near brodia it's all mountains up
there
I'm seeing fewer Villages as well
makes this a good place to hide an
emblem ring I suppose
yeah the closer you are to the brodian
border the colder and quieter it gets
look not a soul in sight
you're right there's no one around
unless
can't accept her
I already love her from behind I can't
tell how much I would love her from the
front
[Laughter]
take a little look around
she looks like a mate
I wonder what she's doing here
don't cry
[Music]
oh well doesn't that break the heart it
does
let's do some cheer her up now
I'd better help I am her prince after
all I won't stand by when my people are
suffering
somehow that statement really pisses me
off because
she's just a random girl
and I don't know somehow somehow I don't
know I can't explain
he feels like he's like in charge of
every single person's personal problems
like
do you live your own [\h__\h]
I don't know wait
yeah he's white knighting her
yeah
scrape what's great what happened hey
there also I just want to help her go
away Alfred go away
oh what's the matter something I can
help with
um
oh cute
I knew we'd startle you sorry for
popping up out of nowhere and
Libby you came just in time
[Music]
I like her fluffy hair with the style I
watched something earlier and there was
nobody around to help so I got real
stressed out oh right I skipped over the
niceties you can call me yunaka hiya
papaya
hahaha
can we please go back to Japanese but
her voice was actually good I have
papaya I am papaya hey
poo I've never heard that one before
anyway what did you lose you Naka you
knocked yunaka
not yunaka yunaka
pound ring kind of shiny with a hole in
the middle emblem ring wait
yeah well that's a ring and it talks for
some reason and that must be an emblem
ring
come again
yeah I figured you wouldn't believe me
[Music]
I believe you it might be an emblem ring
please go on what did it say
[Music]
if I remember right it asked me to take
it to the Divine Dragon oh she's right
here in front of you to me perfect is
that did you
thing you're the Divine dragon
well actually yes I am I'm sorry I
didn't mention it sooner I'm the Divine
Dragon well that's quite a weird and
um unlikely considered a coincidence and
now that we're doing introductions I'm
Alfred the prince of fiorinae
no one cares about you
holy broccoli potato salad well no I as
I say I'm holy macaroni but maybe I
should be saying holy broccoli
I say holy macaroni we could
allow
I think I just had a heart attack
alarm
yeah
[Music]
yeah yunaka how did you find the ring
was walking along the border minding my
own business when I heard a woman's
voice
she does the magic hands a lot doesn't
she help me I'm right here I'm by your
foot
hmm
you're quite the performer
anyway I picked up the ring and she said
take me to the Divine Dragon
but at that point I had no idea where
the Divine Dragon was so I told her I
couldn't help
do you know the way though told me to
start heading for the capital of
fiorinae well that's good advice the
quickest way to get to lethos is through
the capitol
but on the way I was attacked by Bandits
and ran off full speed and now the
Ring's gone she's so pretty I like her
bronze eyes I must have dropped it
somewhere whoa is me sniffle sniffle you
idiot but now that you're here you're
gonna help me find it right right
and of course I will anything for you
after hearing her story this definitely
sounds like an emblem ring
probably the Ring of the Dawn Maiden
or it could be another emblem ring we'll
just have to find it and see for
ourselves all right yunaka we'll help
you
golly that's great news she'll be so
happy if you're the one who finds her
stay with me
[Music]
stay with me good at saying that one for
me and karaoke
one of the songs she's saying that was
really nice let's start by retracing
your steps
[Music]
now sign of the ring so far
maybe somebody got to it before we did
to old song Old J-pop yeah everyone's
combing the area everyone was lying
around we would have found it by now
something something
stay with me
I think that was the name
you're sure you didn't lose it before
the bandits attacked I had it on me when
I passed through that ghost town over
there actually she's really just like me
for real for real because uh the other
day because I bought like a set of rings
you know because I felt like oh I need
to accessorize more because I wanna I
want the girls to then I meet to think
that I'm cute so I got a lot of rings
and then on one day I was wearing free
rings I was wearing uh one on each ring
finger and then one on my smaller finger
that you can you be the small one the
pinky and then at the end of the day I
realized oh seems like that one just
like slipped at some point and I lost it
so just like me for real for real
sad
what is it
it looks like the town's overrun with
Bandits
what how can you tell I'll bet these are
the same Chumps who ambushed me earlier
let's take a closer look
how can she say it and I can't
very familiar
these are the bandits I ran into earlier
no doubt about it
and that means one of them's got the
ring
ring right there I really like her
they really really really like you all
you see it
time to visit the eye doctor and see
she still doesn't see a Burly guy with
something glinting in his hand she
smells like that's gotta be our missing
ring you're blind can you think to find
one is it an emblem ring
it's too far I really can't say yeah she
needs glasses
must have great eyesight Monica they
even mention it yeah I have a Killer's
eyes
surprised I still have decent eyes
this is I'm actually like astonished
because I've been killing my eyes for
years now
what was that
kill her eyes I've got killed her eyes
if you ever need something lifted real
good I'm your girl
[Laughter]
anyway what's the plan now we've got two
problems that need solving I I I got
something that might need to be looked
at by you
a stolen ring and a town called Bandits
oh my God the Ring's our first priority
but we can't leave them unchecked wait
and now I'm curious too
usually never look up voice actors but
you knock on Fire Emblem English voice
actor
our approach
[Music]
oh
she was Rocky I'll kill you in and
killer kill Rosalia and saw that online
Etc
[Music]
twice
I tweeted at her
what was the other one that I looked at
before
the other one
[Music]
you're really cute dog online
for the [\h__\h] grape oh The Creep
[Music]
will only attract attention if we all
charge in it once I say we split up oh
Erica
very good does Erica have a Twitter
[Music]
how do you write that immediately
recognize
foreign
nice
[Music]
what a creep
how to get some contacts you know you
know send in a small group to recover
the ring nice and stealthy all right
okay then come on Divine one you're with
me she's just like me for real for real
man
and before they block you they want
one thing
maybe one day they need to voice act me
in a movie about me
oh here we go Okie dokes if we go
through here I bet we can sneak up on
that guy with the ring
it's so dark though flipping through a
side passage damn smart thanking you I
should have bought more of those staffs
but is it enough if I have one person
like if one person goes through with the
um like light
will it stay lit up for everyone else or
how does it work
[Music]
torches do I have any torches
well we'll find it who did I give oh no
what did I give
the item
[Music]
foreign
that's the one right
okay okay so we definitely need him and
I guess we're leaving
home behind thank you because I don't
really care about like people leave
behind
do we need two healers right now though
because then we could bring Boucheron
and leave from
bench Vander well I guess he's like what
level is he where's the level
I'm blind
[Music]
I'm blind where where is it
oh
[Laughter]
but promoted who else is
how do I know who's promoted and who's
not
[Music]
ah the s
and everyone else's b or this one's c b
c
yeah
okay I'll switch I'll switch those down
I guess we can find it
[Music]
it's pitch black out here hmm how can we
fight them if we can't even
don't worry Divine one that's what I'm
here for that's what you're here for
[Music]
um
my side's so sharp I can stop Daddy's
even when it's dark or foggy okay so we
don't even need a lamp with her
torch at least then you'll see as well
as I can ah okay
and Dark Places only the areas around
allies beacons and torches are visible
proceed with caution enemies may be
lurking in the Darkness
as he did
there he is let's take him by surprise
good idea
okay so it's she has like a passive
skill that makes her see more please
take me to the Divine dragon
this looks pretty pricey it's a pretty
looking ring and it was a female voice
yo so net me a nice lump of gold but the
boss doesn't need to know about it
oh dear you can't even hear me can you
who's that
I hear her that's the voice from before
that's definitely an emblem ring you
Naka will you help me get it back of
course you weirdo that's why we're here
right well thank you you know
that I hear her your impression was
incredibly accurate
stop you're gonna make me blush
okay
is that the dude who has the ring or
this is the one right in front of us
what
yeah it must be him because he has the
item
Mark item icon
so
[Music]
um
do we send some up to join them
or do we send them down
it looks like there's a path here though
that goes like this over here but then
we would arrived so early
foreign
[Music]
there is no way up okay
okay but I have to take care of these
two it seems like
and then I can walk over here with my
whole team and then somewhere here we'll
meet again in the middle Maybe
this one oh I guess maybe he just
doesn't have have an icon for the item
because they just don't show that
all right sounds affect poison some
classes like peeps there's knives that
inflict poisoning foes they hit poison
enemies take extra damage repeated knife
attacks will increase the potency of the
poison units remain poisoned until the
end of a battle or until cured with an
end-tight toxin or restore staff
[Music]
but she's beef go ahead too much damage
with children oh they both feel like
pretty much the same hmm
and I can't
attack twice because she will block the
path
damn it unless she has something to
throw
she does
[Music]
she uses iron daggers
all right that works well
um
[Music]
yeah all good maybe we can yeah yes we
can finish him off perfect
oh do I need to engage though
look we can still stay normal
breaking him too so this looks fine
[Music]
in free houses all the weapons like all
of them have uh
what's it called
like wouldn't they also break like all
the weapons
yeah durability
yeah they did right
I'm like why does it not have that now
was that always the Fire Emblem thing
and it's just not in this game or was
free houses special
[Music]
this is the first Fe without that
that makes sense
kind of easier
but we're playing hard this time
he lost we didn't even need healing
[Music]
she's she's sweet
I am emblemakaya I sense the future
shifting no Victory lies ahead
[Music]
machine
is a bit of a weirdo
but she's sweet
so it is the ring of the Dawn Maiden
yunaka I entrust this ring to you
all right let me put some honey in the
tea that I just poured myself
[Music]
Raiders are good we want you after all
yeah yeah and let's say we're back we're
all weirdos
[Music]
yunaka is an expert at throwing just
like Kiana for real for real
um
you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
I just got
a a
good message
foreign
[Music]
can't talk about it now but
[Laughter]
let her cook Let Her Cry
[Music]
you will know about this in the future
me but I
she belongs with you
all I ask is that in return could you
help us defeat these Bandits
will you join with emblemakaya my name
is
yeah okay I won't let you down
not gonna say what happened but thank
you yeah
hi what are you thanking me for because
you're not telling me
but you're welcome I guess
all right we got the ring
um
wait so how does this work one torch is
lit here and in order to LIT like this
torch I have to light it with that one
item right
Jean
so I would like does he really need
but he doesn't
okay he doesn't need it never mind
um that's fine though now we see there's
an enemy here sword was a lance okay can
we reach
him no okay for you anything to prevent
not a kill though
[Music]
engaged already
lit
Alfred's tanky yeah he really is he
barely takes any damage
he'll break anyway
[Music]
voice
hey I wonder who I should give that
emblem too oh oh [\h__\h] look at that mage
I'll better stay here
give that emblem to It's A Healer emblem
so should I give it to a Healer should I
just always put the ones together that
like seem to match the most
[Music]
do I need to kill these two as well
not turkey oh it's on on her okay should
I just keep it for her okay
I left it on you now call okay okay it's
good
[Music]
okay okay
can you reach no
do you guys hear that audio crackling
because I hear it let me fix it
[Music]
don't give it to a Healer she makes
everyone a Healer
oh so she'll be a mage that can heal
Louie can attack oh yeah with the
javelin huh
[Music]
so your tail ends
this kind of game
[Music]
for the Divine dragon
Fire Emblem games really are like my
kind of game
I really enjoy them
kind of dangerous for him to wait there
you know what I'll put you here
it's ready
[Music]
on guard yes I'll put you here too
I don't know if I should actually make
my way up to them on purpose what do you
think guys
[Music]
point away again I could
triangle strategy it wasn't that Square
Enix
their exp bait them let them come okay
see if they'll come just come next turn
whatever you say
[Music]
let's go let's go oh that's the first
time I met her voice this Chloe voice
sounds fine to me
looks like we got us some uninvited
guests
you got it huh
[Music]
uh-huh he's going for Louie
Thunder
oh
this is why me why me yeah I'm sorry
it's because I put you there I thought
you were safe down there
oof
looks like our cover's blown they're
snapping the Torches
don't sweat it we can re-light them as
we go
to light a bacon move next to it and
select light
yeah I already did that uncover hidden
enemies by Illuminating darkened areas
now
you can't oh
for real like it only showed after I
decided to wait
maybe if I would have gone with her
first and I would have seen her never
mind okay
[Music]
just like our cover's blown don't sweat
it
you know let me show you how to use
staves oh it's a tutorial for unicorn to
become a Healer
and let me Kaya and let me call
specializes in healing magic with the
same skill cleric a unit can use staves
regardless of classes so she will still
have to bring a a safe in her inventory
the engage weapon shine attacks
illuminates the area when used oh
cool
might come in handy right away in this
battle
skill augment increases staff range and
area of effect noise
engage attack great sacrifice fully
restores the HP of all allies at the
cost of reducing the users they switch
one
[Music]
that is sick
today engage
[Music]
that's really good
your other skills don't need staves oh
[Music]
really good if you have another heeler
to heal after her heal her after yeah
yeah yeah yeah but then with her that
means that I don't need to bring two
real healers I can just bring one Healer
and you'll knuckle
big brain
[Music]
lend me your strength
I knew the beef girl is a cute girl yeah
she is a lover I thought she was a mage
though
I keep on thinking she's amazed because
she looks like a mage but she's a thief
[Music]
oh it kills him
my prayers are with me
she stole mine too now
[Music]
wow wow wow we're bonding
all right
[Music]
ah
I wonder this thief
you can't shoot me huh
this one will attack me now
okay
let's see what we do down here actually
this one did come to attack us
um
Lance
show me perfect
but you know what I'll do it from here
[Music]
I will not like that one again because
we're moving away from there anyway
oh wait a second why am I doing that why
I can't just throw a javelin on him
let's see how much that does oh it
doesn't do much though
this one doesn't do much even though
ah well how and breaks him
now okay I'll do this 79 is a little bit
low but
I'm hoping for it to work
[Music]
I'll go for the Mage oh
damn it another hotel I see
I could have I could have I could have
maybe I should have but
[Music]
whatever
yeah there's another accident over there
so far going well and it's getting EXP
erience
decks and speed doesn't sound so bad for
her let me call clear let me cook
although
ax is effective on lands
[Music]
chain guard although he might go for my
healer now
is that a stupid idea
[Music]
when she's chain guarding
in case he attacks her she will still
take 100 of the damage right
okay but she does take 100 damage
[Music]
she's not also guarding that's what I'm
like wondering now
she'll take full if she gets attacked
huh okay I guess we'll see because
there's different opinions out there
um
those Shields
there's a mage there
[Music]
oh he's healing
oh oh [\h__\h] I guess I'll just use a I can
still help a pulmonary on him but
[Music]
I'll move him down
let him use a wolverine he doesn't have
one wonderful
I didn't give him one
and I must protect him in other ways
we can punch uh this one though which
will break him
therefore
[Music]
no
that might not be worth it
[Music]
um
sacrifice and we don't need him
laughs it's amazing
walk the back oh yeah so one road one
road path
that's fine
[Music]
can he reach Handle With Care
Bingo here which still would be blocking
I guess
[Music]
but
if the Archer goes one more
over here can he shoot him
foreign
[Music]
how come he can't shoot me back with his
Longbow from there
use Alfred to the thicket
hmm
not there
[Music]
oh cause he can go further
oh he can kill
what
[Music]
job nice
what
is he not how overpowered horseback
units op yeah seems so
um
uh I'll stay in the ticket
yeah because ax is strong one lands but
even if he gets it
before it is safe and defecute and now
we shall
I wanna heal Lily but that puts Jean in
the very dangerous position doesn't it
I really should have moved the flying
horse to kill the mage
[Music]
might have not been
really smart of me but I don't want to
change my ways now
saline first oh
okay where to
put some magic from here
but he'll fire back too oh but I barely
take damage if if they fire back
if I engage
foreign
[Music]
which one
ah
ah is it from Lisa no not that one that
replies from you guys
[Music]
[Laughter]
and Kevin from Unica
I'm getting all the voice actors so
inside
it's the privilege of being a cute
rebooter
[Music]
foreign
it's public anyway you can see it and
what was I doing
this
and Jean continues to live for another
day others must meet you as well
[Music]
I wish I could finish him from here
Maybe
either go down this path together with
Alfred
[Music]
to risky
this would be okay too
and Louie killmate with javelin now
oh no and
um
Selena's in the way
huh
can he do it from the side
no
[Music]
no no backup might be good okay and he's
kind of safe down there
a good choice all right
[Music]
um
if you're gonna get attacked anyway I'm
gonna move you all the way over here
[Music]
that's okay you'll die now
oh
and the upper side oh we have a really
exciting battle going on
face and ask people
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I got you
she need a blip with a horse
oh
God no damage again
[Music]
how how thank God I was worried about
him there sheesh
and my throat so far is fine
at the moment it's fine thank you for
asking
um
[Music]
atus really like playing chess
I guess let's finish this here
uh
pure
it only really be damaged by Magic
anti-amma weapons
yeah I guess that's kind of realistic
[Music]
shield and all that Armor after all
hmm
so you can move through I'll put you in
the picket
I hope you're safe there
now who wants to get the kill
um
level eight
you're level eight
I don't know if you can really kill him
you might you gotta probably Focus On
Healing this turn
[Music]
I can definitely get a Kill
hell yeah
get ready
[Music]
finally getting some justice
however it seems like she'll probably be
lagging behind for the rest of this map
because she's the most far away
[Music]
okay you uh you go here to heal the
Healer
and maybe the Healer can heal so yeah I
owe you for that
[Music]
Marshall monk HP magic speed resistance
luck
what do you think
how was that
stats wise
[Music]
I think I'm using normally the honig
Alpine Salva yeah
good level up plus five solid oh is
there like sometimes you only get like
free and sometimes you get five or so
damn well that's
all right Jesus please uh
[Music]
is there another mop here
did we kill everyone
I want to move on
I can't reach
[Music]
sometimes we get zero what
sir
get some damaged back
I don't
well then I will do this
as well
huh
my alley I got two level ups with only
two stats rising in a row
he's only got two
but HP Andres
we said she says this isn't a bad start
it's a bad level for you
[Music]
generally remotes to avoid you getting
no stats up
someone got it two two times in a row
which sounds really freaking painful
[Music]
um
how am I gonna do this
[Music]
kind of want to move on to
tap first and then maybe
ah we have a raid
thank you ah thank you soon welcome hiya
papaya indeed
I guess that's our new greeting for
today no more kikiliki only hi Al papaya
[Music]
didn't Emma have like um a bgm song and
she keeps on using that her view is
called papaya because it sounds like
it's like
I don't know
hope you have a great stream thank you
thank you
cutie I wish you voiced someone in this
game I wish you would have voiced maybe
uh it here
[Music]
yeah papaya bgm
Final Fantasy 14 also has a papaya song
what
it's been called papaya for like two
years yeah
yeah no I know every time it's played
everybody goes like
I don't know what to do
but I'll do this I'll do it
I'll do it because he can't fight back
and I'm a coward so I like it when
people can't fight back
it's relaxing uh but I can't still not
kill him that's kind of lame
what if can it reach no we can't
[Music]
doshio
okay now that sound I guess I'll take
that back
don't take it out of context please
she's engaged she should use her
how many rounds does she have left how
where do I see that
there's somewhere where I can see
how many rounds she has left with her
engagement
that's why I pick on chickens no
no no no you guys can very well protect
yourselves
no way why am I like such a fan girl
doesn't matter with me
no way
you guys are keeping your eyes open on
this one
[Music]
you just responded with Emojis
so wait uh she's wait she's not engaged
oh never mind I don't know why she looks
engaged to me
oh but then there would be a number okay
okay okay
[Music]
um
I will take those sweet sweet thank you
you were beautiful while you lasted
in this view the whole world is lit up
even in the background
in the view that we just saw
maybe maybe I should have moved him
first
[Music]
you
stay in the bush
okay
will do but
[Music]
maybe there's a six percent crit chance
because nice
he'll probably try to attack me next
turn and then I'll counter and then and
then we good
whatever you require
you know what you don't even need to
stay in the cricket but
huh
but I will I will put you in the ticket
and then I'll do my best
[Music]
why thank you you know I did a nice
thing today
um you know my my apartment comes with a
seller of course
and it's a pretty Spacey seller
and I have totally not been using up the
whole Space
but who knows holy [\h__\h]
that's more than I expected
um
but anyway my
landlord I guess the Lord lady landlady
messaged me a while ago and was like Hey
My My mom is moving in
to the same building and the thing is
she has like no
um specific room
to what do you what do you call it in
English
storage room there's no storage room in
her apartment and her selling room is
kind of small so we would appreciate it
if we could switch sellers then you have
a smaller seller
and she gets the bigger seller
and I'm like okay well I live alone
so in truth I really don't need that
much space
so she's lucky she's lucky that I am so
nice because I said yes but the whole
time I was thinking should I be
requesting at least a little bit like a
tiny
discount on my
uh on my on my monthly payment yeah
[Music]
I was wondering because I was and then I
looked at my my contract and I was
trying to figure out if
the
seller the size of the seller is
specifically stated on my
um on my contract the thing is that that
seller definitely belongs to my
apartment
but I didn't really find anything that
specifically would state that it has to
be this one with that size and so on so
and I'm like you know I and just
a lonely girl
is not good at defending herself and all
that
um
yeah so I I just kind of said all right
for now and then it wouldn't have
happened immediately anyway
I'm very considerate so in the end I
didn't ask for anything
[Music]
in exchange
and today it happened like we switched
settlers and they were really nice and
all you know but
oh now the seller that I have now
really small but my stuff does fit in so
it's okay
it's just that I have another storage
room in my apartment
and that lady doesn't because she has a
way smaller apartment than I do
yeah yeah
it's good to get in The Graces of your
land learn yeah I was thinking so too
like don't need to be like so annoying
about because I know
and with all the like details of it you
know
I can't be bothered with it
um she can attack from here right
[Music]
sometimes it's better like that it's
good to be kind yeah I was thinking like
don't really there's no need to be like
super picky about every little thing but
I was thinking like I I I wonder if
I would have the right to request a
discount now
but even if it would probably not be
that big of a deal but I do pay a lot of
brands
[Music]
yeah maybe they see it as they owe me
maybe I'll just remind them one day oh
by the way remember that the fact that I
gave you my big ass
seller hmm
[Music]
they're nice too so we're both nice so I
think we won't have problems in the
future
I'm nice they're nice
let's just all be nice okay
[Music]
next time I burn down my kitchen so
hopefully that will not happen
um
the [\h__\h] is that dude not that yet
one if someone will show up if I move a
little bit like over here and heal
myself with the vulnerary and then I'm
gonna finish in with the Mage that that
would be my plan
[Music]
I really need healing but the healers
are all out there
good plan okay I hope so
[Music]
just so he can pass through
okay okay
now that wins
getting smarter the more I play this
game
brain inflation
[Music]
your orders please
how far do I want to go
ah he's bulky
it'll be fine
and then I can even
do a chain guard but when I set a chain
guard now and then afterwards I put
units next to him will they be
considered chain guarded
too or do I have to change I set
everyone
where I want them to be
a good question yes no yes yes
units first and chain guard hmm
but it's okay okay it should be fun
seems fun
[Music]
Shields are just AJ sent allies from
Attack
definitely
so you are shielded
you will be also shielded amazing
beautiful
oh hey we have a Healer down here you
know what
I might send her down
yeah
[Music]
okay
hang in there
there's no way that
her skull is not split into two pieces
right now
oh martial law HP string for punches I
guess magic and speak
for a Healer do they need magic the most
it's pretty good
[Music]
hey
okay okay okay okay not bad more magic
more heels okay
so they don't have intelligence as a
step
you guys don't have as good eyesight as
I live to fight again
enemies
the path is clear once again
oh but she's not engaged anymore
unfortunate
oh she can stand
I don't know
of course you can stand on top of this
for a moment
and alrighty I'm happy to help we're
moving on but
how far
I guess
self-improved
[Music]
the joystick just always goes way too
far
[Music]
please wait for your healer
she's on her way maybe we'll bring her
too
we'll meet in the middle anyway right
and those Shield oh there's a there's a
there's a thing right there
maybe I should
use him to heal
maybe maybe first attack and then heal
it's level eight though even if I get
the kill I don't want to kill because
he's level eight we have a level four
[\h__\h] what are you doing
kill
what about you
okay we can combine our our strength
back from behind
[Music]
no no way
can I use Javelin formula here
[Music]
and then I think it's enough
do you see how I'm using my brain juices
although she's in a dangerous spot for
the ax man
that worries me a bit
[Music]
um
but I have an idea
[Music]
that was good I was gonna chain guard
her and turn the light on with someone
else
we brain juices
could make a smoothie with it oh HP
decks and depth oh definitely HP you're
definitely good I don't know about Dex I
don't know who Dex is good for
[Music]
so
all right I can't because I don't have
full HP
[Music]
and that's unfortunate
that is good accuracy
some of the low needs more increases hit
chance
all right then that was a good level up
then
um
warp Ragnarok time
[Music]
warp on that ax guy
is that what you're saying I I will
consider that as an option an answer
please grant me your strength
[Music]
hell yeah
oh
[Music]
should I still do it
before I still do it wait a second
what if um
one second one second I have to try
everything do you have a javelin
who does What if I fish him off with him
no wait the other way around oh no
they're both level eight it doesn't
really matter
[Music]
okay okay here's my idea
here's my plan
[Music]
first
whoa
[Music]
it's been strength difference look whoa
yeah
not bad
[Music]
that is like hey what's the maximum six
or is five the maximum
that was really good
um I know I could heal but at the same
time I want to light up this thing
oh it didn't really like give me much
more insight that I already had
but anyway
we'll finish the zoo now
[Music]
all can level up all sets is Max
whoa
[Music]
it sounds a little bit more
tonight
[Music]
never seen that before
cute
magic proficiency
[Music]
oh Archer hi everybody
you're not getting away without a
scratch
nice Miss
nice Dodge
that's it that's all they got
[Music]
can I engage
because then I can move further right
it's kind of lame that I have to stop
there
or I just stopped there in the thicket
but then both all of them haven't really
been doing much
doesn't hurt to engage
okay
emblem engage
[Music]
every stand has its own percent of
growth depending on the unit and class
so having all sets growing is pretty
rare
[Music]
all right
uh I don't think I'll override
I'm fine with him surviving I just want
to do some damage
[Music]
uh 86
yeah I'm fine with that oh
[Music]
Lance power free
those are not orangey though are they
[Music]
maybe it made no sense to bring her
along this path
in hindsight
and now oh
he can go that Hill let's go he reaches
[Music]
determined for each rank
I see I see I see minus 10 Dodge is that
supposed to be a perk
it is that what it said Handle With Care
that doesn't sound very good
um level seven can you do the dean maybe
uh
from here
[Music]
oh wait here's an Archer
might want to do it for a close-up right
javelin 94 100.
correct you were beautiful while you
lost it
foreign
doesn't need to be
handheld anymore
she can be docked in the switch dock
I made it
[Music]
you came up with that myself
what was the percentage on that one
[Music]
yeah
Modelo
73 what if I throw my accent
I was considering that anyway
oh wait what Oh I thought that was a
throwing ax the compact one
83 73 okay 83
let's go with that one
I hope you find peace
as it's as if I did it according to
kikaku
and maybe I did or maybe I didn't oh we
will never know
[Music]
she's level six by the way okay okay we
can't none of them can kill but in
combination we can unless I accidentally
critch
nine percent crit
[Music]
maybe we do liberation
Dropbox
[Music]
I'm gonna let yunaka finish
wait Max
oh my God you're gonna get married
that was a cinch wow Bruto
okay uh where am I going is this where
I'm going
I don't see any more torches to lie this
is kind of weird
[Music]
I'll go this way
or should I have gone left I don't know
I'll go this way for now
here he comes ocean eyes a little late
to be saving the day we killed off the
villagers ages ago
scripted right
and I don't really like Celine being in
the front here well I might not survive
oh no she did it
online
all right all right all right is there
any more enemies over there I want there
can't reach
can reach but doesn't do [\h__\h] damage at
all
maybe I wanna see her engage maybe not
the healing one just uh wait can she
like
actually like some cool attack when
she's engaged
emblem engage
with my magic you may illuminate even
the darkest of places oh that will help
too
and then
what what choice is that
[Music]
as well as it belongs too oh you know I
noticed on the others that when they're
engaged they look kind of like lit up
but I thought that was just like a lit
up filter
but this looks like her hair color
actually changed
[Music]
and even that
is not really worth it isn't it
unless I go a step back you know
[Music]
no no no
wait he still hits back
he also has range
and how far can I go back by the way oh
okay uh
[Music]
that doesn't seem so worth it
break him first
[Music]
with home because Kiana can't reach
can't break
[Music]
oh look how far he can go wow
do I want to do an override just for the
fun of it
Celine sword oh she's got a sword
but override first anyway
because then Celine can get the kill
setting Celine is one level below Alfred
or whoever wins to kill
override
[Music]
and oh hey there's still someone there
before I could have overwritten that too
all right all right now I want to undo
it
now I need to undo it
if I just
I think I would say it if someone would
move their first like Celine no
I can't even then oh okay okay thank you
thank you for telling me
[Music]
um
is this an option oh a dangerous option
though
in the next round
kind of dangerous
boss has two HP but oh I didn't consider
that either
[Music]
well
I have to be here
[Music]
I'm ready to dig in
I'm sorry
what
sometimes you just have to go for it and
then you'll be surprised with
happy incidents
happy accidents
um
[Music]
want to heal and then attack
what good fortune
I'm going getting up on the bus
[Music]
wait let me just check how far he can go
can I hit him again after he goes to a
second HP bar
[Music]
oh but he hits me back so hard
and remember he's arranged too so it's
taking a step back doesn't help
but if I'm raged he attacks with a
different weapon and maybe it's weaker I
don't know let me let me see
no still still
seeing damage
allow your soul the rest it deserves
[Music]
we won't count on the first one
so she's like so broken but he's like
kind of reset
[Music]
okay I'll still attack again this is
worth it to me
which is worth it to me and also he has
only 60 hit
so maybe he misses actually it's quite
likely that he misses
uh
99 94 94.
hey Miss I was really lucky so far with
my RNG you damn okay okay okay hmm
brightest page
72 82 87.
go with the iron lens
[Music]
ah look at them being so far
that's such a waste
that's okay though
um
I think should I heal everyone now maybe
[Music]
he wants to go for her okay okay wait
wait wait
[Music]
I'll hide in the picket and so she isn't
really necessary anymore it's fine if
she has one HP I'll do my great
sacrifice now and
there then come on
foreign
[Music]
but it ain't classic
it's okay and Jean thanks for helping
though
I will avenge you
after I make some more tea right here
imagine if you got those people some
killed in this first bounce
[Music]
listen to me
cool okay I can break him
that would be amazing
[Music]
it's hard mode not gonna rewind no not
necessary in my opinion we're almost
down
[Music]
and he's broken now who wants the EXP we
got uh level nine level nine level eight
oh seven and can you can you uh she's
week too weak
[Music]
it's too weak Maybe
someone else was weak
does some groundwork but
[Music]
um
oh you would want to go for her
so greedy he always goes for the weak
ones
[Music]
ah Echo
interesting interesting
wait no we're we're past that I can't
Echo again
again
let us
that looks like a full kill to me
looks like a full kill to me too
um
he's in range but yeah I know I know I
don't know if he'll really go for her
but I feel like he maybe would
she's a piece of [\h__\h]
[Music]
I want her to get the kill
I could just let make everyone wait
and just
you know
there's work to do
uh interesting
I didn't think of that I thought she was
already used up
ah
what's 22 crit chance is a lot
wait one more check how much damage uh
[Music]
Chloe
I'll get him down to five oh oh I can
get okay okay with a steel lens
mm-hmm
[Music]
she gets crit in the void tiles oh
wait
will she die
[Music]
no no no no no no
is he countering I didn't see it and
he's not countering okay
[Music]
do the one with uh more damage but let's
crit chance
or
no never mind this one is zero now
because we're not in the picket okay
sorry sorry sorry I'm just trying to
play it smart
should be fine this one should be fine
foreign
[Music]
and here we go the last step
okay
has to be the slim Lance
or the steel lands students is safer
okay or is it no this one has more hit
percentage but this one I can do with
one hit
if it doesn't work I'll rewind she's
okay
[Music]
I had to say it I jinxed myself
foreign
[Music]
thank you Talisman okay
original I always I always kind of get
like nine Tunes
MVP
for once
living up to her hero status damn
kakata
[Music]
it took a lot a lot of time I'm sorry
guys
[Music]
that's the last of the bandits
you've been a huge help you Naka I was
kind of trying to perfectionize every
turn every every move
if not for you we'd be scratching our
heads in an empty Shrine right about now
I can't thank you enough
it was nothing really
I wonder who took it from The Shrine in
the first place
it must have been those Bandits right
uh well oh what's the matter
I have a uh
confession the thing is ah I didn't find
the ring I stole it why well she is a
thief so she's just doing what what
she's supposed to be doing
and when I saw the shrine I figured it
might have valuables
I went inside I heard makaya's voice and
pow there's the ring staring right at me
I was just looking to make a quick
bundle of dough I'm sorry
stop about it it's okay
it was a beep what no but honestly until
now I didn't even think about the fact
that she might have stolen it
see
when I learned that YouTuber royalty I
panicked and kinda well wide
really I'm no different from those
Bandits
I'll accept whatever punishment you give
me
hold on you were planning to sell the
ring oh oh [\h__\h] he gets mad yeah
well then why didn't you
in no time because she [\h__\h] lost it
we could have run for the hills as soon
as the Divine Dragon handed it to you
yeah
we're useless in the dark would have
been easy to give us the slip
the person
let's roll with it yeah yeah but instead
you stuck around and risked your neck
for us yes why she is
set well with a good heart yeah
when she started talking to me I got
this feeling that I just couldn't shake
yeah she's a good person at heart as you
can see I felt like like I had to help
her get to the Divine dragon
yunaka has shown me nothing but kindness
Fighting by her side I saw a bright path
ahead
when I sensed some bronze return I
called out in the dark it was she who
answered
[Music]
him
pushes them
I'm wondering if to Japanese people the
English voices sound natural and nice
and it's just a thing of
the language that is
like not native to you will sound better
to you because
they say they they don't have a problem
with it
I don't know
[Music]
I like a lot of dubstep it's preference
yeah
still
[Music]
method for line readings but some
people's voices just sound better
[Music]
I am to blame for entangling her in all
this
yunaka has done nothing wrong name is
I hear you but she did lie to us
as Prince I'm not supposed to let that
go without some sort of punishment
slap that butt timer
bent down and let him slap your butt lay
it on me I can handle it
is in a lot of places
joining our forces oh what a punishment
say what now
we are on a journey to collect the
emblem rings and defeat the Bell dragon
you're hired I know it's a lot to ask
but
will you pledge yourself to our cause I
guess this works well
what do you think Alfred the fitting
punishment
I love it our army is pretty lean so
adding a new recruit makes a lot of
sense
[Music]
clearly has Raw Talent she could be a
real asset it's one of my favorite
characters so far so
I'll gladly have her I won't let you
down
thank you
both of you
don't mention it
and you Naka apparently asked the first
to say
hi
[Music]
hi Papa you didn't say it back hiya
papaya back at your Divine one there we
go there we go
[Music]
the client's very close to the fifth
character in her game
to a fifth card ah the fact that she
found by I'm a parent with a fever
sweater fitting ah another hotel that's
sweet with that settled let's hurry
onward you've got to cross into brodia
right yeah let's go yes Mother sent a
letter to the brodian king when we left
the castle he should be expecting us
good
Kingdom of Might
curious to see what it's like there I'm
curious to see the new characters there
[Music]
oh look at our team down there
and they keep running running and
running running and running running and
walking
running and running winning I winning
Goods oh what is this a taco
I know
I thought should I just adapt literally
everything I can
the more the Merriam
adopt it and he's happy about it being
like doggle
I can't pass man I really want to adopt
those like burps and chickens though oh
the pigeon I can adopt but not the
chicken excuse me
I'm done
foreign
did I never make an end up video
I should I haven't made an AM video in a
long time anyway
and Zoo
[Music]
oh
I can get the cartoon
oh I did
make an m dot video I'm pigeon I guess
probably
did I make an End pigeon video
for me that's kind of the same thing
no
all right put that on the list if I ever
ask you
what should I do next
and tell me that I wanted to do a and
pigeon video
okay
June in full size
[Music]
for some reason she really Treasures or
cherishes her legs because those are
like the most protected parts of her
body
thanks
I've gotta say I'm not used to having so
many allies
what's the wipe of your Divine Phoenix
I love you
ah
as royalty I feel partly responsible for
letting the Bandit situation get this
out of hand
I don't give a [\h__\h] it's all good
so I guess Samuel first
if you're fake if your legs are shot
you're done for her I'm gonna run right
now
hours I wonder if that was
considered
huh
is that
hey
so I've I've been thinking about it even
though it wasn't obvious to me at first
but I'm guessing that she's the one who
was hooded before but don't tell me
but because it's because she's kind of
small and she's Barefoot you're the girl
I met in Flora Middletown Vale wasn't it
also she got this like two colored hair
thing going on
so that would be like a nice contrast
later on if she's still on the
mysterious one
oh we're coincidence finding you here
oh
I'm glad to see you again you left so
abruptly last time Oreo really caught me
off guard
truth do you live around here
but that's just a game I'm just passing
through well looking for someone really
she's
after Google give me a second
fail Fire Emblem English
voice actor
you can tell her happy I feel like I've
heard of that one before foreign
voice before
anyone I know
[Music]
oh
I guess the girls in her Twitter Heather
what
[Music]
you know Twitter and it is Hulu
she plays turtle
[Music]
oh my God what she's huddled okay I have
to write to her
hey I really loved you as
cool and now you are a cute perfect girl
good job
[Music]
and she's also Ringo for soul hackers to
Hannah be for scarlet Nexus
is acting work but
I know I don't know how to get a job
like that like while I'm in oh no
[Music]
yeah bingo
maybe maybe you can hear it the
similarities now who are you looking for
she don't
know
[Music]
the person I must talk to again no
matter what
you were separated then I'm sorry
it's painful to be apart from one's
family
do you have any idea where to look
nine I don't even know what face to look
for
we've been apart since I was very young
but they did give me something long ago
this
Nanny ring
what a pretty Stone
[Music]
maybe there's also a blue one it's my
good luck charm
I know that as long as I have this
we'll be reunited someday
I'm sure you will
don't forget to take care of yourself
look your legs wounded
huh
this kind of thing happens all the time
[Music]
it looks pretty deep kill
Ed there Chains set out to hold for a
while
[Music]
she's got cute feet
thank you you're quite kind to help a
complete stranger like me
you're not a stranger you saved my life
remember
[Music]
she might be evil that brings us friends
as far as I'm black and white girl and
Friends help each other she's from
pins
there must be a plot twist somewhere and
it's me or to her
should I not have said that
no no I'm just so happy to have someone
I can call a friend it's like a dream
her voice reminds me of some Beethoven I
don't know who I can't recall the last
time I was treated with such kindness
should be a YouTuber too
all these voice actresses they should
all be features
what do you mean by that
I wonder why they don't do videoing or
maybe they do and we just don't know I'm
sorry but I have to go
she has a little bit of a fauna in her
yeah yeah I was thinking that too it's
like a a less Whispering fun of us are
you sure
foreign
[Music]
um thank you for the bandage hope to see
you again
that movement was also fun like I don't
know why
[Music]
There She Goes
see you around Phil
interesting
where was the rest of our team when we
were having that talk though
anyway we are going to the somnia now
oh
yes Vibe relay tickets
eh records well something has been found
and look at Richard
wait are we in chapter six right now
we're gonna see what chapter I am
his name is here uh chapter six ah
what's up can I not get um lady edelgard
now
look out Rich yeah which one was that
somewhere here
but wouldn't it be shown on the map that
there's something going on there
I'll just
look around everywhere
[Music]
oh I can fast travel there hello that
wasn't there before
what is that like a god
[Music]
Nani
it's like a
weird cat
thing
[Music]
oh my
what in the world is this creature above
him is a DLC okay
I missed the last playthrough
I'm I was here there was nothing
standing on top of it
ah so you have found it at last huh you
guys are saying the same thing as him
not much unfortunately
it began to appear shortly before you
awoke from your slumber
Humera once said it is something of a
guardian spirit for the zombie hell
sounds more like a dog claimed to have
played with it in her youth
you did
so this creature has been alive for a
very long time
you know I do feel a sort of affinity
toward it
it seems to have taken a liking to you
as well Divine one if it is truly the
guardian spirits of the somnia what a
great idea now that I've met it I'd like
us to be friends okay the past
three lines she said to me
uh
does it sound like someone else to you
guys too
foreign
[Music]
it sounded to me like fruit
I don't know if you know her but
she's in vishojo
no that means it's like a fill-in voice
I said no no no but those lines kind of
sounded like fruit to me
let's see I'll call you huh
it was just me
and give her the name
um
[Music]
Cube
how about not cue
but I see what you mean but not that but
QP
me
this makes absolutely no sense
oh I like
no
it's gonna get bullied in class no it's
okay no there's a QP mayonnaise but
small yeah I guess it's spelled
differently but still I want I want to
make a combination of QB and QP
mayonnaise
um
yeah I'll give him this name though
it's kind of cute as a name it's kind of
cute
hey you're QP QP the cutie pie
yes I like that name kill me
it's nice to meet you I hope you like
your new name kill me it looks well
pleased oh God for a moment I forgot to
say hello to that's when next you see it
around hello voice
thing sometimes I do this thing where
some weird
really unfitting voice comes out of the
cutest characters you too
the enigmatic killpin has watched over
this land for Untold ages
you take good care of kill feet the QT
something wonderful might happen oh
oh
dress up Nani
[Music]
just like me for real for real
okay we're keeping that one
a butterfly on his tail
in the river
[Music]
oh baby both of them in her
in her
kimono maybe wings
ah like my mommy
wait I love these accessories
[Music]
I guess we'll combine
you know what I like the wings I'm gonna
go with the wings
[Music]
okay oh I can change that too oh let's
match it to my ribbon on my neck
foreign
[Music]
looks just like me
what happens if we get friendly with
each other
there was a
in the sky there was a shooting star
but in three times in a row oh I was
gonna do that anymore I was gonna see as
it uh gets of the heart thingy
it's more no
I did it three times he doesn't give a
[\h__\h]
[Music]
at least nothing visible
and Max's friendship nut scene
any amazing things happening yet it'll
follow me around
oh that's cute
I somehow
[Music]
who's that we got bad fragments oh
that's worth it
I was like pressing B and nothing was
happening and suddenly I thought he was
like pooping
[Music]
nice okay can I only do it like once per
day
cute he poops bonds
he really does
once per battle ah okay
all right then I've uh done everything I
could
no okay it's not over there right
you go on top
[Music]
someone said on top
here
Divine one we 've covered this
mysterious bracelet in southern pyrene
there appear to be more of them
enshrined on the islands off the coast
we should investigate can I eat some
chocolate
[Music]
now that I don't have to read I can eat
there's an emblem inside this bracelet
all right
the presence inside is complicated
presents inside complicated why is this
complicated but I think I have the
invocation
lead us emblem of Rivals
well because uh they're all rivals of
each other
[Music]
um
she looks a bit different is it because
she was like re-drawn by me my Mommy
we're free I am emblem edelgaard
[Music]
either bring by love
no
pleased to meet you I am emblem Dimitri
Dimitri
I guess that makes me emblem clawed
the only one that gets my heart doggy
Doki him the only guy
that must have been a crowded bracelet
sorry I should introduce myself I'm the
Divine dragon
[Music]
Chihuahua you're obviously not from
Elliot's may I ask what you're doing
here until recently we were the
Guardians Of Another World it seems we
were moved somehow why don't they all
have the same eye color did they always
have to say my car
I get the feeling you've come to give me
some sort of test no need for that you
were able to summon us that is enough
and your timing is excellent
we were just growing weary of each
other's conversation
[Music]
this must be
some kind of
alternative ending of free houses where
they all three of them end up dead and
they become ghosts and now they're in
some sort of ring forever and they annoy
each other
because they're stuck as ghosts in the
ring so speak for yourself I thought
Dimitri's stories were getting better
with every telling oh dang it along well
the boys
damn poor little guard yes the sarcastic
interruptions kept increasing too
coincidence never mind
you three all seem to be really
comfortable with each other
appearances can be deceiving
really edelgard
kidding you can tell because your face
looks exactly the same as when she's
serious
her face shape it's kind of more
baby-like now
[Music]
we have always been in competition
sorry sorry we were all students at the
officers Academy but we LED different
houses
free houses I remember that very well we
all do we all do good times
and and bad times but mostly Good Times
that's what you meant by competition
yes we only truly came together for
special events like the battle of the
eagle and lion
a traditional mock battle between the
houses to celebrate one another's
strengths the real celebration was
afterward our festivities got rather
exuberant that night
Dimitri looks pretty straight laced but
don't let him fool you
between you and me he's like a force of
Destruction at a party I'm surprised
they didn't expel his whole house for
those shenanigans
must have been quite a night no
you just met him so you can't tell if
he's joking
just ignore half of everything he says
come on be fair at least a third of what
I say is worth hearing you do know a
third is less than half right even I
just noticed it
before they said it
let me say it formally
our power is at your disposal please
make the most of it Victory will be ours
have no fear
we are here to help and if these two in
their conventional tactics fail maybe
I'll show you a few tricks that's all
very reassuring thank you
I'll do my best to help the three of you
work together
foreign
[Music]
switches off with fellow house leaders
Dimitri and Claude at random providing
access to a broad range of abilities
[Music]
ambits changes based on which of the
free house leaves is currently active
oh
red hair
look
is that it'll kind of is that me
it's me right hmm
[Music]
me in the uniform what the engage weapon
aim can smash both I think I remember
that weapon's name and deal bonus damage
to a dragon
that engage skill combat Arts
provides access to one of the three
different attacks at a cost to the
unit's remaining engage turns the engage
attack house unit this strikes with uh
ax lands a boat all of us
increasing the chance of breaking an
enemy
it is effective against Flyers
okay and all of that sounds very broken
it was her ax wasn't it yeah
oh
all of it
you can travel to the emblem bracelets
Island from the world map
s
suddenly different topic you can return
to the main store at any time what is
this about
why are you telling me that now huh
they'll see Island ah
a or what what can I do there just fight
more battles
still nothing here
[Music]
oh that's where the tiki emblem is
okay but not for now I'll keep those uh
current ones always happy to see you
wait is that a ring and then I have to
put on kiwawa
I was switching out Rings now no more
sorry marf it's over I know we bonded so
much but it's over fatal guard indeed
beautiful
so then
who do I give marf to
or should I give Mark to
[Music]
give to Vander
I feel like it fits Chloe
[Music]
Chloe good option
mistake all right
I guess I'll give it to Chloe Mark let's
go I'm gonna cut Mexico use of the Dodge
you don't comprise with dungeon hmm
but you're not I'm happy with what
yunaka has now to be honest so
[Music]
okay and what should we uh let me I
guess go sleep see if someone wants to
talk to me
[Music]
when I sleep
foreign
[Music]
I mean there's all kinds of options but
I think I'm happy with how it is now
resting time who's gonna creep into my
room this night
oh
a girl this time please Yahoo I'm here
who's sound asleep huh
is that
I know that sleepy face so well
but you better wake up soon again time
no
it's from again
such a fine dragon is awake
feeling a bit of deja vu
well good morning
she's obnoxious but surprisingly I don't
dislike her for being obnoxious
normally obnoxious types are so not my
thing
totally hate those most of the time but
for her I don't know what it is
just because she's cute I don't think
it's only that
yeah no I think it's more than that
something about her
it just kind of balances out the
obnoxiousness
um
okay uh let me work on those bonds and
supports
whoa
Peter you're liking princess Haley
very much so I particularly enjoy the
aroma I smell a hint of citrus along
with floral notes yes more than one
variety if I'm not mistaken it brings to
mind the blossoms often found during the
warmer months taken all together the
scent is most pleasing
I Endeavor to satisfy this black tea is
a mix of leaves from Southern firenay
with dried fruit rinds and flowers it's
Heavenly as the Blends you prepare
always are the chance to sit to sit the
TU Brew is one of the small choice that
gets me through each day
you're too kind Prince
somewhat related to
Dutch relieves I mentioned recently yes
of course you said that they would
produce a unique and distinctive flavor
if I recall
call correctly I have a lead on how one
might acquire such leaves I take it that
would interest you truly you're right
I'd love to sample it for myself
excellent the weight from fans or people
they spilled the tea
fancy tea talk
oh hello princess saline you look
radiant as ever thank you Chloe we have
some free time today
it was so like that's a good question
[\h__\h] you shut up your Pegasus to a
nearby tea Farm be thrilled mind you we
don't have that much free time I doubt
it would be like it was before if only I
could return to those days of wiling
away the hours with you princess saline
oh well let's do something else when
this war ends I'll take you wherever you
like as often as you like we'll visit
all the tea farms in the world
and we can pass the time taking in
beautiful landscapes while sipping
delicious tea now doesn't that sound
lovely
it does indeed wonderful idea Chloe I
shall hold you to it when the time comes
don't kiss and I will be happy to oblige
these two
[Music]
it's so pretty
okay
now let's see who Chihuahua with marf oh
we just broke up oh
we're just about the strongest person I
know we'll be friends forever how can I
be more never going past you can
accomplish great things if you let your
bonds with your friends become your
strengths awkward yeah
[Music]
we got so far and now
oh mercurius
uh that will be absolutely useless to us
[Music]
okay am I ready to go
or do some shopping
what would I be buying
thank you
now about the boutique
dried potatoes and gold for clothing and
accessories to wear around the Sawmill
wait this doesn't like change any of my
stats right is this just a visually
once made most successors can be worn by
anyone
progresses more items will become
available
how that doesn't even look so stupid
[Music]
no
insomnia that feels kind of like a waste
oh you can look at their casual clothes
here oh what does she look like
oh she changes completely like I feel
like for
for example for Celine I feel like she
just took off her like big skirt
well actually they were all kind of like
new clothes made inspired by their
original ones oh
oh killed
oh
wait can I zoom out there we go
[Music]
what's that
it's like a really fancy evening dress
[Music]
oh they all look kind of the same
depending on the gender though
[Music]
I like these that much more than their
actual clothes to be honest
I really like their normal clothes the
Casual ones
yeah
be well
[Music]
welcome welcome
what's this place the equipment needs to
tweak I can Hammer here's how the
Smoothie Works refining engraving and
exchanging trade materials and gold to
strengthen your weapons at the Smithy
improve or upgrade your weapons by
refining and Engraving them after an
alter a weapon by Engraving
it's with the power of an emblem each
emblem can be applied to one weapon at a
time
you can also exchange one type of
refining material for another
[Music]
um
oh okay I'll talk again one second
should I like do something here uh
[Music]
I don't know I have enough materials
liberation
there it is
[Music]
go with the strongest one for
plus two
[Music]
hmm
you're finding Liberation at least once
okay well there we go
um what about the other ones
I'm not sure
Liberation needs those upgrades
let's donate for chickens all right
let's go to dagger
uh
this one iron dagger I don't know like
better weapons for her that I get later
I guess it doesn't cost much so do this
one for now
sounds good what about engraving what's
that dude
[Music]
let's say I engrave it with the Rival
one
it raises
empty hit ever quit a lot of them but uh
what is the WT red when it actually gets
raised
[Music]
steel daggers and stuff like that okay
fun
[Music]
oh wait ah
so I can engrave it with like this one
for example even though I'm using the
rivals ring
or do I have to use
this one's all positive
yeah
okay well um
hell yeah what's exchanging
ah um
good for now thank you let me look at
this again thank you
rare set some frilled stuff Brown
spectacular milk
[Music]
or like I guess this is my change
options already
[Music]
huh wait did she always have to swim
solo did that come with the DLC too
[Music]
yeah
foreign
[Music]
just uh this one
so that's actually
pretty nice of them
but again I only say this when I'm up
here in my base camp right
ah
I wish I could see it on the battlefield
man
um
oh yeah she gets a ponytail with this
one this one gives her like ribbons
okay I'll wear this one out
there what about
oh
oh cute I like the big ribbon that's
cute
foreign
oh yeah you look good
with those glasses and what else I got
uh-huh
[Music]
now keep this one for you
what about my cutie Celine
oh look at her swimsuit which is like a
little lemon
squeeze her oh I love that one
ah this was cute too okay we'll go for
the rare apron let's see how about this
one
[Music]
why not single earring and
there's one ah
actually it are they all like kind of
looking the same
[Music]
yeah it's just color variations
I just realized
this one
[Music]
they're all the same
oh
she's got quite some squishy thighs
[Music]
okay somehow I really think this suits
her
I don't know why excuse me
those hip-hop dancer Vibes for some
reason
[Music]
she got the Pegasus dress
no don't have to change all of them I
guess you know what I really like you in
the Pegasus dress although that swimsuit
is looking banging on you
go for this window
um
[Music]
that works so well for you
cute oh cute
cute
well not hold on that's the first time
I'm seeing it in full body what she
normally wears she wears a long skirt
huh
I'm sorry someone someone has to wear in
a swimsuit
for testing
you can keep that one too and Vander
Vander
oh
this one and the rare vest really don't
change that much
it's both like kind of like a suit
I'll keep it
be well
the first time
[Music]
you know the two colored hair that works
really well
wow what a glow up
welcome
[Music]
okay can I sell something by the way do
I have anything that's like
sellable oh look at this
[Music]
I don't know what I would be selling I
guess I don't have anything any
valuables
[Music]
hahaha
okay
but uh who needs a bowl Marine
it's got a torch wondering
you might need a vulner in case you need
to heal yourself I thank you
[Music]
and oh she might not need the hammer
we're gonna switch it out and optimize
later
[Music]
I thank you
remember to donate what's that where do
come again I don't have any amiibos at
all not a single one
get better weapons you can get a bit of
extra cash for the Nations Cafe
in the cafe
uh I know
let me check
bulletin board of the cafe I completely
forgot about that I feel like that was
told to me before but where is that
bulletin board
hmm
this one
there it is donations what can I donate
if you support countries enough to raise
their donation levels they will reward
you with gifts oh
with high donation level country will
have more rare monsters that you can
earn in bonus gold or experience for
defeating
huh
a hibernation level also means you will
find more materials while exploring in
this country among other things
so right now I think we can only donate
to fareen
uh and I need 5 000 gold to get on to
the next level
sure wait
[Music]
oh it doesn't change anything and like
no no if I donate I can adopt the
chickens
that I couldn't adopt before
oh and a donkey apparently too but I've
never met a donkey
all right take my money take it off so
that I can have all the chickens in the
world
oh wow
what a harvest
oh and I get National clothing if I
donate it again five thousand no ten
thousand
wow that's a lot of money oof
should I go one more time but we're like
leaving fareen soon anyway so
um
I don't stay for now okay
okay
I think I'm ready to go
but by the way I want to change the
music I can't it's
not change the music but it's only one
song
I'm gonna get more songs
check that door
I should cook I should let him cook okay
one second
what is this
what the [\h__\h] am I what was behind this
door Nani
training schedule
[Music]
3xp but it's like doesn't take as much
time as those other battles that I
always do
[Music]
bloodborne elderly
click okay
in the arena you can have allies trained
to earn experience and raise Bond levels
instead of training an ally you choose
will spare with another Ally it costs
nothing but you can only go the few
times between battles oh
emblem training increases the bond
between an ally and an emblem correspond
fragments
[Music]
um wait so I got exp from this
then that should maybe let someone do it
who's like low level
[Music]
I am Boucheron Royal Knight of firenay
nice to meet you I'll be your partner
[Music]
I worked up a good sweat
that reminds me of something you know my
flight back
they took a completely different flight
route than usual
they completely like
they flew uh from Japan to the west
but uh they flew pretty much only over
ocean
um they flew on top of all the
continents
barely like almost never flew over any
land only over ocean
and do you know what I got
they flew over the north pole north from
the pole and they gave me
um a certificate like after a while like
around the end of the flight a lady a
flight attendant came by and she was
like did you already get this
certificate and I'm like what what so we
actually Flew Over the northern pole did
you notice I was like no it was not
awake I was sleeping for the whole
flight
but apparently yeah we went with the no
from fall and then got a certificate
which is like nothing special it's just
like
I guess kind of like a joke but it
really happened yeah yeah I flew over
the Norfolk pole and I got a movement
sticker from them
and I wonder if I was awake maybe I
would have seen something but it was a
Night Flight it was constantly dark so
um I don't think I would have seen
anything
how does did this remind you that
because of the auroras that happens in
cold places doesn't it this isn't Aurora
right
foreign
somewhere
I wonder if you go to the right place if
they're easy to catch
no right there it is
if it's easy to catch or if it's like a
RNG thing where the gacha is a line the
right up is a lie
[Music]
no no no from the reindeers but thin air
the one I took they claim that they are
uh Santa Claus's Airline
[Music]
hmm a bit of RNG I see them very often
where I live and that's cool
near the poles
let's do it again somebody said press a
while I'm doing it really does that do
anything
I love it too
impressive
should I really be here huh I am Vander
30 second Steward of the Dragon not fair
that hair up is not fair oh it looks
like a fighting game
potatoes
you still got the XP
he does does he get less when he loses
because this is not fair
[Music]
I'll give it another chance
let's try not to hurt each other okay
please not Bender again I'm Alfred Crown
Prince
[Music]
this has been an honor
Ed that's so mean another horsey guy
does he have a chance against anyone at
all
should I do this too
does this work
well this is what is it though
[Music]
not really okay
uh where's the exit
oh there's always so much to do
but I guess the fights really take a
long time too so
it's good to have
I think you might regret joining up now
yeah um they're like treating him that
well not on purpose but
welcome
please cook ah didn't in free houses uh
eating something help with something
like some stats were raised or
something like that is that a thing here
too
or the meals to eat with your allies oh
yeah if the meals prepared well your
allies will receive a Staples in the
next one
[Music]
nice then repeat allies to earn support
punch let's go let's the chef may pack
some leftovers for you oh you can take
this meal into Bella and use this as an
item to recover the HP nice
okay
[Music]
um
is a chef can I never eat with him
dining Partners
[Music]
I'm so biased again only going for the
cute girls
oh but is there also something that they
prefer
today
it's like but here it says likes is
there something they don't like because
ah yeah there was
okay it's not that hard to find
something they both like
oh
wait
peasant bread
and bread is this it
is this a typo
no I guess it's really peasant bread
because only bread
for the peasants
oh but I do need the ingredients for it
oh
oh Peach
Peach whoa that gives a lot of stat up
up up
[Music]
go for a peach cake
oh
does that help
putting a topping on it
[Music]
hey
first select every oh wait oh oh wait I
didn't realize I have to select this why
why what if I don't select it does it
fail
s here we go stop cooking let him cook
let's try not to waste Nature's Bounty
exactly thanks for letting us use you
ingredients
it turned out so well
I could cry
on pancakes though
such deliciousness for me
[Music]
proud lip smacking peach cake rank ass
I tried packing it up as a meal for you
thank you
[Music]
so she wants me
huh
that was easy and now it's already
daytime
[Music]
20 hp
oh hey
right a monastery was not floating
island but it did offer similarly
impressive View
all right since it's a new day
there's new items
[Music]
so this is the legendary Samuel huh
I'd better be on my best behavior let me
give you something
not the horse when you are don't worry
I'm not giving that to anyone you gave
me this to me you're unbelievably
generous Divine one I love you poor to
talk please now
oh I should have done that first
impressive work out there today yunaka
I got praise from the Divine One
thrilled really exaggerated it looks
like yours are in high demand
you must have left of the mercenary or
something right
um mercenary yeah you can tell I mean
obviously I've murked a time or two no
big deal I thought so with strength like
yours you must be pretty well known too
sure I mean yep people uh people know me
I'll bet some of our allies are well
acquainted with your reputation already
I'll have to ask around there must be
stories
that's no I mean could I ask you to
maybe not do that I love what why
because I lied a gun I've never been a
mercenary
compulsory liar I went with it
sorry I'm confused you asked me about my
past I panicked and just like always I
hid behind a lie sorry Divine one
you were only trying to praise me and I
just had to go and ruin it I'll take my
leave
well you know
she would have been two perfect
otherwise she needs like one big
negative trait about her
um
[Music]
but the good thing is if we give her a
negative trait like that
we get more points for giving her
positive traits
wait this is not a ttip ipg
[Music]
now what was it how does it work give
someone negative trait and then get
something good out of it
what's that again
anyone here who has something important
to tell me
stable for pets oh I never saw that
before where is that
[Music]
where's that item
yeah I need some complexity otherwise
it's too boring
get it
um
she wants
[Music]
no no just the golden one okay let me
move over here ah wait I know where the
stable is I don't need to go there
anyway
thank you
this is so chill today is so chill I
hope you guys are not bored I'm just
generally feeling more on the chill side
today
although the battles are definitely
very interesting for me very
challenging too very focused on those
all the time oh
oh I can let them out
need to go outside and then the free cat
is called free cat so the free cat must
be free
and
um one of the docos
[Music]
now
having fun
playing engage at the same time that's
the way to do it that's the way to not
fall behind
oh these vitamins look really weird
is that maybe just how their hair grows
although
if you look at the
than their feet
[Music]
and then how
um how the thighs look
it looks like the fives are that like
brown part is actually
some kind of fur too but it just has
like a
like a lower level of fur and then a
bigger level of fur
starting to grow there is that just how
their hair grows it's kind of weird but
I guess I shouldn't body shame them
author shame them all right what else
can I do at the stable
is that it
just chilling there
this is the stable right
[Music]
that's where I am I
no I didn't exercise yet
it's too real to me
I don't wanna little can guess I should
do it also I should talk to her that's
why I came here
living here once felt like an undeserved
blessing but have grown accustomed to it
now I love you
I really enjoyed our tea party today
thanks for inviting me saline the
pleasure is all mine Divine One our
conversation made for an excellent spice
over an already fine tea and the tea was
fine wasn't it that floral note it had
was almost unbelievably did they all
talk about it the leaves were grown in
firenay you know the delicate subtle
taste embodies
it is my utmost favorite yeah I've heard
the fairies prefer the Pastoral life
over any kind of open conflict that
really came through in this tea
there's a fierenese folk tale I think
you might find interesting take a shot
every time she's home to a spirit who
ensures happiness for The Virtuous for
thieves or Interlopers however the
spirit drives them off with mischievous
tricks
imagine driven off by the prankish
antics of a spirit
how effective a deterrent do you suppose
such a spirit really is
so it's a lovely it's the kind of
good-hearted tale that reflects the
Pyrenees character I think yes I like
having a leather
well then we must have tea together
again sometime Divine One
please I'm working oh okay you don't
have to participate in the game don't
worry
[Music]
I'll check out what the training is
about
huh
[Music]
what what's that house
records hole at the record tell you can
edit your profile card and review the
cards of others you can perform the same
actions via the reference menu though
you can only stage photo shoots in
outdoor parts of someone okay I don't
know sure about that
money
[Music]
is this worth doing guys
yeah yes
[Music]
not really oh thank God
a temporary stat buff
oh a stranger you can choose from Arena
each exercise plays differently and
affects the different stats try for
tough oh this ring fits
fit and Fire Emblem
what'll it be
canceled by accident yes
um Dex
[Music]
HP strength
hmm
I'll go with strength
push-ups are about timing stop the bar
at the perfect position ah right when it
speeds up it ends if you miss three
times do the specified number of
push-ups to complete the activity the
bar will get faster over time to stay
focused over here
to get fit how hard do you want to go uh
normal for now there's iron muscle
what
QP will help me out if he likes me I
don't know if he likes me that much yet
but why not will he also
distribute if he doesn't like me
keep it up
nice
[Music]
20. nice oh my God okay pretty good so
far and I'm actually playing for OBS
today oh
[Music]
nice don't ask me why I'm playing for
obese
hang in there
foreign
[Music]
looking good
nice
I can't mess up anymore hang in there
keep that you'll get there
man can I try again
[Music]
you won't get any further bonuses or
rewinds I'm gonna quit let's do this
again sometime
foreign
okay I can imagine 20 times
thanks to QP for trying to help out so
much
[Music]
killer thank you
yes
stop please oh my God gonna make me
blush why is that horse manure over here
let the horses out who who who let the
horses out
I'm gonna go in the Overworld now
[Music]
so you know
I win one more thing
uh inventory
why
[Music]
after I've select my finals during
battle okay okay
then I'll do that there now I finally
get it
oh a handex will be sure
[Music]
oh we can go left away and go straight
up oh we can go even further what where
the hell is that going
huh
what anyway soldiers or corrupted foes
sometimes go back to areas that you have
already cleared
you can return to these locations for
optional skirmishes aha I will do that
off screen completing skirmishes can
earn you experience and other rewards
like golden items
uh these ones
are optional though huh
oh
paralog for cute girl what about this
one
huh what what black screen
[Music]
divine paralog
oh that's DLC
[Music]
should I do it now can I not no
oh
this was long I think he's really hard
maybe not now
[Music]
okay okay
foreign
okay I'll do I guess this one
um
I hope it won't take too long
[Music]
wait was that it wasn't armor right what
what's your story what hand hand ax or
what was it called
[Music]
oh yeah there it is
oh what it says uh he only has one in
stock no problem that's exactly how many
I need
cannot use
hmm
oh wait because it's on the mini bow
sorry I got confused and
[Music]
now
begin chapter
[Music]
do we get another unit here
I wonder do we get a unit on every
parallelog
Rams I still haven't found her good luck
sorry boss the thief was too quick for
us we lost track of Where She Went we're
supposed to be the thieves you bums
don't get stolen from well she can't
have left this Fortress yet go catch her
no excuses yes boss boss
bad news
am I about to hear an excuse
there's a tough looking bunch headed
right for us our arms too typical how
much worse can today get whatever this
won't stop us either battle squads in
position and ready to move I want our
thieves in the treasury now once the
treasure is secure get to a safe place
you're so mad
[Music]
um
super heavy armor for thieves
oh
I'm sure no one will mind if I help
myself she sounds like Iron Man someone
talking
sounds panicked whoever they are
move your butts and get in position
she's cute
is there about to be a fight
she's defeated
ah
can you help me yes this is my best
option
chest can you believe the luck we're
having today
let's talking more stalking make sure
your gear is ready before things kick
off
every Fire Emblem has Anna this one way
too many things I make a clean getaway
that's a cute gimmick
Girls Talk the townsfolk told us about a
bandit base
and I'd say we found it I feel sorry for
all those poor villagers who had their
valuables stolen
precious keepsakes family heirlooms she
was the emergency
it looks like we're in for a fight
before that can happen
okay uh wait are we only four
no no no okay I guess the others are
just somewhere else
um
five
five uh
what's who why are you just level two
six all right switcheroo
and level nine
bring her
always bring the low levels that were
always on around the same level that
would be nice
but I need some of my stronger units too
so I'm gonna
keep it like this maybe
[Music]
wait
um
wait what if I do this then I have no ax
spider do I
yeah
why not bring at least one ax spider
you can ditch the kids he's not that
strong this one
which kid do you mean I got many kids
around here
Louie
ah
[Music]
we have all in the engage of UMC yeah
but it would be nice to have a normal
one around too
foreign
[Music]
yeah but I can't use that one all the
time
[Music]
we can try but
yeah okay
and also there you go optimize all
finally
here we go
[Music]
wait does she have
well don't worry can I give her give her
a vulneri somehow
uh
from this screen can I not give her any
items because next step is fight
on it
S screen okay
so go back
at least one would be good
on her I think just think
I think you know when she does that
skill that leaves her with one HP
oh wait we have so many monaries
I'm gonna take one of these
as well
unit selection is this now
and here we go
defeaton
and let's have me not defeated
okay I didn't check where everyone was
standing where are the others on the
other side
what ah all the way over here
eight units
okay I don't know if that was smart
um
plants
they kind of need like one bath dude
over here oh
I should have had one of them over on
the other side
can I yeah can I reset
[Music]
Auto Battle by the way
interesting
retry
[Music]
okay okay okay can I do the units
um placement no
um
[Music]
let's try again
how about Louie
you'll go over here and switch with
a
[Music]
h
let's see how long this one takes we're
at five hours stream time
I wish I could reach
they're gonna go at me
maybe they'll like go for different tips
at least I can attack
by Javelin that's quite a lot of damage
[Music]
kfp March
here
gotcha
later yes
oh
I think it's gonna be a quick one and
when the at the end
that dude is over here
but I have to open this chest right
I can't just go straight for him
that's your steward
let's go
[Music]
all right all right we might actually be
able to take this one down
[Music]
quickly leave the kid in the chest
all the people open it ah well she kind
of like free herself
hey there we go
for the Divine dragon
people open it so no rash
[Music]
I mean their feet
and level up maybe whatever you ask
[Music]
I live to serve
I don't know why really
what
somewhere else anyway
all flowers oh he chose The Wrong Enemy
oh oh they're going for Selena again
cool this time they hit
you need
oh [\h__\h] you look beautiful while you
lasted
so Lane might not be very bulky but damn
he can do some damage
[Music]
um
magic user
[Music]
I can do some decent damage too my
resolve is unchanged
oh I just realized
[Music]
she might want to take a bone around
here and her turn
is already pretty hot
[Music]
I think I'll lead with
her oh Shield Gambit
first long-range attacks do no damage
what
does that mean
well I mean first long range
range attacks oh that's from Dimitri
[Music]
oh
in the other in the enemy's turn
the first person that hits me for long
range well miss
huh
I see
not necessary right now
[Music]
oh well wait that's a lot of damage
woof
okay oh that's good
yes
[Music]
looking good
move on with him do we want to go to the
sky and he'll come to me
so we'll go this way
I'll stay here and I want to go too far
right now
and then like this
okay
somehow
with a range attack please no
please have mercy
yeah of course I was gonna heal
I was gonna heal
[Music]
oh
yeah
okay I'll go here
[Music]
bring her here
she shouldn't really be leading either
but
Point condition
[Music]
rip him
are you sure
engaged to everyone engage
okay to advance slowly
[Music]
why aren't you telling me to engage I
don't see what that does
[Music]
I see the Mage but
Maybe
maybe
this is looking bad
nine will be fine
[Music]
I want to see what happens
so I'll be going here
wasn't that much damage
that's all right
[Music]
that was rough too nothing happened on
this side
no one came for this team
interesting
now
uh wait
um
I will do what I must we will continue
to advance
[Music]
not going very far but
well
it's fine this one is he's just never
gonna come over
fine with me
[Music]
attack
big oops on the right side yeah
should I go in the Spiller
but I'll do way more damage on him
I'm so hard yeah
[Music]
oh he has a good item over there
I can reach him quite easily right now
[Music]
75 78
okay I'll go
for the item
a broken
peeps in the treasury will run away
with some Treasures well
if I if they run away do they just like
spawn away or do they walk all this way
because
I could still cast them maybe if they
take an item they walk
they run to the South okay well maybe
then I can still catch them when they're
on the on their way
[Music]
here until the end
okay I'll let him do that next turn
[Music]
yeah bit
and was effective against acts again
sword we don't have a sword fighter here
unfortunately and this [\h__\h] really
pisses me off I want to move away so he
can get me anymore
it's all danger zone better to
kill first
whatever you require
mmm
musukashi
[Music]
try like this
let's be careful
I think I'm all right
[Music]
uh
foreign
[Music]
I'll use that you're gonna come at her
probably but that's okay and then get
the kill
[Music]
drop your guard
noise crate winning
wasn't really necessary
and now and I mean I've locked up
everything but he's safe here
Mage can't reach him but if you close
your eyes
ignore reality oh a monster seal what's
that there's some fancy
[Music]
okay so where do they go south how did
they exit
I'll have to check where I am
the noise
what a workout
[Music]
class change class upgrade oh
thousand gold
item was just some money
holy [\h__\h]
you try you tried respect for that
Celine
That's Heavy Armor I need some matches
on that yeah
yeah
man everyone's bullying my Celine yeah
no Chloe why am I leading with the
weaker one what
it's not like I want to
post it
no oh
[Music]
I guess ah for that door here okay so I
looked down I'll catch him here and then
I go for the middle up
yeah okay
that works
[Music]
kind of difficult
because I want to use this magic to find
this dude
but everyone's in the way
I could move her back I've got to hang
on
[Music]
the Healer because she's not gonna do
any damage this round anyway
[Music]
um
and he can attack from here right
after I moved her
maybe I attack with her
from here and then I may move Louie over
here okay okay I think this sounds like
a plan unless unless the magic won't be
uh
oh it will actually not be I want to hit
kill
[Music]
okay let me see let me see let me see
although uh I could go for
[Music]
go for him then that should be enough of
a kill for a kill in combination with
the mage
and then with Louis I go for the sword
guy
[Music]
yeah yeah
oh [\h__\h] ah
yeah now I have the problem I wanted him
to attack from here this is
dangerous
it depends on how much damage Lily can
do not enough
then if he stays here he'll get hit by
the sword dude
[Music]
armor of a counter attack
and that's a problem too
[Music]
who knows
I have to redo something here
let's start from where
uh From This Moment
[Music]
um
Maybe
no on it
why does she not have a javelin thank
you
[Music]
heck
engage Chloe it's just like my fairy
tales
[Music]
it doesn't kill anyone I think oh never
mind she can take down the big guy
[Music]
my prayers are yeah
get her a javelin remind me next time
I won't let you do what you want I think
the redo was worth it
yeah yeah
[Music]
okay
however
these dudes seem like they want to go
for her next time
you have to
will she be protected if he's in front
of her
[Music]
see what I can do here first though with
the those two together can get him to
die
[Music]
quick change
all right I'll engage
um
but do you mean
[Music]
with the
staff
Dave
do I need to be engaged for that though
can she I guess she can't use it unless
she's engaged
[Music]
and I don't I don't need no
one engagement heels anyway you mean her
great sacrifice though right I don't
really wanna use that yet I think
well in that case if I'm gonna be
healing
then I guess I'll try to take down the
sword guy with
Louie and uh mermaid
and then heal with her
yeah I can use it
[Music]
thank you
a vape healer you don't see that every
day
[Music]
take a step back
because otherwise you can attack back
[Music]
now I'm gonna move here
and give him the
last hit
yeah
[Music]
was that sufficient the maze will kill
him
what you mean this mage
will kill Lily
[Music]
imagine that
but if I don't put him here then I'll go
for Chloe
[Music]
maybe he'll be fine
yeah he's a strong boy
oh let's let it happen
gotcha gotcha iron Jesus let's play pray
to the orange Jesus
let's get you out of the way
[Music]
that was a good session
yeah he got hit by the midge before and
he seemed okayish
if he gets hit by both then
[Music]
um
I don't know
[Music]
sword should be effective
I think I'll engage
emblem engage
[Music]
but even that doesn't kill
what but she looks so cool
[Music]
armor can be broken and I need Magic
the top of my hair
don't fear for me
[Music]
oh
yes you know it looks so cool
I will not forget it
spread out and look at all your options
and now finally we can put him in him in
the front
and then he'll run as fast as he can to
catch those feets
yeah how far can they go four you guys
said right four
[Music]
um
so that's where the thief went
[Music]
open
hey thief let go of the lid don't make
me work up a sweat
come on
thing to do now if I want to get out of
this oh time to show my skills what
you're gonna do
there was a child in there how do you
say that we have to hurry and rescue her
from these abandons how could you see
her on the corner oh yeah there's the
thief get her be careful if you think
you're gonna catch me that easily
thank you
she needs some magic
yes nobody open the door oh oh
that hurts
and the Mage goes for Louie okay split
and they both survived
oh
they have a Healer what the [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah no one died I'm also kind of
considering the big hill right now
[Music]
is it time already even if I use a big
hill now there's a charge over here
[Music]
talk to Anna click
um what is it so
I'm sensitive
happy time to engage Alfred to catch the
feet
oh
yeah it's uh he's faster than I thought
he was gonna be
I'm past the worst part of the chapter
oh
what was the worst part
plot armor she'll be okay but hey she
walked all the way over here
look look at her big smile
and
if I start attacking him well he still
run away
because I can reach him
and I can't attack him
[Music]
yes he will
oh but if I engage and I do the swoosh
and then I stand here then he can't oh
yeah yeah you guys are saying you know I
was thinking of it too now
my muscles are yours now then it might
have been destiny that we had Alfred on
this side of the map
[Music]
one strike will decide at all
landing on the horse just like in
medieval times
[Music]
in bed and kill the enemies record
it'll be fine we'll join together again
soon
okay he's gonna wait here how far can
she go oh wait
let's get off
y'all
uh what if I don't talk to her right now
can she give me like a minute to kill
the mob pop first
[Music]
okay
what's a little girl doing here ah this
is a bandit Fort Anna can do it no place
for children okay I can use it right
away to Bandit right so why don't you
you beat me safe well
I mean I could but it's a deal thanks a
million you might not think so but I'm
pretty handy in a fight let me help you
help me
sounds logical
makes a lot of sense to me all right we
talked to her and now she can
maybe I should have you you got it
who knows you might
[Music]
we might use them engagement
she's like she has like a carpet as her
cape
maybe she mistook
the word carpet and thought this is the
same as the cape so basically you can
use a cape as a carpet and the carpet is
a cape
[Music]
wait before I make decisions here
let me think about this side
this is almost kill interesting that's a
full kill
does he fight back
he doesn't
[Music]
all right
yeah I stopped using the Japanese
voiceovers
[Music]
listen in
I guess but I'm not sure if I'll keep it
like this yeah she took him out
[Music]
maybe we
will win just yet I'm not sure what
about the Mage what do we do about that
stupid ass Mage that one pisses me off
yep
[Music]
I attack first
so this works
[Music]
you were beautiful while you lasted oh
and there's no other enemies close by so
we can actually chill a little bit
[Music]
yo
I can heal one by one
um
well just casually here normally don't
need to waste my skill I feel wonderful
and another thing
look at there
but wait the other thing is in fairy
well which one this one he's not even
close to the door
you'll walk over here next turn and then
we'll kill him
we'll reach him just fine
we'll reach him
I see no issue here
hmm
I think we'll reach
worst case if I don't then I'll just
warp over with Celine
how does that sound
now I'll send her down
the volume
thank you
smart job
yeah
there you go there we go
and like next turn even he would only be
able to open the door but not walk
through it yet right so
um now what is he a thief
so only a punch could break him right
well then
I'll just first heel Chloe
oh that's a big help I'll see you in
Avon thank you
hello future kaito Kane let's go thank
you for starting the Vault here welcome
back how you doing
[Music]
I can't attack over there
this isn't so bad
Javelin oh thank God he does
[Music]
started
what a loser
my my shield was just way too big
oh wait I can't
even thousands prefer English for five
seconds since I want to stream while at
the gym
what you work out like eight hours a day
is the internet there is bad and I have
to watch it
144 feet so I can't read
all right so my swim is eight hours long
and you were at the gym the whole time
you work out all eight hours
oh
[Music]
making ATM proud
it's bubble chicken
super swell chicken
alright I'll Attack anyway I guess
oh but he attacks back with six
oh well
that's okay that's not that much
[Music]
though all too late now
um
I wish you could attack but he can't run
away anyway right he takes the steps he
opens the door and he stops right there
right
actually I can leave it to everyone I
could already go up here
[Music]
I only have one charge left so I'm gonna
go closer to the charge
[Music]
okay I have time
long time
um they're blocking the path uh
sword okay
[Music]
set full space and nearby spaces on fire
after coma
[Music]
try this
silver always at night
[Music]
please how are Blues in me lazy
first
[Music]
probably
no more attack is fine thank you but I
don't I don't want to see I want to see
this but but if I set the space that he
is on right now on fire then when I walk
through don't I take damage too
I'm my Slayer oh
foreign
[Music]
I'll let her wait up here
crowded here already actually I'm gonna
put him all the way up here too
um
huh
okay
okay and last but not least oh
it's a lot of damage
done I took my hand all the time
that's it hey
you are wasting all the potential
that's okay with me
playing like a champion this one's
pretty easy for me right now
having a good time
and you could access I can get to Anna
Maybe
if I do then I'll give it after though
I thought it's easy no have to it's only
easy right now because I'm already used
to it and I'm thinking fruit I'm
thinking for every turn being very smart
um
it is still hard mode they do a lot of
damage when they hit me you have seen
but so far I've been I've been staying
alive quite well
uh Universal 10 and up can use a Master
Channel you guys already told me change
into an advanced class makes your units
more powerful and boosting stats and
granting access to new weapons
and sales to change to a different type
of person at the same time
you can change classes in the inventory
menu okay cool thank you for now I'm
good
all right
this one
needs to be taken down
and then we can advance
[Music]
and she's really cute
beef with an ax too kind of cute not
gonna lie
all right
[Music]
hmm I could warp her
I'll wait this turn
but I'm gonna warp her next turn once
everyone else is also a bit closer
[Music]
no I mean I don't need the whole team
there I guess
already
[Music]
everyone's just waiting everyone's just
waiting
okay okay okay I think the rest of them
how do you just uh
I hear intern
I think I think I think I'm good
[Music]
it can't be counted well how lovely is
that
[Music]
see how far we can get I think I'm ready
to advance
with uh heavy armor right
Mitch
[Music]
so close
not close enough to attack himself but
he would be attacked though she'll what
about
um
[Music]
who else uh
should I take this one down with the
warp
you know what
sounds like a good choice
emblem engage
[Music]
a bomb
here we go
no more painting for you I can't
activate yourself
[Music]
surprise Beach
that is such a crazy attack man
[Music]
well
uh Magic user
if you want to hit with Alfred damn
yeah
85 90.
[Music]
well let's go for that
I think you get more confident yeah it's
already like much better than how it
felt
um
the day before yesterday
in the first part
I already feel like I'm really used to
it
[Music]
quite the quick development
hmm
Louis is a little bit left behind again
that's okay
we all have those moments
good [\h__\h]
you always learn and improve how fast
thank you gamer chill yeah you will be
final hard from now on yeah after the
last episode I was quite intimidated
but now
I'm good I'm good will he come for me he
will not walk away from this movie A she
this is a girl sorry
but I'm wondering if I should go to the
science first but we have like a big
team
right here so
[Music]
um
chapter five was also one of the hardest
ones it is what
[Music]
now if I don't rush then
the hardest spot and they still give me
that
time uh return thingy so we're good
[Music]
well I'm really not sure the gold for
one of the side mobs
what will happen at the middle one
foreign
[Music]
well they're all ax users
you're in a good group now hell yeah
a lot of Fire Emblem games have at least
one chapter in the early game that
Frozen NASA's challenge is playing as
well we have limited office to health as
well
sound purpose
[Music]
go
I could have still waited one more turn
for everyone to reach but
be honest
[Music]
I think I'm ready to move
you know
and this one she will really not attack
me even though I stand like right in
front of her down
[Music]
quite some balls
now this I don't like
so I'll stay here
[Music]
well it's very small range is that light
also is is he poisoned
is that what that means
but is uh doesn't mean that they take
like dot damage right right what am I
what oh I already moved him
well it was just in Shadows
[Music]
oh here we go
more damage okay
[Music]
we'll get through this
unfortunately
kiwawa cannot reach this dude
so close
oh but this is a wanted killed
the yeah
[Music]
why don't you believe me
follow me
she's so pee I love her so much
these units really grow on me I'm gonna
struggle to like
choose my units that I'll use later on
when we have so many more choices and
I'm already so like emotionally attached
to all of these sick ass units
how am I gonna be able to choose maybe I
should turn on classic to lose some of
them and then
I have the choice but to say goodbye
well that's kind of cruel though isn't
it
[Music]
yeah yeah
how do you guys decide
and then you want to use everyone to
keep the levels balanced eventually you
will just have to decide
like a certain amount of characters that
you'll just won't bother with because
you can't keep everyone's level up high
[Music]
that's why you play classic they die and
you don't have to decide yeah first I
was thinking like yeah bye
I'm gonna run out of units
but looking at this now I guess it's not
that especially if you play on easy with
classic then it's not that
um much of a problem
running out of units
[Music]
oh wait I didn't use these at all [\h__\h]
but she has her
engagement ready
I guess we'll just have to do it without
Maybe
[Music]
unless you lose your favorite yes but
then used to rewind the time and all is
good
oh actually we're not bad but
I don't know if he'll survive the
counter
well
oh that's strong
[Music]
damn you for playing us for fools oh
you'll never get here
happened
time to finish the job
another kill for me
[Music]
they did hit me but
I didn't think that I would get rid of
the first HP bar so quickly and now
she's poisoned
[Music]
time to build some pressure
foreign
[Music]
whoever I don't know who should Target
though
[Music]
it's gonna go for you now
I think someone will die
at least one person will die
down to one
yeah
[Music]
I don't need to worry about it that's
okay
oh
still had him but unfortunately
he's a little bit too far away
better keep him somewhere in the back
then
I'll I'll put her as an option maybe I
feel like she's more likely to survive a
hit because she's full of Health
[Music]
y
who was supposed to heal
him
[Music]
the mage
they prioritize breaking
and they would go for her right
give her the options like here here was
a platter of options
those whoever I don't really care
maybe she misses oh she goes for Alfred
wow that's okay I don't need the EXP
he's already so high level
[Music]
I didn't train hard enough after all
sorry
for now
sometimes sacrifices are necessary
appreciate it though like I really do
[Music]
lend me your strength
don't hold this against me
laughs
[Music]
I guess to you first for us
I was really cool
noise
thank you Fire Emblem free houses for
your help
Celine MVP I agree I totally agree 100
agree
well how long did that take me
almost an hour I think
didn't I start when it was like five
hours in
here's hoping the local authorities will
keep these bandits from causing any more
trouble they all just take so long
[Music]
really strong huh do you have room on
your team for me if you want to join us
I should warn you our battles will be
much more grueling than that pretty
strong be placing yourself in danger
[Music]
what
I can take care of myself guaranteed
besides I've got nothing better to do
not until I figure out where my family
went oh you lost your family
lonely on the road
s or paths will cross someday what
should she be if that's what you want I
have no objections I'm the Divine Dragon
looking forward to working with you hang
on what you were the Divine Dragon my
snail
oh and the name is Anna but you can call
me lady Anna pleasure to be in business
with you
excuse me why Lady Anna did I miss
something does she have something Royal
in her
Ojos
[Music]
looks like she's wearing a freaking
carpet as her cape
haha they copied the house tonight
maybe she deserves the title because
she's in every freaking Fire Emblem game
maybe that's why
thanks Anna song yeah
broiling
[Music]
read
what did you say what did you say little
[\h__\h]
sorry lady [\h__\h]
haha
.com
like a hot hot dog
[Music]
huh
we need one more over here
it's nice that you can explore the area
after you
killed every single body
in here
and I said all the corpses are removed
already so we can enjoy it freely
so anyone else who wanted to talk to me
doesn't seem like it but wait animals
animals
hmm
ah there it is
[Music]
I wonder how much longer I should play
today it's 10 p.m now
we need to cook food
um
[Music]
I do also feel like I need to read super
chats from this stream
but we didn't progress much in the main
story I'll do one more but we'll have to
link
hurry again
eh might be a good place to call I feel
like we didn't make progress till
starting wise was it only like side
stuff it feels like
or what what what what what what what
main story was what what did we get
hmm
[Music]
yeah I did I don't feel like I did a lot
but at the same time it was mostly
parallels
[Music]
chapter
yeah
last time I did 5
that shots are kind of long as cute
girls in your choice yes
maybe I should stop now hmm
and then read some super chattels and
then cook
gotta make foof
is this the legendary I guess I'd better
be on my best behavior
no it's good you can do whatever the
hell you want I will give you for
anything
this place is filled with power it's
from you isn't it good you're not got an
eye on your side or whatever she said
because it went way too fast
hi Peppers this is all pooper
[Music]
okay it's not just poop
oh
oh does it depend on what animals I have
out there they will produce different
items
[Music]
um
wonderful
[Music]
what's that
that horse
is
whiter than
[Music]
I don't even know what I
mean why are you gonna ghost
this horse must have seen a ghost or
this hose this [\h__\h] hose this horse
looks like someone
painted it with white paint which is
animal abuse so please don't do that
that's worse
what the hell you're a fight for Sore
Eyes
I mean there's white horses but that's
like
what
[Music]
super white
I'm not talking call Colgate I'm talking
like pure white
[Music]
apples it's orange trees dough isn't it
grapes
if someone's trolling me someone's
trying to confuse me
all of those are orange trees it makes
absolutely no sense
Michelle White no that looked even
whiter than actual white and that's
quite difficult to achieve
foreign
maybe it was missing it's
color
maybe next day when I visit that horse
it will suddenly be
a brown horse
texture was just lost somewhere
it seems like I forgot something there
there we go just the same poop again
but maybe this poop is special if it's
from the White Horse and the poop might
also be white who knows
[Music]
but I guess I will leave it here
we are in
what chapter chapter seven so
chapter wise I guess we didn't make that
much progress but I also wouldn't say we
we didn't
the thing is also last time I didn't
read super chats now this time I want to
read them
[Music]
because
down and gets all that inside of the
honey toast really
flavor
[Music]
and gouda wrote me
you know the karaoke we went to of
course was again the one with the honey
toast
because I you know I was like we can eat
honey toast all the time and she hasn't
had it yet so we went there and we had
the honey toast but we only
um see I wasn't sure which flavor she
would like the most so I got those small
Samplers again
um but she said to me right now that we
should go again to the karaoke and get
the the big honey toast and I said yeah
that's a good idea because I think the
big ones taste even better I tried the
small one several times now and the big
ones there's just maybe you heard what I
was writing but the
you know inside it's like a big block of
bread right and inside it's like cut
into cubes
and I don't think it's just honey even
though it's called honey toast but
there's something that's just like
drips into all the insides of the toast
and it gets it really sweet and yummy
it's so good
[Music]
so okay I guess we're gonna go karaoke
Again karaoke and yummy food
thing me and
um I'm actually really glad Koda enjoyed
it so much because remember when I went
with um
final fails
didn't sing that much I guess they were
not that much into karaoke I know they
were kind of on the shy side
[Music]
foreign
should bring Callie along Callie been
Kelly good on me might be the most into
karaoke out of myth members
[Music]
will Emma enjoy karaoke
good question
we should test it out too
aren't this [\h__\h] did she go to karaoke
and her say did she say anything
because she wasn't part of the one that
we went to she wasn't there yet
[Music]
uh I think she might be shy but I think
it was like among Miss members
look she would open up and sing a lot
too
I don't think she would feel shy
[Music]
foreign
did I forget some tangent stories oh
there are definitely still some tangent
stories yeah
um
[Music]
having you I'm waiting for specific one
aren't you
[Music]
spring everyone yeah yeah
I know
okay okay okay
let me let me unleash that but it's a
long time that's a long tangent though
um
[Music]
foreign
don't forget to give Carl a javelin and
promote Celine
uh it promotes Celine uh what can I do
that now how how how how how
do you mean promote Celine how do I do
that
[Music]
foreign
class all you need to start with innate
proficiencies units have the strongest
potential in those areas
units can acquire new proficiencies from
emblems this allows them to change to
any class
the dab what's that
magic willing swords woman who can cut
through enemy Mages oh
she's also capable of willing staves
that's what we're going for
unique class for her oh
it's fine what does a change in stance
um
oh it's all just like kind of plus one
[Music]
oh fierce
from a noble till of the dam how do you
say that with them
there is power building up in me I can
fail
oh yeah
nice can anyone else do it or do I need
a like more of those Master Seals huh
[Music]
we already got
lots of them
hmm
okay so I'll save again
now
you need to promote it early on FB has
always had early promotes strategy
and more sales than I need more sales
can I buy them
poopy dress yeah it's cute
she's like a big jellyfish
oh they sold for Hefty gold
all right we'll take a look next time
[Music]
um
foreign
no more
see I also don't want to drag it out too
much because
even if I Fire Emblem engage engage if I
cooked too late then I will sleep too
late and you know
this one
is what I'm doing tomorrow early on and
then the member stream later on so I
want to be fit
um
[Music]
okay let's go to my office
uh
here I am
I still have the Fire Emblem music in my
head
oh Dragon child
oh that's what my character is at the
moment
showing me classes right now
let me let me turn it off
okay
um
excellent games for today boss yeah I
think I really wasn't bad tell me tell
me
I think that was pretty good yesterday
on the day before yesterday I saw it was
way more Reckless and made lots of
oopsies
are they really good
thank you
guys wow look at all the praise all the
compliments yay
thank you well
question
oh not so many mistakes this time and in
the end everything was always very
salvageable right
so everybody
knows good calls many choices of your
own yeah
great thank you so potato time is now
and what bgm should we use
foreign
[Music]
so we're staying on for super sense if
you want me to keep it on
you like it um
I'll be uh what's her actual name Alia
or whatever for you tonight
I'll be someone else
um
the shoes stay on this sucks no the belt
stays on just the belt
mmm
BTM I want a new one
I have like this is like looking into my
closet of clothes and I say like a
million clothes and when I say is oh
I have nothing to wear
and
um
kind of I want one of those like
um calm evening Animal Crossing bgms
let me go on all your stuff it's been a
while I can go song shopping I've got a
um
subscription after all
I can get as many as I want
so much
um
not sure how to describe it
I'll just type yeah
Animal Crossing Loop
[Music]
um
which one did I not hear before also let
me
make it so that you hear it here
foreign
yesterday Sparks was chill I want
something
oh there's not much Choice when I type
in Animal Crossing
about this one have I heard this one
before
oh it's dark
not logged in
oh it looks like I'm not looking
stuck
does that really feel like
uh Animal Crossing to you
foreign
[Music]
I'm not logged in
they say that it's beautiful it's music
in my ears
well I'll check again on some morning
[Music]
ah nothing what if I just go for soccer
gym
hmm
wow
[Music]
welcome to my church
you are now part of the kfp cult
please rip out a feather
and place it on the altar
[Music]
now please proceed to rip another
feather
and give it to me
and now pray
[Music]
there's so many of these healing ones
what the [\h__\h] what's this
[Music]
foreign
how did I not find this one before
what a banger I'm downloading this one
not for now but
damn
I want something more calm right now
what's this
[Music]
Ohio
bgm sagashi
[Music]
let me skip some part
oh
I love it let me download that one too
oh what about this one
on this one
oh what's up
oh oh I want that now
or it doesn't Loop
let me type in
wasanoba
[Music]
thank you
perfect Maldives we gym yeah
I'm just ah
you can't just you cannot go wrong with
Bossa Nova
there's one that's titled A Bossa Nova
track that sounds like
uh and every day Bossa Nova tried it
sounds like a girl is failing at cooking
uh-huh
[Music]
she doesn't seem to be failing
foreign
[Music]
just helping out Google
what's this oh
this one is with a guitar
[Music]
oh this one doesn't Loop
I can see it
because you can kind of see like
the track visuals I don't know how to
explain it
where were
[Music]
I got what I need
let me throw it in VLC
please don't burst my eardrums
oh no we good
oh but wait it doesn't show up on
desktop audio
[Music]
why not
oh there we go
wait is that really the one I wanted no
it's not
sorry one one there's one
I want the bossa nova right now
thank you Genie
have fun with work hope it goes well
don't worry you're just missing the
Super Chat raining
it's not a big deal
all right so put you at the time
supercharger time
[Music]
I did not download the church one
um
but today is the 26th
so should start
okay or somewhere oh oh there it is
there it is
okay are you guys ready it's only from
this stream oh my God I can't believe
we're actually like oh oopsy
actually caught up and I don't need to
read the ones from ages ago and I only
need to ask you uh remember where I need
to continue reading
yeah I tried my best yesterday to
finally get it done
I kill him
[Music]
here we go
okay more fine Bloom next week
um I think off screen I might do
[Music]
something
I don't know what what can I do
was there something I can ah that one
with the the new icon that they showed I
can do the Skirmish that one yeah
I'll do that then
[Music]
fellow thank you one out of 52 huh
what
you don't mean one out of five
I hope it's not one out of 52.
you make mistake
thank you
oh 50 memberships that's how you that's
how you raise those numbers 50.
thank you
look at all those lucky chickens
surprise there even is 50 non-members in
the chat
Chad
so much damn
oh here we go
that makes a lot of sense stuff I want
to send you those new recruits hopefully
they will be uh of use for the Divine
Phoenix love you Daniel oh thank you
thank you still
damn that's crazy is that like do I owe
you a kiss now like what is the
equivalent of that I feel like I
definitely owe you a kiss
one membership is like five dollars
right
five times
10 is 15.
so five times twenty is hundred
and then
so is it like 250
did I do the math right let's go
fellow thank you let me read the first
part of that too right now before I
forget later
your amazing Chihuahua I loved watching
your collabs in Japan really and now we
get a chance to hear about more awesome
things that happened although you were
very busy today I hope you were able to
get some rest as well
thank you Islamic fellow
not much rest actually I got some
well I don't tell you uh unlike
um the second to last day I think I got
a massage because I was so in pain from
the dancing like I had
insanely sore muscles I guess and just
in general pain pain pain
I got I went to a massage
and that was one of the most
lamest most terrible massages I've ever
had and it was just weird in general I
think I've had this before well I told
you about a massage
a long time ago where it all they did
was just like
poke one spot with a finger
and wait
for like five minutes and then poke
another spot
you know
I mean
it's called tsuba in Japanese I guess
but
yeah it wasn't even strongly poking it
was just really lightly poking and that
happened before I think I told you about
before and then this time it seems like
uh I got the the Poke gotcha again
mm-hmm
sounds very soil science that's what I
think like he would was a dude it was
kind of like first funny and nice in the
beginning but then
it got just it was it was weird like I
thought maybe he would do it for 10
minutes and then I I thought okay 10
minutes I can tolerate of this stupid
[\h__\h]
but
um so he would poke not even poke that
didn't even feel like poking he would
just lay a finger on top of for example
um between my thumb and my
uh the the UV next to it there's just
like you know that space there
and angle
so he would put a finger there
and maybe a finger on a hip
couldn't even feel it
yeah and then just wait for like five
minutes
and then move it slightly wait for
another five to ten minutes and then
just time kept on passing and I was
wondering when is he finally gonna do
something that I can notice
and sometimes like after 20 minutes or
half an hour
he would say okay let's get up
this should have helped a lot now
and then
he's like okay like try bending for
example doesn't it feel so much better
and I'm like
I'm gonna lie I'm sorry no nothing
nothing
absolutely no difference
so he's like yeah that's weird
let's try again so
I'm like starting to get pissed because
I feel like I'm getting scammed
but yeah then he does it like on my toes
and just goes on and on and I I'm like
what the [\h__\h]
this must have been going on for ages
now is he never gonna like what then
after 10 minutes he's like stand up
again
well now it must have changed right and
I'm like
I don't know no no no
nothing
you can't just like get rid of my
chronic pain by slightly touching me for
20 minutes with a finger what the hell
and then I was getting really pissed and
I think he noticed
so and this was supposed to be a one
hour massage I think and after 15
minutes I I'm not lying after 15 minutes
he said all right I guess it's not
helping for you so I'm gonna gonna do a
normal massage now
I'm like okay [\h__\h] finally but uh I
only have like 10 minutes left this is
such a waste
and then I think because he noticed how
pissed I was he also extended the time a
little bit he said
yeah I'll give you some extra time
so I got maybe like 20
15 or 20 extra minutes
on the clock
yeah
how much was the massage
a normal price you know but
it was very very very very very
disappointed because I was just angry
the whole massage
um through
and didn't feel any better afterwards
[Music]
um
could you leave a bad review I kind of
wanted to
but I don't know
hello if I do that then I feel like the
the guy will know it was me who left the
review it's not like he can haunt me or
anything but
um
you're gonna massage before that and it
was fine not at that place no
I've been to a million massages and
something like this happened to me once
before
where a massage therapist would just
really just lay a finger really slightly
Softly
on me and
expect a miracle to happen maybe they
think it would work with
a non-austrian
cool is too nice and cannot directly say
no this ain't working and we'll just be
like yeah not not yeah thanks I guess
no never tried acupuncture that's one
thing I never tried
um
yeah but I was so mad because I didn't
have time to get another massage before
my flight before I would leave
and I didn't want to be in so much pain
for the flight you know
oh well I'm almost in pain so whatever
useless are you sure I've heard good
things about acupuncture
oh yeah I do want to give it a try
sometime
so streaming during my lunch hour yeah
oh oh
anyway I wanted to say one more time
thank you so much Slavic family of all
the memberships and the support thank
you I guess I attached it into the
massage because you were saying you
hoped I got some rest wow wow wow it
wasn't very restful but it was so much
fun the whole stay next time I think
I'll have a less stressful schedule
I already got so much done
previously so yeah
thank you
[Music]
big kisses to you
thank you soon from the bottom of my
coconut
yeah thanks to you tomorrow the member
stream
we'll have a lot of newcomers if they're
interested in coming by
[Music]
the ones who just got the membership
gifted I
demand you to come to the member stream
two
I think it's a lot
the Lord you gotta come
oh
what time it's in my schedule and the
schedule is both on Twitter and on my
community post
check it out check it out
I should retweet the schedule or just
pin it but I also want the songs pinned
let me
let me retweet my schedule
so it's at the top
retweet it
imagine being a member what do you mean
you're like a proud member
don't say that
this is the second time in a row YouTube
has hidden your final stream from my
Subs page
have you guys done
guys know your subs page
like
um
I see it shows up for me okay okay
am I a member I just gotta check right
make sure
it's still there you need that batch
a placeholder often doesn't show up
oh that's a thing that often happens
once I'm live they normally show up
often though before it's live
it's just hidden which
kind of sucks
but that's why you guys should be
following me on Twitter so that you
don't miss out on these kind of things
because YouTube has a lot of shenanigans
going on well Twitter nowadays too but
maybe if you're following me on both
then the shenanigans balance each other
out and cover one covers for another's
shortcomings hopefully
hmm yeah
okay let's read some super chats a
cruise donkey shin
and that could strayed away with the
rainbow thank you I sent you my episode
20 and final reviews as a tweet on the
Gilma Wawa
#you mean oh it will save you some Super
Chat reading time and it will spare chat
from not from not doing what I'm talking
about yeah
[Music]
you know they don't watch gamer girls
because they don't get it they just
wouldn't get it but duckhood you have
opened your heart for it and you now get
it
yes
yes cultured chicken
no need to respond enjoy them whenever
you have time well thank you thank you
for reading all my other camel Girls
season one Impressions I had fun hearing
your thoughts on my thoughts it was like
getting a waterline for a show that
normally wouldn't get one and there you
go it's a great show though and I'll
keep watching on my own yeah foreign
girls comments now they don't need to
put up with it I need to put up with it
and I really enjoyed putting up with it
try to ask Kian an occasional question
related to the episode to keep things
interesting and her answers were always
fun hey
good strategy
you're the best by ownership thank you
for your recommendations interactions
and your hard work on and off stream it
is all appreciated so much
you're so sweet I'm so glad you you know
didn't feel like watching camel girls
would be too cringe or something like
that nah you are open for it
thank you very much
I will open that
Gilmore what was it Gemma Waba
right away so I don't forget it later
there it is
okay
your header is uh my map of America
nice
seems like you have completely accepted
it as
the actual official map
as it should be
as it should be thank you Douglas for
everything your sweet support really
means a lot to me thank you
[Music]
have a nice evening hopefully and I'll
see you tomorrow
I think probably thank you
foreign
whoa oh a meet-up happening in Japan
that's sweet
um
enjoy ttkfp
.com
thank you for the red pink Super Chat
last month I got a raise at work oh so
shared with my ocean this month because
last one I treated myself with steam
deck ah
which one
which version
thank you as always for your hard work
and being lovely Phoenix good luck with
Fire Emblem
thank you which one did you get the
middle one oh I think I also got the
middle one
matching
so what do you play on the steam deck so
far
inspire me
no you still didn't get the tall
attention
what are we doing in my Mr Moon I don't
know
mostly racing games oh I see
I think I pulled up the members stream
reservation after
um I wake up so I'll decide after I wake
up
it will not be a movie Watcher long
so no need for you guys to prepare
anything
yeah no I haven't watched anyone is it
already out I remember when I was like
waiting for someone in Shibuya I saw a
big
advertisement of it
looked really cool
it's airing right now
free episodes
already what
[Music]
the [\h__\h]
it that would probably be 5 A.M jstm
um
I didn't know I don't know either what
what why is everyone delayed actually I
was told that in Japan
a couple of days ago
it was like or maybe in Tokyo only I
don't know but
the sea thing was officially
acknowledged uh to be on the same level
as a normal cold
so a lot of restrictions have apparently
been
loosened
so but maybe there's a lot of people got
sick who were supposed to animate the
anime or so
um
well I don't know what's going on but oh
well I guess
I'll watch it maybe eventually someday
has it been good have the three episodes
been good at least
foreign
can stand in for her in exchange Ohio
it's good
I liked it
I like them just near but animated
let's see
do they use a lot of free Dido
or is it still mostly 2D
or is it 2B
they do use a lot of 3D yeah
for the flying stuff oh
nice one hey
high five nice
first episode was the one-on-one copy
but the rest is a little different
one more copy to the game
[Music]
I'll hold it anyway
um
thank you enjoy your steam deck and
thank you for sharing your race with me
it's an honor thank you
I like the bonus too thanks for those
jokes they're not really funny but
they're cute
[Music]
do you have a favorite Lord of the Rings
character uh you must be new here yes
Sam wise country
I think and
we also Kim Lee
um
yeah but I love Sam
hmm
such a sweetheart game 8910
special costume for idle guard if you
unlock a certain ammo before
I don't think I got that
Sonic Master 2008 thanks for the pinky
hi Daniel I've been having fun watching
your streams and I'll be about as much
as I can
I got my Fe engage Divine Edition today
oh
to find a dish is that like the
collector's edition
so hyped about two weeks ago was my
birthday so is it possible to ask for a
Beverly's birthday it was very late but
Happy New Year no problem
probably New Year to you first of all
your school in the
coming in the New Year in the current
Year and happy belated birthday
two weeks ago but if you think about it
every day is a birthday otherwise it
would just be your birth year in my
opinion but whatever
congratulations Sonic Master yay
so much to celebrate at once
thank you for supporting me and watching
my final
names even though you need to play the
game yourself but hopefully you're
playing it on the side you got a couple
of days now because I won't be playing
until next week so
you've got some time to catch up make
the most of it
art book wow nice
who wouldn't like an art book from Mika
mama
way ahead of me oh nice
chapter 23.
damn
respect oh you're so fast
are you playing on easy
David
thank you
uh foreign
[Music]
oh
yeah I'm I'm indecisive about which dub
to use now for lockdown thank you
I hate
whichever voice I heard second I didn't
I didn't at all
your boy Stephen Adams Danke Schoen
thanks for the sneeze chats everybody
[Music]
foreign
thank you
Elio
Leo also sending a rainbow
thank you
hi attention today
second birthday at kfp
I'm glad I can celebrate with you and
kfb I'm sorry I only can send birthday
Super Chat for you but I'll always
support you even if I can only watch the
VOD even that I always open new stream
as a sleeping as always gives me a good
night's sleep I always want to thank you
for sparking my life your personality
your everything always always inspires
me a lot so this time I wish you to stay
healthy Hope on my third birthday you
won't get sick again
okay if we won't get sick too and I wish
my one and only also janma
you can eat well and sleep well
and
just kidding you know that the Phoenix
Empress is the one and only ocean for US
ah close
very close to going to the usual room
here
thank you can you say for my birthday
wish also can I get an employee number
of course
all right employee number
hmm
260 rows
no particular meaning
it's written in my documents like this
I can't help it 260.
um write it down write it down and now
[Music]
the young one
so
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I totally butchered it I'm sorry close
enough
I wonder what I actually said
because
depending on the pronunciation it could
have been a different word right
what did I say
did I say something else
and how little sense does it make
trying to say
well then I hope that works for you Leo
uh again happy birthday
thank you so much for the support and
don't worry about not being able to send
my new super chats that's okay
yeah you don't have to send any at all
but thank you for the support
and I hope you had a lovely birthday
and hope you can continue supporting
kiwawa forever so that in the third
birthday next year
I can talk to you again
[Music]
hope to have you around for a long time
congratulations
mwah
Hatsune
Captain meow Duncan for the red super
chat
before it's actually actually hurting I
can't talk
foreign
[Music]
sometimes
just a little bit
or lay only a small one
I'm okay
try to not speak
oh yes I want to play Magic
I'm cool peaceful
[Music]
thank you for the right to protect
Captain meal
happy Luna New Year channel here is the
lies
this see
it is a bit late because my back didn't
let me send the Super Chat oh
evil Bank
January is a crazy month for me and it's
my third birthday with Carefree oh
another birthday
what hope you have a wonderful year of
pickle ah yes it's a year of the rabbits
all those nice coincidences it seems
like everything's going so well
foreign
she's on a roll damn
Jessica
year of the pickle
I hope year of the chicken or Phoenix
can come eventually
but thank you so much for the Red
Envelope I'll take it gladly
unfortunately I can't give you one back
but I'll try to give you my streams in
return so please take them please be
there or be square
and I wish you a lovely birthday
happy birthday to you
happy birthday captain meow happy
birthday to you
[Music]
in nine years that's
chicken did it happen recently or why is
it so long ago long to go
cheers
that's still too much time
uh
[\h__\h] animals on there thirteen
watching Santa Claus for your comeback
don't worry maybe it won't be that bad
for you because I'll be streaming at
different times like mixed times
foreign
twelve
well at least I am
like some animal out of those but I'm
not really
but that's the closest I guess
fire rooster was in 2017. wait what does
a fire rooster
specifically a fire rooster
huh
foreign
anything
oh I should be just a shape-shifter yeah
and then every year is my year
I did I'm Zoo so I'm basically a
shape-shifter
that's what I am
you're right
um
thank you Captain meow meow
[Music]
then I hope you're happy
and healthy
but as long as you're part of kfp
I think one can only be happy and
healthy hmm
Tucker Tech thank you for the red super
chat sorry low energy right now
warfund donations
for a Divine Phoenix made a year of the
rabbit find you well
why now I'm looking forward to all the
whole life to all that whole life has to
offer and I'm happy to happy that you
were able to go to Japan and meet so
many colleagues it's good to be home
though isn't it it really is
I'm so glad to be back I wish I could
stay longer but at the same time you
know as I told you I also want to go
back because now good and Inna are there
um yeah once I want myth to assemble
um
I wanna like show them some things
and hang with them you know but but I
also need my alone time and right now
I'm taking as much as possible of that
just don't meet anyone be alone as much
as I can
yeah cat time desperately need the cat
time
oh I hear smoothie in the distance wow
wow mental color
now
well it's getting closer I think
well
until she's so far
I'm so tired
why am I so tired
oh
anyway thank you for understanding
I'm really glad that kfb can be so
understanding
I appreciate it I'll be going back soon
but as I said hi Sylvie I promise I'll
do my best to stream more next time
and I think I will
have no issue streaming next time so
it will be not that much different from
when I stream in Austria I think
um
thank you happy year of the rabbit to
YouTube well let's just say it's the
hero of the kiwawa
[Music]
I'm on Earth
thank you oh my god smoothie just
suddenly jumped up here you wanna chill
with me falling asleep
this movie is
taking her spot
cold ears you have to warm the ears
So Soft by the way I did I did dream of
gura
and I dreamed of
pickle Miko because they is there a song
out now
that tickle
27 so
so many whole life members showing up in
my dream
ah tomorrow
oh yeah bye
now
[Music]
I think they showed up because
yeah
because of the song like kind of like
putting that in my brain
David wait they were wearing maid
outfits
yeah
for some reason they were like
cosplaying as mates
was kind of a part of a different
section of my dream
really where
you kind of make a big deal out of it
okay but we were having I guess a
sleepover and we were sleeping in the
same bed
and we were kind of spooning
don't make a big deal out of it okay
It was friendly spooning
[Laughter]
I played it myself either
I don't know why
it's wholesome okay it's Tity
It was friendly spooky
what am I supposed to do I can't change
what I dream
I think it was just because I was so
happy about interacting so much with
good all these days
which I really am okay
got so happy I dreamed about her
don't make it weird
now
um
I don't ears down cushion
and some Tracy Duncan
Ellie Smith thank you for the pinky
you did oh but it's day two
okay well I got accepted to see the day
two concert I finally get to see you and
only Glory I can't wait
uh Ellie are you here
oh well I have to tell you something
I don't think I'm part of day two
oh do you mean The Deco concert
I'm on The Deco concert
but but but
just even if you don't see me on on the
concert in the venue then you'll you can
watch the stream and and at least you're
you got a ticket for one of the new
concerts thingies
better than nothing it will be a great
experience to experience it yes
it is
a fact that it will be a great
experience to experience hello tired
brain
you're in day two part two
Ellie Smith are you sure
are you sure
in any case I am happy for you know that
you got at least one
I'm gonna take it because most people
didn't get any congratulations
did it say deco
27 on your ticket
is that the one you made
because besides that I'm on day one
we need a bigger venue we really do oh
you're crying so you just realized huh
that's so painful
I'm so sorry but uh I'm sure there's
other whole life members that you like
right and they might be on the day too
and the other one you can watch the
stream it'll have better angles better
View
trust me
oh
[Music]
who else do you like Emily
but I'm still upset oh I'm sorry I wish
it was easier for people to get a ticket
but you know whole life is so popular in
Japan I guess they
sell out even this big ass venue easily
by far
so sad
you can trade maybe I wonder if that's a
thing
I actually don't know
maybe look into it
maybe you can trade with someone who has
a day one ticket I don't know if it's
possible though so
tied to the passport
um
probably
I'm so sorry but try to say the bright
side of it
um
trying trying to still be happy about it
there's a loud gulp thanks for the pink
name sorry for ruining your excitement
[Music]
but I really think the stream will be
great too
yeah please enjoy your time there
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
you should stream it too we died
thank you
refresh time
what was that bleep I always made that
bleep
for that name
uh yo my teeth are my
not all of them just mine like one tooth
it's really sensitive recently
to
everything
gonna go to the doctor Maybe
oh
foreign
I wonder if I can go before going back
to Japan
yeah dentist that means dentist is still
a doctor
and again so I'll go I want to go to a
different doctor to them I don't have
that much time
can't go through so many freaking
doctors but I guess I'll go to a couple
next week
[Music]
no
I mean it's still like
uh I can still uh uh what is the word
brain sorry I'm like so slow today
foreign
no that's not what I mean I can
I can
um
whatever let's move on
uh
the game recruit
fellow again thank you soon
yeah you were bumped That Fire Emblem is
on PC was it ever on PC
thank you you need to chat I was never
well done
no candy
for the pinky I want to thank you Kiara
thanks to you your early streams from
Japan for Europe I finally fixed my
sleep schedule
I'm glad I was able to fix someone's
that's great well now let's hope it
doesn't [\h__\h] up too quickly
but you you live in Europe right
well it's bedtime now then for you
don't worry I'm ending soon
looking for the top temperature
Raven don't worry I as I said it won't
be so bad
and I'll mix the times up
Mrs Duncan
oh thank you
we want a long TV show to suggestion I
want to recommend Buffy the Vampire
Slayer
no I don't know even the title doesn't
impress me
oh Alison Hannigan isn't that
um
oh it's on Disney Plus
wait that's the really old one
like watching Charmed if I would watch
this and I would watch Charmed because
this gives me Charmed Vibes but then I
might as well watch Charmed because I
wanted to watch that anyway but at least
Buffy seems to be on Disney and Charmed
is like nowhere I had to buy the whole
DVD box set
but damn this this gives me strong
Charmed vibes
haha
they're both on at the same time oh
like the hairstyles and the clubs and
the
um
quality of the video and photograph and
the logo
and the theme of vampires vampires were
also I think no not quite
was it was it vampires or something like
that for sure wasn't Charmed too
uh Super Snake Mario donkey showing for
the pinky I can't it's been really fun
watching his Fire Emblem so far kind of
makes me want to go back and watch your
free houses stream since I didn't really
take the chance to watch him
but I imagine that will take quite some
time but still well you should watch
those
um in the future whenever there's
another kiwawa lack of streams
not now because now
there's many quinoa five limb streams
and other things
but you can keep them for another time
where I got sick or I'm traveling or so
yeah
if you enjoyed this one right now and
you might enjoy the free houses one too
but back then
oh
I was still young and naive
and not the best gamer that I am now
[Music]
next Japan Adventure I'll catch up on
Farmland watch you mean these ones
oh well if you have something to catch
up on yeah but
no more Sicky wow please I hope so too
like that really [\h__\h] sucked and it
took so long and I still have some of
the aftermath right
flick them
I can live
I lived I lived [\h__\h]
yeah
you don't want to get that sick anymore
this year please
knock on wood
okay I think I read all the super chats
sorry that I'm so
elconaviable
thank you soon
sorry that I'm so blah right now blah
blah
on there
I have to make food now and I want to
cook
I don't think I have anything in the
freezer really
maybe something simple
and I'll have no frozen pizza
I can cook for you well that's a lie
yeah maybe some speed pasta with some
pesto
[Music]
you'll have frozen lasagna damn
no French toast I would eat for
breakfast I need dinner now
now my fridge is definitely not empty
there's a lot of stuff in there
but
cooking something from hellofresh takes
so much effort and time
oh this movie is going real hard cuddle
mode right now
[Music]
yeah
Bob Dylan
bonjour
hello
it's been a while since I've last given
you my set I mean your salary ahead
that's right
saved yourself
I haven't been able to watch a lot of
your streams lately well for a long time
what were you doing you doing
is it because I was in Japan when the
time zone sucked and then before that I
was sick so I was just not streaming
working
um I was glad to hear your voice and
your stories love you didn't you
thank you shantam I'm more
thank you so much
glad to have you back at least for the
moment
I'm happy that you're still around and
you didn't forget about me so don't
worry about it
two jobs
oh but you're still here thank you for
making it
but two jobs that sounds rough
I hope you can find a better work life
balance eventually
everyone deserves that
thank you
merciable cool
my French chicken French chicken
French chicken
kiss a French kiss oh again
no normal kiss to a French person
makes it a French kiss
now I'm gonna fall asleep now I have to
make food
I think once I get up from the chair
and go to the idol meeting and then I'll
be awake again
probably hopefully
I'm flattered
me too
thank you good night everybody and in
German myself in Austin tomorrow
don't miss that stream
you know which one
is
[Music]
this
on whole life official Channel I already
retweeted it today
I think 9pm Jersey
or 7 P.M
I think 9pm no 7 P.M
I forgot
9 pm okay
9 00 P.M
I'll definitely be there thank you
um it's an unofficial channel so you can
guess
there will be very
exciting things revealed such as new
aisle outfits the first one in ages
since the beginning
so
one must make time to see this when it
happens and not accidentally see it
later on when you scroll through Twitter
no no no you want to be one of the first
ones to know
shin
I do the issue
okay
I did my job here
my job here is done
see you tomorrow members and official
Channel and enjoying myself videos then
I need to go to another meeting
I love you Kevin
foreign
[Music]