[Music]
w
a
[Music]
see
no
[Music]
hello we back we back all five of us
from the beginning let's
go are a little loud oh yeah yeah yeah I
I made us a lot of chickens but I needed
it for the arrows and for food oh true
true yeah I want give you guys a tour of
what happened but did a lot of [\h__\h]
apparently show us the chicken pan it's
kind of loud in here oh get out of there
get out of there save yourself they're
aggressive chickens they eat people free
them free them I'm free how could you do
that to yeah so chicken chicken C now in
where there were villagers before uh
feel free to you know deal with the
chickens however you
like
them
[Music]
hello the sound of
waking scared
me wait come with me as soon as my mouse
starts working I'll be right there K I
ordered a
new I'm in this house it's a beautiful
Airbnb for future villagers
ooh
blueo wait it's really
pretty come Callie come Callie I'm
coming I'm not going to miss out why is
it oh my God there's literally so
manyas in the bowls I think it's
oatmeal the Yum y that Grandma's oatmeal
don't say it
he why is that
like it coffee with your ooh I already
have some I got my morning
shot o I'm about to get real annoying as
you can see we have beds now because
yeah we found a sheep got
sheep one sheep a single sheep single
sheep if you
need over here and yet like and yet we
have about eight pandas might it's
important we have to I need each one of
the blood
lines
okayy can we Harvest their meat
G no I'm just asking can we I'm not
asking permission I'm just saying can we
Harvest their meat is it possible GI F
no yeah in terms of food I got you C
with bread now as well for free
har yeah of course the chest above has
seeds if you need more if you want froz
away hey it's smart you put the ball I
help I help I help W did you think of
that or did your I'm of it
I'm who smart you you NE hurt from
holding on to that mess
brain seriously though wow wow wow
okay and then if you remember the old I
mean it's still the same myth house but
it has our colors now in terms of beds
and some more
decorations I want to see you put my bed
next time
sleep you don't want to be next to me
all right feelings freaking hurt we
can fine I understand no
fine have some nice pillows
yeah I got wait I got double pillow oh
no I'm fine with this I'm good with this
you seeing double pillows
what else do you make
k a yeah if you go let's let's go behind
the um chicken house I have something to
show you I can't believe my little
Merchant pen became a chicken
house the chicken po po yeah we have a
big portal now I didn't go in yet but we
can go in today cool don't we need some
golden stuff though good thing we saved
all that gold right well check out that
chest over here I already did it all
right let F that's okay we're fine we're
fine and in the chest there's also the
Eyes of Ender that we need yeah turns
out we already had enough of the end
eyes so I just made pears I made some
eyes out of
them yeah good that's like the most
important stuff I did and some
decorating in
there yay very nice
very off rain is always
loud in Minecraft oh my shaders aren't
my shaders popping off cuz I got
shaders
shers
oh do you want to know why you are a
genius without knowing
it the I was like I was mining my own
business yeah yeah yeah um and then a
creeper popped up a creeper spawns right
and because you're so close to it
automatically it it goes off right I
stepped back but it went that and then
bam and it exploded in this whole
construction that you made and I was
like y b it's going to all be destroyed
but the water took the explosion and
therefore nothing exploded
science okay it's as if it was on
purpose thank you Mr White science
totally she's a scientist
scientist all right I'll do a little
more
organizing I'm kind of stuck what the
hell how kind of C to organize all of
our chests for us it's very cool of her
that she does that oh you're doing that
yeah I am take this take all of this
then thank you God yeah you're welcome
and Silent please I can't click on some
of face
please into the ne I want I'm stopa we
need we need weather to shut the up
that's good
wait what what do we do what what's
going on I just turn the weather down
the weather shut its P hole is dead oh
no is somebody stuck oh
[Music]
no is there a trap door oh is she fine
now the is opening it leave it
[Laughter]
open no I I think wait am I like
crouching but I keep on pressing it to
like release it you got to come out this
way somehow I legit cannot move that way
oh thank
Youk yo
y yeah in terms of armor um we don't
have that much iron uh I don't
think we're going to be that lucky I
want to dismiss we have a bunch of we
have a ton of emeralds um oh we have a
block of iron why not crack that bad boy
open here I'll crack that open even then
I don't think we'll all have full iron
armor well we can we can like partially
get dressed up mhm sounds good to me is
it still better to have gold armor than
IR but we have diamonds we do have
diamonds imagine imagine putting on the
diamond armor now and then dying in the
never that's true enough I'm still going
to crack open don't give diamonds 27
diamonds from a block of diamond here so
now we have over 64 we have 68 diamonds
not bad Lads not bad oh okay yeah 68
diamonds all right yeah 68 diamonds [\h__\h]
M wait how many 68 diamonds holy moly
yeah we have a fat stack of them but I
mean I think it is a good idea to save
for later if we
can we're rich nice money money can't
believe we have more diamonds than iron
ah yeah that really doesn't seem to make
a lot of sense yeah it's because I I
used uh most of the iron to make an
anvil ah that'll do it and tools we've
been making a lot of iron
pickaxes okay those are necessary those
are very necessary they are they
are but yeah that's how it's been going
so um the the thing is we have already
enough enough Ender eye thingies uh to
open our portal so we're not going into
The Nether to really get Enderman or
Blaze anything we already have all all
we need but we're just going in for fun
and we can get more NE Wards and blaze
rods because with that we could make
more potions that would definitely help
us what if we die though are we risking
losing
resources uh well if we die there we
life always carries a risk of death
magma just got to live with it true just
don't die in the
magma die don't
die oh should we bring some should we
bring some gold so we can trade with the
Pigman that might be a good idea I was
thinking that might be fun but I looked
at a sheet of like percentage and what
you can get and it's like going to be
such a waste we could use the gold for
golden apples that would make more sense
in the end but we can take a little bit
some we have a lot yeah yeah yeah wowo
who made the wow take all oh I made the
wowbo yeah that's pretty cool that's
cool Kar that's cool I want to enchant
something oh that was the the bow that
was enchanted but broken but I fixed it
with the Anvil yeah
and then I named it wo cool
W we're going to use feather falling for
later if you die in the nether you
should receive a
punishment a
punishment punishment for endangering
the team's resources
yeah what is said punishment we should
make um we should make a diamond sword
with a power three enchantment
oh go okay okay but we can share it we
can like share give it to our war BR a
bow and some arrows so that I got one I
can take care of gests I got good bow
and I got some arrows infinite arrows if
you die in the nether you have to be
slain on stream for Shame by the Power
Three diamond sword that's a that's a
good idea so you you die double you die
in the ne die in real life exactly in
Minecraft slay for shame Minecraft is
real life in front of everyone here
people are saying that power is for bow
what if we just did an Infinity
enchantment on one of the bows instead
do do we have Infinity we do we have
Infinity one is just we have levels
that's the question though that's
excellent question can't make a diamond
bow right that's not possible you can
only do a
regular damn that' be cool nice
though lied bow or Arrow resources yeah
why not both yeah why not power and we
keep digging we'll get um well it would
take a while anyways to level up like a
villager right that had the right stuff
yeah we could do sweeping Edge though
sweeping Edge a sword yeah it gives it
like kind of an AOE a little bit like a
bigger bigger sweep and and there's
looting too yeah we have looting get
more with more looting is always yeah go
for it go for it can ask what
everybody's listening to nothing guys
Sound of Silence nothing nothing nothing
listen to you where where' the music box
go Minecraft I moved the music box into
to the house because people told me that
parrots would dance to the music and
then I tested it out but it didn't
actually work even when I removed them
from the bed wait I want to see no no I
think it's like a new version Oh wait
now it's dancing it didn't like the
track maybe he's
dancing yeah okay where'd he go outside
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh your
own one oh
yeah like let them dance bring him into
the
disco dance
bird yours doesn't want to dance what's
wrong with him do
something poke him with a stick do it
may maybe this tune is just not it we
need a little more exp to enhance the bo
different tun boogie
boogie I have created the Bodacious bow
it shoots Infinity
arrows he wants to escape he wants out
so bad oh
God I'm excited not quite his
Tempo not quite as Tempo let's try it
out oh it does shoot Infinity
let's go
go audacious
bow should we take that into The Nether
though cuz we need that for the end what
if we lose yeah maybe not we'll store it
in the weapons chest it's just cool to
make important weapons yeah it's good to
one bow and a couple of arrows though
for the gas I I got one bow and a couple
of arrows okay I think I think we should
at least have like
Stone weapons yeah very Le
definitely what about what about should
we do one piece of diamond armor per
person maybe
maybe I mean as long as you don't fall
to Lava it's should be fine cuz it'll
just drop whatever you're I'm to
yeah so I got gold helmets for everybody
so let's do I don't know maybe the chest
piece for chest piece good
idea so maybe that's what I I'll just
make some Stone I'll make a ton of good
weapons for the
endons I'm going to make the chest
plates for all five of us so don't don't
take diamonds
doie uh right before this stream I I I
ate uh some stuff that was sitting out
for like uh maybe almost 12
hours why do you do that what what was
it
snack Oh no just it was just a single
rice cake oh that's probably fine but I
mean don't do that for things like me or
whatever do you
say
yeah F I should as long as it was like
meat or dairy right um had meat in the
you in the
broth be F you'll
be wait Kelly wait
[Music]
yeah I won't die I
promise I might die I might die I'll do
I'll do my best I'll do my
best okay everybody's got a piece I
guess I should make rainbow friendship
call it it's a big
ring the music is kind of loud
now should make some pickaxes too oh
yeah mhm I have them iron I still think
iron pickaxes are for the best I think I
think we for normal mining we can use
the St ones but if there's like a
resource like gold or something we can
use the IR one yeah good
[Music]
idea so everybody gets a stone picka you
get a stone pickaxe you get a stone pick
made some or I have I already have an
iron pickaxe so I have enough
food oh this is so exciting
going on the field trip yeah field trip
so what do we need from the nether by
the way T nothing why are we going just
going
into yeah normally there would be things
that we could use uh from there but we
already have everything thanks to mining
endlessly so we're just going in for fun
is there like an increased chance of
diamonds or I mean no no diamonds but we
can get more
gold golden app and we can get never for
which is a little little plant which out
of that we could make potions to help us
resist the dragon that we're going to
fight okay yeah and if we find a
fortress we can get blaze rods what if
we make a portal inside the nether does
it go anywhere like if oh usually yeah
and it goes further but I wonder I feel
like they would have blocked it
for I'm going to bring some obsidian to
experiment okay experiment there's a
fire charges in in the cool things chest
if you need the fire charge for the cool
things chest I'm sorry I didn't hear
about this obsidian chest it's also in
the right here oh
okay we don't have we don't have sugar
cane do we no fish no we don't dang it
we
need cuz if we had sugarcan we can make
a lot of Pumpkin Pine that would be nice
Yum Yum Yum Yum nice idea wait fire
charge is that what I'm getting uh yeah
yeah yeah yeah to zap it on it's only
one time used though okay okay I brought
an extra just
case IR IR oh there's a fish in here
fishy fishy fishy fishy fishy
fishy you're going to need more chests I
have so many materials oh I guess we
can't we shouldn't do that this is why
your boy wanted a trash can
listen we just have so many
things there's a lot of stuff in
here make sure you organize it properly
just because we have a chance to die I
think going in with half armor is going
to be okay we can help each other to not
die protect each other get that gold
home so that big floating jellyfish man
dude guy comes like shooting balls at
you and stuff like that you're supposed
to hit it back with a sword or do you
slay him with a the bow and arrow you
can there's another bow here with
infinity bous bow oh yeah I put that in
there um that's that's the stuff for the
end that's call okay okay yeah it's just
I'm making a bunch of weapons to get us
ready for the end so we'll use it then
it's the Bodacious bow yeah someone can
can use the Bodacious bow when we fight
the Ender Dragon what does that mean
Bodacious bow oh have you heard the word
bod should we should we at least make a
shield oh the
pane how you look it's a new panda
panda we at least make a shield if we
can oh yeah Shield would be a good idea
we should make Shields we just make them
out oh yeah okay just one iron purse so
it should be
okay what you I'll make shield for
everyone okay
tasar by the way K Bodacious means nice
body I just wanted to let you know oh
bous B dunk all right then I should know
what yeah I I just said
here's thank
you oh thank you thank you Goomba here's
your I looked it up it can be excellent
admirable or attractive yeah I guess it
is oh yeah nice Dictionary look up there
Austin I appreciate
that your
Shield my before I go make a baby make a
bab baby why you double shielding AO
oh it's like the anime with girl oh I
didn't know you could do that D let's go
okay thoughts try harder maybe
eating taking our
resources we could use that for
something with the pant eating them the
bamboo cute must resist urge to
murder what it's okay it's just a bit
bamboo look how cute they are
Banda oh Vanda it's for morale boost all
right we need that right we going into
The Nether to die can we even ride on
our backs like what if we could we ride
on them into the nether like that would
be cool me me no no they're just cute
all right that's their purpose their
whole
purpose oh right my OBS died for a
second let's go let's
go one more Stone
Pickaxe mine has also been
[Music]
dying OBS what's wrong with you is it
OBS or YouTube is drunk for me right now
that was OBS but often it's also
YouTube need some sticks then we can go
I'm pretty sure I need a
help gu what I'm making after the stream
wait guess what I'm
making I'm going to make a chocolate
chip Skillet cookie oh no way sounds
kind ofum yeah wait what what's the
skillet part that sounds like a like a
steak thing it's like a it's like a a a
like a cast iron thick heavy bottom pan
pot thing and you yeah put the cookie
dough in and bake it that way and then
you put ice cream
on we're invited
right no it's single serving
sorry yeah that's messed up girl you
can't just tell us about it in stay you
can't have any come on
now I am putting the dough in so that it
fills up the whole Skillet like a
pancake or yeah oh it's like it's like a
cake kind of what you're making
yeah dang yummy Dam yeah that's a good
idea give me the recipe later please
please please please please yeah do I
need a skillet for
it um I guess it would be easier that
way yeah okay time buy a skillet you
could just use a cake pan probably yeah
yeah a cake pan if you want singles in
the oven or a cake pan on the okay oven
it's in the oven okay yeah yeah there's
a restaurant that serves it it's called
they make they call it Pazuki Pazuki
pazooki what they serve Skillet cookies
sounds y yeah what they're known for
what the hell me time to die fre string
fre string yeah
we oh is full that's a lot of stuff that
means your boy isn't doing her job okay
hold on a sec CI my brain was like
breaking yesterday when you were gone
and I had to sort things on my own man
that was rough rough rough rough that's
all right it's just cuz you don't have
the configuration down like I do if you
figure out where it all goes You' be
fine fermented spider eye it's better
handles it
though yeah I'm I'm used it's just it's
just not super entertaining is the
thing sorry everyone watching my POV I I
don't really not really doing much here
besides
organizing okay does everybody have
enough food by the way there's still
like a watermelon and bread in the food
chest if you want yeah I got the food
you're having a great time I'm
happy take it take it take it take the
food I'm sure chat will watch paint dry
with with us if it comes down to that be
an interesting interesting stream watch
yeah they would especially watch it if
it was drying on your body good point
maybe that's a good that's a good stream
idea we got we got a situation situation
where' everybody go what oh no hello
okay what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] oh boy
oh no excuse me what what the what why
is there two enemies anyway
okay I SL down I'm
scared damn here last phase Pillager
dare uh attack Dam that was super
unlucky wait why are there so many
ofes
ow here should I log out it's okay
there's only like four left it's cuz
they're scared they're [\h__\h] what they
came all in one damn that's why they
attack in a group cuz they're big
cowards got one crazy those those traps
man mm come here you see those traps
y'all traps they said traps yeah the
traps that the the Pillager was like
setting up while were flying around that
was I saw that in Full full
4K I got caught by one come here
buddy smells like chicken in here get
him
there's a chicken in here down here
coward oh
sorry I feel like we're hitting each
other more than they were hitting the
enemies did they die think so I think so
seems peaceful great job guys that was
crazy nice one team are we ready yeah
high five I'm Ready the shower let's go
oh I need to grab my helmet has to get
her 1,000 a lot
no purposeful no don't do that
replace your helmets with the golden
helmets yep oh they're in the chest
behind the house house here here here
here here here at the portal okay over
here think my mouse is dying but I can't
find the charging oh that's why I only
only use cable
tools I used to but I have a lot of eggs
go those mouses mes my are a little too
heavy hold on I'm just going to go ahead
didn't
see didn't see nothing
chat oh well if I die my mouse dies
uhoh let's go M let's
go okay okay so uh goal would be to um
find a Pillager just for fun did anybody
bring gold for that a villager I mean h
villager uh uh P piglin
piglin did anybody bring some gold just
just a little bit no no I grab I'm
duplicating my friends I'm rening space
in time please forgive just just going
to bring my bird off a little bit of
gold just for fun okay um
dollhous the other goal would be finding
one of those
for some Forest that has the ne Ward for
potions
and if you find a fortress that would be
sick actually I found the
cord what wait don't joke with me man no
I'll I'll play Barbie dolls with you
girl anytime dude let's do it come down
Barbies
Barbi I love doll dollhous games my
weapons are kind of dying I kind of need
to fix it can I fix it move my friends
around a little
more there we go friends moved okay ch
ch
one second then I'm ready to
go I'm going to eat my the gold oh yeah
I brought like 20 I don't
know okay uh building should we bring
bring some building blocks to make paths
perhaps I think we'll be able to get I I
have some
Cobblestone okay I got some endstone too
like one one stack yeah yeah I was
scared for a second cuz it was like it
went so quiet for like 5 seconds I was
like did this
die no it it went super quiet for like 5
seconds on my end I thought this died
even like Minecraft sound died I was
like huh but no it's just me I'm I'm
just being scared of my
own it's okay we're
coming we're
here okay and I think we can go
this okay I'm ready okay come to the
next portal if you're ready gives me
energy ready to go wait before we go in
we should take a picture in front of it
sure sounds good to me stand in line
whose bird is this whose birds are these
they going to get
in yours and mine I thought I thought he
was going to sit in the house we got to
get that cat out hold on we got to the
Crouch sority
sority girl squat did you kill I don't
know where the cat went
but get your bird where is he he's in
front of the portal he's going to go in
by himself oh no he knows not what
Horrors await getting
photo don't lose the bird in the never
that would be so sad hello have you seen
my bird he's about this tall green it
was there he
is I'm bird jumping no the other bir the
green one oh I jumped it's on your
shoulder it's
on guys I'm
scared come on come on come over sorry
struck by lightning with the okay you
I'll hold your hand wait if you get
struck by lightning while your bird is
on your shoulder do you get cooked
chicken as the EM o what if you turn
into like a bird super like the Birdman
or something like that your origin story
is you were struck by lightning when you
had a parrot on your shoulder and then
you turn into the parrot
man the bird man sound
scary and Darkwing Duck yeah something
like par Moth
Man you a cryp hry for the wait whose
cat is that you let them sit they don't
follow
another oh [\h__\h] maybe mine yeah it's
your cat in the boat but that's the bird
boat so okay he's
sitting okay all right let's go good
she okay cheese got the hello look you
camera I got it okay then what shall
await us on the other side it's so
dramatic cool let's go the donkey fre me
careful you don't fall there's a lot of
lava the donkey went in let's go
no no he's buring
alive when the donkey burns alive wait
is he really Burning Alive hold on a sec
no don't worry guys he's gone he's
gone what is this portal spawn that's
messed up wait where are you guys are up
there what how'd you get up
there hold on also it's super
dark yes hold on I'm am I stuck in the
for wait let me try this again why is
the server so Bor okay hold on no please
please let me go let me join my friends
okay I think we're good there's all it's
all
lava
horrific the hole KY I'm here I made it
I was just tripping out I had some weird
mushroom stew we're fine that's better
okay yeah be careful of your paths you
may not be seeing a hole but there may
very well be a hole dang should have
brought blocks did anybody bring a ton
of blocks I'll just go back and get a
big stack I'll get a stack too two
stacks
okay
some oh there's Soul Sand over
there need those for be useful go Nether
wart
growing
we have a lot of Soul Sand but more NE
wart would be nice and finding a
fortress would be SI we got nether one a
little bit yeah oh the we can totally
grow them already we should we should
have planted them on the soul stand oh
we can duplicate them okay well then
don't don't take away the things the few
things that we have to oh yeah now we're
good let's keep an eye out for the
Fortress oh wait the coordination Cords
Cord it'll slow you down what are the
cords okay I took a screenshot of the
cords okay wait one two three four this
is not a very nice
I brought we're missing call I'm here I
brought blocks I think he went back yeah
okay I'm
here we that way to the next
[Music]
platform wait I think I found something
what did you find what it's a
fortress already are you sure it's a
fortress how do you know it's a yeah you
see to zoom in with optify it's bricks
it's a fortress
wait where over there over over where
I'm
looking should go this
way it's [\h__\h] Fortress right okay
well now we have a goal so that's good
yeah we need to make a path over there
let's go I'm at the Builder okay now the
blocks to give you if you need more
blocks let me know I've got a ton sounds
off let me turn guys I hear a guest I'm
scared it's
okay need more blocks might fall off
here if he G to me oh yeah sure here you
go hold on a sec I hear him Netherrack
hungry you he does sound hungry that's
okay it's right over there oh it's right
over
[Music]
there it's okay it's fine it's fine we
got to also remember um how we got here
I have the quartz no worries cool and I
mean the Fortress is so close I think
we're going to find no way back fine
we're so
lucky so lucky
man but I'm glad why did I okay I didn't
get any of those okay making the path a
little
longer or a little wider you know wait
if you dig another what is this red rock
with a stone pickaxe do you get them or
do you need iron you should get it it's
just like dirt basically it's this it's
this realm's dirt in in essence
okay Ena does this remind you of
something
recently you and does being here I feel
like I had more gear last time okay hold
on this go
past okay did YouTube die again for
anyone that's why I made it really
bad we'll fix it when we come back yeah
word on the street is yoube is
struggling what fine falling down like
that on the one block path where the
other side is lava
o you're not fine you scare me yeah no
my God it's fine it's fine it's fine no
worries no worries m i mean to put this
down of the well
example it is a fortress no way yeah
lucky us that's nutty looks like the eye
of sa he
fine goodbye load of the Rings watch
along let's go oh full extended oh oh
yeah I've done that actually before with
members remember when I got sick in
Japan when we were doing our 3D watchong
Frey uh debut I uh when I got sick I did
uh lot of the Rings extended version
watch Longs with my members one after
another oh my
God I'm out block 4 hours yeah make a
little
stairway make a little stairway oh I'm
actively making it worse okay hold on
can I what you catch me oh you made
stairs that's a lot less romantic RK in
theat tonight oh let's go fun I helped I
did one black woohoo
RK
Ronin RK stands
for oh how do we get into the we have to
go up dig in yeah I think we got to go
up it's an M from Mo oh mo Ka that's me
can't go in through the
bottom I I think we'll have to go up
like this is just like the the pillars
of it yeah the path seems to be above
and then the main part seems to be
further uh over
at the end of the that those pillars
there all right well if everybody mines
some uh nether rock that we just like
boost ourselves individually you know
what I mean sure oh yeah like a big like
elevator yeah okay I didn't bring a
normal pickaxe I only have the diamond
pickaxe just in case so okay well we can
get some for I'll give to you girls to
to mine yeah I think I have enough easy
I'll start and make a bridge careful
there's like lava right
there's a lot
everywhere
everywhere yeah careful there's lava um
all over the place watch out there the
wi we lava
everywhere stop it I think I saw
hob I saw
herob over there blind going
oh man oh get some levels from
this you making like a a circle circle
stair like a little platform for you
guys to uh build up to took about 40
blocks or something like that okay can
somebody also give me blocks done okay
I've got quite a big stack I'll give you
64 qara where are you thank
you there you go you want me to go in
and Scout it out yeah we need a
scout but then
if we want to go back
we we just I guess we get rid of the
blocks we made up I guess uh yeah that's
how the elevator works we'll we just
mine our way down again M your way down
don't worry if you have to use a diamond
pickaxe to get down it's fine no no no
oh I hear guys I'll use my hands here
some dudes it's okay they're friendly we
have gold they respect
us why not just build stairs
right somebody says make a spiral
staircase yeah right that that's what
she was making up here so you know I'm
good I'll go then right
beneath this is kind of scary thises no
this is enough blocks yeah should be
fine wait race you race you youa race
you oh God it's
so I got a head start
though okay I got 30 uh six here oh yeah
okay just be real careful
okay making me nervous here with these I
think they all went back to me wait
let's did you can drop the whole stack
yeah wait wait wait let's go over here
so this is a fortress Tada never seen
one of these like the sound of the
stairs oh wait what are these do we raid
it is that what you're supposed to do
here yeah we're taking it over be
careful though very dangerous very
dangerous dangerous can we fight with
stone swords you think we'll win totally
although if we find a blaze
spawner it's going to be a little bit
rough okay we rush it we don't give it a
chance to spawn and then we rush it yeah
yeah yeah sounds good okay I mean we
just need a few blaze rods just for fun
we don't need to you know make the whole
spawner our
ours
just if we if we end up getting wither
like two more wither heads we can spawn
the wither okay oh a side quest side
quest side quest yeah side quest I don't
know about this ooh more poisonous
mushrooms for poison mushrooms oh sorry
yay where you going dude sorry left or
straight uh girls Democratic vote please
left or straight cuz it's easier to
remember how to get
lost um uh no have some
torches me to me to should put torches
like on one side each so then you know
which way to go
back oh yeah good idea we're going in a
straight line I think it'll be okay
that's a good way to Mark oh but
actually straight is a dead end oh then
never mind left is
good okay come on come on we going this
way it's so quiet in here so far wow did
you just say thator yeah oh my God bye
Kiara
big one there's some stairs here I want
to go
up W what what possibly could go wrong
it's so quiet here it's the Cal before
the storm as you know photo photo
[Music]
photo where is that we
with where are the skeletons o I like
skeletons this is maybe also dead end do
they have like chests and stuff here to
raid uh yeah they should have some
chests yeah oh sorry dead end Goblin
uh-oh that doesn't seem run back
inside Retreat Retreat Parry it just
yeah you got it g wait go find him you
have to this dead end anyway go tell
beat [\h__\h] I want to hit the thingies
don't risk it for the skillet
biscuit I'll kill you hold on I'm just
trying to hit it wait yeah do it do it
girl where is he
dang it it should have di yeah let's go
she did it let's go yeah fall off your
horse yeah you suck uh yeah yeah yeah we
got
it okay back
down and then the this
way
yay it's so empty but the bricks are so
nice I want to take some bricks
home somebody else choose the path but
this seems to be a good
section this stairs straight oh there's
a thing there a spawner there's a
spawner there oh nice rush rush a rush
it's scary how do
we the fire should be fine you just put
a torch oh just put a torch on it right
go Ena Goa go am go
Callie oh he's very strong oh he's very
strong does not like me oh sorry yeah B
the the the potato fries oh no it's
spawn behind you too
okay well done
ladies that was easy drop something do
we need
to oh nice uh I mean if we find more we
can kill more sounds good more right oh
or we can build this thing where it's
like you can like block the line of set
and just hit it from like down here that
would be nice if we knew how to do well
there's a lot of do you know how to do
it if anybody has the torch you can put
it back on
now don't fire nice H oh I got a blaze
rod too be nice for XP I guess but
they're kind of tough we need more rods
for the Eyes of Ender we already have
all the Eyes of Ender chat that we need
actually we're just doing we take the
End Dragon now I don't have any more can
I mean we could but we need a little
more diamonds yeah a little bit we
should go in with a bit more armor at
least I mean we have enough Diamond to
make armor
for I think so everyone don't you think
we have like a stack plus more no we got
to drag it out at least one more day
come on
yeah guys torch oh you pushed him into
me
all right
wasn't he torch Tor it no today is never
day and the next time we can
do if we're so
[Music]
eager oh torches I have torches oh okay
oh yeah yeah you listening kill the
end oh but I I thought we want to fight
more yeah sure well did we get what do
we need do we even need it just it's
just you know for fun it's okay we
finish Minecraft one block Minecraft and
then we just find a different different
thing to all do together it's
fine am I using the wrong oh sorry this
is the wrong I'm such an idiot I don't
know how to fight y I was doing so good
potions basically the more of these
things we have the more potions we can
make like OverWatch we will not be
playing OverWatch together I'm sorry
it's an ex isn't bad no I don't think
it's bad either it's just not what I
want to play play with you
guys why
not why not over watch hey is this where
you need this stuff it's fine ooh skin t
wait where are you too are you where are
you and some red
stower a sniper where did everybody
I ooh free lava oh free lava for fruit
oh yeah this is good yeah pick them up
good goodone going to have to direct us
out of here cuz I got no clue where we
are but where are the skeletons is it
like bugged why are no random random
spawns in the Fortress a dead beats are
in my chat
Kiara it is speaking of the devil hell
yum I should have brought milk damn it
why did we forget about the milk dead
beat enough uhoh oh oh oh no oh no oh oh
no oh no I'm going first one that dies
get spanked by the diamond sword bye go
bye go
byebye bye everyone pick up my face
please where are you uh I was a little I
I was a little bit past that oh there's
another
one yeah milk would have been good oh
and there's a place too think I might
die that's not great no did you find my
stuff y yeah okay good maybe retreating
is a good
idea okay
yeah those those the the curses they put
on you they're no joke yeah I was really
surprised by that I can't believe I
survived behind you behind
behind
uhoh I just want to get the chest o nice
chest oh whoopsies no please gold
armor nice in there don't worry all my
all my moves are C got it all
oh boy it is dark I do wish I had a
torch just a hole there's more nether
here blocks I have to build my way up I
got to build my way up again
a uh if you follow the path uh I started
building oh I guess you don't have any
blocks I'll be fine I'm bringing
blocks but no gold armor sorry I have no
shovel should be
fine a ladder it's over there I don't
want to make a ladder now
nothing in there okay here we go found
the entrance you guys hello where
where's
everyone I was looking at that chest
over there by the but there's nothing in
there oh
really I know if someone already where's
everyone else wait won can you
backtrack okay you guys come back come
out of the chest area Okay does he is he
going to ATT hello the entrance is here
but there's also this unexplored
uh part here go deeper we must go de
from yaha oh it's just more chest it
looks like oh is he going chest to be
looted iron horse
armor golden you have a lot of horses a
quite a few to ride into battle
valiantly don't get guys I'm standing at
the staircase scared he won't does care
about the gold tell me tell me chat tell
me chat okay that sounds all right I got
everything in the
chest okay we're going back up sure get
Kiara
K you're going to get me yeah you're
alone I thought I was just going to go
back to you can you find it com back to
me do we need anything here I feel like
we got everything what you want to leave
already what I thought we were going to
do the Ender Dragon yeah no we're not
doing the end today no
not
no today's never day don't end our
beautiful time together so
early wait what if we made like a like a
like an arena and we have one each one
of us has to fight the Ender Dragon one
at a time o that could be fun a true
test of our and we watch watch you just
watch and die back seat each other damn
oh my blocks oh
uh I think it's a good
idea oh
boy I might indeed need help to get back
up we're going yep a
Coliseum a Coliseum sounds good
huh yeah I do Coliseum you guys think
you could beat a bear in a fist fight
speaking of Coliseum no no no no can you
there was there was thing like that in
like a game called M noi it's like you
can get a title for beating a when
you're 10 years old wait I think there's
that in in Witcher as well you fish
fight a
bear can you start oh you don't have any
blocks I got nothing I have a few a few
I was going say you can start building
stairs oh my God there's a guest over
there guys I don't feel
very we got to
goon I'm trying
you are the
distraction I think it's
Z okay okay go go go go go go go go okay
maybe I can help build two maybe not
there's two of we're almost there we're
almost
there those speed
speed careful
girls I should have bought like a slime
block or something so I can just jump
down now down okay emergency
boat oh I do have
boats I don't know if I can do it with
this ping though right now we just
stairs why why why do I not have
problems with the Ping I'm so
lucky okay what if you're coming back
then I guess hello we're here oh hi here
we're right up here okay see hold
on you can get in the boat and dive off
the edge oh all right
thing okay can we T what does that
mean uh two oh like a tandem bicycle o
girls I got to go like AFK for a second
but I'm just going to log out for a
moment okay where you okay I'll I'll be
don't be gone too long I miss you oh
okay hurry up okay to all right I got a
I got two
boats nice
are we are we just going to boat it
let's try it let's try it let's try it
yeah that could be good get cie okay if
you say so okay aim do not aim for the
lava I wait am I in the front oh Fu
you're a driver now driver I can't see I
can't see the bottom I can't see I can't
see I'm going my life's in your hands
fine Houston you're clear clear clear
for
launch let's prank there we go oh nice
oh it works
wow we lived I can't believe we live I
mean I knew
it get me for a second did you of course
not I was just joking jokes jokes
jokes oh who oh look strange on the
screen hold
[Music]
on did it work I'm just going to put
them oh oh
oopsies okay get out of the
way oh I have Mario Kart DK Mountain on
Loop I'm losing my mind oh in the
background
yeah nice it is pretty have your battle
Tunes battle jungle
music so you know that we're here and
kar's AFK we can uh test by putting um a
obsidian portal o oh nice idea where are
we going where's it going to spawn the
unknown wait that's what you titled your
stream isn't it drop title drop title
drop but if it's one block on the other
side then what if we spawn
nowhere you need a pickax well then I
have cars Diamond one I'll just use
it
oo I'm
telling don't be a title tail girl this
is this tall
enough 1 two three I think it's supposed
to be
too
wide is it three it's okay it's it's
going to be 3x3 it'll be
fine hopefully this works those are
weird noises oh who wants to go in
first be careful you might spawn into
nowhere wait maybe you should leave your
stuff
first not going anywhere oh I guess it
doesn't work yes it does oh wait wait no
just you just wavy and then it just
stays like that forever oh oh wait
[Music]
[Applause]
what oh I'm wibbly wobbly where did you
guys go you alive I'm barf I'm going to
barf I don't know everything I'm
I God I can't
leave do you guys have any blocks oh um
I have some there is nothing I just wait
is this why they call it Sky Block I'm I
I spawned underneath the portal and
there's like a little obsidian platform
that catches
you I have some
blocks come give you some I can't really
go anywhere okay uh just chill everyone
stop don't walk off I have to walk off
no no no don't don't don't walk off
don't walk off it's just really wobbly
um let me see if there's I stand so
shift just wait you made another portal
oh uh don't com in might not be a good
idea come in it's just really hard to
place a block right now you did you did
you did you make a portal and you were
like in the middle of the sky oh nice
middle of this guy right now oh that's
fun that's so
fun get up have blocks I I don't have
any blocks I got
some get here drop it on the other side
the other side what's happening I want
to
see can I going okay wait okay we have
enough enough platform this to stay okay
can anyone see our house oh never mind
Saving Private
Aon What's Happening Here what's I've
got five blocks to help you oh my God
wait
so um what's the plan to be here what's
the purpose of being here restart the
challenge you're
trapped restart restarting the challenge
we try save Watson oh what if I what do
you mean she's there what below us why
wait where are you WatchON there's a
obsidian platform underneath the
onto see this here what what does it
mean you see
that okay I just made another portal at
the bottom never
mind what okay go back into
the I'm already on the other
there was enough block to just make
another portal I wonder where we
ended okay I'm coming
in
[Music]
hi well that was that was good for
science right so we know that if you
make another portal you'll be again in
the middle of the
sky yep here I can give you back your
stuff hold on I'm going to break this
portal so we don't go into it again
yeah why not what a strange silly thing
all right here you go
this and this one oh I didn't pick it
[Music]
up oh I guess that's our portal over
there I think you have the chest plate
now it's mine now I'll two chest plate
no M what do you need two chest plates
for why not one for Monday and one for
Tuesday
a all right so are we going back in cuz
we I think we pretty much got everything
oh why well I mean yeah we can go back
but I'm not letting you go that easily
can I make all my friends really wide
let me see wait what if we dro the
dragon into a portal like what we just
did and then he falls into the sky out
yeah can you build another portal in the
end I don't think I don't think so but
then we can break the portal and he's
stuck in the void
forever oh oh you can't build a portal
though okay interesting says yeah the
dragon kind of flies though so it won't
have fall
damage nether doesn't work in the end a
that's too
bad okay then let's go back to the to to
the real
portal and we can still do some stuff
though we don't have to end it here that
would be we still have to collect
materials though K we don't have nearly
enough golden apples or weapons and that
kind of stuff so we still have we need
to mine diamonds let's just endlessly
mine because we need some diamonds and
we need maybe if we find a villager that
would be nice and I me if you want
something to do you could build pppp
more organizing chat doesn't that s fun
okay do do we need that well we need
nothing really but um I want to make a
bunch of cool weapons together this time
I'm going to be a weapon Smith what I
can help buil together yeah yeah hell
yeah all right I'll look up a
guy fun small
child we didn't do it but we could it's
not these though the it's the
normal
L welcome home everybody oh not yet hold
on are the pandas okay or did they did
they uh perish so sadly
they're okay I mean they're starting to
get so many you might need to expand
their
territory or call some I thought you
were about to say execute execute sounds
like a good idea if you need me to
execute your pandas I'll do it for you
anytime why are you so eager
sorry that's not part of the pack
[Music]
right what I'm going to put this
horse armor on a can put on a
donkey I don't think so sadly
unfortunate where all the horses go oh
there's one horse all right I shall do
some organizing wait that's a
donkey so that we can mine more close
enough wait did all the horses
die a skeleton
one he yeah we had like so many zombie
hes I know that one is like
underground oh a broken music disc why
is it
broken why BR I'm stuck in the all right
guys I'm watching a zombie spawner farm
tutorial let's go can I help I want to
help put me to work yeah we can help
absorb information first absorb it yes
learn and then do a ton of dirt blocks
by the way if you want to expand the
forest I don't really think expanding
the forest has much of a meaning now
though but cuz we have enough trees I
mean we can still farm and get more
trees oh that oh we can get more apples
actually from the trees oh yes yes
apples would be nice
really yeah you can take that as one of
your side quests cool okay side quest
yay nice nice nice also there's a ton of
coal in this fuel chest over
here and
coal yeah all right expand the forest
then I'm going to grab some dirt and
then we're going to expand the forest
have fun I'm chopping down the forest no
no how do we
theora it's okay it's just you're
chopping it down to make it
bigger it all has a purpose it all
serves a purpose how does not making it
bigger I'm just getting more apples okay
good that's fine too uh how does how
does one plant apple
trees oh apples are random draw from
these
leaves you got to punch the leaves yeah
you can punch the leaves and or just you
know let them disappear on its own see
what you can replant the trees okay I'm
going to create a forest that branches
off from where we're planting a ton of
wheat
so it's going to go this way here's the
path to the
forest
go come here help me where are you
[Music]
putting you to work Kuba oh okay either
sword or mine oh not Birch Oak only wait
that oak trees
okay I'll sort I'll sort okay have
fun have fun finding the right chest was
going to get a snack um just so you know
in the storage room area I've uh I've
separated things by how the chests are
actually labeled so if it says nether
chest that's blocks from the nether if
it says ocean chest that's blocks from
the ocean oh yeah so they're already
like pre-labeled that
way nice yeah and then the ones that are
in the regular storage area have signs
that say like the top chest has these
things in them the bottom chest has
these things in them that kind of
thing yeah oh
W good job yeah so by the way go we got
some heart of the Seas but it's like so
useless I thought you could use it for
Atlantis but you got to make a whole
ocean no I just need a little bit of
water I can put I can build a conduit
and and it's cool but yeah yeah it's
useless yeah so
sad but it's
fancy I can build it anyway
oh yeah if you're up for it I mean it's
useless can you build under not
underwater or is it only underwater go
I looking at your chat for the
answer
um only water or also only on water
well try to make it in the fishing
pond or in the dolphin uh
pool how much water is
necessary then the the dolphin can can
swim even faster if it has the conduit
he's not allowed in the he's not allowed
in the conduit pool he stays down there
in the stinky dolphin confinement Zone a
that's where
belongs yeah he stiny dolphin what oh
yeah okay he bit me yeah true he's a
little [\h__\h] yeah yes I think the grass
will grow in go into the
aquarium I'm stuck I feel the grass
should spread from there Dolph John yeah
that guy
sucks we hate DOL John
it'll grow
okay I can't go that
way all right start mining cobblestone
cuz we need like a I think we have a
cobblestone maker that g made
right how many you need we need what do
we need how many second second I'm
making the my myy you guys this is more
all we need 20 stacks of cobblestones
one stack of
trap okay okay okay we already got a
couple we should make a cob chest let me
check how how much Cobblestone we have
in the other chest wait this is I don't
know if I does it have to be
Cobblestone specifically I guess it
doesn't it just needs to be 20 stacks of
something oh then we should have enough
stacks of things right all right let's
make make a moossy cobblestone stack
cracked stone bricks stack chiseled
stone bricks stack
I can't ride zombie
horses they'll fall apart they're
running in the chest by the cobblestone
generator I'll put uh put like full
stacks of stuff if you find any good
idea okay 20 you say 20 yeah we need
20 we're so ready for this there's so
many stacks in
here
hands make a torches
one two Golden Arrow spectral Arrow 1
two three four five 6 seven8 N9 10
There's a Zombie 11 12
Stacks sorry that's my fault oh a lot of
zombies oh there's a really a lot of
them spawning okay whoopsies I again man
I don't think you need to mine at all we
have enough stacks of things hold on to
light the new yeah yeah that's what I
was going back to do I'm sorry all right
that's fine hey more full stack I added
them just now when you left thank you
okay we're done stop I'm sorry I didn't
think SP this many look how
much wait wait but there's only 42 on
that one you need more no no no no
that's enough this we have not a full no
no that's
okays I swear to God dead beat I know I
know I've seen the error of my ways okay
I'm sorry Kuba you did all of that wait
sand sand is going to follow although I
guess that's no it should be okay we're
just going to be stacked up okay okay
okay I have too much stuff look how
efficient she
is maybe then trees can't go there
that's fine why is it so slow anyway can
it not be faster come on it's my
ping always the Ping
cursed ping
pong oh it's my chicken
sper what the hell get out did you spawn
there oh you have a new family
now a little fence around people can't
fall down
it's
close count count the stacks go try
counting the stacks why don't you count
them for me why they're over 20 you can
him yourself I need to complete this one
stack okay let me for your own character
development right let me finish oh no
the other let me finish it's unpaid
anyway of
undying okay there okay what 3 6 9 12 15
16 17
18 23 Stacks but at least now we have
extra ooh
yeah because what if somebody di who's
died the most here what's that noise who
turned on that music me
it's a broken
one it's a broken one I don't know what
what it
is there
way no why do you do that no hey stop
coughing someone get that man some B
She's coughing cover your mouth cover
your mouth spreading
germs it's like an audio book it's a
voice pack it's a voice Packie I like
this voice pack I didn't buy it I want
to refund my money
back this not quite my
Tempo my Tempo I'm
scared he's running fiara
run W stop until he kills
you y That's How do I get into this
dolphin Center I think it's over where
is the
dolphin it better still be there he's
gone I think he no
way he must have despawned or so because
like why would he die we more carpets
four carpets oh yeah yeah we did oh my
God I should probably go share the
Sheep again it's fully grown M but uh
for carpet should already be possible
with the yeah stuff that's in there yeah
the only thing is I don't think we have
enough iron cuz I need I need five oh
wait what is it four Hoppers but we only
have 11 I think we keep right now we
have two Hoppers
now oh we do somewhere oh yeah yeah okay
well I wait for the forest to grow all
organized oh there's a chicken in there
we got a chicken I got to use the rest
of the iron wait Dolphins can
drown yeah they can also
have no air I guess they do go up for
air I feel so stupid right now but I
think they do wait what yeah imagine a
sea and
droning couldn't be me couldn't be
me okay I got the
carpet oh there's a Sher box
no are you perhaps
Gess when I say again like a
issue good one girl another one
happy he's happy that you met with the
one and only Phoenix mommy come on
chicken yourself blessed come on chicken
come on time to go it's time to accept
the new world you're in come
on get moving y he should be grateful
we're going to be like feeding him and
stuff yeah or killing him no we're going
to be killing him just don't let him you
don't need to hear oh just giving him
free like C before you know the end yeah
that's how the meat gets really good is
that you don't tell them that you're
going to kill them you know they leave
happy lives when we're done with the
series I promise to my chickens I'm
coming back to the server every day to
feed them every day I will come back a I
will I might not stream it but I will
open the server every day and I'll come
have made the for so much bigger isn't
this Ser we going to get down though
anyway I'm going to pay to keep it open
just to feed the
chickens all right well I'm ready to
start if anybody wants to
helpit I I'll come to you yeah what are
you doing I want to learn how to make
it yeah I'll still work on the trees
is it like version
specific yeah yeah it said it should
work for uh version 1.14 and up oh wait
I got to ask chat a question chat should
I build the um mob spawner XP farm uh
should I build it like at the end of
this Atlantis
Road or uh cuz it's close to spawn right
or should it be further away from
Spawn what or Forest needs to be bigger
far away is better okay we might uh I
have slabs we can build a little bit
further wait how many blocks
away live Tod is bugged no it's not I
just changed how they
look yeah don't worry about it what did
you do to us nothing nothing I just you
know manipulated your images a little
bit it's fine don't worry about
it
6 oh is this your for expansion pack
can we yes it is MHM I'm working on the
my my it's going to be a really big
forest and we're going
to's Mor's M app go wait you can put
melons in the my myy yeah
exactly oh the melon
money got some here that's good oh hell
yeah mhm damn you should make like if
you ever do like a charity stream again
or so maybe plant some trees to make a m
oh that's a goodidea idea yeah every
every uh Super Chat that we get for
charity plants a tree in Minecraft
yeah yeah wait no but then we take the
money then we take the money from that
and then we donate it to plant real
trees okay yeah okay real trees real
moris we want them real moris yeah
breaking Dimensions with that
[Music]
one 80 bucks for one tree
all right I'm at the end of the Atlantis
uh okay thing if anybody wants to is the
only normal one well yeah she's the only
human out of all of us so I thought I
would leave her image untouched is she
do is she she's
British British people are humans
kpet go so make for you four carpets
yeah we have it we have it in a
shulker there dare
wait where did everybody go wait
helloing extra slabs I got to I got to
extend this place a little bit extra
slabs coming slabs okay go is making I'm
here anyway I'll make them nice I can't
believe you can just make a PPP that's
so
cool yeah what the heck imagine having
the brain capacity chat I know I don't
you can't just make PPP your name has to
be also Amelia Watson true only she is
capable oh made a lot but why isn't it
the the papap then I don't
understand previously property because
it is
previously yeah true that was already a
PPP and I guess that was
P should we just talk in abbreviations
from now on thank you
why isn't yes why
stop stop you stop that would be maybe a
joke stream idea just only talk in
abbreviations could be
fun sounds
hard
BRB getting more mushrooms too
lol all right I'll need you guys help in
a second just this quick maybe we can
expand the forest in time to go watch
how the PPP is made almost done F
FR FR F
FR for real for real oh stop she's
they're actually oh my God I'd never
last that kind of stream
SM I can't think of so many need to make
some
notes TGF
ladies wow it's not Friday though it's
not TG T TG TG M TG M TG I don't know M
Tuesday Wednesday Thursday Friday satday
Sunday it's one wow I just Dr The
Talky let's see what she's doing wow
here feel like I'm going to fall down
can I make a wall around here am yeah
maybe fences would be good or something
BRB BRB um
GTG got I will tame that
horse tame him tame
him I wish we find some I still can't
ride this horse it's just a donkey give
me those does not meant for
horses a no horse around youa no horing
around donkey donkey
full myth Shrek watch along
when oh man we've seen it so many times
k k you and I have seen it together
right we watched it we did a one and two
watch along we really need to get the
others in on this yeah we watched both
damn oh Marathon at my place yeah was in
the beginning honestly it felt so short
I
know shre shre I'm always down for a
shre watch along why is his name Shrek
what do you think you're mine now donkey
could it be a reference to a German word
of surprise which is I'll look it up
right Shrek I am surprised I am a shre
why is he I knew that was a
j girl related to the German Shreck
meaning Fe or bro uhuh you hit the nail
on the head K oh my God that's why I
brought it up because I I thought it
kind of sounds like and you know ogres
they surprise you right with their looks
so you're like
shre oh Shrek Shrek lure new Shrek lure
just
dropped Shrek years later we're still
getting new Shrek lure what a
world e that makes me so happy that that
I speak German wow you were right you
you donkey donkey me I'm donkey or don't
be a dony I came the donkey okay good
nice how tall is get shreked idiot Shrek
is probably like 8T tall block of iron
oh yeah he's pretty big he's a big
guy yeah yeah oh my wait Shrek is based
on 7 feet Fiona would be 510 as a human
and 6'4 as an ogis oh she
ogis it's like oh ah female ogre
ogis hot not g NGL
NGL hot what in what way Kiara would you
like to elaborate girl win yeah where's
our ogis in h live
English no no it would be cool you can
have like an alternate
form she changes at night yeah for all
the night streams that's cute okay
that's cute yeah yeah see see see some
people in the in the chat are like
hot y see there's something for everyone
here
iy you guys like an ogre lady huh I
think they don't not like an ogre
lady why not what's there not to
like okay I'm going to make oh yeah you
do bunch of iron bars you're just joking
you're not serious about it I'm going to
put you in front of an ogre lady and
you're going to be
like
help don't out them like that
Kiara be careful here cuz I got to build
down somehow I ogr they're fine with it
with water that's why they're myy
fans wa ogre outfit next who's going to
do an ogre outfit not me ogre onesie
with little Shrek ears on it Callie it's
got to be you come on you have this
whole like Shrek
thing through your whole streaming
career here no not
really a little
joke just a little T hopefully I don't
die doing that
[Music]
we catch you bers gate three ogre K oh
yeah oh yeah Bal oh man balers gate is
so good I wish I could have played the
full game yeah have you not played it on
your own no well I I did a little bit
right like simultaneously when we did
the collabs but then I felt like doing
both is kind of rough and then I left it
to the collabs only but then you know
you know what happened to the collapse
so and I was like ah I don't know
continuing now is a little bit a little
bit late I didn't realize that we had
actually finished act
one oh yeah we kind of did yeah M we
just didn't like we had to do like one
thing and then it would have been
finished I think right yeah well oh
maybe I thought we already did it and we
didn't realize we passed act one we were
in active oh for real yeah that's okay
though it's hard to do a really long
Ballers gate play play through it's a
long game meanwhile narissa yeah narissa
she did the whole thing she's crazy he
play it like several times I also have a
friend who's played balers gate six
times with
mods yeah
je well you can play it differently
every time that's the amazing thing
about these kind of
games I love
that ready for the part where guys help
okay I'm here what you
mean uh hold on we're going
to not a single app
water let's grab a stack I guess we can
do sand for this one because it's
fine build sand it would be
fine 20 up in any of these like Corners
thingies yeah good at going AFK now that
we need
her boss please put me in charge of
golden apples I promise I won't let you
down wait uh oh yeah am I the boss yeah
well I kind of figured since you set
this whole thing up 21 cuz I don't know
I I count it but I don't know if it's
right wait if a block is 64 and then
it's
403 at the end of it cuz I didn't count
wait is there water down there how are
we going to get down oh oh you got the
water oh just temporary
yeah that shadowy spot little suspicious
hold
on oh I can go up with the uhoh with the
water
wobbly water oh shoot 4 fre I was right
okay
[Music]
nice I'm going to go to SN I'm going to
maybe we should sleep you want to sleep
you can sleep yeah let's sleep all right
good night oh God good is out in the
open though oh AFK G we have to defend
her I'll try where is she okay I got a
bow too she at the at the the future PPP
I got an I got a bow but it's not coming
closer right now where are
you at the future oh over there oh
beyond the pandas
gotcha ooh
cool I can fight him too I can fight him
nice going to waste these arrows like
that we have we can use infinite bow
yeah nice good idea
I'll don't have it at hand
so hit
him hey okay cancel Arrow cancel it's
fine it doesn't matter let's go sleep
yeah doesn't it not matter oh I guess a
majority of players can sleep okay
yeah hey Chad how do I cancel an arrow
if I'm like about to shoot no it's not
that's a majority but uh so this n we'll
we'll await
we started having a sleepover party
without
[Music]
you no
okay which item oh okay thank you chat
I'm not much of a bow Smith but I'd like
to become
one Co goo oh did I just see her move I
[Music]
imagine yeah back with the abbreviations
it's not really an abbreviation I
guess I wonder why it's like why it's
like zzz for sleep like where did it
start not much of a b yeah not much of a
boson I feel like at least GD is one of
the few ones of these onop which are
which is like the same all over the
world like you know how for
example bark bark and woof woof they're
like different in different languages
but z z z is like same everywhere
oh uh since
1918 yeah it's it's been used to
symbolize
[Music]
snoring who decided it who who decided
it uh no one really knows but it just
started appearing I guess in Like Comics
and newspapers I
[Music]
suppose kind of like you know like
Comics have like the Z like those kind
of things zap
Zippity so now we're just like chilling
here oh goa's back gooa can you like
sleep with us in our beds sleepover
party come over gooa oh sorry it's okay
it's okay no sorry it's because uh one
of those Phantoms spawned and you know
we want to be safe up there when we work
wait you didn't protect me what if you
came we did we did we protected your
honor we killed it and then we ran away
after we killed one which means another
one could have spawned
totally oopsy Dole I we all sleeping in
the right beds oh I saw
you
hey oh good morning
oh sleep with me did the forest grow did
the forest
grow dang it oh this grass is really
slow need help is there a way to make
grass grow faster everyone oh thank you
for the 50
wo faster ah the grass you need to
connect it to other dirt blocks and then
it will just happen got to wait for this
cuz it's going to start going yeah okay
well I'll wait
then that's really a lot yeah thank you
so
much bone meal bone meal is for trees
that's what I'm going to start doing to
get apples uh afterward after the forest
is ready let's go to the be while we
wait we can go watch him we don't need
the corners we just need like to enclose
this water area okay
wa can we make a clay
bricks clay we have a ton of clay yeah I
was thinking we should use some of the
clay stuff that's a good idea yeah feel
free there's tons so yes yes go
ahead make pretty
bricks wait did I make too many no okay
you got to cook clay oh it
requires yeah yeah we got oh we could
pick up some lava from the never so we
can have endless you know no coal for
the thing but instead just use lava good
idea yeah lava Farm kind of thing I know
maybe not a f that was one good thing
about going into the never at least
let's
go yeah it's a long
process I me put these back in
here so this is the
PBP yeah oh wait there still that will
require me getting more buckets that was
SC
I guess we can get there's like one side
that needs to be sealed so the enemies
fall in here and weat them goodbye
fish one more right one more oh yeah I
got it oh you got it okay she got it
she's got it poo Fight Club
yeah looks kind of nice actually as if
we purposefully made a nice pattern nice
design good design skills
yeah totally on
purpose
premeditated wish I can give it a
home looks
nice Temple of
PPP I don't know we need to do something
eventually yeah get
him so watching watching nature do its
thing huh what does that mean
[Music]
how can we help now Amy uh I'm just
waiting for this water to dissipate hold
on oh wait I have a sponge but it's wet
actually it's go it's gone already damn
it okay well now we have an extra
bucket oh sorry where did all the other
Pockets go all right one second I got to
watch this video more sorry you guys are
just waiting for me no it's okay it's
cool to look at to be honest
I'm so excited we're getting
sick must be not if you're not streaming
I think or like taking a video you got
to react to it live or some but then
what about watch alongs wouldn't by that
metric watchalong is not be react
content cuz it's not on stream yeah it
yeah I thought this has to be showing on
stream oh no no no I I don't mean it
needs to be showing on stream but I feel
like you should be at least re not doing
the we have to go back up there Som we
need ladders for us ladders we can make
easy I shall make we need like 20
something
okay 20 lers let me guess you make it
super dark in
there uh yeah we're going to we're going
to build a platform up there
cool live myth reaction yeah o sh box I
should have checked out how ladder
damn it wait wait wait wait
wait okay okay we're good we're
good I'm eating like rice crisps they're
pretty
good are they covered in chocolate or
just blend sour cream and
onion
oh I was thinking of different kinds I
think okay I got a I got uh almost two
stacks of ladders
okay going to throw him at
you wait wa here uh uh oopsie
uh scolding requires string doesn't it I
don't think we have that much
string I think we need
scaffolding I mean yeah okay okay up she
goes and we are looking up oh if you
guys grab some uh some blocks we need to
make a platform on each side so it'll be
like
uh four platforms extending on each
side eight yeah at the top I have some
platform what are they called half block
I can
do do it like how I did here but on each
side blocks or slabs on it
tutorial oh sorry blocks or slab blocks
or
slabs oh um blocks blocks okay
huh
huh I got got blocks wait SLS work too
you don't work I thought that they don't
spawn on slabs uh no don't use wood just
in case if you don't have any other call
jfyi um that only counts when you put
the slab at the bottom of the block for
example cuz you can put them both in the
top and the bottom position so you see
for your Minecraft knowledge thank you
do we extend it this
way it was the bottom
jfyi jfyi I didn't understand what you
meant there for a second but now I get
it really yeah now you know how far is
it again
am uh eight blocks long two twoo
wide five four five six seven eight nice
this is some real Sky Block kind of [\h__\h]
now this is react content
feel the danger oh you want some walls
too am with
that uh yeah yeah we're going to encase
everything in a two block high wall for
now sick you want a side of walls with
that yummy go back down for more blocks
oh shoot speaking of going
down for this video I think it looks
like a propeller right now like a you
know helicopter yeah what water
down okay give me a second I think
there's water in the uh in the chest
over here the Sher box oh wait I have
water never mind she's doing the water
landing oh I'm just I'm just making the
elevator oh nice can just make a water
elevator Minecraft's
insane oh there goes the Torches torches
oh wait could we make an actual
functional water elevator we have Soul
Sand right what else do you need yeah we
can I don't think we really need a I
mean unless there's something else CU I
don't think this needs a water
elevator oh yeah kelp oh okay I think I
saw
though we got so much stuff go down so I
press uh space right when I jump in the
water uh shift is it shift if you want
to go down it's shift yeah gotcha going
oh
yeah I'll put some whatam call it
torches on the fences maybe oh
help keelly are you coming back to
finish the wall or should I oh yeah I
mean I was going to get more blocks but
you can finish it go ahead okay I going
to watch the rest video yeah
okay oh I had two
torches this looks cool I like this PPP
we should give it a new name I think pip
was actually
cool was it stand
for previously am his property could you
if we have enough buckets uhhuh I need
three more buckets of water three more
buckets I have one I don't know where
all the other I have all the buckets
because I filled them with milk thinking
we need them when I went back but might
if I just can I just I'll I'll go pick
up some water watch out I'm coming up
you mind if I just I'm on the ladder so
I'm just I can bring one but me you know
I actually kind of want to make a whatam
call it a carpet sorry just a little a
carpet I'll put I'll put it back wo wo I
promise I'll put how many
WS what okay two wool
okay I don't like opening
doors get oh you want to just jump over
hey hey hey I see what you're doing
there four buckets of water four buckets
I have one you can bringing one uh oh my
God I have four oh okay you kfp is silly
guys you guys are silly what did you
guys do okay now we're going to um the
trap doors okay I said what they were
saying I just out loud a now you're
pointing fingers at each other s they
started
it so we're going to do it like this oh
I see close it
gotcha sides going to be on both
okay sounds good uh oh oh oh wait like
okay I'm coming with the buckets I just
went up the ladder and realized there's
no opening there wow perfect now no
delay in going over
fences hi are we pouring the water here
in the middle uh no no no it's going to
be at the end of this of the Halls that
we're standing in right now but uh maybe
you should pour
it I think we can't make the W until we
get another sheep we only have
one this is not a
sheep this is a sheep o it's getting
dark in here it's a sheep Ena don't tell
it otherwise it's going to cry don't let
him
know TR it's very much a
sheep
okay it's white it's thick it's
fluffy mhm honestly I didn't even lead
it there it just like went over the
fence somehow and suddenly was
there it really wanted to be with the
Sheep it wanted to give it some
company
the yeah we're supposed to put them on
both sides sorry the water pushes you oh
W if you fall down you have one half
heart he not bad that's that's how it's
supposed to work it's like exact amount
oh so I'm
zombie now nice test see tested it for
us more water so it's going to push you
go to watch out H watch out don't worry
get washed away flush back out to sea
yeah it shouldn't break the sand I think
she's not
gous meow is St down there no I'm I'm
made my way out oh is it in here down so
the hopper is already working I can tell
you that you got your stuff yeah did I
didn't die but like I broke a block and
it went into the hopp okay nice waa
tested I did I did waa approved it was
on purpose according to
Kaku of course can we get a translator
not thank you thank
you nice
ooh wo the view from here is really nice
you can really see what we all made
together
a right damn it's pretty big
whoa that's a good I can see from here
too ni it's
teing be a shame if yall SLI hey
girl she sleeping I trust girl she's not
going to push me off I couldn't
reach points finger
oh oh it's
working nice kind
of I don't Spa him in yet I'm in here
yeah send enemies send enemies wait
pause pause the game wait pause the game
I got to figure out how to get out of
here got destroy oh look a spider hey
look taking down the water elevator
please it's working oh yeah go down go
down down go down go down over there no
go down dang it I got to put the water
in they won't go down is that a
skirlington
[Music]
that's bad idea to use
sand yeah that's
a who
died wa did all the Hoppers and chest
blow up oh just the Hoppers all right I
can repair this part grab Oh that's oh I
got to eat I got to eat I got to eat
hold on you have a bucket of fish
oh God oh God it's going to need some
repairs for
sure that was so good I saw like GAA die
and then I saw the sand falling and then
I slipped and I fell off with the sand
falling cuz you put it and laughed at
me yeah I get it I think it exploded
about in the middle it was
midway it's okay it's okay I'm staying
down here man blame you for that one
back going up there PPP giving
PTSD sounds about
right but hey you know at least we know
it spawns
monsters K mod K mod I'm not K mod this
was fun I I enjoyed every single
millisecond of that I think it exploded
in the middle is so maybe we'll need
some pairs in the
middle yeah that that creeper would have
e exploded up at the top or at the
bottom so maybe the top would have been
better maybe not he launched yeah we
just need to fix the sides the water's
out now uh yikes I'll fix I'll fix the
bottom if it could light up first maybe
at daytime might be a good time to I
don't know yeah maybe we should sleep
okay more stuff will
spawn oh oh really I'll put torches up
there right now okay just while it's a
work in progress I guess s sleepy my
time yeah sleeping time the beds are
being used sleepovers are
nice I miss
sleepovers all right there's already
stuff up there spawn so I'm just going
to go to sleep mon nearby so we can't
sleep oh there's zombie hold on I got
him hello kill him hey idiot stop
watching us while we sleep you creepy
weirdo my it's fine he'll live oh wow
okay wow all right he punched me back so
you know what we're even
we are even
Steven even St even Steven who's Steven
know freaking weird freaking weird
zombie outside watching us while sleep
yeah
the no do you have my stuff I have I
have your stuff cool do you need help I
have the W Bow Wow Bow oh no the Wow Bow
sorry excuse me yeah I think wow bow
sounds nicer
so it's or you
say let's just call it wo bow like w
this is a bow it's called a bow it's not
a
bow okay so it's a wo
bow yeah okay oh there's Hoppers missing
and we don't have any iron I think we
should have some iron
missing yeah yeah I only found one no
they they br oh no so recently I split
up an iron block that gave nine iron I
feel like we should be able to make some
more yeah we have 17 ingots so we should
be able to make a couple more yeah let's
try cooking yeah it's just five per
Hopper so we just need 15 iron and then
you put a chest in the middle if
somebody wants to build it okay sure why
we I make the Hoppers how many Hoppers
do we
need uh we need three we have a million
chests so oh yeah we have a ton of
chests yeah oh okay yeah there's plenty
if you want to we need to use them I'll
get these trap
doors you got the chest Cena or do I
need to grab some I got the chest I I'll
leave it all to you I'll make the three
Hopper leave it all to you and uh me see
if I can want to mine a little bit I'm
going to
mine find some more
iron
Bo Japan bro
three okay sh well actually if we make
pppp our iron is actually Sal cuz some
of the zombies or something drop iron
bars oh oh yeah that's temporarily we
can get more yeah there's some a lot of
good sides to PPP so I think it's good
that we get
it okay I'm bringing the Hoppers over it
will yield more iron surely yo if we
could make an iron farm though that
would be amazing but it's not really
hard to do yeah we need at least one
villager that's right at Le
two them here all right okay let me see
and I was trying to get one yesterday I
was like mining endlessly but they just
don't show up they've got to show up at
some point so I'm going to keep trying
okay I put the hoppers in the the
shelter box
nice nice
Hoppers hippity hoppity you are now am
his property yeah
no the
hopper Kitty see that's a good sign we
got a kitty cat wish you were a villager
but that's
okay baby
cat more cats is this white
cat oh I wish I had I wish I
had go fishing Ena go fishing you have a
fishing rod there's a fishing rod
somewhere we have string to make
one is it is the fishing rod broken the
one we had before uh no there should
still be one
there okay bucket of Sal Z
tight thanks tight tight is that is that
German yeah it is knew it it means
Health oh Health yes just Health be
healthy dummy why' you see much can I
get your help over here on this side yes
all the sand fell cuz the bottom ones oh
so we got to reput this hand cuz I got
to put
Sal Panda's freaking pissed at me tell
won't use sand just in case it brecks
again
yeah we got other
blocks we have
Str should be good
6 hours later SpongeBob is a fishing rod
oh there it's car a stick that's not our
fishing rod oh wait there's a fishing
rod beside it is the top like blocked
off or can I still get like build up
there no you can get up there there's a
a letter to get out okayo oh
wait wrong block oh here wait don't
start from the oh we got to get up here
honestly I feel like I've learned so
much about Minecraft just from this from
doing this even though it's not standard
Minecraft oh yeah give me one fact have
letters oh oh like I didn't know about
the grass thing right
guys what grass thing you know that you
need to have like a grass block
connected to dirt that like leads to the
you need to have like one grass block
and then it makes more grass blocks I
didn't know
that I know there's speed at the top I
didn't know that either
uh just knock them off I have like no
weapon because you got my things but
I'll try yeah I put him I put him in one
of the chests down here when you can
back a glistering watermelon slice
better uhoh
was a Miss I'm so sorry that was you're
not allowed to go back up
there she just attracts them she
attracts creepers hope you
helped
M me
was there no uh Diamond chest plate
within my
face oh I have it you have it oh let's
go oh you know what speaking of which
I'm going to take it
off I'm going to put my diamond chest
plate into the final chest box oh that's
a
spoter die monster more Str give me
swear to God just die monster all the
time what if I don't ow you don't have
any you don't oh no you know it no you
don't have any
arm no please have
mercy please God oh thank you oh
oh you know next time I I see you IRL
I'm going to do the thing where I hold
something high above you and you will
jump and not be able to catch it
oh no I uh I was trying to fight
something and I fell let me pick up
those okay Watson you're doing God's
work don't worry about
it all good we here to assist if we can
feel like there's um there's a lot of
obstacles in the way and uh by a lot of
obstacles I mean
somebody you mean all of us need to
leave your work work space what what do
you mean what nothing nothing it's fine
we're do it's a hard head Zone not a
hard headone hi
Captain all right shouldn't die again
but I'm going
to oh well it's G ah I took it it wasn't
really I think it went into the
hopper blistering melon slice your
diamond Armor's in the other one that
should be good
oh you can't eat it okay it sucks I
can't see you white catle where are you
then I I have your helmet too wait same
there you are I took a different helmet
thank you that's actually I think that
is possibly not even my helmet but
yeah C please if you put torch under
sand it breaks automatically
oh speed St lat bone meal bone meal how
are you supposed to get underneath the
sandz gr trees keeps falling good
question yes for the
fish fish yummy fish where did all the
bone meal
go we have no bone
meal maybe somewhere in some chest still
I can't see the cat Kelly Kelly Kelly in
your light colors chest cuz I see no
other theme there than light colors
there's nine bone blocks that you can
turn into bone meal oh okay cool yeah
know that's supposed to be end chest but
I guess you don't get those things in
the end never mind I yeah like the
Sandstone yeah so I thought it was just
your light colors chest
whoopsies okay chicky chicks uh it's
time you know it's time there's many
orders all made by
me
[Music]
so oh hey I can kill them one by one
with this okay never
mind okay never mind okay myth is hungry
feed
us just keep falling all
right sorry K love you though love you
right
soon you know I love you right
okay I'll also get this
CLE okay enough okay I can now save you
I need more seeds why are they running
they're gone why are they trying to
escape I'll get you out of there C I got
to leave in 20
minutes okay has it already been so long
maybe Le So Long Farewell how long has
it beening 2
hours oh God it's getting dark again
okay
sleep just
finish take your
time let me know when it's ready for
sleepy
time Stu spawn while we're sleeping
right for yeah probably
but
torches I mean if you leave if there's
no water it'll just
[Music]
burn oh yeah but the creepers don't burn
do they do creepers burn uh-huh oh wait
do they not I've seen them walk around
during daytime but I don't think so yeah
they they don't
burn and spiders also don't burn I think
I got framed for a chicken Maser
yesterday what did I do hey yeah well
yesterday I was like you know slaying
some chickens to get feathers and then
the chat uh like I can't see the chat
thingy but the chat told me that the AI
was saying that Mory Ki brutally
murdered the chickens and that's why the
chat is sad what I had nothing I mean if
it died it probably had something to do
with it but not in the way that they are
trying to make it seem like a oh my God
not me wasit are you girls in bed
someone sto my bed what who keeps on
whistling by the way what the
birds it's the birds so loud
loudly are you waiting for me in bed yes
okay just dropping some eggs really
quick
okay no no God damn it oh no chicken
chicken don't hurt are chaotic okay I'm
here oh let me take a
picture hold when comes I need all of
your guys' help just finish it quickly
that way okay
okay we shall
do all right teamwork what you got to do
c we're going to connect all the corners
to make to right now it's like a cross
right but we're going to connect the
corners to make like a big
platform and then uh yeah so we'll need
a lot of stacks for
that I'm going to stay out of the way
enough materials just don't use sand cuz
it's going to fall
wood um did someone use
sand well yeah probably not wood ah
[Music]
okay SLS out the Cobblestone right uh no
not slabs I think BL
okay is it safe up there right now yeah
okay
hey what's the percentage drop rate for
apples guys okay low it's low we just
got to wait so we got to make it into a
platform yeah so connect the corners
like uh like I'll give like a little
sample like this all the way to the next
corner and then fill it in okay yeah oh
go
window got a
wall all right planting then
you good go you're trying to say
something no
no if if anybody has
uh somebody could go down and make more
cuz I I ran out of platform or um trap
doors I don't know where they went the
rest of them I got some yeah sure you
need well it was a full stack so I don't
know probably like 30 okay I got you am
I'll make them now I'm already
here okay thank you
yeah let's see okay doors teamwork all
the wood I can find this is so
[Music]
cute dirty or
so trapo
cute pikach
time okay
we need planks what did you
photographing us and you have more block
without my
consent
uh
okay I'm going to sell
it to the highest bidder did you get my
double chin you might need more wood uh
no I took it from quite above so it
should be flattering
okay don't worry I'm also worried about
my double chin
we'll make aaia ones it doesn't matter
what kind of wood it is right on
it uh no
okay AIA AIA sorry stop stop
that whatever it's
called paparia paparia
papar oh that's that's what else
okay we're just waiting on trap doors
and then hold on watching the rest of
the video to see what it does next it
looks so
beautiful looks so proper
colorful Patchwork this whole island is
Patchwork all right I'm going to down
some should do it pat family all right
so now we're we're doing the wall it's
going to be two blocks high so have more
blocks more oh I didn't bring any
uhoh yeah need to go down
two maybe maybe an apple drop I've
almost got enough we got 21 trap doors
I'm just chopping some wood we do not
have enough
wood leave it
me I'm my I'm great at annihilating
forit sorry that's
wrong what I fell I made a one block too
early I think I'll replant
them okay
I just want to see if we can get an
Apple just one apple get those
apples oh iess opening there yeah it
seems like it okay we got to help so
that should be
enough an
opening wait do we need openings oh
maybe
not no we'll close it all okay yeah I
just need you to get yeah
okay so I have 30 but it's 10 of each
different type of wood so it's not
really consistent but it's enough yeah
it doesn't matter cool I'm coming it's
crazy how much more efficient y'all have
gotten at Minecraft compared to when F
myth first
started Pros we're pro G now we got
better okay so now we're going to seal
it but it's going to be like this like
this and then we don't we don't need
this EXT really doesn't want me to oh oh
okay guys how do we swim the shift right
you guys can start building off mine if
you want to you don't another I'm going
to get
blocks hold space sorry thanks guys but
yeah I was such a noob I played
Minecraft for the first time after I
joined the Holo for the first time I
think I played Minecraft before but was
back
2009 or something really really early
Minecraft here you go oh
I played Ed and then here no problem am
I the only one have another Quest For
You c yeah let me know what do I need to
do I need more torches to light up above
thees what we're building right now got
I have some oh yeah okay I'll go grab
some be right
back here never mind what I was go up
top for now and just put the Torches
down up there here I'll drop just light
up the what we're building right now
like what we're putting down that way
stuff doesn't spawn up what is pocket I
on the iPod
Touch that's the thing that all the
six-year-old IP touch gu say Minecraft
for everything I watched a video
recently where somebody got uh Minecraft
running on a calculator oo I believe
that yeah that was the first time I
heard a Minecraft zombie and I cried a k
me so bad cute I never had an iPod a
jelly oopsie
see torch I only had normal MP3 players
the ones with the US lot of torches it's
okay we'll never be low on torches
again you want to know how many torches
I
made I made about
wow so we'll never need torches again
they're all in the wood they're in the
wooden box but I'm going to give some to
Amy okay I'm all the blocks again
Callie said how many yes yep let there
be light down there can you can you
close up on the back of the at the
bottom yeah huh you know that one
there's like one uh wall that the tall
wall That's not finished yet okay it
needs to be finished then check it
out ah that one
okay okay here you go Amy
your torches oh two walls actually I'll
get a few more blocks actually we're
outs
bu yeah no but it's okay it's okay I'm
getting something else side quest failed
successfully what apple quest that's
okay oh no no no the Torches yeah I did
make too many but that's okay don't
finish it all the way
cuz uh should we no it's okay I don't
think stuff we spawn in here hopefully
not well I guess I'll make it fancy put
some torches for now
okay all right now apple
quest it's going to be so
colorful should have had should have
made the whole thing in those fancy
terracotta
blocks oh yeah I don't think we had
enough though yeah he okay I'm going to
make the back side like that um o creep
creeper but it's in the water there's
like
a
here
uhhuh you see there's like one wall
That's not there's like two walls that
aren't finished down there uhhuh oh
boy I'm sorry it's okay it's okay it's
okay nothing much has been destroyed uh
chest and Hoppers are still there yes
yes yes yes that's what's important I
bought w
you know die in the water such was not
the case all right well we just need to
finish the yeah those tall walls down
I'm on it I'm on it I'm on it I'm on it
okay upstairs she's on it on
it on your on your way up there's like
one that's halfway built if you could
finish that one too I'm on it okay doing
bu at the same time watching you and
then we'll be done pretty much you guys
probably want to move out of the way cuz
I'm going to start putting well actually
I'll wait till she's done to put the
water so she doesn't
well no do it now I'm water right oh
wait k look look to your left there's I
don't know if you can reach it but
there's like a little Gap there oh okay
I can just that do oh they're watching
wait I'm being judged okay I do good job
what are you
dropping dropping trash on
me oh there we go nice and then I don't
know how you're going to get
down fly I won't be able to place these
last blocks though cuz like I need to I
think we can we shouldn't die if you
drop from here I don't think oh wa let
me let me get over there first in the
middle and then I'll like replace it and
have no oh wait maybe now I do now I
do oh
thanks I'll go here and
then and then I guess I'll die gu I'll
die here
guess I'll die that works too that was a
really genuine guess I'll die jump
bye oh I survived I survived out I'm
just waiting for the death the death
text to come up at the bottom all right
if you guys want to get up here cuz I'm
going to we'll take out the Torches but
now I'm going to put the water so I want
to get in the way oh it's night time
and going to mine my way out and then
I'll fix
it yeah
wait wait don't take the Torches out yet
oh sorry sorry sorry sorry not a single
god dog dog on Apple chest oh okay okay
okay wait
chest in the
chest no okay should I use on the tree
you
guys shears no it doesn't work for
apples like uh it shears are the most
efficient to get rid of leaves but it
will not drop apples when you do that I
see so I should just use other random
things
yeah just a a sword or bird is up here
scared me
yeah Bird
Bye it's
gone wait it should the water shouldn't
be flowing all the way down I don't know
why it's doing
that we can sponge it up
maybe yeah well if you bring up some
spuse which chest is the spawn I can
find it I can find it but I'm just
replacing the chest
fast oh creeper creeper watch out no
this oh
no creepers really like
to I didn't blow up too much we got to
put torches down up
[Music]
top oh oh it's okay it's not it's not
too bad he killed my parot oh oh there's
zombies just log out just log out I
understand to log out and then should I
go to sleep okay I'm out yeah everybody
else just go to sleep sorry it's got an
apple
okay we good oh no bird dead oh no all
the parrots are like going instinct I'm
going to
sleep watch
bed Instinct that's not how you say it
okay you're good you guys come
back we can come back yep morning time
extinct are we good mhm morning time
yeah there's probably going to be Ms
there still oh yeah oh yeah it's
[Music]
working zombie zombie be like two apples
I'm starting to get
apples
no all
right yeah chig gami love apples don't
you know finish this wall again and uh
need sponge cuz I don't know why the
water actually I don't need sponge I
just
yeah oo
drown drop that trident baby come on
going to get a trid one of these
days fix anything can happen H I might
need a couple more blocks I have a
couple but I don't think it's enough
yeah I think we get more I
have it's not
enough okay I'll go grab some
okay who died up there
some oh a person di why you bring your
bird up here he followed me me oh
[Music]
no well now he'll never follow you again
CH I rub salt in the W bring this for
just be enough I think I don't see
anything is it gone can be gone oh so if
I farm the wood the leaves drop the
stuff on their own like apples and oh
okay I didn't know
that we do need more wood so we're going
to have some colorful
ceilings yeah oh oops
it got picked up yeah yeah yeah
yeah what's you doing goall I should
leave this one I didn't want it to go
over the edge but it
it yeah
oops good yeah hopefully I'm going to
try should should I uh plug this
here is it I can trying I plug
it uh not yet hold on
okay I left the Hole by the ladder so it
can get up
here sponge found the
sponges all water but do we have to
place a sponge at the source or just no
no I we don't need it it's
okay SpongeBob Sp Spongebob
spob
Spongebob German
version yeah let's go naughty naughty oh
in English it's Square Pants right in
German shamov means um sponge head oh
Shram any more trap doors here Spong you
close up close up this water I have trap
doors like just put blocks here to get
rid of the water oh my Lord
Bob but where are we putting blocks to
get rid of the water where top Bott no
don't worry e got
it or B I have some block I'll take
these okay G let you drop your
St sponges
BB
sponges I'm fine I'm just
tired no feel continue continue to
practice this is probably like five
minutes away from being down wait I must
I must leave H yeah thinking
I must make my grand exito that's okay
no wait goba wait let me sing to you
really
[Music]
quick there you go that was for you f
thank
you okay good
I'll byee go have a nice
evening getting rid of them yeah we can
just make a bridge like
this how can I
help we're let's go do we need this w
down here
maybe so I'm going to have that empty
chest
here yeah we it okay and the one below
not just wooden things is there
something below okay no there was a hole
but okay all right uh she go all over
I'll yeah yeah I have enough to seal it
[Music]
okay gar
okay I think we
have all right should be done
yay now we can Farm
exp thanks for working on that guys get
some random stuff let me check the rest
of the video just in
case what about this water though it's
not go away
it's down down there's one chapter
that's not closed
should we
check what what was it chat says there's
one chapter that was not closed but not
sure I thought I what that was
did oh I heard chapter oh it's working
there yeah it's working fine
creepies eight golden apples are they
going to be not exploding okay uh they
shouldn't looking good oh yeah oh we can
get gunpowder from here and then with
the gunpowder I can make bombs and with
the TNT I can get us some um never
ride I don't know why they're
exploding or not exploding but they
they're like
making are we safe let we put put a trap
door maybe and then like put it
up I don't know I think it's okay cuz I
I I uh I think it was just seeing us cuz
we were too low yeah oh okay
okay nice great there's so many of them
W well get a lot of bows
too heck yeah this is going to be super
helpful oh oh get so scary but it seems
fine
CH is that normal make sure you're not
make sure you're not standing on the
Rock but you're actually on
yeah
nice ah the carpets are gone are the
carpets supposed uh are carpets supposed
to be there Amy yeah H where did those
go I have them in my
inventory where'd they go
all I can't and place them in the on I
can
try
difficult difficult but it's working
without them what are the carpets
for uh I think it's just supposed to
help like cushion the fall or make it
look nicer
oh it's kind of difficult from this
angle
oh uh-oh bro I think I hit you sorry oh
I think no I think it was the enemy it
felt like it was the enemy was me okay
damn damn
crazy so um maybe no carpet is fine
maybe yeah do we need the
carpet it's working really
nice SEC oh carpet is for the EXP to not
drop into the
[Music]
Hall oh and so creepers don't see you
when
explode it's better so enemies are
higher and don't see you as
easily okay so it's like two two
different mechanisms how are we even
going to fix it I don't even think we
can right now all right maybe here here
you keep somebody keep H give me the
carpet
oh yes yes yes Apple there's a
[Music]
witch yeah from the higher angle you you
could place it probably well we can
really good weapons now cuz of the EXP F
yay oh well
yeah we can get the EXP and the enchant
thing yeah I got it yeah I got it you
put you put a carpet up above
okay with power three oh no I got rid of
it oh
okay yeah I think got it ouch nice nice
comple good job thank you Amit for
leading us through it
yeah actually I think we should block
off the side a little bit because there
is a chance we get hit and
then which side like just on the side
like here on the on above the uh or we
can just put fences
cuz yeah yeah yeah oh check for apples
later hey what you what are you naming
this
one
uh uh I don't know chat you guys have
any ideas pressure spider
clog oh it's
spiders
oh okay something
dropped nand
n yeah I saw in the video they said you
can put um like carpets inside to stop
too many spiders from spawning oh Ed oh
pretty I like the design work p should
you want to call it PP ppp2 or pip
or
um myth mob maker somebody says that
sounds cute M
the previously Lost amma's Property you
guys just want to say p l a p no M M M M
please
okay M I like it it's just ours no one
else's well it was working great until
the other there they go oh nice maybe
they'll despawn if we go away yeah let's
sleep let's well it's working yeah thank
goodness for that Yay good job everyone
nice job
team yay oh yeah we should add that
power three enchantment to the Bodacious
bow true I've got enough exp
yay sleepy time feel like things have
gotten a bit disorganized here though so
I might need to fix that
M oh yeah I'm
coming I kind of want to make an
enchantment table but we would need
books to make a powerful right mhm
probably but it's it really that hard to
find book leather I feel like is not too
hard to find well we got quite a bit of
we have plenty of leather we have hor
our cows and stuff we can breed and then
you know take out of this world we
haven't really gotten any paper like
things H yeah how do you make paper I
had like three pieces of
paper I had sugar like that's it here
it's working cie look I'm test it o y my
turn oo okay I'm excited let's see go
reap some Souls c yeah I've been waiting
for this o there's a bunch of them just
don't Crouch when you're hitting them
cuz the creepers might see you I gotcha
so wa so don't Crouch gotcha yeah oh
there I'm die
dummies oh there's so many there's so
much exp that we can get she's reaping
oh my god well I think uh they saw me oh
all right this is there goes the XP
fall no we'll fix it and as long as we
just like stay further away get out just
get out just get out just get
out oh no I hit wasn't oh God it's it
never ends we we just got to as long as
we were like one step away and and
killing them it was fine so we just got
to you know safety precaution think we
can fix don't you Mor dot dot dot me it
should it should be able to you should
be able to go up close and hit
them it's okay that's how it's supposed
to work so it's okay it's a design
flaw Power Defense game now I'm glad I
tested it before someone else hurt
themsel
okay well what you can do is block off
the area and then just like build kind
of around we can hit them from afar
that's the best we can do if they keep
yeah but somebody has to go in and like
fix like we we can block it and then I
can fix it if we can get blocks in there
okay to seal it but they're going to be
constantly
spawning yeah I have no arrows that's
why oh the
creepers there sure are a lot of them
they should be one XP or one HP one HP I
mean this is one way to farm XP right
it's a different way right just every
here uh who here Ena I'll Trust Ena to
come in and uh fight them cuz they're
one HP I just need to get in there and
put
block on my
way
yeah nice all right what we
doing yeah yeah I I got to get in there
so just go and we'll kill them they
should be one HP except for the spers
Creeper Creeper it's okay they're
they're low okay okay you can probably
get them in one hit I need Flint God
damn it whatever all right just keep
keep getting them as they fall I'm I got
to seal it it's a shooting range yeah
all right all right it's it's sealed for
now it's sealed for now oh not okay okay
I wonder good yeah is it supposed to be
kind of lower do you do you think um
like cuz I feel yeah they saw me and I
was like as I saw I was like oh I bet
they can see me but it was too late okay
need to be lower there one hoer I think
it was working fine when we were
standing like one or two steps behind
like further
behind
M maybe put like a fence or something so
we can't get too close left oh yeah
maybe that'll work yeah okay here's the
limit where you should not go no touy no
touy damn
um that good stream
content is it well it was my turn to
blow it up everybody had blown it up
before so I guess it was yeah we did we
just blow it up several times in the
process some bonding
experience uh I need the Hoppers but I
don't know where they went I think
they're gone no destroyed yeah I bet
that I bet we have some more hold on I
have I had one so I put it in already
okay I'll see if I can find another one
I need like a slab or something I can oh
there you go I have 60 free slabs if you
need them I just needed it to put the
carpet on
two
well or we've only got two iron but let
me see if I can find some
more uh iron block would be nice come on
Minecraft Gods you've really been
testing the team today give us
yeah there's a hole in the side it's up
there I can get
it see get that can't see it oh there up
there
oh oh got one
y why can't I place
this oh cuz there's a slab there oh okay
I see now hold up I'll just
wait this is the feather falling four
nice that's really
good and then oh it's
loud so if we put Gates right here well
we need we need to make more Hoppers I
don't know if we have anymore yeah it's
okay we we'll work on that we'll just
leave this for now yeah I'll find more
iron we'll fix it we'll fix it okay
carpet is easy to get
yeah yeah there's there's a block right
above so we can't put the carpet there
yet oh okay let's just go get the uh you
just need the Hoppers and then put
the put the no no no not yet okay just
need the Hoppers and then we can fix it
up okay
okay iron iron
iron we thought it was finished but we
finished it a second to
yeah and new and improved oh yeah yeah
we learn you know
it it's okay slow and steady slow and
steady you do win the
race
oh I'll mine a little bit to see well
the box is full right now um oh cuz I
was trying to find some iron this the
one thing there's so much stuff
obviously we're going to get so many
blocks we don't need need
mhm need like two fences or three fences
that we can get safer we don't have any
wood wait we don't have wood oh actually
I just farmed a bunch of wood actually
um so I'm going to put it there's a a
storage chest um let's see which I have
some wood too here I'm putting all the
wood I put it in the what chest here um
Iron trap doors are more durable and can
handle a creeper EXP
guys there's a problem with that we need
iron yeah have what do they mean like
cuz we already finished the top part we
don't that's not a problem them
exploding up there there's no trap doors
on iron we can't really IR yeah that's
the main
thing yeah that's why we got to make we
need aill we need a villager villager
please we could get a villager that
would be a game
changer m only two villagers that's the
yeah need to get lucky
twice
yeah it's okay we'll we'll we'll be fine
in the end
yeah we'll be
fine yeah we'll just need to get some
iron freaking
from I got
two does this also drop water
awesome trying to use up some exp before
I inevitably die it
all what is that for more apples for now
I'll let you guys do the mining I really
should organize those so they can do
more mining Poli
kaop yeah we I am carrying a lot right
now ah one moment
let's
see sort
[Music]
sorty let's
see cute Fe oh Pig well that's kind of
nice cuz we don't have any pigs oh let P
out of there come
on come on yeah good job
good job who's a good piggy you are yeah
you
are I'm not sure if I can drag this into
here you need help or is it too
full yeah if you can get like if you can
grab like a or something and then like
drag
them the word wheat was cut off but I
think as you said wheat so yeah just
just bring the cows to the other side so
come on follow me
yeah they seem they seem too thick to
escape
anyway you sure do get a lot of gold and
not good we got the
pig oh freaking random ass zombie oh but
this one's did you come from the nether
oh I think it
did all right oh oh no I'm going to
introduce a new mechanic we're going to
have a chest so that you guys put things
that we don't need in there like rotten
flesh and such and then I'll take it and
I'll throw it off the side when it's
full yep that's what we're going to
do free
gold more gold for
example I don't know where to put
anything here so if you don't if you
want to throw things away put it into uh
one of the Sorting chest oh wait I can't
throw it off the side never mind you
can't unless it was a Shuler box such a
dummy yeah just put it in the Sorting
chest it's
fine okay it would be such a good idea
though we trash can this is why I wanted
to make a trash can we can't though we
can't because that would be
iron and everything that's fine yeah he
can visit us let's see visitation hours
are currently open you don't want it
just throw it off the
side H priority
is five five iron per h all
right more
sorting put it next to sand and remove
the sand o that's a really good idea
actually for a trash can cuz we have a
gazillion chest like too
many iron please please show yourself
the good thing is that at this point
where it's All Phases combined sometimes
there's iron blocks like full iron
blocks okay just like how there's iron
Emeral blocks sometimes so you know we
can get lucky sometimes there's always
that
possibility look my inventory is very
full even though I'm dumping everything
okay don't put that in
there I wi
i i
i although the more we mine the more
pickaxes we're going to use going to
just mine with stone pickaxes I gu I've
just been doing that unless there's a
like block that's hard to get m
yeah it's definitely the best way I'll
do it too after this one breaks get a
sand I'm making a trash can I'm going to
try it out wait is so wait maybe chat
was saying that instead of carpet we put
trap doors I don't know if that has the
same function on top of the ho
first I guess the trap doors are a
little bit higher s
Stone they're a little bit higher so I
suppose they would we we would be lower
but I don't know if that really you know
helps
yeah unless it's iron of
course but we have so many fancy blocks
but no iron so much terracotta and okay
diamonds are nice what was that what was
that egg yeah what was
that it's like a zombie something
no can not here right here what was that
I want to see let's just off the
side this I'm trying to trying
desperately to make a trash can I need
to just give up all right uh let's
see hold on what was
that I think it was like a zombie
something egg oh I got it zombie zombie
villager spawn
egg is that good I mean we could try
curing it but we wouldn't need like a
potion of weakness or something and then
a golden apple we have plenty of golden
apples but we need a potion of weakness
how do we make that side quest side
quest side get the potion of weakness
the spawner we it spawn several of them
no just one okay but then let's say
let's spawn it in a safe environment in
the
airb okay I'm going to put this in the
precious goodies chest
sick twist they have a chance I didn't
know they includ thesea or what the hell
items it was in the chest so like I
guess the chest can spawn extra special
things let go let's go oh nice one that
is a game changer throw the trash in the
nether that's also possible
iron
iron diamond and gold I mean if we found
the uh try if we found a like a normal
piglin we could have totally tried to
have a
traded gold for iron bars and stuff
[Music]
but
yeah yeah those piglins all look kind of
yucky like all of them were messed up
yeah they were kind of dead they
groy oh this a random
chest okay
yes are you okay I'm stretching oh
stretch sounds nice right about
now
sugarcan all the game changers all the
game changers changing forever
now let's go this game will never be the
same now that
you we can ench enchanting
table eventually but you know there's
some work that leads up to
that ah sponge stole the water yeah I do
happening often it do be happening often
cannot Engish finally sugar cane let's
go we can make pumpkin pie too
O Let's go
Team a win for us finally at
last it it's the it's the it's the bad
one it's the bad one
oh Yik okay um okay he's dead good job
but the the vexes are still around all
right we got to
kill chickens protect me hey dummies
come over
[Music]
here
nice thank you
kfp got it for being my refuge oh
there's one more
what I got your stuff sorry I pick up
come
here
[Music]
no yo why is he allowed to just face
through the freaking
floor I have
trap okay I got some of your things yeah
what was it you sword pretty much yeah
your sword I think this is your sword
and then did you have an iron pickaxe
cuz I also had one but okay here you go
you can just have it and then thank you
go anything else Granite oh here's your
granite and your
torches thank you that one is so
aggressive
okay pickaxe oh I gave you an I gave you
an iron one maybe no I didn't it didn't
go oh it didn't hey where' it go then no
that was an important Pi I just I'll
just make a stone one oh wait I have
your iron one picked it up you I have a
block of iron I have a block of iron oh
nice nice we got nine I love that we're
celebrating over
blocks that's what I really like about
this game mode because we we start from
the simplest things again and you know
we can't just use all these farms in the
Japan so okay I'll cook these two IR
or okay how many is that 14 oh we just
need one more for a hopper
yeah I wonder if we can decompose the
iron horse armor that would be nice that
would be cool if we could break it down
we can do that with our own armor but
not with the armor of the yeah
sad oh yeah I would have only been a
nugget H I love nuggets but not those I
mean still it's more than something
yeah see also cuz we do have some other
iron
[Music]
nuggets probably need to check these
more often these
trees
Tre how long does it take for the apples
to despawn if they fall Wonder long long
long oh no oh despawn oh despawn maybe
not so long oh I see got to keep an eye
on it mhm
okay start with
those maybe this
one 5 minutes okay I'll be careful I'll
keep checking on them wait this used to
be a stone box what the
hell right now I'll put this wood right
actually I'll make a chest that's just
wood from the forest
okay now the sponges shouldn't take the
water I think
oh another Improvement
made yeah
she did you oh how did you do it some
bread I just put more trap doors and put
the water block a little bit higher
oh oh
iron we can fix the fix the Hoppers now
yay okay I need to break some of these
leaves down I'll make them oh we already
have enough we already had 16 oh oh wait
really yeah I thought we had 14
math no math is hard all good math is
hard for a man oh oh always has just for
us
no math math class with myth we released
an English language book before now
we're going to release a math class book
oh
yes oh is there any more car oh wait we
can already make a potion of weakness
cuz we already have fermented spider egg
or spider eyes yeah what you mean for
the oh but we need a yeah yeah but we
need a potion making thing I don't know
what
oh like a potion table potion mixing
table or
something H H maybe I should make a
fence around the uh around the forest I
wasn't really holding anything important
I don't think okay a brewing St kaop
fopi don't fall we can totally make one
yeah okay what did you lose KY uh I
think the only important thing I was
holding was maybe two apples which is
it's too bad it is what it is damn all
right we'll make a fense I can just get
cobblestone a couple of chests too oh
well all right let's start making some
new
things not like we don't have materials
to make new things so yeah
okay cobbly
Stone so I got a cool potion that gives
plus one luck maybe that's all right it
was just two apples do we have any uh
carpet or wool can make carpet oh
there's carpet in the Sher
chest oh
yeah there okay
thank okay okay make the brewing
[Music]
stand
nice I'll put it right
[Music]
here okay we have
glassass one of the chest Kelly were you
still wearing the diamond armor no I put
it away
okay cuz put mine away too yeah know I
put mine away don't worry okay but it
was a good reminder for me to put mine
away too yeah so I didn't die for
anything can happen at any time oh yeah
I don't know where mine
went oh it's somewhere for sure for sure
believe yeah I just put it in the final
chest that we're taking to the the last
battle I've been hoarding stuff oh okay
yeah good idea I'll put it there too all
right and the golden helmet so I can
make a fence oh we have the Apple I
already get new
apples where's the Sheep I I need like
more simply adding
fermented spider ey to water bottle it's
the only potion I can with the nether
oh I'm so excited Ena I'm so excited oh
hey we got a potion maker let's go oh
wait we need to get was powder no
problem we should have some we've got
that
[Music]
covered yeah I was pretty calm after I a
splash potion was cool yeah I learned
recently how to make potions
too fin we have gunpowder from the from
the creeper I
don't where did I put there's how many
do you need there's four here just one
oh okay here
those thank you
H are there children please be quietas
andas at
year I'm so excited I'm so excited this
is not how I expected to get a villager
but it's it's way to get a villager
where we putting the Villager in
the you bu yeah there be end making sure
they can't get out right yeah yeah we'll
close it off somehow okay we got three
of them so if we happen to have another
one more down the line we can use it do
you want to make it now or
do I I want us to make it now as soon as
possible we be good um we need a golden
apple we have plenty go check the final
chest behind the uh the chicken cop cuz
we can already give him a job right and
then we can already have him start
working on like armor we actually give
him a job that gives us iron of emerald
oh yeah yeah yeah
it's it's it will be the the the problem
solver for
everything when if we can get enough
iron we can change this job much more
things they can open doors can they open
fence gates that's a good I think so cuz
farmers do that right no do they open
them what's a good way to do this chat
there AR gives they buy IR they don't
give iron am I thinking of like the
merchant ah oh okay we'll put it in the
thinking about the merchant yeah but I
in a
boat is he going to restart going to
make a million sticks we can we can put
him in a boat for temporarily might
have
okay okay I think we have more sticks
let's
see are are you here
Kara wait wait
wait yes I'm so
here let's go okay should be enough
let's find
out oh cool he already has a job does he
wait wait hard stand in front Okay and
then you want to get out of there it's a
splash
potion okay and then C me from my then I
throw this right guys do it do it see
right
chat he's a map maker Splish Splash and
lame
job okay I also got weakness and then
Golden
Apple
oh Magic he's
evolving he's shaking oh he needs a hug
gosh you cold there buddy once you are
not a zombie anymore we'll give you a
hug yeah first stop stop being so
green don't press B
he's dead he's dead oh it may take 3 to
five minutes okay oh oh really okay
we'll just stand here wait just make him
uncomfortable you know I mean we should
put we should also get can you get a
name tag just so good idea what you
going namea them yeah what are we going
to name
him uh Shrek that's a bad idea he won't
be green never mind sorry we don't want
we can have a legally
distinct that is not shre
he's like a Hot
Pocket yeah are you okay shre with
g f what wor about it guys no no I'm
good okay I made I made I made a
name actually I need help again the same
thing before I'm
anticipating can he be something small
and then uh you got you guys watch over
the Villager I'll watch him I'm a good
baby
consider I I'll make another ax cuz
mine's kind of like
half durability oh yeah good idea some
Stone oh he's giving you a old whack
he's got a name now if you look at him
nice shre I have Li G oo can I make it
with d and then we we should make
another one and also call that one shre
so we can have shreds
can't sh too yeah shre shre love
shreds come on get over it already walk
it off walk it off shre come on I like
his monacle he's F I'm in a [\h__\h] boat
yeah get him shant good
idea hey that was Chad not
me they have shs together y you ready
I'm ready I just need to seal it off
again so one
more
Shing TI
I will kill what's there and
then come on buddy you want to see both
what I do what I do when I want to see
both you're too far oh there's
more shoot creeper watch out also
there's a piglin walking around are we
cool with that got to seal off something
a piglin no where he was that one it
won't attack us
oh even if it loads chunks does it not
load people I wonder uh there's a hole
there on the side
shoot it's okay keep at it we'll keep at
it come on do something they're not
taking as much damage uh fall something
falling on the
sides he looks like he's really
struggling I'm going to go get some soup
he better not super constip
I bet he's going to transform while
you're Tower Defense I know if we need
to back up it's
fine might need to eat come back
yeah go get your mushroom mus do 50% off
go get it now okay fall back fall back
all right Retreat retreat was able to
fix some of it but I couldn't see it all
the way
okay you go
you uh I guess I'll borrow a bow and
some arrows I can shoot down first from
the
side power three she's a regular P he's
nervous that's okay he's got performance
anxiety K some of them not while people
are watching it's a freaking Battlefield
damn crazy it's okay just give him a
minute girls if you need help help let
me know yeah I think we're right yeah
okay you think it really
worked for sure yeah it's the because he
has the swirly things around
him a zombie talk to
co
W it's okay it's okay damn it why not
the other way around let me out no leave
bed I want to talk to shre
[Music]
paper but he's got to change his job
then I I ran out of stuff to seal it
with I need to make it change his job
what job shall we give him ready okay I
think the armor would be nice we can
still switch his jobs
afterwards he's a novice though he's got
to get
better well now yeah his his uh current
job is kind of useless you good I'm room
all right no I'm going to die empty M oh
you can't change theob I can't change
the job
okay I can't the zombies there's like
one hole on the left I got to seal up if
you trade with any he locks into a job
they
say when we come back help um like in
the back go of paper oh wait if we trade
with him you can't change after trading
after trading yeah okay but so you're
saying now I can still change it once
and then once we start trading we can't
anymore so now we haven't traded with
him what's the tool again for armor um
makers what's the work table
thingy what was it a blast oven o that
probably needs iron right all right uh
we'll need to go around the back cuz I
got to seal up the left side all right
if you if you go in the front like on
the left you where the see where the
purple blocks are on the left side yeah
and then I'll go around the other side
steal it what if I make that it'll te
me got to get the first
first I need some Cobblestone I know
it's yeah I want to
[Music]
check a
lot that seems not
good was
okay I was blowing up some my stuff
should be
around I had a totem life but I blown
off I was blown off the edge yeah
damn I thought we didn't lose that much
stuff it's just like junk that we lost
at least for
[Music]
me CH wait was Ena wearing the diamond
armor it's still there right I was
indeed oh I don't know if it's still
there cuz it technically was blown up by
a creeper there
hopeful yeah that's while there's just
like one hole that they keep coming out
of that I need to like seal it but I
can't get to
it m m yeah it should be at the base of
the farm if it didn't fall how do you
make it into a blast
furnace get over here St
the void claims another not feeling so
good what's up is you have a t oh I
heard that oh that come from where is
that sound good there's yeah there's
like stuff spawning back here somewhere
oh I think I know where it
is looking for Cobblestone here just
back
here I'll be all be okay
okay think I spawn here in a while
[Music]
so bring cat against creeper can we
bring cat yeah bring kitties I guess we
could it' be nice a cat sitting by those
chest cuz that's where they everything
spawns right there I think I fixed it
cuz there was uh one block behind the
wall that didn't have the
Torches I got
it ding ding yeah bone meal guys sorry I
lost the bone meal when I fell off
invisibility potion what's invisibility
potion o would that
work one potion of knif vision and the
ferment spider we don't we don't have
any more fermented spider how do you
make fermented spider can you make
fermented spider
eyes like if you have a regular one
maybe spider eye and then do something
to
it yeah Brown mushroom sugar and spider
eye oh we have brown mushroom I remember
I bought some from the the nether oh
yeah oh yeah we have seven or eight okay
we can make this and we got sugar from
the sugar cane
nice cool okay and then spider
eye I'll just go over there with some
blocks and like a you know like kind of
like a suicide mission give me the
invisibility potion and some blocks and
I'll just seal it up okay and then
potion of
invisibility need a potion of night
vision which
is
H of night
vision nether W and one golden carrot we
do have golden carrots right yeah we do
if you check the chest behind the
chicken coop Okay so
one nether w we have lots of nether
wand oh we do need more water
bottles oh W upy you be
quiet need
one make a new we'll make three three
just in case
one two
three and
then three Nether
wart makes awkward potion and then we
add the golden
carrot was it was it uh glow stone
powder that made it last long I think so
right no we have plenty of that if so
yeah
you know for the extra
cautious you know of course stay
invisible long oh yeah oh glow stone
amplifies oh it's red stone that makes
it longer okay we have plenty of those
oh plenty of both of those
yeah somewhere oh yeah they're in the
fuel chest lot of chests around
okay okay we
got got the awkward potion so we add the
golden car right awkward potion
what the H that's a weird name for
something yeah it's it's pretty
awkward what the heck why would you ever
want to use
that
ocean hey are you you okay can still see
you when you're invisible shoot all
right well I'm going I'm going with just
blocks
and that's all oh what if what okay I
got an idea since the block
blocks are the the place you have to
block is kind of up above right yeah so
why don't you build a bridge like up
above so the mobs can't reach you and
then you go get to the oh get to the get
to the hole Yeah I could
work that's by Archer well we'll have
we'll have
uh
uh maybe if I can make a shield I can
tank some of the mods I was able to
close it except now just the side parts
are are open there's some side part open
was able to close the bottom cuz that
exploded
again um yeah I Can Build a Bridge I'll
just just build a
bridge Apple hunting
time
oh oh I real that CL soon
Apple
hunt wait that's not that's
a come on come
on don't fall off there we go and
now they should start despawning on
their own once I kind
of okay I have to go soon so I'll
quickly try and help out before I go
okay what do you mean try to help out
you've been helping out all along yeah
no like like last like on the oh yeah
stuff I'll just seal it for now and then
we'll fix it another time yeah I dropped
um ladders if you want
to I just need like a form of
Defense yeah these they seem there's of
right now so yeah I get you
all good it's cuz they they don't spawn
until you're close enough for the to
happen I have no idea where working to
get another more Stone now we've got
three Apple app you are wait what do you
call an a lady that has an apple farm
and collect apples isn't there a nice
word for that an apple farm
stress no not nicer word an apple
princess
yeah no no that's not what I'm thinking
of I'll figure it out someday okay
anyone in chat now Orchard well okay
Orchard is probably the the pro most
proper word for it an
orchard well I guess Arrow would have
been better huh or I'm just going to um
get a pickaxe I can't get in there to
seal it
okay see this this Forest is really good
at least the zombies are burning once we
get it's good right
guys oh that's a lot of Creeper this is
good oh you swimming I was swimming for
a minute there it's cuz my Forest is so
Bountiful Apple ja you'll also get a ton
of wood at the same time too
axe okay at least I brought my
cat cats the creepers
away um a cat's not doing anything with
the
creeper yo do your job it's like when
you want your your cat to chase a
cockroach or something in your house and
they won't do it yeah just because you
command them to if you're not there
though they'll do
it oh shoot I forgot to make slabs
okay you got they got to sit down here
cat this what the pandas are
doing all right it's sealed off for now
so the ones that are here are the last
ones that are going to spawn the one the
I feel like there're still spilling out
from somewhere it's just my
imagin like on the right like where
they're standing no they're just
standing there they they can't get they
can't uh fall that far down okay that an
apple
no we're going to have so many gold you
guys are still at it oh my God this is
CRA we're almost done though we're dead
for now this is
crazy
oh okay I'm going to go bring a bow
Apple come on it just blew up
[Music]
the no I didn't have any items that was
just uh that was my suicide Miss
okay
y break the block above there's only the
really good buet I use it use it it's
okay okay oh my inventory is not full oh
I died with all the weapons huh maybe I
need the infinity bow yeah infinitely
bow would be
good I have one Arrow so I can you can
use the bous bow if you'd like we
good yeah no it's destroying everything
maybe we should build it from scratch
again no we don't have to build we did
have to build the base again but uh else
F
yeah oh no no no no no no no are we sure
it's
fine I don't know how there's still
stuff's I'm probably going to die right
now
but why have you no mercy why why why
that's
cruel there is a ho there is there I
miss should
did you there is all yeah okay I'll I'll
bring the you doing that
wo together we'll like you know snipe
everything wait is the Sher box gone did
it blow up I think so oh no this hurts
so bad I want the
Apple it's ghost
Apple ah it's been a day full of
different rough Adventures
but it's been fun yeah all the the H we
got to fill everything in right yeah
just I'll just
no it should be yeah it's it's done for
now build it using obsidian we do have a
lot of obsidian not that many well at
least the base
maybe like the the first couple of
blocks in the bottom could be obsidian
even if it's obsidian The Hoppers will
still oh yeah the base could be
obsidian don't isn't there still a hole
over
there water you think that
work it's because I sealed it you see
where the bridge is I sealed it right
there oh that's why they keping at no no
stuff can't fall past that the hole
where the
bridges uh the ones that were here in
this chamber I think they're just um
they were just a lot that had
accumulated uh okay yeah all right
the right let's go
cat I mean do we even need an XP farm or
something I mean it's already finished
basically and there are definitely uses
good uses for it I would say yeah could
drop usary iron and bow
and and for enchanting things anybody
have a pickaxe I can borrow so I can fix
the base at least a few Stone pickaxes
no oh if if there's obsidian though
we'll need a diamond one right no I'm
not a mining well unless I mess up if I
mess up I need in trouble here you go I
got to head out for now okay see you
later bye thanks for playing bye bye see
you later thank you survive we'll try we
will try also our our house is open I
don't know oh it's cuz of the
creeper oh oh yeah hey do you have any
torches Cara um I got we have a gazan
Tores no you go I'll TR oh wait I got
the Sher box guys I got the shulker box
oh ho oh nice there you
go okay now I can
leave uh my job here is done you need
torches on me okay
yes I got a stack of
see byebye now care
okay here you go on Torch
delivery thank you you're welcome
all right maybe a few
more I wonder how many golden apples we
should aim to
have many
many many many many maybe honestly
probably five per person would be good
too okay yeah that's good so 25ish
like we're getting pretty close to
that this is so
sad I should at least make a wooden one
make a wooden
one I want to make obsidian
fence ooh a fence out of obsidian
doesn't exist sadly oh that would be
really strong though I bet yeah
oh 32 bone blocks so we'll have bone
meal for
days okay all right this should be good
for now
okay I will be your replacement for Ena
so let me know if you need something are
we going to fix it now oh I mean if you
I mean if you don't want to if you don't
want to then we don't have to um but we
still we need Hoppers again because
again I they gone four Hoppers we need
I'm pretty sure they're gone I don't
think Ena had them well if you want to
do something else on it then yeah go for
it we can pick it up later yeah I we can
fix it whenever we or somebody's going
to tomorrow or whenever the day after
sure I think I understand how it works
so if I'm playing alone I can fix it I
can try to fix
it trust me I'll join okay I'll let you
know I'll let you know got the
vision uh okay well it was it was uh
working for you
know um a little amount of time and uh
that was a good time
and this is fine too there was a time
when it worked and there was a time when
it doesn't work and all times are good
times yeah it's fine there's plenty of
other stuff we need to do anyway I feel
like apples I think I'll make a second
floor underneath so that when this
explodes Again by any chance we will not
fall into the void yeah that' be good
like a little bit wider of a platform
underneath to I'll make that I'll do
that nice idea just leave it for now
yeah let's leave it for
now
okay um I'll probably go too okay I'm
okay thanks for a nice evening thank you
for being here today thank
you hard
worke see you now it's me and kaop then
two morio we're going
we're going to grind a little bit more
Cali or what well yeah I wasn't really
planning on on stopping until you know
about when it's time for the 2.0 reveal
so ah okay okay okay you want to like
raid yourself into that or what I was
thinking maybe I'll do that but now
we'll see what time is it um hour 9:30
so it's like an hour and a half or so oh
okay still a good amount of time to keep
playing um I'm going to I'm going to go
check on my cats real quick
so don't say anything suspicious while
I'm gone you mean your real cats but of
course oh yeah not the ones in the game
I really have no connection with them
right now but I'm sure we'll get closer
get closer surely okay I will be right
back but yeah don't don't say anything
weird yeah just be I won't say anything
okay I'll just be asep just say
Chad what no
no help me please oh please I need I
need aist I need oh that sounds bad okay
hold on hold
on going wait it's going to fly away
it's probably going to fly away let's
hide in the house okay
yeah all right oh no is it did it shoot
the farm I wonder oh we can check on the
damage later yeah should be fine should
be fine my bow it's okay it's okay I
only have like two arrows I would
probably I don't know if I would have
hit it surely it's fine see hear him a
Snicker and go away you can yeah you can
go AFK cuz you're safe in here oh yeah
all right I'll be back
maybe okay you can skip the Hoppers and
use chests as bottom is what I've heard
their
feet to grind the MS yeah I guess so the
chests will pick it up right anyway
Hoppers is just more
convenient Ponda is
free at one Panda what about the
others they look fine
I think it's gone okay I was going to
say sorry I I don't even know how much
longer I'll really play because maybe
you've noticed I
have I'm not feeling so good right
[Music]
now actually it's like it goes up and
down and up and
down uh oh oh dear oh dear oh dear no
the Potion No the potion maker no damn
it um oh I'll be um giving cie a little
bit more company for a little bit longer
but then I'll probably dip soon as
well I think maybe you think it was a
salmon I don't know could it be so
delayed because it's been like 24 hours
since I ate the salmon but I was
thinking that too like was it the salmon
after all it didn't smell weird and it
didn't taste
weird but maybe it was like really like
on the brink of being good and bad and
then yeah I don't
know oh I got the stand okay maybe
[Music]
salmonella that's my dinner for today
though the second serving is my dinner
for today but I'll just eat the salad
and the potatoes because I have plenty
of it chest don't pick up items
automatically you need to us to get the
IR in chest without you have well I mean
when we're standing there we'll pick it
up anyway right but it will be a lot of
trash I I want to you know get more iron
again and fix that but it's how much
iron did we already waste on that it's
kind of
sad can we not make a two Hopper version
instead of a four Hopper version rep
plant the sugarcan first
y I need some more one more piece of
dirt
right
somewhere there must be
dirt careful there's holes
everywhere but yeah I I want to I want
to play along and I want to play
energetically but today something's
wrong with my tummy and I feel like
wobbly when I when I'm starting to feel
it feels wobbly doesn't feel nice and
then I feel
[Music]
weak but the cats came to support me
they were worried about me it's so cute
having pets has emotional support it's
so nice it's the only oh does it need
space it's the only emotional support I
have at
home thank you
Kos m
wa this is actually I just realized how
awkward this is I feel like I'm talking
to my chat only but in reality there's
another chat who's listening to me
right hi hi that beats uh sorry for
telling you about my Tommy heart
sorry it's like somebody's like it's
like I'm in a phone conversation and
unknowingly someone else is in the phone
conversation that I don't know
about they're listening in and I don't
even realize
it and the tacos are here too well who
knows how many who knows how many are
still here but the tacos the tacos have
a history
of invading kfp but I don't
mind it's it's
fun they are spy within
kfp I don't want to wear this Shield
it's
annoying wow w w
w I wonder if we
can maybe we'll go to the end the day
after tomorrow and tomorrow will be one
more day of grinding the Villager and
iron and like whatever armor and so
on I feel like we could probably uh YOLO
it it might even you know be fine but
why not just play it a little bit
safer right what do you guys think we
could probably yellow it right but I do
want to I don't want
to you
know I'm going to ask the girls if they
all have time the day after tomorrow for
the end
and then we'll
see b
b yoloing could be fun H well I
definitely didn't want to Yello it
tomorrow because if we were to go to the
end today you know I would have wanted
to advertise it that way but I think
it's nice to like separate it in
different episodes The Never at the end
even if the never wasn't really that
necessary I think it's
good to keep those things separated and
then you know announce it like oh my God
we're going to the end we're going to do
it final episode SL Ender Dragon would
be a waste if we wouldn't do it like
that in my opinion
yeah the F first time y'all fought on
the an server was already YOLO didn't we
at least have like a full set of diamond
armor and I think we were decently
prepped because I feel like
Ena like very much
uh you know was very into preparing
us like making potions and stuff I'm
sorry is there any more holes oh hi K hi
sorry my cats were just they were just
really
cute understandable I I know how that
feels ghost cat was sitting on the the
corner of the sink and I was like all
right I have to pet you for five minutes
it can't be
[Music]
helped I wonder if any apples dropped oo
apples apples apples apples app Che
Apple check no nothing all right that's
okay no problem yeah the trees are
gr this broke why did this break what
the hell maybe I should try doing some
quests I feel bad I haven't been doing a
lot of quests and no apples are good to
have yeah I figure once we get 25 that's
like one big thing off the checklist
right are you not tired by the way
Callie not really Dam not really and
then I'm going to be up until like 1:00
a.m. and I have a recording today and
then two other streams so it's a busy
day I got to be g
girl it's a busy time but you can keep
that reveal stream short no oh yeah
it'll be quick it'll be like hour two
hours or
so yeah I haven't just chatted with the
fans in a
while I I told everybody about my tummy
hord oh no we're suspecting the salmon
that I ate because it was expired and I
cooked it anyway no you are but it was
only one day expired and it tasted and
smelled fine so I don't know uh who
could say I mean I don't know I I I'm
always worried about that because I've
been watching especially when I was
recovering from my knee surgery I was
watching a lot of those uh videos where
it was like documentaries um or not
really documentaries but you know
internet videos where it's like this guy
only ate vitamin gummies for 10 days
here's what happened to his organs you
know stuff like that they do a lot about
people that eat like this person ate
pasta that was sitting out for one day
this is how she died yeah yeah yeah I I
watched a few of those too actually yeah
yeah kind of got into that hole for a
while don't risk it guys don't R it this
guy ate gas station Sushi this is what
happened to his organs oh don't trust
gas station Sushi yo what you doing what
are you doing it's already bad enough in
regular regular old restaurants that you
in Japanese you called that
jig like your own fault oh
my yeah that sounds about
right it's convenient and cheap I just
realized for the blast furnace I need
iron as well so I'm just going to mine
I'm just going to mine you may say the
gas station Sushi is is cheaper than uh
than than regular like nice restaurant
sushi in America but if you come to
Japan and you eat sushi the sushi here
the good sushi will be cheaper than your
gas station Sushi just saying MH so come
over here yeah if only I like sushi then
I would totally you're not much of a
fish person are you if it's cooked it's
fine right yeah I mean I don't like
seaweed that much either but you know
there's like a kind of like a Korean
version of uh Sushi do you know it yeah
yeah I've had before called kimbab yeah
kimab kimbab right I love that I kind of
want it for lunch that one is wrapped in
seaweed too and I can kind of
like ignore the seaweed because I really
like Kimba because it's with like
veggies and stuff oh yeah yeah yeah was
yum yeah kind of tastes like the ocean
with the the seaweed I get
you kind of don't notice anymore but
yeah I know what you
mean oh
yeah these ones leaning off the side
have apples I'm going to be so
upset okay got a make got to extend the
platform oh yeah I think I think the
forest is all right on my end the forest
is in okay shape and
amount so why did this why did this
happen why did this
happen can't do it here or what I just
put it in the food
[Music]
chest
okay w
I have a workmate who fell really sick
after eating sushi that was being served
at work just because it wasn't properly
refrigerated dangerous y yeah yeah
proper Refrigeration is really
important I feel like I may have broken
the we uh the cooling chain in German we
say cool cool cool C cooling chain cool
the cooling chain yeah you know what I
mean like the with the cooling chain I
mean like you know when you transport
food for example from the factory to a
restaurant and then it has to be cool in
the in the in the car and so on as well
so that the cooling Chade is not being
interrupted yeah so I feel like when I
got the salmon from the um from the
hellofresh box I left out the hellofresh
box for a little bit too long but
generally there's ice in there to keep
the fish cool but I when I when I took
it out I felt like it was actually not
that cool like the ice was not really
nicely placed so maybe the fish wasn't
being being cooled properly so that
could also added to
it I could still know that there a
lawsuit there's a lawsuit right there I
can't really prove it and it's okay I'll
survive I know you like the hellofresh
stuff
so well we should sponsor
you wait do we still have a diamond
pickaxe somewhere um someone had it at
some point right I'm not sure
though I have it still I just can't see
cuz the inventory is so full oh that'll
do it
gws thanks get well soon feel
better let's
see cool make it to in finish it sounds
so
similar cooling shade come on come on
come
[Music]
on um
make more tools stone tools are the best
though cuz we get lots of
stone where's my Cobble e
still okay sorry I haven't been
organizing I've been on an Apple
Mission it's okay all right I'll see if
I can do a little organization real
quick
y
okay always in the market for more
cobbly
Stone okay by the way chat I did not
watch the new Season's first episode yet
of gameer uh not game of thrs House of
the Dragon of dragon watch it yet maybe
I'll watch it today before I go to
sleep oh yeah does kfp who they also
watching along with you I mean I think a
lot of my viewers watch it
yeah but maybe not House of the
darg
dragon dragon these not oh my God
it just I really don't like these kind
of jokes but it's like this culture is
making me say them I get you it same
happened to me it's
okay it's going to happen I I tried so
hard to resist for the longest time you
know we all try to resist and then CU
some of us are weak and we fail that's
okay yeah we're too weak for this
environment trying to get strong yeah
got to resist those silly
jokes oh well ask oh yeah I was I was
wondering if um since Kar is such a
Minecraft Master if she knew anything
about coblin
D she's already seen that clip hasn't
she dang it I mean I don't know if I saw
a clip but I know what you you know I
know what you're I'm sure you didn't see
a clip all right yeah whatever cobbling
these
[Music]
n damn she said it it was funny the
first time only and only about 50% funny
what's this chest it seems kind of like
a mess over here oh uh someone just
started throwing random things in there
so I've been slowly trying to organize I
don't know I don't know what they were
going for in there not even
me not even me it's another sorting
chest
now yeah so I have a couple
projects here couple different projects
couple of side quests yeah little side
quest my own personal one
the apple one I'm excited about because
I'm like ah yes we really need this you
know oh yeah we do we do it's going to
be really helpful especially cuz I don't
know if we can really get like proper
armor and all of that and weapons for
all of us but yeah the apples will help
keep us strong and healthy I hope
so that's why I'm gathering them so see
right I'll do a little more
organizing were you able to change the
villagers uh thing uh not yet because I
need iron for the work station for him
okay gotcha well if you want to keep
mining for a bit I've just emptied the
chest thank you very very
yeah another
[Music]
nugget let's
see like a saw spider web
somewhere somewhere for sure oh well now
they going
here can we plant more sugar can for the
books H Kelly while you're waiting for
the apples to drop you could also make
another Farm next to the trees for
sugarcane oh that's a good idea how do
you plant it you just stick it in the
ground yeah dirt blocks and then it
doesn't even have to be like you know
properly made with a hoe as far as I can
tell but it has to have water around it
okay water around it next to water okay
it's probably like with the wheat right
that it needs um one block of water and
then you can place four fields of sugar
cane around it right in all directions
probably same with
wheat okay you just need in any case
yeah in any case if you get started
there's like two pieces of sugarcane for
uh that that you can use in the food box
okay sure but no pressure If you don't
i' like to once I can figure out how to
do it um just cuz you know my brain's
really small that's okay uh yeah maybe
we could needs a block that touches oh
it always needs to touch water okay so H
it needs like you could do like rows of
water
uh rows of water you could do rows of
water and then yeah the sugarcane always
has to touch the block of water like be
right next to it oh I see gotcha damn
why couldn't you have been a villager
why do you got to be a merchant sadness
so close so close get out of there get
out of there always touching get out of
there
water
move you left I'm right here not
you but as long as you're here I'm also
happy so I was going to put water in
this trench maybe not alone
yeah not alone I think he's I think he's
gone oh and okay um I'm going to bring
up the topics that I couldn't bring up
when it was so crowded but Austria lost
against France of course 0 to one but
that's okay okay apparently I wasn't
actually watching chat you might think I
was watching but I I was taking a
nap and apparently Austria wasn't doing
so badly yeah they played really well oh
let's go that's good to hear I'm proud
yeah cuz they always had this reputation
that the that ustra sucks at football
the diagonal yeah oh that's cool
congrats they were playing aggressively
and they had the ball like 50% of the
time
apparently and they were not inated you
know with like 5 to zero or so so that's
good so maybe we have a chance in the
other matches
congrats ke sorry it's like so unrelated
to you probably did you fall who did
that what did you fall who pushed me
girl no it was the pounda probably wait
is there a hole where's a hole no
someone pushed
me I fell right wa where did you oh a
spider no why did that
spawn what where's the
spider did it fall down too yeah and now
it's under where did that come from God
damn
annoying away with you maybe this is not
lit up enough let me light up some
more where where exactly where you I was
right where I'm making the what youall
it I was going to get rid of these
diagonal blocks to save blocks
but let's see that's
fine not lit up around the aquarium
over I see well let's see how about a
little find more dirt blocks does it
need to be dirt or can it be any rocks
for any kind of whatever to put the
water in uh sorry sorry bra can you ask
the question again my brain was like oh
that's okay so I'm trying to make the
trench like a ditch for the water does
it need to be dirt around it or can it
be whatever sand works it should be dirt
around it so that you can plant the
sugarcane yeah okay well sand will fall
the the block where the water is
basically on top of can be anything oh
okay well that that defin sand also
works for uh sugarcane if you want to
use sand instead okay but the sand will
fall down if you have nothing underneath
yeah that's the thing all right well I
found dirt so we're good okay all right
now we won't fall again
my stuff is at least I wasn't holding
anything important I don't think I'm
going to go with you for a moment to see
if you need
help oh this is good already yeah yeah
you're getting it this kind of thing
you're getting the
point oh and we'll put water in there
exactly you know how to do that like cuz
you'll need to like probably fill up
like even when it looks that like
everything's filled M it's a couple
not yeah I'll have you up with that I
was building an onent at a certain point
so I kind of get it yeah oh
okay experience is
helping this will be the main field and
then we'll put like some regular Stone
around it or something you want
to put one more block here oh yeah
definitely let's
see there you go just round it out yeah
y nice
y sick okay yeah I like your point you
like my pranks thank you I love
them thank you so much for enjoying
them it's just a it's a force of habit I
guess at this point you
know can't be
helped I need a prank emote you guys are
right oh yeah see I don't think I was
pling like if it wasn't for you really
yay you taught me how to
clink yeah see I think the first trench
is filled up all right cool and then
around that I'm just going to I'm going
to need to put a fence cuz I don't want
to fall I know I'll fall so mhm we're
going to but maybe we we could make
another line oh yeah sure we could do
that one more one more one more one more
I like this so like another line on this
side you mean another trench yeah like
uh this this block here you could
uh no actually this one yeah the
furthest one out cuz we can have we can
have um we can have sugar cane here and
then we can have sugar cane here cuz
this one will touch the water over here
oh yeah I see gotcha so we should turn
which one um let's see we should turn
which one into so the the line all the
way here that I'm standing on we should
turn it into a trench oh wait wait it's
the furthest one on the edge turn it
into a trench that should become a
trench and then you make another line of
dirt blocks there okay yeah I'll just
need more dirt we just got to get more
dirt blocks and once we have more of
those then we can do
anything wait does it need not be oh is
it because
there's
yet ah so you really literally can't
plant it even okay I got 24 dirt
water dirt dirt water wait before you
place that dirt
mhm um I have an idea okay we got to
make it one more block wider but it's
ites it won't be dirt I just want to
place torches in between oh sure um how
many it can be Cobblestone under the
okay cool then we'll put Cobblestone
under where the the water trenches
mhm cobbly Stone coblin
D okay so I was
thinking oh I see why make it fancy
that's where you want to set up the
Torches that's pretty cute yeah and then
the next line next to that will be dirt
again and then water and then dirt sure
okay sounds good beautiful okay we'll do
that right over here right next dirt
okay wait did
wait what what yeah ah wait no wait I
did it wrong okay it wrong oh yeah it
just needs to be moved one over I guess
huh yeah uh I mean this could work too
right if this if this line becomes water
yeah if that was
water get rid of the the Terracotta
blocks again yeah hold on I'm going to
get rid of the dirt over here
so you know I'm here so don't maybe
don't hit him
yet is that a
merchant hey it's yeah it's a merchant
but like come here I wish he was a
villager not a merchant oh what the heck
would have been more useful ah dang it
he should invite his friends over that
are regular
dudes
yeah Dam it it's
okay okay so now that we did that uh
yeah this will be water then then dirt
again no no no no I'm going to do it
proper okay what I'm what I'm getting
rid of now is going to be the Terracotta
path okay just hold on to that dirt cuz
we'll need it yeah oh not
again
who no no did you what oh my was that a
was that just no it was just me walking
backwards all right we really need to
build some freaking fences how many
times have I Fallen I should I should
extend the floor down there before
anything
yeah okay you would think that I would
be holding shift I got so good at it
when I'm focused on something I just
forget all right well I wasn't I had
made new tools so that's good
but uh now our dirt's gone so I got to
find more
dirt I feel like in some chest there
should still be like randomly a chunk of
dirt son of a
gun you can change your settings to
toggle Crouch so you don't have to hold
it that's right it's on toggle it's on
toggle I'm just a dummy got to toggle
yeah now I'm going a dirt Quest right
seven dirt seven dirt is
good I've got a few cool cool and
then for the trenches we'll just use
Cobblestone or regular Stone too that
should be fine I'll go underground and
make you a a floor down there
thanks yeah pay attention to your
surroundings Mory pay attention it's
fine okay it's content Kelly oh God it's
not the kind of content I want to
make okay so here's what we'll do um
actually want to go down here what are
you looking at cat what are you looking
at oh hi guess I could have gone down
that
way oh oh kind of hard to reach
no oh you you're kind of making a floor
too then yeah just cuz I Was preparing
for the trench over
here
okay there we go
that
work Takami building
time it's going to be great and then we
can make paper which means we can make
books yeah books and and we can make
more Foods we have more options with
food kind of hard to reach
[Music]
I don't want to get rid of this
no okay oh
[Music]
maybe what did did
these okay and I think you have more
dirt so I'll leave that to you mhm yeah
leave the rest to me you can continue
with like apples or so apples or just
sorting looks like it's coming
together this Panda doing here you
trying to eat my trees little
dude how dare
you get out of my
Fields bless younee thank
you thank you very much at least I'm not
holding any apples
yeah ooh
I wish you sold cool
stuff those mer Merchants they kind of
never do it's so lame yeah I was going
to say how do we level him up but if he
never sells cool stuff there's no point
they don't level up no not as far as I
know your merch sucks my
dude the only cool thing about them is
that they normally come with
alas ah yeah but that guy is alpaca list
so yeah kind of know where worth
huh no alpacas no alpacas really no
[\h__\h] you know that image of course I
do what do you take me for silly I've
been on the internet for a little
bit it's just you know I'm behind the
times at the end of the day my internet
Days Are Over My like grand time of
being on the internet all the time is
kind of P at a certain point
it's hard to believe but it's true I
feel like now is our prime time it
should be right but it's our job after
all yeah well that's the thing is that
I'm mostly on the internet for my job
now
but I don't know if I if I didn't have
to be I don't know if I would be to be
honest like not very much not as much as
I used to be I was a quite a meme Lord
back in the day it was pretty intense
but Lord those memes are stale now no
one cares about
them yeah I don't know any of the new
stuff what blocks could I
use
[Music]
diorite and the
side beautiful oh you're cobbling these
cobbles no time for meme homework
exactly also things on the internet just
they make me laugh a lot less than they
used to I
feel yeah maybe it's just the times
changing I don't know or too too grown
up too adult too mature I don't want
that
yada people want to stay children
children want to stay children want to
get adult hood into their hands and we
want to get back to Childhood times that
that is how it feels often yeah I will
say yeah I don't know I also feel like
my brand of humor is Extreme niche in
the first place so it's like hard to
make you laugh these days I don't know I
don't think so ah it's pretty Niche what
would you describe your humor as it's
like it's so specific it's like a very
specific kind
of humor some of it is also the the
darker the darker part as well is just I
can't really I can't share it you know
don't wanted his dad [\h__\h] up well know
I feel like the dead beats don't want me
to say things that are too self
degenerating or too like
morbid that kind of stuff well but
morbid I mean you're literally Grim
Reaper and they skeletons how can you
not be
morbid out of the edge see here we go
it's a perfect
example oh yeah it's fine it's better to
hold back a little bit and don't be too
degenerate
yeah I'm making you a second floor under
the forest too oh thank you no accidents
no
more oh and I was going to make a second
floor under the p a mmm it's
mmm I really was the Joker all along
yeah you wouldn't get
it I you wouldn't get it only watched
that one one Joker mov what was it again
is it the super serious movie with Walky
and
Phoenix Chad we didn't we watch it
together actually Chad help me out I
don't know which one was
it Joker that's the title literally
Joker 2019
okay that's the one I watched 2019 one
yeah what do you think of it I loved it
I think yeah but that's only like a tiny
bit of the Joker Batman Paradise
he Woodson's
back yeah I don't even think the Batman
appears in that movie where's where's my
question mod
here Arthur
Flex oh my God it's the maybe she just
wants to to work on work on it like on
her own the
something can you get out of my business
sir she couldn't get that Minecraft out
of her mind she couldn't stop thinking
about it
yeah it's the Minecraft brain rut a once
you get into it it really is pretty
fun yeah that's why I felt like so sad
when you were like I'm not going to play
Minecraft again because I was like I
feel like you can definitely learn to
like it you just need to get into it the
proper way without suffering too much
you know that's going to give you a bad
experience
mhm yeah but I got into I feel like you
could have a good time with it
yeah I'm having
fun yeah I just had to like relax I feel
like I was I got too stressed out by it
which is the opposite effect that it
should have right no
exactly so
you put too much pressure on
yourself on
maybe I don't know I just know I can do
better where are the apples there's like
this one corner of really tall trees I
know we're going to get an Apple out of
this but I don't want to climb up that
High m
i you know I will probably fall down why
do you drink a potion of in why' you
drink that invisibility potion why you
supp yeah cuz it's getting dark that's
what they do oh it's their defense
mechanism yeah like turtles they hide
away in their
shell I get
it it's the turtle
[Music]
hurdle if you want to hurt a turtle you
got to get over the turtle
hurtle who whoa whoa whoa you're very
silly who silly
person is dark in here y Monsters can't
spawn in trees right and I mean if it's
too dark dark there then yeah
oh I mean not in the around the tree
around the tree
yeah but should be relativ a lit up
there cuz I am deep in this tree in this
tree's guts right now oh oh and am like
in there well then you're probably
fine oh yeah digging around
yeah
yeah there's got to be one want to hurt
a turtle exactly don't hurt the
turtle it should have brought that
turtle is already being bullied by coron
Senai small
house no small
house no no Senpai that's not
funny I mean maybe maybe to us it is but
not to the Turtles that's not fair
Turtle had it come
in turtle is trying
okay oh this looks like a
watermelon this is nice Terra Cota and
I'm using it for stuff like this but if
this was a normal Minecraft playthrough
I'd never have so many of these know
blocks ever like especially the
beautiful terra cotta with the patterns
yeah I feel like that's it's so odd that
they show up like this I don't know it's
m and now we have so many of them we're
using it for stuff like this yeah cuz
those don't just show up in the randomly
in the world you have to make them
right oh no no no they they do show up I
think in like in the
desert a I thought that was just like
regular one color terracotta shows up in
temples but not the fancy patterned ones
I thought you had to make those H it's
like no it's like
a what is it a
desert some kind of dungeon in in the
desert so to say right guys in some
structures yes but not a lot yeah
there's not many of them oh and the
Ocean Floors too yeah oh
interesting but I guess maybe you can
also make it yourself
yeah many ways to get it but I feel like
normally it's it's too much of a
b
not I'm going to just go make some
golden apple to appease
myself okay cuz we have a bunch of gold
we have plenty of gold
thankfully for days the choice of blocks
to use is getting smaller and
smaller I think that's a good sign it
means the stuff that we're we're mining
has a use mhm we have 11 golden apples
so
far getting
closer that's pretty good H getting the
work
done 35 diamonds so far it would be nice
if we had more
but all right I'll put some of these
terracotta blocks with bless thank
you
whoa you can roll your tongue fine huh
yeah but not the way I want to
here's a specific way you want to do
it yeah Japanese
way can't do
it
yeah does take practice I feel it would
help my P impression cuz she does it a
lot what she does m
she goes
[Music]
like like that
yeah the tongue
Ries it sounds like she's rolling her
G's rather than her I watch her play a
NAA one of those like you know you know
all those games like the one where you
need to get up high what was that one
called again climb like only up or oh uh
yeah only up like all those kind of
games the one with the stone recently
yeah I have no sword I saw her play one
yesterday today yesterday mayday mayday
that that looked kind of medieval oh
yeah looked actually yeah watch
out maybe I'll play it you Watson yeah
sorry wat I'll f for
to that's Al for that's the name of the
game for yeah oh yeah I've heard of that
game before Oh
oh yeah she was throwing chickens I was
like hey yo throwing chicken you have a
chicken in your bag your backpack so
cute
oh and then there's Medieval music so
this s kind of fun it does look like a
fun
game I was like well I I have too many
other games I need to play right now but
it did look
fun
potato you know what's the best way to
make potatoes what's the best way in
your opinion cuzan way okay explain it
to me you got to line it up for me lay
it out so you you peel the potatoes then
you cook them once they're done cooking
you um like kind of melt butter in the
same pot like you pour the water out and
then you put the butter in mhm and once
they're all buttery and all that you add
parsley or do it at the same time I
guess chopped up parsley like a lot of
it so it's like buttered parsley
potatoes it's so good it's what you
normally eat with schnitzel wow that
sounds really
yum potatoes are
yum potato do you think potatoes are
vegetables
Kiara of course they are but they're
like starches what about corn is that a
vegetable too of course it is okay but
like if you eat it it's not like good
for you three apples in one tree oh
let's go that's a good apple tree that's
a really good apple tree I want to cut
it down want to grow some
more flavored mashed potato packets yeah
it's not as fun as cooking though
right cor is are green but it's still a
vegetable no what the hell I mean I
guess so I guess the way that I think
about it is vegetable are like healthy
things that are like good for you right
but potatoes are not really good for you
okay I mean it maybe some part of it is
not good but still isn't it like mostly
good um not not really I mean I I feel
it's a starch like it's all carbs like
if you eat a ton of potatoes you get fat
you
know well man like if you eat when I
think of vegetables it's like those
aren't things that really make you fat
but do they have no vitamins
I don't know do potatoes have vitamins
in them
guys and fiber yeah fiber there's
certainly good parts about it right you
just got to not deep fry them oh I see I
like grilled
potatoes yes well the Skins do the Skins
have vitamins in them oh I see yeah cuz
I kind of been I don't know I've been
avoiding potatoes these days cuz I'm
like oh yeah these aren't good for you
so potatoes do not have fiber okay but
they got other stuff like friend sweet
potatoes are better that I did know oh
my
trainer sweet potatoes are nice but I
don't like cooking with them because
they're usually like so big and
so oh yeah look so big and so hard and
it's like really hard to cut through
them you know to chop them
up I don't want to say it but okay it's
it's just how it is okay it's how how
sweet potatoes are no it's true
definitely they're so yummy though I
sweet potato fries those are
[Music]
yum I thought I heard something are you
okay good yeah yeah yeah be
good is that's fine was very scary did
oh am I still here did somebody end up U
getting the lava I wonder I might go to
the nether really quickly oh yeah it is
like right right there
yeah going to go grab some lava buckets
for uh efficient
furnace cooking nice idea oh do it do it
you can make a blast furnish now oh my
god let's go I guess so yeah iron for
that yeah cuz we have so many emeralds
so oh wait wait I should oh there's like
horses and donkeys in here in the nether
oh yeah they kind of wandered in there
didn't
they
a let me just bring this just in case oh
I already wear it oh can't you just make
armor normally at a crafting table
though or is it Enchanted armor you want
to make or something like that um well
the thing is we have I think more
emeralds than we have diamonds so if we
make our own diamond armor we're going
to use up all the diamonds and maybe not
have enough but if you use the also
yeah and if you if you level them up
enough then they might have uh armor
that's already Enchanted and might be
some cool stuff I get it
interesting this is all new stuff
mear you can use emeralds instead of
diamonds basically yeah yeah yeah yeah
and that's pretty much the only use we
have for um emeralds you know a yeah
exactly cuz you know we're not really we
haven't been very lucky with merchants
and stuff
still some oh
Apple okay I
want I thought four apples that's pretty
good there's another one damn
it living on the edge for these
apples there's so much lava here but
it's like so
far got it
oh nice it's working there's another one
up there but they're going away so
that's good apple will fall
down eat new
axxe
okay
cobone thank you physics
H gas
CH gas boo please no
gas somewhere y don't bring him in
here he's too fat to fit through don't
worry but he might just spawn in our
world on its own he's a chunky guy you
never
know okay okay okay oh wait oh no no
two apples nice I bet we'll we'll have
this apple quest done by the time that
it's over today's session is over y y
indeed get rid of this and then plant a
bunch of more
trees wait how am I going to get down I
guess I'll mine
down oh yeah you're in the nether right
yeah oh am I up there
[Music]
okay word maybe not I can't
reach zombie DOB
he's looking for
you I'm scared suddenly a lava pocket
will open up there oh yeah that would
not be optimal oh nice I think they're
disappearing
yeah touch it lava touch the lava touch
no no no don't touch reach still don't
touch it don't touch
it I don't want to touch it what do you
want m
[Music]
can't
reach should I rather go to the bottom
what do you think
guys
y bottom
better this might not be a good way of
doing things either let me mine my way
down which one
is that one that one that one
okay the things I do for the furnace and
for efficiency I mean it's going to be
super helpful
though okay oh no I almost died hey but
you didn't though that's what's
important hey
let's go she lives I like the the
feeling of being almost
dead it's a nice
kick oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah all right I guess I'll try to go to
the bottom that's actually really funny
hold on
[Music]
oh this is the most effective way to
search for
apples what what what way have you found
to just Spam a sapling with bone meal
and then quickly cut down the tree and
then let the leaves fall
away instead of letting the tree grow to
be super super tall and it's kind of
annoying to chop down
and yeah
I think this is the best
way we found out what Callie's humor is
small tree no you know what I think I
think I know how I can maybe describe my
sense of humor but you probably might
still not understand it I was thinking
in like a comparison to like a wine or
something like that you know I kind of
like like uh oh yeah dry and dark yeah
dry and dark y but I feel like I know
it's kind of hard to express sometimes
it's very
specific
hilarious I can't explain why certain
things make me
laugh it's
odd tastes better with time
maybe but how do I build down when
there's nothing you know for me to make
a stair
[Music]
guys maybe if I drop a [\h__\h] ton of Soul
Sand or sand oo and then like stack it I
know further further
where you don't you need sand yeah
that's what I was just
thinking mhm and
then shovel it away is this even worth
it right now this
effort there
dig into Mountains to form stair yeah
Ender o o o Callie
Ender o o o oh he's zipping a rep please
sir don't I want nothing to do with you
sir
please just use
coal Coal we also need for the
Torches but yeah okay it doesn't take
forever with you right now never mind
then s
[Music]
oh wasn't this more before I
guess isn't that am's roommate uh
maybe do some
sorting I'm grinding a she's probably
making Hoppers right now let see there's
so much Redstone oh my
God there's a lot of redstone falling in
here okay I'll do some organization
then cool quick she definitely is uh
working on fixing
[Music]
it my
fox my fox is going to steal
things yeah it's obsidian now I think
it's a good idea cuz like of course if
it's like fixed in a way that we don't
uh you know have any explosions anymore
then we don't need it anymore but you
don't know what will happen until the
point that we get to that point you know
you know oh true
enough so better to put some obsidian
there now so that it doesn't all fall
apart again yeah much
agreed what am I doing what I I guess I
was trying to extend the bottom floor
let's go
vage this is the random chest I almost
forgot okay oh hey there's one lav
bucket I can sort this
chest
nice
cool guess that
works oh oh oh oh
no don't do
that all
righty what the
Amy wait I got five oh oh wait am I
might be needing them forgot to put them
I didn't intend to take them I don't
know if am is watching this stream or
now and she's like oh K took my iron
wasn't my attention it's back in the box
now eight pieces of
iron dang
it okay oh this can go in there too and
then red stone here make a blast furnace
no I don't want to like in case there's
like doing you know that work over there
and fixing the Hoppers and stuff I don't
want to take the iron that we have
now once she's gone I can look at how
much iron we have
yeah the chicken I see you kie you see
me hey oh not anymore you're too
far oh I see you again making trees
happen
hello so close yet so far give me
Apple a yeah we don't have gripstone no
no don't guys this version is very very
old I don't know why this version had to
should but m is there a reason why maybe
they
can't yeah it's got to be like the mod
and I think there's
other one block mods that also work with
newer versions and it's just the the
version that they got I don't know well
it's got to do something to do with
that oh yeah that's right 30 minutes
from now guys I got to do the reveal oh
yeah so we'll play a little bit more 2.0
2.0 y I like it a lot I don't know if
ever else will but I like it a
lot I liked it you liked it there's a
lot of
movement and I don't think it's too
different where it's weird or anything
like that I don't know I'm
excited guys please pay attention to her
cheeks I think the cheeks are cute my
cheeks look at them now and then look at
them later
ah oh yeah actually I'm interested that
you say that I'm going to look
too what if you saw someone else in the
distance on their own own Islands doing
one block that would be really cute
actually I'd love that a yeah like an M
PG exactly I'll make these apples
golden that' be cool I think so
too but like then if they get too close
it's like whoa there buddy it's going on
a little too close for
comfort I just want to see them from far
away that's
all almost reached it we now have 47
diamonds that's pretty
good
okay wow does that also do we still have
iron blocks that we didn't unleash I
think that there's uh only one there's
only one so I didn't even bother putting
it in the
oven don't worry about the Torches guys
don't worry oh boy I think we're at 18
golden apples
now almost done sick thanks for the
membership gift thank
you your cheeks to stop looking at me
stop looking at my cheeks how about
that you can stop looking at my
cheeks BR dang you
[\h__\h] okay
new blocks it's incredible how many
blocks are necessary for all these
things
man so many blocks but we only have one
block well we started from that's the
amazing thing is like all this came from
one block can you believe it yeah I
really love it that's why like all these
buildings they just they feel really
special
mhm yeah we built it all together I mean
you definitely carried though I will say
you built a lot of
Stuff n no a lot of like unimportant
stuff yeah only a few important things
only a few quite a few but it's exciting
excited to see if we can beat the Ender
Dragon oh we can think so we're all
adding to it and with all our Mighty
power we're going to do it can't wait
can I make slabs all of this oh
yeah give me those
apples I know you want to grow apples
you just gave me three from One Tree I
know you're there don't you lie to
me this Panda really likes this area I
don't know what's wrong with
you Anda why ah the ingame hunger is
hitting me uhoh
we have a decent amount of food though
this time that's as long as I'm like out
here I just keep on refilling my um my
bowl with mushroom soup because that's
endless doesn't take up anything endless
mushroom soup it's
easy at least ingame kiata likes
mushroom soup only in game though right
you're just not a mushroom person huh I
like I think I like mushroom sauce like
if it if it doesn't have any mushroom
bits in it a is it the texture you like
M the texture yeah but also partially
the flavor but with mushroom sauce like
for example for a steak or so I think
it's not as intense and it's like a good
balance so with that I can tolerate it I
feel like mushrooms don't really have a
taste to me I just like it cuz the
texture is like soft
and she exra hair also they freak me out
like when I I did cook with them
sometimes even with hellofresh and then
I feel like they look like very
terrifying like a horror horror like a a
vegetable out of a horror
movie well there are quite a few
mushrooms in horror movies I feel like
you know the bottom the bottom of a cap
you know those like it looks like a
filter like a air filter or something
yeah it's a run it over my tongue e what
it's like a fun texture like little
flaps
yeah what it's yummy and then when I
wash a mushroom it gets all slimy I
don't get it why does it get so slimy
and weird okay well I what are you
looking at dog I mean I guess I get what
you're saying I actually do have a bit
of uh trauma that affects how I taste
mushrooms so mushrooms um always taste
like pool water to me um and the reason
yeah but I kind of tolerated the reason
is because um I was at a cookout with a
bunch of my friends one time um and it
was it was like we were really excited
to all cook together wash them oh oh no
we washed them yeah they were all like
they were stuffed mushrooms they were
delicious and then someone was bringing
them to us and they tripped and fell
next to the pool and they hit the pool
water and then we were we felt really
bad so we're like oh we're going to eat
them anyway and so we ate a couple of
them and we didn't get sick and die but
you know they always taste like pool
water to me because of
it what yeah washed them in the
pool
chlorine it wasn't bad associating them
with it yeah I think I probably always
will cuz it's a core memory for me
but yeah I mean yeah I'd never eat them
again if they were soaked in pool water
but when I taste them I just that
lingering memory you know yo where my
apples at I feel like we should we're
due for an apple now what's going on
here okay going on got to run for one
more small batch of blocks Bo but
then more bone
meal it's not worse than bathtub Pizza
in my
opinion
yeah the bathtu pizza yeah dang it need
new
axe yeah that's another core memory
you just
got yeah everyone can go if you believe
in
yourself okay more blocks more blocks
give me more blocks what could I take
this
time T nachos how about these that
doesn't sound good
oh looks so
nice I want to help I'm in mining I'm
almost done well Oh you mean in the the
one block right yeah she's she's been
mining probably looking for iron oh I
should clean up over there okay I'll
organize oh she would probably
appreciate that
yeah oh bunny I can't believe am she
felt like N I can't leave it like that
after all
yeah when she was the one who was like
ah do we even need the this do we
need it's like once you have something
like that going you just can't can't get
it off your mind you know yeah I can't
leave it like that did you forget about
your stream in 20 minutes no I did not
forget about my stream in 20 minutes I
didn't you guys got to calm down calm
down we'll do it we'll be there my brain
worms
about constructions yeah that's a good
way to put
it all right food time time food
time you got me man I want to eat some
McDonald's right now McDonald's why I
feel like that would heal my tummy H oh
yeah you think it would cleanse you yeah
nice tummy cleanse with some
mcdonals I want to eat some really salty
potato fries yeah that's like drunk food
I guess oh but you would I don't think
you know anything about that but yeah no
yeah but I guess it does the same kind
thing a a alcohol
virgin you've never had any at all at
any time I mean I've tried sell of
things cuz people are always like oh you
should try this you should try this I'm
sure you like this one oh this doesn't
taste like alcohol at all I'm like it it
tastes so much like alcohol to me pure
pressure oops sorry sorry elmet sorry I
hurt you that's fine you don't need
it yeah so i' I've tried sell our things
I tried wines I've tried um I don't know
I don't think I tried beer cuz I already
know by the smell that I'll hate it beer
tastes like dish water this bad mhm I
can imagine that I know that if I like
really force myself which is probably
what a lot of teenagers like do they
force themselves to like drink it
because that's cool and then they'll
like work the tolerance against it and
then they'll end up liking it or they
just get addicted to it or whatever I
don't know oh yeah but I haven't hit
that point yet so I still hate it and I
don't feel like forcing myself to you
know yeah it's not something you need in
your life you already know you don't
like it so no reason to force
yourself cuz honestly I've been saving
money and I've been saving sanity oh
yeah better for your health too oh I got
a new music please
better for my health exactly I don't
have like you know like problems
with getting drunk and getting into an
accident or something like that or or
having crazy bar fights or [\h__\h] like
that y bar fights kind of pop off though
at least when you watch them yeah but I
get what you
mean yeah probably I mean really
actually it is for the better you don't
need to change a thing
yahua I think so too yeah
oh I like this track this is a Bop yeah
Waffle House fights for example they
sound fun to watch but not fun being
yeah I'll watch from
outside catch me outside how about
that you remember that that was a silly
[Music]
time my first tequila shot I didn't like
it you mean tequila sucks tequila I like
the song Tequila
oh this is nice do we already have this
CD because it's really nice I really dig
this one it's cute this is
cute it makes me think of shenanigans
between all of
us oh yeah it's new we didn't have that
one nice new
Tunes cute
[Music]
s what
the me and AR hurting each other no no
no no no infighting
sorry you good on me we hurt each other
it's
okay what is love baby don't hurt me
[Music]
trying to identify the right blocks but
I'm too
slow to efficient and shovel my way
through every day I'm
shuffling oh I wonder how much more oh
yeah we're still mining okay I'll try to
be
quicker actually not too much in here
right now sh
sh chest
oh who needs that okay more things to
organize okay I'll try to organize this
myself thanks oh my [\h__\h] god 50
memberships are you crazy I got dropped
to 50 too you guys are super generous
thank you so much hey same person maybe
who who is
it that's a different person but still
Hey Big Ups to you big UPS big up to
everybody for the memberships you guys
have been
sending wow so generous yeah in collabs
I don't really I can't really say thank
you out loud all the time but appreciate
you very
[Music]
much so true what am I doing what am I
doing what am I doing
[Music]
why are you standing on top you can't
have anything in this chest sir don't
even
think I my final inventory is looking
pretty good gosh those chickens are
popping off Kiara gosh what do you what
are you feed them they will not shut up
chickens need to take their meds calm
down that's oh 10 more let's go let's go
question mark stop walking out still no
freaking apples that's we have some you
said you can
leave you're not
[Music]
allowed yeah yours are pretty good thank
you
welcome oh it's so crowded in here sh
yeah maybe you should thin out the her
yeah thin out the a little BS eggs eggs
eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs
eggs eggs eggs am I right
Kelly
yep oh yeah eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs
eggs eggs she knows what she's talking
[Music]
about hey hey can't open the chest if
you guys are there oh God there's so
many many okay like I said you got to
thin out the herd survival of the
fittest just give him a
[Music]
sword this way at least I possibly won't
hurt the small
ones oh that was a strange noise a
phantom that was weird why is it
appearing
now I think I maybe came out of the one
block oh
but it's burning already no worries what
a big
dummy chill chat
CH you know this is how we
do this is how we do this is how we do
do
it this is how we do it oh two different
songs Katy Perry to what's that song
This is how we do it oh yeah I don't
know who sings it but I know it it's one
of those
[Music]
songs that was 50 Cent
really that was 50 cent no way
Backstreet Boys question
mark
maybe mon tell Jordan okay that sounds
more like it cuz two people said
it
Jordan that's a Bob I need to listen to
that and get again this is how we do
properly yeah and then sing it in
K is a
Bop Mory KY clearly wrote it ah yes one
of my more famous
bangers why are you guys standing up
there is this like survival in Instinct
oh my God it's kind of making me sad oh
where they standing feel
bad this really hurts my heart just
saying kfp I'm not doing this with like
an innocent light lightweighted heart or
so oh are you killing him hurts yeah you
feel bad I I multiplied them and now I'm
like taking them
down bring to the frer yeah you got to
thin out the numbers I'm here to witness
the slaughter oh we're pretty much done
do you see how there's mostly only
children still there wait there was more
than
this
yeah I mean at least more grown ones
yeah
I see broke a you need a new one f is
strong I'm always happy to supply more
murder weapons if you ever need any just
let me know okay no you can't
escape what about me it's cuz he tried
to escape I had to kill him I had to do
it understandable oh the panda is on top
of
everything okay it's bread time oh yeah
cook L
of can you please stop with
a I have a sword no I have no way to
defend
myself we could
[Music]
EP hopefully
he'll sleep might be a good idea I think
I have to stop actually playing I got to
stop playing yeah possibly
yeah it's 2.0 time let's go at long last
the
reveal oh I'm nervous
only a little nervous though I hope you
guys like app sorry I should end it too
and then right into your reveal oh only
if you want to you can keep playing are
you doing it from the right right from
The First beginning like I'll chat a
little bit we'll chat a little bit but
yeah don't worry about it take your time
and even if you want to keep streaming I
don't
mind no it's it's late anyway I should
end it anyway oie doggy especially if I
want to get up for jackbox oh true yeah
jaet Foss party yeah yeah Mo place'll be
fun it's still happening right it's
still happen I I
think I think all good all good we'll
see I just need to check something but
um but yeah thanks so much for watching
everyone and please look forward to it
look forward to tonight I think uh we'll
update you if anything changes um but
I'm excited and yeah keep watching our
adventures one block Minecraft things
are really off getting int possibly
another do you think you can stream
Minecraft tomorrow too yeah I can try to
wake up let me see um I wish they they
weren't lining up these recordings day
after day but that's okay I think I
should still be able to wake up for it I
think it'll be okay I'll let you know
though okay yeah and maybe I might not
stream fine too don't worry about it I I
don't think we're going to the end
tomorrow so it's not like the big
important episode that's the big one
that we got to coordinate on when every
big one yeah okay well I'll see you guys
later bye kiaha bye dead beats see you
guys shortly and yeah I'll catch you
guys on the flip side you're welcome
goodbye peace Goodbye by bye bye
see
that