[Music]
my
[Applause]
[Music]
um
go
[Music]
[Laughter]
huh
come on man you
[Music]
why is it always obs
i think you have a magician in your
computer
pc
must be
i'm damn
good
all right cool it's fine it's fine well
it's fine it's fine it's fine it's fine
it's fine
i'll figure it out
okay uh then switch back
all right
come on now oh my god what was that did
you have teeth
there we go
now we're back
[Laughter]
i felt that in my heart
deep inside my soul
no i can't
even the bang isn't it's not enough
that's not enough you guys may notice
something special about today's setup
that special thing being everyone is
cardboard
we tried so hard and got so far but in
the end it did not even matter um
actually we we actually did not
even try today because it just wouldn't
have been possible um we're just gonna
keep waiting for things to get fixed
someday
for now this is the best we can do um
you guys know everyone's voices right
it'll be kind of semi-podcast style uh i
don't know if they really know our
voices though
do they even know who's talking right
now
[Music]
yes no
now they'll never be able to tell
i mean i can still tell by your laugh
kiara i i know where
you are
[Music]
i'm so ready for this i got my nails
done today at this parlor at the
shopping mall and the lady was such a
[\h__\h] like honestly the first look that
she gave me when i walked in there she
was like she's something better than me
and i'm honestly just like girl look at
yourself in the mirror and then rethink
that right away okay i'll come back girl
was it it was like she wasn't like
undressing you with her eyes oh my god
it was absolutely incredible you know
her her name's sandra sandra looked at
me like that can you believe it
unbelievable
sorry i mean i don't know
i'm done i'm done i'm done
what uh what a crazy ride he took us
through there here
oh my goodness
before the stream before the stream when
we all turned that effect on we all
sounded the same and you literally
couldn't know who was talking i mean
kind of there were different there were
a couple different levels but for the
most part yeah uh you guys i could not
tell
i could not tell
it was very frightening
but i'll all get in the hood
oh good
now
everyone else's name kelly what else is
new i see something new you do it's a
logo
you guys like the new logo it's by
spirit snare big ups just
snap
it again
dude yeah my dude made several different
versions of the the myth breakers logo
so you'll see some different renditions
of it but
yeah what you guys think it's all the
characters together
it's us yeah it's you guys beautiful
very
very accurate i would say good good
stuff and also very cute
thank you
is even chilling up in there up in the
corner
it's very mystical and um i like it it
fits the campaign perfectly also big ups
um to that intro
that was done um
but it was so good i felt like i was in
a concert yeah me too
the one the only raw hence thank you
very much raw hence
for the amazing raw
that was really cool when i when i heard
my my bgm in there i was going i was
like yo what
yeah
it looks it sounds so good i've never
imagined my my opening music
like that you know
good
definitely yeah big ups threw us through
a loop there but
big
because
yes something like that um
um guys today's session is pretty
special because um it's a session that i
got ideas for from uh the deadbeats
we made a session yeah
[Laughter]
a squid game based ttrpg would be cool i
think that would be neat but um
no today i've been trying to stay away
from that please please don't drag me
into i don't think you would like it
kiara is the thing yeah exactly that's
the thing so but you don't have to
that's fine that's fine it's not for
everyone not everything is for everyone
so it's all good um but you know if if
you ever do get any vibes from from that
it might be because i watched it
recently you know you never know what
kind of inspirations are gonna work
their way
uh into the
into the campaign some random ones some
random ones too yeah hey hey what's that
what's that there's the episode you mess
up you die
i mean these new characters of course
yeah if your character dies you do get
to make a new character
so this is the it's the semi-finals
right before the end
one total of the second one one two two
one two one two two two
never dies i will protect
yeah
forever at all costs yeah well you guys
are heading close into the mid-season
finale i realized that this was not
going to uh be over in five sessions
um oh so you guys are getting close
though and once we get to that point you
guys can decide whether you want to keep
going with it or maybe uh switch out
with someone else or um
etc that's completely up to you guys so
and don't feel bad about wanting to do
that that's also cool
um
but yeah once we get to that little that
little mid-season finale which will be
coming up uh in a couple sessions
um you guys can make that choice so yeah
okay just just for thought
um but now we are getting to a point
where you know you never know characters
might die
um
so just awesome yeah just uh
be careful with uh how you approach
things and you know i'm just going to
give you the regular caution that you
ought to have my
my gm in the past was very kind and
really didn't like kill any of us
um unless we asked for it um
but that's not usually how it's done
so you never know and i am death so i do
have a certain obligation to fulfill
right kelly if you kill me i'm coming
back because a valley girl just dies
oh
god you can't say that
you can't garage
goddammit
all right valley girl ttrpg oh please no
please
everyone plays a different valley girl
we're like barbie dolls let's go yeah
it's like the mean girls movie but
everyone's a different character
and kelly is ken
oh god
hey ladies
oh no is that what you want
yes
oh [\h__\h] okay we all want it and when do
we want it now
oh yeah oh yeah no please
so today's session it might be a
two-parter guys it depends on how fast
you solve the mystery which could be
fast or slow just depending um
however we are going to hard cut off at
two hours 30 minutes of playing the
session because
um some of us are dead inside i'm not
gonna say who might be me
um
running on a little bit
i also don't want to rush the mission uh
for you guys either i want you to figure
it out on your own
so with that puzzle time oh i don't know
it it could be
you always have to prepare yourself for
a nice little riddle um yeah it's
probably a riddle
no riddles yeah riddles are very uh very
close to puns
hopefully indeed true
yeah they're in the same family for sure
exactly all right now let's see
no no do not i don't want to go to that
playlist
we're going to start
we're going to start now
with a little wreath
okay i love recap with a little recap
and if you ladies need some bgm
i'm throwing it your way
thank you
and there it goes
all right
okay
so then
where we last left off excuse me
last time on
myth breakers
the team had just gotten finished
dealing with
a certain debaucherous vampiric party
of the blood-sucking
nature you had just barely escaped
after a
especially intriguing card duel
with a certain
part of the basis the special heart of
the cards moment
with a certain bespectacled uh vampiric
being
from a certain place that may or may not
be
russia combined with italy who could say
scout had uh effectively poisoned the
party guests and definitely left an
impression
that was awesome
yes that might be where the impression
was
um
watson had accompanied tiara on her
mission
to effectively
quote unquote
seduce but more aptly um distract
distract the vampire twins
who were hiding the ledger
in the master bedroom but got into a bit
of a predicament herself thankfully she
and wattuto managed to escape unscathed
and with the ledger in tow it was enough
to put them the romanos behind bars
or so it would seem at least that's what
the news outlets tell you right
you never know who has sway over the
news and
who has sway in other areas for example
are they really behind bars are they
roaming free
you guys couldn't actually be sure you
don't have access to that intel
unfortunately they're in prison in peru
on the beach but a pina colada
possibility possibilities wait peru has
beaches right okay never mind
yes
i i don't have my lap in front of me
sorry
i kind of i'm not good at remembering
[Music]
sorry i need to take super bang
right back at it
so you all returned after a successful
mission complete
and
you all managed to
get yourselves a pretty hefty sum for
your salary not too bad
each one he has received a grand total
of
500 bucks
not bad not bad that was a good mission
a mission well done so you all do have
a bit of wealth to you now just a bit
just a bit and also with the free
lodging that is offered to you
by the bar
it's not overall a bad deal
and now you may do that money as you
please you could do various things like
buy a car with 500
you could
buy a weapon if you like
but hoverboard
they can
skateboard if you wanted to buy a
hoverboard by golly you could certainly
search for one or you could always ask
the merchant kid that's living in the
basement you never know
possibility online
online shopping is definitely fine but
you may need to do a roll depending upon
what you're looking for
to make sure that it's available for you
and you can effectively find it
[Laughter]
that is important
[Music]
yeah so that is the current state of
things and um in addition
where we are currently um before this
next mission is actually several days
have passed
about four days or so and you guys have
been taking on little side missions
just on the side just just little things
that the guild has assigned to you this
this bar guild here
they have assigned to you uh a couple a
couple little small things
here and there dealing with the
supernatural going to check out this
spot make sure that these two clans
aren't fighting with each other and
normally things are pretty okay nothing
too noteworthy that would need something
like a session right
so
with all of that combined you guys have
managed to scrape up even a little bit
more money but only about a hundred
bucks each to your name sadly these are
a little different okay so 600 total
nice
we'll go ahead and add that to the
experience sheet as well so you guys
know how much money you have
yes yes it's important to know
and 600 what did you say yes 600 for
everyone
totally in that wallet
in that wallet thanks for the alka super
p.m
[Music]
i did get athletics one plus one point
uh before the stream gotcha just knowing
for the viewers who were keeping count
of everything right yeah we will have
updated sheets a bit later um
well i will try to post them as they
become updated and mass or rather as
they have big updates made to them i
will continue to post them but so far um
yes tiara has upgraded by one stealth
point and one athletics point since the
original sheet
yes and scout has upgraded an athletic
skill point
and watson
excuse me wato has also upgraded with
one skill point
all right
so this is the current state of affairs
now
for today's session
we start off with all of you guys
hanging out in the common room
all of you guys are just chilling out in
the main lobby area that i will pull out
dude you guys can see the floor map
just get an idea of where everybody's
room is etcetera and i'll show this
again for you guys
essentially this is the main
room
uh the main area for you guys's uh
activities
you guys had separated yourselves
between the various rooms and of course
there's a common area where you guys can
hang out and there's really only a
a shitty little tv in the middle you
guys all have to share it a big couch
but shitty small tv
oh
is it
at least from this era or
you know if you had to venture again
might be from the 90s
[Music]
oh
has a vhs player built in
oh man it works it works you can watch
the original air bud
it's already loaded in there
yeah
cute movie
vic is also a big fan constantly
watching it
he would be wouldn't he he would be a
buddy
he would be
occasionally kid joins in poking his
head through the through the market for
the little market stall window
um movie night
movie night indeed but you guys are all
just kind of chilling hanging out um
off to your own sort of
machinations and whatnot when you
receive
a call
from lady m
who walks down the stairs and says
are you all busy right now
yes no
yes no which one is it
i thought oh not busy
oh excellent how about the rest of you
would you like to hear an interesting
prospect i've got
some news that i heard
through the grapevine so to speak some
of you might be
interested in this
how much
how much we make in ma'am
not so much a matter of how much you're
making but rather
how
much um how much you may be discovering
because there's some information i
received that does not line up
ma'am we just about died last time
well you're 600
all the more richer are you not
is that really yeah
though
yeah discovery isn't gonna really do a
trick for us for the next mission you
want me to seriously answer that
i mean
all right all right fine hear me out how
about this
when on earth did the four of you go to
a carnival
what
when did you go can you tell me
i've seen him on the television time
but don't play dom with me
come on now
what you've only been watching air bud
i see
good good taste in movies but honestly
when did you go because i've received
several reports that say you four were
seen at the carnival on the beach
that's impossible anna no you haven't
left i mean
carnival on the beach though no i
thought for sure that yule would have
gone there because it is the beach that
is organized by euless college every
year so i thought that it would make
sense
uh i'm not really a party goer
huh well carnivals aren't quite like
parties but all right if you insist then
something fishy is certainly going on
because
apparently
there are how do i say this
there must be other versions of you
running around
plus
well gosh darn it there's some imposters
among us we may as well go weed them out
because if they're getting a 600
paycheck and i'm not i'm sitting here on
my ass rotten in this room with a bunch
of these
folks with this
dog film
money myself i'm not letting no scout
and posture take my hard-earned money
sure i'll go see what's up
well that's the spirit scout all right
i'm glad to hear it and by the way not
to say there won't be monetary
compensation it's just you need to find
something supernatural about what's
going on here and there must be honestly
if all four of you were seen in the same
place that's no coincidence
something weird is going on here
interesting adam
i think it's better than the 50th
time watching airbud
hey it's we're going to the beach
sandals
oh yes it is indeed a beach carnival
organized by a yule's college in fact
every year
i hear that i hear that they have a
really good musical guest this year
oh yeah
who is it anna
i don't know to be honest i i wasn't
familiar with the name of the band i
even forget what it is now but they
seemed a little odd
they seemed like they had a gimmick
about them and they really liked soda
i don't know it's all a bit confusing
but perhaps you will see when you get
there
yes
also um
i'm not entirely sure but i heard i
heard that somebody saw yule of
volunteering at the carnival and so
perhaps the professor might know
something about that
a volunteer
oh i guess i haven't checked in with the
professor in a while ah
i thought they figured it out
clones
the government clones
ah
i see
well that makes sense makes sense to me
aya
that would make sense indeed
the government
ah yes
of course it's it's definitely the
government and and no supernatural
things are happening just out of nowhere
um
that's it anna yeah
wow what a lovely tinfoil hat you have
what would you do what would you think
about that
[Laughter]
what would you think that uh we could
what what would you think would come in
handy on our little trip this time
what do you have to offer to sell us so
we might
need on our trip i know well you can
always ask kid over at the market but i
would like to advise you
you guys need to be careful you need to
not bring big weapons with you because
this is supposed to be a family a fun
event
you know
a family fun event with clones um
apparently i mean but they don't know
that they don't know that they're
interacting with these so-called clone
people but if you walk in with a big
sniper they're not going to let you
inside so you'll need to be careful
exercise some caution
let's see that's all right i have a
revolver anyway anna so i'll just leave
my rifle here then um
we can pretend to be uh wild animal
control with our big ol weapons we are
the last resort when that lion gets out
of that cage there ma'am ah this weapon
is for your safety
that's smart
that is that is smart however i do not
believe there is a petting zoo at the
carnival it seems more like a theme park
kind of thing you know one of those
cheap carnivals you just pop up on the
side of the road
oh i'm so sorry i was confusing with
circus my bad my bad we don't have none
of that room for i'm sorry i do wonder
if there's a reason for that perhaps the
god of this world
named uh something incorrectly
the circus huh isn't that a place where
clowns hang out oh wait a minute
well
there's a little underhanded roast i got
there for you guys if you would be
interested in buying something you
certainly may
but you're calling us clowns oh what was
that no no of course not did nothing of
the sort
why would i do that
come on now you're my my esteemed my
esteemed uh colleagues
of course not clowns don't be silly
don't be silly
ladies
it's not like clouds oh watso do you
have a fear of clowns
well i'm sure that it's fine i'm sure
that clowns are so
so back in the day i think that it will
be fine now you don't really see a lot
of clowns in carnivals anymore circus
sure but
carnivals um it's a bit it's a bit rare
so i wouldn't worry too much about it
they hide antenna in their nose
ah
i see i was not aware of that thank you
for letting me know so i'll be sure to
steer clear of clown noses
wow
with that being said
um
are you ready to go or
would you like to oh no okay would you
like to prepare in any way
yes you should probably prepare a little
bit yes sure absolutely then feel
absolutely free to do so what would you
like to do in preparation for this
mission
uh
can i see at kids market if he has some
kind of um
um
[Music]
acrid
uh
liquid acrid liquid sure let me tell you
if somebody would drink it they would
like um be
burned up from inside and i don't know
die oh that's quite the lethal weapon so
some straight up poison okay sure yes
like heartburn
all right
i think yeah literal heartburn very nice
you approach kids market stall and kid
is of course waiting there leaning out
through the window and says
hello madame what can i do you for
wait
do you perhaps sell any
um liquid that could kill someone
perhaps some asic or
you mean like cyanide like poison
and [\h__\h]
i suppose so what would happen if
someone would drink that i don't well i
can i think i can certainly go look
through my wares just a moment
he turns around starts
rummaging through some boxes
heads to the back rummages through some
more boxes you hear him drop something
and yelp
sounds like there's some glass back
there and eventually comes out with some
kind of vial and says well this is about
the last that i got for poison but it's
gonna cost ya if you drink this though
it's bye-bye
oh
sounds good how much you say that i want
300 smackaroos
all right i'm taking one but could you
put it into a
maybe into a
a soda bottle
oh okay soda okay
uh let's see what do i have
uh what do i have in the fridge let me
see what we got here we got
cola
pepsi
what's this huh
hold on a minute
oh i got some strago
what straight yo what is that
it's it's a really kind of niche soda um
it's only enough made in a certain part
of the uh continental u.s but it's still
really tasty all my other stuff is
expired
i see i see um okay um however
i do think that 300 is a little bit
too expensive would you mind going down
a little bit with that especially
because now it's not an original bottle
anymore but in a soda bottle so you can
keep the bottle though
you're not using that empty soda bottle
anymore you can keep the bottle where
the poison was in originally so
you're gonna get some maybe some money
by recycling a bottle right so
how about
going a bit down on the price for miata
because we're doing good stuff here we
we're using this for a good purpose
we're helping you guys so please
consider that don't forget that anna
you drive a hard bargain missy but i'm
gonna need to be persuaded so go ahead
and roll do a persuasion roll i want
your persuasion plus manipulation
um persuasion
[Music]
um
is there is there anything else i could
use instead of you could use presents
oh instead of persuasion intimidation is
also fine but
you may have to play it a little bit
he's just a kid
okay so i can i can do presents can i do
a presence and manipulation oh no
unfortunately you have to use persuasion
in there yeah
persuasion and presence yes or
manipulation up to you
okay okay
ah just just barely
just barely he beats you out by one
success but you know what he does say
he leans over the counter and says
i'll make it 250.
if
i can get a little smooch right here on
my cheek
ew
punch him
i would need you to give me the bottle
first and then i i'll give you a smooth
shout out
you're not gonna trick me are you
no why would i do that anna
i'm a good girl you know that don't
check it
okay well here you go hands you the vial
taking the violin turning around bye-bye
thanks
hey
i will get you for that i'm not going to
forget that you owe me 50 bucks lady
you owe me 50 bucks
okay i i got that poison
anyone else who wants to buy something
from kid don't forget to bargain with
him
hey kid
i got a motion sensor
oh some deer pee
um
[Music]
i don't know hmm
wow deer pea i mean motion sensor i can
probably look into but let me let me
check
let me check the uh let me check the
piste jars be right back
oh goes
a place you can order from
oh
oh thanks i'll remember that
all right no i never
never mind on the the deer you're right
and just emotions
i have some elephant urine will that
work
no
no no
how about horse urine is that
all right that's fine i'll get the
motion sensor all right one sec let me
see what we got here
okay got a motion sensor uh this one's a
little old though so
hopefully it'll help you but it might
might glitch out every once in a while
sorry about that it's gonna be 50 bucks
because it's kind of a broken piece of
[\h__\h] yeah
50 bucks for
now what do i need to make this thing
work again
squirt hmm well if you really want to
make sure that it doesn't like break or
anything oh
let's see you might have to repair it or
you're going to need some special parts
though i can let you know where the
parts are where you can buy them but
it's gonna take some time definitely
more than a day
you're gonna charge me 50 bucks for this
stupid contraption that doesn't even
work and then i have to go out and find
the part to make the parts work would
you like to give me the smooch
[Music]
take 50 take 25 bucks off of it
it could be on the forehead
my shoes i i don't care anywhere is fine
anywhere is fine
just like on the tv
[Music]
is your mama ever told you what happened
when you kiss a girl before you're 18. i
don't have a mom
okay uh
how about your happy don't have a dad
either
all right let me tell you what happens
when you kiss a girl
before you've reached the age
of age
[Music]
you're
yes i like
scouts i want to listen so i need you to
give me this wait what do you do eggs
all three of them fall right off oh
i didn't even know i had three
so i'm gonna have to ask you to hand me
over this me
piece of [\h__\h]
oh this piece um
this piece of machinery
[Music]
why would i trick you
why on earth i'm just trying i just want
i just want to get my money at this
point i just want to get my 600 bucks
and come back to the stupid box in this
stupid stinky musky old bar and deal
with you're the stinky one
watch your mouth squirt or i will kiss
you and you will have all three legs
fall off give me the damn machine oh no
okay well you're gonna need to roll for
that um
you can use intimidation
and presence or manipulation
all right i'll do that one all right
wait what did you say presence and
manipulation intimidation and
manipulation oh my god my ears okay
one more time presence and intimacy yes
presence and intimidation let's go
let's go
intimate
wait where's someone
intimidation should be under uh skills
it's a social skill
i seriously i see
okay that's four then so that's a
forward 40 10 man yeah
well how many episodes into this i'll
get this eventually you'll get it
eventually everyone does even when i
played we didn't all get it until like
episode 10 so
oh boy yeah we did like 50 though
ugh all right it's just neck and neck
but kid offers you final price
of 30 dollars
i'm taller than you
give me
it's 30 or you don't get it arm wrestle
me right now
okay i'll let's throw down
here we go
arm wrestling is straight strength
how strong is he callie you can't be
that strong
well what does that say to you
yeah okay not very strong come on
count
this squirt all right hand it over
you you very swiftly
uh punch his hand into the ground with
your hand
and um he squeaks out in pain and says
fine
here you go
take it get out of my face i don't want
to see you
thanks junior
yeah whatever
and with that you have a motion sensor
yeah
it's kind of dinky but it works most of
the time
thanks yeah you're welcome
anybody else wanted to buy something
uh
do you have
pepper spray and maybe a pocket knife oh
pepper spray and pocket knife is easy
hold on
i'm actually
gonna grab the official book
let's look at the armory
let's look in the armory
let's take a look shall we
let's see what kids got in store here
for by way of pepper spray
and pocket knife
so
blades
um hmm i don't have a pocket knife but i
have a kitchen knife
uh it can do one lethal damage
um how big is this kitchen knife pretty
big it's like one that you would cut
like a big steak with so it's a decently
big sized kitchen knife but it's
definitely like for cooking food
it's not very durable so it might only
last you this mission
um is it carryable without being seen
you could probably conceal it in your
pocket
if your pocket's big enough just wear
some big pocket pants and you'll be fine
i have a pretty pocket in my jacket okay
continue with the scalp
okay what about pepper spray let's see
for pepper spray what do we have here
[Music]
ah pepper spray pepper spray i know that
i had some here
hairspray flame thrower
gloves
looking through my ledger right now well
i could do a quick online order ayesha
here let's see what we got here
all right
we have to wait for shipping
no my guy's pretty quick
that's good
amazon now huh
yeah
what else happens at a carnival
there's like loud noises
and rides
funnel king do you have anything
disguised maybe like wigs
that'd be useful
oh okay i see i see
interesting i don't have any aesthetics
i don't have any pepper spray
but i do have tear gas
how does that cool
sure all right sounds good i'll i'll
give you the stats for it
whatever that means
there you go
should be pretty useful uh let's see
here
[Music]
i don't know what this means maybe you
know what it means but it says reduces
target's dice pool by two for one round
per success scored
so that sounds pretty helpful
all right i'll take it yeah there we go
and it should effectively uh
incapacitate whoever you're fighting
against so
it could be useful
yeah three basketballs the free bashing
is actually pretty good
i'll take it all right very nice
all right anything oh of course the cost
got paid up kitchen knife i'll sell you
for 50 bucks because this is a
state-of-the-art kitchen knife tear gas
is gonna be a hundo
scam
do you wanna i don't know what is that
at a wig as a uh
as a um
buy to get one free
um you're telling me how i want to do my
deals lady please
i could be convinced
all right i could be convinced you want
to roll persuasion
uh okay i'll try
all right translation was
oh you got this in the bag
is it manipulation and
and persuasion
personally
hey
i don't know
anything's possible
oh okay
with one success um kid just kind of
leans over the counter and is like
madame
you have such lovely eyes you know what
i can't help it
i can't help but give you this
incredible offer that would be
knocking it down to a grand total of
could you believe it only 70 bucks
oh
got yourself a deal madame
here you go i'll fake it
yeah good kid yeah
he winks as you walk away
look forward to doing business with you
all right watson anything you want
well i thought i needs a tube
tube what kind of tube you want what
tube tube uh
bamboo casing lead fortified four inch
tube for blow dart
oh i see i see i get what you're talking
about
um
for a blow dart you want the darts too
or just the
tube oh how much
let's see
well there's two all we got is nerf gun
bullets
yeah i got some i got some nerf gun
bullets with poison on the end of them
they basically work um as for the tube
though don't quite have bamboo but i
have so i have a cheap wooden one
that'll still work
sell it to you for
50 bucks
how many darts
let's see each dart's gonna cost you ten
you wanna do a total kiss
um
you smell funny so no thanks
maybe if you if you smelled a little
better
maybe i'd let you kiss my shoe
but well if you don't lower the price
watoto will kiss you wow
okay okay fine wait hold on
you drive a hard bargain
i'm still gonna need you to roll though
either persuasion or intimidation plus
manipulation and presence or presence
up to you kelly while while you two are
doing that can i send you uh something
uh and ask you if that's something that
we can currently buy or if we're like
too low level for stuff like that or
like before it's not available
oh that's a good role did you roll
intimidation or oh i mean that's a good
dice pool but what did you roll
yeah i have two intimidation and four
manipulations all right here let's see
let's see you could you could it could
be fine
it was a good dice pool but
oh what a shame
i don't know uh
kid doesn't know it's okay it's because
kid doesn't believe that you'll do it so
just kind of shakes his head and says
nope this is the same price
okay what auto case now
he says okay okay i'll lower it a little
bit i'll lower it okay
i'll lower it a little bit
okay okay how about this
i'll give you i'll give you the tube
and five darts for a grand total of
for a grand total of 50. okay that's a
really good deal listen you're basically
getting the darts for free
um okay good deal
will take oh
okay
just please go away please oh my god you
just take a shower
do you have a free water cup
[Music]
uh
yeah we got some red solo cups here
sure what does not take
oh these these are uh definitely cool
kiara i would say maybe after one more
mission
if you guys do a good job then kid can
upgrade the market so
okay yeah
it's kind of a bit too much yeah it
scales a bit with like how well the
business is doing so if you guys do good
then that means that you get better
better possibilities for a better market
in the future
okay mm-hmm these are very um
are there like any kind of uh free
uh basic materials around here like a
lighter or like a torch and stuff wasn't
that like basic stuff we could take yeah
yeah you guys can take things like
flashlights if everybody wants to take a
flashlight if everyone wants to take
some rope it's all basic stuff you got
to return it later i didn't mean i
didn't mean did i say torch i meant
lighter oh yeah yeah yeah you did it
okay lighter works too yeah they're
definitely free like lighters and stuff
like that so okay yeah whatever you want
i'll
then i'll take my phone i'll take a
lighter and i'll take a torch and can we
take a rope as well sure yeah rope
apparently okay okay make sure you write
it down share it though mm-hmm
very good okay i'll just write it all in
in the document here yeah sounds good
okay
phone all right
can i ask uh kids some more questions
while we're preparing sure he'll listen
enthusiastically
depends
depends on the question
what
what else you you got anything on sale
there sh
skippy oh let me see what i got
hold on
i'm pulling out the ledger
all right what do i have here
um
i've got some ear plugs i've got a bag
of dirt
got some
some flash paper
uh oh there's the motion detector got
that for you rear view glass is pretty
cool um let's see you got some glow
sticks
uh i got a ladder
um
oh what's this a stink tag
that seems fun what wait what stinky
i'll explain it to you so basically you
can use this as a sticky fluid with a
persistent noxious odor and you tag it
on an enemy with a powerful unmistakable
and extremely unpleasant scent
[Music]
so maybe you don't need the stink tag
let's see what else we got here
rescue whistle um
let's see what else
digital recorder
duct tape and then as by way of weapons
a way of weapons
i'm slipping
i got a hairspray flame thrower
that's pretty cool
um taser glove
uh
what's this
uh do you have a cane with a hidden
knife inside
who came with a hidden knife i have a
cane and i have a hidden knife
uh you could probably put it together
if you're smart enough
i can put it together for you if you
want
what
yes please thank you
okay sure you had gotta buy it though
yeah you gotta buy it
what's the price well the cane itself is
gonna be let me think
um no pretty nice cane here
uh kane is gonna be 50 knife is also
going to be 50. no bargaining you
already bargained for today
what if we broke the cane does it become
cheaper
if you broke it
yeah oh i mean i can't sell it if it's
broken
my toe will pass for today okay
let me know whenever you want to do
business
you got a rubber mallet in there
rubber mallet oh let's
see yeah i can get one for you
i can get one for mallet yeah got any
guns any weapons any
sure
oh i got lots of weapons what kind of
weapon you looking for a gun revolver
pistol rifle shotgun something else like
uh
we have a dark gun
slingshot flare gun
uh-huh i have made a slingshot i don't
think i need one of those
uh you gotta you're gonna
you gotta one of them one of the mascot
costumes just extra furry ones with the
big old fuzzy feet and the you know
let's see um i have a big chicken
costume it's uh i think it's a mascot
for that uh that really good fried
chicken place what was it kf kft
[Music]
uh-huh yeah
it's kft tn
kfptm
are there any other creatures you got
what is it i got an octopus big old taco
for that takoyaki place close by
anything else
let's see
uh what's this
i got a big old dog
holding a magnifying glass
right uh
uh-huh you may be more specific
i don't know i'm looking for i said
furry
okay
i have another one that's just a huge
dog that looks like a human with like a
human body but it's got a dog head like
human proportions but it's it has fur on
it and there's a dog head
is that what you want
is that what you want scout is that the
costume that you seek
what's that orange one in the back that
you refused to talk about what is that
one don't make me come back there and
search myself squirting what is that one
oh dear god sure i'll take it how much
oh god
sorry brash candicute um
all right let's see
that's gonna i got it out of a dumpster
so it's gonna only cost you 25 bucks
i'll
take it yeah it might be a little i have
a little stench on it a little bit a
little stench a little bit of matting is
fun and all the parts included i'll take
it yeah here it's yours get it out of my
warehouse
thank you wait do you have a hook also
what kind of hook like a clothes hook
actually never mind i can make that
nevermind okie dokie
okay i just have one last thing do you
have a
uh a lock pick
yeah i can sell you a lock i can sell
you a lot pic i make really good
yeah i only make really good lock picks
though so you're gonna need to drop 40
bucks for one of my lock picks you'll
get a lot a lot of it's very likely you
can i'm holding on
hold on before you get scammed by this
three foot tall
booger petri dish i'm not three f i'm
four foot nine that's pretty tall for my
age
cat tiara do you have your hair up right
now do you have hair ties or hair pins
or anything i thought i remember seeing
you i have a lot of hair pins i do like
hey
you're ruining it
i just would like to point out to you
the hairpin gonna give you a plus two
modifier hmm
or is it gonna be some wanky stinky ass
busted oh it might work but here i'm
gonna charge you forty fifty dollars so
talk about my lock picks like that
kid
he shuts the shutters to the warehouse
oh you can hear him grumbling behind
oh don't uh oh
[Laughter]
okay but did you did you just say that a
a hairpin has a two two dice modifier no
k kids uh lock picks have a plus two
modifier a hairpin won't give you a
modifier
okay but i could still try this yeah
sure of course you could
oh there's tons of hairpins though so
you get more chances than once you try
several times yeah
but how many hairpins do you have we
have to establish this right now
oh
oh dear wait let me uh
i'll count it has to be realistic
yeah it's realistic i have one two three
four
five six seven eight okay that's fine
you officially have eight hairpins now
to use this lock face
thank you you did include a lot of those
in the design
that was yes i did i'm smart
all right ladies before we head off to
the mission let's take a teeny tiny
break and then we're gonna get into this
thing
okay
be everyone
[Music]
hello
we are back
we're back the myth breakers are back
from the break
mid break we're back from the
myth breakers from the uh from the break
indeed
[Music]
yeah i know i i got them good
here we are guys we're on the way to the
beach now this little beach carnival
um you guys have officially
grabbed everything that you need in your
inventory you have a wealth of different
items that can help you out here but you
don't really know exactly quite what
you're getting yourselves into yeah
that's true yeah
um
you guys are actually uh dropped off on
location
um by vic driving a nice van
i say nice it's like okay
normal white van
drops you off you guys go oh by the way
um
i forgot to tell you
you guys are gonna be taking grandma out
hey grandma
excuse me from from the back seat of the
truck you hear a little voice pipe up oh
hello
dearies i do love a carnival
um
are you sure this is a good idea
oh i can be useful and and even if not
i'm just going to go off and and ride
some of the rides on my lonesome so
don't worry about spending too much time
with little old me i just wanted to have
a chance to go to the carnival with you
all that's all
grandma though uh
if you see anyone that looks like us
make sure it's really us maybe we should
have a safe word
oh that's a great idea well what should
the safe word be
what do you think uh girls what what
should it be
pies
that sounds tasty but i don't really
make pies
hmm
it's a good idea cookies oh way to be a
downer grandma oh well would you like me
to make you a pie i can just not right
now
my cookies are pretty good
why do we need a safe word
because she might get in trouble and be
seeing our
imposters at the carnival and we don't
know what's gonna happen scout i don't
good point gotta make sure that she
doesn't get killed by our imposters who
knows
ah we should have bought that stupid
emergency whistle from that kid
wrapped it around granny
life alert can i make a life alert
um
i'm just kidding we can keep going
i'll be fine but that's okay safe word
grandma
the
the safe word
is
but lingleberry jam
lingamberry jam
that's it i am i see remember i can you
remember that grandma we just want you
to be safe
all right i can i can remember that
lingenberry jam it's been so long since
i've had lingan berries
all right then well i'll let you know if
i see anything suspicious won't we dear
she says looking behind her at no one
well
she waddles off
seems to be talking to someone you can't
see
i'm sure she'll be fine right
she's talking
granny sees stuff that we're not seeing
she's like a cat we should keep her
around
should we may follow her you should get
one of those kid harnesses and strap her
to someone
someone's strong like tiara
can we do a little perception check sure
everyone go ahead and do your right
perception oh yeah all right as you
arrive on this new scene
what was it again the combination the
magical clowns with plus composure
i'm sorry
what with
here we go again
you've got huh
what's happening no successes uh-oh
oh uh
[Music]
okay i got one
all right everyone finish rolling
yep
please type your successes below how
many you
[Music]
got great
all right so let's see what we have here
watson uh unfortunately there are a lot
of things overwhelming you about the
carnival right now for example the scent
of funnel cakes
and other delicious things
yeah
but then occasionally something foul
will will creep in there like um a
portable toilet so uh yeah it's just a
lot to take in right now
overwhelming cakes
[Laughter]
oh there goes my appetite
all right next up we've got
tiara and scout
the two of you noticed uh that this this
carnival looks really like just a little
pop-up carnival you've seen them
sometimes occasionally um here and there
they just kind of appear and disappear
as quickly as they came but of course it
would make sense for something that's uh
just like someone's uh college project
or like a college-funded thing
um
so is there a lot of people here
there's a decent amount it would mostly
you would say families and a lot of
children um and it looks just like an
overall fun event you aren't getting any
strange vibes right off the bat
um
but as for you uh for you yule you'll be
all right
for you um
while indeed the carnival doesn't give
off any immediately spooky vibes um you
also notice that um
this place is full of many various
attractions attractions that you
wouldn't normally expect to see at a a
pop-up carnival like for example uh
there's a corn maze and there's also a
hall of mirrors you thought those went
out of style a long time ago
and it is also approaching night time
you'll you have noticed that you guys uh
came a bit late so it is sort of turning
into night but night is really when the
carnival pops off apparently that's when
the musical guest is supposed to be
performing
amongst
the families um
you'll you also see some
strange folk interspersed interspersed
they're not really strange it's just
not really quite what you would expect
they
they dress oddly a lot of people aren't
they just aren't wearing shirts
heavily tattooed
sandals
they all seem to be carrying some weird
soda with them
soda yeah
craig what is it called the pain
oh
there it is it's that stragos soda
how odd
uh
can can my
curiosity flaw lead me to trying to
drink the soda well sure
that's all right there we go that'll
that'll get you a beat later um
with your curiosity flaw you just kind
of walk up to one of these dudes uh
tiara
and you just kind of stare at the soda
and this dude looks at you
oddly like what are you looking at but
then actually kind of turns out to be
kind of friendly
this odd dude with spiked hair and he's
got like
some face paint on it's it's a little
odd but he kind of he kind of smiles at
you a toothy smile and says
wanna drink sis
[Music]
yes i mean i'm actually not from here
and i've never seen this soda drink
before but i really do like sodas i'll
go right ahead without it
oh thank you
let me take a sip
you take a sip of this soda
what happens
it's fine it doesn't taste very good
okay i'm not pointy no you're not
poisoned it's just kind of shitty dollar
store soda it's not very good but
it's soda i guess it's got an
interesting flavor
in it
linganberry
oh
come on
oh come on kelly
you little i knew i knew it that the
grandma was off to no good and then we
did we would need to save it or
something like that and now you come
here with me and we bling them very down
no freaking way no
this is how you repay me for thinking
ahead no no no listen it might not
become important
okay you might not be coming for i'm
just messing with you
i'm just messing with you okay well well
thank you for the sip that was actually
okay
oh yes we we just wanted to
check it out i guess it's been a long
time for us to be in a carnival we've
had some rough days so ah nice this i
dig you're here to see mad jester clan
too
who who is that excuse me mad gesture
clan
come on sis surely you've heard
they're performing
today
oh are they worth seeing adam
are they worth seeing
you gotta see for yourself the magic
that will unfold before your eyes he
kind of like starts to walk backwards
does some like spooky finger motions and
laughs and walks away
something is uh yeah he's alive
[Music]
magic miracles sure enough there's a big
old sign
big old sign that announces the main
concert will be done by mad jester clan
oh
yeah interesting
you do see a lot of interesting folk
with uh face paint walking about
could these be their fans
should we put on face paint as well to
blend in or not
oh can we find some i'll get into my
house and you know what that would be if
we could put like something specific on
our each of our face paints then we
would be able to recognize one another
uh
in uh you know when the when the
imposters or so are around that is
because
that is smart
that
can we look for the place that we can
get the face paint at sure you want to
look for a face paint stall no problem
yes
all right to search if anyone wants to
search for a face paint for a face paint
stall it's going to be an investigation
and wits check
who has the most investigation
tell me all of them
you can all if you'd like
someone will find it
investigation
[Music]
and wits sure
okay
oh
[Music]
can i put on the brash candid oops
sorry
oh yeah sure
yes you are now um you are now brash
candicute
i know brush candy coot
right
smell a little bit
[Music]
wait is it is that carnival free did we
pay to get in oh you haven't gotten to
the ticket counter yet good point
you realize that it is only five dollars
for each of you though it's a nice
little low-key carnival and as soon as
you roll up actually you'll you
recognize a familiar face
oh
you'll what is up dude what's
it's been a while
how are you says chad to you
hey uh
chad
oh my god dude you remembered my name
hell yeah
can i get a hell yeah you'll be all
right
oh yeah you
yeah yo what are you guys doing here oh
just checking out the carnival yeah i
thought you were working the thing
could've sworn i saw you the other day
was that mistaken
oh where did you uh see me around
just walking around generally helping
with stuff and selling corn dogs and
stuff like that no no you're doing a
bunch of different stuff i was confused
anyway you guys can come in for free
oh for free oh
yeah but don't look at the box
big old secret just between the one two
three four oh wow
you expanded
very nice oh you have
there's some friends is this your eye
you're a wink
they're my family friends
and
oh i see
yeah not a crew per se all right well
that's fine
well just so you know
me and the bro hood we scoped the place
out and it's totally fine
just have fun
what does that mean ara
what do you mean by fine
like we looked around for like
supernatural activities and [\h__\h] no
vampires no werewolves no man we can't
just be talking about this in broad
daylight though just go have a good time
everything's fine here this is about you
guys having fun right
we'll get up thanks for uh letting us in
well
we'll check it out thanks thanks hit me
up later you'll i got a party happening
next weekend and do some keg stands
together i know you have the potential
in you
talk later yeah but for sure yeah got my
nose
back
yeah
chad goes back to work
you you do hang with some really weird
people adam
i don't choose it
they just kind of show up but let's see
yeah you guys finally enter into the
carnival and has everyone rolled to
search for a face painting stall
yeah please type your successes
everyone who ruled
okay okay so both wattato and ciara um
actually do manage to make a bit of
progress um it's not too hard to figure
out where the face painting stall is
because there are quite a few uh folks
on the way there
however um in your search because it was
a bit slow it looks like there's kind of
a line
i might have to wait a bit in fact until
it gets dark likely
yeah well it's not too long it's about
30 minutes to an hour
okay
uh girls get in line
man this sand here
our feature is
oh wait are we in the sand never mind oh
yeah there's sand the carnival is on
they say wow this is sand it must be low
tide it sure is starting to fall
for face painting maybe
oh
or not a sand mask
[Music]
i think we might need a wig color then
yeah i feel like they'll come off easily
adam
that'll be okay yeah you guys can wait
until night that's no problem
just me when is that when is the concert
is happening oh concert's not happening
until night for sure okay good we got
time yeah you guys got some time for
sure
so you guys wait until it's about night
time
and then the fairgrounds have gotten
really dark
[Music]
there's a bit of an eerie glow to them
got roller coasters and all kinds of fun
looking stuff around nice
some wild rides so to speak
yeah once it reaches night time all of
you are able to get yourself some face
paint
and everyone looks a little different um
how about you
tiara what kind of face paint do you
have to distinguish yourself from the
others you can make any request
uh
i will make myself look like my owl
hoodle
who plays too much tails of her eyes oh
my god
yeah not hula ooh
yes i have an owl now
heck yeah all right so you have some ooh
face paint popping off how about you
yule
um
i got the joker
[Laughter]
mushroom on the forehead
little mushroom mark very nice and of
course scout although you are brash
candicute you still may get some face
paint if you like
i'll put it on brush candy coo oh okay
perfect give him some
some cute blushies on his face all right
nice idea
and there we go give them some blushies
now we have brush candy cream with blush
marks
in fact all the little kitties love to
come run up to you and grab onto your
leg until they get a nice whiff of your
fur
and then they saunter away
uh actually it's a it's a bandicoot
it's a what it's a bandicoot i think
it's an australian creature
like uh like yara it's real mm-hmm yeah
it's real it's a real animal you can
look it up
bandicoot
it's like a mouse yeah
yeah it doesn't really look uh like
crash but
oh sorry crash fans don't come after me
i didn't know i thought it was a fox or
something
you got the long nose it's cute you got
the long nose
so it works
yeah marsupial
that's right and good old crash i mean
brash
smelling good smelling fine
and um
with that being said uh you guys are
standing here in the middle of the
fairground now with face paint on you
what do you choose to do
reception chair
sure if you'd like let's go
[Music]
oh for once
oh no you will
you will see nothing you'll see
it's that's the it's the face thing is
running into my heart it's getting into
your eyes
it's burning it burns mega
now please type your successes ladies
all right here's what we've got
here's what we've got you'll
unfortunately for you uh you used all of
your good perception to check out the
outside of the carnival so you got the
basic idea of it but the inside is a
little more crazy nuts though the lights
are flashy they distract you they make
it hard for you to focus
um as for scout and watsuto looking
around this place you see all kinds of
really um
sort of unfamiliar um crazy sites
uh like for example
neither of you have really been
on like a big roller coaster before yeah
um i've been on a big one oh okay well
this is this is a really futuristic
looking one
this is not a wooden one scout
one
oh what do you mean actually no scout's
never been on one oh my god
yeah well this is a pretty they have a
pretty big one and they have a huge
ferris wheel
huge ferris wheel very big oh
yeah and also a large concert venue as
well but you can't see any more details
beyond that lots of fun rides though and
also the scent is amazing
you've got funnel cakes and
corn dogs and all kinds of tasty fried
foods and there's a corn maze too scout
you're familiar with this
you have been in a corn maze before
of course i've been in a corn maze i was
practically born in a corn maze yeah i
don't know where i come from we call it
maize yeah that's the corn meat it's a
maze
oh it's the best maze amazing corn i
love corn eat your way out
so is your bird i bet
that sounds good
nice fun maze and what do i see
let's see so for you tiara um you also
see all these magnificent sights as well
and you see that it's gotten to be
really quite dark outside but thankfully
no concert has begun however it does
seem that it will start in about
15 to 20 minutes
oh
rather soon and it's very easy to see
who is gathering and who is there for
the magister clan
lots of other
face painted individuals
with tattoos
they look like their taste in music is
interesting
not good not bad interesting check out
the
concert
girls or
are you not interested looks like it's
happening in about 15 minutes i don't
know what to rock
oh
we should check it out i have a feeling
god wants us to check it out
if you want
it it's your world ladies
oh we are going in
okay
could be a trap but not all of us have
to go though i guess
if someone else wants to go somewhere
else
up to you guys we can all go but can i
stand
back
okay never split i agree maybe we
shouldn't split actually
i wish
callie needed this to be
a bit shorter
let's keep it together
okay okay oh no problem
we i guess we'll stand in line uh trying
to get in yeah well the crowd's already
pretty big but even as you guys enter
the so-called quote-unquote venue it
still seems that folks are coming in
slowly but surely filling the area even
behind you die hard fans standing behind
you which is you know not the best
position to be in but
at least they aren't being too rude now
the front that's where you don't want to
be
ever
i'll notice one thing though i'm leaving
my bird outside to keep watch
all right sounds good ooh hoo we'll stay
uh out in the back
yes
all right and we've made our way over to
the concert hall which looks exactly
like this
nice little
roof over it um to protect from any rain
that might occur
and the
the guests are waiting anxiously to have
themselves a good time with their
favorite group
now
as you guys um
are sort of kind of waiting you see that
there are a lot of folks drinking this
familiar soda but they don't seem to be
you know changing their behavior it's
just a soda they like that's all
i see eventually
[Music]
it's hypnotizing potion
hypnotizing punch yeah something's wrong
with it for sure you drank it dummy oh
you said i'll sit i'm curious i can't
help it
so
here's what occurs
eventually the emcee enters the stage
and begins speaking to you all
thank you all for coming too
does that look like one of us perhaps
oh
i don't know they are wearing too much
face paint
in fact they're wearing a clown mask
well the voice does sound a little
familiar
oh huh
it does sound a bit familiar
ever so slightly
oh
oh this this is definitely vic
i'm wearing this
all of you know him by now
he he starts speaking to you all
welcome to this year's installment okay
i feel a little bit safe right now maybe
the beach carnival
or is it really big aka
glitter beach
oh no
welcome why are you speaking to us kelly
i don't hear you huh oh
when i turn on the effects i'm trying to
use my megaphone
oh why isn't it working
oh i'm hurting her yeah i gotcha hello
can you hear me
ah
what a shame then i'll just here we go
hello one and all welcome to
this year's installment of beach
carnival
glitter beach
glitter beach this year's carnival is as
always organized by uh he holds up his
his hand to read off the palm of his
hand the smudged handwriting that was on
there
uh mython
something something university for the
special
uh gifted
good at stuff technology people
i have a friend who goes there
i don't know the sharpie is smudged i
can't read it anyway
that that's not over that's not what
we're here for no one cares i see as you
all are getting a little angry in the
front calm down we're about to start
boom all right that's not me that's the
audience
oh okay look hey don't don't shoot the
messenger i'm just here to introduce the
ben
the tonight's eggs is the one the only
mad jester clan featuring the esteemed
scooby three super lit and pacifist k
welcoming you to uh to today's uh grand
festivities
of madness and wicked trickery
um
welcome
i'm gonna leave now i'm gonna i'm gonna
give it to scooby
and uh he walks off the stage and
suddenly make a perception check
he does a lot of weird stuff
could be the extra cash so this is a
volunteered event you'll have to ask him
later hey
alrighty
now let me see those successes
all right
okay watson so everything is really
overwhelming right now especially
this area
just just having a good time
too short to see anything this can be
said about any concert but you do wish
sometimes people would shower
like it's not that hard at least wear a
little deodorant every once in a while
it'd be nice to watch the essential
areas but it is what it is it's a
concert it happens
next up we've got
scout
um
you immediately sense a change in energy
here as soon as those two make their way
onto the stage you squint to see them
but they're kind of kind of out of your
vision uh you see though however the
crowd's got a lot of love for them and
before you know it
soda is spraying in the air
oh
god
you get a little get a little sticky
sticky film over the uh
fresh candy coot suit
hey it smells a little better now though
it smells like soda yeah
oh
like six hours yeah
and then as for as for tiara
um these two characters that make their
way onto the stage are
definitely interesting performers um
there's one guy who's um who's
a little more a little more heavy
walks out onto the stage and has clown
makeup on
some spiky hair
the other one's a bit more lean but same
clown makeup and they seem to really
resonate with the audience
and are very excited about getting down
today
with the audience
in fact they have their own soda
they're beginning to spray on the
audience but thankfully thankfully you
guys are enough in the back that only
the audience's soda spray gets on you
good good good yeah
and as for you uh yule
you immediately notice that these
interesting characters um
these these interesting characters we
have here today um
there's something intriguing about their
motion the way that they move it's
it's different
it's like this is almost a hip-hop
concert sort of but there's something
odd about it something strange about
their movements like they're dancing in
the rhythm to to some kind of odd
chant or something of the like
it's a cult
and then yeah the people in the crowd
start to move with them vibing
immediately with everything they say and
do
they begin to spit their rhymes
oh no with very inspired lyrics
cali concert let's go
they start they start doing some head
bobs and immediately
immediately
tiara you especially start vibing with
the music
you feel it in your soul
you're into this i wonder why yeah
you're into this you're really getting
down with it you hear their inspired
rhymes they go something like um
yeah get down with the wickedness
uh bow down to the sickness pull down
these trousers see how long this
they want me to get naked
suddenly a a ringtone rings out um and
and scooby three super lit uh answers
the phone
yeah
oh
it's time
all right all right all right gotcha
gotcha it's time
all right hangs up the phone
hey everybody everybody out there
everybody who's got love for mad jester
clan we're gonna need you to chant
together
with us right now as we summon
the one
the only
what's the word again in in in fullable
don't ask me
okay okay got it got it the
sorry the infallible
baba ginthalamush
the devourer of dimensions
everyone in time with me
they start doing a chant that you've
never heard before from another universe
even everybody seems so into it
you as well tiara you feel a strange
tingling to this
[Laughter]
yeah i see people's lips moving but i
can't hear anything all i hear is noise
white noise
they seem
my heart of hearing on top of the
muffled sound from this fox uh bandicoot
candy cute head sure is making it hard
to hear other than
bass
you hear them repeat over and over and
over again
bobbin bob and gathalamush why why is
the name so long bobbing a thalamus come
down to us
a miracle so mysterious
bobbingthalamush
over and over again it turns into a song
um but there's definitely something
alien and weird about it
hey
and suddenly that's what concerts are
really like
is this your first concert yo
[Music]
uh
wait hold on so i have the ignorant flaw
right would that work as not being not
being knowledgeable about what concerts
are like um yes so what do you do as a
result of not really knowing what's up
with concerts
do you move a certain way
i i
i try to
join in with the dance but my but yes
moves they're not very uh on point
oh i see i see
gotcha when you do this yule one of the
other members who's really getting down
with the chant looks over you and says
hey
hey man what you doing come on it's like
this it's like this and tries to teach
you the steps to the dance which tiara
is doing flawlessly
i hate this much
yeah it's like a little four square
thing and then like um some arm
movements back and forth back and forth
back and forth
um
but you can't really grasp it yule you
just don't know what concerts are like
unfortunately
and suddenly
lightning cracks through the sky
and actually strikes down right before
you
you oh
as if you've angered some deity of some
sort
and suddenly
the sky is now completely black
it's just night time
everyone looks pretty confused
they are also not sure why this has
happened and um the two mcs at the front
also look a bit bewildered
looking about i can't hear or see
anything
all right all right everyone just just
calm down just calm down
they try to calm down the crowd but even
the crowd is bewildered you can hear
some people asking where is
bob and the thalamus
where is the great deity
nowhere to be seen
and suddenly
the sky becomes a deep
dark blue color and you hear a cracking
noise as the earth begins to shake
a mighty rumble breaks out across the
fairgrounds as it seems
that the beach is trembling so hard it
might just detach itself from where it
sits um
[Music]
is getting into it but the chanting is
stopped
oh
you can continue
keep it up
at this point
um
the fairgrounds have turned into
a strange
odd place because not only is the sky
black but a lot of the rides have taken
on a strange neon quality and it looks
as though eyes have appeared on for
example the merry-go-round
oh
are they watching us
you know if you look close enough
you might just see
you are indeed being watched by
something
something is watching you all illuminati
but what it is you couldn't be sure
at this point the crowd kind of begins
to disperse and see what's going on
because the rides themselves have also
changed
these look strange they're lit up in an
odd way
the lights they flicker and
turn a bright neon that you've never
seen before a neon color that your eyes
would not previously be able to register
but here we are and a strange
stifling air begins to flow through the
area
it's
stuffy here
almost as though there's a powerful
ghostly energy around you
[Music]
what do you guys choose to do is things
are starting to get
strange around here
maybe we should group up
yeah
huddle
cuddle
should we try and find a way into the
the back of the stage like is that where
or
is because i don't really know where
else
sure you want to go to the back of the
stage
yeah is that where stuff could be
happening because if everything else is
just general carnival non-sensory then
yeah if you want sure whatever you want
to
do
what about you tiara
i'll i'll follow you scout
and follow your lead
all right follow the big fuzzy orange
thing we're going to the back we're
going to try and find a way in the back
see what's going on
oh right
so
you guys follow the lead of brash
candicu walking through this
strange altered carnival
where everything seems a bit off and
demonic and strange people are starting
to panic a bit by now as well but at
least that leaves room for you guys to
walk through the crowd that is slowly
dispersing
it appears that the two front men of mad
jester clan have disappeared they are no
longer there on the stage but they could
be backstage
you guys kind of work your way around
and it's easy enough to get back there
because even security has dispersed at
this point in time
now you guys get backstage and what you
see is
some general normal stuff lots of wires
sound equipment etc but what's most
interesting about this area is
it looks as though
it's on the edge
of something
the edge of this carnival
is no longer just an ocean
road perception
yes
ma'am should i be scared
perception oh come on i have succeeded
holy [\h__\h] once again
but don't worry today is not not gonna
be i think the next next next uh stream
is gonna be more important
i feel it
well i see everything
yeah yeah
i mean
i i misrolled the second one
[Music]
no no no wait why is it no no oh you got
to do the 1d10
oh i missed typed that's okay there you
go i mean yeah that's three successes so
please type your successes ladies
all right so
for tiara you notice immediately that
the outside edge of this carnival is
water
makes sense
this is a beach right
should be water but this water is
different it doesn't have that same
salty smell no instead there's something
musky and off about it
oh
and then you'll you see it
you realize
that you guys
you can't be anywhere
anywhere on this actual planet earth
because surrounding you are many many
rivers
in between those rivers
an innumerable amount of rivers they all
seem to be leading somewhere that you
can't see
and in between these rivers are
lifeless mounds of white
indiscernible
river after river after river
abounding endlessly into forever
and it appears that this carnival is
moving down one of those rivers
okay we're moving
indeed you're floating so to speak
down a river
what about all the other
people who were at the concert
well they've also figured this out um
and some people have begun trying to
swim in the river you can see them hop
into the water and immediately get swept
away into nothingness
oh [\h__\h] why would they do that
perhaps in an attempt to escape you
would assume but other than that who
could say maybe they could be
influenced by something
who knows thankfully though the drink
doesn't seem to have done anything by
way of making you want to jump into
these rivers but they are sweeping folks
away and now the sky has begun to
pulsate with a dull blue light
[Music]
and the winds are getting stronger
winds that carry something that sounds
like
voices on the wind
something ghosts okay so i pull out my
revolver and i shoot the sky
all right you pull out your revolver you
shoot this guy
this causes many people to run around
and be extremely scared
about 20 people jump into the water
after they hear your revolver go off
and then about five other people who
look to be big fans of the mad jester
clan pull out pocket knives
no no hey this was a joke i didn't even
roll for it
you can't just stay into it though i
didn't even throw you then you normally
you would let me
you would roll if you're aiming at
someone you can just shoot
i need to aim at the sky if maybe i
could accidentally shoot i don't know
someone's just the ground
not generally
in the party
it's okay they don't approach you at the
pocket knives they just take them out
okay
and they're running free now well at
least now we know who to fight
i mean possibly
they they could just be you know
chilling maybe they just trying to
defend themselves you could say
they too are just civilians but
yeah
the families too are especially afraid
and no children have attempted to jump
into the rivers so you do have a lot of
kids just kind of standing
there not knowing where their parents
have gone
no
so what will you do now at this point in
time
will
set up a search and rescue
okay
sounds good who are you trying to search
for and rescue
all the kids
all right a kitty roundup
sounds good how do you intend to do that
do you have something to lure the
children
i use now
[Laughter]
i use a brush
brush candy coot
yeah
all right
hey scout
how does that sound
sure what do i have to do
oh i thought i'll need you to dance and
i learned a bit
and what and where
where am i
to our same spot i guess all right
first let's search for a safe spot water
i'll need you to enroll your
investigation in wits to scout out a
safe spot
go water
let's see let's see
mission safe to children yeah
go
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
yeah so you scout out a nice little area
in what appears to be
something like a chicken coop
oh full of chickens
but it seems to be a safe enough spot
yeah and um there's plenty of hay for
the children to rest so this place
should work well enough it doesn't smell
too foul thankfully
oh yeah it'll cover up the stench of
meat yeah exactly
nothing by ksb now brash i need you to
dance
please roll
presents and expression
can i dance with
sure go for it you'll absolutely
in a dancing mood after the concert you
owe me for this one
you roll the other ten wait what's the
what's the real
uh it's gonna be your presence plus
expression
yes expression
oh do i roll that 10 yes ma'am
we roll that 10.
oh oh
well scout at least you bust a move
[Music]
yeah
break dance no no no no no we line dance
around the head
that's my kitties follow the bounce oh
the bouncing
fox friend
do you know what a bandicoot is kidding
all right you dance around and yule is
trailing behind but
you'll just kind of
it looks odd it's cute though in a sense
anyway children do kind of look even
though they're worried about their
parents they do seem
attracted to your dancing your dancing
for advertised yeah
almost so a couple of them run over to
see what's going on and they seem
excited about you so
you are generally able to lead them over
to the coop whether they stay um or not
is one thing but you do manage to
collect about 15 lost children not bad
awesome nice job you guys
you could zip tie them into the kitchen
this can be a it's like a triage center
you know like uh if somebody gets hurt
they go to there yeah that's a good idea
so that has now become
that safe spot for you all
nice
now
next up
you see
as you are finishing to finishing
rounding up these these little ones
um you see approaching you in the
distance um a figure who looks as though
she's lost her way
grandma
granny
i was about to ask
there you are i was so confused you said
the safe word was lingenberry and so
when those when those face painting face
paint those face painted uh
silly uh pieros started talking about
lingonberry i thought for sure you had
transformed my dears
but that's fine
i did see someone who looked like you
all though
each one of you uh interspersed
throughout the crowd it was most strange
but they didn't know the safe word
okay that's good where were they what
were they doing grandma
well let's see last i saw them they
disappeared into that hall of mirrors i
assumed that you all were going to have
some fun in the hall of mirrors
hall of mirrors so
that sounds um interesting yes i'd
recommend you not go in there seems very
spooky especially considering the
situation that we found ourselves in
hmm
um
grandma are you sure you still
feel safe here anyway
maybe you want to go into the chicken
coop with the children because it's
really not looking safe by any
uh in any case don't touch the water
that's important grandma you understand
that yes and definitely don't drink it
that will be a big problem for you um
well the reason you know you're the real
grandma
well it listen i really don't feel
unsafe in fact my husband and i were
just enjoying a stroll that was how i
knew that we had passed to somewhere
else when i saw my dear husband
hmm
oh you haven't worked with your husband
when we came here of course i was he's
always on my shoulder right behind me oh
okay oh yeah right he is there yeah
indeed but now he has materialized
completely last i saw him he was at the
shooting range but he he may have
he may have gone off somewhere else i
need to go find him
anyway dears there's uh something
strange about this place if you haven't
noticed we've transcended
we are somewhere else entirely now yes
well if i can see my dear
then we are definitely not where we
usually are
she's so chill about it
yes i have experience not your first
time seeing a place like this anna oh no
no in fact i've been here before
oh
is there a way yeah
um hmm well usually
this kind of place well we are going
down the river
um we absolutely should not reach the
ocean of fragments
when we reach the ocean of fragments
everything here will effectively sink
and disappear uh into nothingness as
though it never existed so it might be a
good idea to turn around how to do that
though well i'm not entirely sure that
much i don't know so i figured for now
i'll go enjoy some games
no wait how did you do it last time anna
well i certainly wasn't on a floating
stray carnival that's for sure was much
easier then
all right then have fun finding your
husband anna
all right you guys have fun
try to pay attention to any clues that
may help you figure out how to change
everything here back to normal i don't
really quite know though sorry but i'll
be happy to help if you need me
thank you yay carnegie games and she
walks off
oh oh can i ask you a question sure
are we still standing in the sand
yes
the sand is broken free but you guys are
moving down there can i pick up some
seashells sure
okay
plus
five seashells okay
yeah it'll probably take you about 15
minutes
yeah there you go you got five seashells
thank you okay all right
now what do you guys choose to do from
here
you have several options you could
investigate you could ride while this is
happening the
the people are still uh operating the
like stalls and all that
well the funny thing is the rides seem
to be operational no one's operating
them though
oh golly
no
i think we should investigate
yes
because granny said
we have a time limit we don't want to
reach that whatever ocean
well okay then let's do um i'll go i'll
go to the merry-go-round and do a
perception check there because i'm sure
there's a merry-go-round i see it yes
indeed the one with the eyes on it the
strange demonic one
indeed all right go ahead rule that
perception
okay
okay i got one
okay with one success
you approach the merry-go-round and see
that there are plenty of blinking eyes
on this strange merry-go-round and it
seems to turn faster and faster and
faster and doesn't stop
interestingly enough there are still
people riding on this on this wild ride
except they seem to be enjoying it they
don't necessarily seem to be
in pain or anything like that in fact
they seem to be chanting something or
rambling on about something over and
over again
i would like to shoot
the eyes
on the america rent sure it's kind of a
nice idea that's what i was gonna say
all right
go for it roll to shoot
with your dexterity
dexterity firearms okay
one two three four five six
uh seven eight okay
that is a really good roll
okay okay
all right
very nice so with four
successes with four successes you
managed to shoot out one of the eyes
that starts blinking rapidly
rapidly and furiously uh confused as to
who could possibly be
shooting at it at this point in time
um
and
soon enough it begins to swell up and it
explodes
and as it explodes
the merry-go-round seems to speed up
faster and faster
faster and then suddenly
screeches to a halt
and then begins spinning in the opposite
direction
oh wait does that
and all of the eyes close and the people
riding on the ride
fall off the horses unconscious
well i
mean at least they stopped chanting i
suppose true
yeah you couldn't quite hear what they
were saying though
are there still like i are your eyes
open still so they all look to be
completely unconscious but you can try
and wake someone up if you want up to
you no no no
no okay um
so can i do a perception check if like
for the i don't know
generally generally sure
any of you guys can roll perception to
investigate whatever you'd like
can i ask another question certainly
we're still holding on to the items we
had on our persons last time right
unless we stayed otherwise indeed
awesome yep you still have them
okay i got one perception check
all right
with one perception check let's see what
you got here
with your one perception um
and just observing the general area you
see that um
oh there we go
she sees it all
you're seeing
that's okay i will i will let you know
ciara that you do notice that there are
a lot of other um
rides around the carnival that are
similar to this
a little
erratic a little strange going a little
nutso almost as if possessed by a ghost
let's see
next we've got
thanks
i swear seattle is going to get really
good luck somewhere else though
hopefully i think so
this always happens all right if you
guys want to type your successes let's
go
all right i have to reroll too hold on
okay
all right so we've got four successes
for watching though
okay
so you'll you basically see the same
thing as tiara actually there are
various places not just this
merry-go-round um
various other erratic coasters etc and
areas um
and as for you um watson you're able to
discern exactly what kind of places you
have here
first of all
you have a castle
a ferris wheel oh
the high swing sets
oh and you have
death sensei's wild ride
as well as various food stalls
and the shooting gallery
shooting gallery
i'm going to the shooting gallery
all right it's still there and the corn
maze of course can't forget the corn
maze and hall of mirrors
these are the places
too
well i thought i'll see the castle maybe
we should head there after the shooting
range
yeah i want to see if they maybe if
there's something
to win or something special to get yeah
all right sounds good
so we're gonna have you go ahead and
head on over to the shooting range first
yes yes yes all right
let's head on over then
to the shooting gallery
the spooky fairgrounds
scout can shoot too if the slingshot or
maybe i mean that's maybe there's a guns
there anyway
perhaps
you guys roll up to the shooting gallery
and um at first
uh you guys notice i'll go ahead and
kind of
actually i'll let you guys roll
perception again don't want to rule it
too many times but this is a completely
new area or at least it has changed
quite a bit
so you could get some good information
from here i see nothing
oh
all right
i'm distracted
right
everyone's distracted
eagle eyes
literally came back from that
zoom
all right everyone type your successes
please
here's what we got here both tiara and
watato um you guys are a little
overwhelmed and also excited hyped up
for the shooting gallery in a sense yeah
um as for scout as soon as you approach
this place you what you notice
immediately that is strange um are the
prizes are weird the stuff you can win
here is
odd
in fact kind of odd
what you notice immediately is that
there are weird plush dolls of
you guys
yeah
it's weird they definitely exact copies
of you guys in fact you're even wearing
the brash candy coot suit
oh no
with the face paint
yes with the face paint oh
small they're small and cute it's almost
as though an imprint of your soul has
been copied in some way onto these these
beings that's the sense you get i don't
know if it's turned on though
but they do emit a weird aura and you
can confirm this yule because it almost
feels like looking directly at yourself
when you look at this doll that looks
like you
you can feel it calling out to you in
some sense can i try to win it
you certainly can
um if you'd like however what you also
notice is that um
there is
someone
quote unquote running the stall
a dull blue figure
of someone in a hood
that you cannot see
they wordlessly
they wordlessly put
a sort of demented looking nerf gun on
to the counter
it's not that kid is it
it's not the kid actually this is pretty
pretty
dude
something kind of ghostly about him
he's wearing stilts
i know
do we have to use a nerf gun you do
all right
might as well give it i can try
i can still use my firearms dots right
indeed
but you know you want to go first you
will
face
what what should i roll
you're going to need to roll your
firearms and dexterity but before you do
so the hooded figure stops you with an
almost skeletal looking ghostly hand
oh
and then you realize suddenly
there are no real targets here no no
instead this ghostly being points
at your doll
oh no
and suddenly you kind of figure out what
you're supposed to do here
is
[Music]
once you get damaged from that probably
yourself
well i don't know
gotta try guys let's try right sure you
can certainly give it a try
don't die
all right who's the tank here who's the
tallest
who is the tallest
oh no
scout tiara yeah
well
i guess i'll take aim for my doll and
try to shoot the nerf gun all right
here we go
i don't know
all right
that's a really good shot
that's a good shot
all right let me look at this gun that
you're using here
okay
you take a shot at the doll
and that's a that's a good hit
you hit it squarely
squarely uh in the middle of the
forehead and suddenly a shock goes
through you you'll
as you feel your forehead cry out in
pain
you jolt backwards
and you have the worst headache you've
ever felt but interestingly enough
interestingly enough you are actually
bleeding
from your forehead
and you have a cripplingly bad headache
so
from this you take
two lethal damage
however the hooded figure
grabs your doll and hands it to
you feel a sense of congratulations
admitting at least no one else can hurt
you for that doll now adam
hello
i'm alive
you are alive
what does it mean though
wait what is it no
what a good can't try tickling the doll
you tickle the dog
and you feel a tickling sensation inside
it
well
i have a feeling we should probably uh
grab the other ones but probably not
shoot it
and create a version and take those they
seem
it seems like whatever happens to the
doll happens to us
indeed we shouldn't let them hear
yeah all right then who's next i've got
an idea
well i left i loved uh outside so who
should be somewhere here right
right
right technically
i have a physical larceny skill with
pickpocket uh like specialization i
could try to take them
okay sure you can certainly give that a
try but in in terms of where your owl is
um ooh is unfortunately not anywhere to
be seen
is it dead
you don't think it might have just not
made it to the uh
when we ported or something
[Music]
could be somewhere here
not here now
a pocket toto let's go
[Music]
should we maybe create a version or
something oh yeah i don't know
um
you can start a fire
starter yeah
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way
well we could light the doll on fire
ian's dog
she's gonna burn a life
what else are we gonna burn
i have
matches
oh uh we could get some hay and um
put it next to the stall
and uh
burn it
yeah yeah light up a hay bale would you
like to do that
okay
probably not me because i guess i'll be
the one
deceiving ah yes
uh i seem to be highly flammable i'm
also not sure that's a very good idea
ah lots of polyester
i mean i still could
i'll screw it i'll go do it all right
where's the hay bales at let me add them
you recall some hay bales that uh the
chicken coop where the kitties are
hanging out
all right um my morality will drop by
how much
oh are you stealing the the hay from the
children how much are you stealing
because they have plenty i was just
gonna light the whole thing up i don't
know
oh with the children inside all right um
i'm just kidding i don't think
there's gotta be hay around that didn't
work when i shot the sky
the kidding didn't work
not saying that because we should
actually
no i'm not i'm not saying that we
shouldn't should really burn up the coop
but i'm just saying that it didn't count
last time when i said i was getting
that's the saying yes that's true
gura but no don't do it don't do it
shoot me this guy is very different than
setting a chicken coop full of children
on fire
20 people 20 people died because of my
act and
it was pretty bad as well i don't know
if they died
they just got spooked they're probably
going to jump in anyway
okay i'm dragging a hail hay bale over i
don't really like the children on fire
you drag a hay bale over and some of the
children follow you out hey brad no no
no no no no no where are you going
if you follow me i'll eat you and you'll
never see your mommies or daddies again
they run back to the coop
all right okay
you get that hay bale over there uh by
the shooting gallery
and i'm just kind of set it down yeah
where'd you put it i'm gonna ah put it
right where toto said to put it
all right
and i'm waiting for the the cue toto
okay uh
now uh what should i roll for a thief
like uh all right you're gonna need to
roll a larceny roll larceny plus
dexterity or i'll allow you to use wits
as well
whichever one you want you have to
choose wits or dexterity plus larceny
okay
oh something
nice very nice oh yes
that is a really good success that you
got there
all right
um
now to light not to to commit the fire
to commit fire you know how to light a
fire right that's a basic action i would
say um
however you want to do it um in such a
way
that it doesn't uh catch other buildings
on fire yet or do you not care
uh
i don't care
cool
just make a big old bonfire in the
middle of the um in the middle of the
carnival you betcha
all right so you just throw the match
yes out
i can all right
however you want to approach it you just
throw a match uh
well we'll put the hay bell next to the
shooting gallery so that you know the
obviously the person got distracted and
right yeah the distraction is key here
yes
all right
so scout you throw this dancing oh
nevermind okay
you can dance as well
all right
uh you you throw that match and suddenly
the hay bale is blazing on fire
and um
and immediately the shooting gallery
post
is um
distracted by that fire and um and takes
a little peek a little look-see kind of
goes around the back
a scout you want to get out of there uh
real quick roll in athletics and
dexterity to get away
all right brush can a boot let's go
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay wait wait one more time
it's gonna be dexterity plus athletics
all right
oh dear lord okay
baby run run run run run
or roll the suit no less
yes
scout you trip and you fall on your face
right where the fire is
huh
wait into the fire oh no no no right
where the fire occurred right where the
the arsonist would be
oh okay and this ghostly figure kind of
walks up to you
with you face down on the ground and
stares down at you
reaches out a ghostly hand
touches your fur
and pets you
pets
and suddenly you feel a piece of your
soul being drained away
oh [\h__\h]
well would you look at the time
oh
kind of feels pleasant
and to be honest
[Music]
what can i do in this situation
while they're eating a piece of your
soul uh it's not necessarily unpleasant
however
they aren't being forceful with you
they're just very gently caressing your
soul and taking a piece of it
is
you want to throw a match on the ghost
is he flammable
um
you can try
can he take damage
can can the ghost take damage
yeah
you don't know
i don't know that's right i don't know
if he can take damage
however the way that this being is
touching you you really can't even
entirely feel the hand so you assume
they might be a little transparent
but i probably can't grab you either
yeah exactly being very not forceful
just gently taking a piece of your soul
just a little bit okay can i just can i
get up and walk away then
sure
[Laughter]
ditch all the violent options be nice
you do stand up and walk away you do
feel that about three years of your life
have been taken away oh no
that's that's fine which is unfortunate
but it's nothing
yeah that's nothing do i need to roll
anything are we good
um if you really want to shake the dude
you're gonna need your athletics and
dexterity
okay i'm gonna roll and see if i can get
a
a dodge roll
does this mean that scout is now three
years older
nope just me
that scout will likely perish three
years before intended i was dead it
would be fun to like say okay she's
legal now so she can drink alcohol or
something like that
oh no
okay so i don't get that i don't get a
fast getaway can i still get up and walk
away yeah sure i'm
sure you can keep walking away but my
dude will continue following you
all right
however off i go this is good news for
watson though because scout
uh you have dragged away
you have dragged away the owner of the
stall entirely and now watato with that
good roll is capable of taking
everything in the stall
nice yeah
so it did work out
nice nice all right so now we can
protect ourselves hopefully a little bit
better indeed interestingly enough so
you also had time um
thanks to scout's little distraction as
well uh you also had time to grab a doll
that looks like grandma
oh no
don't turn it
indeed i kept it okay
oh no i just realized i rolled wrong
oh anyway
oh yeah
did you roll two less or too too much
unless it's fine though i got away okay
but
we're good no worries no worries you do
have a stalker now though
chilling out watching from afar
that's fine getting excited about taking
more of your life if possible he doesn't
he doesn't know what i look like inside
the suit so we're good that is true
that is a good point you do have a save
there
he's in love with the the band of pood
that's right alexa smell
yeah
now interestingly enough something that
you had noticed ever since
um
yule shot herself there in the shooting
gallery is that the shooting gallery's
lustre was beginning to fade the
demonicness about it was slowly
beginning to
diminish
intriguingly enough
oh now it's definitely gone though it's
burned to a crisp so that's fun
does this mean we have to clear all of
these little things and then we cool
maybe you don't know though
i'm just thinking to myself yeah
all right girls where you want to go
next
where are we gonna go to the castle
head off to the castle the spooky
mysterious castle in the distance
here we go
this is the grand castle
is that a disney castle no
no no it's not there
isn't it
no this is not a disney castle
oh
i mean i've seen classes like that
somewhere else before i guess yeah yeah
yeah any theme park
right
with castle there's only one
yeah
it's not as it's not big enough and
grand enough to be a disney castle
looks like it's christmas season again
well
yeah
yeah it's a million percent not disney
though we i don't know that company i've
never heard of it before in my life
excuse me oh you guys are right you guys
roll up you guys roll up at this
mysterious
um
that seems to be glowing in blue
spiritual light and as you approach it
you can see that there are actually
quite a few
beings that seem to be like spirits
around here but they're more like balls
of energy
light blue and glowing
i should have built a
ghost vacuum
are you going to call it
luigi breakers oh that's luigi's fine
too
oh
should we roll perception certainly yeah
can we yeah if you would like sure
go for it
oh
yeah yeah
i was too distracted by the fact that it
looked
similar
oh
yeah i guess so and point you think of
yourself like what less could i have
been here before
so are we doing perception check yep
okay on this here castle
oh no
no worries please type your successes
ladies
uh well then i lost my cursor that's
okay
oh nice one's good
hey yo
all right here's what we've got here so
both tiara and yule you guys can't help
but feel like
like you've been
here before
this this place
this place that
you've never seen before
it looks like
it it it looks like it could be a
castle that you've never seen before but
it feels like a place maybe you saw
before we're gonna give you just the tip
just the thing
somewhere you can find a door to
darkness of course yeah
of course
it's fine you can use the blue function
and use the blur function
um
goddamn free images
just just the tip
of this this place um that you're so
distracted by this fact that that's how
your mind wanders in that sort of
rambling way that i just did
in some place maybe i've seen but i'm
not sure
you kind of don't really perceive
that much
however
however um
for you watato
you've never been to any freaky castle
so you don't have these thoughts
they don't even cross your mind
what's it so instead you're focused on
kind of what kind of place this is it
seems to be kind of small it's not that
grand and big it's not as grand and big
as it looks from far away
interestingly enough
it looks in fact as though it might even
be
the size of like
a decently large inn i mean that's what
these castles have anyway in the right
places to stay and whatever kind of
weird that it would be in this carnival
except
this is when you realize something scout
you didn't see a castle that looked like
this
uh when you came here
first time approaching the beach
carnival
no
the one that you guys saw when you
entered was different it was more like a
haunted house like little place this one
has become a bit bigger and spookier and
full of blue lights and it looks almost
as though exclusively ghostly figures
roam this area
that's the vibe that you get from this
place scout and you also realize that
there are a couple entrances and neither
of them seem to be guarded by anything
okay oh
right
i don't know how that's going to help
but
i mean okay you have entrances now
we have
right
all right all right yeah okay
well i guess we're going in then if
nobody has any
uh uh
doesn't want to guys
we can grapple up the side of it i've
got a rope
if somebody can lend me a hook or
something
the entrances might be a bit too uh
obvious
[Music]
i can go in the front door
or uh
i don't know the word the you know going
up the side of the building or we can
just go through the front door that also
works as well yeah scaling the wall well
i mean
we could scale the wall but we might
fall and die
yeah let's just try the front door front
door
all right you try the front door
let's try it let's head on over to the
front door all right you try to open the
front door and
you open it
and there's nothing in there
like nothing nothing no it's just
blackness
do we shine a flashlight into it sure
you turn on your flashlight
you shine it into the blackness
and see nothing
maybe there's a mirror in here
can i
can i take uh with my phone a picture of
the darkness sometimes don't you see
ghosts and pictures but not um maybe a
flashlight that's a good idea sure
nice idea all right sierra you take a
photo
snap
hold on
you take a photo i'm gonna do a little
sound effect you take a photo
there i don't you guys probably couldn't
hear it but yeah
it's fine
it's fine i imagine it yeah uh chad
could hear it um you take a picture
and
um
you look at the picture and you see that
it's still just a black void but
you do see swirling balls of spiritual
energyphobia
let's go rotating and twisting and
twirling throughout the dark spaces and
it seems that it goes down a long long
way
oh
down to where sorry my cat is making
weird noises cow
oh you can't see you can't see the
bottom if there is one
can't we kind of like
follow does this disappear in the ground
yeah
oh okay it would be like jumping into a
big hole you assume
oh
one of which you can't see the bottom
should we try the back door
the other entrance
sure sure
better than
here so yeah
nothing here so
maybe a different swirly portal at the
other door i don't know um
all right
so you go to check out the other door
open it up
and a black porter's portal still awaits
you
the void because right
i can jump in first
oh i have a rope
who's the lightest white total remember
that you owe me that i talked about
ah
okay
we had somebody small enough so that we
could tie them to the rope and feed them
to this portal and then hopefully pull
them back up okay i thought it would
feel like a pinata
can we do that sure
whatever you want
go for it all right because clearly this
is where it wants us to go right
maybe it feels like it feels like it
i mean i'm not really sure worlds
okay
all right what's up you have your rope
are you strapped in now
yeah all right who's holding the rope
all the three of us
right excellent you guys can combine
your strength checks
yeah wonderful and want the toes pretty
light so that's the good news
you guys are gonna let watson down now
wattato the good news is uh you don't
have to roll anything here
you're just kind of entering the hole
you gotta hold on to the rope but you're
pretty light anyway so i'm not gonna
make you roll anything
however your friends are going to all
have to roll a strength check let's go
as you are slowly lowered into the void
everyone
roll your strength
don't jump
just strength
[Music]
okay
okay can maduto still hear us if we if
we yell from here interestingly enough
this place is a vacuum
so watson can't hear anything
oh [\h__\h] oh
yeah you can still be here door's open
nope
can we call
you want to use one of your hands to
grab your cell phone
okay
oh you grab your cell phone oh we could
say okay google call
on speakerphone
all right do you guys call wathaso
no
yes all right you call watso watson so
you have to answer your phone uh please
roll your athletics and dexterity for me
oh no to hold the rope and answer your
phone
please don't drop the nokia one second
athletics
ah
nice
one successor
all right
you did it
with one success you barely managed to
hold on to the rope but you do answer
your phone
hello
oh
however this place is a vacuum so no
sound can come out of your mouth
oh
can you hear us
is the snoring or is it just a big hill
wow understandable have a nice day
i think it was a scam call
what's a butt style
perception sure
role perception was so let's see what
you see
down here in this void
oh
all right
one success
with your one success um
you realize you've gotten pretty deep by
now pretty deep into this dark void but
interestingly enough things seem to be
getting lighter
and lighter around you
and lighter
as you realize you're passing through
some kind of odd portal
and suddenly before you know it the rope
it continues along with you but now
gravity is shifting
there's some kind of weird gravitational
shift happening here and suddenly water
so you realize you're sitting in a
window frame
a window frame
of the castle
okay
you look down now yes it does you look
down and you see your friends below
way below
you're at like the top
[Music]
okay they're not in the vacuum it's just
the hole though is the vacuum exactly
gotcha
place where you can look through
it's kind of hard to hear them so i
guess i'll give them a call
you guys connect over cell phone
hello
uh
i think up here
uh it's just a room
i don't know it you guys just jump in
it's fine
it's
okay okay i'll see you soon thanks
we jump in you jump in i don't know
about the others you all want to jump in
i'll jump in you guys all jump
why don't we jump down
everyone jumps in the portal
and because you jump
you're sent flying from the window
one by one everyone flies from the
window past watertow who's sitting in
the frame you guys fall to the ground
everyone takes three bashing damage
but okay
good good good free bashing
three bashing
that's on the left side right indeed we
have the right side
right side
but like in the in the in the square box
right exactly
one two three if you have lethal boxes
uh xed out already go to the next box
and start slashing those
so at this point we have you guys laying
in a pile on the ground outside the
castle that you've now figured out is
some kind of weird portal system
and watso chilling in the in the window
frame from high above i say hi above
it's not that high especially because
you guys only took bashing
um
but it was still a fall
and you guys are sitting on the ground
in a in a lovable pile
and that's where we're going to have to
end for today
okay okay
so you guys can get some sleep
welcome to the circus
[Music]
circus comes
it is progress indeed and i will still
award you guys exp for here i know it's
not the end of a mission but i'm gonna
give it to you at the end of every
session
okay okay
so here's what we got here guys for
experience today otsu by the way otsu
yay
let's start off with watertow
so what's it so let's see what we got
here um
fulfill us we still haven't done
aspirations we're probably not going to
do aspirations until the mid-season
finale once your characters have a more
developed sense of what they want etc
um
next let's see
any time you fail a role you may opt to
make a dramatic failure you did not do
that character takes lethal damage in
one of the rightmost health boxes
sorry i meant left box you guys need to
yeah cross out the bashing from the left
excuse me i messed up i was thinking
about this but it's the other way around
um okay all right you didn't take any
lethal like that end of the game session
okay you get one beat
that's uh did not risk a breaking point
um
however good role playing i'm going to
give you two points because watson did
some great role playing today
oh
yeah
and then good team work yes was it so
you came up with a great plan to both
save the kids and to also uh burn the
shooting gallery
uh and get the dolls so good that's for
so far an action-influenced advice did
not see anything like that unless you
can point something out
uh
no what about your virtue wasato what's
your virtue
um
i forgot because i have it cropped out
on my version oh that's right i remember
that all right that's okay no problem
maybe cat remembers yee
and then you remember your flaw and use
it in session not this time um complete
the mission have not done that yet so
you have four total beats swathito
oh from like uh
i got four new ones yes so four of us so
now you have seven beats total
and with
beads
that equals one point of experience and
then three beats left over so now you
have five total experience points nice
yay
oh next up we've got you'll be all right
you will not all right
all right let's see what we got here so
first of all um let's see
at the end of any game session take a
beat bingo bango bongo there you go um
as for role playing you did have some
good moments i will say i'm gonna give
you a one for this session because you
had good role-playing moments uh next
good teamwork yes i would say that um
you did you did do some good teamwork
and i especially appreciated uh the
effort in dancing along with scout
to get the kids to come to the pikachu
so i will give you um a beat there
uh vice virtue i would say not this time
however you did remember your flaw and
you used it in session
um
which caused the lightning we don't know
if it was your flaw exactly you dancing
out of time with the rest of the group
that caused it to happen we don't know
but
it did it could have caused shenanigans
so you know what you've got four total
beats now
sorry four beats awarded to you so four
plus three is seven beats and then
that's going to turn into one exp for
you with three beats left over so now
your current exp is three
yeah you have three exp points
next up we've got
tiara
yeah that's yara very
let's see
finish the
finish the session yes and then good
role playing going to give you two
points for that really good this session
uh good teamwork definitely that's
another one um vice virtue not so much
but you did remember your flaw and you
used it in session to drink to drink the
strago
that's gonna be five beats for you
so six total six and you can go ahead
and convert that into one exp with uh
two beats left over
okay thank you yeah you're welcome and
last we've got scout all right let's see
what we got for scout yeah baby let's
see
um all right so for scout
uh let's see
finish the game session one good role
playing yes i would say so i would say
you did a really good job today um i'm
gonna give you i'm gonna give you two
actually
you did a really really good job with
your role play
let's see next
[Music]
vice virtue i would say not so much um
so that's going to be i wrathed i think
i rashed a little bit at the the kid
earlier or maybe not i don't know what
wrath is really uh wrath is uh generally
getting pretty angry um in a way that
it's like kind of fury
um
like
oh okay maybe that wasn't wrath
necessarily then yeah i would say it
wasn't a huge toll but you could take it
you could take it pretty far next time
if you want to
right so let's see what we got here uh
and then good teamwork yes yeah you
definitely effectively teamed up with
wasato um
to cause that distraction
so i'm gonna go ahead and give you four
beats
yay so that's a total of seven which we
then convert
to three leftover beats and now you have
a grand total of three exp for you
yay good job today everyone what a
session indeed we'll finish it up next
time when you guys unravel the mystery
of the spooky ghost carnival
who knows what could happen please don't
die
apparently it would seem so
all right
yay nice job everyone you guys are
getting the hang of this that was fun
yay
i'm glad you guys had a good time
that's what i want try my best for you
guys
trouble always a good time with you oh
you guys are really good role players
actually i think um
yeah i i feel like um you guys being so
like good at role-playing your
characters really contributes to it
being super fun so um good job you guys
good job
we shall reconvene in two weeks to
finish up this story here and see how it
all unfolds
i'm gonna go sleep
okay good night
good night you guys got any
announcements things you want to tell
the folks at home
members were watching us
in the like hour or so so
i'll see you then fun
have a good time yeah
nice nice
anyone else
not yet no it is not time just yet okie
dokie
sounds fun
i'm playing fan made games tonight on my
channel guys come check it out oh sweet
yeah
so i got i'm gonna be playing three of
them three that i got the okay for so
oh yeah i hope you guys will come and
enjoy
um with that being said uh we are whole
life myth we are myth breakers
um
how should we end this one
trick or treat nice that's a good one
actually because it is that month it do
be down here
all right guys let's do it on three okay
okay yeah all right three
uh wait no not on three hold on do it on
start it's three hold on
[Music]
bye
you