]
[Music]
[
Music]
[Music] [Music
] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] Te aku [Clapping
] kok
once [
Clapping]
[Music]
please are ready
for
much you  guys are
practicing you guys are
ready Are you guys
ready We good
We're going to do it What is what is
your team name What is your team
[Music]
name
come and next team The Dead P team
here Dead team
It's not to L  Okay I list all right so
how are you uh How is your
preparation for this for today event we
are preparing so much right oh so
much Oh are you guys are positive
that you guys can uh Win today so
positive no idea Oh yeah we'  re so
positive yeah yeah
and uh What is your team name do you
guys have team name k What do you
think no hope team no hope Why so good
You say we need to do the rer psychology
Oh I wish you good luck everybody Oh
thank you  so
mucham come back for to thank you
over here over here please a little bit
away from everyone because it's very
loud yeah
hello
hello Attention please
attention attention Ricky attention
attentionicky we are a very nice synergy
between the two So what is team name
[Music]
didn't even have to think of one because
we were prob Nash all along We Were A
Team for years
now
the winners anyway because we are the
ones who love each other the most
Music]
here
yeah okay
Good
evening J
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
gamb Can you introduce your team name
[Music]
er that our team name team not H
JP
are J okay
okay Inside bracket not and then h j ok
ok not the not is really important a
really important part of our team name I
see yes Yeah I hope you enjoy today and
Um There will be a Treasure Hunt game
So your team
tested
tested teamwork don't H Your
[Applause]
teamk  so I
[Music]
guess hello
hello Kobo have you eaten Have you eaten
yet Kobo eat first Kobo eh S I've
eaten I've eaten this, Jeta also gave me herbs
earlier ah great great cool cool cool
cool spirit Yes
spirit spirit Yes I yes I really really  Hey,
if there's something
e that might be troublesome because you have to
carry yourself for a
while, cheer up, ma'am, it's
like we're looking at you, do you know what?
P, it's
good to eat
this,
so that's it.
oh three of them are
tigtig okay
OK chairman
Guys okay Guys E this is because maybe we are
missing one but that's okay e
first we will Treasure Hunt So
the first game will be Treasure hunts
they There will be around Spot of
Treasure it can be in  CH it it can be in a
Dr it can be in
anywh
so your mission is to find
it has around three
emeralds that you can use for the
later there is a hint around the area that
you can check
[Music]
okay so before  we started Let's sleep
first
[Musik]
again Okay is there enough beds I know
Survival for the
it
my
B
[Music]
than one more one more
everybody the time the time for hunting
The Treasure will
be 10 minutes so after 10 minutes We
gather here  again we will we will ask
you to gather Here by
chat wait where is The
Treasure on the first floor it's on the
very first floor with the many many [
Musik]
grass on the ler with
and GR don't anything Don't you don  't
need my RPG sens are
tingling is everybody
[Music]
ready I'm going to count the timer So
Are you guys ready ready
[Music]
everyone stand
by Yes I'm it
in one go find
treure don't know what si searnya di  near
here there is
l later later later
[Laughs]
later Oh I
think okay what ma'am I don't understand Wait a minute
I'm still like I'm trying to read k
I can man I don't play this game
enough What does look
like things he can step
on most
Stone is the button  by the Oh
that's it guys because
it's
because it hasn't come yet So come on viewer
help me cash in my opinion yes something
like this usually requires two
people so you just look for a shelfer box there is a
green shelfer box or a
gray one De Ay
you can  Oh you found
it How do go back
up
est How does this game Work Sensei I'm
sorry I only show up to you
Canal and not classes Oh thank
you I really only show show up to the
Sports festival and not classes I'm so
sorry  it's I found I found you guys did
it that was one of the trickier
[Music]
ones we did
it I didn't know No they would have
reacted they would have reacted if they
found it I have no idea only I'm looking
here  for like five minutes now and I
have you already checked the book Yeah
it says like among the Flowers Vi and
BRI The Great chest HID from side
so maybe they did find it I don't know
among the
flowers I'm trying I'm  also
like i try
hard Did you find something No I see
buttons though we have to press at the
same time we don't have to break
anything
right How far would trying it be from the chest
should we break it from I'm going to
Desty public property No I don't think
we're supposed to break it right I don't
know I'm going to the next
one uh you guys can like keep on
pressing stuffs and whatever or just look
for them
there's something going on  Flowers
or not, do
n't you know if you're destroying flowers? Don't know Oh
no,
Popy's in the
coy behind it, he said it was urinated on by Mrs.
Coy,
what's wrong, Eh, where can you get those flowers?
If that's the case, we'll pie
[Music]
Inia
went down soruhuh
Oh, nothing's wrong  coy under it Coy
he's not, he's not
destroyed, he'll
destroy it, he'll
destroy it, won't he
[Laughs]
he'll take it, he won't
take
it Oh,
B okay
[Music]
poor thing Hi yeah you know we
Made Nobody found
[Music]
this
is this is the Hardest
one not really  The Hardest
but how does
senp know or not actually does senp look or not
if senp looks in
that direction Heeh there Actually there is II forgot to
take it Oh yeah
H means you put four huh H ah
found it already it's okay it's free
Rao it's okay  hint for children,
whether they are playing alone or not,
children are
good. Thank you for working hard
[Music]
I'm glad if I'm not mistaken,
there's one near the stairs too
or have they been moved
[Music]
yeah, I forgot too, we hid it
where even I forgot  where we hit all
of
them she May have we waste waste it no
we spent our time last night just hiding
all of these HS anders and making
theseaps it was
right?
even know so you guys
did you guys find any No I don't know
what to search for no no did you guys
know that there's actually one really
close by yeah probably right here ah
what the
hell that's what it's supposed to look
like
Said There  and chest and
hoppers i would i would recognize
[Music]
that everyone came here everyone
everyone Who got an Emerald Who's got the
Emerald
We
did Um in total nine
there treasures tre How many emeralds
you
got That's
[Music]
awesome but I  don't know
the puzzle That's
[Music]
nice I gu it's
F How many
you got
[Music]
budet
other everyone
[Music]
everyoo ha Attention
please ok thank you thank you for the
attention since  we've already done The
Treasure Hun so we have to go back and
the bu to continue the Simon say the
next game so shall we
go
Sep let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
What if we share a b Together in
Minecraft the game we are so
[Music]
romantic
C Everyone pleases go let's go I love love
love oh oh I'm catching up I'm catching
up no you're not no you're not catching
up I'm
catching I'm catching up
Run It's okay  you get
Run It's okay pretty well
with yeah that's
true are you talking to me I have I have
a feeling that I'm the one Who's going
to
m It's okay we probably mess up before
we get to five or
[Music]
so
[Music  ]
W I want to go up I want to go
up What Simon
says why does it matter to us say
Hello everybody are you guys
[Music]
here L just 10 anyway until they
can keep going L yaere bisut
s
ready I think B on discord just  Well,
I think Jadiora
[Music]
we have like
demonstration because it is at the top so
goes
[Music]
first are
you my Knees Are Broken but
[Music]
[Laughs]
ak the level
to the end
if it's wrong then it's done
[Music]
I'm right we'll make a group for them
I've already made it for the participants
[Applause]
[Music]
is
Iton
[Music]
ha tu yo H OK l
a
throw away three two
one Hi, throw it away Yes, why throw it away Oh yes,
throw it away, it seems like that's what it is, no, it's
not a throw, it's not a throw, Ris, throw,
throw, throw, wrong, repeat,
yes, l Mas
Oh
yes, okay,
throw, Hi,
throw, don't give me a
bonus, bonus, bonus, the committee said it wrong,
bonus.  it's better to just do it again, yes, yes,
that's okay. Later, there are two, we'll repeat,
yes, we'll repeat, okay, just
two straight
throws, squat throws, three two
one
ramp,
okay, in terms of aspects, in terms of
aspects, throws,
squats,
jump three two one lat
J  lompah
[Music]
lompah three
emeralds Emal facet throw throw
squat lar Jengkok jump jump jkok
forward
twice okay okay okay three
throw lemp squat squat
jump forward two forward two
I
wow lemmp
squat
jump forward
twice facing left left Oh okay okay okay
three two one
throw
dongkok jump jump forward
two left left
uh
cuyyukiiuki
Yes sengwa throw throw squat jkok
jump forward
twice face left left face right right okay okay okay okay
okay okay three two one demp
squat
J jump jump forward two
left
right eh eh sorry  I saw Antoni
Antoni Antoni
we left pretending left right okay okay okay okay okay
okay yes yes yes where is Yopi's mother
eh I I saw it looks like
Yopi is wrong yes right right right should be
right right should be facing right yes but
Yopi turned around Heh That's what I said
Yopi should be facing Muna when he's
facing his right alah Oh that means Sal dong
Heeh Yes Kokom D Alah kok means there's up to en en
wrong l okay
[Music]
okay Gok
Gok
ye this is the emerald yes
okay okay thank you
[Music]
you
please  Oh okay Nice
H hi
[Music]
guys here The rule y i think I think
it's better to stand in the red for the
beginning stand Thank you face Muna
there where I'm here Hello oh Hello I'm
here I'm here
in
BL  I'm blind apparently Ok so The rule
is like explained during the practice so
you guys will be given
progressive
eh Commands
Commands and the more you can do it
the more get yes and if one of
you yes do we do it at the  same time or
do Yes at the same time Ok at the same
because There will be 3 two one okay okay okay Are
you ready now okay
okay start from the first one
the First
ready yes
throw three two one let's go How do you
throw in this  this game is
okay, there's no sound, it's there. So is this
okay or not?
Okay, sorry, you can't see it from the pv.
Okay, I think you have to be in my place
so you can see it.
Okay, you can, you can take your item back.
Okay, my bread. Okay,
next next because you guys are  right so next
one is
throw
jkok three two
one
okay
[Applause]
okay okay okay we're going we're going
fast we're going fast
throw squat jump th two
one getting getting hot next is throw
squat jump forward twice
Okay  three three two
[Music]
one
What You
forget
forg What you JP so you throw and then
you J and then jump but you throw and
then J
Sorry She's A
Cellphone so I'm sorry Brain That's mean you
guys uh pass three rounds Okay give
you three
[Music]
Emerald Thank you Thank you
stud You should have stud you
shouldud I just forgot the order It's
not like I forgot the
meaning uh guys
can now Thank you wait on oh Hello Hello
welcome it's I for everything now please
speak slowly
Ma  Okay I will
be everyone stand by in the red
at JK Jump
left right
okay stand on
the on the red area please i on the
R are stand in the red
area are are yeah okay It will be super
easy speak slowly
Okay R ready kar  ready yeah Okay I will
give you the first one me guys PR for
us
throw three two one go
[Music]
You're starting off a difficult one
because Sounds like So that's like th
stuff or is it just and stu just one ST
okay okay  okay
okay ah Okay okay I'm telling
me so next is l
jok th two one have a question have a
question okay no question Just do it
wait okay
May
okay okay okay
okay And if you want to stay jok
That's also fine don't worry you  got it
you got it ah Okay but you know e ya
gitah Okay next next is getting
Harder
throw
squat
jump
fold One Okay throw squat
jump let's go let go go go go Okay next
next next
throw
squat jump forward twice okay okay
three two one  throw squat jump forward
two
De ah
next next next next emald OK OK OK next
throw
squat
jump forward twice facing
left
three one
eh
jump forward twice
kap Ki Hai
see How is this OSIS president continued
already five continued OK next OK next eh
throw
squat
jump  forward twice face left Ki face
right face right three two one
[Music]
l
eh and right and here and here and then
after that one I forg one I forgot and
then If I Turn and then If I Turn Right
do I Turn 45 De
right oh well I
mean As Long As righted
no As long as you turn right I think so I
guess That's correct okay yeah you can
we hear the Ding Ding Ding no what who
was wrong me right what did I do wrong
No You should you should  end it with
fing means that i'ming the other
way so yeah first you fing to re and
then faing to
Mey but I what I faced right that you
don't see how many Degrees
yeah no No that's 90 De Yeah you didn't
say How many
Degrees Well I think it's just like well
it's a misunderanding oh well it's H
up H up means only like of like we
facing here and then because this is k
and then had right is like to the right
of this position so you have  to face
here
yeah so that means four emeralds five
was it five right five five five
emeralds five
emeralds
y there you go Okay thank you thank you
Actually did great Don't
Worry yeah still the highest so far no
no I think he got but anyways  yeah still
the
same
over not It's Not Over Hello are you
ready yes wa we had a question yes oh So
if you say like kitty
uh KITT go forward do that means I Turn first
and then I go forward Yep Yep Okay and
then the other question was  if you say l
do we just Run Anywhere or we are going to
run in a specific Direction uh Run at
the front side You're facing at the
moment
okay okay okay okay So if facing right I just
Run like
this
okay if facing right face right  then
just
front just face right
Run Wor not
as you can stand on the red dots here
red block
[Laughs]
stop Are you ready for the first
one yeah
okay the first one I'm going to tell you
is
throwing three two
one Setak  ngadap dong dong Zeta ngadap
there
zetaun ngadap muna ngadap muna but that
was
right
kaking the right way don't Wor Take Back
item
moving on moving on the second one is
throwing a
squat th two one
Okay I'm really sorry take take back your
item fine  That's
so nervous in my life
before relax relax the third one throw squat
jump three two
one right
fast
ye getting hotter here next is throw
squat jump forward twice three two
one
okay you can get back to your
position wow oh next strong okay okay
thank you  going strong next
throw
squat jump forward twice face left
three two
one
okay okay you can get back to your position
get back to your position going strong
next one
is
throw
squat jump forward twice face left
face right three two
one Oh hm
OK wow  wow
wow guys to get this far
[Music]
ye going strong going even stronger next
one
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right back five times three two
one
Wow the
Oh my God even Harder even Harder even
hard next one let's
go I  'll start again
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right back five times hit three times
three two one
crazy chat that was crazy
okay Are you guys ready for the next one
another one Oh my
God wait go go go Before I Forget Okay
okay
next next get into position okay eh red
block please zetta okay thank you okay okay
next one
throw
squat jump forward twice face left
face right back five times hit three
times jump four times three 3 two
[Music]
one the last round last one  last one one
you made damn ooh let's go
Are you ready here we go
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face right
back five times hit three times
jump four times run to the
red block three
two
[Music]
one all crou by
accident so
[  Music]
apparently forgot
to go back five times
it's
only like three That's
F got far yeah the high so far
Oh thank
you so on the back on the
back that's emeralds it would have been
10 right if we got it got it yeah PR
That's one  less yeah
yeah yeah oh thank you thank you thank
you so where isylaj OK OK OK OK
I have Fa in you
guys where we face
Muna Thank you You a face Muna
Mun Where is
Muna the entrance entrance up
entrance I'm
here
crononon we'  re Running On the time here
Hello where is she here I'm here in the
green Thank you ok ok are you ready Can
I just theand now yes okay so every every
time the command finish you guys get
back to the red block alri and pick  up
any item youve thrown okay okay okay the
first
one
throw three two one
[Music]
that was easy moving on moving on next l
squat three two one
OK next one
uh throw squat jump three two
one I have Fa in you
next throw
squat jump  forward twice three two
one
okay okay okay
next
throw
squat jump forward twice face left
three two
one we have to be patient okay okay get back okay okay
you made it you made it don't worry
believe in yourself
yeah next one next One Okay here  we go
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right three two one
[Music]
apparently don't know i bot
yes yes face left face right face
left face right yes face left face right
not face left turn right okay face
left is left  and front is Yeah but Oh
I was I was like stopping here a bit and
then should I should I do that uh Okay
Okay Okay but that's okay you guys
that's fine you guys are great
[Music]
fon Kyla
five hold on does that mean that  and
Canada are the last y did
you pick it up
thank you okay thank you thank
you should be should be should be the last coy and
ye
Okay Hello ho
hello
Hi yeah yeah yeah yeah hai
hai
[Music]
haii Z
First
throw three two  one go
throw
[Music]
throw throwado
throw t t throw
t throw throw
[Music]
emp l
Okay take the item again Bu
okay
Jan
throw
jkok th two one go ah
ye take it again Hnya Bu Okay we
suiii
throw
squat
jump three two one
go uh
wow cii
okay throw
squat
jump forward twice three two one go
[Music]
okay
that
throw throw
squat
jump forward twice facing left three
two one
go k k k
Don't die
just yet I'm sorry I just can't
hear it
Okay
throw
squat jump forward twice facing left
facing right
three two one
go Oh with
them
[Music]
k face
right face left face left face right
Hidari Migi
m No no no you guys turned
right not
facing right
J turned
right turn back
[Music]
very
triyob Emerald
wait
is my  faak you two
Sal
finish let's go to the let's exit this
grp
Let's Now I am so ready to be a
disappointment
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
This is going to be
fun
akak bisaedah
k
[Music]
here we have  to
R yeah to prevent people
fromting Nice So People Don't
scream but like well you will probably
explain this anyway but like does that
mean That everybody gets the same amount
of time yeah everybody gets one minute
each long as we get it it doesn't  t matter
if we get it 10 seconds Minut yeah
because we wait for one minute
[Music]
anyways you just Open it right
Click I think we have to decide on one
guess we can't WR
[Music]
several you can'  t That's quite different
From Yesterday though like yesterday Oh
so whoever gets it quickly No,
so that no one cheats, so that we can do
all of this, we'll replace it, so we
have to replace it, or not, if
for example just one is okay Oh, it's okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay?
You can't hear it
What's up OK voice GR voice GR
[Music]
so everybody has one minute each and we
will be starting at the same
time
y How do say in
Japanese
[Music]
t apa
H
[Music]
OK so for  the builders you guys will go
to the corner over
here and you guys will see the for
your Made
these are homework any from
cheating so when you know the answer do
notam it out
not please
PR like right there go go ahead Can I
try and I  Guess when we build it's
best
This all of the builders for the
nonbilders please stay in your Lan yeah
[Music]
pleases yeah
yeahke ul
[Music]
i
haveimah Jing is wrong right damn I'm so tired
[Music]
just come in okay
there is everybody
[Music  ]
ready GR chat to have a voice group chat
so we can
[Music]
ka group chat
the team for the book
Ok time to count on
[Music]
it's
okay tired yes
tired it's okay you already you've
done great anyway Okay let's
count  It's okay
count it one
minute one
minute
Okay game start
in
three two
one
go go go go go Gou
Anju go go
go anu
Aju
[Music]
IP ajimaru
ajaru
ohy nice
I I hear what sound is that no
this is okay  We know that if they
don't tell each other, how
can they not tell each other? Right, they're in
each other's VCs ah
maneh never
mind whatever it's
called What's it called? Eh, I'm actually not paying attention to
checking, right?
Sorry
guys, I'm not professional, but I'm
tired, I'm tired, bro.
[Music]
sexy mo
OK Guys
and the
committee, how did you
make two mistakes?
Oh, we don't need to announce it, okay,
where did the sound all disappear? Well,
yes, I'm also confused. They are all
Sonya in their respective VC groups. Next, just run,
eh, the
winner
round
one
don't we don't yet
Ask to be rude, I'm sorry, right? Brother ad,
who is this,
OK? J asmos
no. m book
m
only only right cck oh no
can
[Music]
Okay thank you thank
youar cheers I will
confiscateers
what s thank
you what wait can we are allowed to
have sheers now
[Music]
oh bir
next round are we ready should I check
the book I  didn't check it yeah Please
check the book Oh OK I checked it
ok No I'm assuming everybody already
check it yes
in one three two
one one minute one
minute pretty hard it's pretty
H come
n
kengeng not yet l
this looks like a
Bu  another Temp it seems Wow and this
one is the
attempted drawing and this one w
[Music]
okay
okay wow wow wow
there is
some yeah We should Put Temple ya
see Canada is the closest
one reallyu
[Applause]
[Music]
okay okay
okay
[Music]
Nice this is why the
writing is small Muna so
the writing is
big okay
[Music]
okay G tough them
plus 1000 Aur
awesome R you're so cool Thank
[Music]
you
This is
one two years
[Music]
F Thank you  What is
that cheers Oh
okay everybody ready
Okay game ST
in three two one
go they'll have to make a
circle people who can make circles or a
ball would be great
it also looks like an egg
[Music]
pleases the out in back  turn
ah hi ha ha ha that's Eh
how is it
[Music]
Ye
to okay
answer please
[Music]
oh eh
What yeah
okay
okay Al next round
[Music]
is Oh yeah after this one we tell you
they switch times to do yeah
[Music]
guys
ready everybody
[Music]
ready yeah
Lady
let
Mar AD
[Music]
Oh I can see that
everybody's t
[Music]
t
interesting ah
[Music]
oh
eh okay please put it a picture
this picture is right
[Laughs]
[Music]
ah It's
okay
[Music]
goodak
Good good know
[Music]
okay
Nar ouch
[Music]
[  Music]
[Music] it can
be taken, it can be
done, my nationality,
my nation and my
land
[Music]
my water, Let's
play together Indonesia
go wait
hah Loh
W
halah halah
[Music]
okay, that's okay, okay, never
mind, let's not give you extra time,
that's
fine this one is practically kind of
like
Impossible I guess pretty much
Impossible
give it
Another we'll give you more time
here, here, Ken,
more seconds Actually, I don't know
how many minutes or
seconds have
passed.
my
C my God
Hah What is this
hah ha
you've been laughing to
yourself why
okay okay
[Laughs]
R laughs
alone [Music] Oh kameru Sok
kameru
kameru you
Cel is being inconsequential Cel where are you from per t Mayan
[Music]
you know
Om
where are you going olii yeah  It shouldn't be this,
right?
Hah. It shouldn't be. Is there really
another word? Wait? As far as I know, there isn't one,
right?
[Music]  I
was muting because
I was afraid that suddenly I
'd talk about it
M M one more round
okay easy easy easy easy
easy ah Easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy
easy
Yes
easy uh who's taking the book
etay Wi who took the book saha
hey hey open Who's  ng take Beka
[Music]
Okay W piro next
okay okay
bluetooth
z z take it again
Z
again what donon what are you
donon Oh that
's it you guys ready
eh later copyright won't sing the
song over
nambawan Oh five Oh th F
oh go
on I'm going to
kac
what
ah  Oh I just realized
that my eyebrows are really thick
[Laughs]
eh Kiara's ones are cool too
uh
it looks like snail yeah looks like looks
like
snail
Mar I can actually kind of see it oh
this is nice oh oh oh Kole nice oh koa
watino
ohak  what's so funny about cheating? This is his name,
ah, that's an obvious
name. But he can read.
No, that's all. That's all. Ben,
he understands it. In fact, he
can, because I don't understand it myself.
Once you look at
it, you can read. Can't you?  Yes you can
Oh camel why are there so many camels w
w
w w
Kang that's
great I've been told what that means
Oh litally this is so I wrote
the answer I meant to write his name
his name is just Anjay then he's like
that don't laugh or you'll cough Yes sorry
I didn't
laugh OK I
have to go to the toilet  again it turns out he can
read he can read I don't want to
destroy it, this is really cool,
what's cool,
doesn't that
mean I can go to the toilet in a minute or not
Li, go to the toilet, go to the toilet, go to the toilet
now, I'm going to the toilet
first, I'm drinking a lot of
horses, people have it here,
eh,
ak good  job
eh y
k
cor get Emal
Very funny Very funny like a child
[Music]
school
pleasinin okay
Ok
everyone Deven mute mute don't Deven
Okay
nice to join V Okay gr gr
voice
also what
should mute be mute ah mute okay
Okay everyone thank you so much uh for
playing this game we move to the next
game yay it's a wrong wol so we have
three minutes to play with the team and
every round got five emeralds There
will be like three rounds So let's go to
the wrong W together Shall We Come on
Come  here Come here follow us
let's let's
go I Think first you guys need
to you know Click the bed just in
case so You won't spare outside anymore
[Music]
we're not going to do this
yet come
on  come on up
here every
Ik come on
[Music]
this committee there will be how many rounds three there
will be three there will be three rounds so I Can
we expain
Okay There will be rounds in total rounds
Har and There will be no switching there won't
be any  switch switch gitu switching
[Music]
Nas ro It's A Battle Royale
we're not going by groups we're not Solo
Everybody's going at
the and for the wool cutters You are
Um You are to press F1 when you want to
play the
game and  for the
forem You cannot crouch
well if if hating is allowed then is
eating also allowed or like what if you
die and not fall i guess also hating is
only for like you know make people fall
don't kill you're  not allow to
kill you can hit but you don't
kill but what if like You've Been hit so
many times You're about to die from just
not eating I think there is food there
There is food outside in the upper there
in  the middle you can in here too there
in
here going to
[Music]
please join I have another event
I will change place for this
I will take my now Thank you
Thank
you byee
cheers The Purple
box
cheers okay
[Music]
[  Music]
for all the for can I can I see what
your color is
okell
isink Where's
other What color is not tak There is no
orange You Take Two
or only Brown Pink Green
yellow blue and red because that is the
obvious color yeah it's so as you  guys
requested you guys don't want like
colors that even We won't even like use
one fully I think
so What color should I
[Music]
take for deform
for we're
going should we have Green If It's not
taken
for the for  Who has taken their colors
Please go Upstairs because ITL be easier
for us to
monitor I'm Brown Okay is not
[Music]
okay right here so Green Pink and yellow
is out Green pink yellow and red Okay
let's go with orange I have Brown orange
There is no orange has
[Music]
brown
yellow green and pink is already out so
the left one is brown in Brown Ok Ina
Brown I blue Okay now go up please wa
How many stacks Can we take Sorry two
please two Oh only two should be  enough
two or Three is okay I brought a lot
I'll be
down but I think
every I'm going to say it again
Okay uh is everyone here one two year wait
where are just going to use all VC or
put my
ST on the VC  VC
we going to stop Using the all
vc proximity proximity Yes Ok
[Music]
okity
in just Brown Yeah Don't forget to F1
for the level good luck
[Music]
proxity pleases let
me I think like even if I fall down  you
can still
Okay
okay focus on not falling
down we Cut
F1 can we play peacefully guys up
here no Pushing
[Music]
who's bihin Let it go
L Oh yeah I'm losing it, oh
Okay full focus
hes Where are the
[Music]
holes
yeah out I I
[Music]
I forget they canat
is
it if if everybody dies then the last
one standing doesn't matter if
you but if everybody survives then we
[Music]
everybody  I stopped only two people I
Believe In
You there's Ait
[Music]
right Minut
just being careful It's Okay I'll Be
More careful next time
on
[Music]
it's you need to take more Blocks
Um Where do I put the Blocks I
got  to perspective color How many Emal
is
this could be like 10
[Music]
who's maama back
How
much time pressure Can we try
can try a bit fast
wawa
wawa GM pleases GM every already
in
[Music]
I think we have to speed up the time,
they say they have to leave in a minute,
so 1 half a minute, okay, half a
minute okay
[Music]
Oh I check DMS I have replied
okay oh my god oh my
god oh my god oh my god Oh my God  wa What color
Brown One more minute
[Music]
I think
I If I If I don't go too Close To The ah
[ __ ] really didn't drop
up you the
became a really
[Music]
nice lot of
Brown everyone stop in right now  stop
doing,
I'll count pink, okay, I'll count first
[Music]
two Green is 24
13 14 15
16 C
BR is not there,
OK? It's been destroyed. Oh, it's been destroyed, it was
3 blue, blue, only EMP 35 367 38 39 4 42
4 44 46  so many yellows
[Music]
one more
round here is the one that
Emerald took earlier,
but when
it falls
[Music]
I there
team two rounds and then the fin I
think Come here Come here
[Music]
[  Music]
good stay in that
corner
the okay we
start to the
cor Oh F oNe Oops Oh yeah F1
please F1
Please I'm sorry but if we
]
[Music]
it's
[Applause]
okayry nice nicece
[Music]
green Green wa you can't
anymore f f th
[Music]
Two The Survivors
[Applause]
are e the pink one I'm red
[Music]
yeah
ut different
[Music]
let It's Okay It's
okay I really tried and I think I was I
think I stayed pretty long
[Music]
It's time to comb all your
emerals wait you can take my emeralds
right to buy
stuff
Put sword
[Laughs]
a please
[Music]
nah Stone
okay
[Music]
Have you got it yet shnyaak
Okay again dongrow again dong tig
okayudah
yaisisa apaapa
okay okay
Stone
Okay a thank
you is that all
already
[Music]
Hello What would you
like um We would like
aing We would like  uh Okay Where is my
list okay so we would like one Stone
sword one Stone sword
uh one Bow shoing
Hello Um one Shield one shield and 30
arrows 30 arrows Okay That Should Be 27
I
think okay so money
Please
uh thank you
here are your
stuffs
oh nice nice did you get How many oh
wait I got a lot of arrows like oh three
arrows
right yeah that's 30 isn't it 10 arrows
for three
emeralds I already have arrows so
30 I must have had I must have already
had arrows Okay  is that all I'll I'll
give you some the arrow so I don't
accidentally oh
Oops
uh here I'll give this
back I think Oh
No I'll make a group V Okay thank you
that should be it oh there's  six more
thank you thank you Ah whatever uh thank
you
Do you have
money Yes
what would you like hi hi What would you guys like uh
I'll do the stone sword First
mhm I just uh send the emeralds over now
like oh Just Give me  the whole order
Okay uh Stone sword Stone AX Stone AX
shield and potion I think we have enough
for all of that I did the math Wow you
guys
are Rich wait don't you need Bow Uh I
mean
arrows for the navigator you mean Yeah
you  guys have a Bow but no arrows oh oh I
mean hit anything it's hard I mean the
arrows are
we like the emeralds that we have is
just enough to buy potion Stone AX Stone
Sword and shield Oh okay unless you
don't want to get potion  we could we
could forg
potion No I think hold on if the navigator
dies The Fighter can still fight yeah
ah then just get the potion okay so here
you go okay yeah okay oh thank you money
Please
Okay wait we're missing the shield Oh
right You  wanted a Shield money Please
OK Cuz the thing is waiting Sorry I'll drop it
all at once Thank You Hold on I
think I
think this is sorry what if What if
the sorry what if the we switch it with
[Music]
a The Fighter can
a Yeah I think we have
[Music]
Okay
guysanj Guys
[Music]
the shield is for the navigator or the
Fighter fter is also possible for the vigator
hi
[Music]
Go okay
Hello What would you like to
buy
one a yeah OK It's S right and then
one Shield first one shield and then B
crony or another
Shield um like I don't know what the
durability for The Shield is I think you
would Know Better you play Minecraft
longer I know I don  't really use sheld
anyway
Um
[Music]
Um justord
yeah Just go with sword then Okay one
sword that's all no
stonex no we want both so Stone AX
shield and sword yeah sword Stone sword
yeah is that all that's all y that's all
money  Please two three It's How much is
it
12 19 19 is it 19 Oh
Okay Okay is that all Yep there you
go don't want to give more of your money
no are you sure no thank you this is the
last round you don't  need to keep the
emeralds By the way No it's it's only
two we cannot buy
anything How about this I'll give you
guys a
bargain since you guys are the last one
and since you guys waited patiently for
two emeralds I'll give you  guys
arrows what what
yeah we G yeah we G to take that yeah
yeah okay it's it's a discounted arrow I
'll give you guys Okay sure eight yeah
thank you so much Yes that's Wow thank
you for mone thank you so much y Thank
you that's  great amazing fantastic
would like to sell your soul
Maybe I don't have a soulon sell your
soul I don't have a
soul Let's Go I think we need to watch
them let's go let's go Thank you
bye make GR
[Music]
[Music  ]
Hello Chad Would you guys like to buy
anything Everything's pretty much very
cheap we got arrows we got bows we got
Shields we got Potions If you're thirsty
that sword two times even
an AX two of them two
types a beautiful
smile  Okay That would cost your entire
bank
account
please
okay your soul is mine
I'm stressed stressed all
to are they going to do it soon
[Music]
how many minutes is this By the way
e because it should be 30 minutes that means a total of
10 minutes 10 minutes long too  I The
easiest way to die is also true
three two one
go
ah Where did you fall
to Where's zomie I don't know I I didn't
see it
[Music]
that That's
rainy and is
there in The
Rat In The Rat in KY
please She's waiting
me Yeah I got out I got out You got out
Okay sorry it's okay I hope you're fine
Sorry I didn't know I didn't know where
you were I wanted to guide you but it's
like that's cool we're good
okay  pleas
Now sa
OK good thank
you
ha
rainy ry trying to get
in trying to find a place are they are
they
H
Hud they've Pressed F1 yet
OK How come it seems like you're going to the save place
and then there's no one doesn't want to
move far to go to the place  Save
and go to their place. Isn't this
their strategy? They want it,
they're the ones who come
for example, if he
meets a piston, he can really
press it and then jump towards it, yes,
Kanata will fall, eh, Kanata,
Kanade, Kanade will fall down, OK, wait a minute
[Music]
Hi, shoot
the arrow ah
OK, Anyanya is in
out Oh Anyanya is the fighter, yes,
oh  now
re re and Oh, he's using a
good jump, he's using a
piston, slime, so he can easily go
anywhere, my auntie is looking for victims,
it's so scary, I'm
like a shark, don't you think it's the
same as the sound of being helped? She's like there, right?
there pai er
like that but I'm actually
waiting waiting for Iovi to get hit by the piston yeah
actually or any member like that gets
hit by the piston like that Why do you
miss it yeah it's just exciting to see it oh that
means because Anya lost Anya I'm going to play
in the final yeah yeah no Oh
[Music  ]
okay out ok
hah yes vote out never mind vote out that's it
already that's
it that's it all that's it
already three teams Oh that's three teams
just now three teams heah Okay
OK
next round
two te
OK Seta
Ame
Seta k
kade
y same too
hai
[Music]
hi oh wait no
oh you can go to the yellow Temp
u ru accompany this yeah
sorry sorry we can go I'll leave the
group chat for now okay
there's
pink pink there's no red eh oh
pink sorry sorry
red I forgot
GL I haven't  I've run out of water, I haven't
gotten it yet, I'll bear it. Wait a minute,
we'll finish
streaming it, ah, why not? I ca
n't come out.
Okay, ready
[Music]
Coincidentally, Anya is there
too,
oh, let's just make it fair, okay,
okay, thank you
[Music]
ok ready ready Ready okay
game one
go go go go go go I'm curious risu
kanade Oh risu who is a fighter for
risu kanade and kanade who is a
sniper [Music]
Oh yeah and they stay safe in the
crazy Al
zone
yeah Kyla and crony are also  staying
safe in their zone oh but Kyla is
finally moving
also yes Mr Stone sir
Oh
[Music]
P okay
Kani
[Music]
k I I missed ame keegprek ame
Earlier he said keegprek I missed it
oh what a shame the viewers tu tu tu tuh
he really wanted to
see this already already already already they've been
looking at each other
earlier they have to  be careful because it's
sniping right Oh ohing each other
think oh r falling there R falling there
but it's there there's this don't know why he's
still Staying there even though he's staying
[Music]
up are
you I think all
over go
yeah
sure Oh  A closeup
Battle that's why I'm
scared okay
[Music]
looking at them from Up close
One is really funny if m-mul is
kegepk Come on, keegepek dong I want to
see a squirrel geprek
eh
uh but it's
useless for you
[Music]
hiding but the tools are still  there's
something like that
[Laughs]
the device is that Fun to be Invisible
actually You have to get Rid of your
weapon
[Laughs]
yeah It is it
is yes yes it
was k Tom and Jerry
right wow
this looks like the power of the committee
[Music]
this is a
dog game wait  I'll break this first okay
[Music]
here here Here There you
go This is so dangerous I'm sorry I keep
Falling It's fine So can we How do I go
outside we can just go from here Okay
thank you I'm very bad  with
Directions you will be my navigator I
don't have a bow and arrow Oh that's
okay then I'll just tell you where
Everyone Is at ya How does navigate
you so he's like telling
and then he's like telling you don't come
here because there are  it's like that and then it's
like if we can't see very
far, so yeah, I also can't
get to places that are really far away, you
know? Oh okay I me the room By the
way I think it's just like that g like
Who around and then was acely
And then She was aiming like she you be
careful okay
then uh am make the group first
okay There are lots of substitutes
today Grandma grandma, are
we going to play
Ne yeah it's okay l
the enderman is gone is he still there is he's
already lower
[  Music]
Temple Rene oli green Green Temp k Oh
from each other this This is the committee versus the
committee Buset
okay okay so Norm if in Z area
are
are Okay so I'll stay away from those
Okay who's the fighter for this
team Eh
this is a problem  It's just the two of us actually,
Anjir, I'm going against the committee, which is
really [ __ ], Man, when I'm going to fight the committee, how come it's
possible, how come it's done by one, right by
one by one? Do you know if their Navy
has they have a bow and arrow So I
think it's better  If you play, the
farthest is half Oh
by Okay, where is he,
can see me the most, where, Kam,
half of the middle, Oh, coming
from the careful
[Music]
She's just waiting at this
point I I want to I want I want her to
be  like Where the arrow Can't reach
me okay now she's you guys are close to
each other just separated by Walls I
think She's trying to bait You Into the
like the middle I'm not going to
be baited I Think You  won't get hit by
the arrows as long as you stay behind
like the circle Walls in the middle
Yeah but She's a really good Shooter wa
How many arrows does she have Why is she
not running out I think they bought a
lot I think  they have like 40 Oh
damn I'm Lost I'm like legit Lost Oh
then Don't Worry she's coming for you by the
way I think it's going to be your
chance uh getting close Okay you guys
are separated by one Walls There She  is
good luck, you won't get an error, it
shouldn't be, yeah, it's
dead. You're
great
]
[Music]
Hello I will give
you hold
on
Kara
ohord Oh I can also
discord me tooakapaingop
[Music]
Thank you Thank you, let's get
together first, OK, Man, let's meet first
in the
same place, oh
[Music]
one thank you so much for joining the
for this
year I Really appreciate it that you
SP your time to play with us to try
the
games and also Thank you for the ID
for helping me to build finishing The
B
m anj
m
and after  this after this for the there
another stream
[Musik]
I and for the
participant Anji awas awasan
for the
in
here thank you so much and enjoy enjoy the
game enjoy the Food enjoy
everything Please Don't forget
to play the medle song that  just arrived
for a couple ofes ago thank you so much
where
yaar ajaak's Go
[Music]
Nik
already Oh my
God sleep sleep sleep
[Music]
Okay Where are they
I'm
so tall ya
bangong
the di
phosh
an
[Music  ]
crony fits
doesn't fit
hatingting
Oh and Please go up okay okay
[Music]
front on the bed in front
okay
a Batam can't be seen from
where Okay looks visible OK okay
ah y Yi Okay OK this is okay th two
one yeah
[Music]
yeah eh hang on
guys  hang on guys hang on guys it doesn't
taste good
B it doesn't really feel good wait a minute oh take a photo
so you know Dikas is taking a break why is BEC
Flying B Oh more or less it's worse I
think it's worse I think
[Laughs]
yeah that's
really funny that's it Wait a minute yeah hang on
BB Thank you thank  than
thank Patience Patience guys
OK th two one Gok
[Applause]
[Music]