[Music]
e
w
[Music]
oh
kiky oh that's my greeting by the way
KY hi that's what a rooster makes right
yeah that's exactly
it keep
cut is it dooodle doo in English I
langage but dooodle Doo is lame we
don't want
that it is a little lame yeah
C uh hello everybody yeah I know it's
still kind of crackly a little bit but
it was worse before we were like robots
before
uh you might have to just deal with it
guys
um as long as you can hear me normally
right now I think yeah I think it'll get
better once you get into the game I am
actually I am tabbed in
so it's it should it shouldn't be
oh too so bad I crackle too like right
now what
uhoh snap crackle and
pop oh
I that's that's not so
good crackle CH uh it's when I talk okay
well I hear the same like this is I
think because of Discord cuz we're I'm
screen sharing
and uh and only it only started when I
started screen
sharing but we already made it better
than before um I don't know how to fix
it
so might just have to be this way are
you in the game tab now I I am yeah I am
tabbed
in
uhoh she could just watch the stream but
there's a delay and like important for
AOE it's a real time strategy the real
time is very important yeah RTS RTS well
let me like is it a problem for you if I
close the my screen share to you for a
moment yeah no no close it and then we
can reopen it and we we should we should
be fine hopefully famous last words okay
testing so this is how it is without
screen sharing guys mhm normal
right normal I think normal we're
sounding normal now it's fine yeah yeah
well let me just do the introduction for
now hello everybody uh we're playing AOE
today but uh remember like I had this
like this phase where I was getting into
AOE last year in December and then I was
like really really like getting
passionate about it and I was watching
uh like some
tournament and I forgot what the
tournament was called maybe you actually
know it there's a bunch of tournaments
going on uh it could have been it could
have been the Titans league tournament
that well that that was a crazy uh crazy
crackle um try to mute in the screen
share options what what what mute in the
screen share let me
see uh I'll do that in a moment
but uh back then I watched uh one
tournament where you were casting you
were going like oh this is happening and
this is happening and I was like oh she
knows what she's talking about sounds
like a cast from Ellie this is happening
is
happening I don't know how to how to
cast
Aly maybe you can uh cast what's
happening on my screen later
well you know what we'll
uh we'll check out your strategies see
where we can improve we have one goal
today though do you know what it is uh
oh beating the hard AI yeah no that can
be a secondary goal no no no what the
other go more
important uh be becoming
friends well that's a that's a happy uh
Act accident that happens with it the
first goal have fun oh wow okay wow
that's also sweet that's also very
sweet oh yeah wait but let me like uh
actually so uh when I was watching the
tournament back then I was like okay
maybe I can ask her one day to teach me
but then I I kind of like stopped
playing AOE for a while and recently I
got back into it and I thought okay now
I should get like you know coached um
and it's it's really just because I I
was like playing
skirmishes and then I was really fine
with moderate AI but once I switched to
hard AI I noticed oh my God they keep on
rushing me what I can't stop this no
matter what I did I couldn't stop it so
I really need your
helpers skirmishers are my favorite unit
oh my
gosh they're the well they're actually
really not good but I think they're the
best yeah yeah you mean the scouts no no
the skirmishers oh the skirmishers the
ones on the horses no no they're the
ones that throw the little wooden ah
those oh yeah yeah yeah the the the the
cheap units right they counter The
Archers yeah the trash units yeah well
Golden Boys Golden Boys okay okay uh
would you like to like introduce
yourself tell us your history with AOE
like how long you've been playing and
all that sure well little Ellie played
age of vampires with her best friend
back in the day when she was still in
Middle School oh um we had so many
sleepovers where we played that game so
it was really fond memories The
Nostalgia you know and then uh Co
happened so uh that's a lot of fast
forwarding but fast forward so I played
the game as a kid kind of forgot about
it co happens lots of time on my hands
and uh the new Definitive Edition had
just come out that was around start that
was very very good for Age of Empires
the pandemic was uh you know there's a I
like to say there's a silver lining to
everything and
perhaps it was for hire that's great I
have my silver linings for Co
too yeah so well I mean uh it happened
so the new game uh came out and I got
back into it and then I started
streaming just for fun and obviously
when you're not playing a game for so
long you get really rusty so I kind of
started at the bottom of the barrel but
it was really really fun and then I
transitioned more into casting um and
like hosting tournaments and events and
stuff like that so right now I don't
really play Too Much by myself it's
mostly just watching the pros do it and
uh I'm just commentating on the strategy
I did watch you play too and you're good
she can micromanage okay she she will be
plenty of a coach you are boosting you
are boosting no you you're really good
at the game you're properly
micromanaging everything and you're
aware of everything's happening and I
watched you and you're good I want to
learn from you you see me right now but
I've got like a smile on my face as I'm
waiting for towards the
camera you know like when someone tells
someone they're beautiful and then it's
like stop stop but keep going I me you
you're also beautiful
though stop stop very beautiful I saw
your Instagram too
and I'm just out here trying to become a
muscle mommy you know oh wait you know
you didn't mention the most important
thing you speak decent German oh yeah
that's right I uh actually also lived a
little bit in
Austria
God buy
of so I'm trying to I'm trying to uh get
good with the Swiss German and that's
kind of difficult oh wait you're not
fluent in Swiss German you think Ellie
is Canadian all right oh she's a
Canadian girl
Canadian Oh
[Music]
Canada wait so why did you move to I me
I'm so interested said in your life
hisory hold hold on we have to we have
to just take a moment yeah you're
singing the Canadian National Anthem
with uh I always do I always do I always
do I feel like it's perfect it's in my
brain that is the national can we
correct that though because it's Oh
Canada it sounds the same no not Oh
Canada huge difference it's the same the
same more the
yeah but then okay so you you were
raised in uh Canada but at some point
you lived in Austria and now you live in
Switzerland what's going on well we want
to go way back way back uh to the day of
my birth I was actually born in Eastern
Europe in oopa and I grew up in Canada
yeah yeah so after I finished my
bachelor's degree moved back to Europe
and then I just been bouncing around
town now I'm somehow in Switzerland
that's so cool I want to old time uh
with the best and most important uh
being in my life my baby girl I've got a
daughter
dog no wait Dogo daugh actual daughter
or the
dog
yes yes I wouldn't be surprised if you
call your dog your daughter I mean she's
my little girl she's going to be she's
going to be 12 in December and you know
what that means next year I'm going to
have to deal with a teenager wait so you
really are talking about your dog right
yes okay good oh you on the same
wavelength oh my God cuz I have I have
two daughters as
well I have I got I got I got into
trouble with uh with my little girl when
I was in Vienna oh cuz you know they
have that like restricted breed list
restricted really the list hund list H
yeah
yeah so my little lady kind of looks
like one although she is not one let the
record show it according to my documents
she like like the the one that they
thought she was is like dangerous or
what yeah they thought she was a pit
bull and uh they gave me a two and a
half th000 Euro fine because yes yes and
I fought it and I said here are my
documents from cuz I got her from an
animal shelter in Toronto and they wrote
that she was a um uh Labrador Retriever
and that's the only thing like a
Labrador Retriever cross I didn't all I
had I didn't know pits weren't
allowed what that's are they
banned uh yeah you're supposed to have
like a dog license if you have one of
those breeds and then they're always
supposed to be with a muzzle all of the
time but let me show let me show you to
her and then
you can decide if she is I do see her in
your profile picture but that's pretty
small come here oh oh yeah by the way
she's streaming on Twitch so you can see
her POV um like she's basically just
capturing my Discord but uh you can see
her face cam and her dog I guess and you
see the dog which is obviously the most
important he is clearly a retriever
cross if you've ever never seen
one obviously this this is what a
retriever cross looks like I'm she not
a definitely not a mix of one
either wow wow wow wowow wow wow wow
what kind of doggos do you have uh I
have
cats oh you have kitties yes super cute
Kito
C they're not as old as your dog though
sadly like no we're gonna give Ryan a
treat on your behalf oh treat who wants
a trat who wants a
treat you do you want a
treat the cutest little lady that I ever
did see
yeah okay wow they getting to know each
other okay so I'm going to try sharing
the screen again um somebody said
something about muting something don't
know what that means oh yeah I guess you
can try to mute oh but uh it's kind of
helpful to have the sounds of the stream
so it's more entertaining oh true so I
can hear imedi starts it immediately
starts um but where do I mute this thing
that they said I should
mute what did you guys say that I should
mute tell me again we can put up with
the crackle it's not that bad
really oh wait now my game
is wait Ellie hello yes I'm okay
here
uh
um
uh okay now the new problem has arised
uh oh when I screen shared the game
suddenly the game audio was also like
lagging God why is this so bad
wait uh oh you know what we'll be
fine we'll be
fine wait but like can't you can't when
I go into like does it only work for
online matches that you can like watch
the match like in the game you know what
I mean observe um it has to be online it
can't be offline oh ah okay yeah no
spectator mode okay yeah it's very sad
uh mute the screen share can you how
does that wait mute screen
share well first of all I'm going to go
down to 720p again no oh okay well 720
we can deal with not 480 hold on I have
your little Avatar is working and it's
so
cute and we're both wearing a white
shirt Dam it
wait so the sound the sound the sound
how do I how do how do I do the
[Music]
sound where is
it yeah the crackling is back guys where
is not good we like the crackling you
know we're very professional streamers
so this is why totally we do the tech uh
the troubleshooting on
stream must mute your screen share yeah
but like where I don't get
it
h right click oh what that's a great
idea could we try steam screen
share Ste steam uh steam screen share
steam screen share I never tried that
before well let's
experiment okay how how how how how does
this work uh I guess we got to be
friends on uh on Steam oh well you see
my you see my name uh on the screen but
I it's
actually uh well hold on X out of no
don't share your personal information oh
me don't wor I need my littlea to be
safe and
thank you thank
you that'll be more lightweight nice
okay like Steam remote play
o o uh I guess we got to add a friend do
you oh wait I might have requests off
you should maybe give me yours okay I'll
give you mine sorry guys we're figuring
it out we're going to get there
eventually
eventually more friends on eventually
yay um I think this is my
handle
okay nice nice or do I have a friend
code uh do I need the friend oh you know
what I'll just send I'll just send the
little I
don't one of the two should
work oh there I my code there
are a few people with that thing thing
that you sent me but I think I have the
right is it the one the the one with the
girl and the dog is probably me no
there's no
picture um oh did you just get a friend
invite from me um
did I hope I didn't send it to the wrong
person well they're going to be very
happy to wake up and like who is this
hold on I got to sign in um otherwise
give me a friend code the the numbers
random person be my
friend I'm assuming I don't think I got
a code uh uh oh I I'll send you my
friend code I I think you send it to
someone
else yeah cuz there were like let me
send you let me send you my digits girl
let meend you that looks like your phone
[Music]
number oh there it
is we can be friends let's go oh thanks
everyone who's sending over their primes
and their subs here appreciates it we're
gonna get Ryan something
nice we're gonna get her we're gonna get
the little lady did you some good stuff
oh look how cute she's on the bed oh she
she just had some snacks she just ate
now she's smacking her lips on the bed
as all good girls
should does she always like listen to
you streaming she snoozes oh yeah my cat
sleep too when I stream oh the whole
time and then you know when I stop the
stream like they're in a different room
but when I stop the stream one of the
cats her name is smooy she will always
like notice the because the moment I
stop the screen a stream I will stop
talking so she notices that and then she
comes into my room and she's like meow
and she's saying hi and like good job
today on your
stream oh she's so
smart are they siblings or are they yeah
yeah they're siblings oh you're so cute
little
sisters okay so you got my invite I did
I accepted okay and then how do we do
the the thing
um I think through Steam you might have
an option
to let me let me see how this would be
because I'm not in game currently okay
maybe I go to my friends list
maybe uh in Steam Chat Steam Chat Steam
Chat you know
what yeah how about this this is this is
crazy but I have an idea yeah yeah what
if I just yeah uh invite you into a game
of Age of Empires and then we both pick
the same color but I will just
watch you play against against AI an AI
M no wait we can still let's we have to
try at least this to make this work our
idea okay okay let's try and if all else
fails then we go into oh wait so in your
in your like friends list or so do you
see that I'm like currently
playing uh oh I got to do that oh I see
right click in friends list watch game
apparently
oh okay steam I love you steam steam
you're the
best let's
see where are you here that's
genius are you currently in the game cuz
I'm not seeing you I am in the
game maybe Ellie's blind I mean she does
wear the glasses uh in game g i I don't
see you in game oh guys is there a
reason why she wouldn't see it do I like
hide it or so am
I is there a way to show it you need to
be in a match oh I need to be in a match
okay but it can be a skirmish I
hope then I will enter one I will just
go Vikings against
random uh Map size tiny in I don't know
anywhere Arabia I guess or yeah let's do
Arabia it's a classic map okay and then
uh yeah everything else is normal I
think start
game gos the gos you got
gos so now I pause the game and you you
tell me if you can see a game now oh Bow
Bow a b b oh oh
oh watch game is it happening yeah is it
happening it's
loading Let's uh not get too excited
here but it is loading oh thank you for
thank you something's happening it's
happening something's popping off
finally let's
go let's go oh your community is so
sweet they're dubbing and gifting Subs
to other people really really you guys
are so nice they want Ryan to get
something nice who was just digging in
the bed there um C I don't know if your
cats do that but Ryan loves to make
herself comfortable well of course they
they do be making themselves
comfortable haven't played in a while oh
my
God C uh it's still loading so it hasn't
loaded yet still loading okay yeah which
is um by the way I have uh I have
changed a couple of like um hot keys to
something that works for me a little bit
better but most of my hot keys are
default okay that's fine the ones I
changed just like uh all
Idol um I think I maybe
changed new villager or so I don't know
some of them I changed okay well the
most important one for us uh I think
today will be H which goes to your town
center yes I always hear the
sound it's
yes and you got H and then q q Q's up
villagers so HQ HQ is very
important I
am my my Discord says the broadcaster is
offline and it's very
sad your Discord says that yeah H sorry
my my uh this this the
steam that's tragic I'll try again
yeah we'll we'll try again are you
currently um um like in the match right
now or just in the lobby I'm in it but I
have the game paused but I would think
that's no
issue all right well I have to maybe
click accept really I didn't get
anything like
that we're going to figure it out
eventually we've got we've got the brain
power you in for a
moment no oh okay maybe I have to change
something in my settings am I set
offline uh it hurt my feeling
that I was excluded from this I wouldn't
I
wouldn't how do
uh wait uh I I am online I am
online yeah I I I'm trying to get in
here all I see is
this it's very sad the broadcaster is
offline and tears will be shed what the
heck
[Music]
steam settings broadcast steam
settings I I love you guys privacy
setting friends can request to watch my
games uh no then I'll change it to
friends can watch my games so you don't
even have to
request and yeah record
no show no
okay okay let's try again let's try
again everyone yeah everyone for
everyone who's asking why can't I just
watch the stream because then it's not
it says broadcasting is enabled your
friends can join your broadcast anytime
okay okay okay okay let me get in there
come in come if I watch yeah if I watch
your stream then there's like a few
second delay and then it takes the real
time out of real time strategy which is
not very
fun I'm nervous I'm
nervous
okay let's see watch
game it's loading
loading we've been here before but will
it load all the
way that is the question how how life
how not delayed will steam be we will
[Music]
see come on come
on hold on
it is I think I'm in
here let's go I think I'm in here let me
just
zoom let me just zoom out here because I
think I zoomed in now I got to zoom out
but I think we got this I think we got
this watch watch me watch me watch me
we've made some progress here and I've
never been more happy in my life okay we
figured it out guys it took it took some
time wi by golly look at me am I there
I'm on screen
yes high five through the countries
Christmas miracle
y here we're trying our best here to
make it look all good thank you for your
patience
everybody
D
okay so does it look
good it looks good I think we're I think
we're Gucci oh yeah we're going to put
you there's a lot of support here
welcome everyone who's
new we're gonna be getting
Kiara yes top of the ranked
ladder we'll see about
that and it's going to be amazing
amazing amazing but first you know a
journey of a
thousand kilometers begins with one step
speaking of steps I got I recently got a
new watch uh to track my my steps and
it's been actually motivating me to get
my
goal the last couple nights it was like
11:40 and then I was like oh I'm 2,000
steps away from my goal of 10K so then I
went out and it was like power walking
well people who have something like Dad
they always always talk about how many
steps they did
today they're so into it it's very
important I like it I like it it's also
like a mentally good to see my resting
heart ratees go down it's it's a
personal victory at that point but
anyway you know what else will be a
victory this game this
game I'm scared okay so basically I know
um uh uh F like the first two villagers
I make them build a house and then the
other villager builds a house alone
after they're done with the houses um
while doing that I can send the scout uh
scouting um I can't micromanage so well
yet so I normally just do auto uh
scouting and yeah yeah then sometimes
when I'm like feeling like I have some
time then I send one of the sheep
scouting in the like close by look
at I'm a pro player look at
me okay that sounds great I like the
plan I'm building yeah building the two
houses beautiful and I would still
control group the Scout do you know
control grouping oh yes uh it was uh
here I made one yeah look at that you're
already a pro perfect so I would I if I
were you I would keep this beautiful
Scouts uh control grouped until you find
your sheep so you start with four
already discovered and there should be
four more to find so we got to find
those because that's important okay and
after that then you can control uh autoc
Scout and then get some more information
on the map so let's go let's get into it
um what what's the AI difficulty level
hard hard yeah all right General
Theo so should I
startare your last words down I will
probably be pausing a lot still cuz I I
need to like figure out what to do and
like I'm used to pausing
now all right do you know anything about
the civilization like what
do uh yeah uh I've played Vikings like a
few times recently um and uh uh they
have a great unit that that I really
like that I forgot the name what was it
berserk or something like that the
unique unit from the castle and do am I
mixing something up or don't they have
like
free uh like wheel card and stuff or was
that the two free wheelbarrow and hand
card okay okay so that was right so
that's why they also have a good economy
um and I know about the ships and all
that they have fancy ship uh but I don't
think I don't know if we have really
water so there's no water on Arabia so
it's going to be very unlikely that
that's going to be relevant for us but
could you do us a favor and click f11 on
your keyboard f11 oh perfect so now we
have the
time goes up as well why does it say
casual 1.5 oh because the speed of the
game that you're playing at is 1.5
whereas normal is 1.7 so it's going to
be a little bit slower than the normal
time okay okay so you want me to to
control the Scout still not Auto
scouting yeah don't Auto Scout him just
yet after you find because you're going
to need to practice to find those sheep
it's really important to find those
sheep you don't have to worry about
pushing the deer or anything like that
but definitely pushing uh finding those
those sheeps is going to be important
okay okay no
pressure okay so I'm going to send them
like all around maybe yeah perfect
perfect bring those boys in um what I
would do is bring one goat underneath
the town center and the other ones a
little fur away because you want all of
the villagers uh getting the food from
one sheep ah I did notice before some
problems yeah with having them all too
close I noticed that yeah sometimes it's
like difficult okay so okay okay and
then we make them do this and and okay
oh there's a fat pig there and a goat
it's a rhino yes okay oh we'll get him
eventually mhm uh my my micro energy
normally is a little bit better than
this it's okay you're a little
nervous I haven't played in a while wait
she joined uh we have like six five five
Villages now and with the uh until we
get seven the seventh goes for the uh no
the seventh goes for for the the the
wood the wood the wood yeah
yes okay usually you have six on sheep
um I would bring another sheep uh near
the Town Center underneath the Town
Center just because they'll
automatically go and get the next one so
it looks like uh you're doing good with
the
scouting
perfect what was my key for new villager
plus okay so you have a do you have a go
to your idle villager tab like a a
hotkey for your idol villager uh yeah I
have one for all and one for only one
next up uh at the top you see oh no no
no
no okay okay yeah I see they're idling
okay yeah so it's good to uh have zero
idle time or as little as Idle time as
we can but now work wait this is the
this is the seventh the new one is the
seventh no no uh oh yes actually the new
one is the seventh the one by the house
he joins he joins them and he goes to
make a camp for woodwor right yeah so
you can have a choice here you can make
a forward Lumber camp or the the
defensive Lumber camp at the back oh
oh so which one would you like in the
back all right that's a good idea Lumber
Camp Co and you can also when you're
making villagers you can already set a
gather point for your villagers oh where
would that be what would probably on the
wood so you can you can click on the
town
center and then right click on the wood
okay okay cuz the next how many was it
four five I don't until we're on the
11th the 11th goes for the boore right
yes okay I don't know if the I usually
click a tree I don't know if they're
going to go cut wood by clicking the
having left click or right clicked on
the lumber Camp oh oh wait they're okay
they're going oh no they're going going
for it automatically uhhuh okay perfect
oh wait one more one more sheep that's
maybe the last
one did he find them all I think so I
don't I think there might be two more um
is your town center
producing it wasn't I know it's always
be
always This Town Center does not get any
breaks there's no mandatory days are
timed off no no no breaks no breaks no
breaks no rest for the wicked yes
understand okay she's going she's going
that is the ninth one
so making more making more so now you
have uh no like you should put another
sheep closer underneath the Town Center
yes did we find something
here no nothing
there okay okay how confident are you
with uh luring a boar easy easy easy
okay let's let's see how you get this
one done the next
villager mhm okay so you put
it okay so she goes let's go for for
this one
mhm she shoots once and then she brings
them back and then how's your how's your
population looking uh good do you think
you're going to need to build something
to have more
room he he will build he will build a
house here
new new D makes house perfect so uh
villagers we have to produce No Rest
don't I have a problem here because they
started the Sheep I watched the video
from the guy who makes all the videos
mhm about what's when you have this
situation where you have one boar and
one sheep or so like it's a tragic
situation uh do you have any Idol
villagers right now yes yes uh uh well
well one one go back wood and this one
maybe he can make another house or he
joined the woods too um well you do have
those berries right in the darkest the
most important the farm the most
important the F food okay I forgot yeah
it's been a little while since my last
one oh okay then we'll put it like
here actually I don't like this
placement anyway cuz like the houses are
too close where I could build the farm
like like a like a little Farm Place
optimize later
right now the most important thing is
villagers Gathering food and you have
villagers okay that's okay they took
another goat we'll cry about that one
later why why but you can you can set
the gather point on the berries for your
town center and have like four villagers
on berries it should be fine you don't
really need to worry too much about
build orders um at the beginning it's
just about getting a feel for how the
units work you really just say that that
I don't have to worry about the build
order
yeah yeah we're not there yet we got to
walk first before we can run you know so
let just the first like the most
important thing in the dark age is
literally just grabbing food um your
scout my Scout by the way he's not doing
anything can you do auto Scout now you
can put him Auto Scout okay bye-bye
exactly we worry about that later okay
ah okay by the way oh no should I
actually cuz you know what my biggest
problem is with hard AI what I just
couldn't get across is like the the
start rush cuz I can't create my own
like defense so fast I tried my best
with my stream but I was told that I
should send the scout to the other uh to
the enemy to see what unit he is
creating so that I can at least for that
should I do
that
um I I don't think hard AI usually
rushes in the Dark Age so I don't think
you have to worry about that too too
much if you want to you can always
having some more insight Val soon don't
worry about it we're not doing too bad
okay all right then then H should I keep
on bringing them to the berries yeah I
think that's your first one and then you
probably right is that four on berries
uh that's usually a good amount looks
like four yeah yeah cuz you you are
running out of food underneath the Town
Center so it's probably good to grab the
other Rhino and bring it over oh okay
then this new one I'll bring her to the
Rhino but
villagers oh what
[Music]
villager so oh hold on do you really
need that much cuz you're going to be in
the feudal or dark age for a very long
time let's try to go up with okay with
20 population I think that's good okay
One Moment One Moment
don't let her die don't let her don't
let
her okay okay I got it beautiful oh but
what about this when it's left over I
let her finish it okay and then I I
cancel a few villagers yeah yeah so
cancel two bills okay two more and then
we're going to want to pick up uh uh
loom loom loom loom loom loom and we're
going to hope that by the time this
researches we'll have uh how much food
do we need to get into the f
age testing question 500 500 I didn't
exactly I think you'll be fine yeah
there you go perfect so you got some
Idols we can bring them over to another
wood line oh oh new one yeah like this
one okay yeah but try to take the
healthier ones and if you have any
villagers that are have been weakened by
the boore we'll leave them underneath so
Feud let's research
Feud clicky clicky
okay and I I'll make the new point at
the new Lumber Camp maybe sure I mean
we'll get the feud age in a while okay
should I send one more that's like
collecting the meat right now to the
lumber I probably one or two villagers
from the berries it's looking a little
saturated berries okay yeah usually it's
just okay to have four villagers there
so do we have any Idols we need to take
care of yes this one that I just moved
and then uh her
mhm I'll I'll add her to the lumber so
how's your population looking do you
have room for to make more units here I
make house perfect and if we want to
make military units I think we also need
one more building okay indeed which
building could that be ah a Barracks but
they're done by the way they're
completely done so I I I sent some to
berries uh yeah you could put them also
on the straggler tree and then you'll
build some farms around later when you
get everybody on on one or like what's
your well you can you can select more of
them at one time you can just yeah but
do you do you want all of them to go on
One
Tree sure okay cuz we'll put them to
other work as well I'm assuming we're
going to go for Scouts of our own
because they're quick they're strong uh
and I like them so we need to build that
Rex should I build the the barracks like
close to the exit
where okay here I like that one better
exactly
perfect nice okay after we're done with
feudal age I I'll add some more
villagers mhm so once we get to feudal
we can also upgrade our economy a little
bit yeah yeah yeah indeed and you have
uh I think we have to UNC some villagers
otherwise it'll be hard to afford
everything okay you can keep three
that's fine okay we're here we did it
okay so now our economy is super good
with that free wheelbarrow no big deal
so let's get the wood upgrade and the
farm upgrade and then build a stable
okay W upgrade Farm upgrade the horse
CER yeah okay nice he's also Advanced
but we're ahead of him we're a little
ahead of him perfect so we got to make a
stable now yeah a stable stable stable
okay stable stable stable right next to
it maybe mhm okay
you could have built it one side closer
so there was no hole in there but okay
that's fine um so let's go uh the Scout
is in in general Theo's area so we can
kind of keep tabs on what he's planning
so you can take control of a scout now
and then move him to the front of the
base the front of my base his base his
base if he's building production
buildings like right now what what is
that does that look like a an archery
range does that look like a second
rack no one is barracks right or
or second
one is hores stable okay so he's going
to come up with with some Scouts okay so
what is the counter to SC no
Archer Archer it's from the racks so
let's go look at the okay then it's the
the ones with the Pikes Maybe or the
spear the
spear exactly yes yes so que up a couple
of those um maybe that's too that's too
much
too easy easy does it girl should he
continue scouting what about the town
center it's hor Town Center Town Center
do you want more villager you want more
yeah we need more houses and now we need
to make Farms look at the wood that we
have we've got 780 wood farm that is
prime Farm real estate and you can send
the spears that are coming out to defend
your villagers so you have some uh like
you can put one on one wood line one on
the other wood line okay okay are the
houses being constructed no um um you
can take those two ladies uh and just
make them build houses
okay um maybe while because your town
center is not doing anything you can
queue up uh UNC those villagers and and
pick up town watch just to have a little
bit more visibility okay yes what was
that do again for building oh okay visib
you have extra line of sight and all
those villagers they can make farms
around the town center okay uh
hey no no around the town center it's
better to build them around the town
centerz there's going to
be
okay there you
go all right economy booming
booming perfect exactly so look at the
wood that we have got 800 Wood do we
need all of that wood uh no no so we can
pull a lot of villagers off of wood and
make Farms now all right we're going to
need to keep making the villagers mhm
keep making making farms and did you
want to do a scout rush or did you want
to just play defensively want be
offensive all right so let's make some
more maybe a couple more
Spears and protect our economy okay I
sent one to both one to each uh Lumber
camp and I guess I'll send one to the
town center yeah pick like five
villagers off of wood and make them all
build farms okay even more even more
even more look at that we got 900 900
wood that is not you want to have as
close to zero resources as possible you
want to be spending the resources all
the time unless you're saving up to go
up in age or for some sort of technology
so just you're
wise are there any buildings that you
can build right now do you think that
could help you as well uh uh probably uh
uh uh wait uh let's see
uh uh blacksmith the blacksmith the
market you've got the wood for it you
might as well build them and you can
kind of build them in the way that they
protect uh as part of your wall okay I
built this like right right next to it
yes
villagers
villagers what about what about what
about the SP what about the
span well you're fine now there you
don't see any you don't see any Scouts
on the map uh so you're not being
pressured just yet so you're all right
but definitely uh do I want like an
defin bu more houses houses okay more q
c who perfect so you can also take like
five villagers off of the wood line cuz
you still have so much wood just build
yeah yeah you don't need I think you
have your hot uh gather Point set to the
farm like or the wood line but we need
to get gold right eventually we're going
to want to go up to Castle age mhm so
gold Farm yeah all right so we need
uh we're not going to comment on that
Lumber Camp placement all right no you
mean because it's too far away now com
it's fine it's fine too far now yeah so
more
villagers
villagers villagers yep y y yeah okay
perfect you know what uh have we built
the market we need to build a market
we're going to need to sell some of our
wood and then we can just go up to
Castle and that's when we start our
assault on Mr Theo okay should I should
I add more to gold
uh yeah yeah but you have so much wood
right now that we really don't need to
be we don't need to worry about wood at
the moment at all so as like look our
our general Theo is already oh oh okay
okay queue up more Spears we're going to
just need to have lots of
Spears I feel nights are going to be
incoming and I'm very scared me too me
too uh more
Farms more Farms more
Farms with one villager also maybe I
don't even know if it's worth to make
house house walls maybe I just feel like
we want to defend uh defend our economy
with with some sort of something so
maybe bring the spears that are standing
by the racks closer that they're kind of
defending the gold as well and
can send this the scouts a little bit
forward so we can see what's coming for
us the Scout forward okay yeah oh
there's a tower on the okay he's built a
tower uh what was I where was I supposed
to to put the
spars by the gold okay yeah you just put
them there so One V one villager yeah
she can make more houses she can just
make 15 houses right now okay yeah and
oh they're coming they're
coming you've got spars you you got
Spears they will okay wait I let me make
a group for them and now
attack no we lost this man man okay just
leave just leave your Spears be bring
them back bring them back to the to
your push the wrong thing uh uh return
the game uh okay bring it back to
the or do you know how to patrol them uh
no no but hey they're doing it they're
doing it they're King they're doing
they're doing it okay we need to go up
to Castle clicky clicky up up castle
castle yes yes yes yes
y okay okay you you've done it youve
done it amazing okay perfect perfect so
with that Scout careful not to go too
close to the Tower and just kind of see
what he has um and while that out is
going around do we have any Idols yeah
yeah many many uh we make more Farms
you can make more farms uh oh there's a
let's go back to the Scout there's a
little
alert he's dead oh no we don't know them
we'll have the funeral on Thursday okay
but for now we got to go back to the
action so we have a lot of wood yeah I
say we're gonna make two new town
centers what do you know about dropping
Town centers all right uh like like here
maybe
one why there cuz it's further away and
so they'll reach it later I don't
know the thing is with Town centers you
want to drop them on as many like on on
resources so your villagers can be
really efficient so you see that space
between your gold mine and that wood
line oh yeah that would actually be a
really nice place to drop a town center
if you want you could even delete your
Lumber camp and just build a TC over
there so there's one and you wanted to
make
berserks yeah so what do we need to make
berserks castle
castles and what resource that mean
Stone yes is there any stone in the area
where we can build a town up here so
okay I'll I'll make one Town Center wait
that's not a town center no wait where's
it no no we're not in Castle yet this is
this is a forward thinking oh wait wait
can I not make a Town Center right now
no no you're still in feudal you have to
be in the castle oh see I never made a
second Town Center before in my
playthroughs okay all right um oh okay
you don't have to make a a lumber Camp
there or a mining camp there because
we're going to make a Town Center there
so don't worry about it we can delete
that Foundation how um and instead you
can just make some houses how do you
delete it just with the delete
button oh
okay but I have so many Idol make more
Farm
or yeah you can make two more farms near
the Town Center okay yeah you see the
the villagers at the back um at the wood
line uh
yeah so they're walking quite far to
that Lumber Camp aren't they make new
one what can we yes we can make one
closer they'll be a okay next time I
would have made a little bit more to the
right so true but this was also fine
don't worry I mean I want to get my
steps in right but the villagers are are
are working long hours no paid overtime
in fact they're not getting paid at all
so we want to at least bear them the
extra walk yeah true okay okay okay
efficient U okay it's built so I delete
this one should I make one here too a
new
one on the other um you can there so oh
fine okay oh we're almost almost in
Castle age yeah and no
Idols beautiful this
is a big beautiful sight to behold yes
we're going to need to make an army at
some point but let's drop those TCS
first okay uh who to take so take uh
take like five villagers from the back
wood line the back one oh okay back wood
line so they don't have to walk too far
take like five just select five you
select six doesn't matter and then build
the Town Center on that stone on the
stone yes
beautiful
beautiful and then we want to delete
this other forward Lumber camp and then
make a TC there instead
forward uh this one yes okay uh delete
it but first first maybe okay yeah sure
that's also fine sure okay put more
villagers to build it okay so it goes up
faster
and now we need yeah queue up more
villagers perfect what are the what's
the idle situation looking like uh uh
could be better uh uh we can make a
castle maybe well we can't afford a
castle yet we we'll have to set the ga
the gather point for that New Town
Center that's built to the stone and
just queue up villagers like crazy in
the meantime we can pick up some Eco
upgrades Eco
upgrades mhm uh wait so uh to uh this to
the
stone uh yeah if you want to get them a
mining upgrade sure that's from the
mining camp but I was thinking the the
standard wood upgrade the farm upgrade
uh-huh uh-huh more more Farm upgrade
okay heavy
PL yes
Bowa a golden one too gold mining we can
afford it take it Stone mining too oh
yes okay no what do I do with these
people um you can uh send them to the
back wood line okay cuz we're we only
have six villagers on wood we can use
some more okay okay Town Center this
one's finished so maybe also g a Point
somewhere HQ HQ
HQ
wait HQ HQ h q uhhuh what was that yes
yes I have a hot like for for me I said
uh when I click H it goes to all the
town centers and then uh you want to be
producing out of all of them so that
means we need so many houses one
villager can just go build a gazillion
houses right now just oh wait do I do
you know how to multiple houses at the
same yeah yeah shift and then oh what
wait how how does it work yeah yeah so
so you uh click her to build a house and
then you shift and then clicky clicky
clicky
clicky oh
okay yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes and
just click click click everywhere with
that you're going to make so many houses
and you'll never get housed again and
we're going to need more villagers to
pay the villagers oh wait she doesn't
finish them though she'll go back to
them don't worry she'll go back
to she'll go back and villagers
villagers
villagers that's
cute um
um what one more more have like five
queued up at all times
okay yes okay good good good good good
so 21 Farms we're going to need to send
some um hold on I think you have a
gather point for one villager in your
town center do you see that flag
yeah yeah we're going to need to put
them to work let's put them on the gold
okay yes also I can get rid of this
Lumber camp now
right yeah it's taking up some space
okay
so okay now we
have an interesting situation we've got
so many resources mhm um I would build I
would I would start getting some Eco or
some blacksmith upgrades if we want to
go for berserks mhm we're going to need
to get which
upgrades uh
uh for
forging yes
um Fletching is for Archers but that is
for infantry yeah it's an infantry armor
perfect you can get Fletching as well
he's building something close by he
wants to he's trying to build something
I don't know what he's doing there but
he's in the wrong
neighborhood should I ignore him
more what the audacity gold the audacity
the audacity of this one what he just
wants to build in the middle of my
Village what is wrong with him wa okay
leave him alone that's wild that's crazy
uh okay what can we do oh God I have so
many resources wow you do so you can
make your Castle you've got quite a few
idle villagers if you want to bring them
to go build a castle could be nice
Castle should I make it also like close
to like here you make it on that hill so
it'll be a defensive Castle on the hill
on the hill there we go okay okay I'm
sending I'm sending everybody there yeah
you're going to need more than one for
sure so let's keep up villagers cuz
we're not making we're not making them
that's not good bills bills will more
more more
mhm and uh
that gather point for that one Town
Center is still in the Town Center the
forward one oh really oh why what
happened it so you need
to uh I think yeah yeah The Gather point
and then you can like send them to work
one of those little exit yes yes yes
that oh perfect uh and now you need to
pass them to do a job because they're
just hanging out underneath the TC like
lazy bums oh okay which job do they want
m maybe one maybe a
farm uh oh is the castle up because
we're goingon to need to go to
imperialist soon as the castle comes
almost almost yeah so go let's go to one
Town Center mhm and get ready to click
that Imperial button oh two Castle h
building okay yes there you go that I
make my Army now yeah make the Army okay
what what do all these want to do these
people you can send them on gold and
just a mining camp on that gold cuz
we're going to need gold ah this one
here yes yes okay small mining camp
don't worry about that goth placement uh
that mining camp placement it's it's not
bad it's not good but it's not
bad okay we need to be making berserk so
maybe set a control group for your
Castle so you remember to keep making
those berserks control for the castle M
uh Q was it is it cute yeah
c yeah perfect perfect let's get some
more upgrades at the blacksmith for them
as well so they're going to be
strong yes iron iron
casting as well and get Fletching too
that's going to give you extra range for
your castle and a little bit more pice
should I uh gather them somewhere else
or is here fine here is fine but let's
make another Castle as well oh look at
all these people yeah take them to build
a castle in front of your gold Town
Center oh my gold Town Center yeah my
gold Town Center a little bit more to
the other side a little bit yes over
there over there a little bit forward
uhoh uhoh okay maybe not there the
Champions are
comeing
wait okay okay cancel that let's let's
move it let's let's build it in between
these TCS actually I'm the T yeah yeah
yeah let's build a castle there
you can also um Garrison your your gold
villagers in that town center so they'll
be a little bit protected Garrison
Garrison Garrison I think T is the
hotkey and then you click on the Town
Center I'm scared I'm gonna die yeah
Ellie I'm going to die send your
berserks in there
okay no he brought a Ry we'll cry about
this later
okay b x come on come on a I'm not sure
the ratio is going to be looking too
good they're destroying my Town
Center ah they killed all my berserks
they have a triple we have
we have two castles now we can
double should I should I Garrison them
too yeah you can but we're going to have
to lose we're going to lose that town
center it's going to be very tragic but
we'll cry about it later not Chie or
should I get Chie doesn't matter let's
get
first going to kill me why are they out
they out now go somewhere else yeah yeah
because once yeah put them back into the
castle have a little bit more Firepower
there oh they can go into the castle
they can Garrison into the castle so T
and click on the castle okay perfect so
you can control group your other Castle
to the same control group and then you
can click like you just control and then
three I guess yeah perfect and then make
your berserks am I going to die Ellie
you know I'm G to be honest with you
it's not looking
good situation but I never got so far
before that's
great
uh well you know they're all just coming
out one by one should I like gather them
somewhere else first
or mhm yeah you can gather them that's a
great idea buy the the castles um and
then when you have a good maass you can
fight together but it not the it may be
uh it may be too
late no no no it's a
massacre
no no stop please no don't be like
that no leave them
alone oh he's building a Wonder no no he
collected all the relics okay he's
collected all the relics oh good job to
him wow wow w
w go come on guys come on do
something to
war to war no ah I'm going
down I think uh was pretty good was
pretty good I think you had a valiant
effort I had many resources but I guess
I started too late with getting an
army I guess we had the boom was nice
yeah yeah the boom was
nice now a little less so 39 villagers
is not looking uh particularly beefy
look at the disrespect this man's coming
in here with his Town
[Music]
Center I never got so far before though
so this is
great progress is indeed made shall I
retire you can say you can say GG to him
he's an AI he will will
respond so how do I check yeah you just
click enter and then
GG why he's acting like he's a real
human with his reply he sucks he sucks
he wanted my gold
how dare he even attempt such a thing
fair and Love and War as they say
as
oh what are these
things sure blame it on your ifp what's
ifp 105 one 105 you can resign again
resign come on can resign again you
resign resign again you resign resign
again I don't think he's going to resign
I think it's where are all his soldiers
did he give up on building soldiers no
his soldiers are destroying Your Castle
oh there they are oh
okay you don't got no murder holes girl
God damn it
okay we give up but we we go for a new
one we go again we we pulled ourselves
up by our bootstraps yeah I wonder if I
get out of here do you still see the the
stream I wonder
um let's
try do we see our mistakes
here um well you can see the
timeline we can probably pinpoint where
it started to go wrong
here here we got to imp a little bit
faster in the classic goth um infantry
do you know why uh Goths uh did the
strategy do you know what made it so
good uh I know they have something
special but I forgot what it was yeah so
their infantry units from the racks are
cheaper and they have a unique Tech that
makes their bear axes work like 400%
faster so wow okay maybe we uh maybe
we're lucky and don't get the Goofs next
time maybe maybe but actually that's a
that's a good point here let's install
small trees mod that's going to make it
easier for you cuz the trees right now
are really big and bushy and it's not
that we don't
appreciate
the bushes but just you
know you know I might be is that like
already like in the game cuz like
normally with mods I have to ask for
permission for each mod to use it it's
in the game it's in the game it's in the
game yeah yeah yeah where can I find it
so you go to settings the little gear
icon yeah yeah and then go to
mods perfect then you're going to go to
browse mods oh oh okay and now you're
going to search small oh the small trees
is right there is right there it's from
AOE okay if it's from AOE I think I can
use it subscribe subscribe to my channel
let's yeah and also that that's very
important yoube guys that should be fine
that should be fine also what I find
really helpful is Idol villager if you
put in Idol villager it makes a little
exclamation mark uh or the advanced idle
pointer I think it was over there um
and it just makes a little exclamation
mark so you see your Idols
easier I would have to check if I can
use
that um I'm not sure if I can use that
because uh I would have to ask first if
it's allowed it's not official so okay
well I'm sure the exclamation mark won't
cause you too many problems but you can
get that cleared and and have a note for
next time yeah uh good oh range mod oh
more more okay yeah yeah get the range
mod I I think I think it should be from
uh range is it from AE range you need to
go to the browse mod tab you're
installed
mod oh I like that it makes a circle and
then you know like if your villagers are
building in that I saw that in your
stream but um no this one's not official
ask later and then we'll we'll find out
but that's a good one there's a built-in
one for Age of Empires too like in the
graphics option but it's it's a little
it's a little bit more out there okay
okay it's like it's more bright anyway
we'll we'll worry about that later do
you want to change your little icon by
the way oh sure you
could yeah here um player icons yes
oh I I think these are the lock ones
that you don't have yet oh oh there you
go not available
oh no but you have it it's on okay oh I
earned it that's me that's me you did
that's me that's
perfect big fan okay shall we go for
another
Skirmish yes
okay I'll do you want do you want to be
Vikings or do you want to is is there
something you would recommend me to
learn cuz so far I tried a bunch of
matches with tuttons and the Vikings the
others I haven't really looked at
closely yet I think um are you
comfortable playing Cavalry cuz I think
they're easier to play as a beginner
than archers because archers you need to
be a little bit more focused on them
they can walk into a DC and then trouble
you know of course I prefer the horsey
boys horsey and I like Franks it would
be a beautiful civilization oh Franks ga
yeah check out their their resour like
their Castle on the side
sheep yeah wow um 15% and 25% in
Imperial age Cavalry plus 20% hit points
starting in feudal age so we can get
lots of Scouts maybe yeah their Mill
Technologies are free so the farm
upgrades what a deal they get food from
the berries faster
15% jeez yes what a steal throwing Xmen
is he good the throwing X-Men they're
all right we're going to try to we're
going to try to go for the boys and in
Castle we're going to try to attack with
some Knights okay all right that's oh
yeah kns Knights no problem okay should
I set theirs or should I go random just
again yeah we can go random okay
anything anything come at me bro same
map same map okay
St oh
k k
okay
Cafe Cafe Cafe yeah make it closer at
him so he doesn't have to walk so far oh
mhm
villager okay okay so Set uh keep one
goat underneath the TC and the other is
a little bit further away otherwise it's
going to be a disaster and a massacre
and then you can set the gather Point
onto the the goat the this go okay
exactly move those guys over perfect
beautiful here we go found uh the big
big animal found another
goat so goats are always like in two so
we know there's going to be another oh
no that was just your starting goat
never mind Solo solo goat yeah
okay well nice nice Carpets on the
ground
M nothing nothing where are the goats
bring another one underneath the Town
Center okay another goie perfect he's
ready to be
eaten come on yeah take him no no no no
no that one going off to why did you
they were far away okay I have to put
someone there though I guess so that
it's not like die like villager ding
ding ding
ding I thought it was far
enough that was villagers girl okay I
thought you were you you were just
hating on my
villagers so next one can make a lumber
Camp mhm gold found gold
found okay you you you Lumber
Camp perfect and now we set the gather
Point yeah exactly
beautiful so we need to find what two
more goats and then we can just Auto
Scout that with the rest make it a
little bit easier okay oh they're going
for the next one yeah there's going to
be a little bit of uh Slaughter
happening underneath the town center but
okay good good good
oh oh wait how many that's seven uh wait
they're going they're going to the
lumber Camp though right the the 11 the
new one the 11th goes for the
bo something like that we just need
three on wood and then we can put the
next one to the boar cuz we're going to
go for scalps and so food is more
important okay um grab all the villagers
to
one move the goats
away the chase the chase move I got it I
got
it oh okay now it's more now it's enough
yeah we need uh yeah yeah so we need to
take a villager to grab the boar and
another villager is going to need to
have to build a house okay need to get a
[Music]
hoose yes so villagers villagers what SC
doing maybe Auto Scout now do we have
all the auto Scout going to be a little
bit easier H another goat underneath the
Town Center mhm select all the villagers
so they go to okay I think they're all
going that one anyway so it's fine oh no
they are no no no no no you
it was not fine the narrator says it
wasn't
fine now we
have oh so many dead animals you know
what we'll cry about that later set some
of the villagers yeah to the to the uh
goat okay yes make another house okay
that Idol villager can go to the
boar oh to the boar okay yeah oh well H
that was unfortunate it was unfortunate
villager villager C them up not enough
food what do you mean set the gather set
the gather point to the berries now cuz
we want to go use that Frank bonus and
she can start building the Lum the mine
ah the mill okay
like
beautiful okay I can't I can't cute him
up though you might need a force drop
you might need to select uh the
villagers and yes yes yes now B Bo up
we're going to go 20 pop 20 20 20 20 pop
up yeah so we're going to UNC one
villager mhm and queue up Loom uhhuh and
then it's all going to be good okay okay
yes we're going to get him this time
M okay they're done with one goat at
least maybe the last goat can be brought
underneath the Town Center so they don't
have to walk that much and you're going
to need to go grab the other Rhino the
[Music]
other she will be the woman to do the
job go FAS so those villagers underneath
the Town Center just bring them to the
goat
yes
yes come on come on come on run run for
your life you don't want to be attacked
by Rhino there might need to be a little
bit of a force drop situation happening
cuz ideally as soon as Loom is
in yeah we click up so maybe the berries
can we force drop the berries can we
force drop
those trying to get up there did he do
it
okay okay we
need yeah Force drop those villagers and
then yeah yeah click Qui upy upy there
we go there we go okay yeah next time I
guess we can just make another villager
it won't be so tragic uh so your
villagers at the berries do you think
they're operating at optimal
efficiency uh no cuz one like walks
around to the other side cuz there's a
little bit of a traffic congestion true
okay
yeah will that work better
hopefully
no houses what we still have
space five more
villagers and we're researching it's all
easy have we found the enemy yet no no
he's still working on it he's probably
here any or the goats all been taken the
goats are all dead all right so we can
put those villagers onto
stragglers strag a okay yeah to the
straggler tree and then because we have
the farm for free I thought they were
done Farm you know you can if you click
all those villagers and then shift onto
that it like tasks them for the next
time when they're completed their one
they go on to the next one with the
shift key it's very very useful yes okay
queuing up the tasks oh he's faster than
me oh we forgot about our racks cuz we
want to make Scouts M build now yeah
build in now it's in the military
buildings
yes
maybe here all right those villagers
Farms that finished all on
farms you you can click uh select all
four of them and then just shift and
drop the farms and it's going to be a
little bit faster and villagers we need
to C up the villies uh uh yeah yeah yeah
okay
perfect so one villagers is going to
need to make houses cuz we're going to
want to get pop locked and then those
villagers after they finish the racks
they can make this stable uh okay uh oh
wait uh you said house house house I
make right next to
it maybe one
more
okay uh what you said wait what what you
say stable stable stable St the stable
mhm
excellent uh so I think we need to fix
your gather Point as well cuz they're in
the Town Center so we want to take them
out put them to
work okay and the the wood upgrade is
always good when you age up to get that
wood upgrade
perfect ah you're doing it no h no wait
what no I want sometimes I feel like ah
it's not working cuz I don't have enough
materials maybe yeah so um hold on I
don't think we can afford that farm
cancel the farm cancel the farm cancel
we're going to need to make another
Lumber camp at another wood line at the
back
mhm and from the stable you can make
some
Scouts
uh Lumber Camp here mhm so far yeah are
you taking the yeah set the gather point
to the lumber camp at the back it's a
little bit unfortunate that the other
wood line spawn so far back but we'll
cry about it later mhm um and I would
would have been okay too Ah that's too
forward I would recommend some Spears
and sending them to the back wood line
Spears okay yeah inide The Gather point
to the back wood line H to for them okay
yeah perfect then they'll protect those
and now we want to queue up villagers
and
Scouts
uh maybe make another Farm yeah those
can make more Farms now but remember the
scouts we are not the Scout Scouts yes
how many four five that should be fine
okay
y now with that one villager start
making some walls that yeah exactly
we're going to try to wall our base it's
going to be very ugly because there's
you don't have a nice wood line to wall
to but just try to wall it back to that
wood line at the back wood or stone oh
we only have no no no Palisade walls
Palisade walls okay H yes sorry you said
uh from where to where just here um yeah
kind of in front of that gold at the
back gold you see that one no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no so you
go from the stable to the you know
what I killed him by AC I was thinking I
was thinking more along from the stable
uh to the stone to the gold to the wood
line but we accidentally killed the
Villager no worries I was trying to
delete the the thing that I just I
thought I
built oh
he it's not okay for his family of
course but we'll say is all right that
is really bad so yeah from like like
yeah yeah something like that and then
we want to get some sort of walls down
to have something
okay what's that sound mean uh uh that
we a house or something maybe do but do
I build it through the gold yes build it
like that okay and then with those four
villagers or five villagers at the
berries uh-huh
houses houses houses thees the Beres
okay house
house you can make uh houses in between
those two wood lines and kind of wall it
off M and then you'll be uh in ah
in between those two ah you don't worry
don't worry after they build it they'll
make another
one um we have quite a few Scouts though
let's take them forward for a little bit
of a
stroll stroll perfect with was it like
something with a uh to attack everything
in the way or do uh Patrol I think I
think uh Patrol what's the patrol hcky
um e ah Q for me q
q
patrolling or maybe here yeah don't
forget to control group them and now we
don't want to have the same mistake we
did last time with the bazilian gold I
would rather so we want to make Farms
drop as many farms as you can oh okay I
think you have so many Idols right right
now look you have six idles all on
Farm I'm working on
it are here perfect yes well
excellent I guess here
okay oh okay we're at least not housed
anymore perfect that villager that's
going back make her finish that wall
yeah she's going to finish the wall to
the edge of the map it's not going to be
pretty okay we'll have a wall to the end
of the map and we'll be
happy happy happy we're going to
need to uh remember to fix that hole cuz
it was in the dark spot at some point in
time which hole the hole in the dark
spot in your Palisade walls you can just
you can you can probably fix a Rax uh
not a Rax a um blacksmith in there ooh
okay
mhm you put a blacksmith in there and
take like five of those villagers six of
those villagers from the back wood line
and spam
Farms okay wait how many is that too
many you have
seven go back seven would have been fine
as well we just need oh okay yeah uh
Farms you said Farms Farms yeah don't
forget the villagers villagers are
important
mhm should I build some around the mill
too yeah you can build them around you
can make another Mill if you want as
well and you can one of those villagers
she can build a blacksmith in between
those two palast parts mhm mhm that was
a here
blacksmith oh it fits perfectly it's a
match made in heaven
uh-oh it's the Scout just oh archers
okay archers oh we saw something
important then okay yeah Scout Scouts
are going to be fine then uh we don't
have to worry too much about the Scouts
in oh we have a scout in our base but
that means I think there's a hole in
that wood line we should probably plug
it with a
palis a hole in my Woodline is there a
hole in the Woodline here how do you get
in there that Scout I
mean maybe maybe there is here there's
no hole I'm pretty sure okay I'm not
sure but there is a probably a hole all
the way at the right of our base M so
probably we want to probably send a
villager there and and plug that off and
uhh oh what what else do we need to get
up to the new
age uh more more buildings of that type
thing right we have our we have our two
buildings right we have the stable and
the blacksmith we need another resource
gold gold so take like the villagers at
the back Woodline mhm mhm like all of
them and just put them on
gold all right uh wait uh
ah they don't I guess they all building
it no that location hurts me make at
least one space one space at least one
space please that one I I can't I I I
could let go the other why is it because
it like jams everything
up uh no it's just that gold they have a
lot of resources it's like 800 gold per
per tile um so it's
very it's fine um I think if you click
shift and comma it selects all of your
military and you can bring all your
Scouts in here or inside or or to fight
to fight we're going to want fight let's
go it's seems to be he's coming with
skirmishers and a few archers okay okay
okay okay um make some more vill Villers
villagers V make a make a tower at this
Woodline in the forward Woodline oh
they're crossbows this is looking bad
we're expecting The Archers a tower at
the wood line this
one now I think we just have to go we
just have to go off of this wood line
now you have so much wood so it's fine
let's build a market uh just to have
that uh you mean when you said off you
mean just leave like ignore we're going
to yeah we're going to evacuate this
uh further away further away they don't
want to die um oh oh they actually can't
get a tower on your gold make a tower on
your gold that's going to be really
important a tower on my gold yeah no no
no with the Villagers that are mining
the gold like take two or take two
villagers and make the
tower yes yes yes yes yeah okay and then
so that's fine bring those boys further
back okay um try to build a market so we
have that and are you walled off to the
right side uh uh I'm worry that they
come in uh well we'll see Market uh well
my they my my people were able to get
outside so maybe yes I don't know yeah
it does okay okay we'll have the tower
the tower will save the gold should be
fine uh cancel all the villagers and
click up to Castle okay oh we can and
build yeah cancel all the villagers all
all of them all of them yeah okay yes
yes yes now we need to build like two St
two more Stables we're going to have
three stable Knights and we're going to
hope for the
best you're doing fine you come you get
into Castle age you make a few Frank
Knights you're going to clean out the
skirmishers it's going to be but they
came in F they came in though next time
yeah next time we'll we can do a co-op
so you and I will both be in in in the
game but you're doing all right you just
need to hold out the two and a half
minutes until you get to Castle okay and
we're
fine uh should I get get fling for your
uh for your tower for
my blacksmith
blacksmith Y what do I do hide hide okay
bring those villagers uh in yeah to the
gold you can bring them to the gold so
you should be fine to the gold fine
where are my where am I where to the
gold yeah set all look your your Scouts
are still all alive perfect at the
blacksmith we can uh we can get the
Scout armor at the blacksmith we can get
the Scout armor scout scout the no no
that's the other one one yes yes yes
perfect F
idiot come on no
it's all right build some Stables too
we're going to need to build like two
more Stables okay uh St St stable yeah
stable yeah you can also build them a
little bit closer so your villagers
don't have to walk for glion years but
you're doing fine you're you're not
you're not that far behind don't you
worry about a thing baby
girl cut for all the military units cuz
I think I have none left uh I don't
think you have many left but it' be like
control and the comma I think
control yeah none
left okay uh cancel the scouts cuz
cancel the scouts we're going to need to
save the wood uh I mean the food for
Knights and we're going to lose that
Scout for no reason we'll cry about it
later
is deep breaths let's take let's take
care of those Idol villagers mhm it's
it's fine right all they're doing right
now is just attacking a lumber Camp who
cares we don't need that Lumber Camp
fine what we want to do with them um
we're going we can send them back to
that wood line at the back just to keep
them
working
so all right uh make another stable cuz
we're going to need another
stable okay oh just yeah and then get
the um from the blacksmith we want more
upgrades CU we can afford it okay foring
forging yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes okay we have we have some Idols in
the Town Center mhm so we're going to
need to um make Knights now that's
important and those villagers that just
popped out we don't want them to go to
their deaths so we need to send them
back to the gold put them to the gold to
Gold yeah if okay if I want to make a
castle I would need uh so make yeah we
don't need the castle just yet we need
to start making night production
going
survive you can of course you can you
can do fine control group all of your
Stables uh okay uh St
stles queue up some Knights and bring
them all to the town center and you're
going to need to Garrison your villagers
underneath the
TC so they don't
die TTT and click on the TC yes yes
beautiful okay Knights Knight we need to
make the kn
production uh okay uh uh yes yes yes
nice nice nice
perfect bring them to what about these
Idols um you can send them you can buy
some Stone and make a TC somewhere
you'll be or send them to the wood
line cuz we're going to need that
eventually I think only two I don't
think if your all of your Stables are
are control groups cuz you're making
Five Knights out of one stable oh oh
wait one yeah now now they're all
in I
think
okay okay so we're going to need to save
our villagers uh that are getting
attacked by the gold yeah so move them
move them
back uh you can put them to the Farms or
whatever I think we can make uh control
all of your uh Knights and I think we
can clean up
we can do some cleanup now with all of
our Knights so control uh or shift comma
all of those put them into a control
group control
shift yes those Five Knights they're
Frankie Knights they are about to do
some work should send them
out oh um you can yeah look he's
trickling in his Pikes so we can we have
good numbers we just need to make sure
that our Knights are fighting together
okay and then once we clean that side we
can can bring them all forward to clean
out these Spears he's even bringing the
Rams don't worry about the Rams the ram
can be cleaned out by one night easy so
let's sell some wood
like like 200 wood and buy some yes and
now we're going to make a Town
Center on some gold on we're going to
make a TC on some gold that's going to
be the goal gold can yeah we're going to
need to move the Knight
to the gold and we need to clean up this
area so we can have safe gold yeah you
can build it
there oh okay the knights are
coming in the meantime we have 11 Idols
so they need to go back to work to the
Farms okay uh wait and take those two
knights by The Stables and then bring
them back you can actually
uh Actually I don't even know if it's
worth deleting a palisade yeah they'll
just go around town you'll be fine all
is well in the hood look at your Knights
cleaning up this mess easy they did it
easy clap yeah they built so close to
me the audacity villagers villagers
villagers
okay you can yeah you can send Knights
to clean out that RAM and I'll I'll try
to
um
repair maybe the to a repair don't don't
waste your stone but what we do need to
make is a Siege Workshop we're going to
now go Siege nights
mhm we're going to make some mangels
Workshop a little bit more forward a
little bit more
forward forward forward uh stage work
forward maybe no no no like to the TC
area where they built that that TC like
in here where your two kns are my two
kns here sure outside yes delete you can
delete what Palisade uh palisad so they
don't have to go all the way
around uh what delete one pal it's fine
they'll go all the way
around I'm slow I'm slow doing it I'm
barely catching up with what you're
saying to me should I make you're doing
great we can take those Knights and cuz
right now they're not killing any units
there's really nothing to kill
underneath the TC so just move them
around maybe we can find a Woodline that
we can raid and it will be just fine how
do I how do I like um like when I when
when I don't see clearly if I have like
a farm that's not being used how do I
send one Idol to one of the Farms
without pushing away another because
there there's only like one one that can
work uh on one farm at a time right uh
yeah now it's like looking confusing
usually you see if they're idle or or
not or maybe
just it works itself out but right now
we can't really afford more Farms yeah
just I just mean like re re uh them back
to the Farms that I like just uh
evacuated before yeah if you click them
on some Farms I think they go and then
they look for the idle one really and if
you don't have one then they just stand
around and pick their nose I guess okay
yeah I think she found one all right
with these uh idle ones what were we
doing
we can make some more I I another Lumber
Camp forward we need to get a little bit
more wood you can also make one farm
would also be great to get more on gold
so that New Town Center that we built
sent that hotkey or that um gather point
to the
gold and all should be well cuz then
we'll uh increase our gold income should
she fix the pide wall
maybe you can make a gate there if you
really want to small gate
perfect oh God he's an imperial age
don't worry you have Knights Knights are
strong we just need to make more Knights
okay
uh so we need more villagers more
Knights and from the forget the manganel
we're going to make Scorpions from our
town should I send should I get rid of
them should I yeah bring them bring them
into your walls M and queue up some
scorpions scorpions I can't oh we don't
have the we don't have the gold send the
villagers to Gold okay all right all
right oh no he's going to attack my
workshop oh sorry my nights went they
let them in oh no the elephants
flashbacks
flashbacks I don't know anything about
elephants well Ellie's a fan of the
Ellies but only when you're yeah yeah
they're really really good oh it was
your own
flashbacks well no didn't you have the
bad EXP experience everyone was telling
me about the elephants no I have no bad
experiences with elephants okay that's
good to
know
uh
Ellie it's not looking good is
it but but we we lived through the
previous big rush where it looked really
bad we did that was on the one oh wait I
have I have like uh five five
nights
all do you think uh Knights are going to
do well versus the Pikeman no but that's
all I have you can you can Garrison you
can Garrison your town center they
should clean up the Pikes with relative
ease here if you could just yeah send
your villagers underneath your TC
oh so with the TC helping you out
here maybe
maybe that villager is not going to make
it is he no he he didn't he didn't make
it oh okay more elephants are coming so
right now we're not making any units we
need a we need to make a counter to
these elephants can you think of some
good counters oh yes
uh I think it
was Spearman well Spearman would be okay
but elephants are an expensive unit yeah
so usually it uh your enemy doesn't come
with like 50 elephants right usually
usually usually usually but when you're
dealing with like smallish numbers of a
very strong unit
months quite good yeah there was an
attempt that I also may have done in the
past there were just too many I guess uh
so you think I should take my idol
villagers make uh a church and make a
monk
quickly I mean this game uh I don't
wanna I don't want to be how do I this
not look good you can try for the
funsies you know what we're gonna do
we're gonna say GG
restart okay do you want to restart
because you're gonna load with the same
map and everything like that or do you
want do you want to do the co-op game
where you and I both control
I think but but if you also control then
you're helping me like directly right
you don't want the direct help you want
the uh I need to figure this out you
know I need to be able to do this okay
and you you don't want to go so you have
no trouble beating moderate AI right no
I was fine there cuz they don't rush so
early okay so we're going to need to
make our Scout Rush a little faster this
time so we know where we know where the
berries are we know that we have a
really bad Uh Wood situation all of that
we know where our opponent
is true like somewhere here I think
yeah somewhere there so we have a little
bit of an advantage now no no so the
same modus operandi got the two houses
we can try to be a little bit more
efficient with the killing of the boar
and
the yes good good good C villagers that
should be the first thing you do oh
okay so put one uh goat underneath the
town center and the other two further
away so they don't accidentally die and
now you can shift click oh yes perfect
all right all right all right okay let's
go let's
go the
berries the goat the single
goat Maybe go can you go to your options
right now actually I think you can
change your hotkeys right now yeah uh
yeah let's go to hotkeys um group
commands because I think we can do the
um uh select all Stables because we're
going to want to go for the horsey
thingy uhuh so I think it would be what
would it be in game commands
maybe no unit commands let's just kind
of go down
stable so ah stable no this is just
making the thing we need we need the one
for the buildings uh it would be in
cycle commands I think cycle commands
and then we want to say yeah uh select
all
Stables it only has go to I think it's
further down oh it doesn't go lower it
doesn't go over there's no select all
Stables no just go to maybe go to all
Stables is that not one am I blind
go
to go to go
to
stable just stable then it must be in
game commands if we scroll down a little
bit this is just going to make it easier
for when you need to oh yeah there it is
there it is select all Stables you're
gonna change
that
so uh what do you want it to be well
like it seems like every hotkey is
pretty much taken um but I I have my uh
I have my Stables bound to my scroll
wheel I just scroll I put select all
idle on my scroll wheel do you have any
side buttons on your mouse oh yeah I do
I never used you put one of the side
buttons and
then okay there you
go uhoh warning extra button clashes
with hotkey Cycles
CER no
way so we need we need to fix this
discrepancy so I never put something
there well I'm not going to use this
anyways I'm just going to clear it okay
so clear that one so we need a a group
command or the game command for select
all stables and select all Town
centers o I guess you can make select
all Town centers
H
select all
and blind TR set here H yeah you can
make it
h and then you can clear the uh go to
town center okay perfect so now H it
should make our
game this much more efficient we'll
see we'll see about that um
perfect making the sixth villager
who also goes on the
goat and then the seventh goes goat
underneath the TC one more okay and now
that we have six on sheep the next one
will go where uh uh on uh wait he will
go here uh yes make a make a camp good
good good but I can't select him and
like give him the Quee to make a camp
before he's even born can I no no no no
you can't make them build something
before they're there but it's like you
know some parents have an idea of what
their child will be doing in the future
already when they're still in the tummy
right like he will be a doctor he will
be a
lawyer could be could be the same
way something like
that okay so now they will all go to
there did we find oh hey villagers
villagers uh yeah and send that goat
back uh yeah didn't find them I guess
can the goat find it no the goat can no
no no the goat can't claim the goat uh
oh problem underneath the
TC what
oh select them all select all those
villagers yeah and then move them away
yeah yeah
ohed but we're move it a goat closer to
them uh yeah one's one's going there
okay with him I'll actually Scout the
edges so that we can see
them okay uh what was I doing what were
I doing oh yeah Villers goats yes yes
yes you can set the gather points to the
other side of the lumber Camp if you
want to be super efficient with your
villagers and then we're going to want
to get
what three on
wood uh the the bo the boore Villager
yeah C up the Villager
perfect this is the this is going to be
the yeah we need another goat underneath
the Town
Center oh I think the little vill the
little villager guy is going very far
away he him well well kind of on purpose
I thought you meant to set the Gava
point on the opposite side of the lumber
yeah I meant to like the right side of
the so you wouldn't have three villagers
otherwise they get into a little traffic
jam cuz you kind of have to micromanage
that side okay
uh oh oh they uh they went for the other
goat that's like outside yeah it's it's
okay we'll cry about that one later
we're going to need this um oh you have
that other villager she's walking very
far and this villager walking very
far to the berries to the berries send
them to the
berries yeah so C up a villager wait but
she must she must make a mill right
mhm we need get the boore and it's
looking like we're going to need to
build a house at some point in time yeah
but they're already one
two that's seven so one of them can go
get the boar right one of them can go
get the boar okay drop it off and then
get the boar uh uh uh uh
uh house house next she make
house and then she can go to berries
bore bo b I forgot about him I forgot
about him shortterm
memory you're going to need a Garrison
underneath didn't it should I
restart do you want to restart we're
totally in the game we
can I don't
know we we have to per make this perfect
we but no okay we can we can continue if
you believe in I believe okay I believe
but one more died did we lose another
villager
okay oh okay now restart now two one we
can recover this is
unacceptable
no okay villager queue up villagers
before you build the houses girl okay
okay
sorry
Mommy here go go go villagers girl I
thought I had them
K I'm F I
[Laughter]
had okay okay
okay am I a lost cause yet no no you're
doing
great you're doing great what do you
think about the p and I sent my Scout in
it's so good it looks like a PE yeah uh
what was I doing oh yeah
here the other goat go bring the other
uh exactly good good good so we got that
Idol villager bring him over to the
party you need invite welcome welcome to
the Goat Party the greatest of them
all I need to win Ellie you surely don't
have problems playing against hard AI
right it's just I'm the I'm the
barrier if only you could be my hands as
well I think the that's enough on the
wood on the food so we need to get the
wood now send the gather point to the
wood line yes good good
good villager villager villager
that's my new that's gonna be the new
uh the new s Idol oh yeah the idle TC
the police are
coming please I am
innocent I'm just I'm just
trying go bring a goat underneath the TC
perfect that villager who's not doing
anything at the wood line sen Itor work
oh work work work work work wait let me
got to see you do the work work okay
sorry we
love wow you have such a perfect eye for
this man how do you do
it all right we got three villagers on
wood so let's go grab that Bo
okay the next the next one right yeah
okay
[Music]
I was waiting for that
one all right so um here here here's
here's the it's going to be a little bit
of an ugly situation but I think you can
manage ugly really why oh wait she
didn't get it no you did
fine oh I think you clicked her to do
the the tree move away away from the
tree yes yes yes yes yes yes yes you're
fine you're
fine perfect they're going to die
they're going to die it's not looking
good for that one let's go let's go she
lives okay uh villagers grabbing berries
they need a building M mhm uh so true so
[Music]
true there's lots ofage under there
should we drop it
Bo
yes I need a wee we we alarm
Emoji okay uhoh uhoh uhoh house house
house we need to build one this is
critical who wants to be you take a
villager from the wood line uh cuz Okay
that's also fine it's just going to be a
you should make it but
we mhm mhm
okay you're fine you're fine you're
doing it okay you're doing it I think
we'll need to send two more villagers to
the berries yeah and then
okay
uh at some point in time we will also
think about getting that other
boar true maybe now okay
uh I'll send oh but she's like pretty
much dead oh yeah she's she is in
hospice okay we cannot we cannot let her
get that
boore
[Music]
okay come on come
on all right perfect it's looking
good
now
okay
all right so we want to go up with 20
pop right so we actually let's go up 19
I think we can do 19 uh let's do 19 get
Loom okay unclick a villager get loom
and you'll be good to
[Music]
gohm directly going into Loom okay as
planned
perfect okay we have an idol villager
what's what's he or she doing uh she
just built some houses but go on the
forward wood
line what to the forward wood line okay
to the forward wood line okay I think
you're going to need to queue up another
villager
one one you otherwise in one more minute
I get another weo
weoo oh that's true I think you need a
force drop though and then you should
have the food oh
okay so if you un if you Force drop and
un those villagers unclick the villagers
and click up the feud you can do
it yes perfect perfect perfect so let's
take those villagers and build a another
wood
line these ones with the
goat yeah maybe the Barry villagers they
can make another wood you can just make
it forward like make another Lumber Camp
um yeah on somewhere forward then you
have less that's closer I think not
there not there that no no no no no
yes yes yes yes oh by the way more goats
I didn't realize I had those how do I
bring them in come on
faster run
goats okay so if we want to make Scouts
what building do we need before we can
make
Scouts
Barracks yes so we can make a barrax and
we can use it as a wall from that wood
line kind of in the direction of the TC
as a wall between that's also fine okay
perfect should I only send
one yeah one villager is fine okay and
then you can build a stable um to the
left of this of this uh long wood line a
stable okay okay exactly yeah yeah
somewhere
[Music]
there
maybe maybe maybe we shouldn't be the
defensive one maybe we should be the
aggressive one yes that's what that's
what we'll do oh okay mhm prepare the
Sheep yeah bring the other town uh goat
underneath the mhm good good
good excellent so um in about two
seconds you're going to hear a we
We There we go should I build like a
house here to like finish off mhm yeah
so take uh take two villagers from that
forward wood line and and build it to
the left of that of that wood
line yes yes beautiful right there right
there right there right there sorry what
where we
building uh stable stable
okay
perfect go so we're franked we get the
farm upgrade for free but let's grab the
wood the wood okay yes mhm mm perfect oh
she's set the The Gather point to the
wood line
forward mhm cuz we're going to need to
build lots of farms so those villagers
underneath the TC grab them all and put
them on a straggler mhm MH and as soon
as you have 60 wood
Farm wa 60 as soon as I have 60 wood
farm so 60 wood okay okay yeah let's
build a couple of Scouts as well bu
couple Scout from this table using our
new hot key oh what what was it h the
side key the mouse side key side key
exactly I'll make a start I start making
Farms mhm so yeah lots and lots of
farms okay is uh let me tell you five on
food sub optimal five on food sub up
sorry I my brain is like I can't I have
to repeat what you say to actually
register it
four Scouts more
Scouts I want to use the hot keys but
like I I think I need to take it step by
step before I can we we are covering
some really good ground I'm very happy
with the progress look at the farm
placement so
good oh no you jinxed it you
jinxed doesn't look that pretty let's
let's control uh or shift comma all of
our military mhm shift the we should
have three right in three yeah or do we
just have two interesting I guess does
it like count it SE separately with the
actual Scout no the starting Scout
should get grouped in there if you shift
and then comma it should select all of
them a shift no oh it did it did okay
perfect perfect so now we can grab them
forward just bring them closer and then
we're going to go on the attack and
we're going to look for basically a wood
somewhere we can poke and
prod but let's take a look at the
economy so we're we're getting quite a
bit of wood now yeah make a few more
farms around the the mill for example
uhhuh but wait sorry I only have these
two where are the rest shouldn't there
be more the other one is a he's joining
he's uh and you said you want me to find
their Woodline yeah but let's let's wait
on that for a little like for for two
seconds I just want to balance our
economy first because I think 14 on wood
is a little is a little much and we have
two Farms that aren't being farmed at
the
moment wait let me drop off of him and
then two Farms are not being farmed this
one yeah so I think the straggler yeah
or anyone just put them and then make
some more Farms okay oh
and with you can build them around the
mill too for
example uhoh no no no we're house we're
house we house maybe one
here so we can uh we can unclick those
villagers and might as well get
wheelbarrow while we're waiting so our
TC is still wh barel
well uh but you said I have too many on
wood right so and they're almost done
with berries we want to put some Farms
there yeah well make some Farms we'll
make make more houses with that one
villager making houses shift some more
houses so hold the shift key as you
place more house foundations
down uh okay wait shift Q yeah and hold
the shift don't let go yes look at you
girl you're doing it amazing maybe one
more and then a curve yeah look at that
this is so good good you say stop stop
stop stop but we can now also do the
same thing with Farms if you take those
four villagers that just finished the
berries you can select all of them all
of them click the shift Button as you
make the uh Farm foundations and you can
put four down wait was it uh a okay look
at that hold yeah yeah make more Farms
oh no hold the shift Button as you make
them and then click click click look
look at this we've just increased the
efficiency
girlfriend let's
go I don't even have enough workers to
fill all these Farms that I just placed
it's great you have so many villagers on
wood that need not be gathering so much
wood right now um Scouts are doing some
work they're chasing that other one H
okay um we're going to still need to go
uh for a raid we're going to need to
look for some wood lines
so okay most important thing I think
take like six villagers off of the wood
drop some farms and then set the new
gather point for the Town Center to Gold
we're going to need to start Gathering
the gold we have we have our sites
plan for Castle then wait I have like
one here one
here she can go
here this one's not being worked out I
think it's
empty okay more more
more yeah gather point on TC to
[Music]
Gold okay now she will make a a mining
camp over here how about that leave one
space leave one
space it's going to be a little bit more
efficient we need to we need to increase
the efficiency here a little bit okay
perfect okay let's uh let's take a look
at our Scouts mhm um and see what
they're doing so if you can click the
one button then it'll select the third
Scout as well to join the action he's
just set to like I guess a stand ground
M um we can try to look for a Woodline
or something okay the goal here is just
not to run into his Town Center oh oh oh
oh found something that res a town
center we see the archery range so he's
going for another archery Strat uhhuh
okay let's build a blacksmith we need to
build a blacksmith blacksmith cuz we're
going to need to get the armor for the
for the them like running around yeah
you can just attack one of the villagers
there just Pok and P you're you're going
to get the V kill look at but he didn't
even follow even though I chose all of
them that's weird uh he should be
joining
okay look at that look at that you're
killing him you say what did you say I
already forgot what did you say about
what was I making a blacksmith a
blacksmith there's that villager at the
bottom the Villager at the bottom uh who
built all those
houses she can build a uh mining
blacksmith and a market there as well
you can ship you can shift a market just
to have that cuz you have the wood for
it blacksmith first blacksmith yeah yes
yes yes okay okay perfect so your TC
gather point they're going to die is
that okay okay so we see archers and
skirms he still didn't go he's still not
coming out to attack you so you're all
right for now should I make more
Scouts if he's not attacking you don't
really need you can you have the food
for it sure make some more Scouts for
some defense okay blacksmith build oh is
it a lumber camp on gold oh it is a
Lumber
no I think I made a mistake when I like
like repositioned it or so okay we'll
just delete that and build a mining camp
and then once our Market is built we can
sell some of our food and click up the
castle and then
we'll we'll be
fine
uh what's the idol doing the idol is oh
she was confused as to what to do she's
helping
out we we
him oh do you speak
French I I speak French too totally
oh uh
qule do you know the qule mean french
fries french
toast wait
oh I win I'm taking the next train to
Austria oh right I mean we're close
we're neighbors we're our countries are
touching and with a little bit of luck
on my side maybe we can touch
too all right girl I'm those villagers
let's Advance our bodies into the castle
age okay okay but what do I do with this
idle
one she can build another stable another
St wow another another one you can build
three stables for okay uh so two you
have the one that you built perfect
build no no no no no no no no no that's
that's good let's get some um let's get
some armor on our on our horsey boys
True
blacksmith the um
oh this one
yes that's it that's all we want he's
already can it don't worry you'll be
Castle AG soon you'll be fine did you
want finish your walls because that big
space from that wood line to the edge of
the map on the right hand side is quite
easy to wall so if you can
send what no a villager there maybe food
because we already have so much food she
could do it yeah yeah she can do it cuzz
I think we're going to want to build two
Town
centers okay so we want to save uh yes
yes yes
perfect Scout is inside
alarm all right is he just scouting or
is he attacking he's just
scouting uh uh what say about this pause
pause pause pause pause okay so you need
gold to make night production yeah
that's very important so we want to
build a tower where do you think is a
good place to build a tower show me with
the mouse before you do it like
here um that's a little bit more risky
because they're going to be within range
of the building like while I'm building
it you mean you want to make it a little
bit behind so it has more chance of
going up so if you take all of those
villagers on gold and build a tower
uh yeah like there with a little bit of
luck it'll go up and then you'll still
have um I don't think we need with a
little bit of luck you it'll be fine
let's get Fletching Fletching is going
to be important now from the
blacksmith FL flet
Fletching
[Music]
mhm okay the Army uh the scouts are
doing something there's some Pikes there
now okay queue up as many Knights as you
can from your two uh thingies from your
two
Stables KN oh I I can't oh you're not in
Castle yet sorry not quiet almost I
thought I thought I heard the castle gar
put them back on gold they should no no
no the further one away the further one
away ah the further one yeah like the
the the tile that's a little bit further
away Oh you mean like here okay yeah
maybe make a lumber a mining camp on the
other side if you can cuz there're going
to they're going to be very close so if
we're lucky he'll he'll run away you
think so because of the tower all right
the power and Fletching is going to be
in so they're going to be a little bit
stronger yes that one no no one house
space
beautiful so if you have some really
weak villagers move them away those two
girls I'm seeing them they're they're
going to be in the afterlife very soon
okay this is looking bad but it's not
that bad you can also just put them in
into the TC for a little bit you still
have the gold to make your Knights so
you're all
right Garrison Garrison underneath your
town center okay cuz the TC is going to
help out as well you have Fletching now
so it's more powerful we just want to M
minimize casualties as much as we can
okay yes okay oh we're castling oh
they're running I think they're running
away queue up queue up the
knights we need them wait uh also but
that's that's gonna be a lot to keep in
mind
so where St um okay okay UNC two knights
from one stable and queue them up in the
other okay
uh this
one yes good good good good didn't
blacksmith from the blacksmith can
we get the armor upgrade
um no we can't afford it that's fine uh
hold on
pause out time out so right now you have
a big army in your base yeah what do you
think is gonna happen if you send one
Knight or two knights he's gonna die
they're gonna die so we do not want to
trickle our units in this very very bad
so set the gather point for the both
Stables to be inside the stable and once
we have like six or so nights
we can try to Ambush the
enemy
okay okay is that for the other stable
too oh I thought so yeah um cuz you have
to yeah you have to set the The Gather
point in yes yes good good good good
good let's keep it like that um at the
market let's sell a little bit of food
cuz we have a lot of food and buy Stone
and up more Knights and que up more
Villers
we we
we we yeah get that TC Rolling Girl
really even now yeah keep the TC rolling
set the gather point on a wood line or
something we need more gold I think
there is another gold uh that can
possibly be
taken in front of our stable there oh
but I I don't know if want to go there
now you're little if okay okay well when
you make when you have like six seven
Knights um sell enough resources so you
can afford the armor for your Knights
that's going to be really important to
get that armor okay uh like 400
food we we sell 400 food yeah selling
400 food okay and now go get the armor
at the
blacksmith
perfect perfect queue up some some
knights from your other stable
M you're only queuing up from one use
your hot
key um but like it goes to both
so okay now it's working that's working
okay all right so we need to fix our
economy those 19 villagers in in in the
the idle World um they can go back to a
Woodline they just need to be working
right now and we can worry about what
they're doing later they're all going to
be going forward into their death that's
suboptimal so select them and then send
them to a back wood line okay where
there is no camp but I shall make one
yeah okay um when like the right Camp
yeah yeah that's that's fine okay okay I
think we have a pretty good
army okay if you say if you uh if you
bring the Army from the stable that's
further away out first
mhm uh bring them closer then eject the
ones from the yeah so that's so they're
fighting together you should be fine
okay Ellie it's fine thank you fine
thank you for trying to sa doing it okay
okay get get them out get them out get
them out and attack attack let's go yes
yes yes yes yes oh but they were about
to leave anyway or is it their reaction
to my KN now we need to set The Gather
point for those Town Center back to the
gold because that's important so back to
the gold we need to now worry about
fixing the problems but the knights are
doing the job that they needed to be
doing clean up cre aisle four is
happening look at this control group uh
all of your Knights so they're in one
control group and then bring them all
forward so they're fighting together
look they're going to kill that they're
going to kill this villager you know
that there was that wood line that they
had so we can go back to check out the
place also
we okay so like uh we need like all of
these I have
so I don't know what to do with all of
them they're all like everywhere
and take one villager Bring It Forward
uh we're going to build a Siege
Workshop okay Siege Workshop M oh no no
no no forward forward forward a little
bit more forward what does forward mean
where your Knights are where your
Knights are okay forward I mean like
closer to the enemy okay we'll just make
it right next and extend my wall do I
want to bring my Knights back your
Knights uh are doing really good work
here you can bring that other Knight
that's just kind of standing in the
middle of the field to attack those
crossbows okay and uh you're in a pretty
good
position look at that
amazing they're doing it okay I should
probably not be pausing so much but I
cannot think otherwise also I have so
much Idol here uh maybe get the gold
upgrade the Gold Mining upgrade cuz
we're kind of gold is a we're struggling
here so to make uh to make Siege what
resource they do the units
cost
uh I don't know question may it's gold
and wood oh okay yeah golden wood and we
are trouble we have some troubles with
the gold income right now so getting
that gold R upgrade is going to be quite
helpful for us and speaking of upgrades
did we get the wood upgrade yeah I think
so let me check we got the feudal one
get that second one okay okay make more
Knights cuz we don't want to stop making
armor uh Army uh-huh more kns more kns
mhm don't forget to use your hot key so
you're using both uh stables and now go
to the wood line uh and see what you can
find here like take them around to that
wood line that's probably long gone but
we want to keep the aggression yeah see
maybe we get some more villager kills
here perfect perfect from the from the
siege Workshop he had lots of Pikes last
time so let's make some scorpions yeah
let's make some scorpions mhm mhm and
keep them in The Siege War
shop go go back go back save run away
take your knight run away run away you
are a knight so you are faster than a
Pikeman so you can just run away you
don't have to die okay we're we're done
fighting now yeah yeah take them further
away oh well tragic okay make some more
scorpions
mhm okay
[Music]
perfect come on come on no no what do I
do what do I do okay keep your scorpions
uh garrisoned in The Siege Workshop okay
uh can
they
what te cuz the Scorpion is going to die
uh we need to have a big mass and they
need to be uh like The Gather point
should be inside The Siege Workshop so
it's going to be the same thing once we
have a nice Army of scorpions we can
take them out at the same time with
support of the knights and they can
clear out okay a lot of good stuff but I
I you're to lose that can't you can't
bring them in once they're out no no not
not for um those units okay you can't
even Garrison them in the castle it's
very sad but it's just just three
pikemen the tower will take care of it
no worries in the meantime let's get
let's get some more villagers queued up
from the the Town Center
mhm wait uh maybe
we okay
excellent let me fix these uh can is
this like reable yeah yeah yeah I mean
okay Garrison the villagers underneath
your TC to get rid of those two Pikeman
oh cuz you don't want to lose them be
very tragic and uh you should be good so
more v um more villagers more Knights
more scorpions army army army more
scorpions more Scorpions so scorpions
are against these Pik men right mhm okay
there yeah they do Pierce damage so
they're going to like if you have a
group of Pikeman then they're going to
damage not just one but like all of them
behind it's quite nice okay I guess I
still have my gab point on the gold
should I change that's fine we need we
need gold we need gold so it's okay uh
let's make some more Knights though so
we're not making Knights
[Music]
uh when I select the stable like that
where I have both and then create a
knight does it like split it between the
two yes oh
okay okay he's going right now we we've
been on one town center right so we are
our villager count is not that good
which means we have to do damage so
let's send our army forward like let's
bring it all in one place and see what
we're working with and maybe you can
send some villagers to castles to Stone
and then we can drop a forward
Castle okay okay so set the gather point
from the Town Center to Stone
uh yeah the new gather point to Stone
and then we'll start collecting those
resources and we should be fine well I
found my oh there it is that's
my I I'll use all the five Idol ones
that I have now for the go uh for the
stone
no sure but we also want to go back on
the farms true that's
important where are all these Idol ones
that I just selected look at
her she's building something here again
he wants your resources what the hell
this lady do I have any
military yeah in your Stables oh yeah I
even
have
all right we do not accept
this it's unacceptable oh she they even
brought two unreal you have another
stable that's probably closer so you can
UNG Garrison from that stable as well
mhm on the other a second mining camp
two wow okay he
died
unreal okay let's let's take a look at
our okay we we we
uh
okay good good good let's make uh yeah I
think we have a good army we got to be
fighting with the army so let's take the
Scorpions Make more Scorpions Make more
Knights and keep bringing them forward
we're on we're on the the offensive now
okay they really did
dead they don't need to waste time
attacking the mining camp okay them
forward more Knights more night
production set the gather point forward
and get those scorpions out as well and
make sure the gather point for the
Scorpions is forward as well uhoh he's
an imperial oh yeah we also have to
finish we have to finish our mining camp
for the stone otherwise it's a very far
way to go Town Center
yeah
okay okay they got it they got
it oh
uh they're all here now right all the
grab Point here gra Point here should
iar you can make an oh you you should be
fine to defend here this is a nice Army
what I'd recommend is is getting more
upgrades from the blacksmith for your
for your Knights so get
forging yes yes good good good and build
a
monastery
mm wait what are
H can I like set them to just stop doing
that like no no they can just they can
clean the yeah yeah it's fine they're
just attacking the the mining who who
shall I take off of work just uh one
villager off of gold
okay should we add it to the protection
line here here yeah yeah that's fine
okay mhm a beautiful night nice Church
to make some beautiful monks
hopefully yeah so actually if you UNC
some of the Scorpions we can also click
up to Imperial after that Monastery
comes up all right I I'll just leave
this one but take one night forward and
Scout what your enemy is doing okay just
to get some insight
also or can we go up to imp is the
monastery built no not yet okay so we
okay uh but um uh we look around here
mhm are we looking for
enemies yeah we're looking what he's
doing if he's going to come with lots of
Siege um it looks like yeah he's got
he's got lots of oh the okay the Pikes
are the halers now don't bring him back
take that Knight and bring him to
another corner of the map just so the
Army don't bring him to your home that's
not good true so he's got halers and
elephants let's let's click up to imp
okay perfect perfect make more Knights
make more
scorpions we're going to make scorpions
it's okay it's just one night he's just
one night he's faster than the elephants
he's faster than the halad
deers okay send them Far Far Away make
another Siege Workshop uh okay
uh
sieg
mhm should I make perfect more make a
couple of monks too we can use them to
heal up our army and grab all of the
army that you have here and bring them
forward like so they're in front of your
base cuz we're going to need to be
defending very
soon you you have some in your Stables
that are not coming out we're also not
making any more army units which is not
ideal husbandry pick up husbandry we'll
be a little bit faster with our Scouts
uh with our Knights husband it's all
good all coming to plan maybe we make a
castle he yeah sounds good also in the
line in the same
line uh or more forward I can make it
more I don't know if it's going to get
up if it's more forward make it kind of
defensively on your gold
okay I'll I'll add
I'll
one so select all your Stables that
beautiful mouse hotkey that we set up
mhm more nights and For the Love of All
that's good and holy please send more
than one villager to make that castle
hey i s two oh they also sending
villagers yeah well one villager the
scor Scorpions can take care of her or
you can just send one Knight to kill her
she's a G oh wait look what they have
here a staple right there m can I make a
Ram or do you think the Scorpions can
destroy it oh no scorpions aren't really
good at destroying houses but the castle
will go up and clean it up uh we are
house by the way so the castle will
provide us 20 population space but
that's far time away from us so uh shift
shift click like 20 houses girl 20 house
house house house yeah just a gazillion
houses you have so much
wood oh he's coming with an army again
let's look at the Army bring uh oh
delete one of the houses I know this is
sad cuz we're House pop delete one of
the houses um in front of the in front
of the stone oh and then bring those
Knights forward you don't want to lose
all those scorpions it' be a tragedy
that way they don't have to run all the
way around and bring the knights in
bring the knights in yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes
yes okay okay there's a hole between the
market and the other place we just leave
that house for no
reason be tragic okay um night numbers
make the gather Point by your castle and
if you're if we're lucky the castle does
go up at some point in time uh Knight
gather Point by my castle okay we have
monks available convert the elephants
convert the elephants uh okay you can
just right click on on a on a monk on a
unit and you don't yes yes yes oh it
works pretty fast what the hell we woo
two conversions that's value okay send
like five more villagers from the gold
to finish building that castle it needs
to go
up okay yes yes yes perfect the knights
can uh can clean up these scorpions with
ease so don't worry about it scorpions
are going to struggle versus the knights
but we need to be making more KN oh no
he's killing my he killed my mon I make
you he killed also my
elephant
well okay how much percent is the
castle uh almost okay yeah yeah it's
going up it's going up you're doing fine
okay perfect kill the elephant
we
whe well it could have converted can
also get uh maybe we can also pick up
town watch at some some point in time
just so we have better visibility cuz
right now I feel like it's all a little
let's we're Franks our castles are so
cheap all the villagers that just
finished that stone pile bring them
forward and we're going to make a little
bit of a of a castle tower rush if you
will oh okay another castle Yeah so all
those villagers select all of them not
just four all of those V yes yes yes yes
and then bring them forward um and try
to drop it kind of I don't
know somewhere close by but also a
little bit more forward somewhere close
by but also okay okay
[Music]
okay here
sure oh it's in dangerous territory so
we we have to keep making more
scorpions you know what I'm I'm kind of
questioning the location of this Castle
right now maybe delete the
foundation uh maybe a little bit more
back so it's in front of the siege
Workshop in the market and that way it
can support from
behind the hill on the left does look
good but uh I I think this one is more
is is
safer let's get the monks forward
there's uh elephants there that look
very nice to convert and we need for the
love of all that's good and holy more
Scorpions from both
Siege
scorpion oh yes
no could that you're doing fine Your
Castle is going to go up and it's going
to defend you and uh did it you're going
to be all right just keep making more
army and right now you have seven
scorpions coming out of one Siege
Workshop when you've got two Siege
Workshop ohar
okay bring the gather point in between
the two castles and then they will
defend okay you'll be
great
[Music]
and those villagers that just finished
building the castle they can go on a
mining camp on the gold in between the
castles they'll be very safe oh okay
okay I make small mining camp here yes
perfect I think if you do uh shift
period you call uh you select all the
idols so it's a little bit easier for
you shift period right now all of his
uh are going to die to the castles but
we want to increase the range of the
castles so what upgrade do we need to
get oh uh wasn't there one of the
blacksmith yes
so this this one Bingo mhm mm I remember
oh is this working
out are they bringing it uh okay
um o o well we need to be making uh we
need to be making more units i'
recommend some more Knights that we'll
want to upgrade to cavaliere at some
point in time
okay uh you can Garrison the villagers
right now underneath the town Cent or
into the castle cuz they they're going
to clean up the the Scorpions with ease
okay okay should be
fine
oh no what what what did I do what did I
do what did I do
uh okay she
died it's okay I need something like
murder holes I guess um well the two
castles are kind of Defending each other
so you're all right okay he just going
to be trickling in and using his
resources so we have 10 villagers that
are idling
mhm okay at this point in time let's
just build Town
centers one uh uh to the to the right
you have that gold just build a TC there
wait where was TC oh here yeah to the
right we have the gold here yeah right
there perfect yes yes yes yes and then
um take some more villagers and build
them on another wood line somewhere well
when I select them now it's the ones
that are in the castle right yeah leave
those in the castle for now cuz they're
going to go back to the gold eventually
um so take some villagers off of uh or
you know what you can do also you can
take some villagers off of wood because
you have a lot of it and build a TC
somewhere in like up north um and then
build farms around it cuz we need more
food okay a TC around here yeah so build
the TC and then click shift and the
farms around it as well you'll figure it
out
um
[Music]
Farms that is amazing look you go so
efficient too but are we not
dying they brought elephants
again I have a little scorpion there's
just a couple of ones just a couple ones
you're fine you're fine so we they went
through didn't they delete that so
that so that we could SS out two
elephants it's okay we're going to make
a couple more Knights yeah so we want
food and gold that's really
important yeah we'll have to work our
way to so right now um between the
castles is it safe to go out to grab
gold
uh yeah yeah MH
okay but they're probably going to get
[Music]
attacked
no we can make another Monk and then see
if we can convert them cuz right now
he's what he's doing right now is he's
trickling them in like so those
scorpions I mean yeah they're nice
scorpions but like he's just how many C
how many has he lost to our castles I
don't
know okay maybe we do have to
vacate vate yeah like those villagers
because right now they're not doing
anything um we can send them to make a
Mill and then farms around a mill
further back make a Mill Farms around
the back okay or to the stone for
example just so they're doing something
and collecting some sort of resources
okay oh no
go over there and
[Music]
then what they bringing in the elephants
to the monk is going to come out very
soon so let's see if we can get a
conversion and we need to make more
Knights right now Knights are really
important okay cuz we need something to
defend ourselves Knights have really
good Mobility Knights
Knights at some point we'll want to get
the Cavalier upgrade for sure okay yeah
I think that monk should be able to
convert one of the elephants for God's
sake please please so slow should I like
move them over here yeah bring him
closer to the monk so the monk can
convert uh one of the elh
the score is not that far off like
look at you're doing
well really oh he converted an alley you
go get the other one too very nice can
you why can't I get the other one does
he have like a cool down until he can
convert again or yeah yeah monks have a
cool down when they convert you have to
wait a a little while
longer but okay let's make another town
center because right now we want a boom
our villager count 41
trash we we can we're going to try to
build like three more TCS they have to
be on flat ground you can't build it on
them yeah build it over there and then
we'll just make farms around it and make
another make another town center
um maybe on a gold somewhere further out
just so you expand a little bit okay uh
by the way there's like a couple Knights
here do we want to hide them back again
like yeah you can put them in the in the
castles for now okay so we just need to
spread out
everywhere so look on the on the mini
map like can you can you scroll a little
bit more to the left side or to the
right side sorry uh yeah yeah on that
gold build a TC in between that gold and
the wood line
okay I deal with more than one person
yeah take like
four three that's fine okay
perfect off we go to the gold right yeah
q and then yes perfect perfect a little
bit more to the left yes yes yes perfect
okay okay so we we
[Music]
we we need uh get that monk to convert
an elephant I was I was trying to but
you have two monks and I think if they
can convert some of the healthier
elephants you should be in a really good
position uh where's the other you see
you see the two monks one's walking
behind and one is
healing uh ah perfect oh you have this
yeah yeah yeah so if you if you set two
monks to convert one unit they convert
it faster but I would oh my got him oh
we still have the the monk juice left
for another conversion
maybe this one this
one convert convert convert and then the
elephant can be used to kind of attack
the Scorpions do we have
um uh Frank don't get bracer actually so
I think we got Bodkin so that's good
we need more scorpions of our own to
deal with the halad or actually what am
I saying uh we're Franks throwing axemen
our unique unit from the castle as a
bonus versus uh versus halers so just
make a whole bunch of them okay well I'm
keeping them in the castle for now yeah
yeah of course keep them in the castle
also you're only making out of one one
castle and you have two
so uh there why they're all elepant
always taking back my elephant by
killing them don't worry your castles
are doing such great work right now yeah
let's focus on adding more villagers so
we we
we make another TC further away from
this base take those two villagers
standing there picking their noses and
build a
TC even further to the left by the
blacksmith those two
villagers uh Sor sorry what what what
what those two villagers by the
blacksmith these ones okay send them so
far to the
left not not there not there left of the
map
Oh that's oh right sorry the other
left the other
left on the wood line on the wood line
or on the stone just get more resources
okay all right okay so those villagers
up in the north that are on the wood
line put them all on fire arms
[Music]
mhm wait though which which
ones which what
lines you mean these these ones yeah
yeah those ones exactly select them all
and put them onto a uh onto Farms so
shift farm farm farm uh
okay okay perfect
so hopefully that's enough yeah I think
they're going to start tasking it after
they finish the farm or the wood but
whatever uh don't worry your castles are
killing are actually calm right now I I
appreciate this
moment you're doing well so let's uh
take care of the idol situation do we
have six Idol villagers we do yeah why
why
[Music]
uh what what what what do we do with
them more make another town center
another town center another town
center make it on that wood wood line
you can make it on any neutral resources
literally anywhere it doesn't
matter perfect get some so we have we
need to be spamming the V the Villager
okay to be they're back again they
killed my they're back again try to get
the
conversion don't worry your castles here
are going to be fine they're buying us
whole time these two castles are
literally
MVPs but we
we uh
uh more more more more not just one1
more more max that more is it actually
like working do have the food for it
okay now we need to make get Cavalier
Cavalier Cavalier from the
stable uh St St stay stable stable St St
St St stable St stable yes perfect
Cavalier yes yes yes can you get
conscription for me as well from the
castle and that's going to make our
stable units go faster um yeah no yeah
the coin the coin okay all right try to
get a monk to convert an elephant
uh
wait you can take out the you can take
out the throwing axemen you have in the
castles oh oopsie uh
okay are they good against elephants
they're not good against elephants nor
are they good against scorpions but
they're very good versus the
halad
okay well the elephants are pretty much
dying anyway he didn't want to do the
convention I guess he's on the cool down
when there's the white bar here yeah
yeah exactly so let's go to the
blacksmith and get more upgrades for our
um for our Knights for the Infantry
units and the attack as
well okay uh this top row basically we
want all of it okay need oh wait I ran
out of food wow yeah we have 20 idle
villagers they can all build farms okay
20 idle
okay perfect look at that you guys are
so much better at the farm
placement well if you go back and watch
the first game where you were like one
by one oh also we're going to be moments
away from
[Music]
we I don't have the food
oh he actually like killed
oh come on get this elephant please
please please please please it' be a
nice conversion to get yeah
yes yes oh now he healing him yeah yeah
yeah yeah oh yeah I destroy that shitty
building
finally yo I can't believe this AI is
just losing so many scorpions but okay
okay okay all of these guys will make
Farms okay uh
this is this is a comeback waiting to be
had wait wait give me a moment give me a
moment need
to okay oh more more that sound you you
don't have the food for it so mind okay
we need to we need to now the 27
villagers they need to be making Farms
or something because we need to make
military we need to be making our um
scorpions and we need to be making our
Cavaliers because this is getting a a
little as we say
dicey do you have any uh units get get
them out get them out and try to convert
try to convert an elephant or
something okay I don't know if I have
anything you're still fine you're still
fine I feel like I I'm running out of
units so I have like
nothing yeah so we have 21 idle
villagers we need to put them all to
work
um
the castles are still
cleaning still doing all right honestly
I think building these two castles was
the best thing oh was quite yeah quite
smart and hindsight we really needed
them um but yeah yeah my all my holy
why do I have so much Idol like
okay no no no you're look at like you're
doing all right it's just because we
built a lot of town centers and we
didn't set a hot like a gather Point
yeah that's that's why so we're going to
need to set gather point
points
points well I guess on the
wood on the
stone on the
gold more
gold here we have some oh yeah oh look
at all
them you can make a a lumber camp and
then they could all go on the lumber
Camp oh
Lumber perfect uh what's happening is
this okay okay your castles here are
going to be fine for for a little while
longer I need though I need units we
need units exactly
so let's queue up some Knights Knights
Knights Knights Knights Knights or some
Cavalier oh yeah now they're Cavaliers
oo fan
[Music]
mhm oh my God these castles are
amazing mhm okay we don't need to look
at that that fight happening the castles
will try to take care of themselves but
if you could somehow manage to build a
third Castle in its vicinity I think
that's too risky we have no armor mind
let's try I want to try TR to get those
14 villagers all to build Farm Farms
Farms
[Music]
okay uh
okay oh where's that Knight coming
from uh C up also we want some scorpions
of our own okay uh scor
scor
scorp okay
very good very good very good um he's
killing the elephant let's go look the
Army is retreating good good good good C
are so sexy they are very very good okay
okay they're now uh oh this is a problem
no longer pushing the castles he's going
to be pushing elsewhere so we need to
make um a castle uh if I mean he's going
to be just attacking houses so I would
build a castle where that idle villager
is okay with hopefully more than just
one villager please take like take like
seven villagers from those farms and uh
build a
castle the hole in the house is kind of
triggering yeah yeah you know what yeah
the castle will go up and all will be
well the castles right now are are
working overtime do we have any months I
don't think
so no I don't have any it's
fine make some uh throwing axe
from the we just need some sort of
units yeah
B ah they're coming in oh they're
attacking my
people I mean the score like this is I
feel like this is all he has I feel like
there's not much else and like the
castles are about to clean up like a
gazillion worth of gold for those
Scorpions so like look
you
get your army uh get your Army on those
elephants maybe if we have a monk we can
bring them in there like you'll be fine
we just need to get this Castle up so
send more villagers to build the castle
uh and you'll be fine wait wait send you
my Army my Army no no no villagers to
build the the
castle so select like all of those
villagers that you see on the screen
there and just send it to build that
castle we need to get it up M some of
you may die but it's a
sacrifice can they get
there we still have 103 villagers we're
fine
okay oh no come on yeah it's
there okay let's build a university okay
with some idle villagers um and then
we'll work on getting some University
upgrades mhm it doesn't have to be like
anywhere close to thetion right anywhere
else it doesn't really
matter okay I want to point out that the
score is like neck and neck true true
you you're you're holding you're holding
unbelievably like this whole time I want
to give up
though it looks bad but you like that
castle now that the middle Castle is
Fallen though it it's going to be like
once that falls it's going to be a
little bit more of a it's going to be a
little bit more dicey um I would
send lots of villagers to repair I feel
like we're at that point in time now
where we want to repair so like take all
the villagers on the up up north a
little go up up up up up up up on the
wood line all of those villagers at the
wood line and bring them to repair okay
one second just this uh
[Music]
or
okay and don't forget make more Cavalier
like make more Stables make more
Cavalier repair that castle and uh make
more
too more more more more more yes okay
good good good all those 19 villagers
that you have idle Farms girl you taking
the score lead you'll build the Farms
you'll build the army take this
game um wait ah they're all like coming
one by one I realize because I have them
um set to gather here
here it's probably not good but I maybe
at least they can kind of defend like
the that's fine are supporting so you
you'll be fine bring the monk monk that
you have up north try to convert an
elephant
yeah only they weren't so I have can I
like give them monk
speed the the monk speed that's a
fervor can I give that to them uh yeah
do do we have it in the tech tree yeah
yeah F I just clicked it I was just
wondering if it's something you think is
worth investing yeah yeah I mean we
don't have too many monks but we have
resources we can afford it okay 32 Idols
not ideal
suboptimal Farms Farms bring a Mill
Farms all around uh send the gather one
of the TCS to those uh or actually I
think we have in that castle some
villagers we can Ungar those right uh
yeah there's
yeah and work
perfect okay your two castles are about
to demolish these scorpions like look at
this look at this oh it's a Slaughter I
hope they can make it in time for repair
they're almost
there but like who's going to protect
them from the blacksmith can you get uh
more armor for your
Knights yeah get the final armor this
one armor armor armor oh yeah get that
get get that and get the armor too click
yes perfect perfect this one too
infantry oh you can get the Infantry
armor it doesn't really matter you can
afford it okay wow okay look at that
wait I sent way too many you s way too
many girl we got to get back uh we got
to get back on our food department
because we want to make more Cavaliers
that's food and gold gold and food and
there's a little bit of red uh on on the
mini map that I see oh so I'm not quite
sure oh oh they want to farm my wood
okay it's just one we can we can let
that be okay well all these that I sent
here
now uh I can bring them back to Wood
here um yeah you can bring them just so
they're working and then we can figure
it out you can also send like 10 onto
Stone okay it'll be
fine you're fine just don't stop stop
making
villagers cuz you're you're
um and
kns mhm and you should be
fine okay make more Stables can you take
um yeah
okay where just here so like there yeah
make like five of stables five five
Stables sh is going all in oops five
yeah make
them you're only making one we need we
need the foundations of the other ones
oh and then we're going to go for leav
and then we're going to start raiding
his base because uh this is
getting oh we're being too defensive
right now yeah drop two more drop two
more you're fine you're fine can you
pick up the light C upgrade
uh yep perfect
all again with they can help don't worry
don't worry we'll sort that out
later then they can spread their work
and they'll be done at some point can
you pick up murder holes from the
University that you built you built it
to the to the right
yeah oh there it is murder murder holes
yeah also get ballistics and also get
chemistry
ballistics chemistry all of it perfect
okay perfect wow this is still
standing and and and we once again
defeated one of their waves yeah
so do I still have a
monk sorry what did you say um actually
those eight villagers make Farms with
them we want to have like 50 Farms
[Music]
okay oh
oh uh I'm I'm confused uh
uh you send one one Cavalier to clean
out those three villagers it's very
disrespectful one Cav sending those
villagers so close to you oh okay
where where are my oh those don't go
there you you go clear this okay
perfect okay those 24 villagers we need
to oh the throwing axemen are coming out
send them for I forgot about
them can we check the blacksmith um I
think we're missing some infantry armor
uh
yeah perfect just get everything
everything all right all right go axan
go
go do we need more scorpions by the way
or anything SI Siege Workshop stuff um
we need there's there's that stone that
you have up north right cuz I think we
can take between those 25 idle villagers
we can put some on this gold that we
have in between the castles and then
some on the stone that we have here so
you can take actually all those
villagers from the wood and these Idol
villagers here by the stables and send
them between the the stone and the and
the gold
and then we can drop a forward Castle
cuz it looks like we can be on the
offensive now between the stone and the
gold only the
stone yeah no so on the stone and I'm
saying the villagers that you have you
can put them spread them between the
idle villagers between the stone and the
gold Oh Oh I thought you wanted me to
take them off of the
no back to Wood no on the stone you have
a lot of wood right now so it's okay
yeah what's going
on in
it can you convert
this how much does the Paladin upgrade
cost from the stable we wait Paladin
Paladin Paladin from the stable Paladin
from the
stable too much right now 7 okay sell
some sell some wood we don't need wood
right now okay get Paladin actually how
many how many Cavaliers do we have I
don't even think we have enough
Cavaliers so I make more Cavaliers and
we'll worry about upgrades later we need
army army army
army should I send them back or keep
them on the offensive um make one treb
and then you can move with that treb
forward okay you should be fine ah Tri
was Castle right oh yeah I need more
more
gold okay we have lots of it we need to
fix them I'll make two so those 33 34
um just control control period and bring
them all to the gold in between the
castles and we'll worry about
Distributing them later all of
them wa which between the cast ah this
one okay yes good good
good
perfo I like this okay
um now we're we're kind of don't have
gold right now but can you select all of
your stables and queue up like all light
cap and send the gather point to be deep
in his
base okay deep yeah okay deeper
deeper here
yeah and just like C the light C until
you have no more food okay
perfect more and more I think if you
click shift uh If We Hold shift then it
goes like by fives or something like
that okay good good good good good so
bring your bring your thoring axman back
so they're between the castles cuz
they're going to try to save you from
the uh from the incoming H be mhm now
there's a lot of congestion with your
gold here so you can make another mining
camp on the other side of that gold pile
to be a little bit more
efficient Ellie I'm losing it
you're doing so are we gonna win soon
it's looking good for you if you if you
can now start coming with your siege and
bombarding his production
buildings be golden girl okay um uh
so what well wh what are we doing
sorry what did you just just say number
one take like five bills and make a a
mining camp on the other side of the
goal to make it a little bit more
efficient
okay
uh mining like with one space yes yes
one space to give them a little bit of
extra room
Perfect all
right look on the map are there any more
neutral Golds that you see on the mini
map if you go exploring like somewhat
close by not if they're far away just
got to be not in his
base I don't see anything see them okay
I would then control shift all or
control um period all of your idols and
build another Lumber Camp a lumber Camp
yeah build another Lumber camp and then
see you you have uh you see that there's
opponent's villagers there so you can
send um the L Cav to the wood line and
you'll be fine okay um is here okay yes
it's
fine okay just one light C maybe does
the trick I guess I think you have some
Knights that are hanging H and out doing
nothing on on your on the right that you
sent earlier oh there's a castle so send
the two trebs to the castle castle
castle oh this one
oh Castle mhm looks so nice oh so
basically right now your L Cav are
distracting him and he's going to try to
clean that up um now make your gather
point for your army by your trebs like
for from The Stables um cuz they're
going to want you're going to want to
defend these trebs now wa how do I
select all all AR all Army no no no no
no not not all Army uh your Stables so
your gather point for the Stables is
going to be by the trebs now okay okay
perfect you join fun have fun okay okay
looking looking good we're we're not oh
he's trying to do some stuff here I he
got one of my
Cavaliers but we got him we got his monk
we'll that one later it's fine uh more
light C more uh more Cavaliers
more everything there's a lot of
villagers there that aren't doing
anything please send them what the
why what's going on space I guess
they're not really moving we need to we
need to move some of the army from that
area or just send to the wood then
anywhere it doesn't really matter they
just got to be getting some sort of
resource okay
uh well
maybe to the look we've got a lot of
stone so we can be more aggressive and
build uh castles actually why don't you
take half of the villagers on the gold
yeah more more more more
more yeah and then build a forward
Castle forward Castle good Castle on the
stone there a little more forward
forward forward I
here
yeah Ellie aggressive
Ellie there's no other
way those eight Idol
villagers Farms
more like C more Stables make like seven
more Stables where are
they get those two Cavaliers involved in
the action they're far away from yes yes
yes yes they got to join the
action I don't know if we're going to
get that castle up it's very optimistic
but uh I I remain hopeful I want to see
ah it's they're here
oh okay Farms you said right this is a
mill right yeah I so that's a mill get
those two Cavaliers in the action as
well uh I think there's three cavali
four Cavaliers here that aren't doing
anything so you just double click on
those Cavaliers and it selects all the
Cavaliers on the
screen yes perfect get them involved
bring them in here we want to get that
castle up oh are it's a
party oh is a castle down oh yeah it's
long long yeah yeah bring those trebs a
little bit more forward now we want to
we're going to try to attack the Town
Center the town yes you know what's
happening let's see how many Town
centers they have okay more L Cav more
more everything we're just going to oh
look at those villagers send some light
C to kill those villagers oh this is
beautiful to witness some some light C
some perfect make more make more tribs
more wait more Ts mhm oh there's so much
out of there I think we need to move the
villagers cuz there seem to be
oh there we go causing a congestion take
those Army forward bring it in I think
it's should I send my monkey to here
have fun uh what did you wait what was
the Cav what what the arm you have some
Army that's just hanging around poking
their oh yeah picking their noses you
know as one
does go go go go go perfect look at you
go we can take this uh we're finally
we can take those trebs and put them for
uh to the other castle that he has in
the back of his
base uh the the other castle castle back
his base or am I blind I miss yeah yeah
that castle nice that castle nice yes
what was the what was the code again to
tell him 105
105 it worked he really
listens hurry I the hug you I'm going to
go to Switzerland
now did it Ellie
you
kiss kissies for
you finally proud girl I'm so sorry
Ellie it took so
long you you know what it doesn't matter
how long it just matters you get there
yeah now we have the success that we
needed for our
[Music]
bags let's take a look at the let's take
a look at the Timeline I bet that's
gonna tell a story it was it was so long
do you like when you play against uh
hard AI does it also take you this long
probably not you don't play against hard
AI
do the answer you know doesn't matter
doesn't matter you don't play against
the win is the win look at the
Timeline you struggling you struggling
we were
struggling also I was pausing way too
much cuz I'm trying to process
everything oh my goodness but here like
like here we started to you you decided
let's let's go all in and then he kept
on
falling
beautiful ah he got all the relics I
didn't even look at the
relics well he got four there's five
relics but uh oh we'll worry we'll worry
wor about the relics another time this
would you be willing to coach me another
time I'll do it I'll do it we can also
play like privately a little bit maybe
then we can like chill out a bit
more if you don't
mind you want to do like a co-op or do
you want to do a One V one versus me or
do you want to do one versus one versus
you you think you're going to like be
easy on
me
we'll do another coaching
game yeah well yeah like I think you
know for me I um just like you I played
this a little bit when I was much
younger and then there was a big break
where I didn't play it I just like
picked it up again like last year but I
I really like have some some urge to get
better at it just because I can't accept
losing against stupid AI
and yeah and I want to be able to clear
all the campaigns and stuff cuz the
campaigns were actually like the first
thing I where I realized oh damn maybe
I'm not not made for Age of Empires but
then I realized the skirmishes are
actually way more like something I can
handle and somehow easier than the
campaigns mhm
but there's a lot of campaigns I think
there's more coming out with the new
expansions I personally not the biggest
fan of the campaigns I like the like the
one V ones yeah me too but I want to be
able to also go to online matches and
not be a total loser I didn't try it to
go to the uh the online matches versus
random people the ranked ones mhm I
didn't try that yet So eventually like
that's the goal going ranked and and not
being a total
loser you know what it's all about
having fun that's the most important
thing you started playing AE actively
since the uh since Corona started right
yeah but honestly I haven't played I
haven't played a game physically in like
a year and a half possibly longer wa but
like even even then I saw you like
micromanaging so it's like it how long
would you say it takes to get to like
your level
oh I mean that comes the more you play
like you can even see in the course of
this game uh your farm placement has
improved and your speed improved and
then it's just kind of a building block
so you just put another thing on another
thing and then you just you know you
have to keep in mind this game came out
like 24 years ago right yeah long long
so people have been playing this game
since it came out yeah they know how
to yeah so you have some people that are
like really good and then they've been
practicing micromanaging or like
multitasking for 24 years right and
there's also other people that have been
playing also for 24 years but they just
play for fun so they play how they want
to play maybe they want to build walls
and just hide behind the walls or they
have one strategy that they really like
and they don't really care about the
meta so uh I I wouldn't say there's like
a like a a timeline that fits everyone
it's just kind of is your goal good is
it more just to be casual and relax and
then have some fun is yeah I want to get
like decent and I want to be able to
micromanage a little bit like it doesn't
have to be like crazy Next Level
micromanaging but I want to learn like
the hot Keys the important ones and
really be like I don't want to be
stressed out anymore while playing
this I want to be somewhat comfortable
we get there we'll get there so the most
important things to keep in mind is that
we just always want to keep keep our TCS
working um so don't forget the wi cuz
that's really really important um I'll
use those mods I was watching some of
your other games that you played and I
think you were like in post Imperial and
you had like 32 villagers oh and that
hurt me I wonder when that was was that
one of the recent ones yeah I was I was
like 32 Villages a lot of people forget
right it might have been just because I
was playing against like an easy or Ai
and was just like too
easy I think it was a team game that you
were playing which could could have been
it right but the tournament situation
also where you have like 34 villagers
and then you're floating like 10K
resources of every resource but you're
not spending it and you're not making
vill not putting uh military buildings
down so you just have to kind of keep an
eye on those resources and make sure
you're Distributing it if you have like
50 villagers on wood and you have zero
food then it's like okay I have so much
wood let me just plop all of these Farms
down so that's uh that's important oh
working and using your res I think those
are the you were probably watching my uh
our recent tournament within our company
uh I do want to say because people keep
on bringing it up like oh if you getting
coach now aren't you going to be too
good for them like my plan is not on
participating in another tournament with
them can get coaching
too if they want
to but it's like I'm not getting coached
to play a tournament with them again I
want to play alone for now like I don't
want to participate in a tournament so
don't worry guys it's not like I'm going
to like use these skills against them
well you can get these Mad
Skills and then Coach
them coach them yeah you can coach them
you coach me I coach them so coaching
the teacher will the student will become
the master you oh that would be cool
that would be
cool yeah maybe one day one day there's
still a lot of work to
do but I I will if they want coaching
then I will recommend you to them if
they feel like you know getting
serious that's so cute
but you're the perfect coach and you're
so sweet and you were helpful
really like this is the first time right
that you're coaching someone
probably um on stream yeah I mean I yeah
yeah I think uh you did so well even
though I was so
no you did great are we going to do
one
more are you going to show us or did you
want to do something else or I'll leave
this to you I mean I mean I'm wait um
you had the idea of like like doing like
joining right like the co-op one I guess
we can be against the extreme ex extreme
all
right wait extreme is that one after
heart or uh wait yeah I think that's the
the hardest one uh host game
yeah so hold on let me let me open up a
My Age of Empires because I'm I don't
have it yet well you do you when you
play privately just casually kill the
extreme
AI I mean I don't play versus the AI
play we can try I haven't played in a
while I might be a little rusty I'm one
of those like overweight Olympic
gymnastics coaches you know where it's
like I know the
theory
can I do the the double back tumble
probably not what if we're Do extreme
and then he goes not for you but for me
and I'll just die well we can do the
co-op where we control one civilization
together ah oh you can do that oh I
didn't know that yeah yeah yeah okay one
civilization super
Efficiency do you want to host the
game yeah let me just switch my language
back to English oh did you have it on
German I did have it in German what you
have your game in German cute cute check
out you think that's cute just wait till
you see my background I got Ryan in
here got all these monstero leaves it's
so good like look at this look at this
dog the the animal love it very cute
this is a very nice background I think
it's actually called like Le 4K if you
want the the leaves and monstera plants
just for if anyone who's like oh that is
a very nice background wait background
of
AOE yeah like you can mod modify
it
yes
yes okay so we wanted to
um multiplayer Host Game there we go are
you going to put like a password or
something or invite friend or how does
this work I'll invite you
okay together Ellie and kiaha will kill
extreme
AI hold on a second Where Do We Go From
Here we go into stream friends I think
and then I invite you into game okay
something like that you know the other
day I was watching um an AOE video about
strategy that I subconsciously was doing
myself in the in the
Skirmish uh the I what is it called I
think was it
slinging yeah the one where you team up
with someone and you just throw them all
the resources and they focus on the on
the
combat yeah I was watching that and I
realized like they said oh it's not
allowed in tournaments but I realized I
was using it in in the AI Skirmish and I
was the one
slinging the whole time and AI went out
to fight everyone it was really
comfortable I I would love to be a like
a permanent
Slinger it's a fun place to be I can't
seem to invite you I I got it I got it
um oh you got it I guess I have to
accept it like this
yeah oh I'm in I'm in okay perfect
perfect perfect so we're going to make
this
AI o and I joined the
bengalis uh no no so we will be we have
to set our color bolt to Blue let's do
Arena because Arena's fun and then we
can do a fun strategy where we do like
earlier aggression kind of early uh with
with with with
Portuguese oh what do they
do Portuguese so we we'll go for their
unique unit which is pretty
strong and we'll hope for the best okay
okay I guess we'll just be team one this
is going to be team
two you still sounds so so
confident oh there's hard hardest and
then there's extreme yeah there okay
let's go let's go to hardest let's not
let's not go too crazy you lost the
confidence
suddenly I haven't played for a while
man okay let's let's go hardest if
that's easy we can take it from there
okay um and we wanted it to be
[Music]
on Arena have you played Arena before
have I I you start with stone walls oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah that was what we
used in the
tournament in our tournament okay I'm
ready imagine you you uh shout casting
our
tournament but you would be so
frustrated cuz like everybody is so
bad they'll be great um all right you
have to click I'm ready if you're ready
if not then let let's go do you want to
like like focus on something and have me
focus on something or you just tell me
what to do um we're going to do a fast
Castle okay
so you can do your thing and I'll I'll
correct okay I'll help out okay okay I
don't know if a tiny map yeah it's a
two-player so tiny map in theory yeah in
theory yeah two one go
okay let's go
[Music]
SAR SAR okay they might use some Market
abuse but we'll see hopefully all will
be well strong
Market wait can I pause in this oh I
have nine pauses
left we'll be fine we'll be fine can you
make up for all the times where I don't
pause where I'm like
thinking yeah yeah yeah of course can
you control the scout yeah of course
okay
okay so villagers I don't remember what
to do
house uh are my things not
working are my are my HCK keys not
working here oh maybe do my H Keys No no
no I think it should be my hold on let
me you need to find the
Sheep we need to find the Sheep yeah and
I oh you you're creating the villages a
s wow
wow it's all right we're doing it we're
doing it I don't hold on sorry I I'm
just
gonna I'm going to go to my options you
take care of everything I need to work
on my uh hot Keys here okay I don't know
why
I she already did some things for me
this is
amazing
game jeez Louise I don't know why it's
not
working see
why is it my hotkey
C get used to
it oh none of my hot keys are all of the
hot Keys it's orlo hot
Keys you're right it is orlo's hot
keys he you ruined Keys sorry I had orl
come in and visit me another a on my
account he's another streamer and he
changed hot keys and now it's
all very tragic oh no okay
well it's all
right oh they're so fast ah ah ah we
weren't creating we weren't creating the
villagers oh we're we're all right we're
all right
okay okay I'm going to let you take the
wheel on this one and I'm going to try
to fix my hocks okay uh we got to come
back strong later yeah this is like I
can't play like this okay game commands
we can also pause you know wait select
all I need to change the here yeah
bye can't believe he changed my hock
keys I think that's 1 2 3 4 5
[Music]
six 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 that's one too many
right we can get good we can get the the
bo
[Music]
eventually maybe she's doing this on
purpose so that I can show that I can do
it alone you can do it alone what is
this one cl with uh to go to town
center okay who cares alarm alarm thank
you guys for the alarm extreme surprise
extreme Supreme challenge it's uh one uh
one one level harder even so that is
intimidating for
me move these move these
[Music]
away uh wait the 11th the 11th what why
I didn't do it
right the 11 get on the wood you little
bastards we need to do a couple more
okay my important ones like select all
roxes the next one the next one gets the
bo okay she's she's going okay get the
bo get the
bo
uh go go go go
go you don't even have to start it you
don't you don't have to start it you
don't have to you can attack
yeah yeah all right all right all right
okay here we go they're automatically
going to the board all right all right
all right
Perfect
Two
idling ah house okay we can make another
house and
then come back into the game and it's
going to be like uh burning no not yet
not
yet maybe in 5
minutes oh hold on this one would have
been easier to go back back to the
default ones maybe we'll cry about it
later where's my select all Stables
select all Idol villagers now that one's
fine okay now we put them here all right
all right so far so good let's
[Music]
go Scout not Scout here I'll send him
Scout I'll send them to scout at least
automatically better than
nothing okay Mill built the mill the
mill has been created maybe one of you
can get the second Bo where's the other
here this one you got the second
FL there's a hotkey profile for her what
there was yeah but I
uh not working all right the fact that
we have walls might have may may be a
huge Plus
just like this one's
flag wait let me send you back to the
Sheep to this Sheep No you all right
clearly my joke has fallen upon no maybe
the chat uh like realized what you said
but I I I'm
like trying to
survive then you can it's not working
man should I make
Barracks when's the time up yet h no uh
okay good good good note he's changed
it maybe oh where is he going I told you
to do the farm you could have gone this
way what he's going to the
berries
okay what you doing Alie
I'm struggling here changing my hocky
back to what they were supposed to be oh
man we'll cry about it later that's
probably why it's best to just learn
with the
default probably well oh I'm ticking I'm
ticking I'm going to next
age how many villages are we going up to
uh oh
21 not good okay I I suggest we
restart I just I just need to do my
Stables
um
okay I need I need just just for the TC
for the villagers and then every and
then it should be fine uh we'll be fine
we'll be fine let me just go to
the okay you know what I just won't play
can I can I restart this yeah yeah
yeah let's go um um oh I guess we can't
restart there is no restart game oh
sad okay you know
what you want to keep going oh she's
doing suddenly magic all right more
Farms we we'll try our best here it'll
be ugly but we'll we will be fine we're
we're going to try to let's go rearrange
this oh she made a camp Oh my God she's
doing stuff oh mag
think who wow yeah it's it's okay it's
okay what's our Scout doing you just
Auto scouting okay good good
[Music]
good was it too early for me to make the
ticking yeah yeah that's okay we'll just
get our Eco upgrades and uh we'll be
fine what am I doing
now so the goal now is to get some more
villagers on to oh I I'll I'll play the
Scout yeah you can play the Scout I'm
I'm a little nervous to be honest but
we're going to fight for the relics so
we will build a you built a rat right or
no uh no no okay so we need to build I
felt safer cuz we have walls yeah it's
fine we'll build them at we'll build
them later cuz we do want to pick those
up okay would be nice would be nice cuz
we're not booming on this one I found
the other Scout do I want to fight him I
saw you fighting him before I I'll fight
him too oh you're doing a really good
job he's actually dying just make sure
you don't go into his base cuz that's
going to be very he's so far he's he's
missing his
mommy he's almost dead just need to
Corner him
again yeah yeah get another
hit get
him Ellie may I ask you a question of
course what was the first exposure you
had to
vtubers uh he's dead you me really
personally uhhuh that was the first
vtuber you
saw the well that I actually
uh watched a lot of their content of I
would say you but were you aware of
YouTubers before that at all oh yeah
yeah there's some YouTubers that play in
Age of Vampires uh not so much anymore
but I did see them before
M uh you know if you want to practice
your pushing yeah you could have pushed
the eex towards the TC but eex we'll cry
about that one later the eex the IEX IEX
the I move them in there but we got the
Boors everything's looking
okay yeah yeah yeah okay the Scout is
done scouting pretty much at least the
area that he can
scout okay should I bring it back more
food I think our food is uh do you need
help yeah you can push the the the
little deer thing de that's what you
mean oh yeah we we'll get Loom just cuz
I don't want to waste more
food nice see all right buy do I like
run against them oh yeah here there you
go yeah yeah and then we can take some
of these guys on that guy we'll be fine
when the Scout kills them it doesn't
work right yeah the Scout can't kill
them just uh yeah exactly then you can
Farm it okay this is looking a little
disgusting I must
admit oh she already got a market
wow yeah Pro Player here but we're not
adding extra Town centers by the way
just want to point that out there we're
going to try to drop uh two castles mhm
stupid goat struggling with the pushing
you can do it you can do
it okay maybe from here oh look at that
so good I need I need your dog your dog
might do a better job at pushing
them a little closer a little closer
yes
beautiful gorgeous
even
the farm upgrade yeah everything's
looking all right so we do want
to make a castle there it is it's in the
TC the
goat oh it's in the TC you didn't finish
scaven Scavenging or whatever like
foraging the other goat I see it I see
it not very efficient
Ellie yeah yeah yeah I see that listen
we're off to a rickety rackety start
here and all's doing classic degenerate
Strat this is the only one I have we're
in Castle
AG we're fight for the relics okay can I
get the relics it's going to be
beautiful I'll get them for you gorgeous
yeah yeah we'll go with um we'll Pro the
thing with the organ gun is it can't be
converted by a monk unless they have
Redemption and it's going to be unlikely
that they're going to invest in
Redemption so early organ gun quite
nice quite nice we'll get
Fletching okay I'm I'm not doing
anything
Alie um hold on are we not making a
monastery oh you can make a monastery
and make some
monks Monastery
okay I will take I will take one stone
villager
sure you can also take the scouts and
try to see if there's a
monk oh trying to collect the relics on
the mini map okay okay 10 Idols that's
not
good into
gold so now that we have our now that we
have our
thingy mhm okay I'm going to do
something that absolutely
disgusting by the way what so get ready
for this we are going
to go and make a forward Castle forward
Castle let's go oh you're already
sending out some cannon ball person on
no organ gun what the is that it's
an Oregon gun so we need to make we need
to make monks
and I'm destroying this
lady
yes I don't know what she was building
but we we not we won't let her excellent
so we're doing it we're doing it we're
taking the villagers forward probably
need to drop the stone that they have
carried and then we're going to build a
castle on their we have a monk so I'm
going to go get the one of the
relics yes we can make another Monk can
we get more of the relics all right all
right oh we have no resources for it oh
sheesh she's she's she's bringing out
all the people let's go action
action going to refresh the lumber
Camp can we get this one 150 food if
only we didn't have six villagers queued
up we might afford it oh
beautiful
beautiful let's get the gold upgrade he
wait they built it anyway oh I didn't
see any more people building it what is
this Barracks
oh what you oh you that's how close
you're building the castle Castle is
that a castle Yeah we're being
aggressive oh hell
yeah right okay we got one
Relic oh oh oh hold on we got to make
sure that we don't die to the to the
scouts here oh
oh well I'll leave that to
you or maybe I can send the to help
you uh no no focus on getting the relics
okay that we need to get the here cuz
that's going to be a good little gold
income this one okay do we have the gold
upgrade we'll get it at some point we
need more a little bit more food then we
should be
fine go Ellie go go oh you you did your
Castle is finished oh my god oh look at
oh and it's on a TC too it's a Christmas
miracle so these organ guns they um they
actually outrange Town centers oh oh
mhm what no no no no no no I click the
hot key I went to the ding ding ding you
don't want to click the ding ding ding
uh we want why are they strong against
organ
guns uh you need to have like a whole
bunch of knights and then maybe you can
be successful it's a pretty hard um
strategy to counter so early on
especially versus like if you're the AI
cuz they're like they bug out a little
mhm damn you're not being very nice to
them are you no This Is War here death
must consume the enemy ah he took the
Relic ah he's taking no kill him kill
him kill
him he's already castle castle can we
kill the
monk oh did you do it yeah yeah he's
dead oh no did he drop the r the other a
it's
dropped he dropped the Relic though good
job
yeah yeah it's I'll bring our monk over
there just in case all right okay I
don't think we can can we kill the other
monk he took I don't think so I think
it's a little tragic he's going to go
down he got it he got it let's kill this
guy
perfect oh villagers we we we okay o o o
aggressive aggressive we need to make
um we need to make a forward Siege
Workshop when we can afford it
but right now we just need to focus on
getting our convert the ram can I do
that uh no we don't have Redemption
oh I'll convert this
dude can we what's going on here we kind
of somehow at some point in time oh
there's a a monk to be had we can bring
him in and try to convert some some
stuff convert the Knight convert the
knife the
Knight I think we can to be fine here
we're fine the economy
fine fine she says all
right he's our Knight yes beautiful he
didn't have much health but yeah we're
going to need to we're going to need to
repair this
um yeah yeah heal go
go okay what else do we think we need we
need to somehow be a little bit more
devastating with our push no no no no
no man my I need to work on my hocky we
want to get bkin to get a little bit
more
range yes let's
go oh my God I don't even I don't even I
can't even can't even help okay we can
we can kill these
guys
okay it's going well we've got monks
here villagers attack the ram actually
being a monk maybe a villager on the
inside and then like build something in
there you know just be annoying villager
on there inside yeah yeah once we get
rid of this TC oh oh a knight hasn't
entered
who o can we get these villagers in here
can we build a castle in
here let's take let's let's be
disrespectful
oh
damn protect your
villagers that's a horrible it's it's
hideous it's hideous we're doing
fine uhoh these villagers are uh Do you
want to build something with them yeah
well we want to get rid of the gate
first um okay I think those villagers
are going to die we'll cry about it
later come on no no no I want to get a
castle in his base
but it's going to be they're building
the mining camp don't want him to die
you know what maybe that was a bad idea
but we got to we got to do something for
the fans you know mhm mhm some exciting
entertainment we're leading in in
resources and stuff good that's good
let's make some more monks bring them
forward let's build a forward Siege
workshop and I think we need some more
Stone
do we have another Stone Pile in our
base somewhere cuz we got a lot of gold
this is super we we can take this Stone
let's take it take some villagers off of
our gold and put them onto the stone and
then we'll be fine in you mean in their
base right cuz that's what I'm talking
about oh that
one I'm I'm I'm building it well we have
a market we can just buy some gold okay
I'm going to I'm or buy some Stone I'm
going to buy some Stone and we're going
to build a very aggressive Market damn
she's so strong I Mark
the castle all right we're mining we're
mining it's ugly it's
beautiful SE something so beautiful
before make some Rams did you make them
build a castle wow it's it's aggressive
I admit we shall convert the knights
that are trying to kill or heal they're
they're dying before we can convert
them all right let's go we got this is
so rude Ellie this so rude how can enter
his privacy like that oh oh monk monk
convert convert convert
convert get him we got
him
yes let at us
go I think we got him damn I think this
is inspiring like this is a maybe a
strategy that I will use in the future
then this is a really fun one cuz uh you
make nice things early there it is oh my
God like basically we won like let me
type 105 it looking quite good for us uh
we just don't want him to get to
Imperial you know he gets to Imperial
we're in trouble but I don't think he's
the resources to do
that you know what thatu
means it's fine it's okay what means
what uh Dau means it's fine in
Japanese do you know any
Japanese uh oh nice do you watch any
anime oh do I watch anime I'm a wee you
are I got husbandos I've got four
husbandos you want to know who my
husbandos are yeah I don't want to tell
you I don't want to I don't want him
cheating on me I don't worry I don't
really care much for a husband
BND um okay well my OG hos Bondo is
sharu but who's that from Inu Asha oh
okay
inha there's no G1 okay we got the OG
one then then we had uh jeez we got so
much so much uh gold here it's crazy mhm
uh then we had oh you know what we need
our army to actually be attacking stuff
you know be great fantastic so then we
had uh kirima from my hero mamia cuz I
was just very very cute big F that one I
did watch mhm yeah uh and and then we
have the next one that's a little bit
more spicy uh hisoka from from Hunter
Hunter uhuh this one I did not much okay
and the OG one that oh not the OG one
but the best one that I think everyone
can agree on Captain
Levi Captain Levi from Captain Levi from
Attack on Titans uhuh
uh that's also one I didn't watch but
you know what this feels like Attack on
Titan right now but Weir
tians start attacking some he's trying
to expand he's trying to hold on trying
to hold on for de like we're coming for
you okay do we not have enough wood to
like Reed far here what's going
on I shall I shall take care of that for
you maybe thank thank you thank you
receding Farms all all of our idle
villagers that's your job okay you got
to send them you got to send them to
work here
re I can do while the part is going on
what do we need uh more
wood so we can do that okay mon go kill
her she's trying to do some nonsense
here there villagers
here my gosh this game's messy we have
5,000 gold girl oh let's just buy food
and click up to Imperial and get shbs in
here buy food H oopsy yeah we got cuz we
got the relics mhm we're going to have
the RAM on I'll give you some wood too
cuz I think you need
it um because we were low on wood yeah
okay that's what you
meant that's what you you were quiet was
like wait what is she thinking about
oh continue helping
you yeah we're just talking about the
RAM on RAM action
and heal heal help help help the Knight
okay we have one Idol you shall H join
no no
you I think we could easy take care of
hardest uh
insane I think you can like I'm not
really doing anything y y Che out
there's villagers that are mining stone
up top that we're going to bring down
and just drop a castle on this beautiful
CER we don't even feel bad a boot
it they don't even feel bad boot it
telling him again resign yes perfect
keep the pressure up he he thinks
there's still hope you know
what I don't I don't believe that there
is hope but you never know come on come
on come on come on come back come back
yes never know I got us a
night H
hola oh we're putting that Idol villager
to work actually he
didn't
yeah but no worries no Idol villagers
here that is not something you will see
here no no yeah these 11 Idol villagers
not Idol I don't all uh 11 what now I
put them work okay okay oh we can we can
we can try to convert a villager here
and make him you know this is so good
for us this has got to be so good for us
look at
look with your beautiful
[Music]
eyes I I'll help you micromanage some
things m
are actually not bad versus the orgon
guns but we just have so many of
them here you know what we want let's
make a bunch of
stables
[Music]
and then we'll go
for are you actually making them yeah
yeah I'm making them where close to the
action nah close to the villagers M oh d
it's fine it's fine he's still playing
he's this man's still playing
stubborn he's got so much here in the
back though W you know what this means
we got to go for a even more
disrespectful Castle cast I don't even
think that could be more
disrespectful if only we could move our
existing on I don't know if that can be
more disrespectful here okay so we need
to collect all Stables into one control
group what are they doing ah what am I
doing light Cal we should just be
getting horsey boys the thing with
Portuguese is they have cheaper
everything costs 20% cheaper and then
we're just going to make some victoras
and then that's going to slowly get us
some
resources it's a it's a building that
you get a little bit of of food and wood
and gold and stone so it's like 20
villagers it takes up 20 population
space but works like 12
villagers
approximately will that was close we
almost lost our cute Ram uhoh okay what
are we attacking here I feel like we got
we there's a
Siege somewhere no no no no no what are
they doing see please
please oh okay it's
fine we're not making villagers e we
haven't been
[Music]
we
uh keep let leave me the leave me the
the the the the the idle
ones okay can the RAM do action please
what are we paying it
for what are we paying it for if it's
not even going to do work being small
and cute don't worry I got it I got it I
got the idle one okay good good good
good still a goat
here good good good idle
villagers not good do you want something
with
those oopsie what did I do I did
something by accident I think I sent
them did you delete a castle no I sent
them by accident to some weird tree I
think ah we're fine we're fine we're
going to go take our Tre here I think he
probably has there's a Siege Workshop
that we wanted to get rid
of perfect we send
them uh here
maybe one
join ugly ugly Farms but it's
fine all I'm doing is like worth so much
trust me guys like my participation here
is very
important Great
Value oh we don't want our trebs to die
to a pesky little Ram that could be
annoying repair repair repair he built
repair repair repair repair what do you
want to
repair uh I think we I think we got it
okay fast we got it fast change of times
we have 18 Idols 18 that's on you
girlfriend yeah oh no that's ah ah
okay
[Music]
clap we did it girl amazing oh even
though you wanted to restart we still
like Salvage Dad look at the Timeline I
just want to point out that they had
nothing never what did Al have that was
never a
chance problems he had problems Al well
he he's got Tim
Allen do you know the show Home
Improvement it's an older reference but
it checked out boo boo boo it's because
I'm watching it right
now A Tim Allen's besti is
Al but that was a different one I guess
like we did so well look at the Gold so
aggressive I want to copy what you
do I'm going to try the
same but like not not against a harder
AI personally I'll I'll try it out try
this strategy it's pretty easy but not
alone against
harder well you can go against hard on
Arena just you and then I can coach you
through it it's a really fun one
and okay
okay you you you sure you want another
like like what you just had with me like
two hours of suffering and we I don't
think this is going to be two hours
though I think we're going to get there
a little faster I especially with Arena
it won't get rushed if we take the arena
map
yeah yeah so you set that up uh I think
I still have your stream with you inside
or just with uh the watching feature no
I'll just watch it'll be all you okay I
feel like you get more you get more
practice that way okay should I also
take the what was
it what was it should I keep the Franks
again oh Portuguese it's Portuguese
Portuguese okay yeah hold on I got to go
into steam and then and then PE your
stream where are
they peep your gam playay real
quick all units minus 20% gold wow
foragers generate wood in addition to
food what while they're getting food
they make
wood oh yeah it's a new new little bonus
shes it's not that bad ships 10% Okay
Age of Vampires I don't see you maybe I
have to search for you well hard not
hardest
okay oh wait was you you can't how did
we do it last time you just like invited
yourself and I gave the no I didn't even
have to give an okay it says that you
watching me yeah
yeah I am watching you why does it feel
like somebody watching me I got no
promises okay uh so this is gonna be on
hard right Arena
perfect uh yeah see I really didn't
think I didn't think you would like
really want to do even more with me I am
I am
glad I enjoy your company you're so nice
oh my God I'm going to go to Switzerland
for real for
real let's go we're gonna touch
yay I wanted I like I always say when I
get like um Super Chat s from
Switzerland I'm always like oh I want to
go to Switzerland now I have like a
reason I have a reason Yay see Ryan of
course oh yes of course well so should I
start are we ready oh yeah I'm ready I'm
ready uh so Arena this is looking pretty
good I like it um last match if you want
to yeah you're good yeah last all let's
go magars what can you tell me about the
magars
the magars uh they got good Cavalry good
Cavalry got all right Cavalry got a
pretty cool unique unit here as well
okay villagers Villagers houses houses
[Music]
houses too much time wasted on the
placement you just got to plop plop and
go go go wait he he needs to find my
sheep first cuz they're not
found plop plop plop plop plop there we
go sheep closer in and then you are
going to be okay that's also all right
go go go go ah go go go go go go go and
then we will put them on the sheep all
right this is the next one now it's five
the seventh will go to a wood line I
only see this one on the left right
now the one will take
yes okay oh there also one here but left
side is
good left side's good right side's good
doesn't matter okay next Cho next here
uhoh
uhoh uh no no you'll be fine sorry I
thought you were G to you were gonna oh
do I have okay okay be like do I have do
the I saw it I saw it but she's going to
make a oh that's such a good Lumber Camp
look at that right in the corner fits so
well safe for work if you have children
please sexy Lumber cam too good it's too
good it fits like a
glove
we I can't I have no food should I drop
drop drop they dropping they
dropping price is averted okay so we're
going to be going up with like 28
villagers just so you know going to be a
it's going to be like we're not going to
be so strict with the build 28 villagers
gives you a lot of room uh oh
uh okay go go go go take care of those
sheep
than okay um I think with your scout
you I think with your scout you still
need to get some two more sheep oh
within my walls did we get the two sheep
or did I I I had the two yeah I did
okay there should be two more there's
four in total that you have to
find maybe
here okay um sending one over here wait
next one is the
11 no no
no oh there they are they
are they split into two grips again okay
next next one get if you want you can
practice pushing the deer towards the
cuz on Arena it's a lot more chill M
okay wait should I get the boar now yeah
we're going to need a house and then
we're going to need to get the boar
okay yeah
here okay multitasking
multitasking see see we're adding
another element of difficulty but you're
doing
great okay they he's it's pretty much
there okay yeah yeah you can take two It
Takes Two Hits to kill
so you
[Laughter]
have she's trying she's
trying get the
Deering not
[Music]
possible
okay damn they're so split now makes me
really question the timing it's okay
okay oh hold on before we over another
oh too
late it's all right it's all right why
did they go these stupid
they have no brain cells uh she
will make a mill maybe mhm yeah we can
go on the
berries and uh the rest will go join the
mill yeah I don't think we need six on
wood so you can take two villagers and
just leave four on wood and we can bring
the other two to the to the berries
also
little are we are we floting SpongeBob
now I don't watch SpongeBob I do not you
don't watch sponge oh Lord havec yeah
maybe a few times when I was a child but
I don't remember anything from
that oh don't worry
about but I'm like losing track of um
where where everybody's supposed to go
next maybe keep on
berries yeah so we're going to need to
put like um few more villagers we're
going to need to get more boes so the
other boar so the guy going for the
berries you can grab the boar with him
oh I was going to go with her yeah yeah
or with her oh she's a weak one though
yeah she's a weak one though well she's
she's committed to it now okay
okay we will not
question commitment believe be confident
have
confidence yeah yeah send like two
villagers to that boore that so we we
don't waste all the
food uh mm house house house house house
house um que up Loom otherwise your TC
is going to be idle and we don't want
that yes perfect MH
okay he's just scouting inside can I
send him out there we go he'll go
outside he's all right so now we're
going to want to make another house
probably after she builds that one so
that way we'll have population 30 and
then with our 30 like we'll have 28
villagers and we can go up everything's
going to be Gucci um those two idle
villagers no no no no no to the board to
the board to the board faster okay and
and if you can take the house lady she
can build a farm and another Berry
villager can make a farm to around the
mill doesn't really matter where okay oh
wait finish finish and then
yeah send like two the next two
villagers to Gold cuz we're going to
need that for our fast Castle so fast
Castle have you heard of the Str before
yes yes yes yes get to Castle as fast as
possible basically yeah skip basically
the feudal age as soon as we get to fle
our goal will be to build a market in
the blacksmith and then okay off we'll
go we need
a couple more
Foods yeah yeah don't worry we got it we
got it we got time so you'll send like
two villagers to gold and then the last
like four villagers to Stone okay but
two more after this to gold or is like
27 28 villagers okay okay
[Music]
okay no we no my next trauma will be we
we
we ah okay ah they're done uh okay they
make um wait so here they make Farms
don't forget to go to Stone you want to
go to Stone now oh okay
yeah
who's you go to
Stone mhm so the TC gather point should
be on Stone now
okay and and we're going to make two
more villagers that go to Stone so we're
going to have to unclick all those other
ones so we want to go up to feudal oh
okay
mhm feudal
time okay that's fine that's fine can
you send uh one villager from gold to
Stone
mhm mineral and leave one
Village H sorry leave one
villager wood we need to build the um
blacksmith and the market so we need
wood for that take three of those
villagers and then build another Lumber
camp in that other beautiful location on
the other side free of the current
Lumber
man Ellie yeah yeah yeah no no no not
Lumber sorry the gold put the backc put
the
backc you got cut off a little bit
didn't hear you
well so from the gold to the lumber
villagers from the from the berries we
need another M lumber mill okay but
maybe now it's too late cuz we we need
the okay it's never too late we we'll
figure that out so we're going to go up
we're going to try to go up with a plus
two so queue up only two
villagers mhm perfect and then we will
go for a market and and a blacksmith the
market takes a little bit more time to
build so you're going to pick two
villagers to build the market and one
villager is going to build the
blacksmith okay so get ready to place
the market down
first yeah take two villagers for to
make the market oh oh okay from the
current ones okay
uh uh Market Market Market
Market Okay click up queue up another
villager cuz we're never going to make
it in time and then uh what was the next
thing blacksmith blacksmith M okay
perfect I that was too close to the town
center ah it's fine so you can un un one
of the villagers here cuz I don't think
we need that many and then send those
idle villagers to
Stone okay she's on her way perfect oh
she can help and then go to Stone all
right all right we're working on
it
done any upgrades already you have no
idle Villers send them either to gold or
to Stone okay also a house maybe but
okay un UNC that villager and click up
to castle that's going to be really
important okay I'm going to make a house
with herlick that villager so we don't
have to wait for the house yeah unclick
the I thought that was just something
else okay all right building a house so
that we don't get housed mhm maybe send
that Idol villager to Wood cuz I think
we need a little bit more wood our goal
uh to make organ guns out of two castles
we need 15 on gold and 15 on wood so if
we have 15 on gold 15 on wood we can
non-stop produce out of the two castles
and that's going to be our goal okay
okay all
right
[Music]
does a fast Castle don't worry they will
not be thinking that cuz I will not be
playing against
them I'm not cheating or
anything also fast Castle was basically
my strategy in uh tournament originally
anyway that's very good strategy I like
it thank you it was the only one I could
think
of oh maybe another house yeah you can
make some more houses good so I would
suggest when we get to Castle we take
all of the gold villagers and we build a
castle in like the top point of our base
okay here somewhere over there and then
we'll try to do the similar thing we did
last game where we build a little bit of
an army and then we can defend some
Villers as we go forward okay okay have
you noticed I've been barely pausing so
far but only the beginning it's been
perfect it's been so
good so
far plenty of houses plenty of
Villers yep yeah and Castle okay
yeah beautiful over here or closer to
the edge that's fine keep it there and
then when you're done back to back to
the gold yeah send the gather point to
gold now so they keep keep mining the
gold okay uh X excellent we have an idle
villager so we need to put that one to
[Music]
work uh can I make a stone camp out
here outside yeah here there's a little
Stone uh you don't need to I thought
they're going to run out soon out of
this one yeah I would I but there's a
good point cuz there's a little bit of a
congestion so you can make another
mining camp on the other side yay
15 Wood 15 gold was the last instruction
so we want to get there eventually but
first we got to get the second castle
okay
oh oh wa they're almost done uh uh
what's next what's next so to control
group that castle and then you're always
going to want to make organ guns organ
guns yes okay mhm why does he think he's
done
scouting go Scout more
um good question oh there attack attack
this scout okay organ gun production
let's go go go organ gun is it actually
a music
instrument the organ gun he he cored in
look at look at
that look at
you amazing oh yeah we also need to get
the Eco upgrade so maybe get the wood
upgrade we totally forgot about that one
yeah uh
currently wait one one more we can
afford it get it now yeah perfect for so
let's take those villagers and uh take
some villagers off of gold and put them
onto that Lumber camp on the
right okay we don't need that much gold
right now and last game we had like a
gazillion gold true true yeah so we have
enough for another Castle so I say take
those gold vill
go aggressive and take the organ guns
forward too yeah that's what we wanted
how how aggressive more forward forward
forward you wanted it to be touching on
the gold on on the gold on the gold side
yes and the organ guns should I make the
point
there G point there too
right yes at The Gather point there
villagers Oregon guns go go oh I like
this a
lot looking good should I get the
wheelbarrow uh you don't have that many
farms so it's not like super necessary
but you can grab it if you want um what
I would do is I would also send the
scout forward so you can kind of keep
tabs there okay forward and after you
build that the castle forward you can
build a monastery to pick up those
relics mhm and uh also there in the area
or
inside H that would be inside right the
monastery we don't want to would be it
would be outside by your Castle oh I
guess so that it like collects
faster maybe okay more organ guns organ
gun why don't I hear organ gun
production we get another wood upgrade
actually I think we're missing that
other Castle age wood upgrade so yes
there we can afford it perfect we're
going to remember we need 15 on gold 15
on on wood yeah yeah so the villagers on
Stone we like once they get enough for a
third Castle I guess you can split them
up and it should be all right uh okay
split them over here yeah yeah so like
gold and control group that second
castle too
oh uh so it's in the same one yeah
control one perfect and then just make
orgon guns
nonstop
beautiful
beautiful is that the monk that was a
monk I
think that was that value on that
amazing so you have those villagers that
just finished the St Stone mining uh now
now they're have their mine of their own
where they're trying to mine Stone
further out but we don't need more Stone
no remember 15 we need 15 gold 15 Wood
mhm and don't forget to make more Oregon
guns from the second castle so click on
the two and then orgon gun orgon gun
Oregon gun so we're using both castles
beautiful so I split them between the
the forest and the
yes okay uh with one of the villagers
forward uh here you don't forget to make
the monastery so you can pick up those
those uh one of them those
Relic Monastery Monastery
mhm perfect
here yeah a little bit further back
maybe yeah yeah yeah yeah there you go
so take all your army and set them to
attack the gate so you can go into
the okay yes and the castle too Castle
attack the gate as well oh oh oh I
didn't know you could do that okay logic
that was pretty obvious that they could
do that
uh okay those villagers that just built
the monastery mining camp on the gold
mining camp on this gold okay forward
gold yeah I might as well nice this is
going pretty smooth let's go this is
working yeah monk monk to get the relics
yeah I made one already and he's on his
way
perfect perfect let's go let's go let's
get him oh there's a villager coming out
he should die I
think death to this villager I'll find
him he will die yeah do you also want to
make a forward Siege workshop and get
some Rams and they'll help to destroy
the buildings forward SI work oh oh oh
so we can use the monk to convert the
Knight I think we I think we'll get the
conversion the Knight which one there's
a knight by that stable but we'll get
him later uh organ gun production we
need it m you can make another Monk as
well out of that uh Monastery okay
that'll be really good to convert those
Knights that we know are happening so
right now is our army being well
utilized mhm uh think and no maybe some
of them can attack the this yeah I think
we need to go in and try to get some
villager kills right inside okay with
all them go of course the monk can go
get another Relic to the
left okay mhm you can shift Click The
Relic and then yeah perfect look at you
go there's also that pesky villager
going to build that annoying mining camp
or whatever he's
building no leave
my wait where where where where H this
one
yeah okay so Rams are coming we've seen
this before we need to make a we need to
make our own Rams I think our own Rams
should we make it close by mhm yeah
Siege Workshop close
by and then we can go in even deeper
with a castle kind of right where the
organ guns are okay if all goes well we
can even make a disrespect Castle
disrespect base nice disrespect Castle
me likey disrespect Castle
yes of
course okay now now I'm getting now I'm
starting to get
nervous oh no no no no you're doing fine
you're doing fine send the villagers uh
what are we building RS a castle Yeah
Rams from there Rams from there we also
want to build a castle and careful that
your organ guns aren't in the Town
Center range cuz right now we're losing
okay
CLE kind of where the organ guns are
uhoh imperial this is a little bit of a
problem can move the or guns
back they will be hopefully protecting
the production of the
castle yeah he's an imperial though so
we have to worry about pesky okay we we
yeah you didn't worry about production
of trebuchet cuz that is very not good
for our castles but we're not really
using our castles now so it doesn't even
matter get get out of the range my
friends get out of there oh the
foundation's down they're doing it
they're doing it all right up Castle uh
uh what what what's with the castle it's
optimistic but I think I think we'll be
fine send the ram forward to get rid of
that TC and make more Oregon guns and
also we need to make more Farms I don't
think we have the farm upgrade so we
should probably pick that
up uh Farm upgrade Farm upgrade yeah
well wait is on the mill right yeah make
a make
a okay we don't want the ram to kill our
Castle so all those organ guns on that
Ram then we should be fine
okay
yeah the we have some idle villagers so
we don't need to look at the fight
happen we just need to yeah get the
wait they stopped they stopped building
that's the oh they weren't even
building I was wondering like every time
I P pushed this like they went but
here's also some idle okay okay I think
we need to buy some food and go up to
Imperial ourselves okay by bye bye bye
how much do we need oh we're ready you
have it unclick that uh last villager
which one the one that's about to no no
no that's fine
Castle so now we
have a little dice a little dicey I
think we need it to be a little bit
faster um but okay we'll get to Imperial
um Idol villagers and suboptimal as well
uh oh but uh should I send them back to
gold now these
people I'm sending them back yeah back
should they fix the the
castle it's not really much damage no no
the chubby shades are going to kill the
castle Castle it's all going to be very
tragic no I
think if we're lucky maybe we get that
TC
destroyed I can't build uh organ guns
right now
why oh no it is it is okay can you make
some
fetas what's that where is that it's
that very nice building for Portuguese
that give you a slow trickle of all the
resources well well it's in the it's not
in the military yeah yeah oh we got to
be an imperial for that sorry we got to
be an imperial for that voria economic
building wow
mhm okay once we're in Imperial and make
a ftor where do I make that uh probably
somewhere in your base doesn't need to
be super aggressive I would
um yeah cuz you have a lot on gold here
and the efficiency is really not so good
so we're going to need to spread out
move some of those villagers to another
gold pile like that villager is doing
look at that she's like I can't work
under these conditions this I
want stinky stinky workers so we don't
even
shower yeah that's really think we can
refresh some other Lumber camps to be
more efficient as well refresh other
Lums refresh oh yeah okay okay yeah
let's do that in a second because I
think that the fight is a little bit
more important at the moment um the
fight is really important so we should
be looking at our army okay yeah uh we
want to get rid of that trebuchet
and the
villagers
like you should be focusing on the the
trebuchet they they got to go they've
got to go okay from the forward Castle
make uh who whoa it's dying
uh yeah there's a Tre that's still alive
that has a very
[Music]
very okay buy some Stone repair this
Castle buy some Stone repair this castle
please please please please
please oh they need Stone to repair that
okay yeah they need Stone to repair so
send those villagers on gold right now
those three villagers to repair the
castle uh just collect those villagers
yeah repair repair repair repair um and
make more villagers cuz
we okay
okay okay perfect and we got a yeah the
town C and then make more Ts okay make
more Ts and we're going to want to
attack that castle as
well I'll bring my monk in for healing
the monk can't heal these units to their
Siege only uh only villagers can repair
you're doing fine you're doing fine
select all the organ guns and and and
collect uh you know kill the monk go in
there see what we can do cuz there's
also a castle know
that castle we know there's a castle
probably behind that monastery a we need
to find it and uh maybe with the monk we
can convert a villager or something like
that
okay
okay I sent the in even though I don't
know
where has lots of line of scout you'll
Scout with your villain uh your trevet
mhm it's okay make more organ Guns by
the way we need more military should we
take down this town center too yeah but
first we want to get rid of that Tri on
the
yeah okay uh the idol on by the way here
where where are they going when I get an
idol she can
Reed ah okay we
go yeah organ guns focusing on the treb
uh and you need to defend your trebs as
well so send some to that night and some
to that
trip very very important
night
yeah there's that Knight attacking your
boys uh I'm blind I don't see ah here
okay
yeah do they have close range they don't
really seem like a close range unit uh
yeah yeah they they're fine they're fine
okay okay good good good good good good
get that last one more bring all of the
organ guns forward
mhm we're doing fine ooh that's like H
or what was that
no I think just regular Knights or is
that oh yeah it's Maga hassard it's the
his unique unit yeah with
the fancy wings no Castle yet ah wait
that's a castle that's the castle so
we'll clean out the the the town centers
and then move on so we need more Ts we
need more organ guns remember we have we
have 15 15 right 15 on gold 15 on wood
we can have nonstop organ gun production
pick up uh conscription while you're at
it to increase theed okay
and they're
done is there more gold here there is
more gold here that's a risky corner to
go to but uh maybe make some fotorus cuz
we have can we maybe we buy the
resources but we need more Stone yeah
buy this buy some
Stone but let's look at our army let's
look at our army I feel like there's
tragedy
unfolding
okay uh but not for us okay okay or
houses uh okay okay I'll send this one
to the castle now both my both T start
attacking the castle uh but we just need
to defend our trebs mhm defend the treb
sh kill the monk
beautiful can ball in your
face oh he so few yeah houses houses
houses girl
oh take like that one villager and make
her like a gazillion houses all those
Villers that just built the ftor more
houses it's very very important send
them all yeah yeah all of them to the
houses perfect perfect let's go look at
the military what's going on at army I
wrong
fing sorry Army
uh that did you see that dirty dirty
place is good no you're doing well you
can send the orgon guns to kill those
three villagers Gathering the gold after
uh that's good
we can also kill the see uh Monastery
pick up those relics too I like it
Monastery
here what
relics in the monastery for your
opponent ah this one now yeah so don't
get the houses get the production
buildings you always want to focus on
production so the Stables have got to go
yes okay idle villagers have got to get
to work
perfect which look at the score you're
doing so well yeah let's go maybe make
another ftor with those Idol villagers
oh okay yeah it's like a very nice uh
little hack do I have to do anything
with them yeah no they just provide you
resources perfect uh villagers organ
guns collect the
relics should I get another Monk to help
me or I'll just give him third third
to be fasting yeah
villager wait it's not moving why is he
not
moving okay okay now
he's let's get the E UPG too look we
didn't get wheelbarrow we didn't get the
the the other one yeah yeah we need
houses we need uh
upgrades we need to be making organ guns
we haven't made any organ guns in a
gazillion
years perfect uh
uh oh oh he's building something a TC
perhaps well that's interesting can I
stop him you can make uh I guess sending
two organ guns should take care of
it you can also send like half of those
villagers on that gold pile to like any
other
neutral resource I think on
the this one yeah or like the stone for
example I think his arm we're probably
going to find his uh secondary Army okay
secondary
Army yeah wait she was building here
ooh no stop they're almost done they're
almost done
okay it's looking it's looking pretty
good what do we want like
attack but the maybe I go back here and
find something
there maybe the gate first right yeah
okay all right winning we be
winning oh let me cancel these
villagers and then that's a weird farm
that he's built okay so we have so many
villagers over there we uh by the gold
to the right of our base wait oh oopsy
like 28 Idols you can bring them forward
and grab the gold from his base if you
want to okay okay here's here come the
knights here come the knights so we're
going to need to defend on Army
Knights oh these people what are they
doing ah because they they couldn't
finish the
camp they couldn't finish the camp I
think they the stone see do you see the
stone kind of to the right yeah yeah bu
put them on put them all those villagers
that are idling at the bottom onto that
stone mining camp oh okay oh
oh you're fine he's doing so much
now guns also to kill that villager so
she doesn't build any more nonsense who
who who should kill the Villager the
organ gun just so you can kill that
villager and then don't forget to be
making way more organ guns your your
organ gun production
is not satisfying my li
okay go go go
go uh oh like
um what's going on what's going on
what's going on oh it's open now let's
take these
treuchet and bring them to the town
centers cuz we want to get them involved
in here
probably uh I don't know if there's much
there H I guess yeah
okay
um oh there's a castle though oh there's
a castle there okay so
uh no no oh it's going to be tragic oh
we got to need to kill that monk at some
point in time yeah I got him I got him
yeah make sure that pre doesn't go into
the into the castle where's my by the
way into the castle get it oh it's too
late why did he go so far clicked in
there it's fine you still got one one
will do the job it's all right just make
sure that those monks die so they don't
pick up those
relics excellent so let's take a look at
our army in the in the right hand inside
like what's going on there there's a lot
of blue flashing uh oh KN okay that's an
issue are you doing this for me why is
he
moving what are you controlling me Allie
no I think he just wants to run a do
they have a minimum attack distance I
think they might yeah yeah they have a
minimum attack distance so uh help help
him help him if you yeah take those
three onto the Knight um okay so we know
he has lots of knights let's build aax
we need to build at least a Rax
okay and then we're going to go for a
lot of spam kill that villager building
that Siege Workshop right now uh
yeah cuz we haven't been making any
villagers uh not villagers well military
mhm military is very
important those idle villagers we need
more wood we need a lot of wood right
now and those villagers right now at the
gold they don't need gold we have 4,000
gold Lumber Camp to the north uh wait
okay let's let's take a little bit of a
breef b
b he's got a lot of uh kns coming in
okay we got a lot of gold we got a lot
of food we don't have a lot of wood so
it's gonna be hard to
make production buildings if we don't
have
wood
oh too much
okay too much everything it's okay it's
okay it's okay um build like six rxes
right now okay wait I'll make one thing
here by the way six racks
uhuh six rxes okay I'll build them all
close by yes build them all
there
quickly quickly fast fast
fast they don't have to look pretty they
just got to be built okay
perfect let's go to our um blacksmith
and get some upgrades
for uh there so it can be the first two
okay also um Fletching as well that
always is nice to have Fletching all
right uh perfect idle villagers they go
on wood oh refresh Lumber Camp so
they're looking good and nice okay yeah
was very
inefficient they're also not doing
anything C on a wood line and you're
going to be
fine
okay perfect you got a lot of orgon guns
here and they're going to defend this
part of your economy the treuchet where
is the trebuchet going I sent one down
here actually back to the truche by the
castle oh uh it's it's in dangerous
territory put it back to Castle Back
cast back to the castle oh there it
is there it is bring those organ guns to
defend your treb yes CU right now is
looking a little gross and also no
villagers are building the rexes at the
at the
moment I don't know
why hey hey help them help them out
y'all
okay okay oh my God there's more coming
you have a good numbers you have a
castle helping you out you should be
fine but I have any click your yeah just
leave the leave the organ guns be don't
don't keep touching them cuz when you
move them they're not attacking when
they're moving so like they're just
going to be clumped up there from your
rexes get the Pikeman upgrade the
Pikeman my Barracks okay Pikeman oh yes
okay perfect now we make the trebuchet
set it to those two Town centers attack
one of the TCS with that yeah yes oh
they put wait they they destroyed my my
church it's fine don't worry about it
we'll be fine collect all the rxes and
queue up maximum amount of of Pikeman oh
okay uh get the hell of a de upgrade and
arson too while you're at
it okay uh
Pike how so the one underneath mhm mhm
yes and the little fire thing the fire
okay yeah the fire thing is going to
have increased damage versus buildings
so they can actually be very useful okay
I'm going to trash this one out
okay we're going to trash this out we're
going to just trash this out okay all of
your Idols that you have put them on to
uh to Wood mhm yeah I I I just sent them
yeah yeah so put them to Wood keep uh
get more blacksmith upgrades for your
infantry so the first
two more blacksmith upgrades for my
infantry what uh uh yeah y smoke yes yes
yes yes iron and while you're added get
get botkin too bkin and this one perfect
perfect perfect so more more villagers
more organ guns more trash
Al
yes
no I like make more the PR is doing some
good work for you you're doing all right
oh yeah going down two Town centers down
perfect I'll send it
to what next what's our next goal to
destroy just something close by oh you
can also uh send your halers like deeper
into his army like into his base to kind
of annoy him okay you should be all
right all
right be be cautious of these Rams
because you do not want them to kill
your trebs or your Castle uh yeah can my
can my bomb bombing music people they're
not going most efficient but they'll get
the job done okay all right uh I'll I'll
set the barracks scaving Point like here
oh wait yeah sure it going be annoying
make more make more units though you're
not making more units we need more units
beautiful beautiful can you build
another
Victoria m
one moment I'll build one yeah we can we
can also get the elite upgrade uh for
the for the organ guns but okay H oh
yeah houses girl we've been we're
getting housed now
what more more more more more more more
more
more is this enough yes yes should be
fine let's take a look at our army
uhhuh they're going in
perfect they're having a good time I
we're doing well we're going to need to
focus on that Monastery cuz I think he's
collected a lot of the relics oh
and he's trying to build that castle too
quickly quickly attack the villagers
with some organ guns so that okay no
perfect deleted the foundation he did
all right I'm going to let I feel like
you are in a pretty good position I'm
going to let you uh do you oh really
okay uh you uh uh well okay let's send
these people out I think they're done
there are they
Ellie what's done they don't need to be
up here anymore do they no n we're good
okay let's go full in wait not
here I hope so well maybe a couple can
stay cuz the maybe they need protection
I don't know maybe you want to get the
elite organ gun upgrade from the castle
Elite working
ooh even stronger yes oh yes yes do we
have any more blacksmith upgrades for
the uh
hbers yeah get the first yes okay yes
also pick a bracer as well E A what
bracer the little
bracer From the Block
yes okay grab all standard Victory
that's not that exciting he we want
Total Domination ah oh there's a victory
for getting all relics mhm if you have
it
enabled I think the standard
is on the TCS girl you're doing
great
okay let's just send them all let's just
send them all tush on the TC I think I
did is there another tush
coming oh where this one going hey hey
hey hey hey hey hey hey there's another
one okay you're Haler numbers are kind
of looking rookie really yeah where
where's the
production more more more more more yes
okay now now make some Stables St
Stables we're not done
okay make like five Stables six stables
and then we're going to make Knights and
Cavalier cuz we got a lot of gold we
don't need to be making the trash unit
but they're just very good versus uh St
KN who should I maybe
you sta some
St maybe this many they're just chilling
I I guess I can really get rid of
them how's it looking pretty it's
looking really good I feel like he's
griefing a bit like
he there you
go there you
go Ellie come
[Music]
here he did it I I we did it I I went I
said come on 105
victory has been ours check it out
you're the best Ellie the best best oh
shakas shakas sh so a look at the
Timeline
[Music]
Li look at this he had no
military what have we learned it's
almost as if making military wins games
yeah aggressive like normally I I think
alone I'm always too scared to go
aggressive but now I'm a bit more
confident about it thanks to you a this
was a fun strategy because uh as soon as
you get to Castle you make the Castle
start making the units
yeah the
the I am a fan of the Portuguese
now maybe I'll use them more often it is
a very good strategy what's your
favorite Civ my favorite CV has got to
be the Mongols I uh I like to say I'm a
bit of a m gal oh what what did I do so
special uh they're just really cool
because you can go up with them really
quickly they take food from the hunt
faster so H you can have a faster feudal
age and get your scouts out earlier and
their unique unit is probably one of one
of if not the best in the game the manga
oh don't know what they are it's a it's
really strong Cavalry Archer that has a
bonus versus
siege that is very helpful nice nice
Jing Jing Jing is SC hey brother brother
nice
brothering
Jing that's a good song
yeah oh man oh I was listening I was
listening to the pineapple song I think
was the first video you list the
pineapple let's go yeah yeah and I think
I think the cutest lyric was like you're
stuck on me like a sticker all right I
love that
part oh so is that you like that kind of
music
it's a very cute
song I have I have an album if you want
to listen to it I released it
recently it actually has like all kind
of uh uh different um genres like
pineapple is pretty like cute K-pop but
I also have some some more how to say
what is what is retrospective I guess
more like
Rocky Evan Essence Style song and then I
have a more futuristic EDM song that's
really cool a this and that yeah a Rock
ballad emo what's the music you go to
normally music that I go for uh is like
pretty like Teen Angst Teen Angst oh
then you would love retrospective I
think you have to listen to the
retrospective yeah it's it's in the
album it doesn't have uh like its own
video yet uh yet I'm uploading it soon
but if you go to my YouTube channel to
the release section then uh like there's
the YouTube music uploads the automatic
ones then you can go to I send it to you
actually you send it to me girlfriend
I'll check it out but I think uh after a
5 hour stream I got to take myself and
my little girl here to the bathroom so
oh yeah that's see that's one thing
about doggos that I feel like I could
never keep up with like all the
G yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
she gets it but Ryan but Ryan is like
the best because she doesn't make a peep
she just waits for you to take her out
so you don't want to abuse that that's
so swe abuse that well you know what I
actually I was wondering if maybe one
day in the future maybe you want to do
like a a a German challenge by streaming
AOE in German with me on my German
Channel
yeah yeah I did I last I think my last
last week I streamed in German and it's
kind of annoying because you have to
remember there's like all these words
that you never use in ger maybe this way
I can help you a little bit like
Clank
skirmisher okay right okay or a
p what the freak is a
yeah okay yeah these words are H
normally I wouldn't use it either M you
have a whole bunch uh even stuff like
Munch ah Munch yeah yeah Munch okay no
mun so I was like how do you say monk oh
it's m Munch
Munch not mun another one Cassandra what
uh cassana for Barra C
[Music]
C learning German with Age of
Empires yes all of the medieval
terminology for your daytoday awesome
needs well if you want so we can fresh
freshen refreshen your German and you
help me a bit more with
AOE okay look at that Mario cosplay
thereo y y
you're awesome Ellie you're so great I'm
so glad that like you know it was
actually the first time that we really
spoke 10 minutes before the stream but
like we're getting a well so long well I
can't even speak English anymore cuz I'm
so
happy a I don't really fun time too you
have a wonderful
community and uh I'm honored that uh it
looks like they had a good time too so
did you guys like I got a little bit too
focused I couldn't talk with you guys so
much but I hope you enjoyed like we
actually made progress ress that last
that last one there was a lot of
confidence in that one and less pausing
way less pausing yeah you feeling so
[Laughter]
I
a all right then that great are you
going to like do
anything after I say goodbye in your
stream do you continue to play or do you
go with your dog when no I think I'm I
think I'm going to start I'll end my
stream cuz I have take Ryan out and I
have to take myself out you know yes me
too now don't kill yourself that sounds
you know it's Friday so I wish I could
tell you I I had some hot date planed
but um I was the hot date you were the
hot date that's true and you were my hot
dat but I my dreams of mus muscle mommy
status continue so I got to go to the
gym in the morning oh oh teach me teach
me how to gym we're working on it we're
working on I'm 's a big girl all right
do you use the rowing
machine no no I'm more into the I'm more
into like body weight exercises so not
body weight uh how much do you LIF
compound movements compound movements
what I'm looking for it depends on which
lift what we're talking about not the go
well I should be able to bench 60
kilograms by the end of the year but
we're still working on it okay okay
sounds pretty strong I can lift um
maybe uh it depends on how long but
maybe for for if I have to Liv for 10
minutes then probably my most is 5
kilogram oh that's a lot of kilogram no
I really struggle so much with even my
groceries that that's why I bought like
a
trolley cuz Okay well I mean I'm quite
tall I'd say I'm um always a big you do
look really tall in all the like
videos tall how
tall yes
dollar
179 dollar what
whoa
183 dollar what no way no way
186 a little show
oh oh that's
nothing4 like maybe 18 185 in the
morning holy wait what's our
tallest woman in whole life Kyla crony
who was it who's the tallest they might
have even been smaller than her how tall
are you uh 167 167 oh you know what they
say 64 I mean 644 the perfect Heights
together o h narissa our tallest woman
is is
175 that's nothing against Ellie you're
towering over
us damn that's you
know you know I just grew you know it's
not I feel like it's there's not much I
can say other than like yeah I grew I'm
big you know it's not like I I didn't do
anything for it do you but do you like
your your Heights do you like
it um well I would I would be very sad
if I said no I feel like being tall has
been a big part of my identity for so
long I try not to make it like my whole
personality but obviously it affects a
lot of my day-to-day life from like
finding clothes that fit sometimes you
do hit your head like it's not that bad
because I'm not like freakishly tall
yeah you know um so it's not like I'm
190 centimeters or 200 centimeters where
I'm hitting my head on everything it's
not that bad but still like you do bump
it from time to time yeah but clothes
are really annoying um I do eat a lot
like I weigh a lot I eat a lot you
know damn like wow so
tall you get a lot of the
um actually when I was in when I was
living in Toronto I was at um Nathan
Phillip Square which is like the New
York Times Square of Canada kind of kind
of kind and I remember there was like
this really uh sweet Asian family that
came up to me and then they're like
photo photo and I thought that they
wanted me to take a picture of them I
said yeah sure they want your picture
wanted to take a picture with
me they're fascinated by your height I
can see that sometimes like I by
tourists I also got asked for pictures
before just by being cute I
guess it's kind of weird
though yeah if you go to wait have
you ever been to Japan probably not
right no it is on my two visit list for
sure my one of my uh former housemates
just got back from trip really like yeah
right now like everybody's going you
should go
too I've got my little baby but
especially in Japan like you're going to
Bonk your head a lot cuz like buildings
are built like much
smaller much that the ceilings are yeah
well I can be quite compact
okay duck you're just going to become a
duck and ducking everywhere quack quack
quack something like that oh yeah you
could be on my tour guide you can come
to Switzerland then we go together to
Japan oh I'm in Japan quite a lot like
this year um my upcoming trip will be
like the fifth or the sixth trip to
Japan this year so yeah I go a lot for
work so it might just work
out if you need like translation help or
anything I'm your girl are you see one
Japanese oh I I didn't I didn't ever
take like a test but I I speak fluent
Japanese people can confirm oh cuz I
lived in Japan as well girl yeah where
did you
go where I went where did you go yeah I
briefly uh I lived in I lived in Tokyo
and Osaka each uh for a while like for
in total I I think I lived one year in
Osaka maybe and two years in Tokyo but
like there were some breaks in between
like my first two years and then there
were a few years back in Austria and
then I went for another year for working
holiday in Japan recently which is
during the working holiday time is when
I joined whole live but it's also when
the it was the time where um Co started
exploding everywhere yeah and then whole
life basically Saved Me by giving me
something to do and a new meaning of
life yeah that's all coming up mil house
that's up all coming up meal
house what do you not watch The Simpsons
is that a reference that The Simpsons
well I watched The Simpsons probably
more than um um
SpongeBob oh mil house that was the dude
that with the blue hair that was the
dude with the blue
hair okay okay well I I haven't watched
Simpsons for a while but I do like it
yeah a yeah he do you watch it in
English I'm sorry I don't have enough
Tim Allen references for you okay but
like you know it's hard for me to
understand these references from shows
that I watched when I was younger
because I would have watched them in
German yeah I do like Family Guy know
and stuff like that comparing to
Simpsons you know if we're talking about
cartoons then fair enough fair enough
yeah the Family Guy the you know the
Peter Griff and falling down holding his
knee oh yeah love that one that that
that's applicable to so many Age of
Empires scenarios you don't this is
comical at this point really yeah you
lose a villager to a boar yeah that's
a being like Oh my God that just did so
much damage on me but I guess it really
did
so AOE players be very dramatic when
they lose one villager ah life is over
I'm I will quit
forever well at lower elos it doesn't
really make that big of a deal but if
you're playing at the top 1% and you
lose a villager early on to a boore it's
going to be quite difficult to
recover I love
that okay well we can talk more in our
future AOE skirmishes let's go and then
someday we play ranked oh that would be
the day I want to be there for oh you
know what we can do we can like team up
in a ranked match like together two
versus two or something like
that
yeah will I drag you down I would no I'd
say my ELO my team game ELO is very very
high
and I usually when I play 2v tws I'm
playing with like 2K6 ELO H and they
carry me all right I'll get up to your
level first and then we can play
together yeah well I have to like
deflate my team game ELO first but we
definitely play more in the future have
fun today yeah I'm so happy you know at
the end of my streams I always have this
one greeting maybe you want to do it
with
me um what is it girl it goes like and
in German we say
aliden so you can join in in the Alida
Zin as you know what it means
okay okay are you guys ready and in
German we say Al
yay thank you so much it was a blast
thanks guys for watching thanks for
having me thank you for teaching
me Co K her link is in my description
for her twitch you guys can go through
her archive I guess you guys don't have
archives but um no we have vods
something like that yeah we got vods
over here on Twitch too here and there
you know yeah if you want to see more
AOE professional AOE there's a lot of
that being cast use professional term
very Loosely here okay professional to
me oh shakas shakas shakas all right
then bye-bye see you tomorrow for Final
Fantasy byebye cheers
[Music]
Chey
oh yeah guys I'm still here I'll talk
about Kobo and all that stuff tomorrow
in my final fantasy stream so see you
[Music]
theree