[music]
H
a
[music]
T
DET
[music]
H
[applause]
G
[music]
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Congratulations
The white team is all here now, so it's a table.
Display Are you in the vs. room? Are you in the vs. room?
You can sleep well
Star is good
Okay, finally, okay, okay, okay.
I wonder if everyone is here. Let's gather together. Ah yes.
Yes, gather, gather, gather, gather, where, where, gather
Where is it hahahahahahahaaaamanekata teacher yes
I'm not a teacher, but I'm not a teacher.
Not at all, I'm just glad I happened to be here.
Ah, is everyone gathered together?
It's more and more okay book
Thank you very much, teacher, please take attendance.
Please, I'll go. White group A.
I'll come from the other side.
Clearance please
Masu Gan-senpai yes hello too
Thank you very much Masuame Tepa
Kanata-san
teeth
Lemay-chan
Yay yay inami you nai tome
you
It's okay, that kind of candy
Chanameameamechanamechan
Meme-chan
That's great. Let's go home.
Yeah God God
God Wow, thank you very much.
People who break up and become A over a phone call
Yes, yes, yes, B is healthy.
Chocolate Sensei Wow!
Iriorio
Izu-chan is Koazukizuki
Please, please, Captain, yes, hello.
I'm the leader, hello hello haha ​​fight yeah
Yeah yeah yeah
Yes, yes, yes, darling
Yes, yes, yes, yes, hollow up
I'll do my best. Look how hard I practiced.
I've been there forever
It's like, well, can we do this here too?
I wonder if I should go.I should go.
That's what I think of today, Raden-chan.
But I'm a little undecided.
I'm sorry
Sorry for the inconvenience, my second junior is here.
Sorry for the inconvenience
I thought it was coming, so I guessed it. It looks like it.
I did a little research
It's similar to the one I've been doing research on.
So, Nemaraden-chan's
I want to cover the text as well.
Thank you very much for your understanding.
death
Try harder
Home hunting and Raden
chan appears, but that's just me
I came out instead
As a hunter, I will continue to work as a hunter.
I'm not telling you what will happen to the line yet.
Looks like it's going to be a while, so please look forward to it.
Are you wandering around alone? Someone comes?
I'll close it
I don't know why, but I also saw him working hard by himself.
I'm alone and I'm taking pictures of everyone
Maybe, just do your best and hit it and hit it
I might be saying something spy here.
I'm really messed up here
There's a spy-like senior at the festival.
There's a spy here, I'm telling you to leave.
In the white team's waiting room, right here in the classroom.
If everyone is waiting, I'd rather have a competition.
That's right
I'm really curious about who it is, but it doesn't seem like it's anyone.
All of them are gathered together.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good
I'm glad everyone gathered together.
There's a signboard that says something about any grandmother.
Where should I put this?
You can't put it somewhere else, right?
I don't have it, so I can't put it there.
Is this how it is?
How to do this
Signboard used
have
do
mosquito
That's it
Oru
is
Poroporo came to spy on Zhang Lu.
Everyone is coming, it's great. See you tomorrow.
Scouting a slightly different place where the scout group is coming.
Should I go scouting? Red team
I wonder how everyone in the red team feels now.
Let's play it together and have fun
Something?
There's no one there, but there's a lot of people
I can hear the sound of Gozaru hitting from everywhere.
Good time
It's too expensive. Don't die.
Yo
I wonder if it's okay or if it's already started
Probably the main thing is Mr. Rigros during practice.
We were getting into a lot of trouble with each other.
That's right, Kiruro was all Rigro-san.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
You're holding a signboard in your left hand.
I can't take it anymore, but today 1
The signboard may be on during the day.
I can't take it, I can't take it, I can't take it, I can't take it
I'm glad I wasn't able to get the missing cat.
It's not just that, it's true, but what?
Everyone who has a mask is dangerous
Too fixed
Is it okay to bring traps in competitions?
No, it's probably because the signboard tells you to reset your inventory.
I think it is
Maybe when you're infected
left hand all the way
mosquito
That's a lot of knowledge, Minecraft Creator
As expected of one of you, I'll see you soon.
That's right, I'll debug it. Good luck.
I'll do my best again this time as a devilish criminal at the Minecraft Sports Festival.
Do your best and
That's amazing! As always, please tell me anything.
There's no need to attack someone who is lying.
It didn't happen, it didn't, it didn't, didn't it?
Is it true, my dear?
Is it true that Kura made this? Amazing
Well then next time
Carry something like that
hand
Ru
I don't know what to do
We don't know where the camera is.
I can't hear it, but I can hear it.
I can't hear it
I'm not like Subaru Senpai.
It's not a misunderstanding.
Okay, this is it, okay then.
So I think I'll make a call.
all
Please let me enter.
It's the first announcement, everyone's not red.
hey
A lot of people are going
It's white, it's white, it's mememe
[music]
Some meme
Mememe it's this way
I fell down the next morning saying I was going to make fun of it.
now
Here it is
Wow
Sasa-san is a genius again this year, really.
There's a line to get out. I'll do my best to line up the whites neatly.
Let's do it completely here
Hey, come with me, mom here.
Let's stay here
is
Could you please line up here in row 11?
Everyone said yes, so next was everyone from the white group.
Please enter.
Coming soon
O go go go go
Yes yes yes yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, it's Shino, yes, yes, yes, yes.
stomach
That's good, that's the power. Lastly, that.
I would like to receive the help from the yellow group.
Kaonan, Kaonan, Kaonan
Hey, Kashi-chan is hiding, and so are you.
Oh no, wait, it's me
I noticed the length, but I decided to take this route.
I'm sure the camera was prepared, but nothing happened.
Ni-chan is hitting me so hard. I'm hitting her so hard.
I'm buzzing
Why is it such a beautiful composition? The white team is so beautiful.
I'm an honor student. I'm an honor student. I'm serious.
Let's go, I'm serious, I'm going to be mega-quick.
Only Kana-chan who can win in the Gozaru frame is pink.
Hold a sign
It's true, it's yellow.
Signboard Is that what it is? It's true.A white signboard.
It's a shame because there wasn't even a signboard.
Have
[music]
It's a big deal that I asked for it.
Yes, please give me the correct answer.Hahaha
So everyone
Hello meow meow
Hello, it's amazing everyone gathered here.
Thank you very much for your busy work.
Seniors and juniors really helped each other until today.
I think he encouraged me in practice as well.
But today is the actual event, so please help everyone!
Give it your all and get the victory!
I hope I can get it.First of all,
Everyone should have fun and aim to win.
So everyone, please enjoy it.
Thank you very much for your help today.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Yes, please continue, Mr. Yago, President of Cover Co., Ltd.
We have received messages from
Please take a look here Yes, please take a look
Thank you for your hard work, please. Company Representative
of
But when it comes to sports day, it's all about the neck.
It's gymnastics
It's not in the program that doesn't care.
Anochan and the training members and from early on.
Get ready for today
Shie, thank you very much for your hard work.
At today's sports day, we cooperated with each other.
Encourage each other and fight bravely until the end
Let's do it and always use the option
Thank you very much thank you
Please pay attention to the hard work of Mazamazami.
I hope you will support this.
Members, please be careful of monsters.
Please, let me say hello.
No, I'm injured.
[music]
Yo
Please, teacher, I'll go.
Do your best, do your best
Stinky good player
The teacher is the most serious in our serious category.
No doubt please please
Please
Please do it. Good luck.
wish
Thank you very much for your support.
Watermelon
My ears are strange
It's okay, it's okay
[music]
Is it dangerous? Hakosu Hakosu Kamon Kamon
Hacos Hacos Hacos Hacos
Hakos is great, it's great, a great teacher
Do you think you can do your best?
keep it up
Good luck, I'll ask you to do it, Mr. Player.
Is that okay?
Yes, please
Teacher Masu
All of us players are Hololive members.
With the teacher who took over sportsmanship.
Do you want to fight? No, it's 2023.
November 4th Red group representative Virtue White group representative A yellow
Representative Haspels
Yeah
Thank you very much.It's okay to go home.
Thank you very much
I'm sorry for throwing bread at you.
Thank you very much for coming tomorrow.
The sun shines brightly
Ta
Special edition
Please
Who's moving? I'm moving.
Excuse me for being so free. Group 7 has a terrible voice.
The 7 Koehaku group fugitives are on each group's contestant channel.
Please go to the white team's player channel.
The sound quality of a real sports day
Ya Megan
It looks a little off, but it's real.
So still
It's home like some idiot channel.
Is it the first round of hunting? Only those who are on the first round.
Only those who enter are like that.
Well, on the white team contestants' channel.
I'm going, so Ame-chan Kaela Nerisa
yes
O
Good luck and good luck
please
Player channel no
[music]
No, do your best, try your best, try your best
Hey Gluck Good Luck Good Luck
completely
That and Japanese are becoming a mess of English.
Gozaru
That's the third one, Kaela. That's right.
It's Kaela
Hey, nice, that's cool
I wonder if all three of us could go.
Is it okay to be a fugitive? This is no good.
Is it because we're infected or because the white team is the hunters?
Look at the lever and white
I look like a hunter, so I'll support you like a hunter.
Are you going to support me? Everyone except that meba.
You don't have to be a fugitive to support me.
What group is this fugitive from? What group is this from?
Will there be an announcement about whether it will be held? Yes, yes.
I wonder if there will be an announcement?
Check now
Everyone except Degozaru Hunter Team or 2.
Maybe we're different, Hunter.
It's not Team, so it's called White Hunter Team.
I mean, are you going to stab the three hunters?
I'm not sure if it also refers to the white group of hunters.
I guess he's pointing at the frame, right? This is the first match.
It's written red and it's red and white.
Other than that, I am a fugitive once.
This is the entry
It means you can go there with a book.
Hey, you can press it. It's a flycatcher.
I can't do it.
Yeah nevermindwedo
Enter the email that cannot be entered.
I'm in the middle of the day
We were entering
[music]
is now so already entered
Well, I know what you should do here.
I see that you can do it if you do it. At first, it's red.
Throw away the red
It's okay even if you don't press Ruppai Aja.
Are you okay
Oh, sorry, excuse the side announcement.
I'll be happy to help, Kairoha-san and Robo-san.
Nakiamesan Tenkasannamesan Yuchoco
Sanahane White Team Competitor Channel
Please contact us.
Is it the other way around? The creatures are moving.
This may be the other way around, or it may be the other way around.At first, everyone
It seems that the runners are moving, not because they are running away.
Yes, the fugitive is on the contestant channel.
Is it okay if I move?
I see, what number is it? In the same field, there are white team competitors.
That's what the channel is all about.
thing
Or hunter, here, here, here.
It's right, here, here, this, this, this, White group teaching.
Well then, the fugitive who runs away is here.
It's a channel
It's difficult, it's difficult today.
It's difficult, it's difficult, this practice is difficult today.
I wish it was number 1
This is the most powerful among them.
I want to
motion
The one that I couldn't do the most
It's true that if you overcome this and that, you can do it.
Okay, I see, I gave it to you perfectly.
Well then, please wait.
At first, the red one is the hunter.
The White Team will all run away. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, everyone is a contestant.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
say
hey
[music]
Oh this
Only hunters
but
Stay upstairs
Well, only hunters seem to be superior.
Thank you
[music]
O
Where to run away, run away, run away
I'm probably the fugitive from the team that won't run away.
It seems like it's set automatically.
It's not just a mat, it's that theme.
For example, with the people from the red team.
If Kadehunter were from the Koushiro group or something.
We're being targeted, so run away!
There's a rope that looks like a click
Even if I get caught, I'll run away as fast as I can
I feel like I want to
Oh yeah, Korea.
I'm going to Korea. I'm leaving.
It's not there, so it's surprisingly behind the cage.
It's a hiding place, yes, a bit
No one is like that.
On the other hand, I'll go to the wide side opposite the cage on my cat's side.
There's no one behind the cage
I see, I see, it's the same behind the pillar.
Nekana-tan, there's something I'm a little concerned about.
Yes, yes, there's something about the Asa staff.
I wonder what it's like, I'm watching the text channel.
But the 7th fugitive from the white team has arrived as a contestant.
This is the second tier, but you should go.
Kananae calls Nodoka-chan that name.
That's right, it seems like it's not a contestant.
That's why it's the first and second round of hunting.
It would be better if both people went to the other side.
I'm wondering if it's okay to use it, but yes
Well, that's what you call me.
It was about Aa-chan, but maybe it wasn't conveyed.
That's right, that's right, that's what it means.
I see, I feel like it's kind of like that.
I guess I'll have a listen.
Please tell the announcer this
Thank you so much Ramen-chan
Yes, I was called just now.
But maybe Ra-chan will still be participating.
Maybe it feels like that
Yes, I will, yes, I will, that's right, is that so?
Is that what you mean? Then you're really a hunter.
Only those who don't have to be on this channel right now
Something seems to be flying.
But Amichi
It's the power of God. It really is the power of God.
You have the power of God, my God.
hand
[music]
I asked Yosho anyway.
Thank you very much Daikanasuke
I wonder what's going to happen this time.
I wasn't listening to what was going on, now that I think about it...
I practiced how to play the competition.
But it is so
I guess that's the whole flow of Gozaru.
It seems like there were no materials, but there were also some materials.
I'm probably reading Degozaru right now, but it's probably both.
It is written that everyone other than the contestants can be combined.
Please write down all players other than those from other teams.
Which one is there?
Dokidokidokidokidokidokidokidokidokidokidokidokidokidokidokidoki
[laughter]
Yo
Ade staff is inputting data.
I wonder if Takata will come back?
I wonder which one it will be, but today everyone
It's a bit of a long road, so I didn't plan on it.
Well, it's probably around 9 o'clock, but maybe
I also felt like I shouldn't push you.
It has a bit of an atmosphere.
So the atmosphere is a bit timid.
take a break
Ena is hungry, so let's eat some food.
Looks like we'll have a relaxing time
It's long, so this is the real pleasure of the club.
Looks good, looks great, looks great
It's difficult, but I guess it's because I'm watching Daigo.
It seems different.
Isn't that right? It's called Daiten.
It looks like a book
It's a real thrill, it's a real thrill.
The answer is that it says real pickpocket.
Coming
Real Real Thrill Real
First of all, let's take a look at the thrill of Thrillus.
Hunter is AB Channel Adora so it's in its current form.
It seems to be correct.
It's true, it's true, the second time this happens, Deputy Director
The three teachers went over there and it was like this diagonally.
Does that mean I can just ignore it?
That's fine, there aren't 7 of us.
123456789
9 people9 people
That's right, thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your reply
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
In the first game, if red is first, everyone runs away.
I have to, but I'm not sure what it will be like.
What will happen to me? Yes, yes, yes, yes
That's right, what's going to happen? The channels are parting ways.
Just by doing it together, just by voice
It suddenly starts at the beginning
It's coming soon, it's coming soon
[music]
Run away, run away, run away
Look around the English members
Let's protect it by flickering
Let's protect our English members.
Let's protect English members and remember
I'm hiding in the back, where is it?
I haven't
Even if I don't protect you, people are watching me, and my back is also being watched.
No, first of all,
It's dangerous to protect it
Rerurereru
It changes
evening
14 If that's the case
No, this is a high school show, so squat down.
A little bit of 149cm
Let me make a mistake
It's below 149
Hey, but it's failing. What's this?
The perfect person is 149.
It's below, so it's included.
It's quite small, 149cm tall.
I'm not all squatting, I'm 149cm.
Tiny
It's amazing how tall you are. On the other hand, it's kind of amazing
Little people don't run away anymore, they're confident
Just like that
I'll walk with full faith
Yo
It's dangerous to see
Wakakore
The answer is, on the contrary, I got caught, a little bit.
Do you want to be caught?
What is the meaning of this?
too
It's more like a coincidence though
Na-chan, na-chan, catch that!
Someone please catch me, I can go, I can go
Yo, what do you think? Who is it? I go, Chan-chan, me.
I can go, you can catch me, that's right.
shellfish
What is this?
Well, it was a quick kill, but I'll stay here.
Help me before I get caught.
Hey, who is going to catch me too?
It's over!
Who was it?
I'm sure it was quite a bit of Anya.
Looks like it's different
It's so awkward that I can't even say it
It's crackling
[music]
hey
Nehan White Hunter goes to voice chat
Please move
There are 6 people in total, so I guess it's 6 people.
It's written here, it's true
Hello, I'll go, wait a minute.
Excuse me, the 6 people I've been waiting for aren't here.
The six members of Masu are here with all the fugitives of the Ashirogumi group.
Everyone who rejected it now, White group ABB.
Please move to the original voice chat.
I will do it
[music]
I'm tired
Dear Mr.
Hey, I'm back.
Tata
Oh, I feel like I'm rooting for you. I'm rooting for you.
Kaela-san was also there.
Somehow we managed to separate into blue and blue.
I say this without fail.
So I guess I should just stay in the audience seats.
That's right, let's get caught.
I wonder if it's okay for people like this to stay here.
Are you still under arrest? You haven't come out yet. Come out.
I can't get out, I can't get out, I'm actually caught
It's a lie in Toriguri, the game is over
Maybe someone in the middle of the game will be in Korea.
is
It's true, I haven't been able to escape from jail.
can't do it
Don't get out of here. That's South Korea. It's South Korea.
Yoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyooyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyo
Hello, Kia-chan is here too, Umeshito.
Maybe it won't come out until it's a book.
I wonder if it's okay if we stay. Shall we take a photo?
Korean Korea
Nadayo, yes, it's my country, it's Korea, it's a photo
and
Thank you, Korea, I'm going to take a picture of Korea
That's right, my face is stuck in the grass.
Gozaru is so hot, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.
It's nice over there, right there, right there.
It's okay
I got it, I'm going to get it.
Successful jailbreak reset
Thanks to you, I finally got out, now I'm a white hunter.
It's time for you to work hard.
Let's support Wanka, let's support, let's support
Then I'll put it on white, it's Korea.
Yoe
Thank you, I can take it properly
It's kind of like this
I feel like I should show it to the listeners as well.
Okay, this is the best shot. Wait a minute.
Download it too, wait a minute.
Korean Photo Jailbreak Korea Evil Korean Photo
Where is it really?
It's really full, but it's very close.
I can get it underground, at a really close distance.
Gozaru
Wait, let's get it out.
It's Korea! It's Korea.
[music]
I've already escaped from prison.
Wow, the escape was a success, yo everyone.
I'm entering. Yes, I'm entering.
Teru degozaru is getting angry, it's infected.
infection infection
It's spacious, isn't it?
The infection was actually created by this infection seat mat.
But it seems like it's okay.
But in the end, I want to think that there are only 6 people.
I'll try my best
Humans are too wide. Each person uses one block.
There is 1 block
It's really big here.
Even if there's plenty of space left, it's just too spacious.
I'm sure you can see the whole thing
It feels so good
Ta
If you want to create a neighborhood in Korea
I went away, and I'm sure I'm seated behind Korea.
It looks like it would be fun, but it's definitely a mistake
I went to the yellow team that I made.
I've been breaking something right now.
Are you okay? I'm back. I'm back. I'm back.
Ta
There was an interview, so 2 races.
It's like I've seen it with my eyes.
I had an interview with
[music]
Ta
It's okay, Mu-chan, it's just that you're confused, it's okay.
Are you okay
Kete
Avoid me, I'm laughing so hard
It's okay, it'll be fine. It'll be fine.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, I thought
But judging from the way you're talking now, how much longer?
I heard you said something really interesting.
I was jealous, you were so blurry, you were blowing, blowing
A dream where I'm walking around a lot
Senpai, let's do it, let's do it, let's go
Let's do it, let's go
Yaroue shero team cello team
Shiro team Shichishichi
Chimshishia White Team Hunt, so we
That means I'm not a fugitive either, right?
That's true, I want to run away, I want to run away
Hey, run away
It's okay, I'll run away next time, so yeah
Yes, please wait a moment until the next escape.
Yes, be polite until the next escape.
of
Tentsu is so well behaved
I think it's because we're a good team.
Yes, everyone was polite, so it looked beautiful.
The white team lined up the best.
Yes, they were lined up like our colors.
As clear as our white color
Clear and white Clear and clear White white and white
Is it clear? Clear means clear?
Niyabee
Well, 12 people toy
There are 200 people gathered, so it's dangerous.
Feels good
Niiyasu
keep it up
Do your best, I wonder what's coming.It's a theme.
The debut will probably be in 2022 or later.
22 It's easy, isn't it? It's quite recent.
This is it, Holos.
It looks like it will barely fit into the rocks.
twenty one
I guess that's right, up to Holos, maybe Rocks.
He's been caught, but he's running away.
That live English thing
English Sasei and English 3rd season
ID's 3rd season of ID
Yeah, I see it's different. It's a bit 2020.
Yes, this is the summer of 2020.
I want a name that won't be difficult to find.
I found it so rude
Tekunno is
Do your best, do your best, Mouko Daiko-san
Nohachamotomariga
Hurry up and make sure you have enough time
People who wanted to get caught wanted to get caught too.
I feel like I'm being asked for something.
The feeling of being chased makes me happy, right?
Short bob short bob ah nothing at all
It's not secured at all, it's not secured at all.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Okay, catch everyone, no matter what.
Apparently if you catch 3 people, you'll get at least 1 bob.
I'm here, short
Bob is okay for now
There's a better way to go. Everyone's in. Go.
Go go where are you? It's so quiet
Not
Why are you all so quiet?
I'm so sorry for messing around with you just now.
I'm taking you with me too, that's nice.
Nice, maybe this is also stuck in one place
I'm sure they're planning a strategy, but it's all over now.
Kids, no, no, that's good. Rokis, no, no, no.
I'm saying it was good, but it's getting better.
I'm sure it's not kids.
I feel like I'm going to go crazy, but I feel like I'm going to go crazy
I'm the only one who can't get into it, Aokuo.
I'm sure Anya has been arrested, it's true.
Anya it's a scratch, it's a scratch
Isn't it your sister? It was your sister.
Hey, this is wrong. I'm worried about this. I'm worried about this.
Okay, but I wonder if he's going to go into a bar. He's tough.
It's not true, it's not Kits.
No, it's not.
It's a frame of a woman with big breasts and scratches.
It's nice to see it
I'm going in
I have no choice but to run away
It seems like we should just run away
Run away, run away and be with me
Let's catch, catch, catch with the group.
Yes, please catch them all already.
If you don't understand after adding everyone, just choose as you see fit.
It's fine if you put everything in.
I don't know what to do, when the subject is also a question.
It's not easy, it's difficult, it's common
It's not just recognition, it's funny so-and-so.
You seem to think so.
certain
niseewasUnder
TOPSECONDRsaysPRENG
wasKID
frompersEX
[music]
any
Oh, excuse me, kids, please explain.
Thank you, thank you, Gura-chan is a kid.
Maybe, but it was already there.
It's true that sometimes things like that happen, luck.
When I feel like I did something wrong, who am I?
Naru no Todoroki-san and Kono Kaji-san.
Isn't that true?
I think it's probably an entry-level kid.
Looks like kids
face
I can see a lot of things up close
Hello, I would really like to know the answer.
You're the last one
show who was
[music]
My senior was completely on board.
I stroked it
It seems like it is
Na
I feel like Nerisa is like that same person.
I feel it
Too bad I couldn't get that or that.
It's okay to ensure that.
It's okay, it's okay, there were 0 people.
I care
It's okay, it's okay
Big
It's okay, it was difficult.
It was a little more difficult than practice, so it's definitely a big deal.
That's right, practice. No problem, no problem. There's a practice table.
That's too easy, isn't it?
Kotori is fine, it's okay.
No, no, that leader and Chiara are covering it.
I'm going, so I'm looking forward to it.
You're going to change, okay?
I'll let everyone in, so I'll leave it to one side.
Add all the people you can find.
hand
I need some strength, so please use your strength to move.
so move
move
[music]
oh andlikeforforthe
shortcutdidoneoftry
toinfor
shortcut
considered
[music]
hairdefaultJA
Fair enough
It's fine, don't worry about it
Hey
I want to
Noprem so no
problem no problem
Deshika-chan is so worried
Problem no problem Look, look, look
Please, look, look at this poor person.
This is how I feel now
Dee
What's leaking?
Where is it?
I couldn't find it
I really want to do that kind of situation.
Open this door, open it, and close it right away.
Later
It's best to do this in front of a closed door.
It's so nice to be able to put in so much.
[music]
Lola
My head smells like crunchy earth.
It smells like earth
Something big
It stinks.
That's right
[music]
say
Hey ki
I'm sorry, Ki-chan, it's bad.
I'm doing something
a little bit
Close contact with opponents
It's too late, we're standing side by side.
It was cute, wasn't it?
Stand up, oh yeah, that, that, that, that.
Red, that's it
[applause]
Kaikaiko no Makoto Cushion
I can release it. This is definitely a big deal.
I'm sure you're selling cuteness, right?
Your head is so cute, it won't end.
Oh yellow yellow yellow
It's Yellow's turn to run away.
run away
Oh, let's run away, it's our turn to run away, do your best
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Do your best, run away, run run, run away, okay?
Well, I want to go to Korea, but I can't.
No, no, only fugitives, only fugitives.
Touch the fugitive, touch the fugitive, even if it's without permission
You may have already entered.
It seems like it has been done.
Run away, run away, run away
Dandan
Right, this is it already
and others
Who should I do?
stomach
Re-hiding Nice Nai Hidden
I'm messing with you and I'm going to make you mess up.
Kanata Fresh
Deshimashi
Let's go there. It's him.
If you try to appeal to your motivation, it's true
Newa
I'm a newbie. I'm a newbie.
It's dangerous, it's changing, it's changing, it's changing
change change
What's the point of watching it? It's a mess.
It's just 460. Even if you catch it, it's completely through.
I lost my life
There's no way that's true. Wait a minute, Commander.
Caught
But
Gigi, I'm sorry, Nerena.
I wonder if the aura is safe. It's okay.
Hide it in, hide it, chocolate 65 That's right.
Gozaru hidden
Oh, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's hidden
I was in charge
Tekkashite
Please
It seems that it is
I feel like it's dangerous. Even if I catch you, it's different.
Yo
Different and different
I'm losing something
Well, come on, someone please arrest me.
do not have
I'm really prepared for that.
But there's no way to excuse yourself.
Kazari-san isn't very neat anymore.
Even the screams are pure, it's not pure.
Whatever you say, she's so pure and innocent.
There's applause. There's dissatisfaction. There's also dissatisfaction.
Sleep
Nice, nice, I got bored and didn't get caught.
It wasn't there. I've been waiting for you, Gem-chan.
I'm running away, but I'm sure Azusan is running away.
I'm definitely a member, I'm a member, I'm a member.
I ran away, so I'm a little aware of what's wrong with me.
It's cute to have
No, what will happen?
It's scary how innocent you are.
Or definitely clean it, run away properly
I don't think it's great, Naiha-chan
I guess I have to run away, even if it's neat and clean.
I don't think I'll get caught
It was a really strong yellow.
They caught a lot of people. It was amazing.
hey
It was amazing
It wasn't the Captain's War, it was just one more run away.
Well, I've already made an entry.
Everyone did this, thank you for caring about it.
round
run away run away
It's okay, but when you're an adult, Captain.
Or something
Yes, like a woman with a certain color, like an older sister.
I wanted to be chosen no matter what.
Yeah, my height wasn't chosen either.
Money, the girl who misunderstood me, the polka
I guess you misunderstood me, so I'm a little cagey.
I was able to get close to the cage, but the cage is really small.
Seriously, I really don't like it.
It's already a game if I get caught
You can't escape inside, that hunter.
Right, until the next game.
Seniors who stay behind should do their best to run away.Next.
Mio-senpai is wrong. Who will think that? Next is Mio-senpai.
But I think Nemi-senpai is going to be alright.
Yeah, that's what it is, but it's weird.
It's possible that it will change, it's definitely not possible.
There's a possibility, but I want you to protect it.
I want to finally meet you.
If you do it like this,
Just say no, I want to be protected.
Yeah
Shizukutsuio shoes
Shoes
All the shoes are in a tight fit
This is absolutely disgusting
This little hill is heavy next to Shiotepa.
It's creepy trying to be, but I'm not
That's why everyone is occupied.
Caught in between
Look at it seriously, they're cute side by side
Tennoun is cute
hey
Hey, someone please line up next to me.
It became
to
Let's reset, oh maybe one more time
I guess I'll have to start over again.
Okay
O
Okay okay okay okay
Okay ooooo
Oh oh oh
Oh, it doesn't matter at all, but Subaru-senpai
There's even a book that has missing nipples.
I worked so hard to make it, but it's gone all the way
How many nipples does Subaru Senpai have when chatting?
I heard it in words like this, but there were two
But why is it there? It's not because birds are eggs.
I don't see it that way.Oh yeah.
I mean, it's become like a specialty.
Even though it was
What's the debut of Nena? I'm lonely.
In 2019
from
It's terrible, it's bad, I'm not in it, I'm sef
Not
[music]
That was in 2019.
That guy is 201 years old.
everyone run away
Are you a good person?
Chancha, I'm sorry, just take a look.
That's different from the leader, the leader, the leader isn't moving.
It's 20192019
Everyone is old
It's la!
Better than that
Ta
Below
It was too early, but run away now. Run away.
It was scary. Artists are gathering now.
Masuko Al
The artist is so sad and unexpectedly so.
It's quite common for Mu-chan to have 3 or more games.
There was an image that was
It's not a Natamasu station.
is
caught
Caught eating
Na
I'm going to get arrested, I'm playing Minecraft, so I'm going to get arrested.
Like this, like this, like this
This is how I got caught
There is
never got caught
Surprisingly, there is no such thing as no.
He has not been arrested yet.
That's not the case.
[music]
hey
Nai is trying to catch me
Teyoyo
Yo
Nice eggplant one nice nice nice nice
I answered all the questions, but I ran away.
Wow, amazing, amazing
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work, I'm moving.
three hunters
Why was I suddenly forced somewhere?
You moved so suddenly
Hello, something suddenly moved here.
Is it okay? Yes, it probably fits here.
I got caught again, I got caught.
I've been arrested again. I've been arrested.
Korea has become a country.
It's a country, but I'm crawling.
I'll give you this too
Yo, what is Korea?
Yo
I'm caught, I'm at a loss, I'm at a loss
I'm bored so I'll bring this out.
I'm sure it's given to you somewhere.
A shot of rice given by Chico Sensei in Korea
It's so slow, it's so surreal
[laughter]
This Noel-senpai has a great sense of lighting and photography.
picture
I understand
I'm so crazy about the camera.
It's a shot, it's a regular shot.
I want you to do your best in your second match, Nakakana, do your best.
Let's go to the cheering seats first.
Do your best! Wait, wait, I accidentally fired the drug.
Please wait a moment, the mouse
What kind of situation did you get in when you got soaked?
That's the dangerous mouse that shot the whole thing by mistake.
become stiff
Live the mouse
It was crazy and I was just petting her.
That's what I was stroking.
I was stroking him, but he hit me.
Hey
[music]
cute
Yeah, I'm looking down, I'm looking down, wait!
So cute, it moved, it moved, it moved
Cute
It's cool, Gura-chan, that's gross.
Graspa
I wonder if Eungura-chan will be cooking soon?
certainly certainly
It's okay, stay here, it's true, wake up
Maybe he was a competitor.
No, I wrote that I have also entered the fugitive.
I think I'll be taken there automatically now.
Do your best, Peen, the one who disappears and gets taken away.
keep it up
The White Sea scuffle begins
There is
shellfish
It's true, I didn't realize it, that's the Subaru statue
Did it get stolen? YouTube-like
Was it the sound?
Na
[music]
Chimau
Yo
Oh, it's coming, it's coming, it's starting, what's the problem?
Something, something, something
There are so many of these, starting from 150.
Very good, very fast
Everyone
[music]
Good luck, who's going to be the first to enter, Iris?
That's fine, just put it in.
Big iris is here
Toa-senpai is hiding here Toa-senpai is hiding here.
I'm hiding, but Toa-senpai is probably the same as Kaze.
I'm going in because I'm in the corner
Yanto
I hide in a mess
Terue is surprisingly different.
Yeah, I'm sure it was wet.
Make it nice, finally, finally
Okay, give me someone behind me. Give me someone behind me.
I wanted to go and catch the beast ears.
Dodoru
It's too early, I wanted to go too early
Who is Fuwamoko-san being arrested?
I can't see Babyjan
Naekari-chan is tall, isn't she? She's tall.
That's right
Yeah
Catch some cotton!
I wanted to go to see you.
I wonder if people from the Gozaru Naeke Emi clan have hearing problems.
Oh yeah, I'm surprised there aren't any, is that Mi?
I wonder which one it is. Ah, I see.
I see, now I'm just looking at my ears, right?
Yes, Fana-senpai has those horns.
It's not the ears, it's the corners or corners that are broken.
No, it's dangerous.
stomach
There are so many stupid judgments.
This is it
The eyes are pretty blurry, but everyone is pretty good.
It's good, it's really good, it's good, ah
It's so bad, it's so strong that you're catching it
That senior is also stupid.
Hmm, 11 people are too lazy, it's so fast, it's so fast
It's not gone anymore, it's just a blur
Yo, Mel-senpai is a fool. Ah, Mizuo-senpai, you are wrong
Here you are, where you worked hard, do your best
You're so amazing, you're so nice
Nice nice nice nice close by
It's a really stupid cow that I've secured, that's stupid.
It's the best record. It might be the best record.
I'm so [ __ ]
If Tae doesn't run away, it's 2, isn't it?
Karayoshi ayoshi nice ah nice ah nice
Nice nice nice nice nice nice
Nice nice you're in the way get rid of it
Ahahaha
[music]
a
Enan is amazing, the one from earlier
Yeah yeah
What's going on? Wait a minute.
Choco Sensei's photo is too good, isn't it?
This is so amazing, this is so good
That's a really good chat
It's photographer Subaru, send this to Subaru.
This is a really good cheat.This is good.
too much
Okay then, we're all going home
Everyone is back, come home, go home, go home
It was really cool. Welcome back everyone.
Nice, it's a lot of hard work.
The waddling beast is so cute all the way to the end
It almost feels like I'm going to get caught.
It's mostly blurry.
My teeth are really big
There are surprisingly few furry ears like this.
It's a little bit like monebame senpai and kakemomi.
I'm surprised, but there's no sign of it.
Well, this seems to be the case.
There aren't many
I wonder if it's the cat's blur, maybe that blur?
I don't like it, but when it comes to body image judgment, there are a lot of people who are not good at it.
I'll bring you a towel.
That's right, that's right, Mi-chan Kamio
Looks like it's someone other than chan
Hey Hollande
A bonus stage in a sense
[laughter]
Daka
I'm done
If Ne does it for me, we'll all be together, so we'll run away.
Let's run away, do your best
Let's do our best, let's do our best Let's go queue
queue
Leggo
Come, come, come
[music]
After all, they gather in some places.
It was a little hard to catch.
Oh no, I have to hide, hide, oh no, I have to hide
It's dangerous, hide it!
senior senior
Hide it, someone has been caught.
Masako Senpai
That's how you got caught, such a great senior.
I feel like I'm going to be so tired from 0 to 2 years old.
It's okay
Oh yeah
He was also caught hiding in Korea.
chan knew
Kacccha
Tat!
It looks like it
to
Departure
depart
well
red
Senpai Wow book
It's not dangerous, he had silver hair.
terrible
It's dangerous
It was the same. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's the same.
But damn, I chased him.
It's no good.
It's time, I'm bored, I'm bored, it's dangerous, catch me
Cho
Zname is a little
Don't fall in there, even if you catch me
Okay here.
There is one chin wan chan in
Ru
Why are you completely ignoring me?
Why did you do it?
Matsuri Senpai Matsuri Senpai I'm here Matsuri Senpai
Not Ceci
What?
But I'm here too
I didn't do it.
Yay, nice, nice, anyway, this is it.
There were 144 people, or 13 people.
nice
white
No, it was just barely dangerous or dangerous.
Even though it was nice and sexy, it was dangerous.
sexy
I'm glad I escaped the frame, it's really good
I was a little surprised.
Even after that, I was happy, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It wasn't
Jan Tsukko Mii
Hey
Gi
Sorry, suddenly
picture
I'm being dragged away more and more. I'm being led away more and more.
Where did everyone go? Are you here?
Yes, it was moved and moved back.
Come back, come back
moved freely
hey
fall, fall, fall, fall, fall, fall, return
[music]
I don't know who will win in the end
I don't know, it seems like it's just a process.
I didn't see it, what do you think?
I wonder where the sexy judgment was?
Mu-senpai
Sexy aaaaaaaa
Yes this is
Chan
[music]
Nocea senior number
Ceci No. 1 Sexy No. 1 Sexy No Nonono
No sexy no no no sexy no sexy
Sexy isn't here Maybe she's not here
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait, wait
Please, Kaela-san is here, oh Ka-chan.
Sexy Kara-san Sexy Nonoka
[music]
teeth
Secu Kako
[music]
People who say, ``Okay, I put out that,' put out that.
I was
I saw Janii Good Day a while ago.
It was good.
You didn't say that, so it's not sexy.
No sex, no sex
Yo, isn't that sexy already?
Would sexy have been better?
I wanted to
That's too bad. I didn't understand it at first.
That's really true
It's yellow, everyone, do your best.
I want to get it and everyone on the other teams until the end.
I want you to run through it. That's why I say yes.
Well then, the next competition is the Ajashiro group, 20 points.
move to up field
Let's please yellow 25 white 20 red
15 The middle or the 2 middle are all exciting.
There's still a lot more to come
rear second next rear second next
Feeling
Let's go up on the flow up
side flow
[music]
Up is bad because Kia senior is not here
English is terrible English
English
[music]
How do you say Let's Go Senpai Sakiresha in English?
I guess
School School School School
School Upside School High
Flow-up floor after school club
School Upside Stage 5 Up
Stage Floor Up Stage 5 Rooftop
I guess you call it the rooftop, right?
I don't know what the ground is at High Ground.
Why don't you say it's not, High Ground?
up
A roof roof that everyone is passionate about
top roof roof top roof top hee
rooftop gogo rooftop gogo
Rooftop Gogo Rooftop Buchta
Yes, I see. Yes, I see.
It almost looks like the upper body.
All the contestants, now this or that.
I guess it's interview time.
I see, I see, I see
Good luck Roboko Senpai Character Senpai
Do your best, work hard, do your best, right?
I feel like I can even call A and B together at all.
Yeah, yeah, it was like that.
I didn't feel like I was being serious.
In fact, Chiara's presence really helps.
Thank you, thank you, thank you
I have been researching Passioning English.
Only those who are likely to use Ocho
I've been looking up English, so I'll give you some information.
No, I haven't used it even once.
Let's use it
I explained this to Ume-chan during a break.
The book I worked hard on is being asked
A little scary
Oh yeah, what is that? Steak
Yeah, how do you say chicken and pork in English?
I discussed this with Mr. Unkei and
When I asked them to grill something, they asked me what I wanted.
That's right, well done for conveying that.
beef pork
Chicken, beef, pork, chicken, chicken, yeah
Rikara
That's why I should shout this to my girlfriend-senpai.
I have to have beef or pork.
or chicken or beef pork
It's like chicken steak steak steak
steak steak beef beef fire
beef beef fire fire
steak
Steak gogo steak eating
I'm not really hungry.
Someone said they were hungry, right?
I'm hungry, I'm hungry.
It's just around 7:30, so dinner will be served.
I guess it's time for JP.
I see, the overseas group is different.
Wad Time In Now Unknown Senpai
Ah, 33am, 3 What time is it, 3 in the morning?
When it's not there, it's morning, morning, morning, rain, senpai, 3 o'clock in the morning, senpai.
Yes, it's the middle of the night. It's the middle of the night. Wow, senpai is having a hard time too.
It's okay Good morning, great sleep It's raining
Wow, that's amazing, thank you very much for the night.
No, thank you very much, Senkyu, it's okay.
Nice to drink coffee
Coffee nice coffee nice coffee
Caffeine Caffeine is important No caffeine
Cuff Caffeine Power Let's Go Ye
Let's
Go Naka Passion English
Let's go!
A great person told me that if I let it go, everything would be okay.
It's okay to believe in that great person who said that.
It's okay, Gozaru-chan throws the trident.
But it's just Nanka-chan
Apparently he has authority, right?
I heard you can carry a trident.
He's throwing it, right? Ah, maybe that.
Maybe, but my
I just did it on the other side the other day.
Holomen hunting creative
Yes, that's right when editing in mode.
I still do this when I practice.
Flying and
I was throwing a javelin by myself about 3 days ago.
Karaa
[music]
It's so sneaky, I'm holding it in one hand.
Trident is cunning. Trident red.
Hitting Mizuo-senpai is no good, senpai, what are you doing?
It's okay, I'm creative.
Is it okay or not to come up from here?
I'm doing it
Or Mizu-senpai came up and said he could do this.
That's right
Is that true?
You can't pick this up, right? Pick this up.
No, this is a photo of Mercury's remains.
Taken
I can read out the stars
Tehiha's star reading is coming out
It's so expensive that it's so expensive
Please don't tell him that. It's really scary.
Please stop
There's something wrong with the trident.
I put some in a ziplock.
That's what I did
That kind of thing, that kind of iron
No, it's gone
It's gone, it's gone, the shot is gone
Oh, please keep it a secret.
I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do.
It's crazy, it all depends on what happens in the future.
Hey, let's see how the rest of the day goes, papa and papa.
I'll buy the rest.
I'm going to go buy some real shoes and lick them.
Why don't you lick my jacket?
what
I'm not asking you to lick me, lick me like that
I'm not giving it to you.
I'm very happy.
Jaja cookie delivery cookie a
Cookie cookie oh cookie hey there it is
I want to deliver cookies to Nemin overseas.
Everyone at the store wanted to feed San too.
I'm sure that's what I'm telling the world
I want to, after all, I want to tell you a little bit
I took a break from streaming for about a month.
For now, let's go out for some training.
Even if it comes out empty
of
Shall I give you a cookie?
present cookie presentation color cookie
It should be cookie-colored, it's coming, it's coming, it's starting!
to
star
Oh, it's coming, it's coming
Zoeko Robokoroboko Senpai, do your best, do your best
Roboko-san, do your best, do your best
Fight, I like it, I love it
Oh
I'm sure you were good at practicing, Akami.
He's not very fast, he's really good at bi
That's great, do your best, Roboko
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, Roboko
Alright, it's finally number 2. Nice nice now, yes.
Yes, that's nice, that's totally fine.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, I can move, what just happened?
Maybe I touched a checkpoint and fell to my death.
It feels like I'm back. Yes, yes, yes.
Checkpoints are important, yaoi.
It's true that I'm really competing with Sui-chan.
It's true, it's amazing, but it's really good
Wow, that's good, I can go, I can go
Degozaru has a pretty good route.
It's delicious, it's delicious, everyone
Oh, it's not good, it's so fast!
Very good, very bad, very bad
Okay, I'm coloring this remaining time.
Oh, it's true, Sui-chan, do your best, senpai.
Boo is amazing but 1st place is so fast
NaB is too good Ao checkpoint
nice
Do your best, but steadily pursue something from your point of view
This is the point of view that can be seen above.
I can go but I can't go I can't go
Hey, I can't go, right, I'm looking at you from below.
That's right, just look at it from below.
I'm looking at it like it's somewhere around here.
It's like you can go there by touching the signboard on the main line.
But that's a lie. Look, this is the first time I've heard of that.
It says "Entry" on the infected person's right click.
This is not it, I can go up, I can go up
It's true that it's going up, it's amazing, it's amazing
I didn't know I was chasing you, and I still don't know now
I feel like I was able to upload quite a bit of Imaichi, who wasn't there.
That's amazing, it's true everyone.
It's really floating, did everyone know that?
Only your head is floating, only your head is floating
I'm Mo
Hey, hang in there, it's tough but steady and steady
I can't see the polite nice nectar
So it's okay. Actually, I'm going.
It's true, I've reached the goal
You can do your best even if you calm down.
Good luck, that pink one is sleepy.
Yo this this this this this this is amazing
It's so amazing, so delicious!
Teruu
Do your best, do your best
nice nice nice nice
hey
Nice, I liked it
That's so nice
Good luck Susu-chan
Pasoi-san, do your best! This place is expensive.
Sui-chan, Sui-chan, do your best Sui-chan
Do your best, Sui-chan, how amazing is this?
A cute little girl throwing a trident
That's good
I'll do my best to become a great photographer.
I wonder if I can do it again from the fans' point of view.
It's cool, it's finally cool
It's okay, it's honestly going up.
It's rising, it's rising, it's good, it's good, do your best
keep it up
Good luck, I'm taking shortcuts right now
That's right, I'm saying something like that above.
Thank you for your support.
A little while later
Do your best, love
Yeah, nice eggplant is nice
Ffnai nice GGG
Good game good game
I applaud this.
This is great, everyone is clear, this is amazing
Something's weird
[music]
This is amazing
Akira must be nervous.
Are you okay? Is there something on the screen?
Something strange has come out. What is this?
Controller if there are chat settings etc.
Maybe something came out, well, something like that
I don't know, I guess the image that came out has arrived, wait.
I can't get down, I can't get down.
Kaneshifue shift ah shift it's shift
I can get off at .Is there a shift?
Yeah, it's a little surreal to see severed heads flying around.
Yeah, I'm sure it will come back due to this and that infection.
Oh, I'm back, I'm back, okay, okay, okay.
That's good.
[music]
That's amazing, I know that only people with heads like that get it.
There was no such thing as a spectator mode.
There's a mode, that's awesome
People in this normal human state can't see our heads.
I'm sure it's not when I look at it from below.
You couldn't see it, you couldn't see it, right?
I didn't notice it, yeah, that's why I didn't notice it.
So much so that it doesn't even become what I thought it would be.
Well done, I'm back.
Everyone is forced to go back one after another.
I came
Somehow I became an infected person after the game started.
I don't know if I should give it away, but I feel like I'm dying
But later it looked like when I was looking at it from the sky.
What kind of out-of-body projection do you mean? Out-of-body projection
It's like, ``Next Kiara''
Senior, I have to support you, but I have to support you.
When to cheer with Let's Go English
So how do you do that?
Fight fight cheering in English
fight fighter fighter fighter
Gogogogogogogogo
Nnn, that's wrong, go go go, Chiara, do your best, do your best
Chiara-chan feels so good!
Ukia's seniors were really good at it.
It's so fast, it's the fastest.
I was really practicing, so yeah, that's good.
Like, like, nice, nice points!
Okay, it's early
It's too early, I was working until the last minute.
Delicious
It's delicious, it's delicious, it's so good
That's great, that's great, that's awesome, Kia-senpai.
Only one person has already gone 70m. It's already too early.
The checkpoint is coming, it's amazing
The checkpoints are so nice, wow.
I can't go, it's so smooth wow
I'm going to go crazy with shortcuts
Can I go to the supermarket?
Let's go, this is Chiara
Chiara-senpai is not a super genius after all
It's early, it's early, birds are fast, they fly in the sky
It's true that I was really nervous during practice.
You said what to do, right?
If you don't know what to do or what to do, it's totally a mistake.
I haven't done it, I haven't done it, I haven't done it.
It doesn't look like it. I don't understand the mistake anymore.
I don't understand this, I honestly don't understand.
I'm going up again
If you don't chop the eggplant, it won't float.
It's amazing that you sent this.
No, no, no, no, no, no mistakes.
Seriously, I made a mistake and came this far.
Masu
Hey, it's great. Which way are we going?
I'm going that way. I'm going that way.
I don't have any doubts. I've already decided on the route.
Even as if I've already decided, I can go there
It's so amazing, so fast!
Too soon, too good, too good
Nice, this is no longer the absolute number one below.
I just want to go back and fall here.
The checkpoint is quite low.
Kina-chan doesn't fall, thinking she's nervous.
Don't fall, don't fall, it's difficult here
Maybe I'll go back, it's really hard.
It's amazing, it's really scary, Kia
keep it up
Suisu Sugo-chan is so cool
Too cute
Yo Super
Genius nice, Kia.
[music]
If I saw you were nervous, I hope you lose.
He didn't seem nervous at all, though.
You climbed like RTA.
Waka couldn't stop. Nice nice.
That's nice. No, that's nice.
It was good, but I still finished in 2nd and 3rd place.
It's not half yet.
150 I haven't come, so I'm sorry 90
It's been a while. Let's take a look below.
It's so cool, it's so early Shiberi
Genius
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaw
It's true that Quest is having a good fight.
It's falling
Black is amazing, that's what I thought about it.
It's difficult, isn't it? It seems like it takes a lot of effort to grasp the sense of distance.
But this
I've been practicing with difficult characters, so I've put in a lot of effort.
It's a result. I practiced for a long time yesterday.
It looks like it's amazing.
Hey, I'm all alone, just waiting and waiting.
Wait, wait, wait
wing
When the time is right, it's okay, it's okay
Oh no problem is over, it's over, but it's the end
To
Bubbly yellow is in second place or yellow is in second place.
Wow, there's only one more step left!
No, it was just one more step, unfortunately, I had already flown away.
is
Ah-chan fell
I saw an amazing moment, the moment I jumped into it.
It just got interrupted and I fell down.
It was a really amazing battle.
It was amazing
Nice Chiara-chan, that was nice Pachi
Danoko is crackling like a beautiful bird.
Da-pachi dondon
[music]
It was nice and amazing
Now, here's the key point of the second game.
It looks like it's going to be scattered, but yeah...
We finished 12th, so we were probably number one.
The points for this app are high.
I don't think so, I was in 2nd place a while ago.
There's a No. 1 place, oh yeah, it's definitely possible.
Isn't it true? It's quite possible.
The screen where the points are currently appearing on the other side of the stream
That's the point of follow-up.
Then the white team's points are now 20.
I got the first point, so I drew the number
I wonder if number one will come.
Nice fight, nice fight
Nice Yarachanneko
You haven't come back yet. You've come back.
Are you still doing interviews?
That's still the case with the white team, our white team.
But both of them are properly eavesdropping, aren't they?
I went to
Taneyama's
There is a little bit of leeway in the mountains.
I wonder if it's the same level as that or that level.
It was a great game, no mistakes, amazing
Tanane didn't make any mistakes, that was amazing
Nice
Nice, the White team is currently in 1st place.
It's a very close battle, but white: 40, yellow: 38, red.
Desu Jenai Stim 4 Points Yellow
38 Red 37
Let's go, that's nice, nice.
wonderful nice nice nice
nice this is
It's dangerous, it's going to come down to Hihigo.
It's something that takes a little practice, isn't it?
Also, that's right, like protecting the general with a line of fangs.
Yes, there is, so I guess it's still possible.
I feel pressured to do my best.
I'm planning to take things easy with what happened.
I don't think it's 1.
It's becoming more and more difficult to
It seems that there is no pair this time.
I put it together properly so I don't know what will happen.
I guess I don't understand.Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.
Mr.
Yes, I'm looking at your mother.
Mom said yes, so here we go.
The second comprehensive announcement will be an interim announcement of comprehensive benefits.
Click here for the score
is
Yes, I'm 40 and feel that way.
Saga 63 points White 60 points 52 points
That's it
Or 3 points or 3 points or Lee
Lee Maki, then to the venue for the next competition on the Kiba Line.
move
Let's
[music]
Jump from Sekok was announced.
I wonder what the score results are.
The score is out, it's out, I said it earlier, white.
was 2nd overall overall with 3 points and 3 points.
Yo33 Yellow is Ko-san and Chiara-chan nice
It was nice.
Super good game
Game Game Good Game Nafanafa
nafa
The two of you were so amazing!
I don't think so, I'm straining, it's getting too heavy.
Good luck Kia
Please let me ride. I'll ride.
Masuyo
I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it.
General Amin Entry
The entry is on the right, so where do I go with this?
Red, this, that, this, this, this.
It was a book, but at first it was
Mr. Nice Nice
Cute
Yeah, well, I guess I still have a dark side.
For passengers
Even if you wait while you're standing there, what's the target?
The general may be the superior, but the general is the superior.
Clicked side does not have to enter.
If you have already entered, please cancel it.
One more time one more time
times
Come home, general
This is what I did.
That person from Nekan's pair is coming.
I wonder if that person from my pair will come.
Is that person there?
Will you give it to me?
Won't you come? If your pair stay like this, I won't come.
Let's all glue together
It would be better to prepare rice balls.
It feels so good that I want to eat green onigiri.
I want an onigiri as a gift.
I want a rice ball Shigumomogumogua
I want to eat. I'm hungry. Summon Mogu Mogu.
I want to mumble
Please release General Kaela.
Kaaakachankachanaaaaaa it's okay
So youknow
how
OK
O
[music]
aggressive behor
O
[music]
be
a
water
[music]
Mr. Gachi
Where are you? Here are more and more ominous ears
where is the crow
I can see you here, here, here, here, here
This one, which one, which one, which one?
Is it okay which general will go down?
Is it okay? How do you stop the general?
What's that? Press the same button again in that book.
only
[music]
Just nice nice
nice
Mumbling
what
Wait a minute
Did you go there in that outfit? Did you go in a suit?
It's coming, it looks strong
Ken is wearing a suit and looks very handsome.
It's done
Yes, it looks strong.There are parents.It looks strong.
Too bad, it's okay, they charged a huge amount of money later.
It's okay, I won't let you do anything.
There might be, oh porridge.
Thank you to my seniors for their kindness.
Thank you so strong, so strong, I was able to ride it, I was able to ride it.
The one I rode seemed to be the strongest one.
Yaba
Okayu-senpai is so cool.
He says he will help you as a pinch hitter.
By that
Thank you very much.
Aoka-senpai, thank you for coming.
Thank you
I'm going to ride, please ride, I'm riding
I got on top of Yu-senpai.
My senpai is on board.
I'll ask you to become a chair for a while, leave it to me.
Thank you, I'm so happy.
Looks like it's fluffy and fluffy is stuck in my butt.
The corner of the chocolate wire is stuck in it.
Leader it hurts, it hurts
No, it would be better if there was a little stimulation.
is
I feel like it's more stimulating than that, Mio.
chan might be quite stimulating too.
This is being shown on my senior's corner. It hurts.
Gozamomo
[music]
Thank you very much.
thank you
I will participate later.
Wishlist is scary, one person has turned into a suspicious person.
Don't get angry
it will be done
Okay, I'll say it. How do you do it?
What I learned from you will lead you to victory.
I would like to, please
It's too cool and too embarrassing
Let's do our best, everyone in the white group.
Yay!
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best Yes, I'll join the group in the end
I want to ask
This is the strategy of Kigurumigurumi-gumi or Kumiki-gumi.
What will you do? What will happen to the white team?
I guess that's right, I got the general's kill after all.
If you can do it, 1 point will be added.
Probably attacking while defending
Focus on the person you want to work with.
Everyone, let's all approach that general.
All you have to do is wake up the person who is coming.
That's right
hey
So those who are closer to the general will come more and more.
He looks like a weak person.
I want to beat up people who are somehow weak.
You can see the heart, so people with hearts might want to do it.
Reverse wish
At first, be near the general and get 1 heart.
If I see it, I'll attack it.
Scary?
Yes, I'm probably sleeping with that pair.
I think it will be voice chat.
Is that so? Oh yeah, that's true.
There's voice chat, there's a lot of it.
Well, I think there's probably a name at the bottom.
Come to think of it, there is actually porridge.
That's why cooperation is more difficult than collaboration.
Well then
Looks like he's going to protect me, oh well, General, Muji.
Let's all do our best. We'll do our best.
If we're both true, we're both being targeted.
I think I should go to Terutsuta Cover.
If I find you all frozen, I'm sure you'll be rocking me
If it becomes something like that, then maybe
I think we're going to have to move from here, so everyone is moving.
Okay, let's go. Let's go.
Let's Go Let's Go Let's Go
I was able to move. I was able to move. I'll do my best with color.
Is this a red song?
Hey, that Iro-chan from Minecraft Pro
I don't think I should put it above this anymore.
I can't even fight like this or vertically.
If you use it well, you can win. Yes, you can win.
It's probably a ham cut, so that's a han cut.
It depends on where you hit it.
I'll protect General Amo as much as possible.
While protecting
Noame Senpai or Su from Umami Senpai Ame's point of view
I wonder how it looks
Yes, at F5, yes, at F5 it's a little bit off.
Check with the picture
What does Jump look like?
The jump is probably a critical hit.
I guess it's because I can't handle it.
But I think that's the person attacking me.
That's why I can't run much. I can run.
It's just that jumping feels better than running
I feel like I'm flying far away, so I don't think so at all.
Jumps that I think are good for jump dash
Dash yeah jump dash
I'll do my best, I'll roll up my sleeves and do my best.
Short sleeves. Short sleeves.
I'm really happy with the short sleeves.I'll do my best with short sleeves.
hot
And just like that
It seems like the road is touching my motivation now.
I was wearing something on top, but I just took it off.
Okay, take off your clothes. Do your best.
It's actually better to say I'll do my best to defeat everyone.
It's my first time, I'm sure about the subject.
Yes, that's right.The targets are 5 and regular soldiers.
There are three, so the object over there is red.
I think the yellow one is Suba-chan, the one below is
I see, Miko-senpai, who is this? Who is this?
Mel-san Mel-chan or Mel-chan and Chinea
So I checked a bit and found out that Mel-san is in trouble.
Amazing Pom Pom Candy and Swachan Hoawa
Tame-senpai is in a character contest, it's amazing
This Miko-senpai and Mel-senpai are Pom Pom.
Combination feeling
Awesome, are you okay?
Where is the length?
I don't want to go, but there might be some problems.What do you think?
I'll do my best while protecting the general.
Maybe even if it's just for my senior.
If it sticks too tightly, it's probably the sword's fault.
The swing is quite large so you can get hit all at once.
Yes, that's why it's so, probably summary
I tried all the things I thought I could do, and the feeling was 3
There's going to be a fight, probably 3 fights.
fire
I'm so excited, it feels like I did it all yesterday yesterday.
Kia-chan is amazing
Thank you for working so hard on the attack!
I got an amazing 8 kills, so I guess that's it.
Mouse to let those who can get kills get kills
Looks good, yes, yes, yes.
If there's someone the White Team is after, then that's it.
Let's talk about something and hang out together
It might be nice to go to
Oh okay
Turn around
please
I'll do my best, Amamoru.
If not, I'll have someone protect me while I attack.
Carry it while receiving it, carry it while having it carried away
Tsutsuo is also a senior and has a strong sense of strength.
It's amazing. I wonder if it's just the beginning.
It's probably the one in the middle.
Isn't this thing going to disappear?
Maybe the climbing that I think is strong will disappear.
I wish it would disappear, but it hasn't happened in a while.
But I can climb here, which wasn't there the other day.
If that's the case, I'll probably just climb here.
There was a glass block placed there.
I might not be able to climb, but I'm strong at the top.
It's probably better to go to the top.
How cool is this place?
I think there is a high possibility that it will make it impossible to climb.
I wonder what will happen
Yes, that means defeating someone.
Aki is definitely very peaceful, people.
I don't think he'll beat you up.
No, but it's a game, so I won't win.
That's right, this time the BGM is
I'm so excited to see it in sports day format.
I'll put some money on it.
Let's blow this, let's escape
[music]
The sound that starts from the BGM and starts from the sound
The shape and shape of everything is important.
Shape because it's important
It's like this or something like that
When I play games, I think of myself as the strongest.
My grandpa told me to do it.
That's how I say it, when I fight, I'm the strongest version of myself.
It's okay if this starts with me being the strongest.
Maybe the bugs are scattered all over the place.
I wonder what it is, it's okay
Oh, it's coming. It looks like I can go. It's coming. I'll wait.
[music]
Where are we colliding so badly?
It's dangerous, everyone has been defeated.
There's something wrong with the back
I can't hold a sword like that in a brawl.
I could hold it, I could hold it, I could hold it, yeah, wow
It's a bad one, but it's better if you don't defeat it.
It's not strong here, it's not strong, it's a bit dangerous.
I think the legs are as big as they are.
Defeat
Wow, wow, it's so bad I've been defeated
This is bad. Let's go after that tree.
Let's go aim
[music]
Let's do it, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, which one?
It's dangerous here
It's so difficult, I'm sorry I've been defeated so much.
I'm sorry I couldn't beat it at all, this is terrible
difficult
Hey, the game is over. It's over. Wow.
It starts quite suddenly, isn't it?
It's a little difficult to integrate
It's difficult if we can't work together.
I wonder what this feels like
Please wait a moment. If you do it once, it will be 1.
I wonder if the times will go down.
yes
let's
I don't know where you are
[music]
Everyone is so excited
I feel like this might just have to wait.
Is there a wait coming?
What do you think? It probably happened twice.
It's times
[music]
hair
Change your perspective on this
Kane's point of view Yes, no, no, no, this is it
[music]
T
ttt amazing T is flowing
The amazing Kaela-san is doing really well 7
I'm killing it. Ah, that's it.
Wow, the ranking looks like this
Yes yes yes yes
[music]
Yesoooooooooooooooooo I'm probably back with this.
Or is it?
[music]
Everyone please enter this
It was the white team that seemed to have calmed down after entering.
Cooperate
I wonder if it's not there.
I'll try changing my perspective
Oh yes
yes
Run through, run through, or go and pull away
I'm practicing something like this or that.
There weren't many people there at that time.
It seems that there were few
I wonder what that is, but the third person is better.
It was easy though
Well, it's a mixed battle, so I'm sure the upper one is
Maybe 12 is easier.
I see, that's true.
But I think there are only a few people who feel that way.
Easy to hit, but run away if hit
Okay, that's what it feels like
do
It's so good to jump
a jump
[music]
Good luck jumping
keep it up
It's okay, it's okay, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
It's true that the members are seniors.
[music]
I'm in a pinch
Hitter is the president above the president after all.
The president who is this or that or muddy is the real president.
If you think about it, if you're both presidents,
Is this true? We ride each other like that.
It is a matter of fact
Yes, yes, yes, we're both presidents here.
Only here is the echo of Rosa's business assignments.
They are the rebuilders and the debtors.
Sorry, that's not good. I'll try my best.
This is terrible
No, it's not good. There is a Kyushu merger. It's not good.
Memories of not winning
Damn it, it's a painful, painful debt.
If not, I'll go with you.
Oh, let's work together
Teri test
I have to take the weeding test.
If not from Raki
I did a wait dash
Pull
It would be better if it was okay and pretty solidified.
Yes, but
Hey, it's really laggy. It's so laggy.
It's really laggy
Wow, it's been a bit laggy since a while ago.
That's right, but it might be a little laggy.
It's terrible that I defeated it.
terrible
Gulp
Is it too much lag? Too much lag?
where
Daikocchi is so laggy it's terrible
It's so bad, it's so nice that I defeated it.
Nice
It's dangerous
Raku-chan is more laggy
Okay, don't beat Nice, okay.
[music]
Okay
Nice okay, hey, over there.
I'll do my best to read the movement and hit it.
You're coming here.
That's nice, ok, ok, from before.
It's okay, but it's definitely more laggy than before.
However, one person found this one better.
reads ahead
I don't want to read ahead, but it's pretty good.
I was able to defeat it, so wait a minute.
I chased it, chased it 5 kills 5 kills 5
Kill 5 Kill nice nice I did it.
Okay, okay, I did it. I did it. This one.
It's nice that it also includes target kills. Nice.
Red is strong, red is strong
It's a lag anyway
A little guy who can beat the internet
A man who can beat the internet
I think there is a man who can beat the Internet.
Kia-chan did 8 kills, that's awesome.
That's nice
This is the same as reading the trajectory.
It was
The path of the sword
recommend
Don't let me do it, don't let me do it
Jikin standing
Identify the muscles that stand out
Something about my muscles
Somehow, so many people gathered together.
Something like that
I can't help it, I'm so nervous, the next one will be dangerous.
This is the world and which direction is the opponent facing?
It's said that you will read the story at the starting point.
Oh, and there's only one race left.Is there someone on top?
It's true
Which one was Dakara riding?
Let's ride
Yes, this is the last one. White team wants to win in the end.
I'll do my best
Okay, do your best
I'm looking a little backwards after all.
go there
Yeah, I want to go without bumping into each other head-on.
Yeah, let me jerk off there.
[music]
I'll do my best, I'll do it
Color changes
Let's jikinjikin or jikijiki from behind
Even though I didn't like it, I got a pretty good result.
That's right, 5 kills, over 5 kills.
I want to go
Yes, the red team was amazing.
strong
The Red Team says they're going to beat you up.
If there are people, then why is this place super?
I'll send you a good mark Super good
The super good mark has a strong gozane red color.
Is this your team?
Small
[music]
I'm really stirring things up, I'm really stirring things up
The red team is really stirring things up.
[music]
The only emoticon I see is that one that looks like a creepy old man.
You look like it's because you can't hit.
It looks like a smiling B
Na
Oh no, this is the only thing I can do, super good
Even though it's Mark, I'm sure he'll fight.
Just aim for a kill from behind
This is delicious if you go there.
Your fleeting lives are also yours.
All we can do is fight back.
[music]
That's not super super good.
This is super good
Gozaru
Oh, it was probably interrupted once.
Or if it is interrupted, please re-enter again.
stomach
Masu Now Entry Now Entry Now
Good ride
in
Thanks for giving me a ride
Of course it's good and bad.
But Azuki's voice sounds uneasy, but it's okay.
Yo princess voice
I've already practiced, but it's a close attack.
The whole menu is right, maybe one chan.
What I'm thinking is that all menu practice has changed.
I wonder if that's the case. I don't know if that's the case.
I guess it's because they'll take precautions against it.
There you are
That's the first thing that started me off.
That's not coming. Now we're in a battle where we can't make any decisions.
I'm concentrating, I'm concentrating on the battle, let's go, let's go
Wow
Well, I really want to go from behind.
Nayabbe is really laggy but the enemy
read startup
So nice nice nice eggplant just fell from behind
Let's go! Miko-senpai came flying over.
Yes, while reading which enemy to fly to.
Sorry, wait a minute, back.
Sorry, it's too crazy
[music]
hand
terrible
Do your best, wait, it's the world!
Through time and space
Shiro is doing a great job, nice nice
General
If you see something with thin red hit points
Anyway, I'm just punching you.
Behind you, behind you, behind you
[music]
eggplant
terrible
teeth
I beat you so bad, it's okay, it's okay.
Okay nice nice Eri-san
Tachinia
It's so dark, it's so white, it's amazing
Yo wow wow wow wow Ume-chan
says Lissa.
Bad 10
I'm strong enough to do a kill, but it's fine.
I think the damage was done, really.
I guess I couldn't see it from the middle of the road.
almost
No, it's fine, the white team worked hard, it's nice
Too many overseas overseas players have a nice fight with overseas players
Too nice fight, too much
Too many target kills Huge 4 kills no targets
Kill 4 is a big eye, seriously amazing
Awesome, so nice
nice
I want to wake up strong, I'm scared it's strong
Wow, I guess I was aiming for it.
It's amazing, I don't know, I'm so excited to participate.
The selection has changed a lot.
Hey, it's dyed in white that only the emoticons can match
I dyed it white, dyed it red, dyed it white.
But no, I guess this is the end of my participation in the war.
That's right, the white team was amazing.
Strong, strong
I dyed it white
The whole thing
All announcementsThings with announcements
It's better to go back to A, which is becoming better.
I'm going back.Okay then, let's all go back together.
to
Thank you for your hard work on moving.Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, that was amazing, 41 planes are amazing.
Damn it, who is so active?
It's Nerisa-chan. That's right.
Nerissa is definitely 10
Kill and Eiame-chan also got 10 kills
Amazing foreign kill machine. Kill machine.
It was
It's a sleepy night
I was so awakened. I was so awake.
This is an amazing response.
I thought it was expensive, right? 4 included targeted kills.
We did Surprise 41 General.
I also did a nice nice Miko
seriously
Nice sorry 1
It's important to kill, no, no, no, run away.
Kara so yeah so sorry nice 1 kill
nice nice 1
If it wasn't for that first kill, it would have been 40.
That's why it's so important.
Important and important nice things and amazing nice things
Nice nice Chasu-chan strong berry
It's Strobe. Yes, yes, yes.
The Yasaboko-san pair was also amazing and nice.
That was amazing, nice. I was really surprised.
is
I killed him 3 times
Amazing work, amazing work!
It's amazing, it's nice, it's nice
Oh yeah, that's amazing, what's up with this score?
I'm sure you're curious. Go as far as you like.
I guess I must have been there quite a bit.
It's been a long time since I've made a comeback, so let's get back on track.
The second game is also 2nd place, 2nd place, etc.
I think it was about 26 kills.
It rolled up quite a bit and the red was pretty strong as well.
There's nothing wrong with that. It was definitely a strong red.
It was strong, it was amazing at first
I'm scared of what will happen to this dangerous relay.
enemy
The princess's thighs are trembling, her thong is trembling, the princess is trembling now.
Let's do our best Mechan
[music]
Hey, it's okay, you can win, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, you can win. It's time to practice.
I was dodged by the yellow team for about a minute and a half.
I don't think so, but tomorrow
Wow, it was all so fast, this is seriously funny
I'm reading this, but there's been an update.
There is a lot of content about Holomen hunting.
Since it was different, this menu is also unique.
The mystery of whether Chan has changed
That's what you're reading.
That's possible. That's totally possible.
I want to win I want to win What will happen if I come?
After all, you've come, right? How far do you want to go?
I want to go, right?
I want to go, I feel a little bit of desire.
Damn it, you should just have fun at first.
It was like, but it felt like
It's starting to look like we're going to win.
My arms are hurting.
Yae: I didn't mean to rush you.
It wasn't like that at first just now, but it's already around my shoulders.
I can't tear it up, but I can't tear it up.
Janchigiru's sleeves are broken, let's break them too.
For some time now, my skin has been torn up.
But the skin is too much skin.
Don't do it, it's such a wild thing to do
Bare and muscular, after all, I'm proud of it.
I've started climbing below the muscles.
Not coming last 41
I'm in trouble
I turned bright red when Tami-senpai came home.
It's too much, isn't it?
How was it? Who had the most kills?
Who cut it first?
Chankia was also amazing at the very end.
I'm sorry, but Suba-senpai twice.
Defeated Miko-senpai once
That's amazing
Ta
It was huge and amazing
Okay, so the white team was great.
But at the end, a little cat-man
thank you
Thank you very much
Please let me know what you think.Yes, thank you.
Thank you together with everyone
I was happy to play.I will continue to support the white team.
Thank you very much for your help.
Thank you, it disappeared in an instant.
Thank you, Agent Kayu.
Thank you agent for the book
MAGA team agent Okayo
Thank you, thank you, thank you, Pano
Well, this is a scary number killer.
There's no difference between one and the other, I did my best.
I did my best, things will change.
No, thank you really
The Nia interview was fun! It was fun!
I wanted to, it was really fun, it was fun
it was fun
There's a lot of pressure in this competition.
Pressure pressure is different.
Relax and hope, it's okay, it's still okay
Everyone can go, it's okay.
It's okay, it looks like it's okay, I have to protect the princess.
The princess made a little mistake while being protected.
It will also turn you around with a reel.
Even in a world of pressure and danger, danger, danger
stings
that
It's too bad, I'm going to practice it now.
Everyone is climbing, everyone is panicking.
Is it climbing ivy?
Even now, I'm getting better at the vines.
It's difficult to be nice
I said it was difficult to sleep.
I heard that today
When and where did you run? Then you score points.
It seems that the tally has been completed, so I would like to take a look.
I think the total of the 3 games is here.
Good luck, Desu-gumi
Tayaya
Oh no, oh no, the red team got 46 points.
White group has 38 points, yellow group has 23 points.
I was in 3rd place until recently, so I'm making a comeback.
It's Tandananishi Volume
I don't know what this is.
I don't know if it will turn out, but I'll move on to the next step.
Yes, but then the next competition.
Himekoshi Sango
go go
looking forward to looking forward to
Let's enjoy the fight and do our best. Good luck with your dreams, Gan.
I'll do my best, I'll do my best
I'll try harder
Okay
Is everyone else coming?
Na
Hishikishi
Let's do it, do your best
do your best
Fight Add that to the previous point
No, that's right. If you add it up, it'll be amazing.
This isn't the team's VC yet.
I wonder if everyone will do their best Pink, yellow, red is fine
But no matter what, there's no need to rush.
But Princess Iris, let's go, princess flew away
It's a mystery why this princess's outfit is so cute
I just don't know what that is right now.
Hey, you're cute. You're naked. This is naked. Naked is different.
Naked Princess, Naked Princess, Naked Princess, Naked Princess
It was a dangerous exhibitionism to Princess Akana.
Yes to the entry, okay, princess.
I'm a princess, I'll do my best, I'm a princess.
We're a team, I wonder why.
A princess from a neighboring country was with me and did whatever she wanted.
Let's trade with Renka Dou.
Hello princess hello princess princesses
I have to take a look at your face after all.
Thank you very much.
Please include me too, princess.
The meeting has begun, and the pleasant smell has begun.
I hope so. I hope so.
Please, we are princesses.
That's right, that was a very meaningful battle.
It seems like a dangerous thing to do
Let's go without it, run slowly
No, that's right, I didn't run the whole way.
I have never run in my entire life.
tree
I guess I only stepped foot in it once.
Because there is no
Please tell me what kind of life you have, please don't run, seriously.
Don't ever run, sayyabainaha's team
The princess might even be the strongest.
No way, that's no longer the case.
Although she is physically difficult, she is such a delicious princess.
But it seems like he's definitely the best physically.
Looks like it's going to be crushed
Alright, let's start by asking the red team.
Let's
Noe is played by Gato, Hai is played by Shion-tan, and
fire
Blue and fluffy
Since it's Fuchanwa, there are 4 people here.
Defumo is one person with those two people.
Yes, thank you very much
Please, please, please.
What do you think about that? What are your enthusiasm?
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
It seems like we all practiced until late at night.
Yes, I'll try my best. I usually go to bed at 9 but now I'm going to bed at 1
practice until
It's too late, it's true, it's like 9 o'clock
I go to bed at 10 o'clock on days when there's nothing going on.
Wow, you woke up really early.
Yes, that's true
Let's do our best, let's do our best, do our best
Are you okay
Do your best, try your best, then go to the white group.
I would like to
Yes, White Team, can you hear me? I can hear you.
hear me
So I would like to start by introducing the players.
I think Ehiya is sweet, yes, yes, it seems sweet.
is
Nenene
I don't think anyone who doesn't know anything about it should come.
Yes, the knight is Azuki-chan, yes, and then.
Yes, yes, Isomu-chan, yes.
[music]
Wearing
What do you think? I don't have much enthusiasm.
Those my knights, oh me
I think it's okay. It's okay.
Well, this time I want to protect those three princesses.
I think there are three princesses.
I would like to protect it, thank you
1 is 1, no, it's different, it's good, this much
Cute Akichi and such cute Yume-senpai
Yokanata includes Kanata, and here, too, senpai
It's okay, Senpai is also really cute.
I'm sorry, please do your best.
Thank you very much
Finally, I would like to ask the Kigumi
In the Masu group, the roles are the summer festival and the knights.
Hame Ririka Kahame Ririka Festival Yes.
Yes, what do you think? Netsuhime, today's situation is a princess.
It happened with the princess and the knights.
Show everyone the amazing cooperative play
Masu
The fastest
I want you to steal the first place.
Princess yes the true princess is me
Come in, go down
Good luck with your entry too!
Please, yes, yes, then.
It's finally here, as soon as the entry is finished
The tension is starting to build, I'm already leaning against the wall
It looks like it's long.
Is this this or this?
[music]
Well, I tried moving in English. I moved.
Yes
Senior, I thought it would be a good idea to tie it to you.
I was confused. Oh, it came, it came, it came
I’m so excited to see if I can come and go, wow.
The first step is to try your best.
Well then, let's finish with Azuki et al.
No need
I'll call out the names of the passengers.
Carion SouA Carion Kisnem
Sez Okay Senkyu
Okay, it's a stubborn ride that made me nervous.
It was just a ride, but was your ride caught?
Ride member name Sayun Sein Kanata
Senpai senpai Okay Senkyu
oyu doko english sorry already
Very reliable, very reliable
Time movement
Stop when your name is called Oh yeah if
you
Nemse
stop
Oooh I'm going aooh
Kazu-chan comes from the right side of Oashipuri
Mzu-chan Gomenzu-chan Mume-chan
I can go, nice, nice, nice.
Well, next time, we'll all climb up, and now it's disgusting.
Chankazamakakorehazu-chan is not good
Chan
Kazamaa Korezu-chan ohhhhh
Mui-chan ok oh oh nice
Onice nice ooooooo nice
Um no taku no taku aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Okay, I feel like anything is fine.
I wonder if I can ask you to do this. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about this
Do you understand this, this, this? Okay, now.
I get to the point where I can only hear voices.
This makes sense.Sorry, sorry.
Sorry, the knights made it, but wait, there's a book.
Kanae, this must be Luna.
It's a terrible possibility and Luna Cana Luna.
Kizuna is nice, as expected of Kanaluna.
I'm hungry, what do you want to eat?
Um, lamb meat lamb rack ud mototon person
Special hamburger came here Special hamburger
Egi beef potatoes carrots on a cutting board
Please cut it and grill it on a griddle, lol
Lamb lamb lamb okay then cut it all with a knife
I'm cutting everything with a knife.
Lamb Uncut Cut Cut Lamb Ramura Ade
Or cut up the eggplant meat.
No meat, no meat, no meat, no meat, no meat.
I feel like I'm in love with you
Mio made it, yes, nice okay.
Let's go eat, let's go eat Naokai Nice
[music]
The next thing is red red yellow
Hatena left up red red yellow mysterious red
red red red red letlet letlele
Leon nice nice ok let's go
Fighting Lets
Go-o
oh
Mu-chan is stuck, stuck, stuck
Okay, let's defeat this Bev together. Maybe.
Then, with the three of us, nice nice nice oooruo
Ooooooooo
O-senpai
Oh ok let's go oooooo
Too big
Okay fight nice let's
Go nice, fast yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes to
Fight, nice, fight, let's go, fight, fight, fight
Fight!
Fight, kill, kill, nice, nice, nice
Nice nice Shiora I can go.
Or maybe I'll fall
Chan
Ai nice, run, run, run, nice nice
Nice, run, run, ooshi, nice
Nice Aya
That was close, that was close, that was nice.
nice nice
Even if the dangerous baby gets caught, he will still be in second place.
At such a high price
I was really surprised.
It's like a cage coming down there.
Nimu
Chanmu
Changa
Because it was good
Senpai, who are you crying so much? It's so funny.
It might not work
I'm sure it's not you
Ta
That's a 3 second difference from the anxious 3rd place.
Maybe you'll be able to do a jump punch
No, you're back. It's so nice to be back. It's so nice.
At the end of the day, I went to see my brother with everyone.
and
This is a book that made me realize that you are
a little bit
Yasika Kasu
T
I'm thinking, can you all hear me?
Congratulations on hearing that.
Janeno-san, let's see how it goes.
The four of us really practiced a lot.
It seems that people gathered there, so that's correct.
I'm really happy that it came out with that result.
Good, I'm happy to be in 1st place, it's so fast
It was really fast.
eye
Ugh, that was really quick. That topic was definitely
Was it Subaru?
Yes, yes.
I'm pretty sure this is because I was making a chick.
I wonder what everyone was making.
That's a bit right, by all means, by all means
I hope you can take a look at the archives.
Congratulations on saying yes.
Congratulations!
Congratulations, let's do our best in the last two.
I want to do my best
Okay, then I'd like to hear about the White Team.
I think so, but how was it?
I don't care how it went, Jazu-chan.
At the end, when you defeat that monster, it's disgusting.
I guess I got caught falling down
You know, between the waves
It feels like a parent cage, but I'm actually trapped.
Looks like it's messed up
It was a happening, but you guys
I was here, leaving it to you.
It was great to get second place in such a situation.
I worked hard on this. I did my best.
Despite some accidents, I got through it well.
Better
I wanted to ask who the question was. Who appeared?
It's Luna, Luna!
Hey, here too, it looks like Canaluna's bond.
Well, it was that pinkish color, so I thought
I was confused, but I believed in the bonds of Canaluna.
I got it
I went out. I went out. It was fun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much, then continue
I would like to hear from the Kigumi.
Yes, I'm sorry. I'm so frustrated.
It's okay, it's okay, but it's the final catch-up
It was really amazing, we were catching up, we were catching up
I made a mistake in guessing my topic.
Sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Look at how hard you worked.
You did your best, right, until the end of the sports day.
Let's all push ourselves and do our best.
Because it has a meaning, of course I'll go above and beyond.
Let's all run until the end while aiming for
You're beautiful, do your best, do your best
I showed it to Masuota's Laplace and Mito several times.
The last one was porridge.
It's difficult
Mom, how did you make it?
I'll check the archive later, please.
I'm sorry, do your best
Nice fight that was night
Yes, it's okay
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
So let's take a look at the voice race scores.
I don't want to see it, I don't want to see it.
30 points white group 20 points yellow group
It will be 10 points
is a bit amazing
Oh no, I don't know if red is coming yet.
Not yet.
That's right. I don't know yet. Next time.
The competition will be held at the winter race venue.
[music]
I know it's dangerous, but I won't say that.
Is this okay with the cat or here? Come back.
I don't know if it's good or not.
call back
It's a good white, and it's a good match here and there.
It matched here
White Tire Chaki
Chacha was sent away without permission.
Tao was thrown away without permission.
Orida
Well, various seniors are doing amazing cooking.
Really
What did you say to me? Ram Ram, oh what?
It was Kanta one lamb, so sheep lamb grilled mutton.
I'll get something special.
This came out a lot during practice.
That's good, practice came and I finally got there.
It's good, it's good, it was there even inside.
Actually, it was really smooth.
No, my cousin, what's going on?
I'm not sure, after this it'll be spring/summer season.
Therefore, those who participate in the relay must be competitors of the Eshiro group.
Channel Ito please engineer
This is my channel please
I see. Nodoka-chan's
The contestants were sent flying before the announcement was made.
Indeed, cutting-edge technology is cutting-edge technology.
It's so easy to understand that it makes me jump for a moment.
let's
I'm in a hurry to go to the flowers
Yes, please go.
Terasyay, it's better to enter
That's okay, let's enter it.
Because I can get a book, I open it and find myself in trouble.
Choose a runner or a white runner and come
It came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came.
Is it okay? Just right click.
Yeah
I'm number 8 on the entry list.
What level is Teame-chan, my own big troublemaker?
The leader of the memory group seemed to be somewhere in the middle.
That's right, Yame-chan, it's the 5th floor. 5th, 5th.
Mu-chan is 33.
Ok, I see, now I can enter.
I wonder if it's okay if I can do it.
I'm sure you'll be happy.
Oh wow, there's a character contactor again today
It's shaky. It's okay, I can do it.
Naru, it's okay. Yes, I'll do my best. I wonder if I can make it?
Oanka is okay
It's okay, it's okay, you can go, dodge it.
Okay, you'll be nervous at the end.
Confused I have
[music]
Howa
So
ONE, what did you say? English was important, yes.
Kermeaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaam I I'm done I'm going to be able to enter
Oh it's number 9
[music]
Nona
ah
Okay Notobe
one wa
a
Oh nice nice okay
So Gujoburg
job nice nice
Okay, no, this one-chan, this is where I dive underwater.
It's the turn of the 1st technician.Yes, the 1st layer is Enerisa.
Yes, next is chocolate
Yes, the third layer is Mui, yes, the fourth layer is Noel.
Leader, yes, and the fifth layer is okay, yes.
The 6th layer
The 7th layer of Kaerae is Achan, and finally
That's the basics, isn't it?
It would be nice if someone who is familiar with Minecraft
It feels like it's coming in
It looks like they're going to catch up.
I guess so.
I can hear everyone in the white group.
I can hear it
So what do you think?
Yeah, who should I choose?
Nayabai aaaaaaaaaaaahhh
anchor
Hogo
Before I knew it, I had become an anchor.
But I'm sure the wind is moving quickly so I guess it'll be okay.
I'm going to do my best because I've earned your trust.
Would be great
I'm stubborn and reliable, I'll definitely take first place.
I want you to do your best, please do your best
Please, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Yes, then. Finally, I'm surprised.
I was so happy
Leader, I came back from picking flowers. Welcome back.
Go home, I think you're going home, Nerisa.
Open when you are confused
It's called open book.
It didn't arrive. It didn't arrive.
Hey, I'm the leader who responded in an embarrassing way.
Let's do our best. It's all about luck when it comes to the cold water.
If you're at the bottom at first, go back and do your best.
Let's do our best, try our best, try our best, let's try our best
Let's do our best, we're right, we're falling.
Hidemoa
[music]
It's here, the water is amazing
a
teeth
Oh no no no
I practiced nervously, so I guess that's the case.
Oh no!
The mental system that is starting to become dangerous
It's okay, it's okay, it's painful
Meku, it's okay because we're all here
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay today
It's okay because it's Korea. I'll do my best. It's okay.
[laughter]
I'm sure you'll have to work really hard.
It's the last time I'm going to do this, so feel free to do so.
At the end, Nene, at the end, you can laugh at the end, okay?
Once this is over, let's eat some delicious meat.
Let's go, let's talk, Azuki.
I was talking about the chocolate line, yeah, meat yakiniku yakiniku owa
Shabu shabu yes
Ishi's preparations are coming, Ikina's [ __ ]
I'll do my best, Lelli
Sari-san
Do your best, try your best, try your best, try your best
Let's calm down. I'll be waiting for you.
Come on, come on, you
Youa
That's right, finally, finally, come on.
Come on, nice, nice catch, nice
Catch nice catch nice kitchi do your best
nice bread nice bread nice
nice
Nice thing to say, Brett. Amazing!
I'm getting sick
Terua
Go go go go, leave it to me, do your best, leave it to me
Leave it to me, finally, finally, finally
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Nice ass, give me some chocolate, calm down.
You're good, you're good, you're good, it's okay, mecha
There are times like that, there are times like that too.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Let's go
It's totally fine, it's totally fine, it's fine.
Go, go, go, go, wait and cheer
If I did that, I wouldn't understand myself anymore.
Oh nervous
Oh wait, this bread is right.
Left, left, left, right, left.
keep it up
Good luck, finally, finally, guah
Sorry, do your best, do your best, No-chan, do your best
Chan
I'll do my best, Chan-chan, I'll do my best.
I can go
It's so fast, it's so fast, it's so fast, it's so fast!
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
I entrust it to you
Please try harder, I'll do my best, I'll try my best, I'll try my best
Let's go, let's do our best.
Go let's go let's go let's go
That's right
Run, run, come back quickly
It's so fast, so fast, it feels good, it feels good
Do your best, try your best
Give it to me
Sweet and Bitter
I can't go there
I can go, I can go
Good luck Kara-chan
hair
Mr. Frog, why are you doing your best?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
basket
Yukiyuki
keep it up
My
senior
[music]
Is this or that going to get sucked in?
Nice nice
yeah
Okay, finally, let's do our best, Akichi.
Do your best, do your best Aki
Senpai, it's like being punched.
It's alright, it's alright, it's always alright
It's okay, it's okay.
Yes, don't eat, eat.
hand
Yes, do your best, do your best
Let's do our best, let's do our best
No, go for it!
Hello,
Wait, where's the red?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
[music]
Okay, okay, let's go, let's go.
Ots go let's go okay
Good, good, good, good.
That's a good swim
Nice nice nice nice fight
Nice nice fight when it's dangerous
Surprised
[music]
It was a great run.
Na
I was nervous
Do your best, try your best, do your best in the end, nice
Like everyone finished
Kai, red is strong after all.
You were strong, you were strong.
Hey, I forgot to eat.
No problem, Prem Tai, I'm hungry.
I was hungry.
Ah, I'm hungry. Let's eat a lot when we're done.
Neon
[music]
Yes nice run nice run nice run
Gozaruun
[music]
Nice I want to eat meat I want to eat meat
Let's go meat, meat
The meat is so good, my heart hurts and I feel so bad right now.
good job
Japanese sub-sub-o-un
I want to eat rice
Let's eat well everyone
Let's eat together and have shabu-shabu together.
Shabu-shabu
Delicious shabu shabu delicious so cute
Great healing
So cute, let's go and shabu-shabu.
The chocolate line will surely take me
Please take me with you
It's all chocolate now
Leave it to me, raw berry good super nice
Yeah, leave it to me
[music]
I don't want to leave it to you, but I tried really hard. I tried my best.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.
I tried my best
Good, good, I did my best, I tried my best
Let's talk to Iha again, who was there for a while.
Let's see what happened to us.
Everything is fine from the beginning to the end.
I got some chive work. It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, that's the result.
Yes, there are various things that are removed and removed.
Despite that, I was able to finish in 2nd place.
That was a nice fight.
nafa
hand
Thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work, and thank you for your hard work.
I'm mastering it.I'm mastering it.
Yoyo test, how many days off?
Kamouko, this is a regular rank.
It's tough
It's amazing how you got 10th place in the exam.
teeth
Awesome, it was so good
It made everyone cry.
Hey, I was crying. I was crying. Some people were crying.
You're so sensitive. That was really good.
No, I'm in 2nd place. I'm in 2nd place. I see.
I thought everyone was working hard. Good luck.
Tamin, I worked hard, I worked hard, I worked hard.
To be honest, at first I felt like I was having a lot of fun.
I was like, "I'll try my best even if it's just that much."
I don't think so. I don't know until the end.
No, I wonder what the final ending will be like.
Probably
I said yes, so I decided to do this alert ceremony.
Please gather in front of the ceremony table.
Masurei let's
Go first first let's go there.
Gozaru's
There was an invisible wall. Now there was an invisible wall.
We were trapped, right? We were sealed away.
It's closed to this school right now.
Speak out loud
rattling
Yes, the white group is beautiful, so beautiful.
beautiful
messed up
It's a big lump of Mr. Oiko, after all.
My feelings are in tonality, but I won't lose in tonality anymore.
yeah
It's like a team fighting each other.
Looks like the colors are very different
calm and calm
[applause]
Tendemi
Lulu
[applause]
Oiru have
I'm doing a lot of things
But the messenger
It's okay to hit me, yes.
By saying yes
The closing ceremony for the cat is about to begin, but Miko-san
How was it this year? How was it?
I had no idea what it would be like.
But yeah
Everyone is working together so well.
You've done well, it's amazing. It's a close race every year.
I thought it looked amazing.
Yes, that's true, to each his own.
There was drama, or rather there was.
I think it's a drama that includes practice.
However, I think it was really good.
Everyone, let's eat something
Tegu
Mio-chan is here now because her mother can't be here.
I talked about it
It's coming from
It all lined up nicely, after all.
That's a very strong word, Takako's mom who has been remodeled.
It suddenly became quiet. I'm still connected.
However, due to the messy relationship, I feel uncomfortable.
It seems like it's just scary, isn't it okay?
Okay, everyone, let our voices be heard.
Can you tell me if I'm going back?
I said yes, so before the closing ceremony,
This time for the competition, I moved the voice chat.
There were so many
[music]
Yes, yes, no-chan, no-chan.
Yes, that's the voice that says thank you.
Thank you very much for your help this year too.
Thank you very much for your hard work
They are so full of personality and the three organizers
Nono is working hard and we can see everything.
I'm very impressed. Thank you.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much for your help with the book.
Thank you everyone
Thank you for your cooperation in this book.
I think it was fun to be able to participate with all three of you.
I think so, please do your best until the end.
Thank you very much
Thank you everyone.
Well then, news
First, I would like to make a closing speech.
From Samiko, the sports day executive committee chairperson.
Please say hello.Yes, yes, this campaign.
Did you all have fun? It was fun.
it was fun
It was fun, it was really fun, everyone.
It was good
Thank you very much. Every year, every year.
Thank goodness I've been really busy.
CoroLive is getting busy.
But even so, there were so many people gathered together.
Hey, let's all cooperate and each and every one of us can really do it together.
We take the initiative to call out to each other and help each other.
Nemiko and the others had already seen everything.
I was really moved by this.
I always think that it's full.It's true.
Thank you very much for your continued cooperation.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much for this.
Thank you for the opportunity.
After all, it's about newcomers and that kind of thing.
In the future, there will be members of en and ID.
There will be more interaction and we will all do more together.
It would be great if we could make Hololive more exciting.
That's what I think, so I look forward to working with Tomoe in the future.
Please yes wonderful yes please
Thank you very much. Next is Mio-chano.
I hope everyone will participate this year as well.
Thank you very much for your help and for doing your best.
I tried my best
Everyone says they are great at being stubborn.
That's the finish line for this year, thank you
Thank you
I'm tago, yes, next suba.
Yes, just as a point of contact.
I was able to see the sleep of the sleep team.
I mean, which team are you on now?
I've been working hard and this time, the result is
I think it will come out, but please do it like this, everyone.
One big thing is that I was able to work hard at it.
I think it might become a treasure.
I hope you can make use of this bond in the future.
I think it was really fun to watch.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Mashai Nice Peek Nisenkyu
nice
Senkyu Senkyu, I said yes.
Finally, I would like to announce the overall score.
I think so. Yes, yes, here we go. The announcement of the special offer.
is about 1 and then about 100
Yeah, finally 3 in order of 10 or so.
I want to attend a sports meet
Now let's talk about Miko Kara, the sports day committee chairperson.
Thank you for your specific announcement.
Okay, let's start by announcing 1.
Masuhai
Oh that's it
Please, wow, I can see this, red team.
The white team is 8, the yellow team is 6.
I want to, but what's on the screen, what's going on, I'm scared
This announcement is a little scary, though.
I don't know yet
Until now, it's been going on for about 100 years.
Yes, yes, 100 ma was announced on
Here is the book
please
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no
I don't know, I have all of these, yes, all of them.
It's about 100, please, please, this is crazy
No way, I'll go last, everyone.
Please, please, please, please, finally, a little announcement
Please
Please wow
Wow, I said yes.
8 is the winning red Yay, the winning is red Red 158
Um, white
13 yellow is 106
[music]
Just a little more
I know it's frustrating.
But it's amazing.
Yoora
Hey, Relifreeze is friendly.
Yo and E has 138 points and the white team is in 3rd place.
It was a wooden group with 106 points.Yes, well.
Everyone who worked hard, well done, well done
You did your best, Nemi, you did your best, you did your best.
When are you going to give an award for "That's great?"
Well, yes, there is an awards ceremony this time, everyone.
In Sano, the yellow group won the same medal.
This is Geo. Okay, okay then, yellow group.
The representatives of the players and teachers, Haskana Hasbe.
Chanbe-chan, please come here.
please come here
So then, 3rd place medal
Please, how about it?
[laughter]
Nisui
It came easily and it was amazing.
Congratulations on that
About Teru Teru's neck
It's on
Yomokunja
There is no silver medal on white
I'm not going to get tired of it.
But wow wow it's a gold medal
Congratulations to the white team
[applause]
It's so hot!
Teru
Congratulations Ruya Congratulations
Thank you very much Congratulations
Masu
Osa and Hai Toge took first place.
It's Ji with the red medal.
Yotowa-sama and wa
I want to see a big medal I want to see a medal mell
Thank you and congratulations
Oh wow
[applause]
Looks amazing
This is
Hololive This is Hololive
[laughter]
Why did it disappear so quickly?
There were so many diamonds, but for a moment
So that's all for now.
We are holding Hololive 4th club meeting 2023
Thank you to everyone who will
Thank you very much thank you
Thank you very much.
That's not to say it's a bit strange
Why would you want to take a commemorative photo?
Well then, what should I do?
Let's put it on that table in the middle over there.
Yes, please. Yes, yes, it's on the stand.
Okay, what's up? Kamokamo
Kanata
Are you okay with a game you can't go back to?
Is it okay? It's dangerous, it's on the top right.
Chau line up
I'm going to go to the other side here too.
I'll come in, on.
Hey, I can only see it. It's good to be back.
Okay, where are you all? Ah, that's it.
It's just a little bit still not in time.
Sorry, my husband was Lily strong.
Please wait a moment, sorry
It's okay if it's delivered there then.
Everyone is lying, it's amazing.
This is a great book that comes with us.It's true.
I'm happy
I didn't get a medal because I failed once.
But seriously without a medal?
I can't help but be fooled, that's not the case
If I do one more thing, I won't lose my temper.
Emi is gone, it's okay.
not at all
Sad thing happens, so I'm looking for medals.
Is there such a thing?
I can't give you anything, wait a minute, Mio-senpai.
Mio-senpai should take care of that.
Thank you very much.
It's worth it
Thank you, that's great.
Everyone, that little thing in front of you
Where should I look at that? Look at Mr. Ro.
Sanne is flying
Well, look there, cameraman.
It's true, it's the cameraman in front.
Cameraman here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.
There are quite a few
The cameraman
Yes, everyone, are you okay? Can you see the photo?
I'll take a picture, okay?
mercari mercari
I'm hugging you, Alex is here.
I'm going, yes
[music]
Chizu
Yay
Hey hey hey who threw it? Who just threw it?
This year's pitch
Someone just threw something at me
I'm throwing so much I'm throwing so much
Don't throw away your trash, take your trash with you
You can't see.
Thank you for flying this squid.
Dear listeners, thank you for watching that video.
And also, you helped me a lot behind the scenes.
The management staff at Taa are always very helpful.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Well then, Holorime
The event will end at the 2020 Athletic Meet.
Okay, see you again everyone
I'm going to Deotsu Hololive hahahahaha
Otsu Hololive Onai
Thank you
[music]
[applause]
Naka
How are you going to do this?
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, bye bye mina bye
Bye bye bye bye bye bye
[music]
That's why I say bye. Thank you for your hard work.
2 I'm so happy that everyone gets along so well.
hand
Seniors