[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
assistant
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
time goes by so fast what the [\h__\h]
hello
I don't know if should I uh what wait
what was I gonna say I forgot what I was
gonna say
in the middle of
me starting a sentence
I don't know if I should
something
looks like a
chat box for this
um
because I I got a cool background from
Eden Exile thank you
for putting this together but
I got no no nice chat books I also with
the normal office never know
where to put my chat so I just put it on
the TV screen
there's like
there's like free free to use
um
things that I could use
on the window
I don't know
[Music]
um
SCA friendly stream let's go
hope you guys are
appreciating it
and let's smile Wawa let's let's
give them a smile
also I'm sorry but you have to see this
for a moment
no don't look actually um
changed my mind but it was already too
late
[Music]
Maybe
this one I don't know okay
okay
all right okay
this will be at that Sudan stream
maybe actually
[Music]
um
streams much should I do it like this
good luck
bag one is a beautiful I don't want to
cover it up we'll make smaller but then
it's
[Music]
um
well
um I have a better idea but let me
let me find the fitting thing
all my streams are tattoos
yeah they tend to be
kind of true
indeed
[Music]
um
yeah how about I mean I wanted to go for
something fitting but whatever
doesn't have to be
fitting because I want to
do this and then
um
what was it again color correct remember
when I could just like see-through
oh that's kind of cool don't you think
wow wow it's like a filter
like a screen I don't know
so we're not covering up the beautiful
background but we have space
that is for you guys where do we put it
here
maybe I mean
wow graphic design is my passion
I want to stay in that corner do you
like the corner
top left
wait let's see what let me fit you
gonna make you fit perfectly
wow
okay
so
now we have here
or here
or flipped and then here
oh here
now I like it here to be honest
but should it be here or here
very very common guy I think this looks
good
I think I have lots of space down there
it works it works
looking great today thank you hmm
so
okay
oh
what time is it for you guys
I actually oh wow
nice twisting back crack
oh oh
8 AM that's that's a good morning time
7 P.M 8 am
barely anyone in my time zone 1pm in the
UK so there are some UK people here
anyone anyone from London
because I got some questions
[Music]
okay hi
hi yes
[Music]
you might be able to give advice to
yeah I wanted to ask
um I mean didn't mean to ask this
immediately
but you know I'm going to the UK
tomorrow
that been there before
uh but that time was winter
[Music]
um
and I mean we tried to check out that
was me and rmt which I we tried to check
out like in all the important things so
I mean we were
gazing through the gates of the palace
of course you know where the guards are
it's [\h__\h] cold uh what else did we do
we did a like a Harry Potter uh City
Tour walking tour oh we took one train I
think though
um that should have led us through some
important sites that also have something
maybe to do with Harry Potter
uh yeah but I actually oh yeah
I took uh a tour
um in uh what was that
was like a castle area
with some Castle
was that
I'm actually not sure oh
Tower of London maybe that was it
um
Maybe
[Music]
possibly
I know that uh around
was like
I don't even know how to describe
actually there was a bridge a big bridge
really close so it was on the on on a
river
like right next to a river
um
and my land I don't think I can visit my
land this time it's not worth it
oh okay and I guess that was Tower of
London it was quite big the whole like
space
um
do you guys are for UK oh we could do
that
so my question is like okay this is my
second time there what should I even
check out because we only have one plan
me and rmt we're only doing one thing
and then besides that
I haven't we haven't talked about what
we are gonna do
go to Soho for Cafe helping
um you should go to theme parks what
what park
Westminster what's in Westminster some
museums out
I don't know if we like museums that
much London Eye Ferris wheel oh that
sounds cute
um
yeah I mean generally like Cafe hopping
sounds nice so that that's just a thing
like that we would do in between I guess
um Big Ben
oh I didn't check up Big Ben but what do
you do you just look at it and then you
go away and you walk away
look at it what
and tell yourself the time
I guess
yeah you climb it
um
we got like I think I think I'm coming
back on Friday so we got a couple days
[Music]
Splash and puddles what
I know I don't think you're in London
but you should can you can we like
um
to chat afterwards
can you think of some recommendations
is that a cat hair
hmm
I went to a house last time I think I
didn't buy anything
let me just let me just drink some water
otherwise yeah maybe I'll also make a
tweet about like asking for
recommendations of what to do in London
because right now we barely have a plan
also on Fish and Chips I ate that once
like last time when I was there and
maybe it was the place where I ate it
but was kind of mid
foreign
[Music]
my friend was thinking the same thing
but we had other food that I thought was
good
and like one time I was uh at Heathrow
Airport I went to a restaurant
um and I was like
trying to order the cheapest thing on
the menu that would fill my belly and I
got like a plate of like everything it
was I think like supposed to be like a
breakfast English breakfast plate it had
of course the beans and then like this
like blood sausage thing I think I don't
know
um and and uh pieces of I think pieces
of toast and eh did I take a photo I
think I took a photo
I gotta say like it was a huge mess of
like so many things
but
it was actually pretty good like I was
mixing everything I was there was a
fried egg
wait I think the picture should be
ah I found it I found it okay ah okay
the only thing I didn't eat was the
mushrooms but besides that there were
like some grilled Tomatoes some really
thick sausages from the outside they
look like like weirdly shaped uh normal
Grill sausages but I think they were
something specific
uh
um and some bacon and the fried eggs and
then uh yeah the beans
baked beans I think that was like oh
yeah hidden under the fried egg was um
just some uh
potato fries so overall I was just like
mixing everything it was actually pretty
good Cumberland said oh
[Music]
Crib in it yeah
I don't need any weep stuff no no no no
I'm not looking for weep stuff in the UK
I just came back from Japan
um
why do you say beans and not me I said
beans in all caps Banks
I'm speaking how can I say something in
caps
beans
last time when I went there actually
like uh like one friend like this was
before Holo right
I think so this is before hello and I
had a a friend I think like this was one
of my very few or only friends that I
was aware of that live in the UK and now
she's not from London or so but she's
been to London many times and um she's
someone I knew from the internet for a
long time and I asked her you know what
could I do and she apparently loves
putting together like travel plans so
she made me like a really intricate plan
uh first of all how to get to our hotel
because uh from the from the airport to
the hotel was quite a journey and the
hotel was kind of like
uh not like outside of London but it was
pretty pretty like somewhere in the
weird area interesting area not in the
city center and then she gave me like so
many recommendations and she like she
she she put it together so detailed and
like
yeah interesting she fought up so many
things I'm like
did you just write this up or did you
copy paste this from somewhere because
this looks so professional you could do
this as a job and she's like no I just
really like doing this kind of stuff
um
gave me like ideas what to do and stuff
yeah
but yeah uh ever been to Brighton I
don't know what that is okay guys I
guess if I just ask you guys in a chat
I'll I won't have a
I won't remember it so
borrow Market London Bridge to stride is
all around one area
I think I saw London Bridge did I
but the borrow Market I don't know that
both cheapness what kind of things is it
like a
go bowling romance shut up
is it like a
Google them I thought I'm too lazy right
now
I'll I'll ask again on Twitter so you
guys please tell me your ideas on
Twitter
you should go to Scotland honestly we
would have time but
we would have to book a flight and
everything
um I think we'll stay in the area but
um the actual reason why we're going
there we're not gonna be in London
we're going to a
um
Musical
yeah and it's like outside of London
um
this is the only reason we're going to
I'm really really really
curious if it's gonna be good but yeah
yeah it's just starting and they're
doing it in like something that looks
like a barn from the outside but I guess
it like kind of creates a
um like a
like a atmosphere that is kind of
hobbitsy
um
sounds like you're gonna have a blast oh
I wonder
uh I don't know I'm just hoping that at
least it won't be so hot over there
because like previously we went in
winter and it was freezing cold I was
suffering because of the cold couldn't
enjoy it that much honestly but now it's
summer time so I'm guessing it's not
that hot over there
like 15 degrees oh that's nothing sheesh
okay
I hope they use the potato song hey
we'll see we'll see
they'll make up lots of new songs I'm
sure
22 to 25.
it's kind of different from what else
someone else said
um 23 the other day highest
oh that's fine and I'm guessing it's
like I don't know just generally more
comfortable
yeah
okay
that's good they're taking the hobbit's
eyes and guard they're taking the
helmets to ice and guard I really doubt
they're gonna use that in the music
like a meme Musical made up of just
memes
[Music]
um
that would be so funny towels
potatoes potatoes
oh smash on Ball and put them in still
coming straight
yeah rmt knows the movie by heart like
she can say all these phrases by heart
and not even only the famous ones
I can't but I love I love Lord of the
Rings I'm gonna tell you how it was and
then Chet is dead but then you can if
you're still alive you can check out the
musical yourself maybe especially the UK
people
[Music]
big big recommend I'm gonna check it out
and then see Hello Ted come back to me
[Applause]
come back
[Music]
I'm gonna cry ah
you little shits why are you leaving me
what what
oh you tease
oh you're giving me trust issues
when are you really back
are you really back
okay anyway
um let's talk about some topics because
I I won't be
I was gonna stream only one hour
because afterwards I wanted to
participate I told Callie I'll be
participating in the
like her Clubhouse 51 totumachi
I told her that but uh the person who's
like helping her put together the
schedule of things
uh I guess didn't know I was wanting to
purchase the pair too and now all the
slots are taken up
so
maybe I'm not
maybe I'm not joining so I don't need to
stop so early anyway but I still want it
to be short because I I need to
clean my apartment and then pack for
tomorrow
and but still unpack my my suitcases
from Japan because I just arrived
yesterday evening
um
yeah I'm being asked if I want to be in
the drawing collab instead I don't
really want to draw
[Music]
I don't really like trying like when
people watch me it puts me under
pressure I don't like it
good
but but Clubhouse like
can I just
can I join your Clubhouse slot and we
battle
Cali together
I don't want to draw
to be one-on-one in the clubhouse right
there's games that you can do like with
free people right I think so
right
yeah there are a couple
[Music]
um
hijacking
I'm sure like the one I'm asking is the
one who will be the least against
sharing her slots with me
um
okay okay so I'm waiting for that
um but now let me tell you some things
what should I talk about first oh my God
there's so many things
keep some things for
um
GTA and stuff like that
week of July and I only used my art for
July 1.
[Music]
um damn official Channel video
I mean
I'm in
I don't know if I can say what it is
even though it's so obvious what it is
the elephant in the room
oh
I I I wanted to say like damn finally
right like you guys were waiting for it
so long and honestly us too
like I feel like you know after Council
uh
I personally felt you know like okay
we're like a good amount of people now I
don't want to like
uh have en be too crowded not that it's
my decision but I don't like it when it
gets too crowded and I want everybody to
you know have their own thing and have
time to shine and it was like
comfortable and and you know for a while
that just felt like you know this is
comfortable this is I don't need any
more
but I feel like after how long has it
been two years now or so
like halfway through after the first
year I'm like hmm
okay maybe
it's me
at this point I wouldn't mind getting
some newbies you know
um but it took took a long time
yeah it took a long time took so long
and I was I was getting pretty impatient
too not gonna lie like in the past
half year
I think I was getting pretty impatient
like I need some fresh blood is what I
was feeling like I need some things
someone new to bounce off of someone new
to talk to someone you to get to know
fresh blood fresh meat
that's how I was feeling
so that looks like it could be and I
don't know if it is but doesn't it
surely look like this could be something
like that fresh blood
no
no no no
no no no no no no no no
yeah
I I will uh share more of my thoughts
when it's the time to share more of my
thoughts but for now
it is not time to share more of my
thoughts I think because I would
accidentally say too many things
oh sure
probably
um
it's so funny that
kfb has this image of like kfp teases me
by calling me likjo and all that uh it
makes fun of me for that
um but kfp knows very well I think we
joke about it but you guys know very
well that uh there are really like
in three years maybe there's only one
case or so where I leaked something that
I shouldn't have I don't even remember
when it would have been but if I leak
something
if I if I leak something you don't know
until it actually happened so I leak it
in a way that it's like it's just
hinting at something and you've only
understand once you have the information
so that's not really you know me leaking
something it's just hinting just placing
careful hints here and there yeah but
because you guys make fun of me like
that uh
and give me that name some people might
interpret it as I have history with
leaking things and getting in trouble
with that
which is not true
I I don't think I ever got in trouble
for licking something
uh
I mean
um
not something like you know
I don't know not really I think
yeah I mean I tell you my birthday merch
but only because that's like stuff you
know that I I have all the rights to let
you know if I wanna then I tell you I'm
not coping shut up
hmm
[Laughter]
yeah the things that I like very clearly
leak you know are things like my album
and stuff like just because I I can
decide if I want to tell you guys more
about it it's my decision
um
and I like to share the progress of
things the process and progress
anyway I wanted to show you guys
[Music]
foreign
I wanted to show you my notes
for the
the video from the alphabet revealed the
lore video and talk a little bit about
that
because
um so the storyboard I made a whole
storyboard and
it's
it's very sketchy and rough but uh
I think it shows well
what I was thinking about when I yeah
the whole story yeah
um
okay maybe we can like even uh compare
it
I don't know
okay so first of all like I was like
thinking about whom animators huh I want
to make an animation like a lore
animation who to ask oh my god
um and I had like maybe like two free
people in mind
uh uh but in the end I'm glad I went
with matzu because like the style
fits so well in my opinion
um
and
was very efficient and fast
so
um
[Music]
I will I will quote myself and show you
the pictures
my idea is basically
Kiara in default somewhere on the phone
or so noticing a shooting star in the
sky and looking up to it
which is the
very beginning I mean you know I'm on
the phone I'm talking to someone who
knows what it is kind of like bored and
also tired maybe of like every day being
the same and look up but I know it's a
shooting star exactly what I said and
then I have I think
does this work
uh
I'm I'm downloading it from
Twitter now
a messy very messy okay
uh flump rotate like this yeah okay oh
[\h__\h]
okay ah [\h__\h] what
huh
uh
what
what is
ah there it is okay default Kiana having
a flashback when looking into the sky
flashback or I mean that was
in my my final intention wasn't really
flashback but more like
we see we see a plan
it's not her having a flashlight we see
something she doesn't see she's just
getting you know like this feeling whoa
that's not normal you know what she sees
it's not normal and you see me I'm on
the phone and I'm looking at the sky you
know perfect this is exactly this is
yeah and then moving on
then we switch timelines to alter Kiara
who is in the middle I say I wrote
timelines but I um it's more like a
universe so Alta Kiara who is in the
middle of a heated discussion with
Travelers but we won't show the outfit
too much yet only shots from behind or
close-ups of hand arm face she then
tells them to leave but not before they
give her a letter or it just shows up
there
um so
I basically what I was trying to do here
is I wanted to have a lore animation but
I didn't want it to reveal too much of
the outfit yet because I was gonna show
it before actually showing the outfit so
I didn't want it to give away everything
uh so I was like sketching out scenes
and thinking of scenes where you could
you see something some stuff is going on
but you don't see everything clearly so
it's more like close-ups of the hand
close-ups of the eyes close-ups of the
shoes Etc trying to hide a full view in
the end we did have a couple of like
pretty full clear views shots as well
but they were fast and in the end you
know it's black and white and everything
so I guess it wasn't like too much of a
problem right
but here is the the next one so
this is right after that
switch timeline to other Kiana don't
show too much of outfit yet close up a
face hand on desk Etc so this now
leads to this
[Music]
mm-hmm I was trying to have her from the
back there because I thought back view
won't reveal too much
hand close-up
there this is exactly how I asked him to
do it
[Music]
ah okay and then
yeah first the idea was uh I haven't
heard a discussion with sometimes first
idea was they give her a letter or
eventually I decided maybe it's better
that it just you know is like there it
shows up magically
so
yeah alter also love both lavas are
basically kind of tired you know of
every day
they're both kind of tired you know they
want something new to happen change in
life everyday life so she's in the
medieval fancy office kind of place
throughout this we didn't see her
sitting down contemplating what to do
with the letter but eventually picking
it up was my instruction
[Music]
I have to turn this again
yes I did it right
so accidentally thoughtful scene looking
at the letter sit down first they gave
her the letter question mark maybe not
but yeah
see me sitting
yeah basically what you just saw
filling up help
I'm drowning next was when she reads the
letter fought to be unreadable for the
viewer it starts Going Up in Flames she
lets go of it quickly then turns to
ashes and shocked I don't think it ever
turned into ashes but it's actually it
it was pretty [\h__\h] cool and shocked
close-up of the face
and gave I gave very clear
instructions I think because I I I'll be
honest you know I I don't really
um when I was like sketching this up and
like thinking of how to do this lore
video
I did not have a really clear Overview
at first I just like
went
with it like I don't know
I wasn't 100 sure what I was doing
and where I was going with this but it
just you know it's it's shaped itself
into a thing that actually ended up
working out just fine so here uh when
reading the letters start outside then
suddenly the letter catches fire turns
into ashes quickly tearing up with fire
and eyes
yeah wow wow wow
that happened that's happening that's
happening
[Music]
good storyboard Ryan he was able to work
with it
special in combination with the music is
so [\h__\h] Epic
[Music]
yeah and even though it's mainly in
black and white he added some
contrasting colors here by adding some
red or orange yellow hmm
okay
so that happens and um
uh suddenly that should start moving and
growing and surrounding her whole body
like a hurricane and she disappears in
it
yeah it was more like the Flames
surrounded her like a hurricane in the
end but that's fine it's perfectly
fine it's better this way I think
it's good
so here is no one don't know how to draw
this but the ashes around alter Kiara
she disappears within and gets summoned
to our timeline slash universe
hurricane uh no more question mark no
more Wawa on the desk and then oh yeah
the the third picture is supposed to be
a shoe on uh on the on the ground on the
asphalt
spawn in a normal street with my
request
and then lay one more
and then we see her spawn in the modern
world just close up of her feet on the
street then a scene where default Kiana
stands in front of new alter Kiara who
just teleported here shocked maybe from
two different angles first one with
alter Kiara backside slightly in front
of normal Kiara and then one from the
direct side
get it
[Music]
and then we have the last this I think
the last one
um
so
they look at each other shocked and by
it by placing them like this I thought
again it would help to not reveal too
much of the outfit and then hands touch
Kiana hand disappear
hey
sorry Chad
thank you
near this
yeah well there's they switched in
Dimensions is what I'm implying because
there can only you guys always say that
I'm like my Lord doesn't match with what
I'm making up over the years
um but that's not sure so basically what
happens here I told you I told you
before only one Phoenix can be I'm the
only left one I and they can only be one
so uh they're being switched out because
voila Ultima being there means the other
one can't be there at the same time so
they're switching
um
right here the shoe close-up and the
side close up
not revealing too much again then the
back view
can I feel cute
and the touch
oh
[Applause]
Epic
so epic
so good
[Music]
so those were my thoughts my ideas my my
first initiative ideas and I think
mazuru recreated it perfectly we're like
actually yeah put it into
uh form into shape
really really nicely beautifully
she's not dead she's just switched like
now all the kfp WoW is uh in in in the
fantasy world
Get Wrecked
um
yeah I'm really happy with the outcome
the problem was I think a little bit
from us that when when this was being
created
um the outfit drafts that I had were
already very very
you know far in the finishing stage but
[Applause]
dear dear Suave summer one thing I
noticed when working with Suave summer
was
uh I would get drafts and it looks like
pretty much like okay all perfect not
much I want to change like I wouldn't
even request many changes but uh like a
few days later they would come back send
me
um Fruita like but we weren't
interacting directly but yeah the
department would send me like updates
and suddenly like so many things changed
again
so that was a bit difficult because like
uh Mazda was already like so far in
drawing everything it was hard to change
things like at some point I had a
breastplate right Only One Singular
breastplate and originally the the
animation was already finished and it
had me with breastplates and I was like
difficult to change this now right so he
was like yeah
very difficult I'm like okay you don't
have to do it don't worry about it it's
not not a big deal but hello I'm the fan
I'm a new fan hello welcome but he ended
up indeed removing the breastplate out
of all the scenes wow
and then the other way around it was
like
um
um uh one of the early drafts had the
shoes with ribbons and it was kind of
like elegant cute
um and then Mazu was drawing it like
that
in the animation but then swapped later
on changed that
into something else and then it was the
other way around this time I didn't ask
Mazda to change it but I asked 12 like
actually I really like the shoes the way
they were at first so can we switch them
back to when they had a ribbon and so
yeah that's when it went back to that
hmm
yeah yeah back and forth yeah I was
trying to coordinate them so that the
video would reflect the final form and
that the final form would reflect the
video and all that it was difficult
because they were working separately and
I'm the only one like trying to
communicate between them
[Music]
yeah and the thing is like
um
I'm also not even talking directly to
swap though like I'm talking to like the
art department or whatever and and
they're giving my message to Suave and
it's like
um
oh always I have to always like like I'm
not getting like daily updates no I'm
getting like kind of always like updates
and chunks so yeah
um
oh well but it worked out fine and even
if there's some differences in the final
outfit compared to the video I think
it's not a big deal
yeah
I like it I like both no
it turned out great yeah and honestly I
was shocked by you guys's reaction I
I
I feel like in the beginning I
um I loved all the drafts that Suave was
giving me but at that point it was still
like swap drawing it on like his own
sketches of me of my body and then later
on he would put it on top of my body and
then I was like hmm
then it started feeling a little bit
like
unusual to me like this is a different
artist matching their art style a little
bit to the OG art style because he kind
of has to
and I don't know maybe because I was
used to like always seeing it in his
style because the way he would draw my
body looked very different than what my
like base is
hmm
so it was kind of unusual to me but my
eyes I think had to get used to it uh
but it did like throw some doubts at me
like um is this gonna is this gonna like
match well together in the end is it
gonna
harmonize and all that and are you guys
gonna like it it's gonna be weird for
you guys I don't know
but I think the final result
actually uh came together quite nicely
one cool thing now that I noticed
that
was also concerning me a little bit in
the beginning because I never saw this
before
um
with you know outfits being drawn in
live 2D
have you noticed swap is using like 3D
elements
some of the armor
like the yeah some of these they're like
originally it was like 3D elements
and rendered into 2D
um
I think the final
look
it Blends in well
I feel like there were some times where
I saw it and it was like it stood out to
me a lot so I was like hmm
it looks cool but it stands out to me
like I don't know if this is gonna blend
in
yeah that's probably a reason why it's
so detailed but yeah I think it's it it
Blends in nicely in the end and and it
looks so detailed like I feel like
for like uh us whole life members I look
at the default outfits from everybody
these days and then the follow-up like
like casual outfits and this and that
and I feel like you know uh it's not
always the case but I feel like the
default outfit is always like the most
detailed one
which has the most accessories and the
most layers of cloves and this and that
um
and
however
for this outfit
I'm so happy because I wanted it to be
really detailed I I wanted it to have
you know a lot of design
um
points and everything you know so Suave
worked so hard on it and put so much
attention to detail right so I was
really happy elements yes Design
Elements that's what I want to say
unfortunately I had to give up on some
things like the weapons
um that was really cool but I I was
thinking in hindsight like when I had to
make the choice I was like
well I think generally a second
hairstyle will always give me more
meaningful
ways of making use of it than uh a
weapon
because a hairstyle changes the looks so
much
uh I think as a streamer who almost
streams like daily generally
it would work uh it would help me more
and then I I actually thought
uh we can make attachments behind our
backs and the way he originally Drew my
weapon
if you recall it was just behind my back
it wasn't really it didn't really look
like it was attached anywhere in
particular so I could commission an
illustration
of a weapon and just place it
as a PNG behind myself and cheat my way
out of this situation you know what I
mean big brain
and he's
he wrote on Twitter I think it's a he
pretty I don't know but I'm pretty sure
I just have a feeling
but he said on Twitter he please wait
everybody I'm going to make um like a
detailed illustration about the weapons
probably because I was like you know
appealing on my stream that I really
like the weapons and this like regretful
that I have to give up on it
[Music]
um
foreign
so I think that should work if it's just
a PNG of a weapon
I I feel like I can just attach it to my
back behind as a back layer
so Ken kananika um
what DLC that swap do in terms of a rice
remember when I was playing Tales of
arise
um the one that was only for the two
main characters Shion and alfin The Dark
One the dark black
futuristic fancy
outfit
the eduonya
yeah
I'll be very honest with you
when I
uh was told hookah papa will not be
doing this outfit takamasikara you have
to choose a different artist either you
choose or we choose so I was like
if I
have to you know I'm already like
delayed at this point that you're
telling me I can't get hookah Papa
so I'm already getting it later than
everybody else probably turns out that's
not true but that's what it looked like
uh and I have to go for someone else I
wasn't really like happy with the idea
at first you know
but then I thought okay
then I will take this opportunity to go
with someone that
I will be very happy with you know
having on board yeah I'll make the most
out of it
so I I gave them uh like a list of a
couple of artists I think
um
and the reason why I put swap on there
is like I went through the list of
artists that I follow on Twitter and I'm
like who who do I really really want to
have on board who be really cool to have
I was thinking you know of course like
Tales of artists
would be cool
you know the main the main artists uh
uh but that seems a bit difficult I
think I didn't even attempt that
but then I was reminded by my the people
that I follow
uh of Swap and I'm like
he he's
sort of indirectly a tails off artists
hmm and I I was like going for the
Twitter to you know get a feeling like
could this work
and I was like kind of doubting it a
little bit because
normally like his art style is very
particular
um and the designs that he creates are
also very particular
it's very special
um
but I felt like I could at least throw
it out there as a candidate and see how
it goes and
I think originally I wasn't sure yet
what kind of outfit I wanted
but I felt like if if Suave would accept
I would like to do something that he
specializes in like makes his
specialization
into it
because it's only something he can do
it's what makes him special and mix it
with uh you know what I would like to
see as well
so
yeah I think his his like specialty is
reflected in the outfit yeah it's got
the Suave touch
his strong suit yeah
and it's still something that I was kind
of like hoping to get eventually AKA an
outfit that's kind of jrpg-ish and also
kind of dark you know hmm
so those were my thoughts behind my
choice and then yeah Suave accepted
and we started working on it and I gave
like you know I gave uh actually I gave
extremely
clear instructions on hairstyles
especially
uh really really really detailed ideas
of what
the references of what I want
like even after I first got the drafts I
was like for example unhappy with the
bangs and I would give very very
particular detailed
uh sketches like of the bangs of how
they should look like
stuff like that and the the lower like
strands and all that and the sticky ones
that stick out to the side
this and that yeah and then for like
generally for the whole vibe and the
outfit
yeah
yeah I I like gave some references from
suave's own art like hey something like
this like you drew before it would be
nice and also I will not say it's
because
I don't know if that's good to say but I
gave like certain
games artwork
character design artwork also as an
inspiration
and he combined every not necessarily
she or no actually not really
but she combined everything
so well like it's a great mix of
everything I asked him for
there may have been some Final Fantasy
references
yeah fusion fusion
yeah that's why I feel like this outfit
will look so good if I play Final
Fantasy 16.
foreign
[Music]
if I have to go for a different artist
than usual then I definitely want it to
be a result that I am 100 happy with it
is what I was thinking
the whole time I was hearing it tell me
tell me earlier huh
Mamma Mia
a [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
the first person is not there
and she also didn't reply
[Music]
well I mean I can even play it without
being
[Music]
without a blast streaming I guess but
she's not in the
the first person that should that's in
the list
oh wait she did say something like can I
go a bit later I was scared I won't make
it
oh then first is
all right this list is old they switched
okay maybe an hour maybe at 11 PM jst
I still have some time
so that is my
story about this new outfit that I can
think of right now
um I feel like you know it's it's very
different from my other outfits but for
me
[Music]
um
besides just being something to use for
like RPG streams
I feel like if I were to if I had input
in the beginning for my default design
saying that this is how I would have had
it look like probably not
uh but if this was the theme I would
have been given
and then had input then this would be
the direction I would go for
like let's say I'm given an overall
theme and then it's like okay if you
create something if you ask for
something within these boundaries then
it's okay then I would probably go for
something like this and it's it's
definitely something that personally
speaks to me
um
fits your lore you think so so now then
it's kind of like
I added it to my lawyer there's two
hours now there's the fast food K of P
Wawa
and this is yeah this is the warrior the
adventurer the fantasy world wow now we
have two wow
a Wawa that I feel pretty comfortable
and I
yeah oh
oh Kelly oh that's sweet
Cali is like can we like because
everybody who gets like 40 minutes she's
like oh but I want I want wow what to be
part of it can we
and we make everything 20 minutes then
well I don't uh I don't know if it's
good to like
switch things around so much because
there's some Japanese members
participating and they already have like
a set
slot
I don't know
if it's good to switch things around
again I'll just see what Ollie says
um
surely Ollie will let me into her slots
[Music]
I don't want to
I don't like I really don't like I want
to I wish I was more comfortable with it
but I don't like drawing on stream
but I was thinking I kind of want to do
an art stream where I draw this outfit
yeah yeah I'm sure only won't mind I
agree couch
you remembered don't use a grandpa emoji
I was always still streaming with uh
her collab stream I saw something going
on is that right now
would it get better on Art man
I want to
four years
I did a whole passport to play through
all of that was an art stream
that was like a sudden influx of art
strains basically
okay uh
let me see um what's up message
[Music]
um
uh
we want to know what I was saying 999
about so for the couple days where I'm
gone uh
uh someone unusual is taking care of my
cats this time
because I didn't always want to ask the
same people I feel like you know my
brother
uh my brother took care of my cats this
time but I feel like he's he prefers to
uh
chill at his own place nowadays
um and so my mom also has like been
taking care of my cat cats a lot but I
don't want to continuously ask her to go
back and forth back and forth so because
this was just like a short date a
certain someone has been like begging me
over the past year
to meet my cats
again
someone
who used to be a replacement for me for
rmt
um
who lived in my room for a while when I
was in Japan
not IMT but rmt of rmt
rrmmt
or rmtrmt
uh and she's been lying the whole time
like I miss you cats I love you cats so
much I want to show you cats please
please please also tell me about Japan
please please no I'm not really like I
like her but I and you know we weren't
we never got that close but she really
loves my cats understandably so
so
um I'm like okay well you know what if
she can make these dates then sure she
won't be sleeping over
um because she has a dog that she needs
to take care of too so she'll just be
here like maybe for a few hours a day
feed and cuddle my cats
at least she loves my cat so I'm very I
trust her with giving my cats enough
love
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
yeah uh
I think I she probably won't show up in
the morning so I should probably get
that machine to work tonight
the the timer machine thingy
[Music]
I should try that oh
I'll try uh anyway so she was just
asking me can I bring my dog
my cats have never met
any other animal before
so uh nine I don't think so oh that's a
dog a dog
yeah so I said
please no that doesn't sound like a good
idea
they would be scared especially in um
chunky monkey would be scared I think
who knows that maybe they would hit it
up yeah maybe but who knows
[Music]
chunky monkey is like really a scaredy
cat
so better not to do that
um
yeah
no risky I don't like the idea
uh anyway let's see
I want to tell you a tangent that I have
pictures for because during GTA streams
that might
be a bit difficult so let's see what
could I
what's attention
let me send them over on Discord really
quickly
[Music]
yeah
checking for a Reflections really quick
also I keep on having this Like Oxygen
problem
[Music]
okay okay wait
yeah
this picture
uh
[Music]
yeah looks fine
there's many possible Reflections but I
don't see anything
it's fine
I'm so good at taking pictures
[Music]
wow my food pictures are so good
beautiful
[Music]
wow ooh yummy
okay
[Music]
remember
do you remember
that me and Cali went to a spa
on last week
Wednesday Tuesday
which
to tell you the truth
was
kind of
um because you know during my birthday
on the 6th of July
I was in Austria
therefore I could not celebrate it with
Cali
or anyone in Japan so this was a
afterwards celebration with Kelly and me
um treating myself
to a birthday present and afterwards
birthday present because wait what did I
do on my birthday oh yeah I was
streaming the whole day I was cooking
and doing [\h__\h] I actually was really
stressed I had no time for myself so I
thought you know after a flight I'd like
to have a massage anyway so like
together yeah it's a delayed birthday
party with Kelly uh yes so that's what
we did and I went to a place like me and
Kelly have been to several Spas at this
point
um
when I went to one that I feel
very
familiar and comfortable with because I
went there already like
many many years ago several times
[Music]
let me send this pictures really quickly
over
which one is the right one this one
[Laughter]
[Music]
what was that
devious
got it
for a Discord let me do it
sanding to Mommy AKA General
Mommy
[Music]
no nothing's funny nothing's funny
you think this is funny
why did I do it like that I'm so stupid
wait I'm gonna do it again maybe
um
[Music]
comfortable tattoo done Studio
okay
there we go I've got the pictures
[Music]
um we had to meet early because the
earliest massage
time that I could get was like 12.
um but the good thing is that this place
is where I like to go there when you get
a massage but it seems to be the thing
and all of these like hotel spas uh
after you get the massage you're allowed
to stay in the spa area for the whole
day so you can use the pools and
everything the whole day really nice
so that's my life hack basically
okay let me show you let me give you an
overall View
last check for Reflections but I don't
see anything good
okay
it actually is way bigger than it looks
on this picture actually but
this is the inside this was after we got
the massage already this is the inside
it's a big pool it looks so round here
but it's actually way more like
I'll just say lengthy
really long it's really really long it's
much bigger than the pool I usually swim
in and if you look outside the window
straight outside the window you see the
Rainbow Bridge this is in odaiba one of
my favorite places in Japan
it's actually a Hilton when I first went
here it wasn't the Hilton it was I think
a nickel
however the spa area did not change at
all I've been going here for like 13
years
no okay not 14 years
maybe like 10. um
yeah so you see the Rainbow Bridge and
then before you go outside you see
there's a Jacuzzi a warm jacuzzi there
and even the normal pool was actually
pretty warm uh so that was comfortable
and uh on the left side before you go
outside you see there's a sauna there's
two saunas there's an aroma uh steam
sauna and a
a dry sauna
and uh for the dry sauna you get a look
at the Rainbow Bridge too because the
windows face that way and outside
there's also a big
um it's not deep but it's a little bit
lengthy let me show you
another jacuzzi AKA Whirlpool but they
wear like two
freaking Zoomer girls
who wear I swear to God for three hours
straight
I saw them coming in to the reception uh
and I saw them at once they came in
dressed up in her swims in their
swimsuits
with really perfect hair and makeup
I swear there was not a single time
where they swam for pleasure the whole
time while trying to keep their face
their head and their hair outside of the
water for three hours without a break
they were taking pictures of each other
and together
like their shutter sounds the whole time
was going off
they took pictures at every corner of
this like Spa in the water outside of
the water here and there everywhere
except in the sauna but it's not because
you have to be naked in there no
actually you use that sauna in a
swimsuit that's why I feel more
comfortable there
I mean I get it I like to take a few
cute shots you know here and there
you know for no no
but they they only came there for that I
swear that's still there they didn't
even have a room in the hotel either no
they didn't have a massage either
because I heard when they were like
checking in to the spa they just got
entrance to the this spot area the pool
area
and uh so I had to like be careful that
I don't have them on my pictures when I
was taking pictures of not myself but
the area
uh
[Music]
on the right side is the influenza Zuma
girls who had nothing better to do than
take pictures of themselves for three
hours like I was thinking to myself
but like ah are you ever gonna are you
ever gonna get into the water ever to
swim
like I feel like Zoomers are even worse
than millennials
do they know
how to
like get into an ocean or a pool
without
like
oh without the purpose of taking
influential Instagram pics to show off
their butt
is
anyway this is the Rainbow Bridge which
isn't very rainbowy at that moment and
it looks kind of like bad weather but it
was it was it was nice
it was nice it's just that the picture
looks kind of dark it wasn't so bad
though and it was like already uh like
kind of late at that point uh
but this basically it's like a kind of
on an elevated place you look down on
the right side and you see like the the
big Square
um where there's like a fake freedom
statue
also
um but yeah you get a nice view here and
the water is warm and
that's how it goes
um
is like it used to be my
like getaway place in Tokyo
when I wanted to go somewhere else
outside of Tokyo I go to odaiba
because it's not so far it's not as far
as you know remember enoshima where I
would take people to
enoshima is really far
there's also like an indoor uh theme
park in udaipa called joy purisu that
whole life also had uh collaborations
with before but also they have like
Vocaloid collaboration Etc they always
have some kind of collaboration and it's
like an indoor theme park they have like
a
and they have a swish and swish swash
it's really cool if there's like bad
weather but you want to go to something
like Disneyland
several floors of Swiss wall swash
swoosh
um
foreign
company building there and they always
have like some kind of Summer Festival
going on uh in front of their uh
building
and I used to go to it a few times
because my favorite hello project Idol
groups would perform there and which was
really nice and and there was always
like yummy food it's always themed after
something and this time I saw they were
doing it too but
um I couldn't go I was just looking at
it from afar they were doing some Fuji
TV uh like it wasn't related to Fuji TV
but they had like a festival going on
again yeah
yeah yeah
so this is this is nice isn't it so we
were spending all day chenma is reacting
pictures that I sent
she's crying and dying she sent me all
possible shocks and sad emojis
towards the food
sorry
food taro gomezan
and Japanese we like to say meshitero
so uh uh I I was I was hoping to get
lunch before but you know
um couldn't because too early massage
too early
so actually afterwards I was able to
book Teppanyaki Yaki at this hotel
because they have a couple restaurants
too and and and Teppanyaki me and Kelly
went to this hotel sepanyaki before when
I was still living in Japan around the
end of my time there so it was really
really nostalgic to come back there yeah
and I really I really remember the
Teppanyaki from this place very fondly
really really yummy
um
super yummy so I was really happy to get
back here and Kelly is like on some kind
of diet where she doesn't eat bread so
she said I'm gonna eat meat so I'm like
this is perfect I have the perfect thing
so we got the course
um where I had to switch out some things
because they oh they always like to put
like shellfish and [\h__\h] that I can't eat
into these menus uh courses and I'm like
uh can you can I get something instead
of this shellfish stuff and they're like
oh I do you have a little kid
allergy and I'm like
yes
yeah yeah yeah this is the first time I
ever said this guys but I'm sick I'm
sick of you know just being thought of
as a picky person
I'm sick of it so I just went with it
because I you know in the end what does
it matter I just don't want to be served
these shellfish
yeah I did get some fish instead and
which was yummy so you know what [\h__\h] it
I have shellfish allergy hell yeah
oh yeah
so what is this what do you think this
is
guess what it is
this was the starter it was a soup
it was a soup
so this soup uh it comes in a I learned
something new it comes in a foil that is
made for cooking you place it on the hot
plate just like that
without the plate
um it was something like Carta something
like
I forgot the name but it's uh it's a a
cooking foil
and I was asking like I was interested
because you know I'm into cooking
because I'm like it what is what is the
like why why does a chef use this what
is the reason behind it like does it
give it a special flavor or something
and the chef was very honest and said uh
no so actually it's just because it's
it's Bentley it's useful because you
don't have to clean plates
what pots or anything
and you can see it's
when it Cooks you see inside
what it is that's it so it's just for
Aesthetics and saving
you know actually I would say it's only
for the Aesthetics the extra is just you
don't have to clean plates it's just
practical
soup
so he puts this on the Teppanyaki hot
plate and the it boils a little bit
there's a little bit of bread in there
and some veggies and this and that and
meat
and I did not send a picture did I of
the final let me
send it
[Music]
so there was not much liquid in this
soup but it was good you know there were
several uh
courses so you know
this is how it ends up on your plate I
guess you really don't have to clean
anything this looks like
that looks like nothing so I took a
close-up where it looks like it's a
little bit more than uh than in the big
picture here
reflection of me on here I hope not
good night
shockingly little amount of soup for ads
it was good though it was good had a
very nice
um
meaty soup flavor
uh the next thing
was something I was a bit worried about
because I'll be honest I never had fall
gra before and it's like one of those
things that have fancy names that's why
I don't like to eat it
scares me and I don't want to order it
and then not be able to eat it but I I
tried my best because I already cut so
many things off of my menu because of
the shellfish allergy so I was like okay
I'll try it because actually like what
fogra is I guess I've eaten something
like that before on bread
uh in in Austria so yeah
oh it's terrible for animal cruelty
really
yeah it's duck liver
um I thought that it would be served
like like like kind of raw and uh like
as a paste kind of thing but no he
grilled it and he added it
it looks like meat in the end right and
he added this sauce that
um tastes a little bit like what my mom
would always make
uh vinegar with red wine kind of sauce
because the the flavor was very familiar
to me and then
um
picture but you know what it's on top of
it's it's it's it's it's chilling on top
of corn pancakes
like I saw the batter it was like a
yellowish batter with like big chunks of
corn inside and he grilled them into
pancakes and I'm like oh my God I love
corn and they were so good I don't know
what else was in these pancakes but it
was so good it was like I don't know
what's in the batter it tastes so good
and then the fruit fruity thing like one
is a mango and one is um
forgot the word
uh what you like to put in
tea sometimes
um good for your throat I think
Ginger yeah like some kind of like
specially prepared Ginger
um
foreign
wow wow this [\h__\h] was so good
I just had to get over my fear of eating
something something that was inside
someone AKA a liver normally like not my
thing
um but in this form and shape it was
fine with this sauce especially
really good
let me get rid of this too
and then we had
uh oh yeah Callie apparently she she had
full guy before but she wasn't a big fan
of this one apparently I actually liked
it
so here comes my replacement of uh the
the allergy shellfish
um
some nice
cuts of meat from a fish there were two
different ones but they I don't really
remember well but they were just some
kind of like stone fish they said
uh I think one he said was a tie
the other one I don't remember
and of course he grilled it thank God
and the sauce was some I know I don't
remember
but he grilled it
and it turned out
really yummy I don't eat fish much so
this is good
you have every once in a while
so as you can see properly grilled all
good before after goodbye fish you are
in my tummy I absorbed all your
nutrients
I was there too yeah I didn't eat the
flowers though
and Callie Callie got some grilled
shellfish butt uh
she also wasn't 100 fine with this
because she she can't eat the inside so
she had the guts and everything taken
out here disgusting
but yeah they took that out for her
so there's the feet or whatever that is
until now I want to throw up
okay
um
ew
oh was it in it looks like its own thing
like its own insect but
I'm guessing it's uh it's legs I don't
want to look at it anymore
no I don't wanna
next
this was the vegetable uh of course step
whatever I don't know
um the the paste the sauce is uh minced
meat miso sauce
I've never had like a sauce as a side
before that had minced meat and it's
actually pretty good pretty yummy very
special very strong flavor uh behind you
know what that veggie is I gave almost
all of it to Cali because she also
um I think I ate some of her foreground
I think
yeah no no she gave me her bread from
the soup she didn't want to eat the
bread so in exchange I gave her my
eggplant because I don't like eggplant
and oh interestingly in on the veggie
plates the one in the back you know what
that is
it's melon
I like melon on its own like fresh and
all that as a fruit
I wouldn't really put it in this
combination I didn't think it fits well
to be honest they should have done a
different veggie like an actual veggie
and then the yellowish one
I think he said was cornbread it was
kind of like like a sticky texture
oh not sticky maybe not chunky
a little bit chewy but like really soft
I really liked this one
sweet
mmm
yeah grilled into a cube
no I don't think it was polenta because
it didn't taste like polenta I like I I
know polenta didn't seem like polento
this whole time by the way me and Callie
were having the whole day actually
really heated discussions uh about
anything
yeah one time I had to during the dinner
I had to tell Kelly Kelly you have to
speak a little bit more quiet the people
next to us actually speak English
like normally I'm not like I don't make
a big deal out of you know I have to be
sick the client's super careful and this
and that
um but just this once I actually shushed
Cali
because yeah the people next to us were
uh also speaking English and the overall
this Teppanyaki Restaurant the
atmosphere was really quiet
um
so
Cali was uh a little bit loud I felt
like it's hard to know this on your own
so
I told her
just a little bit
um
so you know what we chose for the meat
course the main course
there were like different choices but we
took the choice that was all of them
there was a choice where you could get
like three different types of A5 wagyu
from different parts of the body I
suppose
um
this [\h__\h]
was Yabba
um
okay and on the upcoming picture it
doesn't look so red but this was
probably the reddest meat I've ever had
um I think we ordered it as medium rare
uh
thing
but it's like it doesn't look so red on
the on the photo but it was more red
than this trust me and it was however so
good
it was so [\h__\h] good you can only
really see the inside of the right piece
anyway
um but it was pretty red still so it
took it took me like a little bit of
braveness
to get over myself but um
that this is why I had this Teppanyaki
restaurant in such good memory because
this is like maybe the best meat
I've ever eaten it was back then and it
still is much there
wagyu
sekai Ichi Oishi
MO
Shi Association it's on top of uh uh do
you see a Salt Plate and uh they served
it with some sauces but when I eat this
type of high quality meat
I don't use the sauces I just eat it
with a little bit of salt
so they had some salt too I didn't like
just rub it on the salt block no there
was like salt sprinkled around it too
but this I so I've been to a lot of
Yakiniku places I've had a couple of
different vacuo's before
but this is
um
oh
yeah
please if you make it to Japan to Tokyo
and you want some sick Teppanyaki go to
the Hilton in odaiba go to their
Teppanyaki Restaurant you can make
online reservation there they have like
a like a easily accessible for
English-speaking people uh reservation
site
um
price uh there's different courses some
are more expensive some are less and
then they also have a la carte
singular plates
no it's not 500 per packs I mean I think
there's no even the most expensive one
doesn't go up to 500 per person I think
our whole thing
was maybe
100 per person 120 maybe at most
Maybe
yeah maybe 100.
I don't think that's not I don't think
that's not bad
um
please go and eat this so good at the
end they after the after the meat oh
wait I have a picture of
I took a slow motion video you know they
do like this like fire thing
but I'm not going to show the video but
um this is just one of the
shots yeah it looks fancier and cooler
in real life but it's over so quickly
that's what they do before they give you
the meat and then at the end you have a
choice between like Soul Man or garlic
rice or different type of rice and this
and that to finish it off and I was
really like Curious I was watching him
prepare the garlic rice and like he was
like flattening it on the heating plate
the whole time
and the hot plate
and I'm like what the what is he doing
is he trying to make like one of those
things like they do with ice cream they
like make flat layers of ice cream
uh what's going on and then yeah he made
paper out of it and topped it on top of
the garlic rice so out of the garlic
rice he made garlic rice paper which was
actually kind of a nice snack
but at this point I was already pretty
full and I didn't this this is more than
it looked like I didn't want um
to eat that much
but it's a cute idea and he was like
working on flattening this for quite a
while it's turned into the perfect paper
um
yeah crispy nice
uh and then
and then
no Callie Callie told them
oh it was it was her birthday
so
for dessert you get like moved over to a
different table
and we got the same dessert basically
actually this made me laugh a little bit
it was a cute gesture but it's like
let me show you
let me show you uh
this is the dessert yeah uh it's like a
macaron that was I think pistachio and
the hojita
some tea tea dessert
tea cream
and then
a little candle
[Laughter]
funny to me like
uh too funny
um but the decoration is nice and I got
it on a much bigger plate than Cali
like her plate was Tiny I got a bigger
plate and it was decorated
um
smallest cupcake it's not a cupcake but
it's just a whipped cream
well it was funny it was sweet though
and I also give you like a nice cup of
hot tea with dessert Japanese tea really
relaxing
um yeah that was my my
after party the the massage was uh okay
I've had better massages
uh I keep on like always want to say
stronger stronger please because I can't
[\h__\h] feel anything on my shoulders
um but after saying it like once they
increase the pressure I feel bad for
saying more and more and more
is obviously just like weak weak as [\h__\h]
so
yeah I didn't feel like I was always
speaking up this is my problem with
massages when I'm unhappy it's hard to
speak up and say something
uh but at least in Japan
normally like they ask you very often is
this okay
should we should I do it stronger or
weaker is this okay is this okay are you
okay they ask it a lot normally but this
time like during the massage she only
asked it once and I said play stronger
and then didn't increase that much
yeah but I just I don't know I thought
okay I guess I'll just try and relax
um
um but she gave me some advice because
like she noticed she said holy [\h__\h] like
your shoulder a neck
feels crazy and I'm like yeah everybody
tells me that
and she was saying like
I think it comes from here and then she
was like pushing uh on the top of my
neck like uh under my skull
um
and yeah she says it's like all
connected and I'm like yeah yeah and
then we were talking a little bit about
like pillows and I said I tried out a
lot of pillows and this and that and
yeah of course I also work on the on the
PC so you know there's a lot of factors
but I've been having this for many many
years now and at this point there's
chronic pain and I've been going to the
doctors and this and that uh but now
I've been like swimming a lot and trying
to fix it with that
um yeah oh wait I think
[Music]
which means I have to go in like a
minute or two
um okay
um what was I saying
but I can maybe I can stay
[Music]
but you won't really see what's going on
because I don't really want to capture
it I just want to use handheld mode I
was going to chill but I shouldn't
stream so long anyway but anyway okay
speed run so um we were talking about
like pillows and she gave me an advice
she said
um you know when you lie sideways on
your bed the way you should lie is uh
your nose
should be on the same height as your
belly button
and I'm like oh
this sounds like it makes sense yeah
so a big chance your pillow is too high
and I'm like yeah I'm sure it's higher
than that
so she said uh you should take a towel
or several towels and then fold it
and then test check at which height your
nose is on on the same height as your
belly button
and then even just you know I guess what
I'm gonna try to do because that's like
really low I'm just gonna maybe put the
towels into a pillow sheet and leave it
at that
yeah uh
or you get you you measure the height of
those towels then and then get yourself
a pillow that's that high I guess
um
but even my side sleeper memory foam
pillow
is way higher than that and I honestly I
did have a feeling for a while recently
that my pillows are uh giving me a worse
and worse time
and
really making my next situation right
now worse and worse every night that I
sleep and I've been feeling that my my
head is too elevated
um
yeah so maybe you guys can try that out
too I'm gonna try it out I I don't think
yeah a lower pillow would help me for
just the night time it's not gonna fix
all my problems but it should help I
can't use pillows at all
I kill my neck oh wow
[Music]
I tried the full body pillow in the past
but I don't really think this really
helps me in particular it's just like
coffee you know
I do hold
like not a full on body pillow but like
a a pillow I hold it around my chest to
also elevate my arm a little bit my
shoulder therefore but also just because
it's comfortable
but recently I've been sleeping a lot on
my on my belly actually because of my
back pain
I've been sleeping more and more on my
belly
um with my with my head completely to
the side that might be kind of bad I
don't know
but it feels pretty comfortable to fall
asleep in this position and then during
the night I I'm 100 sure that I switch
pretty fast to just sideways
I fall asleep on the tummy and
eventually I wake up and I'm in a
different position so I don't think I
stay very long in this position
[Music]
um
okay I would like to talk more of you
guys but this was supposed to be
actually only a one hour stream
I'm trying to keep myself from streaming
too much because I'm actually still
exhausted from all the traveling and
I'll be doing even more traveling so
that's that
um
yeah on the weekend I'm planning GTA
at least on one day
I don't know if I'm doing it on both
days but I'll try even purple mattresses
no what's that the most uncomfortable
bed I ever slept in but it fixed my back
pain
purple I look it up
but I want to say thank you to kill me
for spending this
uh special day with me
and it was really really nice relaxing I
slept I swam so many laps and up come
that [\h__\h] I told her Kelly this time
you're bringing your swimsuit because
we're gonna swim you know what she does
she didn't [\h__\h] bring it I'm like
Cali
we're spending all day here what are you
gonna do she's like oh it's fine it's
fine I'm like no why did you not bring
your swimsuit she said she doesn't fit
in it the one she has when I'm like huh
you can you can rent them here so rent
one so she rented one because I I
pressured her
yeah and then she was like swimming in a
rented swimsuit so all good hmm
and don't you have to go yeah
I have to give her my friend code again
anyway because remember I deleted all my
friends
let's see is my switch
maybe I'll just stay here and I won't
show you you can watch from Kelly stream
I'm still in Zelda
I kind of need to go to the toilet
though
oh I Will Survive
just half an hour
51 well but uh wait friend code
oh
okay let me write it down
I deleted all my friends
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
Kawaii pomori
who debt
hello it's it's takanashi kiwawa from an
alternate universe
from an alternate universe exactly that
one how do you know her crazy I don't I
saw her in Final Fantasy 16.
pretty crazy it does fit into Final
Fantasy 16 doesn't it right especially
the hair piece right straight up like a
final fantasy like logo or something
like that I didn't start playing it yet
but I I do think visually it fits
yeah honestly perfect yeah but I
actually perfect
yeah that was so cool I'm so dressed up
and you're just in a pajama yeah because
it's night time of course we'll be
sleeping but yeah of course I was
actually just telling the story of our
spa day with pictures on my stream yeah
yeah nice it was fun yeah let me tell
you Kelly we have a problem
I recently deleted all my switch friends
no so I don't think we're friends
anymore let me quickly send you the
codes leave it to me all right I can add
you no problem I've got my sensor bar
still here from the last interesting
stream I did yeah I made sure to save it
as the lowest res jpeg possible okay
here we go add friends you know why I
deleted all my friends
why I was trying to get
um
Uno to work on the switch
why would deleting all your friends help
with that because because for all the
participants which was for participants
we didn't show up for each other as
particip possible participants uh and we
were shown like others in our friends
list but you couldn't choose the other
the ones you actually wanted so we
thought okay if we delete everybody
except us then it surely will show us in
Uno right it didn't no it didn't no it
was all for nothing yeah what a shame I
sent you a friend request by the way
after three years of working in the same
company finally we will be friends
let's go I see that you have over 110
hours in tears of the Kingdom hell yeah
I'm finished though it was so good I
wish I could have spent more time in it
you know it's a really good game it
really was yeah okay how you doing by
the way which hour is this
let's see uh if it's about okay so we're
almost at the 12 hour mark oh that's
still that's still like halfway from oh
yeah
not not quite yet we're almost halfway
from well technically technically though
I streamed an hour before the start
um so I guess it's kind of like wait is
it halfway was it the the Calm before
the storm one yeah well I had that as a
super chat stream the night before and
then I had a membership stream before
the marathon Street are you okay are you
stupid
why would you add one more hour before
the 24 hour stream and make it 25 hours
Pow Wow with my members
this lady oh my god making it even more
difficult for herself
you'll be suffering at 23 hours and
you'll be like I wish I would have done
one less hour and wouldn't have done the
membership
maybe maybe I'll try to pull it together
the spicy noodles will wake me up I'm
excited for spicy yeah oh my God good
luck with that I'm trying to find the
lobby right now should be in in a moment
oh yeah I found you
take your time let's go let's go okay
let's go okay let's party
I think oh I press
unable to connect to the oh wait do I
not have no it should be fine
communication error
blonde but they've been having a couple
of those if it shows me yours then I
should have internet right so yeah let
me try again
otherwise I could try to put it back
into the dock and play via uh the
capture card
come on come on let me in please
Nintendo let us play you've already
scores enough from Mario Party
[Music]
oh I'll try if I can join you
um yeah let me okay okay
we can't win I was I was telling the uh
My Views that that meet we ate at the
Teppanyaki was like now I know it even
more seriously it's my favorite the best
the best vacuum I've ever eaten in my
whole life right yeah every time yeah
that wagyu just never fails no but like
this one specifically out of all the
vacuums was my favorite ever
yeah maybe it's like a personal choice
but it was so freaking juicy and soft
and buttery
it melts in your mouth and all that hell
yeah it's all good oh it seems like
you're in yeah I'm in let's go let's go
we did it European connection
what you want to play you can choose
what have you played so far
I played uh tennis air hockey connect
four dots and boxes and Renegade
quite a few games all right what the
[\h__\h] is a renegade
oh it's a weird one I think I won it by
accident it's like you turn up yeah I
don't think I fully understood it while
playing it okay
um
I want to play Blackjack but yes I feel
like it always [\h__\h] me over with this
game
even better I mean oh well maybe you'll
get lucky this time you know how to play
this right of course I love this game
okay I wonder if I remember I think um I
think the Yakuza times have put it so
deep in my blood I can't forget oh yeah
yeah they've trained you yeah cool
Blackjack time let's go we gotta get 21
and if it's over 21 then we're [\h__\h]
right correct yeah correct okay okay so
Kiara's right there and I'm
right here I'm telling you already the
CPU will win
yeah there will always be a strong CPU
and a CPU that sucks yeah so that's what
is up Kiara is in control
uh let me see Lauren is in control I'll
do 10 I'll do a casual chill 10 for now
uh-huh careful we're careful I see oh oh
you don't see what I have do you know
you do I do oh
they're busted I should let's go wait do
I stand or do I hit uh I'd stand if you
hold on there because hit I get another
card right so exactly yeah
definitely uh let me hit hit me
hit me
and Kiara wins let's [\h__\h] go oh I
should have I should have just cut there
the house busted come on
I really didn't think I was gonna all
right it's just the first round it
doesn't matter as long as we kill the
CPUs yeah exactly as long as the CPUs
suffer we can't let the computers win
one day they'll take over humanity and
that's not good sky that all right here
we go yes
there's a Terminator reference oh you
watched Germany I never watched
germinate even though I'm Austrian yeah
I was about to say what
confusion ah this kind of sucks
they've got a king
the possibility of them busting
[\h__\h] all right hit me blasted let's
[\h__\h] go stand oh
oh you're standing with the CPU hand in
hand TT oh no
no are you kidding me
I'm [\h__\h] with them rigged rigged
rigged rigged rigged House Always Wins
House Always Wins
we should go to a casino together
sometimes I know what would be your
favorite thing to play in the casino
Blackjack Blackjack yeah I think that's
also the only the only card game that I
understand yeah I also don't get poker
so that would be a no For Me 2 30 again
let's get it back risky risk in here
or maybe a little bit I'm gonna stand
for sure yeah you should use some
decision I will risk it for the biscuit
yeah and I'm [\h__\h] busted again
very close though I'll see a I'll Stand
don't gamble guys don't gamble please
don't not great for you
please nobody yeah I think I would also
like to play roulette in the casino
yeah roulette seems kind of fun seems
simple enough for my pee brain you won
you won this one yeah because the dealer
didn't get 21. yeah nice
yeah yeah he's got rules they gotta fall
too um why am I fourth now what the [\h__\h]
happened
I'm all in I need some luck
all in baby 90s Cali
you can go negative in this game yeah
you're crazy wait communication error
my ears left are you kidding me we were
just getting into it the house just took
our money
and just kicked us out here I'll make a
new one I don't know okay something's
wrong today with the internet
let me check okay what internet are you
using switch you better be using the
right internet or I'm gonna be mad it
might be me if it went well for you with
the others
uh did not go well for me with the
others so maybe it is hold on let me
check the network oh it's just Nintendo
you know how it is with Nintendo online
I mean yeah that is true I am indeed
connected to the right
Network all right well I'll just join
your lobby again don't make Blackjack
work we will make it work again choose a
Lobby leave us to you
um
let's do it again come in here come in
here
if you think about it if you think about
it we just erased our debts you know
it never happened
exactly never happened I never lost any
money in the casino what do you mean
what do you mean never are you kidding
me why unable to connect to other
consoles why let's try again I don't
believe that I believe that's a lie let
me try this start hey no start anus in a
start a new start hey let's start Oh I
thought
that's good anus stock yes
okay wait hold on it's one of my
favorite jerks
jerks word play
no it's English
you know uh
uh was it Arrested Development yeah yeah
uh wait was it
have you ever watched Arrested
Development
no I think we maybe once there's this
guy I mean they're all very interesting
people but there's this guy he's getting
himself a car he wants to start a new
start but it doesn't fit on his car
plate license plate in a new start so he
shortens it and makes it into anal
starts uh
so that's the joke and then and then
mermaid releases a song called a new
start right yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
keep on making fun of her with that I'm
so sorry well now I'm gonna remember
that forever every time I hear that song
someone edited the logo too
oh yeah yeah
okay
um let's not go back to the thing
we got some time to only in 15 minutes
we're gonna play Ludo you know how to
play noodle time yeah it's sorry hell
yeah let's go yeah that's our sorry or
trouble or whatever it is you know in
German it's called yeah the game title
is called dude don't be don't be so
angry
oh really in German yeah
yeah it's kind of based very self-aware
I dig it
we like to play it in families
you play this with with uh Mama Tori
yeah no actually actually not much with
Mama oh somebody said uh
uh sorry is a bit different apparently
really
um we'll see so you you start at one
piece you want to get all of your pieces
into your into your holes oh I see the
ones that are in your color your color
yeah gotcha you have to play with CPU ew
yucky
for sure
uh but I think wait how was this like
actually it's been a while I think you
can like
ah once you Pat no once when you land on
someone's field maybe then you kick them
back into the starting position
yeah gotcha something like that yeah
yeah that's it that's it
okay so it's a lock game
yeah
you can choose which pieces you move
Savage just be Savage
okay sounds good I can do that this
would also be a game that I should buy
in real life and then play in handcam
off collapse this is my new thing you
know to hand camera collapse I bring
these kind of like board games ideally
like non-copyrighted ones or like
off-brand ones understandable myself see
a yellow [\h__\h] kicked me off of my
place a yellow one
yellow CPU I know they suck they really
are the worst welcome What if I
hold on can I not move one of these game
doesn't want to please move a piece it's
not letting me move one of these pieces
so I I guess I can't you have to move
that one first
okay
you got it one
that's so loud
[Music]
of course it's just RNG slowly moving
slowly but surely
all right so have you been like eating
any snacks while you're doing these 12
hours yeah I have protein bars energy
packs you know
yeah that's all you'll be eating in 24
hours protein pack car sweat you know
cars sweat I don't just yeah cars sweat
Makari Sweat Nobody sweat oh
wow
it's so yummy um
yeah I like it
I should treat myself though after this
stream is over I need something yum yum
yeah you should what are you thinking of
oh you can roll again if you get six
then you can move one of yours out aha
okay I'm gonna get that blue guy
um yeah I don't know what I want though
maybe like a nice pasta oh a nice
posture he kicked the green one kicked
the yellow one out and this is the first
time road that I wrote One
the first time in a row
oh yeah I am barely really unlucky eh
the shame don't worry I won't try and
hurt you
yes carefully don't roll don't roll the
two
I'll be mad at you if you're old too
no it's four one two three four ah I
bounced off of your head if I hit you
though it's a wound okay oh move away
let's go
finally moving but I still only have one
piece out there
one piece
I get it you know I I like Kiara so I'm
not gonna I'm not gonna jump on her head
you know when I was uh with kawi uh out
the whole day on our spa day like at
least 10 people
when I know this is when I'm around with
you this is funny like every everybody
will talk to you about your phone case
like oh One Piece One Piece
like three different people yeah
at the restaurant too especially at the
restaurant they're like oh one piece and
then like the massage therapist was like
One Piece One Piece like dang a lot of
Japanese people know one piece and the
dessert guy he was like really really
like interested he wanted to talk so
much about one piece of the feeling he
wanted to talk about one piece yeah like
oh did you watch the movie How many
times did you watch the movie where did
you watch the movies
three times
the whole time sitting there no having
no idea about one piece I feel so bad it
was kind of crazy it's always it's the
phone case and you know what that's
happened outside of just us like hanging
out as well
um Everybody happened just when I go
outside if they talk to you so often in
that just one day I cannot imagine how
many times people talk to you about your
phone on the regular day basis
if I go outside a lot oh my God a lot I
think everyone in Japan knows
aren't you getting annoyed about it at
this point no I think it's cute again
it's a good conversation starting yeah
I'd say so unless you don't know
anything about one piece like me then
it's not a good question
it's fine we have plenty of other things
to talk about anyway yes yes so true
I've never noticed something that
creates such a reaction as much as one
piece that's my turn I know right
it's like uncanny I know nothing else
will get so many interested Japanese
people
I mean I don't wonder why because I like
it a lot but it's like a national
treasure for them I guess I know right
somebody in my chat said one time Oda is
The Treasure of Japan
Japan's pride and joy I was like that's
kind of cute who is that
Oda is the author of One Piece okay okay
yeah he's the guy he's the dude that
that wrote One Piece It's Not Over
no oh
garbage
evil evil CPU I was about to say NPC I
need to escape from you please don't
jump on me
don't worry you're safe I won't hurt
you're not drinking energy drinks right
hey yeah I am if you are okay if it's
just today if it's just today
just for today yeah and only when I'm
tired let's go
okay yeah somebody gave me some tips
from their World of Warcraft days they
said here are the things that you need
they're like I played World of Warcraft
once for three days in a row they'd go
on like binges and they're like here's
what you need in order to survive you
need painkillers uh and then like these
other things ChapStick for your eyeballs
the corner of your eyes start to burn
they said
you yeah I'm well hydrated though don't
worry yeah
[Music]
indeed don't use it on your eyeball I'll
think about it
oh think about it damn
I I used to play like MMORPGs overnight
like for the whole night but I I don't
think I really had anything
so crazy like special
like a strategy to survive it's just
like Cali
uh yours is am I I currently only have
one candidate that I can move don't
worry about it I'm just unlucky
it's fun I know you didn't do it on
purpose
sorry
we're cool it's all cool
[Music]
yeah some wizard tips so you liked World
of Warcraft didn't you I used that was
the first MMORPG I ever played and it
was because my family was all getting
into it so we played it as a family and
I was like I don't know maybe I was like
12 or so or 11. so cute yeah I was too
young honestly to play World of Warcraft
ah too young but you did it anyway it
was fun yeah I really liked it and that
kind of sent me down the spiral of
MMORPG addiction I
get out
no yeah these guys are evil what I will
only be able to move the one that's
already in for now
I think so oh my God I feel you can get
another one in there that's rough buddy
wow
that is rough that's just rude
I need a six I pass
pass oh no really yes wow
give me a six you got this one or six
one or six wow
come on what a waste of time we've got
this
cheering for you six six wow okay wow
that's so good what is so good right
this is so good yeah the green is gonna
win no cap
I hate that [\h__\h] greens man oh I got
some
nice I do oh
oh me yay oh cool yeah that's like that
let's freaking Go destroy great Grand
nice you get them I wish I could hit
that yellow okay game is telling me dude
don't be so angry
in German how do you say it in Germany
Mitch actually
this is not like baby speak I think I'm
a baby child oh I got another number six
but I can only move this one right now
because it's biased in a way yeah I
still like on the starting spot oh my
god oh Nick close takanashi when I roll
again
I'm glad that wasn't a one or a four
yeah that that just passing by yeah
let's go oh you're in you're in your
first one
hey let's go
I think if you're like close to your
goal and you like roll something that
like overshoots it like a six for
example then I don't think you can
actually get in I have to do another
round yeah
so that's also kind of
salt which sucks so bad that's the worst
thing I've ever heard
rude what the heck
brutal game but moving on nicely now
let's go
we got five get in there get in again
number two is there someone after me oh
yeah right there's some someone after me
I mean after this yeah
oh good yeah
six I can cut into drawing a bit yeah
nice hell yeah
um I shall move the one that's further
okay
I love it when it's us against the NPCs
yeah
we're rooting for any one but anyone but
the NPC npcc three letter words for non
non-consciousness having beings
easy to confuse okay I know that doesn't
make a lot of sense but they're similar
and they both have yeah wait it's not
NPC it's CPU oh
yeah confusarino
blue
this one please
oh why did you choose that one
because I wanted to get to the front
interesting chores I'm getting closer
skip it without it oh oh scary Hold On
maybe it's fauna the green one might be
fauna secretly oh Fafa playing from
Beyond the I was about to say beyond the
grave but it's not dead it's just
playing from the Beyond I guess
nice
nice pretty close please please do not
kick anyone away oh I can get in in a
safe Zone
oh thank God okay yeah okay okay
I'm not here to back seat you but your
guy is blocking the exit
for your for your last guy yeah so this
is part of your strategy I was just
trying to get uh that one in as fast as
possible
understandable but now wait have a good
day now we're now we're gonna move on
all right we're gonna be Head to Head
Toe to Toe
I think he gonna win that bastard got in
a piece of garbage let's hope they never
really sick they know you will be fine
yeah no maybe potentially maybe maybe
okay let's go
okay
uh
thank you I'm such a nice person
you're such a nice person
it shows your compassion but
LOL no no you're in my way
I am grateful be grief
get her no chat no Universe
you can't I'm so cute rightful I'm going
to buy you a bag of grapes next time ew
grapes grateful I get it little planned
words you did there
so good with Place wow I think English
is your first language
a boy oh sticky
we go
we're making moves did you see my new
outfit animation
yeah I watched it that's the same person
that did that one fan animation it was
really cool yes so sick
so swaggy that was awesome Lord I loved
it's kind of like a weird thing to pick
out that I loved but I loved how they
used like 3D models and made them look
like like 2D that was cool I was like
whoa I mean I know it's 3D but like that
fits so well oh that's cool efficiency
yeah and then I loved the music that was
with it too right yeah actually I was
like first I was thinking of like
voicing it and doing sound effects and
stuff but I also kind of wanted
background music so I was like who to
ask I don't know who to ask but I have
this one one fan who makes like
Orchestra stuff and all that I thought
oh well actually it might be perfect so
yeah you created it according to the
video fittingly
yeah that worked out perfect yeah so I
just gave up on voicing it because I was
like oh this is all really nice enough I
think it turned out fantastic just the
way it is thank you I love it I'm still
thinking we should all get together and
voice the bad myth bed ending things I
want to yeah I want to do it wouldn't
that be so cool it would be really
normal oh you know what that's one thing
we could uh try to do for anniversary
nice idea hmm let's do that I like that
I'll bring it up I'll bring it up with
Mazu as well if it's okay yeah
yeah yeah
that would be fun
spoilers no spoilers green green is
still struggling to get his last Soldier
out how to turntables
the day on stream I had a Miss speaking
moment I have so many of these recently
instead of oh how did
what I said was how the
how the turbo stained
terrible stain it sounds like a
different language
though
[Music]
I was like what did I just say
oh the turbo's pain
some Elite English right there I tell
you what it couldn't even make that up
to me it still sounds like English
I mean yeah actually I get what you mean
a piece of garbage now yellow is not a
Warpath wow take him down oh rude I'll
do my best but you know they're slippery
um slippery give me one damn it no
that's so scary what if they get one
why not
I'm so scared right now look he got the
last one out
oh God this is so scary
oh
geez
guys oh my God no
[Music]
you knock him out it'll be fine it's a
[\h__\h] game
this game is uh anxiety inducing so say
the least I've got
for you
oh we're going to Destroyer get him hit
him get him send them home oh yeah send
them home
hmm can we still turn this around
yeah we can we can turbo we can
turbotain it yeah
I know we can
we can turbulate it
all right let's go
purple 10 train the tech I don't know a
piece of garbage did he kick you back
again yeah the green one did you know
so rigged freaking bastard
disgusting
all of the turbo oh my God
so disgusting out okay okay I will can I
yes send him home can I wait can I yes
yes
let's freaking go
let's go
yes absolutely goated oh man it's not
over yet also the good thing is even if
green is like right in front of his goal
he will have to roll a one for example
or a two or so like the exact number
true oh my God it really be like that
that's crazy hmm it seems like it'll
take a long time yeah it's fine it could
potentially
fine well I guess I'll just pass again
yeah let's just pass again
[Music]
okay now that I'm past the greens goal
I'm less than dangerous I'm gonna catch
up with my last one nice idea
give me six yeah get him oh go get it go
Kelly
sorry oh my God I didn't mean I didn't
mean to throw you back me you throwed me
Freeman oh yeah you have one back in the
home I'm sorry oh oh I'm wait I thought
you sent get out I thought you sent
green back I did what happened what
happened but then the green took you out
wait what I'm so confused how did he
suddenly immediately get a six he got a
six right after you okay yeah right
after yeah [\h__\h] rigged wow disgusting
disgusting CPU awesome cool I can't
believe it wow gross I hate that
the CPUs like nah CPU always wins idiots
[Music]
come on
let's go as long as we got each other
I guess that is true
that is true or else always win yellow
was on my spot but unfortunately I
didn't get a six goddamn
keep it moving keep it moving um
going around the board somebody wins if
we can kick green again then that would
be amazing yellow yellow is dangerous
too
yeah they're both dangerous
gotta get them
keep them going around the board just uh
just a one
oh yeah
let's go
let's move
I believe yeah yeah yo she's a speeding
officer she's speeding I'm here come
here oh
yes yeah now I'm in trouble you know I'm
in trouble never be ahead of the enemy
watch them from behind observe
God that is scary let him smack him
number six
chicken dinner more Calliope
yay to see if you lost I ultimately get
four let me continue playing you stupid
game come on that kind of sucks they
only care about who gets who takes first
so happy
happy days
we got them yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
awesome yeah yeah thanks kiwawa that was
fun indeed I think it's already time for
me to leave right it is but I'll miss
you
I'll be back
hang out again soon okay okay
good luck with the stream don't die try
not to die we'll see though
we'll see
bye bye
all right I'm still streaming
well I only kept this on because uh I
didn't want to abruptly end it so fast
but I should end it
uh why are you still streaming
foreign
well would you have liked me to just say
bye bye and quickly leave huh
it was fun though
yeah
um
so I guess I'll go
oh I guess I'll go I guess or or not
or I'll go it's so sad though because
like if I could stream tomorrow then no
problemo
but
remember that thing you wanted to talk
about well there's many things that I
want to talk about I think
yeah but there's like so so many
tangents and I'll I guess I'll just tell
you afterwards but
oh that thing what I don't think there
was a specific view ah you were joking
okay
did you get the thing I sent you what
are you talking about what you mean on
Twitter or so
oh man
I'm I'm just I just feel bad because
like you know I haven't been streaming
but
um
the thing the good thing is after this
short UK trip
uh things will be relatively back to
normal I do have to attend a little bit
to Nina
because she's uh gonna be around and I'm
gonna show her around but apparently she
knows someone else here so it's not like
I have to be with her all day every day
she said just you know even a little bit
for dinner and so on would be nice so
I'll just try to do it so that for
example I stream during the day and then
I have dinner with her or something else
uh yeah I'll I'll see how I can
um sort it out and
yeah then I'm trying to plan something
somewhere in August but honestly at this
point I don't know if it will be
beginning or end of August also but I
think it won't be in the middle of
August because uh my friend Circle wants
to do a little like a pizza pool party
uh and yeah my friends gave me one date
and they're like you have a please be in
the country on this date I'm like okay
I'll try
yeah
you're in Canada in September I'm not in
Canada in person but yeah for all the
Canadian kfps or maybe people who are
close to the Border I guess uh I'll be
at a Canada uh convention that was
announced
was my
anime Toronto yeah it was my my panel
partner announced I think not was who
was my
laughs
matter
I'm getting confused was it I don't know
yes okay Elena
because I have some
something else with someone else
uh but yeah
okay
yeah
in Canada Oh Canada Oh Canada
[Music]
that is not the national anthem
yeah I wish I could visit Canada at some
point because people are nice apparently
and it's cool and chill
um
but anyway I do need to go to an idol
meeting so
so is now and I'll see you again soon
I'll be around on Twitter a lot probably
and update you about everything so sorry
I I was just back for a little bit but
you know actually
I did everything I could for you guys
because I even streamed yesterday after
I came back out of a really long 13-hour
flight okay yeah schedule two yeah okay
I'll make one
I think I can make one there will be a
lot of days but you know
yeah okay so see you again on the
weekend and in Germany we say Alfie does
thank you for listening and uh yeah
I think the weekend will be exciting goo
wait for me please
please hold the line please hold the
line
foreign
bye bye guys bye bye
and the German Museum
guess that's what that Kiara says
usually
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]