[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
ER I don't have a vampire costume
unfortunately but I decided to be a cat
instead imagine
just just have to imagine thank you
thank you guys
happy Halloween I guess this is my
costume being a cat
is it a costume or is it real
hmm
I'm not sure so much either
thank you guys for the sweet feedback
happy Halloween kitty king is this the
last time we're using this office
hmm I almost feel like bad about leaving
it I've I've grown so fond of it
foreign
thank you to you too you're a very cute
vampire thank you
did you guys listen to the music cover
the song cover that I just put out
before this video did you did you did
you did you did you
hold on yeah
yeah of course you did thank you
well well well well well finally a new
music cover song cover new music in
general it's been a while the last one
was uh Sparks
right
goodbye was goodbye declaration before
that right
not after that
yeah yeah right we need some painting
and since it's Halloween
we're gonna use some Halloween uh bgm
here yeah yeah yeah what about this one
oh my uh this one or
well but for now let's use this
[Music]
Sparks was the last one yeah it's been
it's been a little while
um I'm glad that I was able to put out
something new today Halloween is quite
the busy day there's so much going on
today that was a matter of senpai's
birthday
uh I'm not the only one putting up music
Bales just put on a song cover yesterday
Cali is putting out something today uh
uh and you know there's just a lot going
on a lot of special streams Halloween
streams and we just had Yuma Khan
yeah it's an extreme it was an extremely
busy month but also just busy
busy week busy day
yeah all right
but I feel like there's even more going
on than last year
for some reason
you're always very busy we got the
details from kfp Insiders
I was sorry
I can't people
at uh oh my God we gotta talk a little
bit about that too because the reason
why there was a delay in the song cover
and the stream is because of yumakum
having uh our panel having quite a bit
of a delay so sorry for that guys
um
sorry for having to move this around
[Music]
can we talk about that cause that's that
cosplay
that wasn't tequila cosplay there was a
Kiana and a Cali cosplay
they both look great
you're adorable vampire thank you thank
you thank you
I was there with Cali today uh just
before the stream we had a panel at this
convention it's in Detroit
I always thought it was Detroit but I
figured I I should look up the
pronunciation and then I realized it's
literally not Detroit
good that I didn't say it wrong today
just heard the coverage Grand thank you
hey it's my thinking I thought tattooed
really he also thought it was pronounced
differently
Droid
so uh actually I was like I thought that
there would be no more convention
appearances
uh quite a while ago because we had this
whole tour throughout uh North America
with like this one
um organization that was like yeah the
same throughout all of those events
um
but yeah so I had like I had three
appearances a free Idol
five or six conventions that was
and uh yeah the last one I was a little
bit sad that it was the last one but
um fairly recently we were invited to
another one me and Callie yeah and it
was announced only one week before so I
know that a lot of you guys wanted to go
but couldn't because it was announced so
last minute but I was glad to still see
so many people there anyway
um
yeah big big big audience as always
welcoming us uh to
North American conventions it was really
exciting yeah thank you vampire Kiara
cosplay what on Twitter is it under my
Arts tag
yep
do you see someone cosplaying vampire
Kiana it is a really good look for you
but you mean my
where is it
it really
who
how do I find it
how do I find it oh wait that that's
that's a cute one I so I have a
different uh
cosplay of Halloween on my timeline
right now which is whole life English as
mates I just liked it so you gotta check
it out
so cute
oh my God
wait those are really cute made outfits
oh oh my God that's that's adorable I
love those made outfits
all right so what do you mean maybe if I
check my Arts tag will I find it
thank you thank you I'm glad you liked
the new song cover thank you
I like it a lot too
it's such a fun song
like it has a it has this Tempo this
quick quick Tempo this quick beat some
people were saying they're gonna use it
for like the workout routine or when
they go jogging and I thought that was a
lovely idea because that is a perfect
Tempo to work out to or run run along to
Big recommend I couldn't find the
cosplay in my Arch tag where the hell is
it
where's that vampire cosplaying who said
there was a vampire
maybe they meant fan art instead of
Cosplay
well yeah of course there's a lot of
vampire fan art now
thankfully
yeah it's really energetic Tempo and and
and I had a lot of fun singing it
because it's so fast I I first when I
started learning the song
I was a bit worried about that part that
goes like uh
which one was it
[Music]
I was worried about that part because
it's kind of a wrap it's very very fast
but actually it wasn't even that
difficult you just gotta be gotta be in
the groove gotta feel the vibe gotta
feel the beach
it's not Scatman
yeah and uh I had a lot of fun learning
that song I don't know if you guys know
this but I I tried to
sing it with
a little bit more emotion than usually
there's like especially in the first
there is for example there is this part
where I go like
I tried to sound angry did you notice
that
because urusai is like shut the [\h__\h] up
you know this really
or uh I tried to have some like kind of
a little bit like sweet sounding Parts
like whispery parts
the giggle you like the giggle I saw you
going crazy over the giggle
and I like the pineapple the first
chorus that goes like
[Music]
that is like so so sweet so in that part
I tried to sing a little bit more calm
and and kind-heartedly
hmm
yeah I would be glad if you would listen
to it over and over and over again and
then notice these parts
stream vampire yeah
I I don't I don't know but
this this song vampire just like goodbye
singing it has this something about it
that makes you want to repeat it again
and again don't you agree
I think it's the tempo and the way it
ends and starts so abruptly
I think
I think that's it like it makes you want
to hear more it feels so fast it feels
like it ended way too fast
and it makes you want to listen to it
more and more and more yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
it's such a good song to Loop
[Music]
yeah with such a Bob thank you
and the playfulness yeah
it's endlessly loopable it really is I
think if it's it connects pretty well
um please play it on repeat
that's what you might feel like it it
ended already yeah I want to hear more
what the hell
already doing that should I mute my bgm
so you guys can listen to Vampire in the
background
[Music]
now I want to talk a little bit about
vampire and then talk a little bit about
yomicon which I already did I already
started talking about it and then we're
gonna
um I guess talk a little bit about
Halloween night I got some uh Pocky with
me to snack on them and now we're gonna
Read Super chats because I gotta catch
up and but yeah it's not gonna be like
an uh only chatting stream I this stream
is definitely also to catch up on Super
Chat so sorry about that
[Music]
um yeah I'm sorry about canceling
nightmare little nightmares yesterday
we will play it next week
yeah so please wait for that I'm I'm
definitely not completely ditching it
you guys said that you were looking
forward to it and that it was such a
cute game such a good game so I wanna
definitely still play it unfortunately
it's gonna be after Halloween but still
um
foreign
[Music]
I got some time for myself yesterday and
and that was really really nice I gotta
say
finally finally
Halloween ends when you say so well for
for the people on on the on the left
side of the club
on the west side of the globe
yeah get gets Halloween a little bit
longer than than I do I mean I guess
it's still the same length but
it ends early enough for me than it does
for you guys
but today we have later we have uh the
big big big Holland collaboration
so you all have to watch it it's really
exciting there's gonna be
a really big big big exciting thing
oh
oh thank you Nightingale
absolute pitch when it comes to hearing
but unfortunately my voice can't keep up
[Music]
you hear it perfectly but you can't sing
it perfectly that's interesting I didn't
think I heard of that before that that
that's a thing but I didn't know that
like
it could go one way and not the other
way
yeah it hurts your ears
couldn't have fun singing like the other
kids but singers like you helped me a
lot so thank you really really
thank you you're welcome yes
I hope with your absolute pitch I hope
my uh singing didn't bother you
um
actually let me give you one fact about
uh
the new song cover vampire
and I changed the key
I made the key a little bit lower which
doesn't mean that I wouldn't have been
able to sing the original key I totally
was able to sing the original key
uh which was much much higher but I
decided to go for the lower team because
I felt like
it's
it's a little bit more comfortable to
listen to as well as more comfortable to
sing but I I don't know it felt it felt
more
um
it felt like it it it uh
shows off my voice more than the
original key
like the original key in my opinion
sounds really good for like Vocaloid
singers like the actual Vocaloids but
for a human slash Phoenix
and it can sound kind of like forced or
it's just too hot it's just a little bit
unnatural so I decided to go for a
lowercase even though the original one
was good too
hmm
but I wanted there to be a bit more of a
feeling to it and I thought that could
be accomplished by lowering the overall
key it shows your range much better
thank you I I agree though
[Music]
knock on him
Harmony levels how many hump how many
Harmony levels I took like
two two different Harmony needs I think
I think is that what you're asking
I took harmonies I think they sound
really good in this song uh they're they
are very very uh
obvious I think yeah did you like the
harmonies I like the harmonies
especially the part where he goes
[Music]
I love that part oh it's beautiful gives
you like one moment to breathe
that's a good song really like it
taking it down the level lets you add
more things to it like emotions and
stuff yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
for example the the high parts in this
song like thank you
that would have been like
[Laughter]
yeah I think it's better this way
foreign
[Music]
that's pretty high isn't it
it's an original
it's possible but it's like
know why why why why why go for this if
you can go lower
[Laughter]
my screen just
isn't it amazing people can make glasses
break with their singing is that really
true or is it always fake it's it's true
isn't it I've seen I've seen it before
but maybe it's fake
I open it the Chipmunks
[Music]
hahaha
let's go higher Casper original Casper
becoming a vampire
Casper you should be happy with who you
are I like you the way you are Casper
there he goes he's gone he's happy I
guess
um
I have like
um my next song covers I think are all
gonna be or all I mean the next two song
covers are gonna be um uh collaborations
so
uh I felt like doing something solo
before that and I hope you all enjoyed
the choice of vampire the next one is
gonna be in like November end of that I
wonder the art for the next one is
basically done the art
and yeah
it actually shouldn't even take this
long because I we have quite the Open
schedule for that one I didn't really
set a deadline or anything because I
just wanted to take it easy for this
upcoming song cover yeah the next one is
with Ina I invited her to a fun fun song
cover
[Music]
um and this one the video is gonna be
quite a bit more intricate than the
vampire one this one is great too that
it has a all these like how do you call
it uh the the leather how do you call it
Leisure there's a word for this letter
letter graphing thingy
uh which I think looks really cool too
but overall I mean it's obviously a
simple type of video where the focus is
just on the lettering the typography
um but you're gonna fix no no no no no
that's not an Eva no I don't I don't
mean typographic either but you you know
what I mean though the the moving around
of the lyrics
there was a proper word for that anyway
it doesn't matter so the next one is
Taco toady
is gonna be very animated
but it's not gonna be made by you now I
know when you think of Kiana animated
music videos you think of Yuna but nope
nope nope it's not gonna be you know
hey
I am so excited for the next one yeah I
have high high high hopes for it
yeah I think you guys are gonna freaking
love the [\h__\h] out of it out of the video
and out of the song it's gonna be
freaking iconic but until then
you better
continuously stream vampire now
um
[Music]
I think I have a good feeling about it
being released by the end of November
because the art is done
just need to
video which could be done pretty quickly
and me and Ina need to record our vocals
sometime soon yeah I'm excited I gotta
practice the song digital girl I don't
know
[Music]
mm-hmm
stream vampire then stream spot so you
gotta make a playlist Maybe I'll make a
playlist for you guys again
with the songs that I want you guys to
stream
well so I hope you guys also enjoyed the
video I think the art is like so cute I
was thinking about who to
um gets to draw the art originally I
wanted to go with someone else like a
certain someone who was gonna like um
not only do the art but also the video
like the whole package you know but that
didn't work out time wise so
um I I was thinking like hmm
cool which artist that I love very very
very very much
whose style would fit this particular
song
who do I want to get this time
and then I was like I've always I've
always wanted to ask jio Madison for her
art contribution in my in my music video
or whatever
um
this
[Music]
I didn't so adorable I love her art
salads it's like so so soft and
um feminine very feminine
is
foreign
sexy
guys
I wanted to ask her for art for quite
some time and that was the right moment
um
and she threw something additionally for
me too did you guys see I retweeted it
it's a surprise look oh my God it's big
looks like
isn't that adorable
so pretty
she understands like the
the girl's taste
um like I like that hairstyle I I do
that quite often that hairstyle
and and one detail I love about this is
the the crack in the in the candy I am
eating amen
Amelia
I I have I have a candy
cute yummy candy that looks so good that
looks so realistic
oh still going now
um
[Music]
cute Bubba the boobs look so soft and
shiny
what
there's been a lot of vampire Kiana fan
art already and it's been so nice to
look at thank you guys please draw more
students
[Music]
good stuff really good stuff
that was a really really nice present
thank you for drawing that Edition
foreign hmm boing boing very good boy
you might have seen a certain art from
her from me
and where like I got some big Band-Aids
on my my booba oh I didn't retweet that
did I I wanted to I really wanted to I
I'm glad that most of you guys saw it
anyway
indeed indeed
[Music]
the way she draws skin it just looks so
like marshmallowy ah
no wait it's both at the same time
[Music]
those two always come together
thank you bye ski
what's your name
Matsuri bra
for some reason I recently like to do
this
I don't know why
did I where did I even pick it up pick
it up
[Music]
with anything else I wanted to say about
Empire
oh I just wanted to say also that I love
Deco Nina what's your name is
like it's like I started listening to
tickle Nina's songs like uh 10 over 10
years ago
um they have always been
I think I could say
one of my top two
favorite Vocaloid
producers
um
[Music]
it's difficult to say I love Michi so
much
definitely my top five but like I could
it would be so difficult to place them
on an actual
uh
yeah it would be very difficult
foreign
[Music]
no just kidding actually really not that
much but
um
[Music]
songs have a emotional
connection actually
like I have a I have very special
memories with
um one one specific song
that uh also sang before in my streams
as well
yeah I love the economy now
foreign
[Music]
I was thinking about like covering it
one day but like currently I've got my
plans already built up like first of all
the collab next one that's gonna be with
uh Ina and then after that one with Amir
so for now it's like I'm busy and
somewhere in between we want a new
original song coming out as well right
we want that don't we want that when do
we want it yes now
hahaha yeah my play is pretty full but
that doesn't mean that I might not want
to sing it in a karaoke stream
s
[Music]
um
gotta stay busy
yeah
um
I I know I had some some motivational
problems regarding making a new original
song but there's like one genre that has
been
uh very interesting to me that that I I
kind of want to give a try I wanted to
see how
my voice would work with a specific
genre and how you guys would like it how
you guys would pick it up it's very very
different from my usual
poppy songs so it's not gonna be death
now
maybe one day one day we could have like
something in the style of baby metal
maybe one day but that's not really what
I'm going for right now
foreign
[Music]
gotta go take some yodel lessons
yo yo the lessons
why so specifically samitoring yodeling
[Music]
good at yodeling I'm sure she could do
it
she has a great voice
[Music]
you must learn to yodel
don't swim before oh good enough
yodeling what
I gotta tell her about
um
or is it calling in
so stupid
Australian traditional dance when you
slap your thighs
[Music]
we gotta Singh Heidi opening I can do
that
that's that's my name is
[Laughter]
let's have do you guys know it why are
so many people knowing what I'm talking
about
dance cover of that dance now
it's crazy yeah yeah
what are you guys doing for what stupid
question I should never mind I was going
to ask you guys what you're doing for
Halloween but I think it's pretty
obvious that you're you're that days
your day is booked out with that uh
whole life isn't it hey otherwise I
would have you know I would have to ask
you politely to leave right now because
what the hell
kidding stay and what's more her life
I mean yeah you're here so
graclet oh oh yeah babe
Halloween is
[Music]
what you're using Firefox
hahaha
no don't leave there's no hello in my
country no Halloween in my country what
do you mean is it banned
we know Halloween in my country I guess
there's like countries where it's not so
big with the I'm sure there's still like
a little bit of a Halloween mood going
on now
[Music]
just to laugh five bucks five bucks was
my go-to browser for the longest time
so no hate against Firefox I was just
extra surprised because nowadays no one
uses Firefox anymore
which country
not in Whiskey Row
purple skin
[Music]
I asked you guys two questions at the
same time now it's mixing up
a lot of Firefox fans don't nice
Firefox I'm something of a Firefox
myself you know
I love this song too much I love it so
much
okay guys let's talk a bit about yomakon
Yoma come literally just having unicorn
is the convention in North America in
Detroit
let me see I want to put up a
image
wait a minute or is it
where do I have the image
shouldn't this be sorted by date
oh it is
what did I save that image
[Music]
let me go grab it
there it is
[Music]
so this is basically how it worked how
it looked like uh it was a huge
panel room because
yeah yeah so me and Kelly were on one
side
and this is they saw us on the big
screen like that
at least we were looking at you guys
like this and there was a microphone in
the middle kind of reminded me of like a
town hall meeting you know what I mean
where where they come up like uh so I'm
quite unhappy with the road on the 5th
Street Avenue yeah there's a lot of
really loud drivers there every night at
3 AM and just absolutely obnoxious
can you do something about that lastly
nope
[Music]
[Laughter]
so but I liked this setup I don't know
it was nice because in the other
conventions they had them come up to the
stage and I think that also made them
kind of nervous coming up to the stage
but I like the setup and and and I saw
some people in Cosplay and I saw some
people with the Halloween t-shirts I saw
I saw I saw people in self-made canopy
uniforms
working at KFC obviously
um I would like to uh expose you guys
but I'm gonna be kind and not exposing
[Music]
[\h__\h] thank you thank you for coming and
representing KFC actually the the
organizers that like the hosts where
obviously quite the whole life Watchers
before the panel we were like chit
chatting and there we were talking about
like they they brought it up like my
Outlast stream and and yeah it was fun
like it feels good to be at an event
where
um the hosts and and the organizers they
know who they invited rather than just
inviting anything that's popular and not
really knowing their self not knowing
what that really is about
um
so yeah it felt good to like know that
they they know who we are
um
so thank you so much you're Michael for
inviting us and doing your research I
guess it's not really doing research
it's like they they were just actual
live Watchers whole life English
enjoyers KF feeds exactly
um
uh it felt it felt very very
hmm nice and I felt welcomed very
welcome they were so kind
funny hmm
one of us won the last one of us did you
see the guy that cosplayed as you of
course I did
actually
um
I know in which row he was I know where
he was sitting I know I know it's I
think it's not
visible on this picture though and I I
wouldn't point it out either because
that's kind of doxing
but but uh you see you see you see here
like right below me there's someone
wearing the whole of my t-shirt
my whole beef t-shirt
yeah he went up there and he was like oh
did you know that this uh t-shirt is
designed by a certain takanashikiana
good advertisement yes yes a certain
whole life English
has designed this t-shirt
it was our first merchandise ever
yeah I want that shirt so bad it's yeah
it's not on sale anymore that was out
for our
debut anniversion
wait was it a Christmas thing or was it
a debut anniversary thing
which actually wait wait wait what was
it
Christmas it was Christmas yeah that was
not no this was not a six month
anniversary thing this was an earlier
thing Christmas
I have nowhere to wear it sadly you can
wear it at conventions and you can wear
it at home and you can wear it outside
anytime you want but honestly I mean I
understand if you if you feel like you
can't wear it outside okay
um
however
[Music]
you still have to wear it sometimes
we're into weddings
foreign
[Music]
apparently self-made by
um
[Music]
the person who also made a whole alive
history panel there was apparently a
whole lot of history panel on Friday of
the convention because this was a Friday
Saturday Sunday convention I think
and there was a whole lot of history
panel I knew about that today
I found out about that today
we were not involved in that whole life
history pen but I would like to um see
that
would have been cool like I wanna I
wanna hear what our history is I want to
hear what it is from their point of view
[Music]
apparently it was like three hours long
because they were kind of like
they were able to have like kind of open
ends I guess they were the last ones in
the room
uh on that day I think it was the last
panel and that's why they could go on
and on and on a free hour panel yeah
about home life history so I wanna know
what they were talking about for three
hours what did they say about Holo yen
hmm
I am I am very very curious
I know
foreign
[Music]
Minecraft about at least one hour and
you could probably analyze it for even
longer we've seen it we've seen it been
done before
maybe they talked about that
in Minecraft my Minecraft hole for three
hours
oh yeah I wanted to snack a little bit
so
um wait what do I have to say about you
we actually did something special today
for this panel
um all the other North American panels
that we did there were like only q and
A's
it was either like uh with one person or
with two people and I think there was
also three people who panels as well
I think and it was literally just asking
questions and answering questions but
this time we both me and Callie
um performed one of our songs each
yeah I perform Sparks
and I was really excited there was this
one moment I took a screenshot uh uh in
Zoom it was difficult because it was a
little bit a very mosaic
wait can I wait where is it damn it uh
oh do I have it do I have it
[Music]
been great
I mean my
my uh manager's son I think sent it
no that's probably the best
I can get
one second
[Music]
oh
foreign
this
probably won't really
do much for you guys but
there we go and there it is
see
huh
this was when I was like eh you know
there's this part where where where I'm
not singing in Sparks and it goes like
it's like a dance break and I was like
clap your hands Detroit clamp your hands
to try and they were all clapping and
then I was like I don't see your hands
put your hands up Detroit and then
everyone put not everyone I mean this
was a moment where
um right after I said it a few moments
after I said it
and they were putting their hands up and
it made me very happy
they were actually
yeah so you still see a few people with
their hands up clapping they were they
were all properly clapping though yeah
yeah good participation very very good
[Music]
um
thank you thank you good audience
oh light sticks would have been good
here yeah but I don't think they
expected
um a musical performance
because
for all the other ones we did on Q a
only
yeah you didn't expect it did you guys
the ones that were you're not going
where are the Unicorn go aways
um
I mean
the human congoans might be enjoying the
Unicorn right now because our panel
was that like
um
uh like between half past 12.
and
how fast
uh two
p.m or something like that
didn't expect it at all right
[Music]
so maybe they're still enjoying the
convention or they already went home oh
or are watching my stream at the
convention
um
hey I'm right here
your intro video did say you did a
performance did I say that
oh
so you didn't expect oh
oh I did oh [\h__\h] I spoiled it
oh
oopsie
[Music]
no no no
wait I actually wait a second let me see
one thing I did
um
I would have to ask a manager stand for
permission for this one I think but I
did uh record something
um before the panel
let me check it right now I don't think
you guys will
you shouldn't be hearing this
I sure
okay nevermind I'll send you as soon as
you send later and be like uh can I
please show this to my viewers it was
just me and Cali [\h__\h] around before
the panel I recorded it uh secretly
little Snippets I'll ask if I can show
you guys
we were vibing
they were like testing out the audio and
stuff and when we were just vibing and
vibing and and uh enjoying ourselves
me and Callie we're having fun this was
really fun
we were both in a funny mood on on this
day
secret secret
I became as clipper
ah so apparently this is the last
convention for me for this year unless
something comes up again uh kind of like
last minute but
a-f-a-i-k
this is the last one and I had a lot of
fun this was a good way to end the whole
tour the convention year for me I think
it was a good way to do it I hope
there's gonna be a lot more conventions
next year and hopefully also many where
we can be like in person
also um there's still one coming up
where our council is going to be I don't
know if you guys know about it but the
in New York City
what's it called anime
YC and YC is that what it was called
anime NYC yeah yeah
the big one isn't that one which I've
heard a lot about it
I think that one is a insanely huge one
um so council is going to be there all
five of them apparently wow
um please please support them if you're
like in the area please go to anime NYC
and support them
[Music]
I would love to be there too but I think
I think yomakon was a great finish to it
and if you guys want us to be at a
convention uh around your area next year
feel free to let your organizers know
like um you should let them know early
because that way they can plan better
and maybe even invite us to come like in
in person kind of
which is what we did for dokomi this
year in Germany and that one was really
really really cool for me it's it's um
this whole uh appearances in North
America were all not in person and and
those were great too it was comfortable
being able to do it from home and all
that otherwise we wouldn't have been
possible to do like a whole uh we
wouldn't have been able to do a whole
tour over North America if we were
actually like flying like that would
have been so stressful and we wouldn't
really have been able to stream that
much in between so this way is
definitely cool because it's so
comfortable and we can squeeze them in
everywhere but
um I Do Cherish the special moments from
tokomi where I saw you guys and like
kind of
even more closer we had a meet and greet
one by one we were able to have a
conversation
and and I don't know it's just it's just
a really nice to be there in that actual
city gives you a little a feeling of
being there properly like I don't know
anything about those cities that we were
paired in for North America I don't know
those places unfortunately and I would
have loved to go to all those places one
day and become a tourist and hang out
there and then in the panel be like yeah
yeah so yesterday I ate those that Curry
worst and it was really really yummy you
know stuff like that makes the audience
happy too I think
because it's for most people it's like
their Hometown or their home area
with our home country even
I ate those food yeah I want to be like
they asked me what about a Kiara
Chihuahua Kiara Fields what about de la
Saga what about the curry horse and I'll
be like I ate those food
yeah this one was virtual I mean we're
virtual YouTubers so this is I guess our
way to be in conventions but I'm looking
for the forward to the future as well
where who knows maybe we can have like
like proper concerts at conventions on
like a see-through screen like like you
know the Hatsune Miku concerts
yeah 3D closets would be so cool
so let's look forward to a bright bright
future with many many conventions next
year I hope we're gonna be
um even more
how to say International
yeah I wanna go to Sea conventions I
want to go to Europe conventions I want
to go to n a conventions I wanna be
everywhere yeah
everywhere so please let your organizers
know that you want whole live English
at your convention
because it works it works that's
okay it works actually especially now
you know like if you're asking for
something like whole alive they know
they know they have proof now that we
are popular and we bring in those crowds
I mean look at that screenshot look at
that screenshot
yeah so it's way easier to ask for us I
think than to ask for some I don't know
some uh kind of unknown person
yeah believe in her life
I'm sure they recognize that whole life
is a good good thing
a good idea to invite us worldwide whole
life goes worldwide yeah yeah yeah I
need to eat more snacks I need to eat my
poke
[Music]
whole life brings down the voice of the
yard and they're like I gotta fall into
the rabbit hole mm-hmm
come to Brazil come to
come to Brazil they say
um I think
um
personally one convention
that I would like to go to
next year
um
is Japan Expo in France
I think we don't have that much of an
audience in France yet but
Japan Expo is kind of like
the um the big biggest convention in
Europe
um oh look at yeah Luca isn't local
happening right now
that's in Italy ah I always want to go
to freaking look at I always wanted to
go look guys
um after a comic Market I think the
second biggest convention worldwide
[Music]
which makes no sense because I said
Japan exposed the biggest convention in
Europe wouldn't that be local then um I
don't know but definitely Japan experts
up there and Japan but Japan Expo is a
bit more about like Japan culture
generally like very very generally there
is definitely that anime stuff and all
that but Japanese was very generalized
um it has everything
it has everything that is even uh in the
littlest bit related to Japan while Luca
is just freaking special because it has
that Italian Spirit Italian conventions
they start in the late afternoon and go
through the whole night and look at I
don't know if you guys know Luca but um
it's like not in like one convention
hall it's in a whole city
it's spread out through a whole city
it's so cool I've never been there but
like I have friends who who've been
there many times and um I've seen like
many many
um like photos and videos of that
yeah the Italian conventions are so
clear Remini Remini I want to go to Luca
and Remini
[Music]
foreign
again I would love to go but
um I also understand if they don't want
like you know too much repetitive uh
guests it makes sense like from the
point of view of a convention I if I
were a conventional organizer I would
probably not invite the same guests over
and over and over and over again
but I love don't call me I just love
dokomi I just freaking love dokomi
[Music]
oh a big one in Barcelona
I feel like I've heard about that one
hmm
yeah well well there's so many
conventions uh also wasn't there like a
big one which one was that one called
the big one in in uh in London
I want to go to that one too
[Music]
MCM ah that was the name you're young
MCM I think that would be great we gotta
get some more well UK fans
into whole life I always say that uh you
guys are kind of like hiding I need to
always call out for you guys to come out
of your hidey holes where are you at
one week
and what the hell I'm right here
I'm here
thank you thank you oh there you are oh
thank you happy Halloween
anime North I've heard a lot about anime
love yeah
I've generally like heard so much about
so many like North American conventions
and always really wanted to check out
what it is like there I've seen some
really freaking dope
um cmvs
from those big big Anime conventions in
in America yeah I always felt like
that's that's one thing that I want to
see one day
go down
yeah yeah
look what Comics was this weekend I know
I know I know I know I talked about it
with my friends I was like
I kind of want to go to Luca but I'm
busy
I actually
uh several years ago
I was being spontaneous
and I booked an Airbnb and a flight to
Luca
foreign
actually my friends were my my
Australian friends they also wanted to
go but they um they stayed in in
Australia
but I had some friends in Italy who were
gonna go to Luca as well so I was like
okay I'll be fine
uh so I was really looking forward to it
and the Airbnb was already paid the flat
was already already paid nothing was
refundable and
[Music]
I just kind of I don't know why I had
this it was at a time where I had this
issue that I would plan out things but
then
like one day before even though I was
looking so forward to it one day before
I would be like I don't want to go after
all I'm not going I don't know why I I
was always like getting cold feet for
some reason kind of like
me just not wanting to get out of bed so
one day before look up
I decided not to go
and I couldn't get that was at the time
where I was broke as [\h__\h] so it was such
a [\h__\h] waste it was such a waste but
I just I felt like I couldn't go I don't
know it was stressing me out too but you
know I just I couldn't go so yeah my my
Airbnb room was empty couldn't get the
money back flight was also
non-refundable
so that was the one time I had the
chance to go to Lookout and I just threw
it away
I wanna go someday
yeah
well I hope Luca was fun this year for
everyone who went there as well as you
walk on
you needed to push I definitely needed a
push I probably would have went through
with it if a friend would have gone with
me because that kind of like pressures
you to going for real right so
[Music]
um
a flightless bird yeah
yeah
yeah I had that experience so often like
even with like conventions in my own
City
I was planning to go I told all my
friends I'm going and then in the
morning in the literal morning of that
convention I would be like
oh sorry guys I'm I'm not feeling it I'm
staying at home and I would always
regret that I would look at those I
would look at those photos from my
friends and join themselves at the
conventions afterwards and I would be
like oh they had fun didn't they why did
I not go I didn't even have a particular
reason of not going
I had that for a whole year
but nowadays nowadays it's better
I mean
not really bad because there weren't any
conventions for a long time
to go to anyway
um but like in a in in a sense of
canceling things last minute just
because I don't feel like it uh that is
not so much a thing anymore
um
yeah
yeah well I'm in a better place when it
comes to that
did you at least go to enjoy Italy no
see I could have done that too right
because I felt stressed out about the
convention I could have at least just
made use of the ticket and go to Italy
and just chill in Italy but no
no I didn't go at all
unfortunately
anyway anyway so guys uh how long has
this been going one hour okay I should
start reading super chats probably are
you guys streaming vampire in the
background
huh
[Music]
hey do you guys hear them the haze in
the background
[Music]
thank you
la la
[Music]
it has kind of a sexy undertone what the
heck
or the whole song
have you guys looked at the English
translation
it sounds like such a cute
fun song
you're at the cosplay okay okay well I
will look
but um the lyrics are uh
see ya bye guys
I feel like when translated to English
it's even more yeah than it is in
Japanese
ah
well you probably won't get lyrics like
that from me in an original song so
enjoy it in Vampire
[Music]
okay let me see let me see let me pick
up those super chats we have to read
them uh from what was the what was the
last stream that I did not read the
super chats from
oh so let me see that let me check my
you added me when
that's it when did you add to me
Now
update yourself Twitter
where's that cosplay where's
speedy
that's the the mirror selfie right I
want to see you
I hope I hope she takes some proper
photos I want to see that
retweeted I actually the only thing I
see right now
is
actually not the
I think not the person who added added
it at me it's it's weird it's like a
someone tweeted at me just a screenshot
of their Twitter timeline with that
tweet so I can't retweet it because it's
just a it's not from the actual person
just a screenshot of the Twitter
timeline
[Music]
don't go well
I like this okay but but you gotta go to
the original I guess
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay let me
introduce myself let me read the super
chats thank you for all the super Chats
on on on this stream as well I suppose
they're like you know to say uh thank
you for the song cover and I appreciate
that thank you because the vampire
um these song covers cannot be monetized
most of the time
so I appreciate the support very much
thank you
that makes it easier to put some
funds into these song covers thank you
thank you very much it's a big big help
um
[Music]
did I read the pumpkin pirate pumpkin
parvins pumpkin carving Super Chat I
don't think I did
just F add you in a cruel toy tweet of
the original okay
thank you
thank you okay now you guys can go to my
likes
pumpkin
we haven't read Minecraft Eva okie dokie
no problem
let's start with Minecraft then I guess
because that was before
the pumpkin carving I threw out the
pumpkin today by the way
it was so
smelly
um already on the second day
the pumpkin smelled like
pee pee
no not PPP
I want to say it in a cute way uh kind
of messed it up it did you guys realize
that pumpkins smell like that
when you just open them up like that
they didn't smell like that when I was
carving it but on the second day it
smelled like
um
pee
yeah
not not very good uh
and there yeah it was it was starting to
um
create some some some Shimmer
hahaha
that's gone now it's to be gone
[Music]
yeah the
molding has started
a life of its own
no thankfully not
did I read the Alice super chats at
least
I think I did
oh
yeah
you got the favorite pizza topping thank
you yeah
I knew you guys would be confused about
me saying tuna at the same time every
time I say it on stream you guys are
like what tuna I said pineapple and tuna
but at least for pineapple there were
some people clapping for tuna it was
like crickets I was like
what they were looking at me it was like
question marks above their head
it's really freaking good but yeah
apparently it's not a thing in in the US
to have
Tuna on your pizza
hmm
he's on all
right
tuna and corn in the UK
good corn makes it even better oh maybe
today I eat tuna corn Pizza I already
ate tuna pizza two days ago
actually I don't know if I even have
time to grab some proper food
let's see let's see how long these super
chats take me so we're gonna read these
these ones here elytra hunting
that was a fun and extremely successful
stream
and I don't know what is it with my luck
why why am I so lucky when it comes to
finding Elijah's and finding n cities
and I was actually really sure that that
one was broken because you couldn't see
the the dragon head for the longest time
I got so close and you couldn't still
you still couldn't see it but it was
there actually why am I so lucky
why foreign
it's good that she went with me Callie
um
living my best life with my lucky
Phoenix lock
you're Trident as well
um
[Music]
now the Kelly did so well
in that stream
getting her
um I know she was so she was so
controlled she was
really gaming she was gaming
she didn't die yeah my mom was also so
worried that she would die my mom
you rubbed black from everyone else
[Music]
yeah it wasn't on purpose
okay let's read these superchatos please
let me know if I missed the red door and
Pinky you guys have been doing that
recently thank you for keeping track
it's kind of weird but it's also helpful
[Laughter]
trick or treat Jenna that's funny
that's funny all right funny
videos
[Music]
Mickey milky Mouse thank you
my Mickey impression in the ttrpg Stream
was fire oh thank you
I don't really I don't know I wouldn't
say it was fire I never really tried to
practice it but I guess Mickey Mouse is
pretty easy to impersonate if you
practice a little bit
ha ha hahahaha
I would have to listen to the original
again
oh no that's not it no
how do I speak and I can only say haha I
don't know how to speak like him the
whole time like you know it was way
better at that you know has like a good
base voice for Mickey Mouse
it's like a mix of Mickey and Goofy
milky Mouse
that happened because of uh isn't that
it has a unique name because she was
speaking like Mickey Mouse while we were
milking cows no no that was actually
even before when she was calling me and
I said I needed milk but she spoke in
the Mickey Mouse voice yeah yeah yeah
yeah she got a new nickname
the milk trade
we got some good voice acting out of
Inna for that
kill Joey Doncaster
oh so many uh
about the fighting ring
the way built her fighting ring holy
[\h__\h] uh now I want to build a proper one
too
that one is pretty well made did you
guys see Portugal's advice fighting ring
she built one after she uh
fighted me fought me in the fighting
ring on the answer right next to my
house
the one that existed since a long time
ago
[Music]
really likes building stuff doesn't she
foreign
[Music]
she's a great Builder and she's so
helpful
foreign
not able to watch my ship on time oh no
hope you have fun with calientation I
will watch the vld back glory to Taco
morning
thank you
I hope you enjoyed the video D it's been
a while already so I'm just gonna assume
that you already watched it
so this was the first time that takamori
had a collab uh since a long time and
since that little talk that we had that
people were making too much drama about
but I don't know about you guys but
uh me and Cali I think both of us feel
way better about it now and also today
during the panel
um I think a lot has improved and and
and we just have more fun together so
um
it's it's it's so much better so there
was no need for the drama I told you
guys
LG for drama
yeah big fuss over nothing
um
foreign
[Music]
time to edit the contracts for kfb
employees why
why am I lying what do we need in there
let me cry for nothing people
underestimate your pro Minecraft skills
all I mean I don't like I've kind of
gotten a good reputation in terms of
Minecraft I think people have even like
non-kfp people have picked up that I'm
pretty good and like
um for example because I
I signed up to be the elytra Elijah
flyer for the sports festival
uh I was like testing it out yesterday
yeah yesterday evening
um if you watched bottomless Empire
stream you might have seen me there
because I was I
don't think I was I was practicing uh
because I saw a lot of my stream and she
was around the area of the of the sports
festival and I was like oh that's what
it is I wonder if I can try it out like
I want to test it out because I signed
up but I actually don't really know if
it's really that easy if I can really do
it so I tested it out and I was actually
it was not that difficult I had lots of
myself I tried to shoot me down while I
was flying but ah I do have to consider
though I was using the wrong Rockets I
think I was using
um strength two rockets and for the
actual sports festival it's gonna be
strength one Rockets I think which I
normally use so I'm used to those as
well just gotta try a practice again
with the right rockets and and also
um
so uh the flyer is only allowed to use
free Rockets
for flying through do you guys even know
what I'm talking about there's this like
high tower that you as the electric
flyer you jump down from with your
elytra and then you fly through like uh
a couple of big Hoops you should be
flying for at least
um
there's like
I think there's fires hoops and you
should fly at least through
um two of them or is freedom minimum
there's a white hoop there's a red hoop
there's a green hoop and then there's
two different Hoops that are like really
really optional
um yeah it kind of changed the whole
setup changed a little bit from last
time I think I think it improved because
it seems like
um now
uh like there's a wall on the side of
um where the people try to shoot me with
arrows which will prevent them the one
word that I had which will prevent them
from shooting me down like one half
second before I land
you know what I mean because in last
year menu Senpai shot akiroz a senpai in
the very moment when she was Landing
which is obviously easier to shoot
because uh you you get slower as you try
to land properly right so that's the
most dangerous area but this time they
added a glass wall so they can only
shoot me when I'm still pretty high up
in the air
and when I still have the most speed and
move around through those Hoops pretty
swiftly
so that is definitely better for me now
the cool guy no editorial
no luck shot cheating yes yes
oh thank you nice eyes
thank you so much I'm glad you enjoyed
it
gonna be using hot wings or a different
Elijah they have a light dress there and
they have fireworks there so every flyer
gets free uh uh fireworks and an elytra
and then you're not allowed to wear
armor so if you really get shot
uh wait a second I think if you get shot
but you still manage to stay in the air
then I think you're fine you're just not
supposed to die
foreign
but I really haven't had the experience
of being shot while being in the air I
think it was fall down but you could
still save yourself no
if you are pretty high up in the air and
get shot I think you can still save
yourself there might be a point penalty
penalty I guess yeah
just don't die yeah
but but honestly like it's so fast I
don't think they really managed to I
mean I don't want to jinx it but it's
like really really difficult
really difficult and you also got to
consider I guess a certain amount of lag
so they they actually don't have
infinite uh ammo either they will be
shooting I think 10 arrows per person
and it will be
uh since I'm in the white sea team I
think the Red Sea team C team only which
is like what six people or so they will
be shooting at me not the whole red team
only the sea Team part of the red team
yeah so it's gonna be like six versus
one with ten arrows each
and I have free uh strength one
um
fireworks
and so by the way
uh for every team there will be one
um point of view that will be streamed
right so for that uh for for us it will
be I think Bales so far it looks like
it's gonna be bales
um but
our team has been a little bit slow on
communication I was like is there anyone
who wants to like volunteer as a leader
and no one really volunteered and
um I didn't want to volunteer either
because I thought I was so busy and
already for I wanted to take it easy
this time and I knew that I would be
tired because I probably won't get much
sleep so I didn't wanna didn't want to
volunteer but no one volunteered and huh
the the discussion wasn't really moving
on very well and and then the superior
Senpai was like yeah uh uh I'm trying to
help out a meal Senpai for organizing
this event and and we still don't know
who you guys are choosing as a leader uh
and as a as a streamer and because that
wasn't decided either at that point so I
was like
um sorry so what is sample I
guess I'll do it
so I have uh chosen the role of being
the leader which I'm generally like fine
with but
just this once I kind of wanted to sit
out so I've been trying to
um communicate and organize
and uh
like who who will be participating in
which game in our team uh see like who
hasn't really decided yet uh who who is
not uh
uh uh who doesn't have a game yet that
they're participating in and all that
yeah fine I'll do it myself exactly
yeah who is on your team
um uh everyone in Hollow Ian accept Cali
[Applause]
and that's it
right yeah and then Cali is actually in
the other in the in the red team see our
rivals which is which is
and Cali
so uh yeah most of whole life Indonesia
is on the other side
and most of Ian is on our side yeah
yeah but that only really happened
because she first was like I can't
participate
I think she was originally in our team
and then and then things got swapped
around and now she's in the other team
but it's gonna be fun it's gonna be fun
anyway
it's gonna be fun
I think that's probably how it was
anyway now now I'm taking care of uh
Team C I don't really know know how the
leader role will be implemented in the
Stream I wonder if I have to be like
talking with Mikko Senpai and Mio Senpai
to represent my team
in that case yes
I am captain Kiara let's go
I'm going to try to lead my team to
Victory to at least uh get team white to
win in general
like super super motivated the Japanese
teams are so motivated from what I've
seen so far
but I also tested out uh the the the
ball tossing game yesterday with vatam
but she taught me how to do it and it's
so fun it's so cool it's like basketball
I did not realize that you could have
such insanely fun games in Minecraft so
well made like oh my God I need you guys
I need to show you guys in my next
Minecraft stream how that works
it's like a field
where in the middle of the field is like
kind of like a basketball thingy where
you have to throw in snowballs
and they have to land in the hopper and
you can see it by seeing if it's in the
chest or not
but you don't just jump there normally
there's like a like an automatic piss
piston I guess is that what you call the
piston
if you step on one
um
uh
uh what's it called the like a not a
button what's what's the thing the big
one called
uh
uh the plate yeah the pressure plate you
step on the pressure plate and like you
have to run over the pressure plate to
be on the Piston right at the moment
where it shoots you up it's perfect it's
like it's so cool and then it shoots you
up and you're like two blocks away from
the basketball ring thingy and then you
throw the snowball in there and I think
it's three people at once free people
from the white team free people from the
red team trying to throw as many
snowballs as possible into the hopper
it it just looks like so much fun and I
tried it out and I think I got the gist
of it
yeah I think I might need to participate
in two games by the way because it seems
like that's how it is with all the other
teams the Birdman uh darts participant
uh seems to always be in at least one
more game uh
uh besides the relay where I think
everyone is part of it but so far I just
put myself into the ball tossing game as
well because we were lacking one member
anyway
um yeah the hopper can receive flying
snowballs if you shoot them with Q
rather than right click if you shoot
them with right click I learned this
yesterday for the first time then they
will break but if you shoot them with Q
it will just fall in there normally
and not break
so I am ready I got some practice on
both of my games already and uh yeah
looking forward to it yeah it's just
dropping it basically
yeah yeah looking forward to it myself
foreign
[Laughter]
block blocks make it seem like you're
throwing it exactly it's so cool I
wonder if that was difficult to build
because that was just so much fun I want
to build it on the en server
hmm I missed your part in her stream it
was pretty much towards the end
if you look for the VOD again you'll see
me and Vladimir trying out the Birdman
darts and the the ball tossing game and
her trying to shoot me down when I'm
flying through the uh hoops
and then we're like oh she she and her
audience they were like oh she's so good
at flying Kakui is so cool
I was very flattered but I wasn't really
that good but okay cool
so back to topic oh my God I need to
read some budget oh my God
zero three zero
Ginger Ranger 13 years foreign
[Music]
is that a red one or Pinky
I think it might be
[Music]
you don't have to send it to me again I
got it open I saved it in my picture
folder
is that what is that
so wait no no it's a normal one okay
Super Chat Speed Run any percent
uh a totally real uh no cheats uh all
real
not rigged not little dinosaurs
Kiara I love your energy and how kind
you are to your gentmates you'll always
be my Oshie I'm glad to see how much
Knowles you've gotten since your first
Minecraft stream thank you oh
I have to um
I have to still do VR prep by the way
but I still got a lot of time I have
like like four or three hours or so yeah
but I'm charging my VR stuff right now
[Music]
is that charging properly why is it
still blinking red what does that mean
it's supposed to be charging oh well
I'll look at it closer afterwards
[Music]
did I just spoil something foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
no one else
am I teased it already
Iris already spoiled it on her frame
okay good okay okay Iris description
already spoiled oh
okay then you don't need to uh give me
[\h__\h] for it calm down
one
okay okay okay okay okay okay
there you go stop
with me
[Music]
no Panic no Panic
that came so natural I really didn't
even try to tease anything
um
oh you changed your name you're not even
trying to get me to say the thing
anymore
okay
see I made up for uh doing so many
tangents we're done with Minecraft
[Music]
I could have I could have been done with
it like years ago
mistaken whoa wait that's smart that's
smart too is that on purpose mistaken
mistaken
[Music]
thank you for the Clapping thank you
foreign
[Music]
I was trying to learn the vampire
choreography until today
but first of all I didn't have enough
time sorry and second of all I figured
um
it would be insanely difficult to dance
that properly with the headset on my
head
and uh yeah
one day
one day maybe
because I already like even just by
standing normally that headset feels so
heavy on my head and and when I tried to
Vibe a little bit when I performed
Sparks last time it also didn't feel
very stable I wonder if I couldn't
stabilize it somehow more hmm
foreign
would be a cool way to promote my song
cover by dancing the choreography but
sorry maybe maybe in a cuddle of the
stream one day
you know what I could do like a karaoke
stream to Vocaloid songs where I
actually don't sing I Just Dance all the
choreographies because there's so many
choreographies to all those Vocaloid
songs
um
mm-hmm
I still know
Fever by heart
even though that's like a million years
ago
I suggested it before didn't I
it's kindness
but the ideal solution to the VR headset
uh being so heavy would be uh just
finding a Tracker that I can just wear
like a headband
like a really small one
and then I don't need to wear the
headset the VR goggles
to be able to do that stream I think in
my opinion so
if that's possible I will once I'm not
so busy anymore I will go through all
these things with Ahmed and I want to do
a I just want to do a wealthy VR stream
um for you guys sometime soon even if
it's just a normal karaoke stream I
thought that was so cute when when Amber
did it we were a little hand sees
although my model doesn't have fingers
so
I don't know maybe maybe I wanna get a
Kiara be a model too or something like
that hey with small little chunky
sausage fingers
yeah I was thinking of maybe
commissioning a model
um
and then surprising you guys but yeah
well it's not much of a surprise anymore
well you don't know what it's gonna look
like and you don't know when it's coming
so look forward to that
is this chat rigged what do you mean
froggiana
wouldn't that be great I know I know I
know I know
what that's that's kind of what I've
been hoping for
shh
stop making so obvious guys
don't let's just say it's gonna be
cat Kiara for now okay don't ruin this
press
foreign
don't scream into the heavens no
Secret
s
okay next up is pumpkin carving
pumpkin carving stream the pumpkin
didn't really live for long
oh that was the stinky pumpkin uh
uh pumpkin pumpkin but that was so fun I
want to do more stuff like that
I already on Twitter I talked about what
we could do next what we could do for
Christmas and all that and my mom
suggested
uh what's it in English again
gingerbread gingerbread house building
so that sounds like a lovely idea I'm
definitely gonna be doing that but I was
still I will still think about
what I could do about that Christmas
tree decorating stream
I will look into it
to see if it's technically possible
you got Kelly what I already sent it to
you
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah what do you
mean I already sent it to you oh we're
in a vacuum package in a frozen delivery
it's gonna arrive in the three to five
business days
oh yeah I should be good once it arrives
at your place oh
she slightly believed me
how does in the first half not gonna lie
yeah I thought I had you in your second
health first half was not really
believable
snowman buildings
uh how how would one do that order fake
snow
stream outside
oh man that sounds really difficult
[Music]
do you wanna build a snowman
a VR art yeah the stuff that Ina has
been making looks really interesting
yeah
the 3D drawing is so cool
yeah pretty cool
presents are having
who's presents am I around thing though
I could just be like a factory present
wrapping Factory let's have a like 10 or
20 for the cardboard boxes and then
wrap them even though nothing's inside
it's literally just empty cardboard
boxes and I'm just I am horrible at
rapping stuff though
I've never been good at that for
instance first movie in chunkers in in
the contrary I will wrap smoothie and
chunkers
I will wrap them
thousand only keep the head open I feel
like I've done that before with one of
my
previous cats
oh who doesn't do that huh only for a
moment
we're really chill sorry I can't
burritos
some are really chill and some are like
nope I'm out of here
which is understandable have a nice day
cat
Miranda
I don't remember Chris
Kiana
thank you
for the hey Kiana since you've been
watching Seinfeld if all the Hollow myth
girls were Seinfeld characters who would
be who oh my God I think I would be
um I don't really remember names I would
be the neighbor Maybe
um
gouda would be um
the bald guy
yeah that would be Kramer could I would
be uh a bald guy what's his name
George yes oh he's George's
football
three would be
Jerry's personality is
not really similar to any of us I think
[Music]
I know Ina is a comedian but nothing
else of her suits Jerry like nothing
else is like Jerry maybe
um
[Music]
not really saying that she's like Jerry
but
and then the girl what's the girl's name
again
who who would she be
wait it's Kelly and Ina left
no we don't really suit those characters
we don't like them
Elaine
I would almost say like maybe me but I'm
already Kramer
gray my such idiot
I don't know I'll leave it to you let's
recreate a skit
why not both
friends with friends
um it might be a bit easier
dashing can speak Spanish
no I don't know anyone who celebrates
that
spark set in 2 million views
congratulations Kiana and keeps throwing
spikes thank you come Sunny down
yes spikes is at 2 million but we cannot
have it end there let's go keep on
keep us guys next to vampire
come on
[Music]
you might be responsible for 500K
so much
foreign
I feel so anxious
kills pumpkin my head shall it got
opened oh no yellow pumpkin look on the
bright side I lost loose some weight
yeah that's right
we have more Apple facts fact number
three like apples pumpkins or fruits
pumpkins or vegetables
[Music]
what
no pumpkins or vegetables what do you
mean
I would
yeah that's the first time I hear that
what the hell
botanically there didn't I I feel like
someone sent me
um pumpkin facts the other day and I
read a lot about it it's kind of like
yeah culinary is the vegetable
botanically it's a fruit it's like both
at the same time it's the Schrodinger is
pumpkin
hahaha
don't start dancing for the pinky
happy Halloween to you you only sent a
little pumpkin a carved pumpkin alone
but thank you I hope my stream was able
to get you into a Halloweeny mood over
there
yeah
[Music]
freeze the Frog a happy belated birthday
thank you for the words open yet of
course you're gonna kiss
[Music]
happy belated birthday to you happy
belated birthday to you happy belated
birthday to freeze the front happy
belated
yeah thank you for watching my stream on
your special day I hope you had a great
one I hope you got to celebrate and I
hope a lot of people wish you a very
happy birthday cause you deserve it
foreign
[Music]
do either of you cats eat pumpkin no
they did not seem interested in it at
all actually your cat used to eat
pumpkin straight out of it oh my God
[Music]
wow
what a healthy cat I guess
meme Gordon Ramsay Duncan
oh my God she doesn't have the tool
necessary please don't hurt yourself
see I
I didn't even realize that there would
be tool sets just for pumpkin carving I
didn't even look for it is
foreign
there are two sets but I'm not a fan of
them myself they're usually cheap and
weak and cannot handle a pumpkin oh
I can see that I can imagine
dragons
you finally had your 3DW
what do you mean
you mean because I put the headphones on
the pumpkin is that what you're getting
at
[Laughter]
[Music]
I think that might want you might have
been what you meant
oh yeah a keyhole saw would have been
perfect yeah I know well even with
shitty tools we got pretty far and yeah
it ended up looking pretty good it was
even my first time and it still was I
think a good result that Lee ended up
with
hmm
[Music]
yeah I was thinking
you can look so cute with those
headphones on now you also know what my
headphones look like yeah yeah gamer
girl headphones
translate Korean to English
thank you
ship Skylark don't understand hey get a
pumpkin carving is fun but did you know
dental hygiene is too fun to always
brush and floss your teeth twice a day
so that your smile is bright as your
feathers see ya
is is
well okay I will uh
yes do my vest is Chip Skylake isn't
that like that is that character that
Avatar
I think
isn't that from what's that cartoon
called I think yeah Fairly Odd Parents I
watched that so much
I watched that so much when I was
younger I love that
for coming here
my honor thank you I'm so honored can I
get an autograph
Ed Korean name
it's a queen Supreme
dances
left hand Squad let's go yeah once again
I've proved that I'm left-handed people
were so surprised because I guess I
don't show that that often but yes I am
left-handed always been
pumpkin was like continuously sending
Super Shots during this
[Laughter]
I'm sorry sorry
[Music]
oh awesome birthday happy belated
birthday to you as well
that's nice
after a bad day I can hear your voice
and see the stream which makes me much
better thank you thank you I love you I
love you too I'm glad to hear that
please continue enjoying and watching my
streams you're always welcome
foreign
oh
what I haven't watched that so
I don't understand what what what this
is about
I don't get it
but you guys are laughing so
the the collab by the way for me is at
half past midnight
but it shouldn't go on for like too long
so I hope I hope I'll make it for the
day
[Music]
ah I know that I know that fact about
Zelda someone told me when I was playing
um Skyward Sword yeah yeah yeah
I remember that
didn't I have to hold the sword in the
right hand too even though I'm
left-handed because there was no choice
ridiculous they should have given me a
choice
you can't just assume that everyone who
plays the game now is right-handed
yeah that was very shocking to me
uh chaos pumpkin
[Music]
try to cut in blocks instead of all at
once also a Sarah Sarah did knife would
work better for you if you have one
serrated knife
where is that
ah like a like a bread knife
ah I had one um actually prepared with
me
and I tested it out to carve out the the
top
uh the the Hat part but it didn't really
work that well actually so I I ended up
not using it I needed I only had like a
big one anyway I needed smaller ones so
I couldn't really use it
thank you
I appreciate that so much
[Music]
Jacob 47 Old Fashioned Mr Pine dungeon
I'd like to just say thank you for
everything you won't know how much you
have helped me whole life really helped
my mental health in the past months you
and Kelly have helped me the most thank
you the best thing I could ever wish for
well that is very very wholesome I am so
happy to hear that thank you please
continue watching us to keep your mental
health on a good positive level
yeah
I'm glad we could help you hmm
that is very good to know
see it always goes and
upwards again after you're like going
downhill and you think like it won't get
better anymore it always ends up going
better at some point so you just have to
wait a little bit and give it a chance
[Music]
Patrick
oh this was when I was slapping
this was when I was slapping the pumpkin
I listened to
um the wand afterwards I wanted to hear
how it sounded and it actually sounded
pretty good I guess
um
[Music]
Violet I'm a garden this is violent this
is violet ever gone right you changed
your picture didn't you
you changed your picture
yes it's Violet of accordion
conditions
Russian thank you for the pinky good
morning afternoon evening to everybody
especially to the lovely Phoenix Kiara
wow so polite thank you
thank you good morning good evening good
afternoon to you as well
will you play Diablo 2 again yeah at
some point I'm just currently too busy
to fit it into my schedule
next week I also want to play so many
games I gotta do a little nightmares and
I gotta do uh uh Alice
uh at the sports festival and the Corral
foreign
[Music]
from my side currently uh organized from
my side with four people but I don't
know who's participating yet we will see
so much sorry I don't I feel like I'm
lacking uh air
meme Gordon Ramsay thank you for the
pinky I don't know what I've missed my
internet went down so I'll just assume
yeah you wheeled the knife like a
caveman with a club I'm dissatisfied and
disappointed you're a chef and the
chicken stop taking it and use a knife I
love that so much
I love that stupid chat
[Music]
Iris thank you sir no saint
317-0 XL 44 Duncan Iris Duncan stable
bread dangashion Kiana's pumpkin
thank you for protecting me I would
school down kitchen Hollow Knight
dankish and back door happy belated
birthday to you too I'm your favorite
whole life member thank you
thank you for spending your time with me
I hope you enjoyed the pumpkin coloring
stream and your birthday I hope you got
some time for yourself with your friends
as well getting those presents and those
those well wishes and everything
[Music]
the very hungry Singularity dance
us for the pinky thank you
have you seen the pumpkin scraping tools
you can use them to draw on the pumpkin
they are like vegetable peelers next to
skin thinner uh and when you put it in a
light it will project the image yeah
yeah yeah I mean since I've watched like
tutorials before I even
um did the stream uh I knew about those
like like
um like strategies but yeah I wasn't
able to prepare any such tools but we
a decent projection anyway that wasn't
even on purpose but Cali's uh Shinigami
sensei
projection looked so good
in my opinion I love that one I was
really proud of that one Kelly liked it
too so all is good
[Music]
is it a Discord Mark hey
it looked the taco daddy looked so much
like a Discord
I know it did
Flora John Duncan president
I am again Korean
cherry blossom thank you
zombie VIP Danger
pretty artsy whole new club there oh
thank you very artsy indeed you did
great with the pumpkin especially Bubba
and death Sensei I was surprised so many
people said their favorite one was Bubba
when I asked you guys because I thought
Bubba was okay pretty good but kind of
cursed looking I feel like the the whole
base like the art was the most accurate
will bloop
and I also liked the way the light shine
was shining through bloop more as well
um
I liked boa because it was cursed oh oh
so that's the reason you liked him
because he was cursed
but that looks pretty good in the dark
hey are you not talking about blue
because buba was like didn't let much
light go through
bubble was like mostly just
ah me scratching the surface
off of the pumpkin
[Music]
I thought Bubba looked cute oh well
thank you
I thought I messed up the the art stuff
like what I drew on the pumpkin with the
marker I thought I messed it up a little
bit I definitely did it wasn't perfect
bloop was much better in my opinion
hmm
[Music]
I feel like bloop didn't let enough
light no I mean yeah blue mostly let the
most light through uh for his hat
but Bubba had like even less it was like
only the eyes
that lets a little bit of light through
but okay whatever you guys really like
Bubba huh
Justin horror danke Schoenberg zombies
Thompson Thompson
pH is difficult to say
thank you
he has pumpkin
outrun the wind dancing
sleep dancing meme Gordon Ramsay thank
you
I will cook that pumpkin I've seen
[\h__\h] with better hand control now
she'll cavemen other pumpkin I'll cook
this chicken for Thanksgiving if she
said something about me
[Laughter]
maybe Gordon Rams
Caribbean caps lock for [\h__\h] sake
it's even uh no wait is it in my
description I know it's an Amish
description for her streams don't write
everything in caps lock
Gordon Ramsay you need to chill you have
a aggression problems I would say
you need a chill pill
you won't know he's screaming if he
doesn't yeah yeah yeah I'm just kidding
please continue
thank you for the pinky
anger management yeah
you may not you may not understanding it
is
[Music]
thank you
my cousin and I talked about carving
pumpkins because we never have then she
said she wanted to make pumpkin pie and
learned there were different kinds of
pumpkins I just thought it was about
size but apparently not you know there
are so many different pumpkins
but yeah this has been the first time I
realized that butternuts uh squash is
a pumpkin and not uh or like it's a
squash yeah whatever but I thought it
was nuts
turns out butternut squash
is not Deez Nuts
meme Gordon Ramsay thank you for another
pinky this was fun but due to the storm
outside oh there was an actual storm
we're not just kidding and my wall
keeping this up will be hard so I will
not be retreating to my storm cellar
good day and yeah I hope they turn out
well thank you for your kindness
thank you very much
laughs
guys
thank you for the pinky
that moment when one of your trusted
friends sends the skin of your mascot in
the male unprovoked hashtag related book
oh yeah good I was really freaked out
when I told her that I spined a shark
she
did something like that I did I skinned
poop
I am carved a breaking pumpkin she was
so freaked out
I wonder if she's seen the picture by
now
I should show her
huh
[Music]
wipe I guess thank you
rat crab tank
it's good I remembered my existence she
would be really mad I'm sorry she
pressured you into playing Outlast I'll
pay for her crimes
no it's all good I think we might talk
about it later but it's all good
um Outlast turned out to be way less
awful than I thought it would be
curry cheese company
[Music]
uh
uh holy [\h__\h] this is a lot of super
chats guys
this is a lot of super chats isn't it
oh my
actually this stream also has a lot oh
dear
I should make some teeth
because my throat hurts
mama
[Music]
Jim Tracy Duncan
now I want to finish them today though
if possible
pumpkins
was I missing red ones I missed the pink
one
uh which one
one ah ah cow's pumpkin this one I think
yeah yeah always says pinky
oh thank you sad okay okay
Ken's pumpkin says Carefree remember I
am I was
thank you pumpkin for supporting me I'm
sorry I had to hurt you
I'm sorry I did it for the content I
have to
I had no choice
but see so many people really enjoyed
watching me hurt you
so you were a great investment
it's for the content
[Music]
energy local
Dr Pepper come on give me some energy
please
I'll it's also um 9pm right now and I've
only had a few Pokey and a bowl of some
cereal it's not even that much it was
just a small bowl of cereals that's all
I had I think that's why I don't feel
energetic right now
[Music]
bird lady
hmm
[Music]
I can't order food now
I mean I can but like
I can't eat food now I wanna
let's just try to
do this come on time for donkey shirt
and move stankishing for the ranks of a
chat moves thank you
MIP icon pumpkin looks so nice and cool
well done Dental happy Halloween thank
you I'm pretty proud of it myself
it was not a very long lived thing to
enjoy it was a very short-lived thing
as soon as the stream was over I did not
touch it anymore except in order to
throw it away
I did not light it up either after that
so it was really really short-lived but
still
um
[Music]
I've made a good memory it looked great
yeah
and and I mean clips and stuff right so
those exist too so it it's it extended
its life length of life
a little bit more yeah
you didn't keep it for a bit no I had it
standing around for how many days was it
I threw it away this morning
it was so stinky
how many days was that when did I do the
pumpkin carving on Tuesday or Wednesday
it was like four days maybe
yeah
I should have at least put it outside
then maybe it wouldn't wouldn't have
bothered me that much oopsie duck and
duck pumpkin
how long is this ah we're done
we're done with pumpkin pumpkin pumpkin
nice thumbnail
is someone
I don't know
check
one thing
[Music]
foreign
left you mean or I read 257 super chats
still haven't watched that one yet I'm a
bit scared too but I feel like I have to
someday
um I think
I think it's not that bad
it's I think as a viewer
maybe it is less less scary as a watch I
don't know how is it for you guys
I just said the same thing twice as a
viewer I think it's less scary than as a
player is it a little bit and I mean
good I was there and I survived I was
able to play the me
the one who was
who was playing for two hours and I
could have honestly I could have gone
longer I was actually having a little
bit of fun towards the end
and it wasn't that difficult so I could
have played longer but yeah uh there
were there were things that good I had
to do afterwards I didn't want to hold
her up for too long so
um
yeah I had a little bit of fun but I I
wouldn't say that I would play it
anytime soon again
it's not like a game choice that I would
just choose just because I want to
stream a game like I wouldn't normally
choose this game in particular
unless I have an actual reason for it
like Halloween
[Music]
no no no no no
but I don't know I could consider you
know good uh could I mention this Co-op
Outlast I I would I would consider it at
least I'll give you that
foreign
let's go p13
say okay
one two three nope that should be normal
okay
and Patrick took Patrick or treat
thank you this is my first Super Chat
sorry for the late membership even
though I've watched you since debut no
problem you don't have to be a member to
watch Kiana you might be missing out on
a few things but it's all good I don't
mind I can't watch this live but I will
watch the vld later always love you P.S
have you ever think of Timber duet with
Kelly
Timber you mean it's going down
[Music]
it's going down
I'm I'm yelling
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
it's going down
I'm yelling timber bear you better move
you better dance let's make a night you
won't remember I'll be the one you won't
forget
[Music]
okay is that what you want me to sing
with Cali swing your partner round and
round end of the night it's going down
one more shot and never around end of
the night it's going down swing your
partner round and round and every night
it's going down when we shine
who's there
ah
right there's a singing part and there's
a red part it would be a good
collaboration song I suppose
that's a fancy dancers
I must not feel fear is the mind killer
fear is a little death that brings total
obliteration I will face my fear I will
permit it to pass over me and through me
where the fear has gone there will be
nothing only I will remain is that a
quote
that sounds so deep
oh the litany against Pierre Dune oh yo
yo you're actually quoting something and
now you're telling me just in time
[Music]
speaking of fear what I have noticed is
I think I am rather than being scared of
Outlast I was more scared of being
scared
[Music]
when it came to outlast or like
generally like for horror games
but it's because it's because you guys
have been like telling me that Outlast
is like so so
so so so so scary
literally so bad and
and I mean I it's not I'm really not
good with horror games I mean that is
true I don't like horror games I don't
like the horror genre
but I was way more scared than I needed
to be because of my expectations
now
you are so much stronger than you give
yourself credits for
you have to remember you're talking to a
bunch of chick literally
yeah that's that's true I can't blame
you I guess
sounds less like you're scared of horror
games and more like you're scared about
the idea of being scared in general
that's literally what I just said but
yes
yeah no I'm also I was also I mean those
screams those were not fake like uh the
jump scares they were scary and I was
scared of vlogging around there at least
in the first half of the game later on
it was getting better
yeah
but I was definitely extremely scared in
the first half of the game of the Stream
I cried Young
[Music]
isn't it
always makes for the pinky let's go cow
don't chicken out ah
I I was uh kind of close to chickening
out because I was not looking forward to
the stream at all I was pretty um
I was pretty
um
uh grumpy
we're not whenever I was thinking about
the Outlast stream I was very grumpy
about it up to five minutes before the
stream I was like
why am I doing this I hate this
[Laughter]
but I couldn't back out anymore it was
happening
it was okay
I guess I'm glad that I did it because
um
at least now you guys can shut up for a
while about me playing cool games
[Music]
all right
not a good username 360 donation and
also like a lot of people
uh enjoyed this stream I wonder if that
was like
if that was even mostly kfp or just a
lot of General Hollow en viewers who
were like oh I guess I'll check out
kyota play out last
I honestly want to know
how how that was like was it mostly kfp
I don't I have no idea
[Music]
it was probably both but yeah
hmm
I I'm glad I got some uh non-kfb people
to check me out again for once thank you
thank you
[Music]
I'm glad but why why does it why does it
take out less why does it take a horror
game
ah well you guys only watch me when I
play horror games is that what it is
well those people only watch me when I
play horror games
people like horror games I don't
understand I don't understand
I don't I mean I understand liking
horror games but I don't I don't
understand why why you would make it
such a huge priority to watch someone's
horror game streams rather than
something fun
and exciting like I don't know like me
playing I don't know Mario Party or
whatever
cute screams
you guys just like watching girls being
scared
is that it is it your your natural
instinct uh from the caveman times need
to protect women
need a protect woman
ah I need a projector from danger
I think that's what it goes back to
caveman chicken
[Laughter]
Phoenix
cannot be scared I need to help Phoenix
chickens get very very scared
you're exactly right how'd you know
um
[Music]
protect chicken
oh yeah
since Taco marjoro dad caveman chicken
yes I can't get it out of my head man no
I can't
I love caveman genius
imagine caveman chicken starting a fire
today with a stone and the stick
making fire for Phoenix
start a fire today
streams box
that would be so cute
[Laughter]
the drawing program right now I don't
know when you're using book I hear The
Strokes already
swoosh drawing ASMR
[Music]
streams
um
statue and it can double as a gift to
Petco
which she might take as a declaration of
war but that's a risk I'm willing to
take
I haven't settled yet for what I want
her to make but the foot statue or the
foot imprint on the ground or whatever
it's gonna be has a big chance of being
the one
Unga Bunga foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't worry guys she ain't scared yet
that's just her high cholesterol
and
actually my my BPM was so calm a lot of
times only for the jump scares for just
a moment it would go up pretty high but
I don't I don't understand how
like people like gouda who can who play
horror games like fairly often have even
just from the get-go
such a high heart rate what's is that
what good I did say to me though that I
have a healthy heart rate
I guess I guess what is like is that
healthy I guess so
then it's really unhealthy that you have
a heart rate over 100
just by starting a stream gouda
you need to work out more or so I don't
know how do you lower your heart rate
working out or or I don't know eating
better and I eat [\h__\h] I eat so much crap
I eat so much fast food guys
diet and workout huh
but gouda works out more than me I think
she played ringford Adventure at least
what two times on her Channel and I did
zero attempts
yeah I don't drink either and I don't
smoke either like nothing
I've been good at least uh drinks uh
some some some alcohol and every now and
then sometimes sometimes sometimes no
okay I guess maybe that explains it
because I don't see are eating more
faster than I do I feel like she eats
healthier than I do probably
and I also have a feeling that she moves
her body more than I do I can't imagine
her sitting around and laying around
lazing around more than I do
[Music]
I didn't expect my heart rate to be so
healthy either
uh next time
[Music]
subscribers thank you for the pinky
honestly Resident Evil would probably
have been the easier option
um
you think so
you guys think Resident Evil is scarier
than otherwise what you think
kssj thank you
Johnny that one dude
there's no evil way less scary no it's
not it's not scary really
it's not scary
really
more action oriented
um it's not scary but it's a shooter
much better depends on which one
okay
you can defend yourself it's not scary
oh yeah
I did like the fact that I didn't have
to fight in outlast
um or I thought I would like to fact
but yeah I guess if I would have been
able to fight back sometimes that would
have been more successful in outlast I
guess yeah
no it does seem like a stupid thing to
do though for a reporter like that is
being attacked by it
some insane zombies why why would you
even try to fight back I I would if I
like it's just a normal dude right so if
I were in a silent like that I would
just run too I would logically thinking
I would never choose to fight
and I don't think any of you guys wait
that's wrong that is not true because I
am a part-time Warrior Phoenix so sorry
I forgot of course I would fight for
said
vessels
[Music]
fantasma free thank you for the pinky
you got this verb fear is a state of
mind it totally is you're so right with
that
it's all right with that
I think also one reason why it wasn't uh
that scary to me anymore after a while
like in the beginning it was just
inevitable but later on I think because
my screen was so small I wasn't looking
at OBS but I was just the whole game
screen was windowed and fairly small on
my screen and everything around the game
was really bright
so I think that kind of helped a little
bit
um
[Music]
oh Outsider you need to stop asking me
about that because I I can't
I uh I shouldn't say anything anymore
about anything I ever ever
I I don't know sometimes
Donovan Lee what
no one usually one tends to set the mood
for those games
keep forgetting about those outfits
if we could have had them in time for
Halloween because
hello new outfit Halloween looks like a
you know like a costume would have been
uh cool to have like a Halloween costume
I mean it's not a Halloween costume but
still
now I'm a cat I'm a kitty cat and I'm
meow meow meow and I'm meow meow meow I
miss the pink
no no no I didn't read it yet
oh wait oh you mean I mean huh I guess I
was one above it Donovan Lee thank you
for the pinky yeah it's gonna need help
after this playthrough good luck
greetings from Japan I'm gonna be a simp
now and give you money okay oh you sound
very fluent in the English language and
internet language wow
and thank you thank you I appreciate it
the luck uh and I ended up being very
lucky I mean look at all those times
when he opened the locker but not the
one that I was in
I thought that was just how the game
works
good I was like whoa
how do you do that
[Music]
then he grabbed you in the hole no he
got me once when I was like under the
bed and stuff that was uh extremely
scary
I actually thought that you were
immediately like dead once they grabbed
him but you actually still get a chance
so that's fairly manageable
you can still run away even after they
grab you once so all good
it is how it works when you're on little
difficulty oh yeah it was a normal
difficulty
Health recovers after five seconds oh
that is so quick really
whoa very forgiving
uh fantastic thank you again for the
pinky oh yeah ah okay see this one I
already read videos
are not applicable to English and
goddamn musician hello my attention
oh
um
for the pinky dear Brave tencho seems
like the pipe bursted in the usual room
the basement is flooded the light is out
it's dark we hear something moving
through the water chickens are scared
would you kindly show us the way down
will pin you
I don't trust it
oh wait that's a reference to Alice I
thought you
thought you um telling me that just to
get me to the usual room and then lock
me into the usual room and then Escape
yourselves
I thought it was a whole plan
to put me into the usual room and lock
me in there
I thought it was a bait yeah conspiracy
[Music]
oh no she found out no no no I guess you
were just yeah uh joking about the
Outlast plot we aren't that smart yeah I
suppose so I I sometimes expect too much
from you guys
[Laughter]
Ramona H tangish and blue batangasium
Deep Dark Fantasy
fantasy and why didn't Kuda care about
my fate you have to ask her that blue
and to help you
foreign
[Music]
was his birthday in the Outlast stream
I'm a little bit late but yeah
apparently he says he works 24 7. so
much I can imagine Japanese people
always work 24 7. but on his birthday he
went to an Onsen that's nice
good for you rewarding yourself treat
yourself
[Music]
a minute
Stephen Rothwell 19 dinosaur
Nights by that one dangerous
[Music]
for the pinky behold her kfb look as
your tend to conquer interferes with a
mostly steady heart and iron will let
her be an inspiration to face your fears
emotional support shark recommended
despite you all have entire chicken
Heights light a brave fire today
was a great emotional support I hope
everyone has a emotional support track
by their signs as well
very much necessary
treat yourself before you wreck yourself
yeah what was that again was that a
Parks and Rec
I know treat yourself was Parks and Rec
but was it the whole thing treat
yourself before you wreck yourself or
did I hear that somewhere else I think
it was Parks and Rec
oh
foreign
[Music]
I'm eating or licking uh
throat candy right now
not really a Halloween candy
but close enough
[Music]
foreign
yeah and I do need to get something to
eat before Nicola but
um do I have something I guess I could
make some simple pasta
probably
no I have to finish the super chance
random collusion thank you for the pinky
thanks very much for overcoming your
fears and trying new things Kiara I
enjoyed it so much oh is this already
around the end oh it seems so
thank you
yeah I am I'm glad I overcome I have
overcome my fear as well I'm happy about
that too
um so thank you
um for watching over me guys
um
thank you very much for watching the
stream and I know a lot of you guys were
worried about me
but I appreciate that too because that
was also very worried about myself but I
guess we all just kind of underestimated
myself
um
[Music]
see I am I'm totally open to trying new
things like this
I just don't like it when people push me
too much and pressure me uh into doing
these things and I have my way of
doing things and I think mostly I like
the way I do things
and I I do think that there is variety
on my channel anyway
we don't necessarily need horror games
or
stuff like that that I don't usually
play
um I think like if you think that
there's no variety on my channel I feel
like you're just not like you're just
too used to my channel by now
yeah because we have a lot of variety in
my opinion it's just I don't really
cater to the two most popular gaming
genres FPS and horror
I just don't cater to it but I don't see
why I need to cater to everything you
know what I mean
um
but don't worry I am gonna try out FPS
as well
I did request some perms
um
I don't know what I will get earlier the
perms for the game that I requested or
the PS5 for death Loop
let's see I haven't heard anything about
the PS5 for a long time
foreign
I have no idea where that PS5 is right
now I think it's somewhere in the void I
think the PS5 disappeared in the void
flying simulator I know about flight
simulator but I I kind of want to try
one of those Simulator games sometime
soon like I don't know
burglar simulator a clicking simulator a
babysitter simulator or anything like
that and I also kind of want to play GTA
uh any GTA game at some point so yeah
there will always be some games that are
a little bit different from what I
usually uh play but I I do definitely
try to
um give you guys entertaining uh and
yeah
funny streams every week
I'm not always have the same kind of
games through the whole week I I try to
have variation I hope I hope that
um feels the same way to you guys I hope
it comes across but honestly every time
I upload my schedule you guys are always
very excited so
[Music]
um
yeah and now we've been playing all
these games that
um I wasn't really thinking about
playing until now like little nightmares
and Alice and Ori and Outlast and all
that
so yeah we have a lot going on and I
think
uh
so Alice we're trying to finish
and then after that we're gonna play Ori
which is also just a shorter game so for
a while I think we're really
um gonna play a lot of shorter games
until we jump back into the long jrpgs
super chats don't go okay okay
[Music]
um
So yeah thank you random collusion
change the ranger 13 dinosaurs
200 oh my God I thought it was a 20.
while it wasn't orange but I almost
didn't see that zero Daisy thank you
what the hell come with the not being a
chicken thank you are you
pressing
are you proud of me
I I'm really glad you guys enjoyed it so
much I didn't think that
like I I knew that you guys would like
that the main kfb audience would be
there and you guys would be entertained
and all that but I didn't think it would
have such a uh I don't think I didn't
think it would be that well received
let's say like that
um
I didn't think that you guys were that
interested
like not only kfp but so many others
yeah I was very surprised
is it because of Outlast
is it because it's specifically Outlast
or because me and gouda talked about it
for so long I guess that that's it as
well
maybe it's a couple of factors also the
fact the fact that it was my first
proper horror game on my channel we
should uh forget about that other one
that I did
feels a little bit uh lame to say that
that was my first horror game the the
one that we did last year in Halloween
good I was feeling it the whole week the
whole week really I thought only during
her own Outlast stream ah
thank you
okay
[Music]
any horror game would get you that kind
of attention you could probably browse
for the other girls videos to see how
our games work for them
it's very new to me I didn't really
expect this at all
I
I was getting a little bit nervous
because
I figured that a lot of non-kp people
were watching
you know made me a bit nervous mmm
[Music]
you should do a VR Oracle I'm a fake one
no we are horror is on a whole number
level no no no I even already sweat a
lot just by wearing the VR on its own
and like doing like the last VR thing
that we did just by walking around and
talking a bit for the tiniest amount of
time I was so sweaty and it was so
exhausting
man the Army horror would probably be um
not very long oh yeah good I I heard
that didn't feel so well after playing
fast mode in VR
[Music]
she felt like kind of sick yeah
see that's why I already from the
beginning when they started talking
about VR fast mode and I was like nope
nope nope nope I was like oh
if Emma says no I can imagine it would
be bad
good I almost barf down the street oh my
God
oh my God yeah it must have been really
bad
[Music]
yeah I peeked into the stream every now
and then at some point I was like audit
did they stop VR and Ahmed it was like
putting up a third camera for only 45
minutes and I was like oh what's what's
going on there
hmm
she screamed so hard oh my God
oh my God
oh man I just want to give her a hug
thank you thank you Daisy again
I'm really really glad you enjoyed it
I'm I'm just
I don't know it might it made me really
happy to uh see people
enjoy
my content and while horror games will
not be
um
a weekly thing on my channel uh
I am open to doing it again at some
point if there is like a like a
punishment game
um so yeah thank you thank you for uh
yeah watching
Italian
for the I think that's a pinky thank you
one of the three actually where's the
rest uh up there oh that that's free
pinkies then thank you
oh wait is it wait uh let me see
uh uh where is it where is it where is
it where is it origin
I'm seeing
I don't see it on the list
a free pancakes okay congratulations to
your pass two hours more yeah I did it
pretty long I was planning on only doing
like one hour
that's not good as to help you too are
cute after so many
stuff that's okay she's braver and
stronger than you thought but this time
you were too scared more than I imagined
at the beginning I really feel the fear
that this game will hurt your spirit
since and so I was afraid that we would
lose you and I just can't do nothing and
staring in front of the screen however
the time goes by and proved me wrong
again
yeah I proved a lot I was wrong
anyway bad things are gone everything's
gonna be okay you're so grateful and I'm
so proud of you hope you have a happy
Halloween mama I love you
oh I love you too thank you for the
support
yeah I was okay
um
I was surprised just as much as you
me too me too
but yeah thank you for staying with me
you need to have a little bit more faith
in me it seems
yeah all of you
including me thank you so much
I appreciate it thank you for supporting
me for a long time yeah
I'm glad you enjoyed it
you're a good employee thank you
for your love
flim flammable
you did amazing part-time Warrior indeed
hey I proved myself huh
no one will doubt part-time Warrior
anymore ever again
thank you Marcus G thank you
um
red Super Chat
why this number
is that two hours and 17 minutes
[Music]
yeah it is oh
147 US dollar and says two two hours and
17 minutes of horror this time
that's why you did that smart
oh so if I would have gone for six hours
would you have sent that in US Dollars
oh my God
that didn't go for so long I didn't want
to make you go broke
thank you for staying with me until the
end thank you I hope you had fun
watching it I hope you weren't as scared
as I was
I was honestly so impressed by gouda
remembering everything so well like
she knew which direction to go even when
I was just so freaking out and running
so fast in circles
that's impressive yeah
she was ready yeah she practiced I know
she played played it the day before but
she didn't get very far did she
as far as I know how can I mean here's a
kiss when you catch it
is
thank you Kiana for stepping out of your
comfort zone and giving out less a
chance it was very entertaining all the
way through well you did a good job
really good job getting as far as you
did yeah
chat
okay that's all it says why oh
it was when I was talking about salaries
thank you Sally channel for your salary
to me
Greg thank you in sky thank you my gray
Junior Dominique
is your [\h__\h] chicken Mr Shadows
for the pinky
well done hot wings Gigi and ski Anna
you are amazing I'm very proud of you
made you conquer your fear and thank
gooda for the mental support she was
screaming with you
a little bit a little bit Yeah but
mostly good I was Brave you guys were
saying that she turned into a chicken
later on but hey she was mostly Brave
okay
I respect her and I couldn't have done
this without her so yeah she is the one
to thank
um
no no chicken
Shack Shack
Shack
chicken
[Music]
uh Patrick
not a good username Duncan jackets
monkey donkey donkeys
an awesomely unknown tank one zero zero
one dankes and Mr Cow Brown
Daniel Mason Duncan hiroshi-san Danke
Schoen muff muffins
Red Room
you sent like a million stickers thank
you Nils Astro man thank you
thank you
fried screwed on kitchen J cred for
Danke Schoen
thank you
he knows
foreign
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] what was this about
does anyone know what did I say
what did I say
um
now this was already after the game
was he about playing Outlast
playing more of it
or finishing the game maybe yeah
[Music]
oh
you guys using the eating Emoji just
because I'm like eating my
approach uh candy
um
um that burger is not that crunchy
though
um
good I was scared because Kiana was
scared
[Music]
see I really don't like
uh these games that much but but but but
if God is looking for someone to play it
and co-opt and as I said I will consider
it because good art was so helpful to me
and
yeah I'm sure there's gonna be other
people who will volunteer for it but now
I feel like it should be us too because
now we have history with the game
now she helped me get through it once
next time I will help her get through it
mine is not even coming out and yeah I'm
considerate yeah
[Music]
I don't know how to pronounce pronounce
not like foreign
[Music]
yeah I'll be her mental support we'll
support each other mentally
[Applause]
she will be so happy really
um
nice rhyme
left your panels more today oh you were
there thank you it was a fun panel yeah
yeah yeah I'm glad you were there I'm
glad you enjoyed it thank you for coming
to my stream
uh the great Billy Mays did I give you a
kiss here sure catch it come on
did you catch it
Jesus Morales thank you soon even if you
didn't catch it you gotta pick it up
quickly
from the ground it's a five second rule
Jesus Morales a girl's chicken of kfb
dangashion
uh
[Music]
um
thank you for the red super chat you
step far out of your comfort zone for
this horror game stream tangible it was
wonderfully done and you survived the
jump scares your emotional support Shack
really came through for you as well
which was much appreciated thanks for
going the extra scary mile no thank you
thank you I appreciate that that's very
kind of you I did step out far out of my
comfort zone very far very very far I
was like on a different continent for
that one thank you
[Music]
thank you
the real horror game was not Outlast it
was escaping from the usual room
hundreds of hugs and eternal love
potential oh thank you love to you too
thank you
I feel very loved
I hope you do too
my sweet sweet chicken
Corner Isle 8098
what is this Korean name
[Music]
what is his name
thank you soon
you have a great Terror scream oh do I
what do you think guys was my scream
suitable for like a horror movie
how was it
a Tiara's hated to cry I don't hate you
thank you
yeah
good to know
I
come on Google Translate
[Music]
she said
um
Hiroshi again thank you thank you thank
you thank you
kfb Chef thank you soon
oh my God Hiroshi you said like was your
YouTube bugged or why did you send 100
stickers
like a million times
pudding Channel thank you soon
[Music]
oh no
yeah
oh another one
seductions
[Music]
oh wait stop
I throw this oh
oh my God
aha what do I do
what do I do there's still so many
ah now it's only vampire left but
there's so so many
but I still need to prep
um
[Music]
but time to finish
uh two and a half hours left yeah
brah
I probably won't be streaming on Monday
uh
and I don't think I'll make the schedule
after the collab it depends on how I
feel after that
um
I will
have I am I won't stream on Monday also
just because I need to prepare for
Tuesday where I will be teaching for
dance and by German
on my channel
but I don't know maybe there will be a
gorilla
we will see there might be a little
yeah you guys already know most of the
things that I'm going to be doing next
week
but I still need to I guess maybe move
some small things around and also I'm
still waiting on
some participants for the collaboration
I'll ask the girls
and afterwards in voice chat because
then I'll have everyone together okay
little gorilla no
no a spontaneous gym perfect
it might be um Minecraft because I kind
of want to practice
um
it might just be
a Minecraft training Arc stream for like
one or two hours where I test out my
skills however it's hard to practice for
the elytra thing because I need people
to shoot me down
maybe I can find someone
maybe I'll I'll stalk the server see
when someone goes online
and that's when I start the gorilla
stream
yeah yeah yeah
I'm done how did you know
other things now and eat some food
now I know okay okay okay okay did you
hear that
what is it
[Music]
you're such a sweethearts movie
all right I'll leave it here is that
okay I wanted to finish today but not
that much time after all
I originally thought that I could
release the song a bit earlier
[Music]
oh it was a little bit of a
miscalculation on my part I apologize
sorry more than fine really thank you
it's more than okay thank you
you want to see Ian collab in two and a
half hours from now there will be more
point of views than only the Amelia one
maybe the reservations are already up uh
yeah but I mean it's not the only one
streaming I will not be streaming though
I think uh you know will be streaming
and then two girls from Council Maybe
maybe Iris as well
I won't no no we don't need every point
of view that's the thing am I was just
asking for a couple of point of views
besides her own and uh I I figured that
I don't wanna
I don't know you know being being uh
with that headset and stuff is already
challenging enough
yeah it sounds complicated maybe another
time
yeah I want to avoid the hassle I
already need to focus on setting up
everything again because I put I put all
the equipment away and now I'm trying to
figure out how it works again
there's five reservations up right now
okay so I I don't think there will be
more than that it's probably just those
five
[Music]
you can choose
which one you want to be looking at
bails fauna Iris yeah that sounds about
right
foreign
and uh trust me it's gonna be worth it
you should watch it
you should watch it yes watch it are you
gonna be there or are you gonna be
square
is
foreign
be there will be square that was the
wasn't that the joke last time
I am and forever shall be a hexagon oh
you're special aren't you
not sure because it's quite late here
that's okay you can watch the archive
but you definitely will be missing out
on some stuff
um hi okay
[Music]
I can be there as a square oh I want to
see that I would like to see that
wouldn't Ina be an octagon
interesting from a farmer
hope you have a good day too thank you
can you warn my Vlog uh no I don't think
there's any need to warn your wallet
not at this moment no no
your wallet can rest assured
by the way I've realized I mean need a
smaller wallet because my I have like a
lot of purses bags shoulder bags that
are so small they don't even fit my
wallets
I need smaller wallets
need a new Walnut I'm gonna get a new
wallet sometime soon I just have like
the typical typical size of a wallet not
the one that you fold I have the typical
wallet size but they don't fit into my
bags anymore
and I just don't want to throw my money
randomly somewhere into the little bags
a clutch I don't like clutches
foreign
I think I know what you're talking about
and I don't like that you mean those
like those little like envelope looking
bags that you just hold with your hand
no I hate that because you always have
to hold something in your hand it's
horrible horrible it looks cute but it's
like
classic girls dilemma exactly
yeah
buy bigger bags for myself no recently
I'm really into smaller bags
so I need a smaller purse a smaller
violence um
[Music]
yeah what's the point of a purse if you
can't even put your own wallet exactly
that's what I'm talking about Ohio
all right then I'll be leaving you guys
I gotta think about uh how to get food
where to get food
and what to get food
what happened to those Foods what will
happen to those foods which foods
as a cave chicken I can't understand
this
what is wallet what is purse can eat
thank you
please continue I'm watching and
listening to uh
[Music]
give me
foreign
[Music]
support and and believing in me and
supporting me with my Endeavors my song
covers my streams yay October is
freaking over oh my God it's November in
two hours for me
that's the 11th month of the year
it's almost December it's almost 2022
what's the actual [\h__\h] is going on
I just realized so no and
hey
[Music]
trick or treat guys
see you soon
bye bye see you in November yeah
2021 is like almost done oh my God
see you soon
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye thank you
thank you for watching thank you thank
you thank you thank you thank you
remember to remember remember
[Music]
um