[Music]
pap
yay
y
k Kitt W who who just syned up real hard
with me on my K ke who is that
must wait no was what what what was it
J no no on my side it was so synced up
we could have been we could have been
twins here
oh oops oh hello everybody Welcome to
the longwa
second uh outfit design stream
yay today we are designing Advent
outfits because last time we did counil
race AKA PR is now yeah and Ena of
course is again my my fashion designing
rival yes but I already has been
prepared no you can't surrender I see
you you you didn't see mine but I saw
hers and they're all good
again so good and as judges I have
invited the gorgeous and edgy looking
ladies of Advent please introduce
yourselves Nissa and she
will yeah I don't know she
she okay sh sh here at your service
archiv of Hall live follow
bye hi you Darlings this is Hell live
English Advent devilish Diva the one and
only narissa Raven craft
[Music]
kikiki
yay so yeah they're very edgy these
ladies aren't they the most edgy ones in
Advent very black and very
white
sare but will you stay monochrome with
the casual outfits that we have designed
for you I guess find out oh by the way
guys is the audio okay generally should
I make someone louder or quieter I'm I'm
kind of soft am I not I agree with
that do I get louder hello I don't know
how this stupid thing
works yeah it doesn't work this is not
how it works
here did it I get I got louder didn't I
not did I did I
not it sound the same to me no I think I
got louder at least on on obious I think
okay yeah okay okay you're good okay
okay and do you guys hear the jazz music
just checking o
Jazz you like jazz you like jazz do you
like jazz yeah they he hear it okay well
today this time we are in this
marvelous
Runway Studio wow so the ladies are
going to appear on the runway for us wow
wow make sure to clap and take some
pictures every time somebody
appears wow yeah so
marvelous who are we looking forward to
the most chat I I'm I'm personally like
I was really having issues with Shion
because I wasn't sure should I keep her
like edgy goofe or should I change her
up completely what were you
thinking it was on it was kind of the
same for me I was like do I go for for
that that contrast from her normal
outfit to the one I drew or do I want
something like similar and I I think I
found a nice midr yeah let me tell you I
think we made the same decision pretty
much um yeah I I I I will say disclaimer
these casual outfits are designed by me
and Ena and they will possibly look
nothing like these girls' uh future real
casual outfits but I'm excited to see
them
eventually I'm nervous to show
it I want to
see oh thank you okay okay I'll be
sharing the pictures with you girls on
Discord uh because we're having some
issues with screen share so discord's
fine yeah okay
um let's get started
we go who do you want to see first first
girls H
Shi Mayo maybe bi boo let's start with
bio let's start with bi I think that's a
start with okay
okay okay I actually bi is the only one
where I have two pictures uh on my side
because I made a variation of hairstyle
um but ignore that for now
okay a so
[Music]
cuteo so
cute she is uh looking beautiful on the
runway
[Applause]
yay wait I can make them enter like like
this they're coming closer and
closer they're totally walking and here
they are so right side the one of the
Buns is waa version and left side the
one of the so cute twin is version both
uh generally the f is casual we decided
on that generally like summerish casual
style so keep that in mind and just in
case if you're curious my other
variation was without the Buns C it was
actually funny Kara cuz when I was
working on the rough of like what it was
going to look like I actually want add
buns yeah that was the original design
and I was like balance wise I think twin
Tails will do so that's that's what
happened yeah that's one this looks so
cute actually while we're at it do you
want to like explain the outfit that you
have designed and talk about it yeah so
for my design I wanted to have something
very I guess like comfortable and very
loose cuz like her normal outfit is like
pretty like well her skirt is Fluffy but
like everything else is pretty like
tight ish so you know like kind of
imagining if when she's just gaming in
her room you know but I don't know if
you can see but like the socks it's not
like like opaque socks it's one of those
like kind of
seethrough ones with like the patterns
on them I thought that was kind of a
cute little touch yeah she's she's so so
so like her skin is so light that you
can barely tell but okay so those prob
but transparent okay okay cute
I think B would like this girls judges
what do you think about this bio outfit
from
Ena I think it's adorable I feel like uh
it encapsulates people's personality
pretty well this is something I haven't
seen her wear before though uh for both
sides actually so now I'm interested now
I'm interested to see it do you think
she would
like this outfit that Ena Drew like
would she would she maybe even go for
this for a casual outfit in the future
what do you think feel like she would
yeah I definitely think
so yeah it kind of has like a a gremlin
playful Vibe
yeah true true indeed okay so then I'll
explain mine a little bit and I first
started out without the without the
cardigan but then she looked kind of NY
so I gave her this cardigan that has
like this stitching of like a a frad
what do you call this like a thick Fred
on top of it embroidery yeah Embroidery
in L squiggle squiggle line and and it's
a it's a loose fluffy cardigan and then
yeah the Buns I think are a big point
and also I cut her hair short because I
thought
summertime good time for a nice change
cut it off so that it's not too hot all
the time mhm yeah and I I don't know if
you noticed but I gave her little flower
earrings and some more there's like some
pins in the Buns that are like yellow
bright yellow pins as some accessories
that if this would become life Tod she
could of course take off the accessories
and she could take off the Buns as well
of course this is
possible thinking Thinking Beyond just
the design yeah
totally and then the the Bandaids were
just there to like make the legs a
little bit more uh less boring um and
yeah some sneakers I'm really bad at
drawing feet so that they're standing up
but yeah she's wearing sneakers with
like colorful colorful little um um um
thingies h two different colors can you
see yeah very cute thank you laces yes
the shoelaces are two different colors
so um let me hear from the Judes what do
you think about this design I'm going to
put no bun bio right there as
well no bun
people love bu for it the little uh
flower earrings and I I really I
actually like the fact that you gave her
bandages or bandaids and they're
different colors it kind of reminds me
of Skittles or
something what what H reminds you of
what Skittles it's some sort of candy
that's very colorful kind of like a
rainbow oh I do know Skittles yummy
yummy yummy yeah n what do you think I
like it too uh I think I think somehow
it makes bioo come off almost a bit
older than she than she
isgeo yeah I feel like this this is
definitely like an older teenage teenage
bi boo who like in high school you know
being like I'm going for a late night
drive to get Taco
Bell yeah okay visco girl B boo I like
it visco no VIs
v s c oh visco you did what are you
spelling never mind never mind never
mind never mind mind never mind it's a
Zoomer zomer term zomer term
oh that stand for vs C I don't know I
just know what it is you just you just
use words where you don't even know what
they stand for I I know but anyways uh
they're both really good uh but kiata
you missed bio's hair antennas and it's
getting to me no that's on purpose I
know but it's getting to me the hair
antennas are just moved a little more
downwards she looks wrong without them
you know
oh I guess so now just want to give her
some some little difference cuz like she
can't have those forever in every outfit
can she you your certain age
H now we'll see if that is a a must half
point for her and I'm not sure if it is
so I just went for this okay uh cute
it's cute thank you we'll go with
scoring then you girls will give each of
these outfits uh uh one or zero I guess
to 10 score hopefully there are no
zeros and then we'll add them up so
let's start with the scoring um from I
don't know narissa to both of these
please why you got to start with me
I don't like ring things um it's
okay I feel like inas looks more like
current bio something I could see bi boo
wearing so for that I want to give it a
nine out of 10 but yours as well I also
feel like again looks like an older
version of bioo and I really like it I'm
going to give it a seven wow okay she
hates me no I I love you no don't worry
about it don't worry about I'll catch up
okay thank you very much for these
marvelous points wow
P thank you and then she will be what do
you what what points would you bless us
with oh no I too do not like to grade as
someone gred all her came here for I
guess so I guess so okay for for inoc
Sen Pi I'm giving that one probably an
eight because of its useful playful
appearance with gremlin bi boo in my
mind seven and then and then for K Kiwa
shenpai I think I I can agree with a
seven because this is older mature beo
the one who go to a Starbucks and be
like give me a cappuccino she she's
think about it doesn't she look like she
would totally be on Tik Tok which she
always is exactly right she's do Tik
Tok I don't know how Tik Tok Works me
neither me neither but this in my image
like she looks like she's on her phone
on Tik Tok the whole time to be honest
yeah I thought she'd be like on a laptop
I I like uh for Ena Senai cuz I feel
like she'd play basketball and she'd be
like a suer and meie so I find it
amusing yeah I do like the really like
loose sweater that she gave to the loose
and sporty sweater that she gave to
people I I love that looks so good on
her I hate to say the one of the things
about enas that I thought of is this
tick tocker who uh excl ly will eat food
with her sleeves covering her hands so
she'll pick it
up and I was like oh my God it's it's so
typical tip Tick Tock is is that person
even good at that or are they failing at
eating things they're they're eating
like a Pixar character so really
dramatically and like getting like pizza
sauce all over their sleeves it's so bad
so that's what it made me think of did
you find that or does biu send you these
wings no sadly someone else sent that to
me and I regret having seen
it oh yeah the many many regrets of the
internet wow VI good job on the runway y
good
job so cute good job fashion designers
oh yeah thank you oh thank you thank you
the triple bi boo will now
leave while walking backwards bi Boo and
her
clones and at the end of the they they
just strike a post one more time at the
end of the walk and then they go out
this way disappear yeah disappear byebye
people bye bye she was Moon walking
she's just she just has the skills man
she's a dancer
wow Sick Style all
right who should we go for
next who next what you want you guys did
fua Moko separately right yeah yeah I
mean both of us made outfits that match
them like they're matching each other
but we will show it I was going to show
them separately and rate them separately
I
guess I think we should do fuaa okay
fuaa okay I do want to show them
together as well but I guess yeah let's
start with fuaa I'll send you girls the
picture oh you'll see both of mine
actually immediately but okay I have
them separated on OBS
okay
a that's
adorable wait I have to
[Music]
start your Entrance B so
cute we both were not brave enough to
changed their like theme colors and kept
them blue and pink mostly M yes so uh
you know started first so now I'll start
with my explanation um you will see
later on but I I made M more like a
tomboyish style and and sporty style so
I wanted to contrast that with fua being
more like the lady like girly one a
little bit more mature too taking care
of her sister so yeah she has I think
she has a Vibe she has also fishtail
fluffy fishtail braids if that says
anything to the
audience and um yeah big big a little
bit slightly uh seethrough because the
fabric is so so so thin uh dress with
some laces on the bottom some cute jeans
uh fabric platform heels H and the
jacket is also jeans because it's
matching with her sister and a nice
little brown bag just you know add a
little maturity there and bring some
stuff along and yeah and also her bangs
also are a point because it's really
fluffy like a sheep I was thinking of
water to miss a little bit when I was
drawing that cute yay y yay yeah yeah
when there's sunlight from the back I
think then you can kind of see her legs
shine through that's what said just last
oh really oh
really oh I didn't think of that I just
picked it up from the chat right now
yeah okay so that's my uh thoughts
behind that Ena would you like to share
your thoughts well
um for casual like outfit I wanted to do
something that was kind of like easy to
move around in at the same time I think
F was I wanted to be more on the
slightly elegant side like with the
Frills and the loish slightly as opposed
to it makes sense what you see M I think
yeah yeah okay um and it's like I want
it to be kind of like the overalls like
feeling but then um you know who I was
mid is a little bit thicker so if you
wear overalls it's not as
like I think cute in my opinion so I
changed the thing so it's only like the
straps and then she's wearing like the
jeans no I think it
perfectly yeah perfectly perfectly works
I also like the blouse you combined it
with but I am not the judge so do not
listen to what I have to say uh let's
listen to what sh has to say about how
about just give me your ideas for both
for both yeah just I I like uh the left
one because to me I see huaa as sort of
a sadistic Ona type oh oh who who likes
to sort of tease Moco so this Cates her
playfulness and it's a little bit more I
guess I guess uh it's also the big
sister feels for it the right one I feel
like this is the huaa who is more on
going on a date yeah
rather sister so it really depends on a
scenario but I like I like both of them
M okay okay and Nissa so they're both
tied for me for different reasons okay
so kiata managed to C uh capture the uh
fluffiness of fua perfectly I was trying
to do yeah yeah the fluffiness like the
bangs are so fluffy the hair the
fishtail braids are so fluffy she just
has this very fluffy feeling about herk
that is just so cute to me meanwhile I
agree with Shi that I feel likea really
captured that kind of uh more uh teasing
on kind of feeling that F also has um so
as to where kiata really captured the
fluffiness of huaa you know really
captured the
sadistic okay okay that's what you all
have to say then we shall proceed to the
rating already I
guess then
FY give me the
points okay give me the math I give a
nine for innocent pie nine wait 17 + 9
uh 26 26 26 amazing thank you I can M
wow I give a seven for K and Pie that's
thank you I can do that math myself
quick MTH thank you okay and then
Thea maybe maybe you can 10 for both I
really really like them 10 out of 10 10
out of 10 so you like really
really I wonder what Fu would think I
I'm really curious I want to hear all of
advent's opinions later
on yeah
okay 36 versus 31 we're really still
close I got a ketchup I got a ketchup
I'm telling you K yours is so good I
love the dress and the jacket like
that's that's something I'll totally
wear you know honestly thinking of
something for f is pretty difficult for
me because you have to think of like
kind of two outfits that match each
other but still are different in like
showing their personality and all that
at the same time so like showing showing
similarities and Sim similar what
differences and similarities is is
difficult and then keeping the colors
cuz I I don't know I I was lowkey
considering to change the blue pink to
for example like green and yellow or
orange and yellow or red and green or
whatever like give them different color
things themes right I think about that
but I don't know what their preference
would be so I went for the safe one just
kept it somewhat bluish somewhat yeah I
like how you gave her a little bracelet
and at the end of the dress there's like
a little uh blue ruffle at the end
of wanted to add some detail well thank
you very much then that completes uh
Fu's fashion show off but fua would you
would you mind staying on the side a
little bit so that we can look at your
sister kind of nearby thank you yes yes
yes C
time okay she'll she'll like I don't
know go go go like in the middle in the
front here be small okay and then I
guess we'll go straight to Mo
Coco Mo Coco Mo Coco Mo Coco bow bow can
I get a bow bow Applause for
M wait I didn't send you Ina one yet
I'm watching the screen there you go so
we both kind of went for somewhat tomboy
at least compared to
fuaa and yeah interesting let's start
with ena's
comments so so as you can see from both
of the design by um theme for their
alfit was overalls so you know um fuas
is a skirt overall but you know m is
like shorts still um I try to make it I
guess cute and her t-shirt it's it's a
important thing that she's she's she has
like the one falling off yeah cuz she's
like very playful and you know she moves
around a lot yeah kind of like that cute
you know you have no idea how close I
was to giving her overalls too something
about her really right yeah she should
have overalls in the future Moco Moko we
recommend these fashionistas here
recommend you overalls for the future
okay are you hearing this paw
bow yeah uh anything else you want to
comment I like I like that you gave her
loose socks because that suits her so
well yeah I was going to give her just
like normal socks but I was like I need
more silhouette in the design so I was
like loose socks it
is throw on some ribbons yes many
ribbons ribbons ribbons always help okay
cute and I see you kept her hair length
pretty much the same we both yeah just
put a little more more on the pigtails
or twin Tails I don't know what to call
those side Tails fill them out yeah half
half twin half twin Tails I would say oh
okay and then for me um well I'm
matching it to fuaa so they're kind of
like jeansy casual summer outfit and um
pretty simple because I I felt like I
want to see them in some in some more
simplistic clothes and I gave them both
braids if you've noticed but M has like
uh like outwards bent small braids
from The Fluffy
ones and then also yeah platform jeans
heels but hers are a little bit
different design so you can see her toes
toe friends everybody we we're the toe
appreciators ehh I know you're there
somewhere and you got a tight uh skirt
but it's inside is connected with shorts
of course so that it gives Mobility yes
yes and now let's put them next to each
other cuz I think it's kind of
important to
see
uh how they look together ah
cute there's so
cute
cute really
quick two times F oh my
God they're not twins anymore they're
what do you call them quadruplets yeah
wow we got CR blets
[Music]
now okay let's hear uh about moco's
outfit from narissa please okay so I I
really feel like ena's really perfectly
encapsulates M Go's energy yes um
it's it definitely I can see the careful
care in the like certain details that
just really screams the M um I also
really like yours kiata but I don't know
why because I just can't see Moco in a
skirt no she will skirts I know totally
real but I can't I can't see my pure
puppy wearing a it's a scir scir you
know but just from looks I'm not looking
up her skirt you know to find out that
it's a skirt so I do not believe
that I
would wow but um I still really like it
and I I like the hairstyle for example I
like how you matched it with Hua was and
I like the style of the braid uh for it
as as well I feel like it that releases
uh Moko um it looks like uh fuaa took a
lot of time and Moko is like we got to
run we got to
go so it really fits her personality too
so I really like them
both okay okay she what do you
say I like uh innocent Pi in terms of
playfulness but I also can't quite
imagine her wearing it because it makes
her look more of a maybe more useful
than
how she would like to bebe really you
think so you think she wants to be more
mature I feel like for like sometimes
she wants to be the older one so H
doesn't tee me as much it's really cute
though so for this one I actually prefer
uh kiaha Senpai simply because I feel
like I could see this makoko and she'd
be glaring at you yeah she' be glaring
at you she'll be with her dog shirt and
be like come on we got to go now
and oh interesting I guess they they do
have that kind of
dynamic to be honest I I can like see
them in both of these outfits easily um
maybe even like personally I would
probably see that ena's designs are like
even more so like they scream for a m um
and I I just wanted to like go a little
bit away from that and then give them a
new look but like totally like the fu
moko casual
outfit yeah perfect
Perfection uh okay so then I guess let's
go for the individual M rating police
fromi we okay I'll give this one 7 for
inocent pie it's really cute I like it
but I can't imagine it as my my
imaginary Moco in my head like my
version of her and then for K wa wait is
that that
44 no 36 + 7
[Music]
yeah
oh 43 43
4 we M can we took us a
while don't don't talk about it we
totally didn't look at you okay okay
okay okay okay and then the next math
one should be easier for
you um um nine points for W cuz I like
her hair a lot and I also find the shirt
really funny thank you I didn't know
what honestly I was like I want to put
some kind of design on the shirt but I
had no idea so I just wrote dog well
didn't doubt put
a it's so like on the nose I am a dog
and B onina shirt
B great t-shirt
designs hey that's that's how you do it
pography yeah no they're great like and
I think they would wear them so
yeah thank you SI for your points than
you and then let's go to no what do you
say being judged is
suffering judging is
suffering uh I'm going to have to give
enas a 10 out of 10 again cuz I just
like it I just have to dock you one
point though kiata and give you a nine
out of 10 oh you're going to make my map
in the next turn the difficult man I'm
sorry oh what what's the the the docking
is the skirt yeah damn I damn I just
can't I'm sorry I will at this very
moment I should give moku a call and ask
her if she would wear skirts I sure she
would but I just I'm not ready for it
you
know you're not ready for to grow up and
we my o sunart would you wear
skirts uh answer me once you see this
okay answer immediately
actually T huaa they'll respond faster
really I mostly get the actually that's
pretty Bal but mostly from moku I get
the answers M oh interesting oh but I
have a group with both of them
so whoever sees it will answer okay no
it's fine I'll take the minus point but
eventually you you if muku says she
likes skirts a lot then she might you
might have my heart will be
broken no that's fine it it's up so
fast what okay uh no problem I'll take
it like a like a champ and now we get
rid of these quadruplets was nice having
double f for a little while
Goode pepperoni
you know I saw something funny um uh
there's someone who counts who's Bow
bows ever
since and it's actually insane amount of
bow bows it's crazy can you imagine how
much more it would be if they were
quadruplets double
amount not even I don't even think it
would be exactly a double because dogs I
feel like they bark more the more dogs
are in the room and just because it's
double I don't think yeah I think it was
just like maybe like double point
something like it's not an even doublez
I think what if it's exponential like
yes x amount of dogs in the room yeah
you shall bow bow exponential yes for
the last
time yeah crazy B
residence bow bow overload let's let's
get the bow bows out of here goodbye by
goodbye cute they looked really cute on
the runway yay and now the ones we have
left over are the judges so this is
going to look really interesting from
here out what they say about what we
were designing for them cuz now it's
getting personal
here really do you pick you pick no no
you pick who do you want to see next you
me I think Rea should go
first I'm nervous about n
house okay I'm
excited I really like the
one I don't want to show it show it do
it
now uh okay give me give me
okay
Enter
oo
wow wow
cute
wow
I difficult
difficult
I Ena Drew her more girl like elegant
girly and I drew her more elegant and
stylish I think so well we won't know
what n's preferences until later on but
you know go ahead and talk about the
outfit you have designed so I want to go
for I guess like a more formal but like
kind of like the rich Ooa of shopping in
the mall like picking out all the you
know like the brand like shop not
shopping bags like bag like makeup bags
and she looks kind Rich you know yeah I
was like debating like if I should add
like nice sleeves to that but I was like
that's that's more formal attire yeah
but then like but it's it's like summer
casual you know sleep's kind of hot and
like I feel like if you wear that jacket
like on your shoulders it like contrasts
like the skin on your arms I was like
okay I'll will leave that but yeah very
nice very elegant oh God damn it Ena you
do it every time you just nail it every
time and her hair you just like really
Loosely curled it I guess yeah cuz like
her her hair in her um normal outfit is
like very straight you know goes down
pretty pretty long but I was like you
know you need those like the rich oosa
you know like loose curls kind of
flowing in the wind kind of feel so I I
went for that nice very pretty she's so
pretty yeah so um for me I gave myself
quite a challenge because um I had a
certain certain type of top in mind a
certain type of pattern I don't know if
there's you know do you know a name for
this crop top crop top no not not the
shape more like the fabric and the
coloring like I've seen this before and
I wanted to recreate it and it was
almost tie dye yeah yeah mesh tie dye
yeah and it's also kind of like sea
fruit so underneath there's a like like
a um a type of bra that it's okay to
show like lowkey lace and and also I'm
imagining like a velvet type of fabric
on the bra underneath um of course it's
a
bralette very
comfortable but yeah so it's like it's
very stylish and fashionable crop
top that should be very very airy in the
summer o yeah and and the jeans was
difficult to decide but I ended up
giving you like more like loose but not
too loose somewhat loose baggy jeans
with some lace at the bottom and Lace in
the pockets um and some nice black
saddles to make it a little bit more
elegant same with the bag I gave you a
little bag with some gold chains if you
can see I thought gold would would match
quite while overall so also big hoop
golden uh earrings and this is like I
think Lissa could Rock a lot of
different styles so I'm not saying like
this is the only thing I can imagine you
with at all it's difficult actually you
would look good in
anything but I wanted this is the first
thing that came to my mind and yeah
little choker of course because I'm sure
you enjoy a nice choker
so and so immediately I want to hear
from yeah sh first
yeah um I I really like inoc senp Design
This is the the Resa I would would have
on my piano and I would take her home to
show off to my parents yeah I mean
yeah and I really like the the color
scheme it's just like you know it's very
fancy I really like preppy outfits and
then the the kiaha Senpai this is Thea I
would not take home to my parents I
would meet her at a club she would offer
me a drink and I can't I have to be like
I can't I'm a good church girl church
girl wow I do this is like the the
mature version of Risa that's a little
bit more too mature yes yes I wanted her
to be mature yeah
yeah yeah she also looks like a Tik
tocker though I got to say yeah she does
she does B and narissa the perfect Tik
Tok
couple I'm the Tik Tok mom yeah I feel
like I feel like Nera like Kiara's
outfit you could tottally be like one of
those like dancing Tik Tok
oh yeah yeah like
yeah oh you'd be the mom selling the
pink sauce yeah oh my
God get out of here pink sauce don't
don't don't don't worry about it wor
about it is like all of Advent on Tik
Tok besides foko maybe yeah probably oh
my God it's like the Tik Tok
generation no wonder this is the
generation that has birthed the
the song that shall not
[Laughter]
beide these damn ticktockers
yeah tumers okay uh whatever the pink
sauce is we will never know narissa it
is
time you must share your fault I'm sorry
I do have a preference here um I
knowa I don't know how you read me for
Filth cuz this is 100% something that
that I've worn
before yeah no this is my
fashion maybe mine is the socks but I
actually have shoes exactly like that
that I wear out
of well I guess my mom will like
youra yeah um I I like dresses I like
skirts um and I actually do uh like 80s
Blazers and draping them over like that
so I feel really
attacked
it's very classy um Kiana with yours I
really love the accessories and I love
what you did with the hair but um I
don't wear pants yeah I know but it's
time maybe just you know for a little
bit of image change just for one day to
show off your other side your stylish
side oh my stylish side you can't make
me wear pants I I
are pants are difficult but I didn't
want to give everybody a skirt so you
had to be the one cuz I think with your
long legs you look good in pants yeah
yeah but like not
jeans
oh jeans you want some sea leggings HH
where I can see your Fong
fruit I don't wear underwear what do you
mean oh my God my mama cannot
accept she does wear underwear she
showed me the ones she bought H don't
tell them that
I already told them yesterday it's too
late I can't believe you um as for the
top uh I wouldn't wear something like
that personally but uh it's something my
sister would wear you it it's it's not
it's not a bad look but just not
something that I would personally wear
okay if it I agree it feels very mature
in a way that if I wore it out I'd be
like I'm so embarrassed I hope people
aren't looking at everybody's gonna hit
on
you especially me no good that's
acceptable okay okay no I understand
totally uh it's it's kind of difficult
to like read you like without like
seeing your casual clothing choices
before it was difficult to read cuz you
look good in anything I think in my
opinion M thank you get a
room we we are we are getting a room
yeah okay
we already got it she's got to reach it
soon
soon okay then uh let me hear those
points you
we uh 10 for Ena Senpai oh she got
so many
T
yeah and then and then eight for kiaha
Senpai because pink sauce mom is funny
what understand the word you're saying
don't worry about it don't worry about
it teach me later
please thank you that's not too bad I
feel like narissa will give me less than
seven points what do you think Nissa uh
10 out of 10 for
[Music]
Ena I forgot to mention the the stripes
on the dress there's five lines cuz it's
like the music oh my
god
wow you didn't even have to but you made
it even better
now oh
um and kiata for your efforts I will
give you an eight which is going to
bring you up to
65 that like you extremely biased but
I'll take that biased you got one oosi
point yeah i' I've worked hard I've
worked hard in my life to reach this
point of in my life and get girls like
you to Oshi me so I'll take it I'll take
the bias I deserve it
thank you than you thank you
yay
cute yes oh my God the last one already
I'm so
sad I know we got this quick she is
making an exit just like she made her
entrance goodbye narissa strike a
POS and
then oh there she goes oh she's so
beautiful I'll remember her
forever she's not
dead she's right here
now I think we're all really curious
about the sh we
W yeah I have to say from all of Advent
shi's default outfit by default already
is way more casual than the other Advent
members you know what I
mean it already kind of looks like a
casual outfit so it was um interesting
to go even more casual from there cuz
like narissa looks like very fantasy
style and from too B too shy what do you
say saying I'm like Hot Topic girl yeah
exactly you're already like casual Hot
Topic by default so let's make you even
more Hot Topic if we can I'll be hotter
topic a hotter
topic all right here are the
designs
t
cool
oh
cute I was really contemplating like
maybe like complet giving you giving you
a completely different style but thank
God I didn't because then the writing
would have been difficult cuz now we're
both uh staying with the usual Hot Topic
edgy golf girlfriend style very good
very good very good Ena with the glasses
yeah the glasses art
there is a reason for this though it's
foul play but okay uh glasses are
versatile so tell me about the
versatility of this outfit Ena so I
didn't want to lean like all the way
into a Hot Topic oh cuz I kind of wanted
kind of like the slightly nerdy you know
like I totally see you in the library
kind of I like that yeah yeah still a
little bit of Hot Topic in there nerdy
was my
it's too good it's too
good damn it okay more tell me more is
that a belly button
window um kind of
yes I don't see the belly button I
didn't
draw but then like okay so like you know
if you've gone to Hot Topic they sell
like the edgy stuff but they also sell
like the cute character stuff so I
wanted I wanted to add that as like the
bag you know like
yeah you're killing me you
[Music]
know so cute I also like the the he like
H cut kind of that you gave her uh for
the side thingss really nice oh yeah and
the and the ponytail of course
ponytail very versatile as well all
right okay okay and one specifically one
loose
sock
yes it definitely it looks like she
would like it SC uh I went for not nerdy
more like uh Kpop golf
girlfriend
uh yeah I'm scared I really like the top
I design for her though I wanted to add
some patterns for this and so we went
for check check check checker board
checker board
checkboard
checkerboard which one is it
checkerboard checkerboard yeah check
check her out check this check her out
wow it is and then if you notice there's
some cute little fake tattoos one on her
waist and one on her thigh on the
opposite side little heart tattoos that
make your eyes go there
both places I'd like to put my
fingers I don't know if she will allow
that she probably will will she will she
sh sh would you allow it what looking at
my belly button
or your tattoos yeah on the
tattoos oh I'm not sure yeah think about
it oh yeah I'll think about it I'll
consider
it gift and because of her um split hair
colors I thought twin Tails will look
really cute and I love ber personally
and I just fought Beret with like low
sitting twin Tails it's just perfect
combination and just generally Beret
just looks good with everything so it's
a little fuzzy H felt FY uh Beret so she
gets a French Vibe I think from that
yeah platform heels little little bit
sefr uh black socks and a belt that is
like silver uh with heart heart shape in
the middle mhm yes eh okay I'm scared
let's start with
Nissa uh they're both really good
actually in different ways uh so
obviously ena's really really
encapsulates uh shor's nerdiness cuz
let's be real Shori is a nerd at
heart um she definitely looks like that
hot girl you'd see at the library but
then you find out she's working there
part time and so she's always shushing
you but like you're like trying to talk
to her because you're like obsessed with
her and like really that was her
intention all along but like you know
like that's just five that she giv whole
novel right
here I swear I I agree with your
assessment of yours Kata I love Beret
first off so I love seeing sh in a beret
and with twin Tails a little bit of a
different different hairstyle than she
usually has and something I hadn't
imagined her with but I think fits her
really well and
further shows off the split tone of her
hair so is very cut off um I love the
top I love the shoulder I'm not crying I
just have something in my eye just
saying okay don't
cry I I love the off the-shoulder look
um I feel like overall the outfit really
really fits shote and it's really sexy
so I really like
that like it's similarly to what Shori
said to me I feel like this is the
shiori I'd meet at a club and then be
like oh this is the bad girl I shouldn't
get involved with she's gonna ruin my
life no she will make your life better
because it's already ruined mhm this is
a St I look at and go I can fix her she
will fix you she may look like you have
to fix her but no she will fix
you she can fix
me okay that sounds pretty positive for
both of
them she won
we it's okay you can be honest she will
we go innocent place I think C is really
cute I like the the cross body bag
because it's like a little mascot
character I I think it's York or maybe
it's just like a yeah yeah yeah BL okay
okay and I like the little hair
accessory you gave and it does exude
comfiness oh that I can appreciate for
kiaha Senpai I like your Sal okay number
one I have actually really like the a
brace I say it so I I like collecting
them if I can me to me too yeah and then
I also like the the pigtails and how you
presented the hair so it's a little bit
more for noticeable and then for the top
it looks very comfy I actually really
like the checkered pattern than you put
on
there I
would go ahead I'll I'll comment after
go ahead I'm I'm not the type to show
off my belly button like a a Shameless
Moco but I think it's a very cute outfit
it's it's less visible your belly button
is less visible on my outfit actually
because it's just the beginning like the
kind of like the you know
where how to say the bottom of the rib
cage yeah that's true but I would get
cold but it's more visible on Eno's
outfit because there's a a huge hole
right where the belly button would be
yeah just CL into belly buttons you just
spin the skirt around
and there that is actually so cute and
such a fashion designer thing to do to
make it two
ways yeah that's want Dr your belly
button perfect don't feel like it turn
it around you can even have it sideways
I mean oh maybe I just put a sticker on
a belly button or
something oh yeah I mean oh a stop
sign or just put a put a pacifier into
your belly button a pacifier you think
it's going to suck on the
pacifier depends on how deep your belly
button is guess I guess so I guess
so I don't know sorry weird it's like
it's like how you put a plug in your
bathtub so the water fills up right so I
don't know that's how I imagine it you
think you think my belly button is like
a Vortex to another dimension like a
shadow realm they access the void
through the no no no no no no no vort is
it is it is it a Vortex to another
dimension we'll have to find out if you
have
pacifier The Pacifier will close it so
it's currently open unless you have a
pacifier inside now I guess so so it's
currently
open okay this is getting weird so uh
were you done with commenting on it yes
I believe so okay then we shall start
with nissa's
rating I'm weak I'm weak to both of them
so I I am inclined give you both a 10
out of 10 because they're very different
but they're very good in the same
different ways you know what I mean I
would take both of these shiori on
different dates yes it's like it's like
a story where like you first meet her in
the library when she's wearing like the
outfit on the left then when you go on a
date she comes up wearing the outfit on
the right yeah exactly and then you're
just down bad you
know I understand yes okay so wait are
you saying you are giving us both 10
points yeah ah yeah okay I can that map
thank you thank
you and
then see we you are the last one to
judge and it's your outfit the last one
standing I give eight points to innocent
pie eight points that's
91 mhm and then and then I give 10
points to kiaha some
time thank you wow wow wow
okay
yay wonderful oh and we should upload
all of these on Twitter afterwards
because they're
awesome they turned out so good wait can
I fit everybody on the stage at the end
can I do that I'll try here we have to
make them a bit
smaller T if you guys really enjoyed
this stream remember we do have uh like
a promised version of this it's pretty
old pretty long time ago but uh you can
look it up on on the YouTube and find it
there oh this is difficult oh like
this people the first one we judged
today for some reason there's three of
them let me get rid of which one buns or
no buns what's
better no buns no bu no buns really
okay well she can you know she can
change every day depending on no it's
like she clipped down her little hair
antennas with the
pin yeah cute oh small people can stay
small I
accurate cute where is my narissa ah oh
no I moved the screen therea is like
somewhere behind you behind why did I
put you there come
here nice oh the elegant beautiful lady
oh very tall tall
she will Tower over Advent like
this two mommies accurate two mom and
the rest of nice okay this is the Advent
casual out design stream hope you guys
enjoyed that but at the very end I mean
this is perfect timing so let's
advertise yeah girls Advent girls talk
to me about it tell me about it what's
happening what's happen coming on the
first all of Advent is going to be
debuting our new first uh new outfits
which are our New Year's outfits of
course that's the the in two days or so
yeah very soon oh my God indeed
exciting
yay wa all right you guys are doing it
in is this debut order yep oh okay so sh
bio weisa foko and each stream is half
an hour and then you do a collab too
yeah oh
wow New Year looking forward to it
you're following the tradition everybody
gets New Year's outfits in haai yeah and
that will be our first matching outfits
you
know yeah we can match with the rest of
us we can
fit never we all want to wear kimonos
this it'll be really fun yes can't wait
you know did you see them yet cuz I saw
them
no I I want after the stream after the
stream yeah of course not
now actually before we end I have one
one more question for Shi that I was
really curious about when I was drawing
these
outfits I mean you don't you don't have
to spoiler it but would you like
consider in the future like doesn't
matter if it's casual outfit or Like An
Elegant outfit or whatever will you ever
stray away from the golf look or do you
think you'll keep it forever oh I I'm
like diverse I'll wear whatever as long
as it looks good oh nice cuz I do want
to see you in different styles I think
that would be really nice and honestly
when you stream for such a long time
like it's it's nice having different
styles for different streams different
games to match the game and all that so
you should you should aim for variety in
my
opinion
gok pink wear Beret and everything oh
yeah
fits every style literally every style
maybe one day we can get like girly
imagine like what what my fua was
wearing imagine shy in like a sundress
summer sundress like that yeah that is
actually like uh my typical fashion so
it makes sense oh really oh
cute yeah that would be wonderful I'm
looking forward to all the outfits that
Adent is going to bless us with hope you
guys enjoyed these cutie patootie design
designs from us and yeah make sure to
check out the kimonos
from and I just want to say quick thanks
to the fashion designers for taking time
with Advent to make pretty outfit you're
welcome yeah I hope you guys enjoyed it
like so
happy literally I needed you girls to
join just so that I can make part two of
The
[Music]
Stream cuz I was looking forward to it
eventually the more Generations we get
the more of these we will make Ena right
yeah of
course Ena do you have a last comment
about today's
stream uh thanks so much again wa for
inviting me for round two of our
designing I always like designing new
outfits and stuff too so it's a lot of
fun so good yeah I want to hire you can
I hire you for my new outfit
I mean it it can be discussed if you
really want but yeah maybe I
will I'll just do the design someone
else can Joy ah okay okay yeah
understandable yeah oh you're welcome it
was nice having you again Ina thank you
for taking time yeah thank you
again I always I had so much fun I hope
we can do another one someday I like
seeing like different visions of people
for these outfits like you know we we
kept a lot of the the color themes are
similar but you know pastel colors and
black and white golf colors and this and
that but yeah different Visions for
different people it's nice seeing that
she won me she won me give me a last
comment thank you for inviting me I love
your outfits this was super fun to be a
part of and I hope you had a good
holiday and you'll have a great New Year
you too happy holidays did you have
happy holidays Shi we yeah I got to see
my parents so I'm pretty happy
nice yeah continue and joy them when are
you coming
back in a few days few days so I'll say
okay finally she will Nissa misses you I
think yeah I know I know
she that was the most sad year I heard
like she only on the scale of of 1 to 10
how clingy is never
saw I I don't know actually I I never
really thought I I never stopped to
think about it and grade it you know I
just accept it I thought you would give
it an immediate
10 think she's
capable how clingy is she
yes
yes okay and Nissa you kind of already
said some things but please go ahead and
say goodbye to me and all of the others
thank you guys for coming to today to
see our Advent fashion show drawn by
these lovely Senai I hope you all had
fun and thank you for inviting
me y you're welcome I love you girls
you're so cute you're all so
cute cute
cute now stop using Tik Tok so much okay
I actually don't use Tik Tok
okay then you have to cut off the source
where it's coming from YouTube YouTube
YouTube godam it I'm recting YouTube We
Can't Stop
YouTube okay everybody thanks for
watching I guess this was my last stream
actually for this year holy um cuz
I'm not streaming tomorrow uh I'll see
you the first and I will put up a
schedule um tomorrow I
guess yeah oh my God it's so sad what
the end of
2023 goodbye
2023 no no no no this is weird no it
can't be the last one e
I'll see you next year K yeah see you
next year 202 see next you'll be there
right you signed up for it
right did you all sign up for 2024 oh
God wait no I need to quick return in my
application form there's an
deadline deadline yeah and did you meet
it was it it was it's um uh actually uh
midnight of the 31st oh gosh okay okay I
still make it I can still make it yeah
we got this and make sure to press send
okay okay okay I'll make maybe 5 Seconds
early before midnight so that it has
time to like go through the internet oh
yeah there there's loading time that's
right yes
is doesn't it renew automatically no you
have to sign up for it the times have
changed because some some humans sueded
the world and the time for renewing
automatically it's not okay no oh no
where's my prepa pre sign up 2024 no
times have changed in know you have to
you have to you know follow the time the
flow of time I don't want to grow up
you're already grown up you
know don't worry about okay okay okay
okay guys say
Z and in German we also
say
good can you guys repeat
that
said what say y happy New Year happy New
Year happy New Year byebye bye-bye by
[Music]
bye