hello everybody and welcome to the
cheering guide for favor 9 my latest
single stream it stream it stream fifa
night uh for this once again we will
need the light sticks yes one is enough
two is even better some people even have
a bazillion but yes this is what we're
using so
make sure to have it ready if you don't
have any that's okay too
all right
let's go
through tonight
i
[Music]
club
club club
hi
[Music]
baby
feel it right through me
say
intoxicating dj keep playing
wow
i
club
[Music]
clap
do you feel the music baby
[Music]
come alive
freestyle by the way
feel it rise through me
[Music]
crazy yeah with them
baby
[Music]
oh no
feel it rise through me
[Music]
but the sound i'm making
i
hi
by the way just in case if you're
wondering it doesn't matter if you say
oi or high or a it's basically the same
thing so you can mix it up with whatever
feels more comfortable to you
and all the stuff that i was saying like
intoxicating do you think you playing or
feel it right through me and also baby
all these parts i would like you guys to
join in with me and yell it out loud all
right you got me
alright then please don't catch a fever
but i'll see you at fever night yay
thank you