[Music]
thank you
I'm in the main gaming screen but it's
full of the screen and there's just no
no options just play
do I get the option later
because every time I Tab out it closes
the game just sucks
[Music]
I don't want to start a cutscene you
know okay
I didn't want to start any special
cutscene
well
I don't need to be with distance under
detail distance
on or off
oh it's on right now
turn it off okay night Shadows on
High Shadow quality very oh my God is
very high
oh texture only High I did the thing the
thing the setting somebody recommended
me
uh where is
[Music]
thank you
subtitles on radar on HD on weapon
Target complex
I guess they cycle complex weapon Target
I don't know what that is
[Music]
basic okay because it was complex by
default
oh
[Music]
what is it for
handbrake can
but there's no Window mode where is
Window mode
[Music]
what why the [\h__\h] is there in a window
mode every time I tap out okay whatever
okay
I guess so
I mean certain games you can kind of
force into Window mode
and if they put it this is this is uh
this this is not so old it's from 10 10
because it's the definite definitive
complete edition or whatever
every time I change the scene in OBS and
so on
[Music]
if they put it onto steam they should
make a window mode implement
the [\h__\h]
yeah that was just yesterday
[Music]
oh well well okay well yeah that's fine
I just uh
every time I tap out
[Music]
super shy super shine
I was up everybody
um
hi
Kitty
key there you go
uh
let me go back okay
oh welcome to the Social Club is this
the anti-social Social Club
hi oh my God we're going to play a new
GTA
hey let's go oh my God it's already like
ah it gives me like the art style the
logo gives me nostalgia
to GTA 5 though
[Music]
city is the land of opportunities really
really is that what they call it ah [\h__\h]
wait okay
uh let me test something
okay
well first of all
um I mean
you didn't hear that
[Music]
oh
did that did you hear that
[\h__\h] hell a window mode why you no
exist still no
you heard that one I'm sure you heard
that one
everybody's like talking about bowling
bowling bowling
really low yeah I mean it's low for me
too
thank you
oh did that turn it up for you guys too
no only for me okay
well I can I can maybe turn it up
it's just that man you sound it's
probably fun
GPS speech
Independence
what is this
I don't know what this is
bowling bowling let's go not balling
kiwawa will be bowling not balling radio
I didn't make any custom radio yet
maybe
um next time although for GTA 5
throughout my whole series we were
always talking about maybe making our
own radio and ah eventually we did but I
also enjoyed just driving without any
sound a lot of the time
um
[Music]
okay so uh in I have my new graphic card
in 4080 but uh yeah we couldn't solve
the issue
but I'm using my temporary solution for
now
uh it's fine I just can't put on any
attachments but besides that it's like
whatever
yeah yeah it's fine it's fine
all the good songs are removed anyway a
yell
that stinks nah it's fine though yeah
um
not that the graphic card will be much
shown off today in this game but I don't
know
no no
first scene is sword on never mind it
will be fine
yeah guys feel free to warn me whenever
something you buy is about to show up
you you warned me in GTA 5 too and if
something was ever really that bad
in GTA 5 though
um there's no nudity in this game okay
then we're probably good uh and it's not
monetized anyway the streams are my GK
four strings will not be monetized there
will not be super chats you guys can
send membership stuff you want
um and yeah I don't think I can play the
copy write it music no gotta be careful
with that
and uh why not what because I can't no I
never we cannot monetize GTA games
that's fine though I'm happy I can play
it in the first place
and this will be a series we're also
playing tomorrow and then then there
will be a little break because I'm busy
yeah it will probably be uh two two week
break
so I know it's kind of awkward but I
wanted to do something this weekend so
here we are to get into the game let's
have fun
what's what's going on
now I understand the edit that Co Karen
made
[Music]
somebody's getting spanked
that kind of oh ah why is it leggings
ignore him come on the [\h__\h] why is my
OBS lagging so much
oh it's better now
did you see that leg
technician
s too much for the 4080
[Music]
[\h__\h] why is it lagging
can my 4080 knob handle it
like they say it is the land of
opportunity
a nice place a house
a dream like my cousin oh yeah and the
right one is Nico right
but no no wait they're not none of them
are Nico he writes me
and they have to write not into trouble
I thought maybe uh today and I got these
kick and I spent the next seven months
with you fine that's Nico
whoa diamonds
birthday cake
diamonds are the birthday cake
so yeah eat some damn things got
involved with some idiots we all do dumb
things that's what makes us human
I can't change any settings now so we
have to deal with this leg
[Music]
well New York New York
I've never been to New York I have to go
to New York
[Music]
this music is making me feel like I'm
like a gangster
yeah
why are they speak in German oh because
they're tourists not because my game is
in German right
okay
did I mess something up my game's in
English as far as I know
man
[Music]
women
what you got two women damn Sons I got
more than two mommies
I got all the mommies baby
what's going on just take over the world
someplace else
they know best
shoes
god I already talked about Serbian
language so against their serbians
is this original music
[Music]
no
should be
okay can I play this music I don't even
give a [\h__\h]
[Music]
their own music
I would stay in broker [\h__\h] standoff
[\h__\h]
can somebody tell me if they know if
this is the music that you know
[Music]
he'll teach you all right
it is copyright what do I do then I
guess whatever
too late now
are there any that are like copyright
friends
[Music]
Oh What A vibe
is that raggy
[Laughter]
self-actualization well actually
I will have thousands more like them
next time on I'm rich
I'm rich only on
empty
hey rectum or what
time of my life
and it never felt this way before
oh
okay I gotta make my own radio but for
now I guess we're turning it off again
sorry
that's I don't know the music really
only the radio
is this anyway
yeah we can play classic music it's been
too long you should have come out
earlier the subtitles are a little bit
low
I I can I can do this
we're still optimizing everything oh my
God history is women too yes but only
locals here we have white black the
Puerto Ricans and the Asians Europeans
on vacation scared Canadians board
Housewives from the Midwest every
possible choice the city is like a big
order milk and ice cream shop 36 flavors
of titties which is a little corner of
Eastern Europe
Beach next to the Ducks
okay they talk so much anyway I wanna
like when they talk focus on the
conversation
[Music]
it is where I make all the money uh I'm
trying to get into the story let's
understand what the [\h__\h] they're talking
about
to hang around the people they ran away
from us
it's just temporary for us though our
sights are set for the talk
I have no idea what they're talking
about
I understand Nico just came from Europe
You've Got a Friend already here they're
going to the mansion they probably got
some shady business going on
oh oh and this area is I guess like
uh I think he mentioned it too that
there's like uh people from everywhere
here okay what
it's the guy Jean area
okay come on Ki wow you can do it
honestly people people the the driving
will be clanky janky but I I don't feel
like it's uh bad at all I feel like it's
the same as GTA 5 so far
Chihuahua Chihuahua
but they're still very exact with where
I have to park it's a temporary place
the Mansion is coming cousin that's the
dream at higher speeds okay
we'll see we'll see so far I think I'll
be all right how do I what do I do about
the lag though in the cutscenes make
yourself at home now it's fine though
right oh [\h__\h] it's because it's
it's full screen
a little bastard if he paid simulator I
wouldn't care and what's that
good to see you I made some settings
like before I opened the game
oh
maybe they [\h__\h] it up to change anyway
lower the resolution okay okay
we'll do
sure can't do it now though I think so
so you full of Creeper what crap what
where's luxury condo oh yeah sports car
the [\h__\h] is this with big titties and
Stephanie who sucks like a vacuum what
are you talking about in your letters to
my mother in your letters to me all I
hear about this camera Mr Wrong did they
cut it for white screen
sports cars condos women money the
beasts
I come here and the only thing big about
your life is the Cockroaches that's that
oh that's what that is
screw you you idiot okay I'm an idiot
but you must admit I have the best line
in Boston yeah this I know [\h__\h] but
here
needed one good guy one good guy I could
do well take over the world about to do
okay now maybe I have this what about
you what about you cousin what
what about me
why you leave home after all this time
if I stay here running with the wrong
kind then here you join the Merchant
Navy now you're here you never tell me
anything no what do you mean no no no I
never tell you anything why another time
mystery man stretched exotic sailor what
happened did your captain make you
pregnant screw you
no no it's nothing like that why are
they talking in English anyway talking
Serbian
two things
you remember during the war
bad things
bad things happen to us
war is where the young and stupid are
tricked by the old and bitter into
killing each other
I was very young
thank you
the frame there's no excuse me
Ramen
come on what's the time [\h__\h] I've got to
get the cab back it's on the ship
oh Jesus
I've got to run come meet me at the cab
office
turn left and the first left of the dino
go down one block and turn right down
there then walk all the way down and
we're right there on the left on the
corner of Cisco street it's fully flesh
we got lots of titties and incredible
molders wow give me a hug good to have
you here cousin I've got something for
you
them wait we're sharing an apartment now
oh yes sorry forgive me okay
okay but yes
[Music]
okay
oh
uh what to change something
um
uh what is this
what's what's 16 to 9
this
or should I do 1080.
whoa whoa whoa
did this just turn it
down I think it did
oh my God it's tiny it's [\h__\h] tiny
eh [\h__\h] no it's kind of it's small too
small for my full screen but it's still
like whenever I Tab out I'll click
something out it's ah it like refreshes
everything on my display and it [\h__\h]
around wait I can't even move it it's
just on the top left of my screen but it
doesn't fill out everything oh my
[\h__\h] god it looked like 1080 though
to be honest with you let me try this
again oh yeah it's the same size now
uh
please don't play 1080. well why the
[\h__\h] am I supposed to do when it's
lagging I don't understand why it's
lagging
ah man City PC Port why
go for okay and turn on Okay we can try
that
uh my my this monitor my middle monitor
isn't even 4K though I think
okay let's try let's try let's try if we
sing God let's have it but we think
I turn this down I I I I don't have I
don't
know for nothing now
okay we're full screen again
we're gonna keep this now and see what
happens as long as there's no cutscenes
we're fine anyway
how do I move
look sleeping on the bed will save the
game in advance number six hours or
that's not a bad
excuse me but that's not a bad the
flashing iron the radar shows where to
meet Roman okay
next next info
what the [\h__\h]
what's going on ghost you won't there we
go
hmm
vodka oh my God the picture looks like
straight out of a horror movie
like their faces is oh God old games
oh man
they look terrible
was that banana peel
ho ho ho well I mean yeah does he not
have a uh here oh my God
shitty ass place ew
wait
Nintendo
it's too big on an antenna oh Double
Trouble okay let's go we're also double
travel Nico and Roman Double Trouble
are we are we sure we don't want to like
lock this place I heard New York is um
you might want to lock your apartments
in New York
[Music]
you can save any vehicle in the parking
spot outside your safe house park your
car there and that's it the car will
remain there for you to use
okay thank you ah to replenish your
health you can visit fast food Venice
hot dog stands right is it nice nice
Chihuahua hot dogs okay the circle
around the Raider represents your health
and body armor aha oh that's what that
is the green left half is a circle that
says you're losing Health Green will
fade out the right half well the right
half is what but sprinting or what
also where did the car go
you lied to me
armor I have to exit vehicle okay just
like a GTA 5 okay
whistle I gotta steal a car or what
Roman what the [\h__\h]
uh also how do I open map
s
how do I how do I open the menu went ah
I guess it's just here can I like make
myself a route
oh yes okay right click
it doesn't show on my small GPS
when why not
maybe if I'm in a car
ah okay well Well everybody's lining up
so nicely for me is that a police car oh
[Music]
the police car
how do I run ah
that's jumping
that's crouching that's running okay
and I don't want to steal a car so
there's another police car they're just
like endless police cars oh my God
Boop your stupid American Motor Vehicle
okay no one will mind if I take this car
right how do I get in F also okay
oh no alarm how easy okay to hotwire
vehicle faster preparing for swrs but
was wait am I not already in dude I
don't need to hot wire it right
I'm in a man no alarm let's go what's
going on here
dive out of a moving car no no no need
to do that um
no F no pressing f
ancy cars take longer okay and what was
the W on something else I have reached
my destination okay I could have just
walked
nice car
oh I guess I'll leave the car it will be
gone afterwards so sad
come on big guy I had to do some work I
get out of here we don't need jerkers
screw you baby when I look into your
eyes it means something I see little
Romans I see a little memory I See Stars
I see angels in my homeland we have a
saying yeah
[Laughter]
how can I take you seriously
this is my cousin I tell you about Nico
Nico this is Mallory the beautiful girl
I told you about see not everything I
tell you is [\h__\h] I bet most of it
was this is
nothing over here
I love it I'm going to marry whatever
you say I thought you were going to
marry me baby
man
you should lose few pounds otherwise
this beautiful lady is good to me I know
I'm a fat freak what did I do
[Music]
dance
treat you like an idiot not a [\h__\h]
I guess it's true the beautiful women do
like the guys with a funny sense of
humor
I'm laughing I'll get you the money I
know and Roman till this [\h__\h] Yokel
here if he doesn't stop staring at me
I'll have his head just up and put a
film of it on the internet oh [\h__\h]
is that a word that I shouldn't repeat
that y word oh good great never heard of
this before fantastic fantastic what you
like but at least but at least that guy
knows how to speak to a lady now that's
fine it's a peasant okay
come on Nico Let's Go Darling
I'll see you later I've got to take my
cousin around somewhere are they really
together
those two
a country bumpkin hey cute
[Music]
get into Roman's car already we have our
own car now let's go oh the the inside
the seats are kind of nice
[Music]
you know
that's not bad
excuse me I'm coming in between
build this Mansion you tell me about oh
funny guy we're going to get money in
America
do anything that is in every country
let's really see this town got
[Applause]
this
I kick all the asses that play me they
call me the janitor because you can't
pay your debts and they make you mop the
floor never
robots no I'm the janitor because I
always clean up
your guards are better than your
nicknames only problem is I'm playing
with some money I meant to give to these
Albanian scumbags here's hoping they
don't show up eh of course they will um
and it doesn't matter anyway when I've
played this game imagine if I wasn't
Austrian but 10 times
Slavic I don't know
mom
look
okay thank you wait for me here while I
go inside to clean up
[\h__\h] I almost forgot I'm giving you my
old phone my new number is in there
oh my God they already had phones back
then so going mainly and show up in some
shitty beige will it
guys I owe money to
and you still have a funny accent to me
no I don't know
[Music]
oh okay I don't care and I don't want to
use the phone what I do now I'm waiting
for him here
wait I'm waiting what a waste of time
what well ah What Remain stationary when
in the car use the mouse to look around
you know
they're walking exactly the same way
could they be the same person
that dude too walking the same way oh
what happened how do I answer ah answer
emotionally it's so quiet out here Roman
you winning tonight
[Music]
oh
skip for the conversation with down or
backspace to hang up on Cocoa
hey
come on keep me into the end
[\h__\h]
I'm on the lookout yeah
[Music]
uh uh enter
uh call
Robin
they're coming the Sharkies two guys are
going in the store I think they are the
lone sharks you speak of [\h__\h] I'm down
you better get out of there all right
all right
dude it's too late
they must have been told I was here well
he went for the back door
the bellies don't hurt the men after his
cousin
quick eh we're chasing my
brother updating I love it
oh nice car
[Music]
hey hey that's a nice car I want that
want that car
sexy car wow
what do you call that car subscribe
leave the funny comments to me I want to
get one for myself that is a muscle car
I think ooh sexy muscle car
we're still driving very civilized no
but what type of what exact name I know
I know the GTA cars hi I always look
kind of like made up versions of cars
that exist in real life so give me the
name of an equivalent a low rider muscle
car I don't think I'll get a muscle car
in Austria man
are this actually are they actually
following me because it doesn't feel
like I'm being chased
but I think I'm maneuvering uh traffic
really well am I not
okay that was that was the break is [\h__\h]
the break is absolute [\h__\h] [\h__\h] up
they're gone perfect
were they ever there
at home do you think they saw me of
course they saw you I mean you're a
distinctive man Roman we're here huh you
like your phone maybe one day you get
the premium quality one like mine then
you will have really made it
oh okay I thought it was backwards just
s
ucking thing happened
and now
what now I got money for that 30 bucks
um customized ring type and ringtone
cool
okay wow
I always feel like they're talking to me
well no
Roman Super Chat
rounds pounds Oh My Cry so bouncy and
cute
almost as bouncy as Coyote's boobies in
her new outfit oh my God
those are those are quite something
different camera memos
oh
oh oh
a helicopter mode
I think I like this one wow what the
[\h__\h] wait actually what the [\h__\h] did you
do with your car did you like put a hat
on it
I never saved the text message what the
[\h__\h] is this car though
it's like he puts a he put a hat a car
hat on his muscle car
s up
then enter
[\h__\h] I need help come to the pool quick
man oh
okay how do I go back
huh
how do I go back what's back
back spit backspace
okay
where am I going
to Roman right
he turns around
uh
back to well man we gotta save his ass
this is the whole game a saving Roman's
ass
and bowling with him him in between
excuse me
pretty much yes
okay that's fine for me I I like Roman
koala
no kiwawa this time
what's that look oh is it is that is
that a side quest the blue dude on the
map
that's a side quest
oh come on Daddy what's your problem I
don't have problem you do
get out of here
[Applause]
oh
what about you
come on
Earth get out of here now and if you
come back I'll kill you you understand
you forgot this you have been in bricks
[\h__\h]
what did you do he was going to stab me
now he's going to kill you [\h__\h] him look
at this man screwed again you want to
know where I'm not living in a nice
condo banging for women it's because of
[\h__\h] like this [\h__\h]
I don't think that's the only original
Dude Mallory hey I don't think something
like that happens so easily
uh
Elise and I mean
I'm in the office
um I can't do it huh and what well why
would you want me then
well screw you then
good girl can you do me a favor Mallory
needs a lift can you go pick her up at
the Hope Beach subway station yeah take
the cab she's got a friend with her
maybe someone you can date [\h__\h] you oh
man [\h__\h] you
[Music]
then [\h__\h] you sounded
that sounded like I don't know
not not so not so Serbian
TBH
yeah and the voice actors are they
actually
I'm probably not right they sound
like the accent is made up also I feel
like they sound a little bit Italian
don't they
I don't know about English but in German
I can definitely tell apart an Italian
and the Serbian uh Accents in German I
can
I don't know about English maybe they
are pretty similar in English
hmm
is the
Vlad Russian Roman American what about
Nicole
are you feeling the controls I'm totally
fine with them I'm enjoying driving I
love driving
in GTA games
I'm having good times riding what's this
Beach
uh also America
I usually go the Russian for Falcon
accents yeah yeah
I mean it's whatever
hello I'm there
genius
get in get in ladies so thanks for
coming I should have known Roman would
find some excuse not to turn up this is
Michelle
I live on Rotterdam Hill up on Mohawk
Avenue you know where that is nah
and I don't it was GPS a thing back then
I don't think it was a thing
at least not on the phone are you
finding America Nico not exactly what I
expected Nico you know what you need
someone to show you a good time Michelle
how about you Mallory stop it come on
come on you're both single you're adults
hey I'd like to see you again
you look like that kind of guy we talked
for five seconds and she's already like
I want to see you again like how is it
like you decide so fast I think he looks
fine the way he is I don't think he even
chains out of those things on the
journey how are you gonna become a
classy girl like Michelle I'm easily
impressed yeah she is already impressed
and I just don't get it
she do be easily impressed oh wait it's
just sitting next to me oh she is and
the passenger seat
[Music]
that big chicken turkey leg though
[Laughter]
thanks for the lift Nico oh wait this
looks like a nice place give me a call
sometime see you soon Michelle can I
move in Michelle
please
yeah all he did was hold on she probably
likes ducks
so he goes like Hong Kong and she's like
oh I love ducks
I dropped the girls off the friend gave
me her number but I don't think Mallory
likes my clothes so much and not just
the place for you it's a mohawk in Hall
go something a bit more 20. oh are we
gonna buy the the brown stuff did you
see on the thumbnail I changed my hair
color and my my clothes
[Music]
I tried to
get the orange out make myself look like
Nico
this is what happens when uh I stay too
long in the pool my orange turns into
Brown
[Laughter]
it loses all the saturation you know
that I built up with gravy
I have to put some more gravy in my hair
again then it will be back to Orange
[Music]
lore
I was sorry about that does that really
happen
to someone slightly and their their
whole glass shatters
I what I spread tofu
you would spread tofu on that what does
that mean
sorry I need to figure out words
and clothing show
oh hello yeah they definitely can we
close the door they definitely have
nicer rides in GTA 5 but these these
there's some some okay cars here
it's all link sale
[Music]
you can buy clothes from various close
traps for Liberty City mm-hmm
this place looks like
every item of clothing out on display
can be purchased by the clubs walk up to
the item okay
um
do I have to buy the
press e to try this oh can I really
decide or is it like setting Stone what
I'm getting
Leaf pads I'm leaving this these pants I
am
I I don't know I find that
wording funny
um leave the pants
I'm leaving them
let me enter the pants these are the
same are they not
they look the same dude
but they look okay I guess
and over there is a little cargo on the
other side what about these wait are
these eh
eh oh yeah I guess
I was gonna say like he he seems like a
type of guy who wants to wear track
pants all day with the stripes on the
side but yeah we already do oh and wear
them okay I guess we're going for it
I'm going for the jeans all right all
right
yeah
and then
cute
eight bucks oh cute yeah let's go can I
afford it but it's a winter hat it
doesn't really seem wintery does it
um
[Music]
don't we have to get the thing that's on
the thumbnail huh let me try this
oh my God that looks ridiculous
okay how about this
[Music]
I guess this is the only interesting
looking stuff
oh God now that's okay
[Music]
no give me the purple one
there's there's no hope man
is this all
all bad oh what about over there
the stripy shirt with the jack that
looks cute I like that it's on sale
ah no no no not the sneakers ah
wait can I not get that one up there I
want no I don't want the sneakers I want
that thing that that that would look
good I I'm telling you
man
I can't get that one
[Music]
I mean okay what about here this one
no it's the pants oh
they're better stores later in the game
they're better be
okay what shoes do we have on right now
uh kind of these no
[Music]
um
and I hate all of this
[Music]
gen okay a leather jacket should look
nice now
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I think that's the best we can get here
not shabia
what did she say I look strong yes
I am powerful man
from Serbia
fear me
okay yeah well I guess I already paid so
I can leave
that's fine right I don't need to
upgrade everything right bye bye
we look good
were you about to touch your crotch dude
and I canceled the animation oh no okay
Roman I got some clothes
it looks like they brought the stuff in
from the old country though
he looks good from behind
anyway you have Michelle a classy girl
for your arm you should definitely keep
dating her yeah the first lady I meet in
America that's the one I'll immediately
pick wow wow men are I guess sampled
they're not so picky huh
or this guy's not so picky you can play
the way I know I know I know
crazy
[Music]
where do we go though tell me game where
are we going
it's Michelle
Roman's girlfriend you remember you lady
what's up Michelle I don't normally do
this but I thought you'd probably be
pretty
and all you do not normally do what
you're not making this easy
it's the language sorry Michelle I'm
still not used to how things work here
in America a date would be good I am
getting sick of hanging out with Roman
all the time how about I pick you up
from your apartment that sounds good
[Music]
bowling for a dead
seems totally fine
where is she almost even got a little
heart and then her leather is is Pink
isn't that sweet
is this really what New York looks like
guys by the way
it's kind of like this this these kind
of places look so nice like we don't
have these kind of houses and or like
apartment buildings in in Austria
they look really nice very American to
me
looks like South and Brooklyn oh wow wow
yeah like how are these townhouses is
that what you call that not quite as
brown yet it's got a whole like brown
filter on top I think
damn
Roman I'm on my way to my bed
what does he want oh I can speak what he
could possibly want or why he'd be
pissed off
come on guys let's be reasonable
first things first okay
please priorities okay first date at a
Burger Shot
[Music]
really
who chose this location
yeah rip Roman
Lincoln is watching coverage shows
instead of Comedy ads
okay
oh are they just showing me all options
oh huh
just hi
uh nice view
but there's no music this is so awkward
um
lady be careful your thigh is in the
poll
many of your friends have special
abilities and they'll that they'll use
to help you should they like you though
oh
these range from delivering guns to
providing bombs to help you get those
hard to reach targets
blobs
this seems a little bit Overkill
uh okay
oh yeah it turned I guess I turned off
all the music
hey it's Nico
hey I'm just finishing my hair come in
thank you I'll be with you in a minute
just move in no
no why all your stuff is new some even
still have tags on walks in two meters
I'm
son how do you know you can see that
the
everything is
yeah I'm kind of obsessed with
cleanliness things get on my nerves and
I just throw them out
OCD or something oh
so where are you taking me
are you taking me
you look good oh thanks
I don't know I'm new here let's Netflix
and chill yeah
fun fair
yeah great yeah great let's go
let's go actually we call it um Carnival
here just a little difference
uh what do you do yeah great so I love
the reaction
uh
awkward take Michelle to the carnival
yay
what do you like to do what do you like
to do come on I asked you don't ask the
same question back in sports working out
things like that I'd like to know about
you though see the places you hang out
yeah maybe another time
wait I went back to 4K and the cutscene
didn't the lag though did it
because maybe the vsync on fixed it nice
nice nice nice if it did
it was fine right
I still have to observe maybe it's just
maybe it will come back I don't know
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] y'all [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you
well New York where is that do they have
the the New York square that
it's not called those jokes kind of the
fame it's a famous place
they recreate that too
yeah Carnival isn't open I think they're
going to turn it into a big Los Ventura
style theme park oh there's a bowling
alley over on the boardwalk why don't we
play a few frames sure bowling
we're going bowling come on Michelle
follow me
is she gonna run to yeah oh oh let's go
I haven't been on a date for a while I'm
kind of lonely here I thought you were
doing me a favor by going out with me
you're the local people
Liberty City I came here from somewhere
where is he so creepiest you probably
know more people here than me more
[\h__\h] Maybe
it's dark and
this makes no sense to me taking
pictures of the beach in the dark like
this with no good lighting set up and
everything
there's no no there's nothing going on
like it looks like nothing
everything's looks everything just looks
so dead here
what oh and here it's kind of
kind of kicking all this free five frame
game with Michelle is free okay
I was pretty good at bowling in the the
game we played with Ahmed
I don't know about here though use ad to
get in position
press left Mouse button to choose a
ready position
press F to check the score and wait how
do I shoot by letting go left Mouse
button or
in one motion pull the mouse backwards
and quickly thrust it Forward angling
left or right right look to direct the
shot press r b to cancel your ready
position okay what
all right
oh
[Music]
pretty decent
whoa yeah I need some space and that's
okay
yeah okay okay
[Music]
whoa
whoa not bad for first try
oh
how is she gonna do I'm not gonna skip
it in the first time I want to see
we should like get behind her and teach
her how to both
oh what if she gets it all no no no
[Music]
no no don't get a gutter
don't what get a Gada
don't get a gutter
can't get all of them
why does she look so other excited
the [\h__\h] that is [\h__\h] [\h__\h] NPCs
everything's [\h__\h] rigged
foreign
I'm always a little bit too much on the
right side
okay okay okay
come on come on come on come on come on
there we go that's what I'm talking
about we're bowling
I want to see her
I don't care
are we losing why did oh my God
okay we're gonna get
all of them
trust me
oh
pretty good at bowling no you're not
we're losing
unbelievable how did hers were also like
separated like that how the [\h__\h] do you
get
you girl like how rich this is the game
to get them all when they're in this
position
[Music]
it's polite to let everyone yeah this is
it yeah let's make her feel good about
her skills yeah yeah true I mean
I think I I would probably be delighted
if in a nut wait
and then not too obvious way
my date would let me win then I think I
would be Loki delighted
I would feel very good about myself yeah
we [\h__\h] go
[Music]
we got an upper game man we're already
behind we can have one strike
what's she gonna do
she's falling apart
by the pressure
oh good job I'm so bad at bowling in
real life though
also I went swimming before the
um stream again so my arms are pretty
spaghetti and my legs are pretty
spaghetti too not gonna lie
if I had to bowl now I would I would
drop every Bowl
Bowl
before I even try to shoot it
um
I'm trying to squeeze in some quick
swimming sessions as much as I can
for my shoulders and my breathing and my
freaking weak ass noodly arms
balls like an angel why am I getting
another round though
[Music]
yeah wow that's a fast boy ah come on
come on
ah last round oh [\h__\h] she's gonna get a
strike isn't she
that [\h__\h] I swear don't get distracted
don't
do it
okay okay
how to like that
[Music]
boom
[Applause]
she ends with 69. nice
I won oh my God I'm sorry how did I win
I played overall worse than her I think
a little bit not too bad though you're
good Nico that was fun
will you take me back home now of course
I'll take you home let's go
take her home
New York gross
to her nice apartment not many people
here in Liberty City no boyfriends or
husbands
no I guess I'm married to my job almost
imagining what do you do come on I asked
first I work with Mallory this is so
romantic
you're not used to talking to American
women
so romantic I'm this imagining guy guy
from overseas on his first date and he
doesn't know like how things work so he
just like runs like this
that's just ridiculous to me why the
[\h__\h] is our car oh my God I don't know
where I feel like we we let we entered
and we left from different sides
[Laughter]
[Music]
he loves everyone's oh my God
oh man good stuff
um
just to keeping up
a lady
there it is there it is
uh my stamina oh no oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
you would think he's trying to impress
her but no he's this just he's dorky he
he just likes to run
he just likes to be really fast you know
what are you doing here
what's anybody doing people already fall
behind because I walk so fast but there
must be something that made you leave
your home he's on the number level
[\h__\h] entirely
babe I just felt like I needed a new
start there's nothing else about Liberty
City then just Roman maybe the there's
more to this place I'm not sure
[Music]
yeah I'm not sure yet either and for me
it doesn't really scream New York to me
yet
maybe we'll see some areas that scream
New York but maybe it was just because I
never went to New York
it doesn't look very different to me
from the GTA City
right now
no never mind
I don't know overall it was like really
sunny and bright and relatively big
streets
it was kind of different yeah
that was nice needs more rats really
interested in seeing you again oh really
be good I'll give you a call please do
Nico see you soon oh slant
okay now we can think about helping
Romans
[Music]
she'll occasionally call me to arrange
James okay do we always go bowling [\h__\h]
up can't touch this
[Music]
where is Roman can't touch this where's
he did he die
oh well
oh okay
cool thank you we're taking the time
of money from them in the first place
I'm seeing Michelle I thought you wanted
me today
right before
no I didn't see your titties yet
you're an animal Roman nothing can stop
you being horny I'll see you soon
I can't believe the game did this to me
I thought it would be like like the game
waits for me
to be done with what hiccup one thing oh
my God
one of the [\h__\h] Bamboozled I didn't
expect this
to be so serious
but he's fine like they obviously gave
me a chance
okay
yeah it has consequences damn but still
we still seem fine
he's alive he's not really dead
hmm
wow
okay but what's always doing the beep up
oh is it the turning signal
people people oh
[Music]
hi Nico uh Roman
get in
I was the man who just coached before
his cousin I hope she was worth it right
come on Roman
it was all your idea in the first place
how was your cousin tell me how she was
I wondered about Michelle when I first
met him she was good at playing with the
balls with the smell of titty on my
breath and you who ended up in the
hospital firstly Morgan my breath does
not smell of kitty
I don't think that your loan shark
friends could hospitalize me I can look
after myself
you'll make your breath smell like
anything
will not let these men treat you like
that again I'm sorry for letting you
down Roman won't happen again
I will set my priorities different now
bros before hoes okay wow okay that
looks more like New York sorry I'm I'm
looking at your beautiful city
but damn this the smog is [\h__\h] here holy
[\h__\h]
can barely see I can barely enjoy The
View
[Music]
so dusty
Ramen I apologize again for not being
there that's like real New York oh dear
I got here choice between some titties
and your safety would have been
difficult for me as well good morning
Nico call me soon
oh dear
someday in the future we will be repaid
for what we just did
hmm
it's fog sorry did my brain same thing
uh things were telling me I can watch TV
I don't wanna I wanna do the next thing
next next next next next
tell me what to do do you really want me
to watch TV look for real for real
like really
we have to oh okay ah maybe maybe
something specific will be shown on TV
that will inspire me to do something
[Music]
okay Roman I'm not going to let
something else get in the way this time
where are you
times
Roman Dogo oh [\h__\h] how how did he move
so fast to another destination
oh God okay let's get out of here
uh Roman why do you get in trouble all
the time
they just wanted me to watch TV
just so that I would move away from his
place for a moment I guess
[Music]
so far I haven't gotten in trouble yet
though
I'm still a law abiding
immigrants
am I see this what am I what am I am I a
Taurus
[Music]
wait what am I
[\h__\h] up oh that is that is that the
thing that thing this thing
Ramen
Roman huh
wait is it the green thing
flower
hi
resident resident thank you it was a
misunderstander hey oh [\h__\h] that is
here and I'll talk to him our problems
with your cousin I told you to stop now
it's too late
oh
beat up blither
uh I'm with the luck okay
and then uh elements are for alternative
punch
or easy nice fun
oh [\h__\h] off
wait what was it f right okay there
there we go let's go let's get a hook
and the left hand the right and then
finish it with a kick oh
[\h__\h] you space to blood
didn't block very well
Caleb you're next bastard [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you hey take this
yeah [\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] it
I said the meeting is for Darden
there's a stick between us
I'll push you harder you're not going to
beat me
[Laughter]
oh
[\h__\h] he's got momentum he's got momentum
[Applause]
that was close you are right cousin yeah
fine
one more of these gangsters tries to
[\h__\h] here's Garden
come on
let's get him I don't feel so good
look at my engine Where's My Car where's
my car listen
oh the blue thing ah
[Music]
where's where's it oh wait where's the
dude why am I stressing out
uh caps up to focus the camera on target
they're gonna [\h__\h] me around and beat me
up because there are more of them not
any longer me and you Nico me and you
are going to show them [\h__\h] dirt and
smashing my [\h__\h] stuff who does he
think he is just some [\h__\h] pretty
opinion Hood if I wanted to buy a stolen
TV I go to Darden who does he think he's
[\h__\h] with the league Enterprises
that's who we're going to the top Nico
the top for now let's just try to
survive cousin catch up to him cousin
he's getting away [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
what
what I was
I didn't see anyone Drive Away Nani
we got some of them cousin but not all
this is not a good thing I was listening
hey
free track
this place is not much of a [\h__\h]
holiday
bleed out what do you mean bleed out
so let the replay
what
[\h__\h]
well I mean I
mean a route going on in my mini map but
I thought I didn't realize like it was
like you know serious like
urgent I didn't know it was urgent man I
don't know maybe
[Music]
good night oh retry replay from my phone
how do I open my phone again
uh
they open my phone
up okay
uh
try aye yes please
what why why is the replay called
Bleeding Out
and from where are we restarting
the whole fight I guess okay
where's the car where's my car
well like how will we escape
I will use his okay
oh
shh please Daddy needs a good friend of
mine it was
my HP is [\h__\h]
oh my God what do I do
[Music]
I'm focusing
nice come on
yeah okay so
get him get him get him yeah let's go
plus interest
yeah yeah
[Music]
[\h__\h] launch sharks man so true is so
true bro
[Music]
but he was like like running after me
like in person like
not with a car I didn't notice he got in
a car and ran away I should get in get
in
where's Roman do I have to wait for
Roman no
how do I know where to go
after no
no no
well
[\h__\h] he was slow as [\h__\h]
like I live time to wait for him
man
he's a slow ass
[\h__\h]
where the okay
man
[Music]
take free I'm getting better at combat
though
come on come on you can do it
next time we'll go through the opening
of the fence
[Music]
give me momentum come on
the [\h__\h] is [\h__\h] me up no this is the
worst timeline
[Music]
laughs
my brother
you all know it let's go
thank you
did he try to headbutt him oh wow that's
that's us yeah okay I still did it holy
[\h__\h] yummy I don't I hope I don't need
HP for the next section
I love it Mamma Mia
Mamma Mia
Roman Roman Roman Roman Roman Roman
Roman hurry the [\h__\h] up
Roman Roman now Bay
okay let's go caps lock [\h__\h] Nicole
ever since I are right here I have been
pushed around blood dark bleeder even
Mallory pushed me around me and you Nico
me and you control from now on ain't
good but no one push us around going to
stand up do all this pimpses one shots
from now on Liberty City won't know what
hit it man we're going to earn this time
Nico Mark the words that are coming out
of my mouth
let's go
I'll make this my city
his leggings so much why is it lagging
ah
go go go go go go go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go
so much
[Laughter]
faster I need a faster car
[Music]
that that was because I used the
handbrake never use the handbrake guys
I will not use the handbrake again it
[\h__\h] me over
once it won't [\h__\h] me over towards hey
Elvis unless oh that was good that was
good
that was a little bit of handbrake but
most mostly just letting off my foot off
of the gas
he traveled
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] where is he where is he did he
where did he go
here
get away
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
should I get out of my car
is it too late
please no
okay wait I bet he's waiting for me I
think God it was still waiting for me
darling has been in this car oh he's
escaping a foot up the staircase okay
okay I follow
them we just played
yeah okay
how
where
[Laughter]
so tomato can you guys wait for me
I can't I can't lose them now can I
is there something here I can't see
a day staircase
okay he's trapped okay I hope I don't
need
much of my HP
I'm dying do I have
no
[Music]
he's got a knife Thomas
faster and [\h__\h] you don't move
nothing else I didn't even have to
disarm him
and there's a cop down there and it said
something about this Army maybe but I
didn't have to
desperate
situation is called for desperate
Solutions or something like that um
did I get the knife
ain't a problem for you no more cousin
drive back to the depot
this is starting to pain
okay ah [\h__\h] wait I'm having a hard time
here
thanks guys for hosting our meetups like
Darden they always try to squeeze you
for everything a man in Europe another
Russian ball got it they live on the
Adriatic believe they owed him money
when I did not
it made my life impossible there was no
avoiding him did you deal with him I
need to garden and bleed her he had too
many connections for that I had to leave
he is one of the reasons I came here and
to see you cuss of course of course we
will have no more problems from now on
cousin it is all plain sailing straight
to the top for you and me we will see
you
okay if you guys see food scream because
I'm looking out the food too
ah what'd you say
want to say it again straight into my
face huh what the hell
food food food
Chihuahua Chihuahua hot dogs tofu
are they getting angry at me for driving
on the sidewalk
is that why it goes we will wee wall
okay I didn't find I didn't see anything
on the way
um
wait yeah
maybe afterwards thank you cousin I'll
see you later
I'm driving well for a New Yorker
not even a New Yorker though
uh oh wait there's food here
meatballs meatballs meatballs oh I
parked it was in a weird way
please give me the food
I have to sleep to heal yes please
I wouldn't mind a hot dog right now oh
see it healed me fully um
I did
the storm in your mouth
dude
but it cost me money oh okay so sleeping
is like free free recovery
which what did we do what did they say I
mean are we waiting for him again what
or do we have to go in with him or
whoa
ah okay
come on forget about the fats sir Lads
shots up
but he's a serve and you're a contest
oh hey Nico where's Roman good question
hey Yoko your damn cousin isn't here go
get me a coffee what get me a [\h__\h]
coffee chill no
unamused
what you keep staring at me I'll burst
one of your eyeballs gorgeous this guy's
a [\h__\h] creep give him a break he's
new in the country I can see that did he
walk here from 1985 yeah excellent now
stop [\h__\h] staring at me I mean I know
I'm good looking and everything but come
on
uh Hey Mallory hey man
about time glad bloody boy what's going
on Reuben Roman boy you tell me what's
going
let's have to say what is that sex past
no it's where is my [\h__\h] money
then those abandons you said you would
deal with Cam and smashed my computer so
it's my fault I I didn't say that
then beat up a couple more then we did
some real lessons is that so I tell you
what well you don't pay maybe you and
Nico can do me few favors
I subconsciously went to the same
position as as romance
no I can't do it my cousin will do it
yes he can drive
no it's not a cop his name is Nico
you'll be reto Nico sorry to ask cousin
can you go pick up Jermaine one of my
regulars what do you mean regular steel
and Mohawk Avenue regular for what
what was this all about Nico came in
looking for you and Vlad told him to get
him a [\h__\h] coffee and Nico didn't
want to Coffee what was he thinking I
know there
it's like office gossip cute
so excited to hear some really mundane
boring story
try to Rotterdam Hill and meet Roman's
customer like what what kind of costume
are what
what
let's check it out oh these Shadows are
cool
oh
you missed the music I'm sorry
I wait can I make my own radio station
for next time for tomorrow and then we
can have the other music on that's like
not copyrighted whenever there's music
okay you guys gotta tell me how or I'll
just look up a tutorial never mind it's
okay I always I always rely so much on
you guys I always tell you tell me
I could just Google it I know I know I
know I know
in Japanese we say Google
just Google it you little [\h__\h]
it's for coming
you take me over to Masterson Street
Jermaine
that had so much passion in it
the Roman was gonna pick me up I need
someone I could trust for this run I'm
Roman's cousin if you if you can trust
him you can trust me oh he told me about
you
my hands haven't
haven't for a long time being here in
Liberty City is just making them dirtier
okay okay
I gotta pick up some hot parts for my
locker you down I ain't got no problem
with that just don't tell me if you
stole this [\h__\h] from a hospital or a
school that's driving thank you I will
think I'm assuming this is a genuine
comment because I do think I'm driving
quite nicely while reading comments and
while reading the dialogue
multitasking
that door isn't meant to be open
wait here while I take a look what
I went I went once again we're playing
the waiting if anyone swinging before
we're going to want to live oh no wait
man
I ain't going down man oh [\h__\h] hell
our first chance
[Music]
oh the streets are so empty that's nice
[\h__\h]
[Music]
what are you doing
relax relax relax everybody relax relax
relax relax relax relax
I
[Applause]
I I I I I I I
get this car fixed though
oh it turns with the handbrake really
[\h__\h] me up man
I want to do like sudden turns though so
that the the police cars get confused
okay let's go into the park is this the
the Central Park
okay the trees don't get easily uh
bumped over I understand
[Music]
no no no no
no no
it's been blocked off
wait this is a street this is a street
okay good yep
are we are we doing good now I think
we're doing pretty good I don't hear the
sirens sorry
so I'm actually really sorry about that
wait we almost we're almost there
yeah get out of the circle
[Applause]
[Music]
for another minute okay laying low
laying low you mean like don't do
anything suspicious yeah
yeah
that was um quite something
three people have died hey did you count
what brings you to Liberty City Nico
Roman I guess
I'm looking for something good luck
finding them how's the hunt been going
so far it really started yet I'm getting
settled in you know Roman has had some
issues with the loan sharks that needed
to be resolved there's this [\h__\h]
called plane who he owes money I
shouldn't have gone into the park I
think
it was still chaotic but maybe the chaos
helped um
wow
I've been I'm in Paris
this is just like in Paris
and I also have like something like that
and then a circle around it around about
big ass roundabout
but I think a lot of countries and
cities have that
what did I miss my huh
I missed my goal
what
what are you talking about I'm reading
my chat excuse me they copy each other
nah just I I think it's just like a
classic uh
classic structure
[Music]
um
and I guess putting a roundabout around
it just makes sense thanks man keep
looking at me like bye bye
I really don't really know what just
happened but you're welcome all right
nothing nothing has entered my brain
repair and respray
do we need some repairs what do you
think
is it free
good stuff just adding a little bit more
work to them so they don't turn me
uh away
oh
looking fine friends I got your friend
Jermaine where he wanted to go good Nico
thanks I can't talk see you soon you
little [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
is he like trying to flirt with a lady
right now or what
free the first time okay nice nice nice
[\h__\h] man Roman
Roman my man I'm coming for you I'm
checking out what you're doing
I'm new in the city you have to take
care of me
I'm having fun this is a lot of fun I
love GTA games man
after we're done with this we're gonna
play San Andreas and then Vice City or
whatever I don't know
and though the horsey game the horse GTA
get a message
what hotel here
same thing
[\h__\h] battery this is chaos
capitalism is a dirty business
capitalism like War yay not exactly
no maybe not when you're going to tell
me properly about what happened I'm not
going to judge you
uh when you got time
another time can I help it's cute okay
yes I'm not my friend Little Jacob he's
a good man what
smoke a bit look after him
Smoky heads
whatever man
it is
wine stock wine stock wine stock
Little Jacob let's pick him up little
Jacob how little is he
and where is Big Jacob
when or will he grow up to be a big
Jacob someday
oh best best accent coming up really
foreign
this would be even more fun with music
on the radio but it would distract me
from reading the The Talk
script
couldn't focus I mean when they're not
talking it's fine when they're talking I
just won't silence
because I'll I'll put something in
uh Prestige oh okay a little dry Cup oh
[\h__\h] I got on my car
oh hi
was that like some kind of like Jamaican
accident
accent or something like that
Hong Kong
yo he's got Style
all right brother Street in shotler what
is two
shortly
the one-man room I've been talking about
all this time cousin Nico gonna help you
woman take over the world bird hunting
and I guess so respect all right all
right we're going to this spot where I
needed to wait if I said I gotta ask you
another favor go for it okay I really
have to read this because going down
you're coming outside I would not be
able to hear what he says you want me to
keep watching things we're in this
brother yeah my man romance cousin
thanks respect he's Rascal that I
Rockets with my bridging really oh my
God
what type of [\h__\h] they might pull off
how does how does Nico even understand
what he's saying honestly like Nico
obviously isn't so used to hearing all
kinds of different accents English
accents
realistically I don't think he would be
able to understand but maybe maybe an
eagle also is seeing some subtitles the
ones that I'm seeing
yeah maybe this part up there watch out
for any Badness sure you can dude
you keep on stumbling like are you okay
maybe smoke a little less
wait look at spot do I go with cars
[Music]
I'm so sorry
wheel up and down to cycle oh no that's
radio
I guess when I'm out of the card and it
works
should I walk oh okay so sorry dude
don't be mad don't be mad don't be mad
close the [\h__\h] door
[Music]
huh okay I go up or what
don't worry I have learned to look at
stairs oh
we get the sniper spot or what select
the weapon
this thing okay
I got it I got it
let's go down
and now I'm already crouching
we'll make my aim more accurate okay oh
sick yeah let's go
oh this is like already set up for like
a gang fight oh my God
watch this yeah there's only gonna be
one of you is coming they're so stylish
Jacob Jacob we have to teach a bad man
his lesson and team free master
faster
[Music]
can I get a sniper rifle
easy we're done
we're done right
there'll be another one Nico check him I
boom
anything else hide yourself oh how are
you still alive dude [\h__\h] you
violence is not the answer guys I think
I saw someone there
really I think I feel like I saw someone
like hide
really dangerous oh nice nice roll I
have had much experience
should I wait is the police after us
uh I was gonna pick up the elbow
are they not here for me
are they
take it out because of me oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
okay I will follow my route now
whoa
my car feels so wobbly right now
nobody's following me
yeah I thought they were here for me
that's why I panicked everything you
can't keep the peace
it doesn't take their job very seriously
I guess
I always let people go
what
we're doing now are you done
I'm afraid to go
wrong I took Jacob where he wanted to go
driving for you ain't as boring as I
thought it would be
physical
okay cool cool
let's go
Firefly Island I want to go to five on
the island
sounds cool
wait did they didn't they have the same
thing in GTA 5 or was it a different one
the one that says piss pasa it's I guess
a beer
it was supposed to be a beer I suppose
German name for it but this is some yeah
pea water
translated
Sam doesn't drink any bells I'm sorry
drinking it like that is she trying to
be suggestive
what
lad has been added wonderful okay
are we going to Vlad
it seems so
I should
there you go
okay next stop Vladimir my man my new
boss
I know
no I don't want to go bowling with Vlad
no
[Music]
I mean
okay like maybe like he would be kind of
chill when just you know having an
outing we'll take
yo we need to answer something
sure I was looking to Branch out a bit
anyway I'll see you soon all right first
I gotta go to Vlad dude
eh
did Vlad say what he needs before
remember
[Music]
it's not a date right I'm not going on a
date with Vlad right
another decision seems like it
okay as long as it's not a date I feel
like we can choose whatever
ah [\h__\h] you you're a bunch of [\h__\h]
and [\h__\h] nice I'm going back to the
meeting gosh I'm going to base
[Music]
excuse me
Simon I see you later okay
what's your name again Big Mouth prick
better catches sit down
Nika that's it Nico not big mouth brick
you're funny you remember yes in these
ones I'll let you take the [\h__\h] out of
me
take this [\h__\h] yes Mickey about I don't
understand Mickey Mouse people who [\h__\h]
with me get [\h__\h] with okay fine calm
down whatever some old men not paid me
in months and I'm not he looks like
Trevor a little bit from this angle on
this lightning
all bastard owns a china shop Dukes
right there you go same hairstyle
got to teach a lesson I got a gun now
[Music]
oh hello camp with e
well I got my own car
ain't that ah [\h__\h] what
we chat ah wait after that but I did
something weird with my chat
oh
okay
and my leg fell asleep bye
it's tingling
remember to save the game oh there's no
Auto safe at all
I want to save his own
I don't even see a normal saving
function
oh oh we're fun and we're fun
but we're already like
no I guess not quite one and a half
hours in the game maybe how long is this
game
how how long what kind of a long ride am
I in for
long
25 hours that's not long we played way
longer games than that
30 hours for main star 25 to 30.
okay cool cool
hmm
and then we might want to do some side
quests in between but I don't know in
GTA 5 I also didn't care much for like
the side quests really
the main story was so fun I just wanted
to keep on doing the main story I was
really curious about everything
you know
maybe a few days yeah
it's a Korean place
[Music]
loot
doing call
no
[Music]
come on
hey let me in you will play protection
money old man
it's protection practicing even in the
game yeah what I mean
I need the [\h__\h] I can break up here well
that should pay me to tell punts like
you to go away you get no money
I don't want to hurt the Korean bro find
something to throw for the shop
[Music]
yeah
find something to throw well how about
my own body
like how do I pick something up to well
can I throw the bat did we take the bat
no we didn't take the bed
can I throw can I pick this up and throw
it
I stop the mini map oh okay
um
[Music]
press e to pick up an object only small
I'm just gonna be picked up okay
whatever picking up a brick
ah
um
[Music]
show The Brick for the window to show
the throw it to show you serious
uh
he didn't even notice that
closer baby
ah
what the window not the door oh that's
the window too
okay there we go ah the door here
I thought Vlad and I had understanding
only thing I understood was you owed him
money
oh
okay we we we did without violence only
violence against window
you're good
though thank God
I was just like
there's a lot of like Asian shops here
Asian uh like
area what
so dark in the city in the night
neither Little Chinatown
oh
sorry I had to scratch my ear
meep
[Music]
swish Pizza Swedish Pizza
is that what that is swish swish Pizza
swish Pizza
what is that no Swedish people like
making pizza that much that they have
their own kind
[Music]
Swiss swish is that swish
it's like Swedish Pizza
oh [\h__\h] now
repair shops stocks Rising throughout
the whole city
mysterious bunkings happening
by mysterious driver
Bonk and run
to love his money he paid up I had to
smash the show pretty good but he paid
don't worry your little peasant head
about it stupid jerk made a mistake of
telling me how much he gets that [\h__\h]
for back East is the biggest crook in
the neighborhood lucky I don't tell his
customers what they're paying for that's
it can I go now there's one beard called
touche which is gold golden shower
and just saw it
on the on the taps
well I mean beer is pretty golden
I can see where you would get that
uh what what happened
what are we doing what about what about
um ah we still have him on our map we
can go to him now maybe it's too late
though who knows
[Music]
let me try to get to him
oh Roman I'm busy
having that much fun since I got here
here not like hard work hang out with
your cousin more often maybe that is the
problem
well we're sitting here
you shouldn't cry wolf Roman who knows
when you really need help
what is he doing
best dude I'll see him soon but he
wasn't GTA 5 too he's skating on my
nerves I think I need to go to a repair
shop my car is falling apart
but I'm busy I don't got time for that
um ah let's train again Vlad
what is it you okay come see me for more
work
um delete
because I don't know what to do no how
do I get rid of it uh what did you guys
say uh backspace backspace backspace
okay
it's hard to use these old phones
I can only work with touch screen
but I used to have I used to have phone
too that had like the keys still the
keyboard yeah yeah yeah yeah
this is a friend of mine
weird phone
no not Zoomer I had I had older phones
too
what yeah I had like a Nokia
and I had a flip phone once I think and
I remember when our house phone still
had like this cable on it and you had to
go I'm still waiting for this big break
to the phone to call or take a call
a wife a creep before him came walking
anyway let's go for a liquid Drive
nowadays I think most people here don't
even have a house phone anymore
everybody just has only their
smartphones back in the day I feel like
it used to be first first only house
phones and then they transitioned into
house phones and uh mobile phones and
now there's only mobile phones yeah
so but still in forms I still see a lot
of like like two lines for phones like
mobile phone and with one of those my
cars
yes this one either
um actually I want that car though
I still see undocumented like two lines
to fill out mobile phone and house phone
's house phones
no bye you still have it damn
maybe like big families awesome I'm sure
Hot Box in so what's the deal dude why
are you sniffing so much um
I don't trust them who arranged this
deal
erships
if this goes wrong
that
remember
quietly don't trust yourself
sure I hear you
depends on what really
[Music]
I'm sorry sorry
he's just like taking it all in
trying to get all of it and maybe maybe
you know it's like people who slurp
Ramen and a lot of people don't start
Ramen because they can't like me
but if you can't slip Ramen you're
obviously enjoying it more I wish I
could celebrate Ramen
[\h__\h]
keep out of this vehicle we might need
to get out of here quick
yeah I agree it's my skill issue
if I have the rear drive to the rear
Outlet way okay
we have arrived
around this nice car nice muscle car
really nice muscle car
do I get out of the car
shoot
[\h__\h] up
wait a lot more waste the drug dealers
uh
uh wait should I
um
are we done
okay
[Music]
you better already be in the car
you little piece of [\h__\h] no he's not in
the car
uh Jacob
Jacob Taylor oh what a [\h__\h] idiot
jacob jacob Jacob
get in get in
good night
[Music]
foreign
why was he just chilling there
should I have just lost him first before
picking him up I was wired then it will
just you know be the same thing as
before when I just drove away first and
it canceled everything
ah Mamma Mia and mommy how how
um no please leave me alone how do I
[Music]
oh how what the hell
[\h__\h]
ah
because I can load Maybe
can I load this
I have a fan I'll get it I thought I
already failed
[Music]
try me try me
I'm dead I'm dead guys
First Step but I I I died on purpose
though
oh that's a nice [\h__\h] car
I know
yes Concrete Jungle
f
rest in peace
a boat game boat gotcha game
of course
good man like woman
in all good money not this world enough
this I am very aware of
I forgot the uh anything in this place
is generous see it I think there was
some other shot gradient
I know so many ship names only because
of those games
otherwise never heard a lot of them
before
sauce you know don't like it at all why
are you doing it brought myself to do it
and I do it like green you don't see
that there could be a problem
foreign
both of it
it's tea time
go
cute
okay how do I not fail should I drive
away before
I pick up Jacob does that not make me
fail the mission too growing up I can
kiss one of them try to get jumped and
run off with the ganja keep hold of this
vehicle we might need to get out of here
quick I can run them over you mean the
the dudes
or the police
both okay
yeah I thought so too like they were
like running in a way that makes it
really easy to just drive them over so I
wasn't sure what to do
yeah okay
let's go
I would already be driving why are you
so slow
you have to be determined
are they dead though like when they say
waste them like what do you mean
is that enough
[Music]
this is stupid
oh
shoot what's this problem why no shooty
shoot
[Music]
I can't I can't shoot I felt like I can
shoot from the car I have to hold
there we go
now we gotta be fast
I don't feel police on my ass yet
it seems good
well how do they manage to not get cops
on my ass
what
how
flat tire oh yeah
I'm still driving I got them honey okay
okay
cause I killed them in front of the
police before did that oh my God
I thought even if I don't kill him in
front of the police they still notice
[\h__\h] my car oh [\h__\h]
all right
umbrella
can we switch cars
Deadpool the boy is no matter
did they shoot my tire
oh we're already here okay okay let's
let him go and then oh this is kind of
cute
oh no wow
yes we're gonna put some roadway on the
ground
he's running come on brother I'm coming
what are we doing huh wait we're killing
people all right you're ready oh I said
this place by fire to blood God what
does that mean
[Music]
what does that mean oh
you you take that one check the window
you see him up there like you could have
easily shot him from there
[\h__\h] coward
I bet I have it [\h__\h]
there we go
oh I got him where are we going
inside
take down all of that drug dealers
is he even capable of finishing people
off
my aim
he's not even looking
[Music]
turn off what okay we're leaving okay
okay
we're taking a different car
um
would you mind following me Jacob
remember to feed the gun
forgot the shotgun okay
it's like we're not stressed for in
terms of police so
okay
it's gone this isn't no gun oh I picked
ah
oh just gotta run over the dead body it
seems kind of disrespectful but I think
everything we're doing is disrespectful
oh no difference there's no I have to
steal a car that's already driving maybe
[Music]
[\h__\h] off alone let me in and me and my
friend please please thank you thank you
thank you thank you oh the gun made us
more threatening
he goes back to the cafe Auntie
[Music]
January thank you my brother
don't mention well it was a pleasure a
pledge
he's my cousin Lord be the tickets
boundaries you know letters
[Music]
etc etc you know it's logical but and I
follow
[Music]
orders are sometimes hard you must be
sure you agree before you follow I have
made that mistake myself a long time ago
for real I know I arrived an umbrella
but Batman is my bro I follow him
wherever
uh-huh
are you guys following
[Laughter]
the Honda Odyssey I know and I wanted to
play the car oh airplane the car that
was like right before it but it was too
slow oh this one looks okay
sorry police car
enough
[Music]
there we go yeah thanks for everything
give this a little something and say yo
we appreciate your assistance see I see
her on the top that's pretty cool and
and we don't stand out so much in this
car
we're just you know a family father
[Music]
Little Jacob is happy
we did a good thing
hmm
get another one okay
I just leave this car right here in the
middle
that one that one looks cool too it's
like a Range Rover what are you clapping
for
that one that one that one maybe
oh yeah
stop stop stop stop hey
hopefully no police
gotta send to send two people out though
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you yo those are quite the Jazz
it's so
police the police
I thought all I'd have been doing since
I got there was helping you out
I stole those cards
as many as you like Nico there are
always more cups
I was gonna say that Pam in this game
it's so easy to steal cars the police
doesn't give a [\h__\h] in GTA I I got in
trouble so much
for everything
and to be really careful
ah
[Music]
maybe still real toxic why
I crashed into a muscle car is fine
muscle cars
very strong
people
what would be nice
very very versatile
I
eat cheese
[Music]
yeah
we're going to Vlad right now let's see
what Vlad has to say yo I've been so
immersed so far I've been able to tell
you any intention
[Music]
oh my God am I driving what's going on
I don't even have my tangent for No wait
it's there
tangent phone is here
I I already talked a little bit about it
yesterday in my member stream but did
you guys see me on Wayne's 3D showcase
it wasn't raining for detail case it was
so much fun we had so much fun
um together dancing together it may have
been a little bit stressful because we
didn't have much time to practice
together we literally only had like
two hours in the studio without a
teacher
because somebody forgot to book us the
notify the teacher
oh wait let me eat something
get out
um
and besides that I just learned the
choreo graphy at home but the Korean was
so cute there were so many like
um like you look like me
so many cute interactions so many hand
touching and it was so sweet so titty
right
yeah
I'm so happy they invited me for her
showcase
[Music]
not lose just tattoos
ah
yum it was so much fun you're going to
have your license revoked my friend
smoking in a bar is a crime plain and
simple
you're joking right this is a joke he's
gonna stick up his ass should I pull it
out this cousin is okay
great girl
girl stay away from her of course now
listen you did good with the pizza the
other day but now one more peasant is
trying to avoid pain who muskowski jerk
who owns their laundry in the Masterson
Street thinks in this country business
is done differently says he will call
cups on us okay
so jerk needs to be taught a lesson give
him a beating let him know might is
right
hey stop that smoking back there
isn't he also smoking was that a pen do
what are you gonna do
you don't know me I see anyone I don't
know you oh
would be funny if he was smoking too
hello
go to the laundromat okay why am I
carrying my guns openly
the the The Fog
there we go
now I can tell all my right attention so
yeah I was I was gonna say she's so
dorky and she's so touchy
it's cute she was always tone joking me
whenever I'm a winner like whenever
there's like a
time where we don't talk she just
randomly tone jokes me and I don't joke
her back don't joke
oh yeah and like when we were like
rehearsing
she was like testing like looking at
herself on the screen
and she would constantly make weird ass
poses that I was thinking oh is this
girl gonna gonna make those poses in her
pretty stream too
in our showcase too oh no like it was
very not lady like roses she like squads
and lift her leg and all that I'm like
wait a minute you're lazy lady bit
for me it wasn't so bad in the actual uh
wait
in the Stream she was she was she was a
quite ladylike oh yeah
not a good car
get in
okay
WS what's this I'm [\h__\h] losing him
I lost it give me this one
hopefully no police hopefully no police
okay okay okay we can do this
[Music]
I just need to
oh
okay
I thought I just left the car I was like
looking at my soul leaving my body or
something
let's go
why was that dude still in there
okay okay
we gotta catch up now
[Music]
trying again
yeah so since this whole like
environment was kind of new to Elena I
was like uh trying to like lead her like
help her with this and that like oh this
is how things are done bleep blah blue
I'm trying to
you know when she had something some
thoughts
even though she can speak Japanese I I
helped her to convey it to
the
to the staff and all that yeah
yeah
one thing though like oh my God it's
such an expensive new studio right and
yet you know what's missing proper
rappering
and I was like oh my God dying from the
heat because like we were dancing really
passionately
or at least I was
Nina also got really hot though and I'm
like girl
normally
I thought I thought Indonesia you girls
are used to really hot
weather temperature
but she was also getting super hot and
we were like dying and they were like
sorry no air conditioning because the
cameras you know the cameras
need to be kept at a certain temperature
I'm like okay but we're dying
yeah beer are they did they say that no
no way
are they marked right now oh yeah
what's marked I need to Mark the enemy
yeah but we were like
to ourselves complaining so much
oh that eventually they they turned on
some cooling but it was like outside the
room
I don't know if it really help
haha
caps lock I don't know if I need that I
don't know
should I is that what they want me to do
fancy there were no fans
I think they could set up fans though
[\h__\h] you're starting to piss me off are
you enjoying yourself [\h__\h]
I think fans don't change the
temperature so that would be a solution
yeah
oh life has no fans oh my God how far
we've sunken oh [\h__\h]
hmm
[\h__\h] this Quest you got me oh
yeah
the trouble getting it together blood is
impatient man you will be getting the
money to him soon
last minute I do not ask for a favor I
understand I will get it to it
I thought this country was different
really
and we got rid of the police
also well it's a good solution
yes
I spoke to the laundry medal he gets the
message it will pay you now I like your
style
it could be an intimidating guy
get back to the bathroom
and yeah still repeating some things a
little bit but I really liked Elena
singing disco thing because I love that
song and it fits her voice so wow that
was really high for me and even though
I'm not like a big fan of whole of love
life
um I enjoyed the song that we chose
it was almost gonna be a different song
but I'm glad it turned out to be this
song it was so perfect for us too
perfect duet song
and what's this like feeling that I got
this Vibe with this genre like I know
it's J-pop but they had like
or Oriental sounds in the song I think
you're not the hell you talking
um
one thing that cracked me up is like she
was cleaning up her room right that was
like I guess it's kind of I like the
idea it's kind of smart because by
cleaning up the room she was showing off
the the room you know and we all have
like some kind of segment in our 3D
streams why is it black and white
where we show off the room that was made
for specifically us
and normally everybody's just like
showing it off normally but she was
doing it while cleaning however
girl
you're such a princess like oh my God
he picks up free trash bags and this is
already like
exhausting this is so exhausting girl
girl girl
come on
already in trash bags she didn't even
have to collect things and put it in the
trash bags
two meters to the side and then the
calls in a day
oh man I
call it
[Music]
I should help her why
why me a lot of money until he pays me
well it was a funny gimmick I liked it
worldwide championships oh my God no in
the finale
my nose is bleeding is my nose bleeding
that's what she promised yeah
oh okay okay
girl come on
don't be so exhausted after free trash
bags
man
well say something you're so [\h__\h]
laid back
and one of us gotta be laid back
disgusting stuff
good we walked all the way over here so
you could snort coke no listen
Ah that's
that's better man Michael gets the good
stuff it's got some laxative in it
though it gives you a stomach problem
that's detailed
whatever I don't know oh yeah yeah so I
need you to head up to dukes and get a
car for me it's a silver blister and
it's packed on the project it's by EIC
subway station okay sure you got keys no
no your girl I need you to take the car
owes me hail some money take his car
instead huh we're gonna drive over there
what
are we gonna drive over there no you're
gonna take the train buddy you think I
want to be in the car with the peasants
I'll just take a different car I'm gonna
go meet somebody this car is tiny as
[\h__\h] anyway look how he's like slouched
in the car because
I need a bigger car
anyway I think Roman was calling me but
no bro
down from Roman don't treat me like a
Yelp review
come on
just trying to finish
finding out what's going on in the
moment
go up to the station if we're really
taking a train oh okay
they're trying to introduce me to the
train
what is this
wow New Yorker train hmm oh I've seen
that in friends a lot of time I guess
oh but not this kind of train
I think
oh
take out your cameras it's a train
wow sugoi train is so empty
I guess everybody stopped riding trains
in New York you I mean okay it's so
[\h__\h] disgusting
foreign
[Music]
yeah I wouldn't want to ride this train
either
[Music]
oh but cool view outside wow
wow
[Music]
amazing
and my chat died on my side let me fix
it real quick
[Music]
me not you guys huh
it's me not you it's me not you
go go go
find and take a Silva blister compact
alrighty where is it
oh
really close
what
does he have a knee problem
he walks down
oh my God
[Laughter]
cute car
I don't see where it is
okay well
oh
[Music]
no I can do it alone thank you
I was just trying to make it simple you
know I felt I felt like he wasn't gonna
give me the car
so I just wanted to
make it quick I have your new car Vlad
it's not pretty though real dirty yeah
over here
hi hey I could [\h__\h] this worse than the
little dirt car look like a praying
mantis
[Music]
where is it
that song was my absolute Jam when I was
in junior high school
I was listening on my MP3 player that
was super tiny my USB MP3 player I was
listening to it all the time on repeat
on the trip to
somewhere with our class I was listening
to it
everywhere I was listening to it
nice thank you for the gifts
[Music]
yeah no super chats but gifts are still
very much appreciated
yeah the real typical old MP3 player
where you you took you take the cap up
and then there's the USB stick and you
stick it into the
you see there's like all kinds of
different MP3 players from back in the
day I think but this like small one was
my favorite
it's so simple you just put it on the
in the PC and then you have a folder to
put the songs in hmm
fascinating yeah I wouldn't even use it
now honestly I would use it now even
hmm
I didn't have iPods no no money for the
iPod no
let's go lime wire
Good Times
oh you know what I I thought in the more
parts of this stream I thought the the
her mascot was so funny
it was so cute and her mascot I've never
seen this before with other mascots her
mascot actually made the sound
[Music]
he actually made a tambourine sound that
was so cute do I have to repair this car
too no
why is it so Gray
and then another funny thing
this
is your nose
oh [\h__\h] I can't chase with this car it's
supposed to stay pretty yeah
all right the circle is yeah already
ending okay easy easy easy
stay on the download
[Music]
for a moment easy
there we go okay I was gonna say yeah
one more thing that I found really funny
was her CM that was at the very end
advertisement
[Music]
I just expected uh like a legit
calm nice
advertisements this time oh God
it was so creepy holy [\h__\h] what's going
on
turned out to be a little bit terrifying
laughs
join down join that safety guaranteed
yo I'm so excited for all these
showcases
now that hour is done I'm just watching
everybody doing their thing
fun
for sure okay I have arrived
excuse me I don't want to kill you guys
move faster
and you dropped something
is he gonna
[Music]
not my
phone yeah you're gonna see how excited
Ollie is like I already like every time
when I saw her like practicing and stuff
she was always like always like
always twerking too
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
you're not as stupid as you look here
come back already
not so far
oh neat car without police looking oh I
wanted I want the strap one that one
looks like it's straight out of um
Greece
[Music]
can this guy get out should I stop for
him you want to get out
there we go
I've gotten out in the beginning Roman
what's it
about time I showed
to show you American silicone filled
titties
with me oh yeah
oh totally okay I guess we're changing
plans because we have to prioritize him
now
oh strip club sounds good I'll pick you
up in next now we have a day I'm waiting
for it nice car
oh
you're funny
okay don't get mad at me when sometimes
I have to do something else okay
mm-hmm
should we do wait does it matter if I do
Vlad first
can I still do Roman afterwards
hmm
can I is it timed
wrong but okay
I got you I got you I got you okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay why is it
so [\h__\h] gray again Michelle shut up
Michelle
[Music]
I'm not picking up the phone
ah silence
I'm already seeing ladies in the strip
club I don't need Michelle right now
[Music]
there we go oh we're here again
how big is the city I wonder
shut up lad
[Music]
think wanting a pace of me I'm so
popular oh my God
hi see what sick ride I got
this car
[Laughter]
I didn't want to leave it behind
okay where are we going oh I guess the
choo choo choo choo marks
what's the sound
huh
it's creeping me out
I think it's just like outside the
window though
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah it was just outside the
window
[Music]
[Applause]
it was short
yeah you're not hearing it then it's
just me I just thought it was weird
[Music]
at the pool
I saw a lady
she had kids too though
and she was dead with her guy
but on her butt I do not know how great
it is to have you here with me on her
butt she has a very terrible I still
remember cousin
red colored kiss Mark before I got here
I was wondering
we are doing all right America is an
opportunity for a new beginning I don't
think our guy gave her that with every
day we live
baggage and we must care he wants it
like right in the middle of her butt
cheeks how could I not look fresh and
clean
just because we get off a boat in a new
place staring at me the kids Mark was
staring at me Time Is A Healer
if you'll put
a tattoo
somewhere
like that it's asking people to look at
it no nothing helps a man forget like um
[Music]
that happened to you and think about all
these yeah
college girl girl
I heard that I haven't forgotten our
language completely
[Music]
I mean yeah if I put some of that on my
butt
when people look at it I'll be like well
yeah I mean I mean that's understandable
your eyes automatically go to things
like that yeah pay to talk if you don't
want to oh
okay
I paid it it's just five bucks
[Music]
yeah it was bright red it wasn't like
black or anything so it didn't even look
like a tattoo but I guess you can get
color tattooses
and I don't understand why you would put
something like that on your butt
temporarily
when you're going to swim
I don't know where
and like who would have given it to her
when she's got her guy
we weren't there's probably a tattoo
that's what I'm thinking yo look at me
maneuvering through that wow
noise
it's not Bronx the police
nice
let's move driving I learned from GTA
I was kind of worried because I saw
people say you know
the older the GTA game the jankier the
controls
but I don't see any difference to GTA to
be honest
[Music]
no difference for me
GTA
um GTA 4 is the worst driving what it's
the same for me to GTA 5 oh
[Music]
Christ
you think so
yeah
[Music]
cousin
you're a titty guy huh
[Music]
weapons aren't welcome in the club I
mean I don't know where to put him
they're still in my body
I mean on my body
can we get in
yeah
never been in the National strip club
before
the shape of things to come the Triangle
Club
what does that mean
eh
what's this picture like so out of place
this picture
huh
you want a little action sugar
okay right over here honey pie I don't
like your own like way of talking about
okay
she's got a [\h__\h] stamp
and in German We Say Goodbye
ask if I ask if I
don't know it's like an an
um uh antler uh ass antler
it's your happiness
no it's a directly translated uh yeah
ass antler doesn't that work so well I
mean look it is literally an ass antler
because they're often they're also
shaped exactly like that looks like an
antler
so awkward about music oh
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no
I don't know how the song really goes
oh
nice view
um
we've got a really nice butt it's shaped
really nicely
um
are you enjoying yourself I think I'm
gonna see you again right honey no I
think this is the only time I'm coming
to a strip club in this game
oh
what kind of that's an insulting rude
comment
are those real
um
why are we not adding money to her money
strap
oh you're a big boy
they don't do like this back home
build what
that was nice
thanks Kyle
looks nice beautiful
is killing me
every word every sentence she starts
with a uh
my God where's um where's my friend
Roman
it where's that
[Music]
where's him
ah
more ice cream
why don't you and I go somewhere a
little more private
damn girl you're wearing nothing for you
to handle huh
two little clothes for me to take off
I I like the I like the act of taking it
off you know so um
what do I do
what I do I feel so lost in here
oh there's a bulldog oh my God I didn't
look
ah thank you
are we done what do you think can I sit
down
[Music]
no
um
thank you
as always takanasi kiwawa master of
making awkward situations less awkward
yep yep yep where is your door
wait these are not doors
it's a private room when I went to the
wrong side
what about here is that all right oh
no
the doors are not in my favor
this is awkward without music wow
let's go Roman
we had some Romance
[Music]
yes coming coming to the car
stop talking about
making me nervous you have completed the
arranged activity
I'm taking Momo girl okay no I'm taking
him home
take him home
Roman my boy
we so so
shaped and
so well oiled
shiny and round
[Music]
bee boobs
you shall not forget though it's not all
about boobies
there's nice bugs too
if you look
at the right ones in the right angle
they look like boobs too just use your
imagination then you got four boobs
country uh take him home
my Roman bye
to the place
where he sleeps lips well he sleep
though
want his dreams off
[Music]
I'm awake oh no I did it
but I'm on a mission I gotta bring him
home
I got it bring him safely home
[\h__\h] out no I noticed yesterday that
my my butt from a certain angle looks
like boobs oh there it goes
there goes the hood
of my car
too bad
it looked really nice
now we only have half of a car
yeah from a certain screenshot I think
it was the screenshot where I was
hugging Dana
it looked like my butt was boobies
cleavage
um
kfb agrees right we looked at it
together in my members stream
you can't deny it
yes yes yes
versatile butts are very versatile
you can Sprint on you guys
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no
oh hold up break it down
baby if you really want me later
[Music]
okay now we go to Vlad I hope he's not
angry do you think he's angry
well not my problem or is it that's
probably my problem man oh well we'll be
fine
[Music]
he's always angry yeah
but he's starting to fall in love with
me I think because he seems really
smitten by me
it's just the irresistible charm that I
have I I know
I fell in love with myself every day too
hello
hey how you doing how you doing
it's up on the wall yeah I just noticed
glass of water
how can you only order you are dead wake
up you [\h__\h] you got me come over here
wow
your bamboozle no guy you saw me talking
oh seems like we're carrying no
consequences for this
this guy oh yeah
yeah you guys are the little kiss very
funny what would you say if I told you
he was going to wrap you cousin let's
see what the problem is he got with my
cousin hold on hey hey hey gorgeous no I
can't talk right now what are you
wearing
can't talk right now but don't tell me
what you're wearing I'll call you back
huh sorry
who was that never your mind was it Ivan
ooh that's funny
guy
yes and for an annoying dick you're
really an annoying dick well it's a real
same thing that I'm the guy with the
powerful friends and you are the little
punk who's only Francis is some fat
whistle who draws the [\h__\h] cab so why
is Ivan going to rob my cousin
because I want you to kill him what what
he's angered Mikhail Mr falson offended
him he thinks he's stealing some
paperwork from her mom you catch him and
kill him then we say it was just a
robbery that failed and what if I say I
don't want to be your Hitman
that Mr faustin will be very angry with
you and your cousin
I am so intimidated okay
I knew we would understand each other
once I put it in this simple way now go
wait for him by the car Depot
card Depot
one from before where were we okay now
listen let's talk about tonight
let's not talk about it let's just do it
isn't that what you really want to say
nothing into this car and no one can
stop me this looks nice
feels like it's gonna play some
synthwave
[Music]
um
what do you mean he's already oh oh whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa I thought we were
chilling
all right
SS
[Music]
oh ah that's the break the normal break
I thought okay okay that's what I've
been using as I thought that wasn't a
break I'm going to
early enough kind of
[Music]
not so bad not so bad oh
that's it right sorry
I was so short
hey driving for the middle is illegal
[\h__\h]
double break
my baby I'm a genius
[Music]
I wasn't sure about killing you in flare
desk now I'm coming around
[Music]
I don't know where it is
uh
oh he's kind of like
stuck up there probably again like uh
previously how do I get up there is
there is there some stairs that I'm
missing again
ladder
don't go here ah yes
turn turn turn
what was it f
do I have to keep on pressing oh
I'm coming for you
you're trying to rub my cousin vlad's
apartment
I've got something to show you well I
don't like you no more man
uh this is not a good place for you to
escape to
yeah
starting to sweat [\h__\h]
oh
nice junk food
got it
they had to show me that so otherwise I
would lose track I guess
we gotta do the same
all right all right
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] why is he screaming like
that
you made me worry about you
there ain't nowhere left for you to run
should I shoot well
[Music]
choose his face okay
can I shoot for this
[Laughter]
goodbye goodbye goodbye
see you never again it was nice chasing
you
nice to chase you
or how do I even is dead
he came to a sticky end hey
look you say that to my face and I will
break you oh um
huh
oh
no
can I fall down to the next one what
would I do
what do I do
I was gonna hold on to it again
[Laughter]
always this is it done I think we're
done with it right
because we already talked
yeah yeah
easy yeah
Karma
there's no karma in GTA
[Music]
before charge you for healthcare oh you
know how much did they charge me in
and probably got into the minus this is
America we're talking about what the
[\h__\h] is that
alcohol patch for liver abuse
that doesn't really exist right
anytime you want
thank you
thank you very useful in this city oh
nice car
[Music]
driving Mr Beverly
you got rights
are you sure about that I'm taking them
away
you have no right on this car my car
hi Carlo my car I'm driving it so my car
are you driving it no
it's not your car easy
it's like math one plus one
equals my car
out oh
yeah
we have arrived what is going on is New
York traffic like this this is the
catastrophe
baby
hey what's wrong hey cousin
[\h__\h] what's [\h__\h] worse probably
yeah
what about her I like her
I really like her but you keep messing
around with other women yeah I'm eating
my one
I saw his car parked outside the place
the other day
he knew what was I going to say you know
my woman was banging this war dog and
you didn't do anything I didn't say
anything I didn't know
what
I did for you
for your dick you're [\h__\h] dead I'm
sorry
all right I'm gonna deal with it right
now
no
sit there
I'm not going to stand here and have you
called me disloyal you might let some
Russian ass wipe bang your woman but I
won't but you
but therefore I knew you cared you
always what a hypocrite wait um the lady
here wait don't do anything stupid wait
for me the lady from them from the
office
no okay okay I won't take care of that
these guys are still like that oh my God
no don't do anything stupid cousin
nothing is stupid as living that fat
swine give it to Mallory hey it happens
do they need help
I have to do this
yeah
I should direct traffic that would be
fun
where is the next McDonald's
just doesn't look like a realistic New
York I need I need new McDonald's I need
kids
stay out here let the big boys have
their conversation inside
I mean not just New York but like any
they need fast food burger places okay
[Music]
did I summon you boy I told you to stay
away from Mallory and now Roman is upset
[Music]
excuse me do you think I give a [\h__\h]
peasant oh there he is don't make fun of
Romans
but we gave them an easy opening to make
fun of them
told me what to do did you hear that
voice yeah now get them out of here come
on come on oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] fist fight
again or can I use my weapons
[Music]
then we're in my way
Jesus
where's my car
do I have a car
there it is
you already in at least that's something
good
again chasing time
chasing is my hobby
all right he's running away we win let's
go
wait should I go here
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] Vlad is getting
away ah [\h__\h] he's like uh where the [\h__\h]
is he
[Music]
okay here we take the next right
this thing is
okay
right right right yeah yeah
okay always I always take the same
Escape rounds did I take the wrong path
I don't know okay okay
he'll come back the only thing
six feet of dirt forget about Mallory
plans change and you know when Vlad is
done with her grow a [\h__\h] spine
I have to end it here and now [\h__\h] I
don't like this
okay straight and then right on the
second one
um
he crashes no it's nice they always end
up crashing the cars don't they look
glad this crashed this car and gone
surely that is enough keep your head
down I'm going to finish this stop
nickel
you've killed yourself and your cousin
Yoko you are dead man
[\h__\h] Yokel you think you can get away
with this can't finish stopping me I'll
find out you think this is worth it you
are throwing you and your fatty cousins
lives away for that be the Puerto Rican
churcher I'm throwing your life away
prick we'll do all right my friends will
track you down you won't last I'll be
like building up for the for the whole
story of the game
[Music]
you can perform an execution on certain
characters
do it do it
yes
whole life Splash party
please buy a ticket to watch whole life
Splash parties
well I guess this is over what have you
done what does it look like
we're dead
no he's dead we're fine
he has powerful friends serious people I
told you to become you holding the joke
I am quiet tried to kill us he screwed
your girlfriend what do you expect I
give him a massage
I mean
it is a little bit escalated and
exaggerated button
we can't do half-assed things
when I was in the Army mm-hmm we're
going on
the meat Squad what killed a lot of
innocent people
they were our enemies what this is the
squat yeah
there were 15 of us old boys from the
village
but one of us betrayed the group
it was a setup
for money
12 people died
three Escape
I know the traitor was not me
so for 10 years
I've been searching for the other two
one of them leaves here oh
why are you telling me this now do you
always get sentimental after you kill
people
you kept asking
some Revenge mission for something that
happened 10 years ago and you don't care
whose life you're ruining away no well
what
I don't know
I just want to know why they did it
well right now I don't think you're
going to find out let's hide the body at
least for a while put him in the river
[Music]
[\h__\h]
get out of here you go I'll catch up
with you later
[Music]
maybe put some fish bait on him
hopefully the fish will eat him
so the body doesn't get found I don't
know
[Music]
if I'm gonna open upstairs scenarios
later and then if you wait to be cold
you can try calling them oh
yeah if we would have this is New York
apparently if you would have just left
him on the streets the rats would be
thanking me instead
okay when we call Roman is that what
we're doing
my pleasure
Roman I'm here what are you doing why do
you whisper
there's a
comedy TV show and German Austin TV
that's called
I think sounds so familiar to me
I think it's pretty good
oopsie
[Music]
or maybe it's supposed to go I also feel
like I heard Ghost Michael before
somewhere
oh well oh well oh well
I had two sips of a monster today
only two sips though
I tried out rbf's monster
I got the first two ships yeah
it was so sweet
it's like crazy sweet how could you
drink the whole bottle like oh my God
of a can
especially with monster they're they're
so huge that's why I really was excited
when I found the Tiny Monsters in Japan
which are I guess supposed to be more
highly concentrated but they probably
just end up still only being half of the
concentration of a normal monster here
because of the whatever laws of how much
towering they can put into it in Japan
as suppose
it's pretty low pretty low
but it did help me
even a little is enough for me after all
Roman
he's dumpster diving get out of there
man
Escape right now
[\h__\h] you everything was fine and then
you show up and never did because faster
needs a psychopath you guys are so happy
now now you man what was his man first
he was so happy when I came they killed
you
he's
so cute to me Vlad was a piece of trash
they don't care about him
all they care about is making money
so we say we work for them get out of
there you smell like cabbage I don't
want to man I'm [\h__\h] myself oh
get out of the dumpster Mr
come on fatty
boss wants a little chat
wow they tracked us down fast
can we do waterboarding and stuff
um
wake up I mean we're not in control but
we have to gag him to stop the screaming
you shouldn't have brought them here
Andre they look like nice people though
oh and the boss is not happy I think
Balkan is his name it's my pants you
know [\h__\h] but you will
who are you working for oh what's that
for cousin Roman
speak
okay okay
you're dead likes it up the ass what do
you want me to say oh [\h__\h]
very funny do you think you're so smart
no not tied up in the basement a long
way from home or some ape threatens me
with a hacksaw
watching television
what are you doing I love how women have
so much control over all these evil Bad
Boys
who is he
it's cousin you were about to cut up
some guy in
making all that noise to find out he's
his cousin
where did you find this idiot he was a
friend of your sergeant when you're
invisible stock he's an imbecile
so
Nico Bellic you think it's okay to kill
my employees if he is an escrow yes yes
him as a look at me like M piece of [\h__\h]
oh I guess he was an [\h__\h] but just
using the logic on him
because I say [\h__\h] his sister
you owe me
I got some diggers in my neighborhood
trying to run a shipment yeah wait what
about your wife found a buyer for the
TVs yes a buyer but you've got to get
them for us so we can make the sale okay
Roman
o
he shot his foot
away
on the floor
listen we'll take care of your cousin
but you better get a police car and then
you call me
I loved one of the escalates robin go go
go I'll take care of him [\h__\h]
Roman you idiot
you little idiot man
escalated quickly yeah oh wow where are
we wow
this in New York jeez oh but it's like
at the end of
whoa where is this
what what place is this
in terms of New York
what's up nice suburbs
sell his car
that one
there's a there's police coming oh
they won't see
oh oh the red one is nice I was gonna
say this one isn't special with this
finally a nice [\h__\h] car
wait
I have a feeling it's not gonna be that
easy
um
good
went well no
wait it is easy why is it easy
wow
[Music]
wow wow
can I keep it
mommy can I keep
[Music]
I promise I'm taking care of me
[Applause]
where are we going with this fancy car
I passed the police car so what and they
don't know it's not my car and also now
it is my car so
[Music]
and they said I need to Copper wow
what [\h__\h]
ah Mama me I want the diesel car why
don't I just take the cop car thing and
put it on top of my car well it's
another one
suddenly I see them everywhere
well okay
excuse me I have a question to ask who
do you mind
now I just want to ask something real
quick
please let me ask
I have a gun in my hand for my own
protection and your protection get me
the car why won't they let me in
foreign
[Music]
big trouble but wait the circle is over
right there
oh nice car wait is it like the more you
progress in the game the more nice cars
will be available
we're out of the circle
really no no no
no oh this was easy guys I have the
police car what now the man is driving
around South broker pull it over take it
to our lock up on Duke's drive be more
specific how many events you think there
are at South broker that is a problem
for you
cousin not me keep pulling Vans over oh
it's the area fancy area
okay okay
find and pull over the Vans before they
reach it
where is the destination what
they're driving
foreign
[Music]
I don't know where to cut them off
because like I'm like here there's no
immediate connection
um
maybe I'll go back
they're up there but
[Music]
what do we what do I do if I got close
to them I Ram them again or what
South
I don't know where South is
[Music]
leg
s
alrighty
[Music]
um
are they all going in different
directions
turn on your siren
okay well um
we just want this one first let's try
this one first
how do I turn on the siren
G okay
okay
[Music]
where did he
okay okay okay basically where it just
came from
can I like lose them or will they just
endlessly cycle Circle nah probably not
but if they all go different ways what
am I supposed to do
um
[Music]
make way
I see him
[Music]
stay close to the van make it pull over
all right pull over perfect
Park up and approach your drivers when
uh like on feet
did I look
I don't got insurance
show me the back you carrying TVs no TVs
teammates are illegal
wrong is it scripted
yeah Vega
is this scripted that like the bird car
the first rock you find is the one
um
random yes random
I'm getting mixed answers
not scripted random oh dear okay well
this one's the closest now so uh I think
I'll go there
[Music]
can I go this way too
oh okay
[Music]
he's on the
the Bottom Road right
[Music]
on the right side okay okay okay okay
okay so I got my vision on him
pull over police NYPD
or Liberty City so LLC okay
LCPD show me what you got two two people
come out real slow [\h__\h] I wouldn't
do this Penny Petrovic is looking after
this truck open up the back you got any
flat screens this is a big screw-up [\h__\h]
wrong move [\h__\h]
oh
I got the right one
uh where's my gun
where's the other one what do I do now I
get the car I got this one right
[Laughter]
[Music]
but we didn't get the card again
let me uh turn over on the side I think
oh
my God
Doki Doki
foreign police doesn't give a [\h__\h] in
the city I'm telling you they don't give
a [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
they see me doing all the crimes and
they're like entertained by it probably
that's why they let me keep on doing it
or their links their fans must be fans
not getting paid enough with this [\h__\h]
if I close my eyes it's not happening
I close I I don't see it I don't know
laughs
just ignore the situation
so far this game feels much easier to me
than GTA 5 I have
look I struggled a lot more but I guess
yeah there might be like a lot of
difficult missions coming up baby
I'm better maybe it's a GTA experience I
remember some some GTA missions I GTA 5
missions I also struggled a lot
yeah
well well eventually we'll have
something like that too I'm sure
sorry
sorry oh my God
but as long as it's not the whole game
that's making me really frustrated and
just a little bit
it's okay
a little bit of suffering and struggling
sufficient suffering you know
that's good oh dear
girl
lady what are you waiting for huh
B
your dream guys man will you say how's
Roman it's okay
good Miguel you'll need someone like you
stop by and see him sometime
the second band was the right one we did
it
nice too maybe I should put away my gun
nobody cares if I'm carrying the gun it
seems
I have yet to see it the other like
Islands
why don't we go in there is this is this
the Central Park
looks kind of small it's called Middle
Park here
where's next
what the [\h__\h]
what's next what do we do next
[Music]
fun bug with a swing set somewhere in
the city you should check it out later
oh maybe maybe another time yeah y'all
fun bug
do you like go on the swing and then
send you flying or something
Roman are you all right
there's shots in your stomach yeah and
then stitched up in the doctor's office
that was dirtier than the basement we
were nearly tortured in oh great you
sound calm actually that's to me
out of it if you're near a shop can you
pick up some adult diapers for me
oh
oh baby
oh man okay there's police stations to
the car right now
where is he
huh
can I see an F just now on the Minima ah
at the very bottom
I build bathroom do I really have to
pick up diapers or is that like a jerk
I don't know how I feel about picking up
diapers
[Music]
things are actually close to where I'm
at I'm now oh really
I could probably find diapers on the
streets
ew
those would most definitely be used so I
don't think Roman would appreciate that
we're doing it for real
we can't give him used episodes we're
probably not even
adult diapers then probably
hmm
well
you know I tweeted about it but
[Music]
remember last year when I talked about
going to a convention with my friends
that was happening like
thank you huh
like
yeah yeah the whole thing where in the
screw up where hmm there's like this
convention splits into two organizers
and one they were like announcing
separate dates for the same supposedly
same convention
and me and my friends we didn't know
about it but we just wanted to go to
this Italian convention because because
it's just like nice
um to have a beach a Beach Convention
for once really cool Italy has cool
conventions they're all like kind of in
the evening too
so we really wanted to go there and then
after we booked everything
pretty quite a while later we realized
oh
we
we made a mistake
absolutely though
I'm sorry
I'm sorry so right now the same
convention or the actual convention is
happening
some of my friends went there or are
there
yeah and I was kind of like thinking of
going too but like it's in the middle of
like in between all my trips if I was
gone now at the convention you guys
would barely see me the whole month and
I felt bad like I felt like I couldn't
do that but I see my friends having a
good time and like they they're like
showing pictures and videos and it looks
like a great time
yeah
yeah all the Italian cosplayers are so
pretty they're so pretty clouds your
judgment not now it's not the time
they're glowing
a judgment
that's a good one
I'm a fool
a drunken fool Nico's here we're going
to go take care of that guy I take it
you won't be joining us
make him suffer no they don't get pain
so quickly
you need to come down with that stuff
why
so I can be like you Mr barbecue
always so [\h__\h] up on painkillers you
don't give a [\h__\h] you need to calm down
where would we be now if I was calm like
you let me guess in a prison camp in
Siberia or selling hash to tourists in
Red Square or still in the Navy which is
it today be careful dimitry before
you be careful
getting crazy
that's the way it works
I am angry you are calm
I scare you reason
it works yes but you've angered the
wrong people Too Many Bodies too much
attention will be dealt with if we don't
start playing by the rules angles I've
angered people
me
how do we
nice couch stretch are we looking at
some ghosts
it's us
when I have to push people
it's me
all alone
[Music]
after all we've done together you're
getting delusional
oh my god look we have to go
I [\h__\h] love it
I [\h__\h] love you I know yes
but you treat me
like a child
I run things
my [\h__\h] way
get out of my sight
[Music]
or I [\h__\h] kill you
I'm not saying don't run things your way
I'm saying become
here
take a couple of these
what are you still doing here
I said get out of my side
oh his wife is pretty
damn
changing me to the sex shop
for buying something for Vlad or what
we're going to that sex shop okay
sure why not
yeah anyway yeah yeah yeah the cool
invention is happening in his basement
okay
how much money there is in selling this
stuff online a whole [\h__\h] rain is
nice
said and try not to kill them taking a
bite of this pie would be very
profitable for our operation I got no
problem with sparing some lives no it's
Mikhail that has that issue can't keep
his finger off it wasn't always like
this though things got to you and don't
get to me
okay okay
you'd love UK why oh because of the rain
okay that that was scary that Thunder
was scary
although I think the rain looks quite
nice in the game right now
well yeah have you guys ever seen
a beach
wait a Beach Convention not to the beach
it would be even nice if there's actual
people there it's like when we went it
was like only like normal beachgoers and
then
yeah us
confused austrians
we already knew by the time we were
there but you know
it's really sad and this year
they're going without me hmm
where's your boss what do you mean he's
uh in the back no no no SpongeBob music
playing oh they're just having a meeting
I swear get out of the way
you see they don't make them like that
no more
that's a vintage bush
if it wasn't for that I'd say this
weren't worth transferring
do you think you can
make these
parts that we was gonna cut you your
books are closed until you pass our cut
Nico take this and cover Joseph I
already have little videos
Target Joseph
[Music]
well they don't react to it
[Applause]
for Mr falston fine here you go we ain't
gonna have the reef you should have
thought of that earlier I'm special I'm
gonna be a star oh don't hurt me I like
big foot this is amazing what Kelly is
so important style what
not anymore
oh we're going to an Alleyway off of
Dylan Street in sharper
[Laughter]
the gun gives me too much power
we're seeing a friend of mine who's got
a good line of weapons
a few around the city the mayor has a
real hard on for gun control guns don't
seem that control I've seen plenty and I
just got here do you know where to get
them for yourself most of the time I'm
the one carrying it though
foreign
we will make more money with him alive
okay okay
[\h__\h]
you're lucky Robin don't try to make you
kill someone every two seconds
what's going on
you put them on speakerphone so I know
I killed the man without killing him oh
oh oh
I I feel bad now
foreign
[Music]
's account
uh-huh
okay wait
[Music]
you buy Robin's gun stores oh my God
this place looks so shady
they're not very stalked either
hahaha
you suck because I was being honest if
you don't see something you need now
I'll come back later hmm
okay
but I mean purchase a micro what some
micro probably small like this oh yeah
this
uh effort or e
what ah
cute
yeah do I have that money how much money
do I have
I don't have enough money
dude
oh thank God
[Music]
you'll be dry I ain't a cow I ain't
Russian
wait didn't didn't he say like I can get
anything though
or just the one thing
[Music]
it sounded like I could get anything
also you guys saying ammo where is the
ammo this thing
no that's grenades
where's GMO
only this thing is free oh okay
go near the gun
[Music]
ah press enter the button okay
this is enough because this is going
from my account
not buying more than that
come on
oh this one
better not be too expensive
oh
am I wearing it automatically or
do it I have to put it on
yeah okay
I understood the blue bar now
wow okay
drive us to Mr faustins
Mr faustin small
I made German puns no you and Mr faustin
have you always argued and made up like
this it wasn't always like this was a
great man he had a temper but he was
fair now he blows his top at the
slightest thing I never know who he will
shoot who he will step Andre who you met
in mikhail's basement he was always
loyal he was a good worker now he's dead
what is that that is why we need your
help remind faustin of death maybe then
he will not try to kill me thous means
fist in means in and I added fast ins
vowel Mao means uh mouth but like you
know kind of like slang not so elegant
way
yeah first in your mouth
well now that I think of it we have like
so many like not so nice words for mouth
probably more than that
what would you guys say in English
yeah
that's very Austrian I think or like
maybe also South Germany
oh yeah we have so many
Gob in English
that just sounds stupid
thank you for your help Nicole come to
see us at the club soon because you will
be cool by them also sounds weird
you're welcome
[Music]
I've got an F and a LJ going on why are
they blinking
I think I'll go to LJ
what's F again
oh Faust is that faustin
wait why did my chat scroll up
should I go too fasten
[Music]
hm hmm
well I'll take his good car again he'll
go
to me
I I wanna I wanna
I Wanna Get To Know faustin
yo how did he get his car back
is it like a different shade this time
it was more like bright red before now
it's like a sophisticated nice wine red
I like it
oh
not tonight
oh my God
and that was burgundy I guess he got a
new car he didn't get his car back
there's just different one
problem
stuff just a little Ferrari
it's basically for us the same as
buying a pair of new shoes
cheap ones of course
oh wait oh a minute
I was having fun driving so straight
I missed my turn again on Young
DPS honestly when I see people driving
because I don't have a license in real
life
I'm always on the passenger seat
fascinates me how people can drive so
well
following the GPS although other people
are really bad at following it and Miss
every freaking possible exit on the
highway
I took care of that thing for you very
good I'm proud of you good
music
yeah
that's what I bought oh my God what's
going on is that fast then
Dimitri thank you
no problem Dimitri Dimitri hey hey uh
meet my girl Natasha Nice to meet
[Music]
a little delicious you should put me
into a future GTA game as an NPC hey my
brother Nico please sit down have a
drink move up ladies we have something
we need to talk about wouldn't that be
so cool
[Laughter]
girls can you give us a minute please
[Music]
keep it warm it won't be too long won't
ever happen but it would be cool so
what is it
we've got police trouble
the feds or someone are all over us
Sergey told me that a friend of his in
the courts told him that is a Dancer you
little [\h__\h] and they know about the pot
pointy bunk
[\h__\h]
who is right it's no one it's just the
way we've been behaving making too much
noise this was inevitable we're going to
have to come things right down for a
while
I know it is
I saw it in his eyes you know that guy
that guy who bought the car but he
didn't buy the pot Lenny he's my
cousin's boyfriend yes he's a [\h__\h] yes
but he's okay I don't trust him what I
just told you he knows too much
you okay
are you sure
sure
right now I'm wondering if it's him or
you because there were ladies at first
it could be champagne I think for a
second this has been going on for months
think
look where you're thinking has got us
you were in charge of security good job
well done make sure you add extra cake
when you mod her in uh-huh you
prove you're loyal Go and Kill the guy
don't question my loyalty that don't
question my orders
he lives on Guantanamo Avenue in Bohan
head up there and call me me personally
when you get there Mikhail please don't
do this shut up shut the [\h__\h] up I'm
begging you shut the [\h__\h] please don't
do this
[Music]
oh dear why
one more 20 memberships let's go
welcome
we had a member stream yesterday it
wasn't what what's on the phone they'll
have to fix that
but we had fun nonetheless
[Music]
what no I don't know when I can do a
member stream next like this month I'm
sorry it's looking kinda looking kind of
empty I'll do my best to do a couple
more than usual in August so
[Music]
also by the way I didn't talk about this
at all but uh like we tried some things
right for
fixing the audio issue that only happens
when I open one certain program AKA one
of our application programs for live
programs
um it doesn't happen with any other
programs although I don't think it's
necessarily whole life's fault because
when I was researching a little bit
I found someone like on the internet one
year ago who's been having the same
issue
with who also uses a ghost or R and who
also reported that it has a 4080 by the
way and 4080 so kind of like similar
situation maybe
um but yeah like when when opening one
certain game or one or two certain games
he would have like kind of the same
issue seems like it
and like he was looking for a solution
and updated like five months later that
he tried everything he didn't really
find the solution but ended up giving up
on it
um
because
yeah and maybe some like especially
because it seems like the go XLR
[Music]
Sports
it's like this contains you not they're
not updating it anymore apparently the
team left
the team which was doing like updates
and stuff
left and was doing other things now I
guess I guess I just heard of that
recently
so that's kind of bad so many people
used to go to R like what the what are
they gonna do
my mind
for the last time
yeah so
[Music]
um
that guy ended up just giving up and
bought himself
like a different setup and then it
worked and I don't know if I have to do
the same thing I mean for now it works
with the the other whole live app and I
I still haven't heard back from the
staff
if they know
[Music]
like any other well what what could be
done to fix it maybe there is a fix I
don't know
[Music]
why would they stop helping people no I
I don't know the team just left I guess
I
something like
financial problems or so within the
company I have no idea there's some
detailed information somewhere I'm sure
but
I don't have it in my brain right now
what's this where do I go
do I go inside
um hopefully the open source version of
The Crystal Apple there is one
what am I doing yeah up
train tracks
okay go there
well I am there
uh there
oh nice car
yeah so I'm still looking for a solution
but
um
[Music]
maybe like the the setup that the guy
mentioned apparently is made by the
people who left the gold XLR Helicon
team it's
like they created something new similar
so maybe I'll try that out
you killed
I'm like in the middle of talking what
take down Lenny who's Lenny
who's Lenny sure
hopefully no train coming
you dead I think he's dead what how can
you not be Dead come on
alrighty we gotta run
oh nice car there
what I lost the Stars I lost the spice
[Music]
what
how
Nico do you know what you have I
followed
not much more before you killed with
this is a very dangerous man you will
not take kindly to this how was I to
know you weren't this is mikhail's
craziness I will speak to you I'll see
what I can do
thanks okay I'm just doing my job
wait is my armor my Blues look so little
what the [\h__\h]
Little Jacob what's up what's going on
Nico I coaching with real Batman hero
tickled on come see I easy LJ
okay I think he's telling me to come see
him
okey dokey we can do that it's a long
drive though
what's Portugal done
what does that mean
I got shot
I know I got shot but why does it
already take so much of my new fresh
armor
is that why you guys wanted me to get it
because you knew that this was going to
be a little bit dangerous come see me at
the Dakota
I always do this because I feel like it
should be escape to close the phone
ah
and then Nico started a fire
the fire today
what's the sound
ah is it the engine
fancy sports car makes
fart sounds wow
[Music]
it's like
sparkling
what
I went way too fast I'm sorry
horticulture
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way
everybody's just leaving the perfect
amount of space in between for me thank
you
very much appreciated and breakthrough
[Music]
[Applause]
that's not funny
she's a maniac maniac on the floor
[Music]
hell no
Maybe
[Music]
we're still good we only have one star
anyway I just broke through the [\h__\h]
thing how can that be a no-go when I'm
constantly ramming all the street lights
and they don't give a [\h__\h]
because it costs money to use the
highway I guess well well well
you should be honored that I'm using
your Highway because
with this beautiful car
I'm creating eye candy for everyone to
look at
out
that he looked at the road but if
there's traffic jam you know they got
nothing to look at and then for that
they have me
hey
oh where you come from how are you hey
man I'm here to see Jake
off the door someone called himself
yeah I should have maybe knocked on the
door not just walk in
you want to control the taxi
I'm Gonna Knock on people doing things
oh it's okay come on don't worry watch
what I do you know see how your boy over
there
you're all right no problem you call me
an introduction is any other
yeah let me hear that you know
anywhere
whoa whoa
what all right let me explain
right they are selling weed but they're
not supposed to sell weed and they're
not cutting they mean okay so when you
go down there and deal with them and God
right there's nothing thank God he made
it where do I find it a little bit
easier for me
about cheap well now we're about cheap
enough
with that
you could be wrapping the part to a
Rihanna song
nervous seeing they will find it when
you go up on the corner of Alpha and
Sobo on saying when you go down and just
deal with them
all right all right I feel like I'm
going crazy I'm having a stroke or
something
yeah sure I'm sure all right
I think we have over there
I don't understand
just not and smile smiling nod
I just know he offered me a small camp
and something about cheap
uh
no hold on
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] are you doing are you
playing GTA too
because you're driving like me
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
you guys are not helping me ah
it's okay I am the problem wait why I
had to go straight
God damn
like I know I created them because I was
indecisive
um
Nico was like you when you watch whole
talk
very comprehensible translation
I
uh
my car
what should I do
oh no we have to do we have to pay money
again not that not like we're paying it
but yikes
wow okay I will pay I'll pay
why do I have to wait
foreign
I want to see them pay
gracias
my turn
hello
good night
is it what
[Music]
no
no no not fair
not fair what what I was trying to pay
the thing was open I was waiting and I
was like should I
mean
[Music]
Mario Kart moments right there whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa
whoa okay easy stay safe
wow
on the wall
damn okay back on track I need a new car
soon
cutting Corners at every corner
I was like offering itself to me as a
ramp oh what's going on here
ladies
well now they're gone that's some good
[\h__\h] you don't clean me out
yo game looks pretty good
be ready
I want to deal with the supplies would
stay behind him try not to be soon okay
well um
how difficult is this gonna be
sneak level of 1000
is he gonna look behind no
okay okay
easy
I'm so sneaky
I'm hungry
so
foreign
still have to be like not suspicious
God damn it it's my [\h__\h] phone though
let me let me in let me in
[\h__\h]
did he crash
oh there he is
so come on
the deal is in the apartment block fall
but don't attack him oh okay
wait what in there
sorry babe
up up
okay
excuse me
where is he I'm looking isn't it gonna
get you [\h__\h] looking for someone what
about in here
no [\h__\h]
fish some all places so difficult to run
through
ah
man are these all like homeless people
kind of a scary place to be in
and excuse me princess are you princess
you oh my is that a gosh I picked up the
gun
damage the luck to break uh open the
door uh which which door
[\h__\h] which door
not this one
maybe right it didn't need to be damaged
uh
I'm lost well I see the point but what
is it showing me this
no
down
there's many doors
this one
damage it
we're taking him down now okay
oh [\h__\h] I switched by accident come on
it's okay to kill him now right
[Music]
I got these let me kill you
their aim is so [\h__\h] wow
mine too
or I will finish you off
okay little Jacob gave me a thumbs up
for that it's like we're on Facebook or
Instagram
Little Jacob liked that
noise
still bad man like a moment of the
competition
the corner belong to I again
One Love
one love I like that sentiment that's
beautiful
it was I got that one too
[Music]
I'm walking back down
I wonder what Roman wanted from me
should I call him
man leave a message hell no
call me pick up what are you doing is he
dead
you wanted to go bowling ah
it's time for bowling
he wow we're very busy at the moment I
need to make progress in the game
oh [\h__\h]
I don't know where I left my car but we
were going to go for a new car anyway
right
so I was totally not trespassing right
there officer Michelle
no
not really
if I say no I'm kind of in the middle of
something some other time
you don't want to hang out
well thanks
thanks a lot [\h__\h] don't be so beautiful
buddy I'm sorry
don't give me that attitude girl hey
man
um
hey I'm gonna go to Roman anyway
oh come on I stumbled
I didn't do nothing
[Music]
yeah bye this is nonsense
get in this car this one looks nice
open roof let's go
I didn't do nothing
you just got did he say that
well thank you for getting the car that
I ordered from Amazon for me from the
shop yeah oh thank you thank you I
appreciate it
bump into them with confidence guys
that's the way
the wow away
this straight through the middle
there's no other way
easy
people will be all too frightened to
Drive outside after I get my license in
real life nobody will want to use their
cards anymore
how's it going okay you and Batman got
any more work you need help with the
point out
so I was reading the script you can do
some extra work now for Jacob
but I'm going to Roman right now I
haven't seen them in a while I want to
see how his his wound has healed
[\h__\h] I'm gonna get out of this car
oh what is this
looking pretty
oh thanks for getting out I'm making it
easy for me
[Music]
yeah this is a sick Massacre although
yeah I don't know about this like hat
looking thing that I keep on seeing
I didn't see that at all the muscle cars
and uh
in GTA oh this is a low riding muscle
car whoa
cool it can be both at the same time
right
um
no
Andrea looks like a hat a car hat looks
weird
like a sandwich looks like a
like a
like those cheese crackers or something
in between I don't know
not this car you can do it but not this
this is not it looks like a muscle car
to me it's kind of wide I guess not I
need to I need to practice my muscle car
knowledge again
the heart is so cute that heart very
cute
oh we came to the car service place
we'll just get there damn this big
who is this
have you met my cousin
we met online heard about you love
me.net
or both players my friend players
for real classy but also fake teeth
that's how I like me we've got fake
teeth I work at it so they should
sparkly yeah what is he talking about
Lucy's a dreamer
he stands my vision oh holy [\h__\h] they're
so white I'm blinded screw you listen
man you should try going online I know
how to come
of course technophob Lou died we got to
get you online it's a world of
opportunity such as
kinds of things yesterday I was online
and I discovered a Blog about the women
who don't like to shave that's very
important
I promise Bruce here go out with him can
you go out and get it sorted uh okay go
to [\h__\h] and register on one of the PCS
there a pretty girl is expecting it
right internet cafe
and the family keeps sending me news for
you
Brucie yeah stop exercising okay
put some [\h__\h] to the sort VIP stock
what does that mean he's a cool guy
speaking weird languages again internet
um
oh yeah that's weird why do I have to do
that
Roman making me do some weird chance
it sounded kind of German when I said it
first so I tried to add a little bit
more attitude to it
that's so German
foreign
[Music]
I need to hear it again I already forgot
the full
sentence
something with putting a sword
makes sense though I think it makes
sense
is this place actually running right now
yeah okay okay why is everything so dark
and blue and gray much better my name's
Nico my cousin they told me to come here
Roman he me about you he's so funny I
set you up on that computer already
follow the instructions on there okay
okay
uh I've been to an internet cafe like
maybe maximum twice in my life
I think it was to print out something
and and the other time I don't even know
probably only once
[Music]
you can use um I want some privacy
I saw like something about an internet
cafe
somewhere in Asia where you get like
like you oh like a booth yeah and then
uh you get snacks in this net like a lot
of food and
and then you watch on the screen you get
to one and actually wait it's not an
into the cafe it's kind of like a mix
but I think it's more focused on being a
restaurant however this restaurant is
for like people who want to eat while
watching a movie so there's like a
screen on on the table
maybe it was Korea yeah maybe it could
be or elsewhere I don't know I didn't
look so closely
um
but it was like they had like so many
dishes on their table it was like a
small booth
they were all eating alone and there was
a screen where they were watching anime
yeah
sounds like something for me not not
necessarily for watching anime but like
I always always I need to watch
something while eating I cannot
not watch something while eating hmm it
was not Japan no no no no
web
I am now online this is the main should
we go on my YouTube channel
am I here to find love or what
dating website
I'm on the internet
click the check mail link to view your
mailbox or the envelope icon on the
browser oh okay okay
your inbox lists all the emails you have
received I find mail team Welcome to our
farm mail
subscribe
okay
[Music]
Oh I thought I thought that way I go
back okay
um go back to the previous video click
the background
[Music]
that's it
that's all we're doing boring
[Music]
okay
they're not doing anything these people
are just pretending
bye bye lady
she was kind of cute
check the websites
now
you almost got me out out of my car and
back in there again
I'm hungry you know I won't be playing
much longer anyway because we're playing
tomorrow again anyway and I need to read
some super Jazz um
I really need to resupage yeah
and it's been four and a half hours
actually time passes by fast doesn't it
we'll do one more thing
whatever comes up oh wait there's an F
we'll go down there again
wow I'm completely ignoring the exist
existence of taxes again in this game
because I just love driving
[Music]
I love it
so relaxing oh somebody's calling me
okay
what
what go to no no no no no no no no no no
Jacob I can't do a show just now no
problem oh my God he's at least
understanding about it my lady wasn't
um
I was looking at comments
good thing this game is 80 driving yeah
I like it I like this
driving simulator very much
full of steroids and tell them how great
these abs are no you can take care of
that dog by himself
is a major Motorhead he's going to send
you emails about all the cars he wants
and you're going to get them for what
I'm going to do
it's like the weapon question uh breath
of the wild let's hang out soon okay
I'm probably in totk too where you
there's this little child who wants to
see all kinds of weapons
I think that's what it was
if you say yes what
you say yes and go back and cancel you
won't lose relationship points
what the [\h__\h]
I told you where she is
how many times oh dear keep an eye on
the [\h__\h] girl
oh man
someday I'll crucify you
nicobaric
yes
good name
thanks where's the images
he said he had something to do something
something poor lady me and this guy we
were
very present together we are like
brothers
now it's always something always
something always something yes
you want a drink no thank you well I do
thanks for the hint
I'll use that in the future Maybe
you all right what [\h__\h] sick
no
I'm [\h__\h] angry
I'm sorry to hear that
let me ask you something
you know her I can't say her okay
camera man
good
you're dead
by knowing her that's a bit too much
don't you think
she's my daughter
I'm grateful page I bring her here
I spoil her rotten
raise her well yeah
look my bubbles
yeah yeah she's uh very lucky
she is she said out of control [\h__\h]
because of you you pathetic mess
but I don't accept my daughter turning
into a [\h__\h] Nico she said Firefly
Island
she's meeting up with this bike
find imagery for me okay have him call
me sure
go all right
I already bursted a couple like
yesterday when I was walking I was
trying I noticed yeah
it was like a big chunk of
skin just like hanging there on the back
of my foot yeah a blister and I got um I
quickly got some because it really hurts
to walk I had it on both sides both feet
quickly got some Band-Aids but I just I
just uh took the Band-Aid off and yeah
it didn't heal of course it doesn't heal
but I had to put them on because I
needed to walk no it's not better now
not better at all I tried to I tried to
tear off the skin now but
Midway through I gave up because it was
not feeling good
maybe I'll cut it
scissor later
yeah no not cheap shoes I don't know
those are even sandals that I walk in so
much but recently every pair of shoes
and locking in gives me blisters
hmm
[Music]
except if I wear uh socks I guess not
even dance sometimes yeah
yeah a struggle
yeah I'll just cut off the Flappy part
sorry it sounds a bit disgusting
[\h__\h] blisters man
it's painful so painful
[Music]
too much walking not even that much
like five minutes walking it happens
already
I want you all to myself how old is you
in the way for Mr faustin's daughter
[\h__\h] you
Russia and we ain't communists her
father who was talking about that and
we're gonna kick your [\h__\h] ass
well at least we got the daughter
oh yeah we didn't get on the back
don't believe in the daughter behind
[Music]
take out the biker damn okay wow
[Applause]
well the sound is funny
press s to break is there also a
handbrake or no
[Music]
it doesn't shoot so far
I got him
okay
I'll probably fail this
[Music]
oops
where do we restart after I found them
or no
[\h__\h]
um
I'll take the free car again what color
is it this time is up
black gray dark gray
you know
and sliver my way through
yeah the checkpoints are kind of rough
looks like it was better in GTA 5.
but it's okay it's manageable still
[Music]
this is as if I was driving and looking
at my phone wallet because I'm looking
at your chat messages don't don't look
at your phone while driving guys
I doubt most of the time it will go
as well as it's going for me
[Music]
don't talk to police under any
circumstances do not Bonk the police
unless we're in a situation like we were
before
wait till you get to San Andreas why
why why why am I property of the lost
now that's how you watch my streams oh
no
I don't want to take responsibility for
that that sounds dangerous
please be careful
okay now I'm even faster damn
[Music]
that was fast
Speed Run what now
hold down
bye for the girl nicely done right
I was on a mission I've killed the biker
I don't know how happy your daughter
will be
here I care about discipline and loyalty
wow you don't care about your daughter's
happiness
[\h__\h] man
like even the like weirdest
fathers who love violence and are into
criminal [\h__\h] I think they care about
their daughter very much
what the [\h__\h] man
I don't know
what you doing now
[Music]
he's psychotic
even travel cared about Michael's yeah
I'm in yeah I still
maybe it will change later I still uh
like forever less
[Music]
but
um yeah but I'm trying to find where to
turn
[Music]
but in in terms of you know
all that
Trevor is taking the win so far
[Music]
oh
I guess I think but that doesn't really
make him much of a good person though
just by winning in that one point
yeah yeah he was very cartoony now this
black guy feels kind of different you
know he's got a very different vibe to
him
you guys understand
oh yeah oh yeah GTA 4 is a dark game
I guess
okay
should I wait outside no no come in oh
thank you you're welcome
and who do I mean
I mean they're all [\h__\h] down
thank you
you want some tea
sure tea time
doesn't let me use this anymore says it
makes sense I I know this we had it at
work before like immigrants oh yeah
thinking it's
funny coming from him
no Hotel breakfast buffet yeah
he did not used to be like this
When We Were Young at home
he was beautiful no he was happy
he made me happy
but um then something changed she looked
prettier on the photos I never quite
knew what it was
so many years I wondered what it was or
what was wrong with me
that I did not see it in him
or I changed him
life is complicated I
I never thought I'd live like this no
when the war came I did bad things oh
we're getting sentimental again I'm
doing bad things
killed people smuggled people
sold people
and you don't worry about your soul
getting real
after you walk into a village and you
see 50 Children all sitting neatly in a
row against the church world
each with their throats cut and their
hands chopped off
you realize that the creature that could
do this
doesn't have a soul oh yeah
but what about you God is very good you
did that you mustn't pull up hope is he
saying I don't know about that
it's because someone else does that
doesn't mean that
be better than the other guy
[Music]
what did you want
I want you to teach people
to listen to you want him to get us the
money for the money Mikhail please calm
down we're already in a lot of trouble I
mean okay it's traumatizing and all that
who are you my daddy
so
what do you want
this prayer who owes me money
owns a garage in Chase point
I want you to pick up a truck and take
it to him
call me when you get to the truck it's
in shotler on Montauk Avenue go
oh
get out of here
but if you're okay with that dude I'm
gonna do that tomorrow all right
because of old-fashioned Furniture no no
no no no no now is
break time uh but I didn't see it saying
that saved are we good
like how um
oh
is it safe sleep to safe it's safe
before and maybe we have to watch the
cutscene again or whatever
yeah nice so
a nice recap anyway oh this this time
with bright red again I don't know are
there only three colors that he Cycles
through
yeah red red on the Ferrari looks pretty
nice yeah
yeah a mid-set Mid Mission am I
um I can find a balance any bed can I
sleep in their bed
no so
on the mission wow I should have stopped
before
can I look at let's try can we taxi
through the map where's my home where do
I sleep
where do I sleep
restaurant
where would I sleep what the [\h__\h]
why don't I have a home
oh unavailable Mid Mission I Want the
Funk ah whatever we'll start tomorrow
wherever we
get back into the game
it can't throw me back too much anyway
probably maybe right before the cutscene
or whatever
that's fine
that's fine quit I quit I'm done
was fun though
it was a lot of fun I'm so happy we're
playing another
GTA game so tomorrow we'll continue so
you guys be there or be square and then
uh yeah there will be a little bit of a
break until we can play it again I
assume
I don't think I can squeeze it anywhere
anytime soon
unfortunately but
I'll be back yeah
I'll be back and now we go to my office
or my my girl's room which one do you
want for Super Chat reading was fun
right it was fun for me too
we're like breezing speeding through the
story at least that's what it feels like
to me
close rail
okay
zooming through it it's going so fast
yeah damn
damn damn damn
ghost oh
what's going on here I didn't clean this
is from the members stream oh no you can
see how much I was
talking about the Showcase
and my my desk my disk space
yeah okay okay okay
[Music]
um
dead Wawa is on my chair can someone
remove the dead Wawa please
[Music]
where is she this
make way for the real Wawa
there we go
I reset something
okay wonderful
oh I'm a bit bit too big still I guess
okay
an empty husk of Huawei I just leave the
I leave my bodies behind
like a snake
yeah so far I really like to day four
just as much as GTA 5. I mean look at
GTA 5 baby is a bit better but
having a good time
hope we can play more
and yeah hope you guys will join me
through this journey
this adventure another crazy adventure
with crazy characters
and crazy stupid lore
um I'm choosing some bgm right now
which one
maybe this one
wait
oh
there you go
[Music]
hope you like this Jazzy Bossa Nova
whatever music
[Music]
used it a couple times before already
so we're still so behind on Super Chat
so I'll continue using a hollow Miser
um
[Music]
I've got to
do
oh but I don't I don't know down where I
stopped yesterday you guys know
[Music]
oh okay
of the countdown stream right
[Music]
around 102
um
[Music]
found it okay
no
[Music]
um
man it's so big ah damn make it darker
again for you guys
[Music]
you need a bit darker
this
yeah this is uh lots of Reds and pinks
in one gold
Maya
[Music]
um
let me take a fruit candy
before we get started
see how I can how long I can go without
food
what are you gonna do our thumbnail
the countdown Vamp nail please oh do I
have it
[Music]
cat hair
where's my mouth
[Music]
no food yet can grab snack
um
no I'm okay
well let me turn on the light
[Music]
but let me stretch
just walked into the room said meow and
then flopped down on the ground and
stood also do a big stretch you know a
good trick
she woke up pretty sure she just woke up
show me how to do a good stretch oh
she's so soft
she's such a plushie
[Music]
come on
yeah yeah I
she eventually left and I was recording
something short yesterday
stretch in between my stream
[Music]
optimize dreams
long stream
stream get up I noticed like because of
my bad poster and how I'm sitting on my
feet
how [\h__\h] my like my legs are
um
okay I'm back
and we have to continue you guys did
under twos around here okay
[Music]
ah good day mate it's your big uh day
today I wish you all the strength and
love from everyone to pursue whatever
you want you never cease to amaze me
with your passion and love even when
you're when you're crook oh is that a
Australian word for sick
you still talk to us like to us you're
the best boss happy birthday
[Music]
crook I see
thank you for teaching me new words I am
expanding my Horizon oh Lord checking
mates checking made something for you on
Twitter ah
I'm gonna check it out later
[Music]
here's a kiss for you um wow
I hope I don't get crook so often
anymore
[Music]
my
Illuminati system
has been disappointing me so many times
man
you're sad
[Music]
um
for the memberships too thank you
3D I'll see you on the next birthday and
I literally every every stream until
that birthday thank you so much for the
support
thank you
go straight oh I think I saw like a
remake or so of it
looks really good
interesting enough if I think if I'm
thinking of the right game
um
wasn't that in the Nintendo Direct
[Music]
where am I confusing from
was ah
yeah it looks cute I I like the visuals
I think
you know you know crazy for it ah
I don't know if we have perms for it I
would have to check
thank you for the recipe chat happy
birthday Kiana you never cease to amaze
me with your passion and dedication to
your friends and fans you were awesome
Sunday night
hope you have a wonderful birthday and
cheers to all your current and future
successes
[Music]
thank you
thank you if you're doing that exciting
time so much going on thank you so much
for everything
please continue to be the loyal and
sweet kfp that you are thank you my one
of my few Canadian chickens I need you I
need you whenever there's a
Chihuahua appearance at a Canadian
convention I need someone I need someone
to show up in Orange
[Music]
please thank you mwah
fandenstein thank you for the pinky
it's been two years since I found you
and won a wild ride it's been from your
report on Ina oversleeping Ah that's a
long time ago to the empress era and sad
Sparks oh to cooking corned beef
board
it's been an absolute blast to be part
of it all happy birthday Kiara the way
you put it into words it sounds like
being a fan of me is a blast
hmm
I do good streams don't you think
the other day I know I'm an overslept
her new show right
but
I was busy with stuff we were doing
something yeah it was right before the
collab
and before that I was streaming though
so I didn't have time to I didn't even
realize I was just like preparing I
thought Ahmed was like doing her thing
um
[Music]
otherwise I could have done a little
waiting stream but it was right in
between me doing a long stream and then
the mythical lab
yeah
yeah I watched it afterwards and she was
like adding more angles because she was
doing it in 3D
amazing
amazing she's uh innovating and and
upgrading her new show I like it a lot
really cool
but then she kind of uh like she showed
up to all the angles in the beginning
and then I felt like she was not really
using using the angles
afterwards after she showed it off once
she just stayed in the same angle the
whole time
you show the amount yeah she showed my
version lots of other things
[Music]
yeah maybe she should give me the
controls over the camera angles I've got
some experience with it in whole talk
just give me the remote
give me the remote control
[Music]
chihuahua behind the scenes I'm the new
Bubba
foreign
happy birthday to the most beautiful
most benevolent and most amazing boss in
the whole universe I'm so happy to be
able to celebrate such an important
moment yet again this year truly nothing
makes me happier than to be able to
celebrate occasions like this to gather
with you plus me too also it's a double
red thank you
thank you for being there for me thank
you you're so sweet
really appreciate it we spent so many
important moments together celebrate
together but also the normal moments
normal
are nice too thank you for always being
there
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
let's keep on spending time together
okay
ah
um
thank you for the pinky It's the final
countdown it's our final countdown to
the wobble birthday
I'm sure you had that in mind right when
you wrote that
feels like it to me
feel it
I'm an empath
before hyping it up let's go
Kiana bus oh thank you for the word so
much oh my God I saw so so so many
photos in my uh art hashtag over the
past weeks
off the bus
what a beautiful bus
happy birthday quinoa overseas kfb held
a project called Kiana bus to celebrate
your birthday hope you like it was 2020.
thanks so cool thank you so much for
making that and the art on it was of
course gorgeous
um
I wonder if the people who posted the
pictures
on Twitter there's there were so many
different people I wonder if they all
purposefully went out to find it or if
they found if a lot of them found it
randomly
but I heard that the bus line
was like one of the most busy bus lines
in the city
um
so
yeah we got a lot of people to look at
kiwawa
thank you so much for doing that really
really cool
I enjoyed seeing it so much yeah
thank you thank you thank you I
appreciate it a lot free advertisement
okay see you next time
[Music]
foreign
well you know our
we're still we're still getting started
connect the web with your wrath even
more than four Fest really
our girl is a center has her EP coming
hard work paying off thank you yeah
there's muchos muchos going on right now
makes me wonder if
maybe
ottoman uh
a winter will be empty but things will
probably
[Music]
um
eventually all come in place
it's always like oh I'm busy now I'll be
I won't be busy if I get over this busy
time and then surprise bamboozle
always busy so
I try my best to balance it currently
the problem is like normally I can
always balance like recordings and other
things
um work related things and real life
related things while streaming quite
well
but when it comes to
those times where I actually have to
travel in person that's where it gets
difficult even for me normally I really
try everything I can
and I think it works out pretty pretty
well so far
to uh balance everything
in terms of work and streaming and
everything
but you know when I have to go to Japan
to do certain things it gets a bit more
rough
it's exhausting it takes up a lot of
time
and it's a very different environment so
even when I'm like chilling in the hotel
at times where I could stream
you know I can't stream because shitty
internet connection no sound proofing
didn't bring all of my equipment anyway
because I knew that's what how it was
gonna be yeah but I'll I'll try to do if
I have some time I'll do Twitter spaces
again on my next trip
um
so keep an eye out for the Twitter
spaces
but there are
two streams definitely happening
proper streams
[Music]
besides that I guess some Twitter spaces
you know the thing is though because I
barely have anything like properly set
in stone I don't know if I should make a
schedule but so far I've used this
month's art only once for this week's
wallpaper
and
yeah when I think about the rest of the
month
[Music]
not many
hmm like not much not much there to put
on schedules
honestly I don't know yeah
one for next week even though a lot of
it would look empty
um
yeah
for the sake of using the art another
time
because you're at Camp well they'll be
recorded always don't worry I always
record them
twin spaces you'll be able to hear it
for as long as Twitter keeps it up
yeah I could use it for a thumbnail if I
don't use the whole art if I just cut
one part yeah but I haven't really been
doing that because I don't wanna
I don't know I just don't want to
[Music]
yeah I wanted to put it on YouTube but
then I got busy and now it's already so
late so I feel like I missed the timing
to do it because it took a while
um I I had to
like ask Twitter to send me the file
basically there's like a function
where you can download your own Twitter
space
but it takes some time it took like two
two days
for them to send it to me
[Music]
no
and I'm not gonna like I don't know I
try to while doing that I also looked up
a different website to do it and that
one also took like it didn't happen
immediately it also took forever
[Music]
New Hollow cure update trailer just came
out oh
oh interesting
[Music]
I'm gonna watch it later but I want to
focus on super chats now
anyway thank you mental Daddy
chocolate insomnia thing for the words
of patan hi tento I can't believe it is
your third birthday and I got to
celebrate with you on all three of them
yo you're always there
have a happy birthday you made us proud
of your Sparks performance and connect
the world concert I made sure to save my
voice to share extra loud for you thank
you
[Music]
I heard you loud and clear
wow
you're so sweet you're on all my
birthdays and you even went to the
concert wow
big kfp thank you it means so much to me
I appreciate it out
maybe I'll look here early access again
no there will be no more early accessing
I think
[Music]
I've been told no more because I don't
know
everybody all all whole life members
well
uh
get access at the same time
I don't know I just asked you know and I
got Early Access anybody could have done
it but um
I think yeah
maybe some
wanted to get early access to and then I
don't know
um
no not because of the steam release I
think but but it's okay I don't care
we'll just wait
wait it's okay doesn't matter when we
play it
I'm looking forward to it though
to see what has been added I want to
play cool ball
[Music]
oh everybody will be so much fun to play
oh my God
[Music]
well if you watch the new trailer I
guess you can probably imagine even
better
I can't right now but yeah
anyway thank you chocolate insomnia
[Music]
I hope you didn't get sick or anything
afterwards because I heard many people
got sick afterwards please stay healthy
for me
I'm here thank you for the pinky can't
believe this Piano thank you
[Music]
kfb so look
that's clang ambition uh
chromatic College
I didn't thankfully good very good stay
stay that way
[Music]
Bruno thank you for the red
birthday thank you hope your special day
brings you as much joy as you always
bring us thank you
Brazilian kfp
I saw right now
Brazilian convention that I went to
before is happening
right now again I think
you going there probably not but
come to Brazil Brazil
yeah good reason to come to Brazil
[Music]
they could invite me though
um
the Brazil girl I'm begging you don't
beg no I've already been there twice in
person
Brazilian cosplays are so cute too oh
yeah I remember one very clearly
I talked to Brazilian cosplayers in
Brazil
one
one specific one I will never forget
because she's so cute
[Music]
free
yeah
[Music]
anyway thank you
thank you so much
happy birthday captain Joe you are now
an eternity plus three years old I wish
you an absolute amazing birthday filled
with lots of love from Friends
colleagues and kfb we are all
celebrating feel free to not well you
should if you write a message like this
and you want to add this then write it
in the beginning
you're trolling me aren't you if you
read it at the end of course I already
read the Super Chat
at that point
[Music]
you have to write it in the beginning
logical bear dance is not very logical
the way you made it
illogical paradox
hmm
Chicken brain
ah Fink chicken think
but thank you Alexander
maybe it was on purpose I will not rule
that option out
thank you thank you thank you
eating my Tyson's ass what's up what's
up vision Amazon thanks
and thank you
[Music]
um
see uh let's see probably
[Music]
said it what do you mean what did I say
oranges look like Reds yeah yeah yeah
don't worry I won't I won't miss them I
see it very clearly oh my test is
[\h__\h]
[Music]
thank you Lord Lord hork 999.
thank you for the rest of the chat
um
happy birthday Tanto thank you happy
birthday to you too
[Music]
thank you for saying hi on my special
day
oh thank you for membership
[Music]
give that cat a kiss for me too please
look so cute
thank you
Mr empty blog thanks for the pinky happy
birthday and to you a happy birthday as
well
wouldn't it be funny if actually it was
their birthdays
and I just so accidentally got it right
that would be funny never gonna happen
though
unless you make it your birthday
can you officially change your birthday
probably no you can change your name
officially but not your birthday I'm
assuming
could you have a legit reason why you
would want that yeah maybe maybe I think
yes if your uh birthday falls on the
leap year
Maybe maybe they should allow you to
change your birthday officially
[Music]
I think that would be nice Witness
Protection
uh-huh but that's only for the time
being right
[Music]
or a bay ow all right because she's on
the leap year
well well
she's still celebrating it every day so
you know
no problem there anyway thank you Mr
empty plug yeah I don't think I see your
name that much so thank you for being
there
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
foreign
thank you waiting on to board the plane
huh did you catch the plane properly
hopefully hopefully thank you
out running the wind literally
with the airplane
chat happy birthday Kiana thanks for all
the great work so far these three years
I hope we'll see uh and hear each other
much more from you hear much more from
you in times to come Cafe is with you
Phoenix down for as the blessing of the
Phoenix empowers us all
give me forever I feel the passion I
feel the passion and the love thank you
you're the best
solo
[Music]
Chad
um
[Music]
no bad thank you for the recipe chat
been watching since Debbie wow sent a
hundred dollar red before but never
joined the membership for convenience
reasons
my membership would make your life more
convenient
okay I give this makeup for it thank you
wait so you're saying you're still not
in the membership
[Music]
I think the money then I don't
understand
what is the convenience
[Music]
but no it's okay you do you if you don't
if you don't want to then that's fine
but I'm happy that you've been here
since the beginning and you're still
here thank you so much
practicing and for the big support too
wow
it's too much but thank you mwah
[Music]
yeah look at the emotes
and the the wallpapers
um
and the member streams more content
but okay you do you if you if you got
your reason you got your reason I'm sure
you got a reason that makes sense
somewhere in in your mind
[Music]
blood donations
and did I give you a kiss though no bad
come here
Sheldon thank you for the words of the
chat happy birthday Kiana a gift from
the bottom of Evan's heart
why
not from your heart oh
don't fight in the chat
I'm Bob Dylan thank you hiya how you
doing
hope you're doing well
anyway thank you Sheldon
foreign
I don't know what's going on what's the
reason behind this but I appreciate it
thank you so much
won't talk thanks for the pinky happy
birthday didn't you loved you in the LA
event thank you were you there wait
um probably you just watched it uh
online right which is fine too of course
but sounded like you were there
guessing you watched it online
thank you for the support thank you soon
nice gift thank you for the gift
uncle
[Music]
looks like a rainbow
very interrupted rainbow but thank you
wow
what a chat because there is not a
single
message written in here
thank you so much for the support it's a
beautiful rainbow
most beautiful rainbow I have seen thank
you
you know guys I'm like really [\h__\h]
tired I'm trying so hard to not seem
tired do I seem tired trying so hard
[Music]
maybe it's hitting me from those two
sips I took from the answer I'm
pretending well good good good good like
deep inside I'm dying
my eyes are like closing itself
no no a little bit more I just started
but I think I'm making good progress
because I'm not like tangenting much
um
[Music]
I have to read
at least a half an hour more
[Music]
skyfacturing Skyward
red Jack thank you thank you Brandon
Powell thank you thank you for the pinky
hi Kevin I'm sorry I can't stick around
because of medical issues I just wanted
to pop in and to say happy early
birthday thank you medical issues
are you okay Brandon
is it like a temporary thing hopefully
I hope you're getting better
please take care of yourself okay
so it's understandable if you can't be
there for medical issues hope you will
be back again I'm waiting for you come
back
and what is this how do I read this you
guys are seeing it now so you can tell
me how to read it somebody knows for
sure
[Music]
meanwhile I'll read this maybe Mexican
things
[Music]
look happy birthday to my favorite
Facebook thank you
thank you
we're singing coming
to me from Far Far Away actually not
that far away I guess
thank you so much
thank you thank you thank you for
celebrating with me
glad you are there
nobody told me how to read this
I'm waiting this how do I read this
[Music]
what is this
or this but I think it just says hello
me how what
[Music]
says hello no I don't mean I don't mean
the message I mean the name well
nobody here you can read this for real
like this I can read as well
tried
it
[Music]
a minute
okay okay fine fine fine
oh come on
[Music]
Google
Translate
[Music]
thank you also thanks for the membership
boo
and for watching me for so long
thank you for wishing me so much love
thank you
[Music]
Arigato thank you sir I think I saw this
when it came in or you guys like
notified me thank you
thank you guys for all the memberships
oh my God
[Music]
or something like that thank you for
eign
[Music]
thank you
thank you for the recipe
[Music]
another year another okay while my
birthday another birthday I share with
my one and only Lucy
thank you for being so hard working and
such a good mom that always takes care
of her Champion kids we all love you
very very very very
thank you I love you guys too
for being there do we
I always like hearing words like these
I like it
it's like music in my ears thank you
mwah
no back thank you for the recipe chat
happy birthday thank you thank you too
for the support
Anton m thank you for the recipe
and happy birthday Kiana I woke up at 2
am to watch you level up thank you
there's no 3D birthday concert this year
but it doesn't matter because just
spending time with you is fun and
Unforgettable stay creative energetic
and spicy
recently I haven't been eating castle
that often for breakfast
I've been eating um like some butter
bread soft butter bread with butter and
Nutella or Jam or uh like chocolate tea
cereals and stuff
[Music]
yeah I just wanted a little bit change
of bread
but I'm gonna go back to the croissant
don't worry
I cannot go too long without quaffle
it's not just normal bread it's special
buttery bread I really like The Buttery
soft bread it's really nice sometimes
yeah croissant is eternal my soul is in
my heart forever
and croissant knows it also knows I'm
going back
Castle is just waiting for me
send me cuanto from France oh please
[Music]
yeah brioche that's the thing I've been
eating brioche
[Music]
to go on a croissant trip
did you guys see the video I might have
mentioned it before but did you guys see
the video of this like guy who's
ironically testing classes of famous
places in Paris while in the background
there's like uh all kinds of riots going
on
and he's just standing there being
filmed assistant he stands in the middle
of it and just like
yeah uh eating the croissant and then
giving a rating for it
it's got like millions of views so if
you look it up like croissant review in
Paris or so you'll probably find it
[Music]
um
yeah some protests going on
don't know what they were protesting
about but
it was funny
[Music]
just him you know he had him he had a
mission he had to film a video
YouTuber priorities you know
[Music]
but I'm pretty sure like that's the joke
for him though like maybe he already
planned to make that video but the riot
being there he saw it as an opportunity
to make the video even more interesting
found it good
[Music]
yeah yeah
Paris seems like there's always
protests going on
it's always interesting enough on its
own but why not why not add a little
extra spice to it
[Music]
huh
Italiano in Paris Paris eating the
croissant
France is just a GTA's online server oh
my God
oh you no I'm sure they were not
protesting against quaso how could they
I don't believe it
oh there's a bug on my display let me
smash it
oh it didn't even it didn't even try to
go run away
I don't know if I really smashed it
like didn't try to resist
[Music]
[Laughter]
make me feel bad about it
um
[Laughter]
all righty thank you Anthony
now you make me want to eat but tomorrow
is Sunday so there's no cluster for me
tomorrow
bug was depressed no bug is tired no
mouth Pros I don't think it was a moth
[Music]
although I do think there's muff
muffs somewhere hidden in my closet and
sometimes on clothes that I don't move
for a long time
I find
like the The Leftovers of like moth eggs
on the clothes and then I have to wash
everything again
[Music]
um
yeah
if you move you're close a lot it won't
happen though
[Music]
I love it eat the struggles
he destroyed clothes really
the only thing I noticed is that my bed
sheets not the
not the ones for the blankets and
everything but the one to put over the
mattress
is getting more and more holes but that
might have just been my cats
[Music]
lavender
lavender house
yeah it's probably just my cat's bad one
yeah
[Music]
um
thank you
happy birthday boss have a nice day
[Music]
for the sweet words and the support
wow
[Music]
space wonderful thank you for the recipe
chat as well happy birthday Kiana wish
you only the best for your first
birthday with us this is my very first
red Super Chat oh you deserve to get my
beloved kamiosi
you're super cute funny kind-hearted and
talented Queen you're my main source of
motivation and my favorite entertainer
ever wow really I motivate you
thank you
that's great to hear thank you I'm glad
I can do that for you
you are
good
thank you for being with me thank you
for your first ever
appreciate it so much
I hope you're not
skipping any meals because of me
[Music]
I'm gonna sleep tonight huh
hello thank you for the recipe chat
happy birthday ah thank you
very very
old school kfp
thank you for celebrating with me thank
you
oh wait I get it now
you're called Flappy boy and you got the
butterfly thing you call it a flappy boy
[Music]
you call the butterfly a flappy boy he
do be a flappy boy
I never made that connection I thought
the butterfly was just a random profile
picture
wow wow
wow breaking
mind blown
are you saying go birdie it's your
birthday we're gonna party like it's
your birthday we're gonna stop um like
it's super birthday
I think I know what this is supposed to
be but I don't know if I sang it
correctly something like that probably
do not that much but
it's good every once in a while it's
pretty good especially when I'm showing
someone around in Austria
I'm like look this is a cool drink that
we have in Austria and I also take
one I order one
okay
I did
no worries
get Flappy bye
[Music]
um
happy birthday
funny orange bird are you laughing at me
are you mocking me
we have tons of fun this birthday and in
the moms to come ciao
my Italian chicken
I love me some Italian chicken
thank you so much we back oh YouTube was
gone what the [\h__\h]
maybe the archive will be fine
[Music]
I was asking if you were if you're
mocking me
happy birthday funny orange bird you're
mocking me you're laughing at me
thank you for the support
Italian here Italian no I seen you a lot
around too
[Music]
foreign
for the pinky happy birthday thank you
thank you very much appreciated
thank you for the recipe
it has been amazing here and I can't
wait for what the future has in store
with your EP official Horror Story Final
Fantasy streams and everything else yay
I am looking forward to those
specifically
you'll have to wait until August but it
will happen it will happen I'll I can't
promise I'll finish it it depends on how
much I like it but I mean how could I
not like it right
it's just like
I think it's something weird going on
with my brain like I've been always
asking to play Square Enix and final
Final Fantasy games
asking and asking and asking and then
now it's here and I'm like
questioning do I really want it that
much
but I'm sure I will like really like it
once I get into it
yeah
so
I hope you don't have to wait for too
long but thank you for being patient and
thank you for always supporting me no
matter what I do thank you
happy birthday boss
guys we went from 102 to 447 holy [\h__\h]
and there's so many Reds and pinks
damn
happy birthday boss congrats on yet
another trip around the Sun
you put it in a different light
and hot off the heels of an outstanding
concert performance known as so true so
true
never had a dull moment of you around
lots of love and appreciation for all
you do Academy Aussie thank you
oh I know I know it's not counting like
really like there's things in between
yeah but but still
still I'm going fast and I'm very tired
[Music]
thank you Arthur thank you for the sweet
sweet and gentle kind words
and I love having you around thank you
thank you for being part of kfp our fur
have a fantastic day you too I don't
know if you're here now but if you are
I hope your day is going splendidly
thank you soon for your sweet sweetness
[Music]
also red one happy birthday thank
you he's a deadbeat is it
you're that beat thanks for saying hi
and and celebrating with me
thank you
[Music]
and the MK free OC Duncan Marcus many
says thank you thank you
thank you for everything yeah third one
already I swear it feels like it's
getting faster while the streams and
walls get longer do they know
I think I've like in the first year I've
said this before but I feel like I did
longer streams in the first year
[Music]
like my stamina streaming stamina has
gone down a little bit still not like
you know I still do long streams but you
look good it was yeah I toned it down a
little bit
hmm
yeah but still like plenty for you guys
to panic about catching up on
[Music]
yeah the 11 hour veterans that was more
like you know me playing stuff like
Tales of our eyes where I just
I just could play endlessly
hmm
[Music]
yeah tltk was also one of those games I
didn't go to 11 hours but still that was
also a game I just couldn't turn off
[Music]
hmm because while they are also like
like
um I think you know some games I'm also
really really enjoying the only reason
why I'm not playing them as long is
because they're a little bit more
exhausting too or draining to play even
though they're great and like a lot of
fun
some games are more draining than others
now taking more energy
um anyway did I read this all thanks for
all the awesome moments and being
awesome yourself hope you have a great
birthday and a great year thank you
so far I think I'm having a pretty
exciting yeah really exciting year we've
had finally the 3D debuts we've had four
fests
[Music]
we're having summer concert we had the
Ian only concert we've been having lots
of Japan trips and part of the like
theme song for the summer concert thingy
there's many things going on
now I'm creating an album
it's been a big year yeah but every
every year is a big year but it just
feels like it never ends on the
excitement
which might be maybe kind of exhausting
for him
the viewers I hope not I hope not I mean
I feel like the thing is like we're
preparing for all these scenes
constantly behind the scenes so maybe it
feels a bit more draining for us because
you guys don't have to do all the work
uh to create these exciting moments you
just get to enjoy the results
I can do this all day wonderful
it doesn't affect you
it's good that's good
okay
good to know
it feels a bit different for us I think
but still exciting just a bit more
exhausting
[Music]
um
more memberships oh my God thank you
guys in exchange for not being able to
send super jets you guys are spending so
many memberships thank you
[Music]
thank you
um thank you
love you
crappy Old MacDonald
thank you for the recipe chat why do you
think
I understand the order here happy
[\h__\h]
internal plus three
months already your first birthday since
your debut yeah
how when what yeah same
how can it be my third birthday if I'm
not at three years yet
but I debuted after my birthday like in
September logic wait how can it be oh
okay I think I understand
it's hard to wrap my my brain around it
um
oh
[Music]
great I agree I agree
zero to one
one
zero one two two
three
yeah makes sense
don't question it uh is also confused
not just me I have no idea what to write
so have a great day hope you enjoyed
reading one more Super Chat love you
thank you
did you have a good day hold on um
are you having a great weekend
spending it with me the Wawa
[Music]
yeah great me too me too so far I mean
busy busy busy trying to squeeze a
million things before my streams
recently
trying to squeeze in swimming workout
and everything fixing PC and whatever oh
my God cleaning my apartment it's been a
bit
trying to not get
um not feel stressed out well yeah
you've been doing a great job thank you
it's actually amazing
that I'm keeping up with the swimming
right now
um
[Music]
thank you Hogan for all the heights
thank you for the red super chat that's
the name that I don't think I've seen
before in the Super Chat reading
happy birthday thank you for an amazing
year thank you for being part of it I
hope you will be part of the rest of the
year as well thank you so much mwah
ahead of time now
you have to stay
the kiss was a promise
thank you
uh
[Music]
how you doing
now crayons a tea face with a random
jazz
Sealed With a Kiss exactly
doing fine
myself
damn
station is
[Music]
foreign
having German discussions very intense
yeah and also I started with that but
please
[Music]
speaking Austrian dialect now
huh
poster and die like this so funny
[Music]
dad dad
how [\h__\h] witty am I in German damn
[Laughter]
[Music]
you will never know
wow wow wow
[Music]
it was it was funny I would say it was
funny
and in German she says what
I was winning I was hella witty
um wear bear cannot keep up with these
translations
and where was I uh Happy Birthday Canada
membership on your birthday which means
I've also revived from the bucket now
I'm excited for wow a winter 3D live oh
KFC has five extra months for voltage
training now thank you
yeah oh yeah you can try to utakere to
all my album songs I don't think I would
be performing all of them
because there's been like some cover
songs that I like already had planned
out in my set list for the birthday
3D live
and I don't want to throw everything
completely in the trash
[Music]
um
yeah yeah yeah
so it won't be it won't be completely
original songs there's certain songs I
wanted to perform with certain people
[Music]
working on it
not really
not at the moment actually not working
on it yet sadly I wish I was
anyway thank you so much
crayons
such a sweet chicken thank you for being
part of kfb
[Music]
a
um
[Music]
we have to sing that sometime in karaoke
hmm
not nautical
not support
[Music]
Ed
mama
[Music]
again
more
subscribe
[Music]
thank you
another polish
kfb KF Poland
thank you so much
for the rest of the chat happy birthday
to you sweet Phoenix
[Music]
always happy when people actually tell
the truth ah
thank y'all
[Music]
sweet
YouTube Sweet Chicken you are sweet
chicken I am sweet Phoenix okay okay
the rule the rules you know very
important
[Music]
um
love you wish you happy
I can hear it I look at this and I can
hear that
thank you
wow sweetheart
[Music]
um
I can finish these
[Music]
scroll bar is like so much lower than it
was before
Lego
[Music]
person
that's
[Music]
the pinky happy birthday thanks for the
pinky as well happy birthday Wawa we
didn't just take pics we took videos so
it definitely happened I believe it
thanks for connecting all of us
worldwide sending about 300 hugs your
way Jacoby was busy this year during
Wawa on worldwide
man I'm kind of like bumped on the one
dookomi the first dukumi where they had
three days instead of two and probably
also used one more convention hall I
assume
than usual I wasn't there kind of kind
of sad but oh well
hope you guys all had fun over there
now
let me just say this again really
clearly way ahead of time I will not be
a dokomi
performing or anything or guesting or
anything so uh
do not like book your trip or whatever
if you think
that I will be you know doing something
there
you still want to go okay and you do you
who knows I hope nothing overlaps themes
weirdly like this year but yeah I can
tell you I will not be like guessing
[Music]
yeah
oh what date
what date is it right before Anime Expo
again damn
again
well they're completely different
continents so I think it normally
doesn't matter to normal people
the 28th to 30th uh-huh
[Music]
oh ax is one week later
so that this year it overlapped right
next year it won't
do both if you want to
I don't know why you would go to both
there's no reason to go to both
that's just uh
I don't know crazy
thank you Dominique for organizing that
though that was really cool
[Music]
thing in person but um
thank you Eugene you Jen L thank
question
marry some strawberries
the koala University
[Music]
thank you for being the amazing Phoenix
you are you make our life so much better
and bringing kfp together it was my
first ever really
cool
you're so wholesome always think
[Music]
I think celebrating my birthday
thank you soon
I will continue doing my best so please
continue supporting me foreign
[Music]
don't break out enjoy don't break out
enjoy don't break out enjoy you are my
eternal let's see and I can't wait for
all the future 3D performances
especially the epitas because everyone's
calling it on the nap but
[Music]
it is an album I'll tell you that it is
an album
um
we're going
full album really yeah
I wasn't sure when I was creating it but
uh in the first like
a few weeks but there's an album now
yeah I wasn't sure before now I am sure
my cat's lips open maybe I wanted to
make you guys uncertain
I didn't want to reveal everything but
now I want to correct you guys because
everybody says EP
what's the difference the amount of
songs
APS are usually like four songs or
something like that four or five maybe
I think everything starting from six
could be an album
to
10 or whatever I mean I guess album
could be endless but then it's more like
I don't know crazy
[Music]
but you will see you will see
so thank you and please wait for that
album
[Music]
again
okay I was too early but now it's your
birthday happy birthday cue out you
didn't have to send it again
you helped me for very difficult times
and I want to personally thank you for
being so interactive with your fans
forever thank you I will have to say
though sometimes I feel kind of really
pressured on days where I'm more busy
because I know some some people get
really used to me being super active on
social media and then when there's days
where I can't like give everybody a like
uh a lot of people
not a lot some people get like I think
sad about it but often like on those
busy days I still read everything I just
don't give everything a like because
brain brain dead but yeah
well usually pretty much reading
everything
I just don't like everything
so yeah don't think that like equals
reading it I often read everything and
also just because I didn't like
something doesn't mean that I didn't
like it
ironically
just because I didn't like it doesn't
mean I didn't like it but I I feel like
also it's like difficult because if I
like everything then there will always
be the expectation that I like
everything and then you'll be like oh no
she didn't like it this time
[Music]
I don't want it to be like that either
it's difficult
so you know there's times where maybe
you get a little bit less likes but that
doesn't mean
another so yeah I'm just resting my
finger
and just those are times probably where
I'm just chilling scrolling through
scrolling scrolling scrolling and don't
want to care too much about liking
everything
yeah
can't get into heaven I don't think
that's how it works
[Music]
no it's not the only way for you to know
because you should know me by now as a
person I am addicted to social media and
your guys's opinions and all that even
if I'm not liking it you should know I'm
reading it that you already have the
guarantee by knowing me as a person that
I cannot stop
being on the phone and on the PC like I
I can't you know you should know you
should know you should know I'm reading
everything
I am I am always watching you guys
always always
[Music]
yeah someone helping
me I mean yeah maybe some stuff slips
through but well I mean that's just
human
[Music]
and I'm I mean I'm not really human but
you know
man that the the plushie is so cute I
was just looking at it
chicken blessing
[Music]
I'm almost done
thank you soon everyone hold thanks for
the pinky happy birthday koala it's been
amazing seeing you accomplished so many
things this past year from your previous
birthday live your success of doing you
know to the first video in concert I'm
so excited to see it where you go from
here thank you
I also wonder where I'm I'll be going
I'm nervous and anxious but also looking
forward to it
hopefully you will be there by my side
and art designs
diesel thank you for the recipe
wish you have a great year you inspiring
me to do a lot of things for this lovely
Community oh yeah you aren't doing so
much thank you my sunshine love you my
OC thank you love you too thank you for
being such a such a valuable part of the
community and doing so many things yeah
participating and organizing things yeah
kitchen wow you're the best
Nathan caught on thank you for the pinky
happy birthday Daniel even though I
can't make every stream nowadays you're
still always my kamiyoshi really
okay I'll be next to support you support
you to the end hopefully for a long time
and
far too many supots also don't mind the
leadership but no problem are you here
now yay love you thank you
you're here properly I don't know what
you're talking about you're here I see
you now I assume you're always here
what holy [\h__\h] I just spilled a lot of
water
um
let me take off my shirt and save you
just kidding I just
yeah I might be accidentally turning off
my pissing now
[Music]
I went on the on the button to turn off
and on the PC
problem
am I gently going over it okay
we're good
I
I don't know why I did that I'm stupid
it's because I I I I I can't even
explain how that happened
[Music]
wait okay we're good
we got into our lives too late it's okay
I'm so happy you're here
I need more newcomers
[Music]
um
so stay
shut up Adonis that's not what happened
it was stuck
oh
[Music]
and we're stunk
oh
[Music]
wow
foreign
because I said the lights not working
and then they came over and they turned
it on immediately and there was no
problem they were ready to exchange
light bulbs and all that and it was like
really embarrassing for me
[Music]
and and then like recently when I was in
Japan uh you know
janma left to go to uh
La earlier
than you know us so I was in Japan a
little bit longer for the stream the
launcher Pan channel stream thingy
um
so she left uh someone else in charge of
me uh who's not usually in charge of me
but was there for the light incident as
well and and was like uh at some point
was like oh Kiana if you ever you know
any lights turned on again let me know
I'll be right there wink wink okay
[Music]
shut up
and any buttons can't press
I mean
[Music]
yeah that's what I was talking about to
Manuel what Adonis was saying I was like
shut up
and that remind me of that
[Music]
where was I this oh yeah Nathan pink
yeah every another call thank you for
the holy moly what 300. you crazy
chicken
recipes
you think I'll forgive you because
you're donating a triple red what the
[\h__\h]
thank you for bringing us little
chickens happiness Kiana forever
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
did I just accidentally copy paste
everything over
no
no just this I think it looked like a
couple pieces there
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
laughs
let me try this again
where is it
I well you can't stand because of the
whole wizard
you know what's going on there right
[Music]
you're not getting away from the usual
room
just because it was such a big donut but
I'm giving you
A reduced sentence
[Music]
300 years
just kidding 200.
okay
just kidding
three weeks
[Music]
um merciful first of all 300 years oh
wow it's so first of all
[Music]
hi
what are you meowing for
getting soft
[Music]
ah your little [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] you followed up with a red
what the [\h__\h]
makes me happy because now I can give
you that you so deserve
[Music]
the best and how everything you plan
will go smoothly from now on thank you
for always being our little sunshine I
love you Blue Blue
thank you for being my alpaca wife
for all the acids
[Music]
below his content look it's so funny to
always make Blue Link lose her [\h__\h]
it's very funny
still got it in me
you are thank you how much more is it oh
my God okay it's not that
it's not that
[Music]
um
it's more than I thought
[Music]
um
I can read more tomorrow
Happy Birthday
Happy Birthday wow wow I've been around
since your debut and it's been really
awesome seeing you grow into the idol
you want to be with your third
anniversary coming up and everything
you've accomplished so far I'm glad I've
decided to stick around
so glad too thank you you are
still here
thank you that's really sweet you put it
into good words
[Music]
no I don't need to cook but I'm tired I
swim swarm today
and I
I use many energy in story mode
[Music]
shoulders
foreign
[Music]
language isn't it
Spanish
I hope you will continue to support me
wherever we go wherever whatever
I hope you support Wawa
rule out all the streams
that's what you mean to me
forever whenever
heart Challenger
[Music]
foreign
thank you for making my life so much
better have the best birthday oh my God
you guys are so sweet what the hell
would I do
[Music]
can't believe I'm making someone's life
better that's like such a huge
compliment man
wasn't making my life better too though
all of you the mass of the chicken
I love you thank you
I see you in the tattoo hello hello
thank you for watching Always
for the pinky here's the first Super
chat
from me for your birthday kiwawa I wish
you nothing but happiness for a special
day and want you to know just how much
you inspire me and other kfp thank you
for the pinky dinosaur wait is that a
Australia well Australian dollars
that Australian dollars oh you guys
can't see that part
ion
Australian mate
oh
[Music]
thanks man bloody thanks mate thank you
we love our Australian fellow I feel
very close to you we've got that
Australian blood in it crikey
[Music]
we have a whole room of deadbeats and we
have Beats cheering for you in Los
Angeles
[Music]
what
why
how
what's going on
at ax when does after ax oh no
[Music]
it's my birthday on a weekday
we stayed longer
[Music]
it's sweet
thank you I was at a whole week oh dear
oh my God
sounds sounds chaotic
yeah
yeah oh maybe you also went to like like
uh Japan Town in L.A
when you spend like so many days you
have to
[Music]
yeah they've got some cool stuff there
I want to go again to
yeah you didn't get the time to go there
onion I have to go to Disneyland too
before leaving town um
foreign
[Music]
but I should try it again I haven't
tried in years
I should try it again because all my
friends all my Foreigner friends love
okonomiyaki I don't know maybe it was
the place where I went
or the choice the menu choice I made
thank you
Prime
[Music]
Duncan simpleton thank you thank you wow
I tried
oh my God oh my God I
just like you
dreads
I fought so close the scroller goes down
so fast
[Music]
like this this scares me this this
scares me
it scares me
[Music]
uh
thank you for the pinky have you ever
did attention so many pretty events this
past year let's see if blood
so anymore to come I'm glad I finally
got to see if the farming 3D by going to
the concert hope things calm down a bit
soon so you can take that week-long
Beach vacation
yeah
not anytime in July
but maybe in August yep
thank you for you know
trying to I don't know I don't know what
to say it but like for caring for me to
take a break
to get some time for myself thank you
that means a lot to me
[Music]
hope you have an amazing day love your
hard work and dedication you deserve all
the love waiting for more original and
cover songs your voice and dance are
amazing thank you I did upload a new
cover recently hope you're listening to
him to him I've read the comments
listening to it many times
[Music]
hmm
and original songs will follow soon
thank you lean for the support
FB
F baby
thank you thank you
[Music]
foreign
um
thank you for the pinky happy birthday
this is my first time super Channel or
another supercharged version
so I just want to tell you that you
might Aussie in her life wouldn't be the
same without your love from England
oh
I'm going to be at your doorstep very
soon
just kidding not exactly at your
doorstep but pretty close closer than
usual
hmm
[Music]
don't run
no hey
you should be happy
are you even here right now
[Music]
I'll be going back to your country you
better welcome me
it's been a while hmm thank you so much
for the support Black Version
Kyle Karen thanks for the pinky happy
birthday thank you thank you for another
year of awesome moments and wonderful
memories and let there be another great
one for you and everyone will give me
thank you I feel like especially in the
past one year
you have fallen into a Wawa rabbit hole
called cow carrot and you cannot get out
of it
but I am I'm really really glad to have
you around
because you make really great clips and
you've been so helpful you know I kind
of forced you in somehow I I I agree
yeah thank you like I really really
appreciate every every little help
and the clips that you make for your own
channel as well of course those are
really great
I'm a pfb
a but
I know
he loves me just as much as
or at least about as much
as honor if only you could have two
profile pictures
I I yeah he loves amadori I love amadori
we love amadori
that's so that I can see Amber in my
chat yeah yeah he's doing it for me
[Music]
um
how Karen not a fan of DSP I'm sure
foreign
I doubt it
kfp Bazookas and Bobby and bazuras
various thank you for the rest of the
chat happy birthday I can't really think
of anything to say that I don't already
say all the time
but congrats on everything this past
year it was a lot of fun here's another
great one thank you
YouTubers like like speak about it
behind the scenes to send Super Chat at
the same time even of the same currency
hmm
that can't be a coincidence two Clippers
back to back sending special super jets
in the same currency
The Coincidence oh my God Clippers
brains connected
[Music]
you two are from Chile
really I didn't really realize that
sounds chill
[Music]
yeah
that's so interesting
say Coolio
for the chilies
what's Coolio
okay me
[Music]
don't da da da da da da what no it's too
late now
what the [\h__\h] bad word
[Laughter]
da da
I don't know what I said
[Music]
what did I say
what the [\h__\h] did I say
worst word
so bad
it means [\h__\h]
[Music]
well it's not that bad
not that bad I need to go idle meeting
for [\h__\h] sake ninja star location wait
Kefi and bazuras
um
[Music]
happy birthday Kiana thank you happy
birthday to you too
[Music]
con
ji thank you Father
wait whatever is it it was right right
yeah
[Music]
I think for the pinky and and some more
happy birthday boss first I'm
celebrating your birthday as a kfb also
congrats on the first in concert sorry
that sometimes I miss the stream fall
asleep while listening to your lovely
voice but I always want to say happy
dancing I wish I could express to you
how much I care in many ways but sorry
writing is all I have right now that's
okay
hope you have nice dreams every night
want you to be happier tomorrow glad you
are here to be with us Julie Kiana Mike
hugging ASMR
hahaha
oh
foreign
even when it's in the middle of the
night
[Music]
almost 1am there oh no worry I I see the
the scary bloody wall and then we're
done pretty much
and fried squirrel we're already there
oh my God we are at the scary bloody
wall
fries of a tent
Feliz
you have accomplished so much just this
year alone thank you so much for never
giving up you have brought us kfb so
much joy and I'm confident you will
achieve even greater Heights you're
amazing you deserve all the best thank
you y'all I've already mentioned this
year so far has been crazy so thanks for
joining the ride dankish and fried screw
I love you
oh Z 176 thank you for the rest of the
Dead happy birthday tinsel another year
pass with entertaining streams and
awesome singing and dancing performances
by My OC and looking forward to all the
exciting things to come hell yeah I hope
you will watch the summer concert as you
guys know by now I have many appearances
yeah
so thank you for supporting mama please
don't stop don't stop keep supporting
the Wawa wow
can't really believe it's already this
far into 2023 time strolling flies fast
like it's
a new hologram for you coming oh you saw
something announced now
potentially flies fast like a chicken of
a jet pack you got a jet pack good luck
and success of all your future endeavors
much love cyrick I only mean that as a
phrase just so be clear you here
cute cute
I know you love me cyrick I love you too
thank you thank you soon
actually I just noticed the amount
that's crazy
stupid
public holy macaroni I'm not cute of
course you could no you're cute you're
pulling a Kyla right now
you do have a jet pack damn sheesh
wow you are doing yourself chicken can't
really fly well so you make yourself a
jet pack
amazing
[Music]
you gotta do what you gotta do to reach
the heights that you want yeah inspiring
lovely
[Music]
and grosses Christians
wow what
wow Ultimo MK thank you for the pinky uh
what am I saying I don't even know
anymore happy birthday Kiana free
birthday means free support the first
one is dedicated to all the love uh
were you planning on sending more
uh and wonderful memories you've given
us in the past
or did you send them any other streams
because I did free
so I just wanted to say thank you for
making these past three years so
unbelievably special for us thank you
I try I really try
to always make things fun and
interesting thank you for
watching all the time and accepting my
my stupidness and and supporting me
thank you soon
um
sometimes I think it must be rough to be
a kfb because I can be very stupid
um but yeah I'm sorry I I'm sorry it
might be difficult to be careful
sometimes but
I love you guys for being here for me
[Music]
we're getting used to it
thank you
oh man
I'll try to improve myself
but it's difficult
thank you
thank you not them all okay wow [\h__\h]
I've I've jumped over the bloody wall
but there's one more and there's some
drips here some blood stains but not
because thank you for the rest of the
Chad happy birthday Kiana today is my
birthday let's go
and I'm glad to be able to have it so
close to yours I wanted to share some of
your happiness with you some of my
happiness with you seeing you on stage
bring the idol you've always wanted to
be makes me tear up sing you live Live
Your Dream stay cool birthday girl are
you here
where are you show yourself an optical
are you here
you know
happy belated birthday
[Music]
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your shoe happy birthday an optical
happy birthday to you
finally
[Music]
say happy birthday to you too and mean
it actually
it's nice to have a birthday bunny you
say it's I guess it's one day before but
still still a birthday buddy
in a way we're birthday buddies in
certain time zones we're birthday
buddies yeah thank you Sam so much for
your support and your love I hope you're
you have a great birthday and you're
happy and healthy I wish you all the
best
[Music]
maybe next year we can celebrate
together again
oh also I hope you catch this Vlad
[Music]
because soon the game of Creighton
to the most wonderful sweetest
hard-working and Charming burp I've ever
had the pleasure to meet I can't even
begin to express how happy I am you
ended up with us here in whole life
giving us all a chance to get to know
you
it's crazy how things
happen I know
yeah
I'm really
turned out this way too
thank you for your sweet words thank you
sharing the game of green thank you
[Music]
soon James Jackson
it is
[Music]
oh you guys can't see it anymore but I'm
at the end so I can scroll any lower
you can do this there we go
and it's interesting thanks for the rest
of the chat happy birthday Kiana you
always work so hard and have
accomplished so much while still doing
so much for your fans thank you for all
you do you're truly the greatest ocean
of them all love your attention
greatest
supporter and chicken of them all
thank you muchos muchos love love love
Jim Tracy
[Music]
thank you for being part of kfp
and last but not least
please everybody stand and clap because
I [\h__\h] made it at least the Stream
wow
[Music]
standing ovations please
[Applause]
[Music]
I survived it I came out alive look at
this look at all of this oh my God thank
you guys so much for the crazy support
on my birthday Mamma Mia Mamma Mia is
crazy thank you for being so uh generous
all of you thank you thank you
[Music]
foreign
barely had any oh the okay the birthday
baking stream had half of what we read
in the countdown stream
in terms of
like total revenue I don't know about
the like how many uh pinks and reds but
yeah
half
half half half off
yeah
all righty
I'm gonna continue tomorrow
[Music]
I feel like I read more than half today
of the count on Stream So maybe tomorrow
we can finish if we're doing if I'm
doing fine we can finish the birthday
stream
in one go maybe
yeah I did didn't I hmm I read more than
half so if tomorrow is only half then
[Music]
now I really need to go to an Arlo
meeting
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
okay
thank you guys
for the first stream today I'll see you
tomorrow for another fun stream
in German we
saying
did you come same time tomorrow bye bye
foreign
[Music]
trailer really quick
oh my God let me watch this
if you want to watch it with me for some
reason
here we go
and
I'll give you five seconds five seconds
five seconds
should I mute my audio
[Music]
five
four
three
two
one
go
Mona Lisa
ah identity oh my God oh my God they did
the identity track holy [\h__\h] I love that
one so much
that works so well
bunk bunk
moons
[Music]
oh wow pink feathers oh umbrella
what was that
oh the grass is cute
what what's Ollie's weapon identity whoa
that looks cool oh water wow what the
[\h__\h]
becomes invisible
oh my God oh my God
all the efe special is cute
oh
my God
my God what
what oh [\h__\h]
come on
what what are these things like that you
can do you can talk to everybody
you can cook
do you like get that like frown at in
the in the game then you can make
yourself a house
[Applause]
do you sleep
you [\h__\h] way yeah
what the [\h__\h]
we can fish together
[\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
Ed up
what
Caillou are you like
crazy
oh my God
[\h__\h] how can you not charge money for
this game
oh my God
I don't know what to say
that's insane
holy [\h__\h] Super Chat you now
crazy [\h__\h]
okay
otsu
yeah looking forward to that man damn
bye bye