[Applause]
[Music]
i am death itself
i am timeless
i prefer not to do that in front of the
people
[Music]
it's elementary ain't it
i'm fresh
i'm undercover so i can't use
my real accent or i'll be
found down
i've noticed your accent waxing and
waning it has made me question your
claims of being british
[Music]
nervous
i was so cute
it's only been six months what the heck
happened
and my papa says i belong
in the bottom left don't worry about
bottom left papa was joking i don't
think it will get attached to your
character oh how reassuring
i felt fine before my debut you know i
was so calm and then like
like right before the debut i was like
oh my goodness i'm gonna be streaming in
front of all these people
[Music]
uh what kind of voice should i do okay
probably should be cute nice to meet you
um
my name's clyde b murray
hey guys two quick questions uh number
one what the [\h__\h] am i looking at number
two
can you stop
my favorite scenery
[Music]
thank you so much you guys ever since
the beginning you guys have really
showed up for me oh my god
please
i told myself after
the mad father's stream that we weren't
gonna cry anymore
when people are this generous and i
shouldn't be surprised but here i am
anyway
i also heard a rumor that uh when you go
in a pool you need floaties i told you
that
when we first met she was the very first
one to like you know that that friendly
i'm gonna make fun of you i i i don't
have a song prepared but i have a lot of
horns
i know i'm really proud of you i don't
know like oh good
since the first time
that i knew you
met you i was gonna do something
really special
and so you shall be known as tentacled
sometimes they um
be gathered
in a big big project to display their
work
on
the
times squares billboard i really don't
deserve
the kindness that you guys give me
happy birthday dad happy birthday oh my
gosh you with the freaking dad
i'm really happy that we became friends
because when i first met you i wasn't
sure if like if we could really be
friends for whatever reason but then
once we met i was surprised that we we
got along so well i made you a rep okay
you want you want to hear my rap yeah
please don't please don't cry
it's a pdf should i be nervous
dear guru
[Music]
250 letters written by all of you
the thing is i already did give up on a
dream that i had i was pretty much done
with believing that things ever go
upwards again
but
something totally unexpected came into
my life called hollow life
i spent
most of my life caring for somebody and
when they weren't here anymore i felt
like i lost my purpose
and so i just played a lot of games
and shared that happiness with other
people
and i hope you guys
also can carve out your own happiness
your own happy place in the world
and find your own slice of happiness you
know we didn't um we didn't really have
anyone to help us um and i don't say
that as like a a bitter thing or
anything like that nothing could have
been done about it you know
we were the first en generation and um
it was hard
i don't know what to say
[Music]
thank you
and i love you all
[Music]
oh
catch me when i'm not blinking i mean