[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
all right guys I'm having a problem with
steam
doesn't react to me
it doesn't do anything
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
okay
today is the last time we're playing GTA
I had troubles opening it but uh for
Steam and then I tried opening it
through the Rockstar Games launcher
directly and that seems to have worked
car
trick or
trick or card trick or drift trick or
what are you trying to say
trick or
trick or drive what
[Music]
I guess I'm a sheriff
Judgment Day oh what's going on
today online student who knows perhaps
yeah
um see I couldn't attach my gun to my
body properly but I have a
sick looking gun it kind of looks like
it's drawn in the same style as the game
artwork yeah and the hat is by Skye and
the gun the gun is by
mother
in the kfp props art hashtag
from
from actually it seems to have been
taken from a fan art that they did and
they just separated the hand
it looks so good
yeah because of that sleeve I'm wearing
my OG outfit today and of course I
couldn't lose the mustache because I
worked so hard on this mustache
there's a mustache you know it doesn't
grow in a day
oh all the effort I don't want it to be
wasted
don't shoot us
[Music]
well so today I'll be on this side where
the phone is I hope it won't be a bother
I think that's preferably the best side
anyway to be on to be honest and then
you guys you guys are gonna be up here
again
mine does but not to this length does it
shows my good side what the mustache
[Music]
finally yes beautiful beautiful as
always
ah
so we're gonna play Until the End today
I don't think we have much content left
but because of that I think
um we can try to do all endings as I've
heard there are free endings
foreign
since we have the time for it probably
uh and then with that I hope uh or I've
been told we might get to like five
hours or so maybe
like a good amount of time yeah and
number one please don't [\h__\h] spoil me
I've already been like kind of spoiled
by
something
and it's not nice because I was enjoying
the game and of course someone always
has to spoiler it
um
please don't try please try to spoiler
no more
[Music]
um
izo arrives and shouts you shall not
pass okay there's a lot of stuff mixed
there that shouldn't be mixed
[Music]
that's fine that's fine it's fine
it is fun
oh yeah okay uh
all right let me drink some more water
and I feel like I'm not hydrated enough
these days
do as deadbeats and fake spoil
you know I thought that's what happened
when we were watching rings of power
because someone in the beginning was
saying a spoiler
and then I was like [\h__\h] you why did you
spoil me but then right in the beginning
of the last episode they revealed
who Sauron is and then I was like okay
that person lied I guess so they were
just joking but then later on it turned
out
you know they were right after all
but at least for a while I thought that
oh I was not spoiled so everything is
okay so most of the episode I spent
uh thinking okay that was just a jerk so
the spoiler was like
had to say
it was it was it was
it was spoilerplus spoiler is no spoiler
they get negated is that a word
the spoiler was negated
okay yeah yeah yeah
yeah
okay okay
are you guys excited for GTA finally
I've heard a lot of people uh like who
played today like my viewers they
haven't even seen the ending because
they've never finished it and they've
seen so much uh more from GTA thanks to
me
I guess a lot of people just plan for
fun and for [\h__\h] around but don't
really actually play it until the end so
you're welcome oh although why is it so
small can I like um
it's so tiny on my
on my side where is so
there
is what's bigger than that
uh
let's Maybe
I know
uh apply change thing oh that's huge now
I mean okay that's weird why is that so
huge how about that
oh that's not that's not 16 tonight is
that 16 to 9 below
it's not
it's a lie it's not 16 to nine
okay
this this seems to be 16 to nine it
takes up my whole monitor though I
didn't want that I like having it take a
little bit less than my whole monitor so
that I can have the chat on the same
monitor right next to it but I guess
we're playing like this the settings I
guess changed a bit because I opened it
differently than usual not from Steam
maybe that's why
anyway how do I get out of here
Escape I'm pressing escape there you go
all right
no it's too big I can't I have my camera
is like kind of overlapping a little bit
with the monitor now I can't see this
this I guess on OBS it's the same haha
hello
hopefully that won't bother me too much
[Music]
you guys are so weird how old are you
five-year-old no five-year-old wouldn't
say that
12 year old
anyway
we're back last time uh what did we do
last time when we finish
um
where did we end it last time
oh it's ready whoa look at those
raindrops wow
oh up there too
wow well the graphics are nice today
nicer than usual whoa whoa cool guys
oh did we do last time
I think we were starting a new Heist
right
and then I was like oh no we're already
so close to the end
so I'm not gonna do this shitty side
quest
I saved Lamar yeah yeah and then I guess
we were gonna start the big one the big
one
[Music]
hi hi hi hi hi
so should we go to that
should we go to the L
or should we switch to a different
character as his next mission L is
optional
hmm
ah you guys weren't I was about to do
the L last time and you guys were like
oh no no not the l oh you have to censor
blah blah
eyes assassination okay um [\h__\h] that
then we're going to S but with uh
Michael
no no l then don't need any
assassination now yeah yeah
next month is November yeah
but you better start showing non-stop
not November let's go
wait why are there no subtitles just now
what's going on
I feel like there were no subtles did
you guys see subtitles
uh that's subtitles on huh
maybe just this one time
also audio logic
I got you fam uh
oh Dave hello
you made it good I saved you again Davey
again so what are you gonna do for me
about Haynes the rest of the FIB the IAA
and everyone else huh history is written
by the living okay you can pin most of
it on agent Sanchez
I get that story right in the agency and
Bureau will back off the problem we need
to deal with is Trevor Trevor Why Try
Meriwether Chinese gangsters General
insanity and so on
Steve
he's our wounded hero right now I gotta
cozy up to him calm him down
just get me out
no well I'm having a dream
that felt like a drift to me
the one that's not drifting what does
that mean
is that what I'm doing oh same car oh
this is this is a donut okay sugar plum
Daddy
what is money
[Music]
there's this guy he's been following me
around I
think something
what what she needs help you can now
make a choice why would you help
Michael's family member or not press oh
okay wait there he's been following me
in my car so let's just drive around and
you can talk to him when he shows oh
yeah we'll talk
a fast champion
[Music]
I feel like I'm breaking my car with
this
no that is burnout oh yeah well that
[Music]
with Michael
is he's burnt out in life man how about
hmm
okay I'm too focused on drifting
I don't know
drift on the corner
I don't know how to dance
okay my daughter
where is she what was that about Tracy
Tracy there
house all right
also uh
I didn't just like start the big one
right
maybe after this I save and then we can
just save for if I want to have all
endings
I don't know when's the best time
was that drifting
whoa
oh cool
what
so I just I just caught them opening up
the the top and it looked like it had
wings
[Music]
that was a slight trip what I didn't
even do anything on purpose
all right I should look at her okay you
see her tapping her toe for foot
really impatiently hi come
on
she's so funny to me
all right we're gonna I don't know help
her find we should try over Hawaiian
snow for
Hawaiian snow
all right we're looking for a guy in a
purple convertible I don't remember what
make okay I'll keep an eye out thanks
Daddy
for huh I mean other than giving you
money putting a roof over your head
speaking to guys who really cool you on
TV I mean there's no purple convertible
I don't even know what a convertible is
that's another problem is he here
okay what's the convertible is that um
[Music]
you better not be taking out credit like
your brother not credit
what you see him
I don't think so maybe we should look
over at the [\h__\h] Bell Rockford Plaza
clucking bell all right on my way
after that video on fame or shame yeah
yeah it seems like there's something
else there get money out of it
we found this trick
who
what what
my baby girl's a celebrity with her very
own stalker there's nothing to be happy
I'm proud of movies or kids in Rockford
Hills what was I thinking
you know it's amazing you've turned out
I love them talk
are they done
tomorrow okay I thought they were still
talking they want to interrupt them
you're around here see here
[\h__\h] he's on you
where did that come from stop the car
well how may I
how may I do that
seriously
sugar daddy
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] [\h__\h] yeah
not so creepy when you're stopping him
man in the car she's not stopping enough
something Dad yeah well now we're the
ones we're gonna do something all kinds
of things
I'm such a good driver now holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
oh maybe I should feel like
out of the car
dealer just deal deal do they mean kill
him
I'm going
on
[\h__\h]
him
what did you expect like well you have
to be more exactly when you say a deal
with him you did that what do you want
me how are you trying to deal with him I
wanted you to
you this was infinitely more persuasive
yeah no more shocking to you look
there's a lot of sickos out there I
couldn't take the chance too many too
many sickos out there my dad is one of
them I'll grow
it's time you got serious with your life
yeah I ain't perfect but I love you I
guess he really scared me but I I didn't
know what well then pretend it never
happened like I try not to think about
exactly what aspect of your creative
expression enamored him so much okay
that's right
denial kind of works for me
that's my girl that's my girl try to
make better choices
drug dealers
so wholesome so peaceful
I don't love it you're welcome
productively for once
I could use my paternal rage
ah funny oh that's funny okay well
thankfully she's safe okay I'm such a
good dad
oh I'm having this problem again where
I'm like not moving huh
come on koala
you can do it hey all right
this will happen a few times today
probably oh wait it happened again
that's so [\h__\h] weird
why the connection is so [\h__\h] up
what's your mind
I think I think froggy Wawa is hacking
into my system
and I'm losing control of myself
it never start I keep on restarting and
it doesn't wanna do it
one more time
restarting like these
oh sheesh
okay I'm moving but for how long
for now
for now we're good all right all right
small town no no no not for long all
right now we go to S
it's happening
is happening
[Music]
I'm assuming that's the right one
I'm shape-shifting so much these days
which one is your favorite Chihuahua
guys you can't actually answer that for
real yet because you have yes to
properly meet froggy Wawa and I think
once you meet her it's not a fair fight
or comparison anymore
but
I think I like French Wawa
my answer is yes
pink uh pinkwell was cute too the one
with the pink shotgun and with the pink
vest and all that
fried prank you want what do you mean
and press okay that's not quite what I
was talking about but okay I'll let that
one count
[Music]
indeed oh
this time they have this the same car as
before I think but in a different color
and honestly this color is ugly as hell
but it looks funny
stands out
that yellow speedy car is cool though is
that the same no
no no
all right f
because I think I have to get in here
yeah oh maybe I should put away the gun
just you know like we're visiting my
friend I suppose so no need for guns
this is so slick
Devin
what the hell are you doing here it's
over Michael you're doing good kid you
kept this [\h__\h] up long enough to
help me trigger a fantastic insurance
payout when the plug is pulled I love
you you're you're like my spirit brother
now
where's Solomon he's out getting the
negatives of film whatever the [\h__\h] it
is the last dinosaur in town is about to
get fossilized what are you talking
about the movie's nearly done so if the
plugs pulled now the investors meaning
us get a massive insurance payout
meanwhile I can use that to get the
other major shareholder the old bastards
idiot son to agree to tear this Relic
down and let me redevelop the area for
condos and in this economy the city is
going to let me build tax-free I might
even get some rebates it is a brilliant
thing and it is all thanks to you and
Molly's eye for the details of the
insurance policy Michael they're [\h__\h]
us the suits and they don't even wear
suits always the students surge clothing
try not to take it too badly Mr Richards
were you ever a human being look people
used to like films now they're like what
videoing themselves beating off on their
iFruit phones don't blame me I'm a
spiritual person I feel badly about this
but evolution is evolution gentlemen
Molly
Namaste Namaste can I take the film now
Mr Richards my plane leaves in 25
minutes can't we do something at least
let me finish the picture the place down
I'm afraid our timetable doesn't allow
for that Goodbye Mr Richards
where the hell is she going with that
movie
is taking the only copy offshore
somewhere nice and discreet analog God
it certainly got its complication
Michael can you do something no he can't
do anything pal it's an inevitability
you only have one copy or what
my wife got screwed by a yogi and now
I'm getting screwed up
[Music]
that's what you call them
people who teach yoga or do you go to
the airport talk to her that's it
uh should I like save or
I don't know what to say but it's not
like I can't
I can't even save now
you've been saving this game
purposefully
can't yet okay
well we'll take this card
it goes uh
I like this music
whoa this car has the ultimate boom boom
[Music]
sounds like chunkers and smoothie when I
cuddle with them
oh yeah slick you're not thinking hey
I'm a producer I'm producing the goods
don't do this slick think she's got a
police escort oh my God
at the airport work for me I just want
to get the film back or she does
anything rash with it Molly's highly
strong she's not gonna stop and talk it
out with a deranged killer chasing after
her that ain't who I am today I don't
want to hurt anyone I just want to get
my move slow down and
very much
[Music]
[Applause]
they only proof that he accomplished
something in his mid-life crisis it's
all he has
all he has to show
don't take that away from him
please
did you guys see my new schedule for the
coming week it's not my schedule
actually I'm being kicked out broken
Wawa is taking over
very exciting I'm actually gonna still
make one small change though
didn't realize Rob detected one and two
were both so short
that's it so we're doing one and two on
one day
and then
we're here to escort you to the hanger
Mrs Schultz
what
oh
wait what
two stars
I'm there I'm so confused what's
happening
look I don't understand what just
happened
I drove past her what no
oh he escaped
why was she I only saw a police cars
then
even look I'm not
all the products
oh okay
um what's she doing as I was saying
was that the red car is here
in there obviously on her nap why do I
have the Stars
they're following her
what is this
[\h__\h] oh okay they seem to be focused on
her now
I'm gonna play here Comes Nico probably
on the other Rock detective stage oh my
God I'm so sorry police car
oh is she gonna get on the plane
what's going on
do I do I stop her by oh God
[Music]
what happened I can't control this car
I'm on his skin it's funny
like it is pal she's totally flipped
sorry
up
stopping her car nice nice
[Music]
sorry I didn't want to shoot the police
car I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
do I have to stop her otherwise or her
oh her Wheels like they have plot armor
or something
no no no no oh this is all scripted
this is all scripted pull it over
already
I'm playing police cop right now
oh there we go all right scripted I
think it's scripted kill me
[\h__\h] club should I have my gun like
are they gonna like be mad at me if I
haven't gone out why don't wait are we
trying to kill her
thing
okay four
let's go
[Music]
was that her
that didn't have to happen wait
stop moving
was that her
holy [\h__\h] well she did not get on the
plane but she got in the plane
wait wait
[Music]
who's the cops lose the cops they said
but I'm having troubles right now with
my controls well I love them love them
well can I maybe take this plane clean
up leave me alone
I don't know how I don't know how how
how how how I forgot how to fly
[Applause]
a full play okay and that didn't work
maybe better just jump into a car
is that like in a situation like that
where you're under so much pressure of
course that's not gonna work there's no
[\h__\h] car in here she's the one behind
this
[\h__\h] I got what I came for I'm leaving
um
did I forget the film
that's so funny no that it says loads of
cops I already have it okay
okay I'm waiting for the police car it's
gonna stop right here
nothing to do with me
hey I ain't done anything
I still left his name hey you got some
mess to clean up
let's go
all right all right let's hope this
police car is easy to drive where do I
go
where do I go
uh not good oh [\h__\h] no it's not easy to
drive
it's not it's not
[Music]
[Applause]
my my backpack oh [\h__\h] oh okay that
makes a lot of sense but if we have time
we're gonna switch to a different car at
some point
wish you don't know now
an equality
and I have to get out of this airport
first
[\h__\h] I'm so stupid ah
[Music]
for your passion
yes okay they're all pretty far I think
at this point
um [\h__\h] I think where's the exit is that
an exit oh God oh God
oh
[Music]
oh my God oh my God oh my God
steady steady steady
boys
[Music]
it's okay
but I really need a different car oh
out of here how do I get out of this
[\h__\h] mess oh sorry
oh man
who made oh there's a card
oh oh
I feel like I'm [\h__\h] drunk
[\h__\h]
how did I get out of here
uh
one car I got one car look good didn't
it
okay no I can't I need to go this okay
we're going that way
[Music]
if I keep on driving that way will I
eventually find a way out
[Music]
in a circle
for a traffic purpose but all right uh
thank you for going to the side oh oh
there we go we're out of the airport
[Music]
uh hello police car you go that way I go
this way yes we all go our separate ways
I know hello
I'm losing them that's that's very
interesting let's take this shitty green
car
foreign
[Music]
I see no trouble oh I feel like the the
back plate is trying to call me in like
a boomer
but it should have been eight zero
eight zero and then
but there's nothing between us now that
I know you prefer dictation really we're
doing this now I just watched Evan
Weston's legal counsel get Juiced in a
jet engine
but I saved the print so we still got
our movie you believe that analog thing
It's All Digital we have backups
everywhere I mean we're shooting on
green screen well you could have told me
I'm sorry look I thought you knew of
course you're McDonald's
green litter Premiere that will stop
them from burying us a premiere for
meltdown
okay can you invite my family they can
finally have something to be PR leg oh
[\h__\h] I wanted to go to settings nah
sorry maybe it was it like this the
whole time
I want to make it smaller
uh what's 1629
I didn't that's the same size huh
just now hmm that's weird
but just in case I I'll go too small
[\h__\h] ah okay
Okay small small screen
and I can move the comments
maybe that helps for sure
at least an OBS it doesn't change
stretched already okay I hope you didn't
say anything important oh hey Jim dad
why didn't you tell us about the
premiere mom and Tracer like freaking
out trying to get ready for the red
carpet oh yeah [\h__\h] will there be a red
carpet it kind of crept up on me have
you actually got a tux no I gotta pick
one up at ponsonby's hey meet me there
we'll go together
okay is that the main quest
this game is really like a [\h__\h]
roller coaster it has so many ups and
downs we were just being chased by
helicopter and a [\h__\h] to the police cars
and a really difficult race
and then suddenly everything's like
super chill again
the ups and downs of GTA
foreign
carpet
really
am I already going to the right place I
hope so
oh can I
without put on some some nice clothes
like a suit
Michael in the suit for the red carpet
um
Michael's gonna look real good
we should invite Franklin too
I don't like this car I would I would
never want a car like this is the color
you and
I want
a different car but this was what I had
at my disposal don't worry you won't see
it for long we'll switch as soon as we
can oh
are we getting some nice clubs here for
real
[Music]
change it to your tuxedo and pawn some
buys to attend the Meltdown Premiere oh
okay that'll look great on you huh I've
got a ride you better get a badass a tux
wait it's tucks in the suit category
oh is this dmca music
yeah that doesn't look like a tuxe where
is the Texas
it's over there
oh yeah that's fancy looking
uh oh tuxedo
um
oh I already have it I don't have to buy
it that material real is imported and
material is imported
press F to complete all missions
looks a bit different that just looks
like a normal suit to me drive himself
to the premiere come on oh I'm being
driven
I've never been inside a limo before I
think oh this is your big day Are you
seriously
a limo gym
open that champagne let's go inside
candles me and the big dog getting our
drink
my dad's a movie producer Jimmy get back
down here which makes me happy position
kids
sorry unfortunately I have to turn off
the music
the next two recessions without ever
having to work and I'm gonna get a
sports car and a drug habit before on
reality rehab show and then I'm gonna
sell my story and become really
judgmental and I'm going to use all the
contacts I make in treatment programs to
become a producer too and I'm gonna make
even shittier movies than my dad does
because I don't care about movies like
him he's gonna make porn movies it's
just an opportunity thing yeah
to his Edge losers
hear that Pinewood you hear me
I hear it and I don't like it we're
going to the Oriental Theater on
Vinewood Boulevard get back down here
and not to like gawk its liberties from
behind a barrier we're actually like
properly invited beads to the I to the B
Jimmy read my neck Bros
nobody's gonna be there no photographers
I'm done spraying this chisel let's take
a drink
what for I'm pressing it
hello Jimmy shut up a second hey Devin
look I need to say about Molly man I'm
sorry but I didn't do it I told you to
slow it down slick it was an accident I
was there but I had nothing to do with
it sure yeah hey you made a fool out of
me Michael and that is something I'm not
gonna forget look Devin I said I'm sorry
I feel bad for you but you don't
threaten me because this movie's
happening all right so let's just calm
down here
oh absolutely slick forgive and forget
yes Namaste
hey we're here
is that traces
okay the fireworks freaked me out they
make me really nervous even though you
did make a pretty shitty movie well
thank you Jim we're the girls oh they're
at home you know they'll uh Namaste
everybody
look we told you a thousand times
you have to show up but you're like this
embarrassing maybe I shouldn't shoot sex
scenes in a green screen kind of
environment yeah yeah it's uh the
thought is that it crossed my mind
[Music]
Mr Richard hi if I could just bother you
for a second um I'm Laszlo from uh Famer
shame um but I do some acting on the
side I was wondering if uh oh yeah of
course you should come see me kid I
think I got a project that would be
perfect oh that's fantastic it's called
the closet really modern stuff
pervert Come on
talk to Michael I never had surgery come
on Milton Milton hi sorry to bother you
quick question get in here Ty
um love love loved the movie well thank
you so much I appreciate it when when
you were that I now know why my
controller wasn't working in the
airplane
all right I gotta go thank you so much
excuse me excuse me
[Music]
what what what
I didn't think I I
play audio we're done you go I don't
hear [\h__\h] it's in the PS5 controller now
I just plugged it in uh let me think uh
it's five control every goddamn time
it was rather to the controller yeah
audio settings
why does it always do that on its own
like I did not tell you to do that
okay it should be okay
I think
oh
well
what what just happened
was that really the end of that scene
okay let me
let me unconnect the controller because
[\h__\h] that
where's mom and Tracy come on so
unnecessary all right we're not using
the controller today I hope we don't
have to fly two minutes to sacrifice
yourself for your family together why is
he so slow get in the car faster
I don't know this Rich [\h__\h] is pissed
off at me because I didn't [\h__\h] can the
movie and then his lawyer died and he
just told me he's gonna hurt your mom
you killed his lawyer and now he's gonna
kill mom and Tracy he ain't gonna do
anything if I gotta say in it but
kill this lawyer no I didn't it was an
accident
oh sorry I'm so sorry I never do
anything to put you in danger
all right okay they'll be fine they're
tough restart the whole mission but
won't it be like
how how far back would we be
thrown to
[Music]
um
how do I when I can't even replay it
anyway unless I kill myself I guess
he's not a gangster or anything no I
just had a little fight that's it it's
not a gangster he's just extremely rich
he says he's got all these connections
I'm sure it's just talk
I mean they kind of recapped it for us
anyway
just now come on are we gonna go or what
I mean I mean wait I'm not here
[Music]
I got confused by the blue
Point dot in the map
okay that's my home
what's that car all right Jimmy you keep
yourself concealed I'll go get the girls
I need to save my family
I just got them to reunite I can't mess
this up
oh [\h__\h]
um
I have released her from the fangs of
the enemy
by killing her
there we go
[Music]
be quiet please
[Laughter]
how the [\h__\h] is she still in the back
rub though the red carpet already is
over you're too late
keep us down be safe baby
you worry about me
oh she sees him as a hero now the hero
that I've always been
[Music]
play the house with my rent are there
any more on this floor
probably not that they would be a red
dots
[Music]
not yet
just keep calm
okay this is not a good technique
okay I should have used my skill
okay
[Music]
shotgun now maybe
I'll stay with the rifles
oh
not yet stay put
stop them before they can even go in
just keep call
ing
let me just stay down sweetie
[Music]
he dropped the gun why would you do that
why would you do that
all right all right all right now please
everybody stop [\h__\h] around now
oh
[Music]
at least one headshot
one more try to run
okay
either do I just keep calm
uh get my skills today are questionable
afternoon
[Music]
I mean I guess it's a good
a good opportunity to restyle everything
also we wanted to move anyway
right
oh
there we go there you go now he's dead
also let me take the med kid even though
I didn't lose that much help
let's see what's up here
what's up dog
what I don't see anyone have you gone oh
someone's there on the other side of the
house
oh now there's more coming
[Music]
up okay okay
let me switch guns what should I use
though
snipe no no maybe the SMG is good
[Music]
okay
oh one more
[Music]
good shot good shot I'm gonna bury you
in this shot
hey how are you doing live
incredible
yo the weather is playing perfectly with
the drama that's going on right now it
knows
you think that sounds kind of like a
flag
well maybe they're really gone are they
are they I don't know
I knew it I know it
no it's not what was that
someone there oh
I'm gonna start shooting what is this
[\h__\h] what is that
yeah you like that don't you huh
[Music]
so you sit on it what is that it's
called
I really [\h__\h] him up good though huh
yeah you did I'm gonna make a call I'm
so proud of you okay stay put
where did he get all those like clothes
and the equipment from though what the
hell that thing on his head
why why did he have that on
like what was that even for
it's not necessary
came to my house Lester my house
so I asked Amanda
aggressions
I ain't looking for perspective Lester
they came after my family yeah to not
know what that is back in the garlic
Stone collab remember Hell no remember
when I drew yaggle bagging
[Music]
a grocery bag at the counter
entertainment Counting
classic yeah move on that right away
before it gets any hotter
it can't get hotter than this I'm here
after all
a little bit long
should I save now is that possible
new game
would that mean I'm opening a new safe
slot
on the phone yeah why didn't he not have
what is this interface
[Music]
uh-huh
why don't they have it there honestly
I know it's all the safe but we want to
do like a separate Save Right can we do
that
create new save maybe it's too early I
don't know but just in case
okay so do I have
let me check
uh it doesn't open it there you go
let me see again okay so we have two
different at least
oh
okay I'm confused but okay um I'll make
one more
just for good measure
save after the heist after the after the
next hotel okay
that's a cool car the gray one over
there I like that one
that's a muscle car that's a muscle car
[Music]
[Applause]
I know it Michael did you find them who
the person who sent the mercenaries to
our house I forgot about them already
you said we would be safe
he's not gonna try that again I'm on top
of this Amanda trust me really you're
sure I'm positive look I love you baby
I'm gonna take care of this oh it's so
romantic love whatever
definitely
is there to protect his family
I'm taking this car going
[Music]
to
smoke all right
okay uh
h
is it h
I'm guessing it's h because I don't
really see much else
oh
GT
a GTA
yeah I like the the white stripe down
there and also the shape oh it's like a
wave it goes from left it goes up and
then and then more up and then down and
up
beautiful four GTS
this is this is not a muscle car what
are you talking about
can't fool me
all right let's get Justice for the fan
of the family
I wonder what the others are doing
Franklin and Trevor don't don't really
care about Trevor
[Music]
happy calls these days so popular Trace
Johnny are you okay
because some guys came to our house with
automatic weapons maybe not again right
dealing with that honey you don't need
to worry money doesn't matter when
you're dead daddy
not worry about that
she worries
that's really traumatizing man
they're not used to that kind of [\h__\h]
like you are Michael
for you it's like every day need to Joel
well not for them
this car drives nicely I wish I had that
in the end of like chase that we had
whoa
need to chill every day Slice of Life
hmm
wait wait
uh all right what's going on guys what
should we talk about I feel like my
brain is so empty at the moment
you guys have that too
I've had a lot of time
uh oh yeah yesterday did you guys watch
me playing on my main Channel some uh
uh not Apex that was not Apex what was
that game OverWatch OverWatch
I was it was fun I feel like I did
absolutely a terrible job but it was fun
nonetheless
I I had a good time
um
that new character the new healing
character I like playing her but it
feels like her heel is
I don't know weak it feels like I'm
barely doing anything even though I feel
like I played her decently
um
she's cute I like her design too
cute girl
how do I enter this place
oh wait I remember this place
I'll have to enter from the other side
right this is like uh yeah the strip
club where you enter
from the front and then you have to go
all the way to the back uh for now
good to see you what's up
oh [\h__\h] music I like it
oh nice aquarium I really need to go get
my aquarium now I've been like waiting
too long on
doing that
wait she's still here
he's been here for like weeks
[Music]
you never leave is he here forever now
I joined right at the right bar well
every part of my GTA streams is the
right part
oh we're just talking about you yeah
another few hours you never have to talk
about me again Trevor you're the one who
likes to talk watch your back you too
the only decent guy between these four
is Franklin [\h__\h] you excuse me you don't
even have to explain that thank you I
like Michael but he has issues a lot of
issues this is it
well we have two options they're both
little uh out there but then again what
do you expect the big ones in one we
hijacked their Armored Cars we take the
cruise hostage and then we Infiltrate
The depository now once you're in there
and you've got the score we send in a
team of modded cars you load up you get
out we'll need to infiltrate the
transportation grid and manipulate it to
Aid our Escape but option two Franklin
is a good one out front make them think
we're dumb he has like a problem
convince the people of that
I know a good heart the other guys will
be drilling taking what they can you're
gonna be the distraction always the
attention seeker you know for a guy
who's always stepping on his friends to
get ahead he hasn't unfortunately low
sense of self-worth okay okay let me
show you the board to uh recap and these
are our options we try to make them give
us the gold or we drill a big old hole
in the side of the bank and we take it
out
if you're drilling a big old hole you'll
need a big old drill a tunnel bore
machine I'll locate it but you have to
steal it and store it near the bank
they're Excavating a new part of the
Metro Network around there so that's
where you'll go in we'll need Choppers
for the getaway too and Trevor has one
we can use the other kids bought the
guys on the ground will need a getaway
car so get something fast and tough and
then modify it as much as you can to
increase your chances of getting away
from the cops and it's got to be stored
in it
it's going to be a lot of heat so think
about that
um per I'm forgetting something uh oh
that's it
and take it to the warehouse you'll have
to steal it again I'll send you the
details
now if you're interested in the more um
don't be mean if I fail a few times and
so on huh you've got to get some police
Stingers the only cops are licensed to
have them so that's a headache of its
own
uh what else um oh right yeah you'll
need to get a hold of and mod some
getaway cars the normal suspicions
of gold Whoa man a couple of tons four
tons in total that's what I can get the
system to divert into the cage we're
hitting [\h__\h] me
okay okay last thing you remember that
underpass we saw from the helicopter now
that's where I'll set up the smoke and
mirrors to get the cops off your scent
I've heard that before
Michael subtle or obvious what's it
going to be
um
drill right
subtle
subtle is really fun
option two for maximum money B is this
real ah okay oh
that's what I thought it's not very
subtle
it's a drill okay
all right
what
Oh I thought it was in something in the
game I would get
195 million for four tons of gold you
were talking in real life all right
okay well then obvious
all right we're going through the wall
so we'll just need a skeleton crew okay
um two gunmen and two drugs is he
laughing like the first driver we'll
pilot one of the Choppers getting you
out of there half the gold will be in
that Chopper so there's better be some
safe effing hands and the second driver
is in charge of the train I don't think
we need to hire someone very expensive
for this okay it ain't that complicated
come on
she's supposed to be good and she'll
work for way less than she's worth it oh
yeah cut five percent
versus 14 but her driving skill is like
almost full anyway
yeah can I go for her and then carry him
because you said the second driver is no
need to be good
yeah I saved her saved her oh that was
good I'm glad I uh chose her to save her
randomly
um
I'm not gonna pass her up
and number two
is you
you don't school this one's New Blood
I've seen him drive but I haven't seen
him under pressure they even charges one
is with Franklin burrowing in and
pulling out the gold gunman 2 hits the
Bank lobby with you and makes it look
like you're a couple of idiots trying
your luck
uh sorry that was too fast so who should
I
should I get good ones or is it like
whatever
good first dumb second
again
chef chef chef oh 12 percent
I mean whatever it's not like we spend a
lot of money in this game like who cares
oh I stopped moving again
what is up with that
go cheap go cheap cheap Jeep
uh the best cheap one is him
Christy short range
it's not that bad
Chef first
all right but then we'll go with the
cheapest of the cheap
oh this one's better than him but uh one
percent cheaper all right oh I think
this is decent hey you gotta give the
guy some cred for coming out of the
bureau with his uh
abilities that I reckon you learned
something I'm not enough to charge more
this is the big one is there anything
you want to go over why
I don't know I'll just let the game tell
me what to do I'm fine great all right
and we're good to go [\h__\h] Glory
Seeker oh you got any better ideas
obviously not otherwise you already
killed me and done the gig yourself I
mean what kind of vain [\h__\h] decides
that the best way to rob the largest
holding Bank on the west coast is for
him and him personally to come at the
front door the kind of vain [\h__\h]
who's stuck working with you you dude
okay all right all right ladies babies
always fighting about what you need
unimportant things
a big one let's go let's do it let's do
it
where's the exit
music
it's like a different version of that
song
[Music]
you're taking me up Phantom Canyon in
this charcoal color land stalker to
punish me patrolling you what if only
someone would save me
and this is also
um
optional it seems to help Jimmy all
right I'll be there soon you know you
you're right interesting guys I mean any
attention is a good attention right
exactly okay we'll help him you some of
you guys don't want me to help him but
most of you guys do
[Laughter]
I'm coming oh my other car is gone
the nice car is gone it's gone
all right let me get the other one I
think the black one is that actually
mine
no probably not
you are the chosen one
no that is mine that's the the cash
money
Wheels
[\h__\h] great start
oh oh I remember one thing I wanted to
tell you guys I saw something today
um a clip of takamata
[Music]
and I've noticed one thing guys
I
I the same pajamas that she has
hey I saw that slate but I'm like yo
my pajamas
look exactly the same and that's
actually I have several pajamas of
course but that one I think I got in
Japan which explains why we have the
same one
and blue one with the with the hearts on
the sleeve the red hearts it's actually
a several part pajama that comes with a
short version as well like long pants
version a short pants version and then
long sleeve version and kind of No Sleep
version yeah
so if I go back to Japan
you know I could say let's have a pajama
party in the same pajamas but I heard
she's very stinky so
just kidding
ah stop moving
I heard she doesn't take baths and she's
stinky
I know how true that is though
I mean so far I've seen some some people
having uh ice front okay there's no
reason at all to be suspicious of anyone
behind us and if there was he would just
be there to warn you you would
definitely not kill you definitely would
not kill you
you gave up your right to free speech
when you insulted a celebrity on the
internet it was a couple of comments
some colorful language uh it was
harassment you're the comedy writer deal
with the Heckle I blocked you you
started another account I blocked you
again you started another but what you
didn't count on is me having the money
and the resources to trace your IP I
count on you having better things to do
well I don't I'm a lonely man and social
media is my life it's given me the
recognition I've been denied my whole
life I can make snarky comments and glib
for announcements and lap up the
adulation banishing any form form of
descent I'm a king and bleeder is my
kingdom okay
um
that's pretty sad don't lose sleep over
it when I'm done the only bleeding
you'll be doing is actual like bleeding
because then you'll be in pain
[Music]
[Laughter]
what was that NPC doing
uh that's funny
you blocked him um what you gotta do is
you have to mute them because they will
see if you block them and then they can
just make more accounts and also they
might take pleasure out of being blocked
but when you mute them they will not
know and therefore they think you still
see them so they'll just continue doing
what they're doing
yeah yeah and then you know
you'll never hear from them again don't
have to go for the Troubles of blocking
them continuously
yeah yeah do not kill the kid
oh I'm sorry
do not kill a kid that sounds like
they're challenging me to kill them is
that reverse psychology
foreign
who is that animal
s
that's my dad you a-hole oh he's gonna
[\h__\h] you up properly oh really oh pigs
just hurt huh
what am I supposed to kill him or not
okay I guess I'm not supposed to go
okay I thought it was reverse psychology
okay okay
but I guess if it's written on the
screen like that I guess they really
mean it there they are
take Jimmy home
I want my car thank you
that was so easy
yeah yeah yeah he's gone
because it holds like oh man he looks
like a grudge and I'm like his Nemesis I
wouldn't go that far look
he thought you were a fat little nobody
now he thinks you're a fat little nobody
with a badass for a dad yeah he'll stay
away but but I'm like his Troll Pop
where's this car oh right why am I
taking this did we go already
come with me
Chris why am I taking this [\h__\h]
broken car in the first place I don't
understand I thought he wanted to stay
in that car are you following me yeah
okay
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry is
my car still there
on it
it wouldn't suddenly despawn already
would it
but that's so fast I didn't even I
didn't go that far oh shall we use this
no I don't want to drive a [\h__\h]
insanely huge truck all right up next
car next car please
that's not a car
I know a car when I see it
home time
[Music]
that's just such a [\h__\h]
annoying scumbag
all of these characters are
is that sweat on the back of his shirt
no hate though because like holy [\h__\h]
the amount of sweat
[Music]
the man yeah well you deserve to lose
your card for that the amount of sweat I
sweat in like Japan and Korea
call me an idiot it's incredible
I sweat fountains and mountains what's a
troll like a joker on the internet what
sort of jokes
like what like someone posts something
and you're all like that sucks you suck
dick some jokes that aren't funny no you
don't get it the humor someone who tries
say it once big deal we say it again and
again and again and again okay like the
other day you post this picture of his
newborn and I'm all like damn son that
right there is one ugly sorry
ugly ass [\h__\h] of a baby
my balls is prettier than that baby
I seen roadkill prettier than that baby
the hell is wrong with your baby and
he's all like actually there's a problem
with its chromosomes or something and
it's actually a miracle that survived
birth it's actually a miracle I survived
seeing a picture of it
no no all right
oh my God maybe that one was a little
Ott but it's generally really good times
yeah good times great spots there he
definitely did which one you have
sorry
could you drive like a sane person
I'd like it if we went like now
you uh
calm down koala don't shoot your son
don't don't shoot yourself it's gonna be
okay
it's all gonna look at his legit a troll
okay he doesn't know better he doesn't
know how to be a decent human being
he may
deserve to die but
maybe just not right now okay let's give
him a couple more years to try to
improve himself driving is making me
wish I was still kidnapped
once you're saying a little [\h__\h] what'd
you say
you want to be kidnapped
foreign
[Music]
the problem is I cannot even take out oh
are you like letting off tension after
nearly losing your son
[Music]
laughs
I'm gone from kidnapped victim to drive
by accomplished
him
you really have to do that it's
impossible that's impossible
oh why are we here just to suffer
ah
yeah get out the troll is back in his
lair now stay off the internet for a
while yeah but don't wind people up so
much I learned my lesson Dad yeah sure
and I'm a tax account
oh that was really simple and easy
my mind what is this place it's cool
Mission pass
[Music]
I'm really aggressive right now okay I
want to kill some people oh it might
just be you
uh okay so what are we doing there was
something about the heist are you gonna
tell me about it like in a few seconds
like do this and that come on I'm
waiting for instructions
I can't do [\h__\h] without instructions
sometimes you have to wait a little bit
until they tell you what to do there you
go
there's a telephone machine on the Depot
in East Los Angeles is out in the yard
there are guys working there around the
clock and guards as well try and get in
without
to the mother
oh one I didn't turn it on
[Music]
I have to turn off the phone
oh was it here
no that's not it
not email it was a message here
uh try and get into without trying to
attention to yourself oh wow oh you're
so funny you're so funny
ah
Eastland East Los Santos the day Market
is it this one H for heist
okay
let's go get it
huh any locomotive and flatbed car will
do app stores to sky crane to do the
pickup just divert a train a day with
quartz and call one of the others to fly
in deal with any station blah blah blah
oh blah blah I don't understand I'm just
gonna follow
sorry
I'm I'm not in my
game today it seems
just gonna follow where the game tells
me to go
yeah
I need more guns for the mission
really for this one specifically where I
have to uh go first or for later on
maybe I'm trying to drag it out maybe
I'm trying to stall
kill um
left Edge
that's right
okay how about now
it's filled up no no it's not
no
[Music]
how about now
still
I it's just not 16 to nine man it's just
not the same size for some reason it's
so weird
oopsie
let me just make it bigger
and there you go
okay
now it should be fine
this car
kind of slow
definitely not my getaway car oh what is
that coffee Stripes interesting design
on your car
I feel like you're a fan of coffee
aren't you oh where am I going no follow
[Music]
Focus
but that was a muscle car no way I
didn't pay attention to that
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
oh
are you guys excited for frog week I'm
so excited
I'm taking tomorrow off though because
I'm I feel like pretty exhausted from
this week I don't know why
was like a long week it felt incredibly
long so tomorrow I take the day off but
you got lucky buddy maybe a small video
will be uploaded question mark question
mark maybe maybe
two videos
um maybe one maybe one
too many emotions this week oh yeah
that's true that's true as well
um
busy week
but
I got done with some things I recorded
like three different things this week
if not four actually I recorded a lot
this week yeah
a lot of side missions
in my quest book are now checked off
just waiting for the reward the quest
rewards Dooku
I am
terrible
one way to do it productive Jillian is
me
and we're finishing up GTA baby
steal the thriller so what does that
thing look like
what do I steal it they said it's
protected right oh
okay don't we have like a sniper rifle
that's like really quiet
it wasn't so quiet that was not so quiet
[Music]
where is that being
that's that's a drill right that's it
it's so slow oh my God
[Music]
[Applause]
personal
what am I supposed to do with this thing
is that even the right thing I think so
I think so
I'm sorry
[Music]
this is an obvious route yeah I guess
already three stars
[Applause]
it's too big to whine so slow
if I get an escape and come back to it
foreign
I don't know where I'm going with this
one here
okay
an option
oh shh
can I though please at least lose the
clubs first
am I am I appropriately hidden oh my God
I can't
no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
[Music]
they lost Vision on the suspect
in fact we have a visual moving in
[Music]
don't go too far away yeah I might lose
the mission right
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no no no no no no no no
oh they're coming right here I have
Footsteps in the water I think nope
stay like that stay like don't stay like
that
they're all there are they coming oh oh
they're coming they're coming I think
they're walking towards me oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
lose me lose me right now let's
oh there oh
[\h__\h]
check it out
I feel like it was so close we could
have gone really we couldn't get really
lucky
if maybe
it would have lost you know the Stars
like right like half a second before day
see me
well I'll just have to kill all of them
no one else is doing this position
they're [\h__\h] everywhere
[Music]
[Laughter]
where did that come from
I just killed someone
how did I do that
some unfortunate really unfortunate
I'm surprised they're not coming down
again
already kill me
oh let's record it here
foreign
[Music]
man I'm like committed to this now
I've started something now I have to end
it
oh
foreign
laughs
oh my
God I can heal back up I can heal back
up
Trevor when I need him huh
I'm losing them
is it
what if I say it here
come on come on faster faster faster
does it take longer to lose them
depending on how many stars you have I
wonder
stay under oh
are we doing it oh my god dude I feel
like I'm in such an open wide spot
was working
oh because it's here with so many of
these streets
did they [\h__\h] he saw me you must have
seen me
no no no no no no no
[Music]
no
[Laughter]
no no no no
[Music]
no no no no no
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh so much pressure
ah
[Laughter]
why it's gonna be like this
oh man this is so amazing oh
well I thought I I did not die I just
failed the mission by abandoning the
driller so I would say I won against the
cops
all right
um what's a better way to do this
oh cause like how the [\h__\h] do you escape
with that thing it's slow it's slow and
it's like being
[Music]
um
a silencer didn't I already have one
though is that a different character
that I had that on
height before taking the drill or selfie
approach ooh muscle car all right
um
cool
let's see I mean I can try to get like a
silencer yeah
at least something to help take out like
one or two guys
Trevor has that uh
sword isn't it
sense
that makes sense
okay I'm Gonna Leave the scene for a
moment
you could even Scout the area for a good
hiding spot but to be honest I think I
have to wing it
I think I'll have to wing it
I have a silence gun my carbine rifle is
depressed oh
is that good enough
it's not a sniper gun though I I would
like to have a suppressor on my sniper
rifle too that would actually be helpful
so let's just go get it
why not why not
uh in here
ammunation
[Music]
oh
I am so sorry oh oh he took it down uh
automatically that's good I thought I
was gonna give a [\h__\h] because I heard
you guys always said don't take out your
gun in the gun shop
so how do we do this
I need like where where do I get that
thing that I need
where
where oh is it like when I select the
sniper rifle
which one is
sniper
uh
I'll hit a suppressor
anything else
of course
if you need advice I am a weapons expert
an expert
okay well then well then that's all I
need are the pink tank
suppressor
all right
upgrade raffle
I guess yeah while we're here you guys
said I need more
more guns
try the railgun Style
[Music]
which one is the railgun what the [\h__\h]
is a royal gun
[Music]
what's the railgun
I know what that actually is
ah
a
[Music]
the one on all the way to the right
where where's that all you have to know
is magnets and it does horrible things
in the things it's pointed at exclusive
content for returning players is it like
uh
it uses magnets
I won't tell wait it's so expensive
what it's 250
000.
she
is it like super quiet or what damage
fire rate accuracy range
guess why not yeah like what else are we
gonna use the money for
pregnant lady by a flame thrower from me
earlier
[Laughter]
I wonder who that was
I'm taking that and oh rounds
a couple runs
they are expensive too
okay that's maximum
what
is one round one shot or is that several
shots
wait should I get more
let's get more
yeah let's get the drip let's get all
the drip
um
salt shotgun SMG hmm
I shoot at all
maybe upgrade what I have as well
uh what do I often use assault rifle
and we can buy some more rounds
uh full ammo
oh
flashlight oh I don't have a flashlight
on
scope standard range okay why not
oh that's cool
painting
[Music]
standard clip
okay
another one
I could even get like a grenade launcher
and [\h__\h] like that I guess but
yeah
what assault SMG is free what do you
mean you can get a gun for free
wow you watch that Republican Space
Rangers I love that show
should I buy another weapon if in that
case which one
[Music]
minigun minigun minigun minigun minigun
minigun this is a minigun it's small it
looks like a like a
like a hot gun hot glue gun
oh
we need gonna speak
[Music]
oh is SMG for minigun
actually this is the one well that's a
machine gun you guys are talking about a
minigun that's not the same thing right
should I not get the machine gun it's
pretty cheap though
you're gonna be very long I need to drop
a deuce yeah sorry about that
bottom right
well the bottom right one is this
swimming launcher
under the rocket launcher that's a
grenade launcher you mean you mean
what is that
a couple of rounds no upgrades here
except for color all right where's that
where's the pinky yeah
God holy [\h__\h] but then Michael has all
the guns and the other ones don't really
well and then maybe I don't have any
armor yet do I
super super heavy armor perhaps that
would have helped me in my Chase a
couple moments ago
and these and anything else that helps
me for the finale
nah I don't care about the tops
I think that's pretty much
all the good stuff all right
Emma I bought the ammo
Once you walk slowly with the minigun ah
I can see that that thing yeah I've seen
people walk really slowly with that
I upgraded the wrong rifle
what
maybe more ammo for the minigun
sheesh
I guess it goes
time to make Weaponry decisions
how about four thousand
[Laughter]
it costs twelve thousand dollars to fire
this thing for two seconds hey yo what
don't let it go now
wasn't there like a function to buy all
of that
I did that by accident before
oh send
[Music]
music
again
okay full full nah it's over nine
thousand no okay
uh so you said I I upgraded the wrong
rifle
foreign
oh you can unbuy it
this one was that the right one maybe
[Music]
so he's getting like really pissed off
hair bun
okay I think I'm happy oh
which one is my pistol no no this one is
that the one I always use
there's no oh wait suppressor
suppressant silencers the same thing
right
we're buying look everything
heavy pistol machine machine pistol
off serial numbers
well guys make the pistol pink so I can
tell the part
but now I almost made everything pink
but this is my it's my only pink pistol
I think
okay
I feel like I'm I'm going to war man
but it's a big one so I guess
that's actually and I actually might be
what we're doing
ah okay all right
I'm done shopping
I'm done shopping we are gonna do the
important [\h__\h] now
sorry for the way um
investment into a better future
and hopefully a successful
mission of stealing the [\h__\h] drill
I don't know how we're gonna pull that
off but ideally I would kill all of them
silently no one would notice I take the
car and no one gives a [\h__\h] but even if
I killed every single person who's
watching I
I still get stars for just stealing it
right
I don't know how to do it
[Music]
safe for doing it
now we could oh wait I went to
um too far behind
just run and grab it oh what are you
doing here lady get up there's some
really traumatizing [\h__\h] about to go
down
that's also the wrong place
if I I just like go in normally and
still okay let me try let me try it
let's what happens if I do that now I'll
nice to meet you sir
well I am here now
[Music]
um
at least I killed no one but I have two
stars all right let's go it's happening
again oh but what if I what if I leave
it here now
oh [\h__\h] why is Friday so fast
get up get up get up before they come
foreign
hide
okay not not the best spot but what if
I'm just here
I wouldn't possibly know I'm back here
right now
right
oh
my God
[Laughter]
[Music]
laughs
yeah baby that's me
missions
successfully you fail but not yet not
yet
don't give up yet guys
helicopter comes in three stars well
marvelous marvelous
we go today kfpm
we go this time
so here is a bridge
um I don't know how to
um well no I'm going down there
in a train tunnel go underground but I
don't know where the entrance to
underground places are [\h__\h]
[Music]
freestyle please
oh wait come on just leave it there for
a while
is it gonna make me fail the mission too
if I go too far because this one
I can go there
and this part alone is taking me five
hours
I know oh Trail
oh so fun
no no failure yet so far
maybe the other way I would go into a
tunnel it was the right way
okay
okay okay
[Music]
do I still have all the guns I bought
wait how can I check oh
oh that's the other
entrance
okay no no I have them I think I have
them
yeah yeah I'm going from the other side
oh
this place is interesting
oh no they're not pink here but yeah
yeah I have I have this I have the
things
foreign
so do you think they'll notice if they
suddenly all start dying
flies
maybe I killed him first and then hide
but will they respawn
that one's
chilling
this one is not silenced
what about this one
I silence at least one sniper rifle
huh
they don't have the upgrades but then
why do I have to oh why do I have
what's the main look side I have the
rail gun but not any of the upgrades in
ammo
did I lose the money too
no
oh that's annoying
wow
I'm sorry guys
[Music]
use the carbine
but that's another sniper
it's okay it's okay we want to buy
everything anyway so
I'll have to go back eventually so might
as well go now
might as well go now okay okay
I missed my turn
why is everyone so for magic chill
I don't even have my railgun out I'm
excited to use that one by the way but
it seems like a really expensive
object
I don't know how often we're gonna use
it
okay okay
uh so this one or this one
I have both I don't know where the
difference is between these things
you're gonna be very long this one
doesn't have a suppressor okay we buy
this we buy a couple oh we have enough
round I think we make it Pink So I know
which one to use
and we go here and we buy all the rounds
how do I buy all of them oh that's
already full okay
yeah yeah
oh wait
we already have
okay okay
that's fine it's fine it's fine then we
buy I'm guessing I guess we're buying
these
there's a weapon that impart the Red Sea
ah full ammo there you go
as hell pink gun
and then with carbine rifle gets uh
upgrade
let's press already in there okay I
think all the good guns I'm gonna mark
them pink
AP pistol
and pink
I think that's really all I need and
I know this reset this as well
yeah everybody said that too yeah baby
fits like a condom
s okay I'm
medically right
oh and I should say
phone oh I can't oh
I can't save
[Music]
ah
so there's a chance I'm Gonna Lose It
Again the blue bar Ah that's the armor
okay I don't know
leave the mission first
um
well we just can't fail this time
foreign
maybe you guys can tell me we look at
the map and then in case I have to hide
the truck somewhere you guys can tell me
where is a good spot because you guys
seem to know this map better than I do
because you're always smart asking me
like
and yeah you find the bridge why are you
driving the dead this and there
I don't know
series are like this is where the water
is
is it
um Olivia Christian North
where do we wanna go
hard to point it train tunnel
I know what the train tunnel is
I don't know what you mean with them no
where is it everything looks the same to
me
frustrated it doesn't say what's Grove
Street
repaint the track
no no I I don't mean abandoning it in
height I mean hide with the big thing
it's not helpful
not helpful
oh too close
you can go to the hairdresser get a new
haircut and that works
no way
really I've never been to the
hairdresser in this game
that sounds like a funny oops
a funny idea in case I keep on failing
and in any case I'm gonna go take The
High Ground now I'm trying to kill
people in silence
maybe over there
the fence is pretty good to hide and
then get down again
okay
maybe this is the best spot what do you
think
I'm gonna use the oh sniper rifle
how how am I gonna kill both of them so
fast
him
what happens
no one noticed
they still didn't notice
I would do I I would be cool if I could
shoot through them if I if I get like
one line you know
but then I think I'll have to get down
oh wait she's moving
oh [\h__\h] someone
laughs
oh hey I have two stars no I thought I
could get away without Stars ah
unnecessary Demps man unnecessary
unfortunately but well
I wanna [\h__\h]
I don't wanna [\h__\h] it up
maybe hairdresser for real
hide
hide here in here
I'm not spotted yet well they're right
there though I'm feeling like I'm
don't drive out the compound yet don't
kill the cops
yeah okay yeah well it was already
[Music]
oh
my God
I'm not going to shoot the castle
as long as I don't shoot the cups I
don't get the first star Maybe
I'll go this way
everybody join me we're gonna get a new
haircut
yeah it was about time
yeah
I'm not armed what do you mean
no I want to take the pistol oh [\h__\h]
don't happen to me
you're making it harder for yourself oh
why did I oh
oh oh okay okay
just a normal day in GTA
a big turn wow this reminds me of you
know in Malcolm in the Middle there's
this episode where race
um is trying to escape from the cops but
then like he drives really really well
and impresses everybody and it's like
really
fun
and the girl is also really impressed
um
hopefully I'm telling you you don't
sleep in that haircut Sirens
um see ya it's not gonna work it has to
work somebody
's people at least said it's working it
works
no way come in have a seat I don't hear
sirens anymore the stars are gone you
know how you want it done well I wonder
if I go outside if it tells me Mission
failed
oh fluffy hair let's go with fluffy hair
this is some of my best
[Music]
did I lose them
love the cutscene love it love all of
this to you
the queen shave even though if I had the
full beard
they probably wouldn't recognize me even
more
it all it works only your first
the the cutscene oh thank God I went
here before
I cannot change the color by the way I
would love to give him like pink pink
hair no come back anytime
they'll never spot me like this
that looks so different
oh my truck is still there oh
[Music]
oh so much
Michael yeah so we got one of these uh
cutter things what do you want me to do
with it
I borrowed at the parking lot around
from the bank he'll open the gates for
you okay if you trust him
but okay just this one we've done
similar things
um similar missions many times before
when I had to escape and I did it okay I
did it many times we're at the end of
the game forgive me this once we're
doing it this way
please forgive me
oh yeah the ammo that didn't work yeah
but that's probably because I didn't
enter for the first time
I get it there it gave me a cutscene
that made the difference probably
yeah no more stars but this car doesn't
want to drive man
ah
I'm so relieved now I felt like this is
gonna take ages
thank God the rest should hopefully not
make so much trouble anymore getting a
getaway car is really not the issue
unless they want something really
specific being stolen from a really
specific person but they only said I
need a fast
car I think
waste it nah
the chases were fun okay
not all wasted
oh was that wrong oh I wasn't supposed
to get up here oopsie
okay one turn
sorry guys I really need to make a
journey oh no
I hate when that happens
oh we attached it no we had it for a
second I feel like
please go away you're gonna get me in
trouble
[Music]
okay drive just drive just right
[\h__\h]
up
[Music]
how is this not good enough huh
reattaching in this game is like the
[\h__\h]
okay
I'm back in the game
it's a little bit painful but I'm back
in the game
I don't want to do that turn though
maybe I can go differently I'll go I'll
go this way
I know the game really wants me to do a
u-turn
forcing me
uh
don't worry guys
the sirens are not for me although I
really oh hey maybe I'm helping them
this
feels like they are oh
[Music]
no I think the police is dead
one of them is dead
oh good luck guys it's not my problem
it's like a you problem I am actually
gonna continue driving this way
[Music]
in your criminal activities
I can totally relate just like me for
real for real
hey this works
it's about time we moved to a different
city man
go to somewhere peaceful on the
mountains or
on a lake on the lake side
that's my dream
Lakeside house or apartment yeah Miami
Miami
Miami you're saying is more peaceful
than this place
isn't there a GTA already that plays in
Miami
the Maldives dad and Maldives that's a
peaceful place by city and there you go
I know that one
okay uh in here
oh we're going along today it's gonna
take a while guys are you still going to
do our Landings um depends how long this
takes and I'll decide spontaneously
um
all right Lester the drills at the lot
good work but let's not get ahead of
ourselves there's a fair amount of prep
work still to do
places to suitable vehicle in the bank's
parking garage this will be used to get
away okay that's easy
oh we're just gonna get a fast five but
it has to be a four-seater I suppose a
couple
what about contact issue
safe okay
when I always think the most obvious
thing that it would be in the obvious
menu no
and
where do I save I'm just gonna make
another new one
okay Ctrl s really does that work
I have not forgotten the getaway vehicle
no I'm on it that would have been maybe
a good one
it's not looking fast enough
[Music]
Kiwana coming through the
fruit I will not show you
show us
decently fast
oh
no
what do you think guys it is I think of
course dinner
could use a custom one it's a muscle car
this oh it says it's unsuitable well
lady you're getting your car back today
is your lucky day
congratulations what about these no
that's a two-seater
an SUV
what about this
that doesn't look very fast but there's
a lot of space
let's see
is answerable there are not enough there
are not enough seats
they're not enough
seeing the police on me
he's calling I feel like he's calling
the police oh my God come on lady don't
fight that's glitched isn't it okay this
has four seats it's not telling me
anything no and
[Music]
um
them all
right
oh my God
[Music]
Escape all the pain oh why why did I
have to steal that dude's car
it could have been so peaceful so easy
so simple
[Music]
it's okay I'm losing them
come back oh
keep it up keep it up oh is that did I
go in a circle
okay answer the ball of course it is
what about that one
dad has more than enough seats and it
doesn't look very fast
unsuitable
if you wish
um okay
okay
[Music]
the one before that was definitely
bugged man
okay uh what I have to select uh
uh uh getaway location or what what was
that
what's a good spot
does it have to be hidden modded
upgraded really is it important in this
case
it's not gonna be good enough otherwise
place
bulletproof tires oh okay okay
maybe we can make it a bit faster too
okay well it's the last mission so
it might be actually challenging
Orange
you sure you want to stand out so much
from such a
beautiful color of car hmm
is this the right place or is this just
a garage wait that's just the garage
isn't it the spray can was it right the
spray can ah right there
I forgot
best color Yes orange is very beautiful
don't know if I would paint my car
orange but if it was like
um that one card the one speed car that
we drove today
that orange looked really beautiful
especially on that car
so you just kind of
just gonna do it right you know
any color can look good
if you
choose the right
hue
and all that
can make a big difference and on the
right car and the right person parents
okay that's the best mechanic in LS do
for you
um foreign
what can you do that's a good question
how about oh a repair first of all okay
and then
armor
how about like 60 percent
or 80 percent
well all of it
okay
um why the wheels here bulletproof got
it
no that's not the right thing
or was the armor already
what I needed does that already make it
Bulletproof
right
race breaks
I guess just bio is the most the most
expensive thing
ah is there a real attire wheel or Tire
s
entire enhancements there we go
some people do this without upgrades I
don't know if we really have to make
everything so overpowered
what what does this stuff to
acceleration
engine
oh wait that's that's what it was okay
and maybe because I don't like
I don't like this green I'm not gonna
make it
like a funky color oopsie
um why is he so shiny
Italian
they have a weird glow around it
see that
that oh that cool too look at that
orange
shine over there
see I like this wine red I don't drink
wine but this I do not mind
okay
I'm happy with that
oh
looking good not too Speedy yeah
can I do over here turbo what about that
Turbo
that's so
again
sheesh you can get that for so little
money
is there like bulletproof windows yeah
it's not suspension no
okay
let's not spend let's not waste any more
time
and confirm transmission what's the
transmission
are you not happy with this
here for the Magic Touch
even more speed dear God you can really
manage those RPMs
no more
suspension was mentioned on the mission
did I not get that
I don't need all this
that's what I'm thinking
okay now we just need to pick a good
spot is anywhere okay I don't remember
exactly what he wanted from me
that's familiar
what if I put it here
you can I think in the context right
Mark it
um
oh let's turn get on my vehicle ready
it's ready
meow
meow meow hey I got something we can use
for the getaway I'll call you when it's
in the parking garage okay I'm not going
anywhere
okay now he's telling me where he wants
me to bring it oh right thank you Lester
very helpful
and the road is above me though
where's where's straight
here
[Music]
yo Pimp My Ride I pimped it I don't need
exhibit for that
I pimp my own cars I'm an independent
Phoenix
holy [\h__\h] is so fast
oh
so well prepared for the heist
nothing can go wrong now I hope I hope
everything will go smooth
as smooth as smoothie
Olympus exhibit
I know how it's so funny though don't
you think the name sounds similar last
time I'm playing I was just trying to
talk about get my ride and said before
right by Limp binskin but I knew
something was wrong there I know
something was awesome
sorry it sounds so similar though
it has like a similar ring to it
[\h__\h]
can you imagine Pimp My Ride with Limp
Bizkit makes no sense
doesn't really fit
oh killed
car I actually after the last GTA stream
I was seriously looking through like
this
old car vintage car auction
and a non-auctional website I was
looking at so many cars man and that is
like really considering not buying right
now but buying in the future like I just
had to get like a feeling for
what the prices are and all that
yeah I really want to get one of those
it's not down here I know it is
you good
yeah I know I can't drive now that's why
I'm not getting the car yeah but oh I
will I will I'm gonna get a really fancy
car
I didn't do anything a really fancy not
a sports car just a vintage card and
then a normal car too
old cars require a lot of Maintenance
that's why I'm not gonna drive a bit a
lot just you know to flex and look cute
it's gonna be my spirit animal again on
the train we'll be ready to hit it
yes two cars one cheap one
that's just for driving every day and
then and then the vintage car
sorry what did you say
what did he say I was so in my
conversation
can you repeat Lester
change to Trevor
let's train
they didn't mark anything though did he
yeah
okay let's try switching
Maybe
[Music]
did you guys say Franklin no Trevor
that's a Trevor
they gonna do their part too why do I
have to do everything huh
ice
do we ever find him
differently at least this time he's not
naked
[Music]
um
he's trying to cope
with something with his love for Michael
that he's he just can't admit
uh
do I have to wait a bit to get a call
hmm I'm waiting
or Patricia ah I almost forgot about her
oh why'd you have to remind me
no no I'm really sad for him oh I like
that color
and we go to age
that's a long ride
but
I'll do it
[Music]
which car
which car which car
panting Trevor Trevor now your help
Trisha Trevor oh that's good to speak to
you my thoughts are with you
you treating you well
ever you're a sweet boy Trevor please
I really missed
go
oh no why do they always have these
short conversations I want them to marry
each other get back together if if if
she's part of his life he will surely
find
clarity
over his issues and problems
completes him is there like any like
side quests I'm not saying I would want
to do it but the way just to say that
you're always in my heart my heart is
full because you already did be good
what we have together it was very
special I love you but I am a wife and a
wife must be with her husband I suppose
is there
is there a quest where you can like
romance her and marry her
but any chance
no
once they're [\h__\h] bathing me I feel
for them
I shipped them
they were so cute together
no that's so sad will he ever find love
will you ever find happiness will we
ever feel complete
besides you know
a friend with Michael
[Music]
yeah
nothing's going on oh
I wanted to convert my car into a
convertible
now I have some fresh air flowing
through and I feel much better now
I don't understand I was pretty sick
thank you yeah there was a lot of
momentum there that I did not expect
[Music]
hmm
you know what time it is tomorrow
tomorrow is Monday tomorrow is
houses with dragon time I'm excited
I was going to say Game of Thrones all
the time I'm like so close to saying
Game of Thrones I really have to hold
myself back it's so hard not to say oops
so hard not to say Game of Thrones
so I stopped
tomato
es
oh Michael what's up
Mike I'm getting that train we need for
the ud job I need you to get that
Chopper Leicester organized and come
pick it up oh now you need me I'm on my
way
is that a bug
[Laughter]
the trail was like oh now you need me
[\h__\h] no I'm not helping you after all
even though I committed to the big one
I didn't do anything
I was about to turn left
eh I drove Pat what I I was literally no
no that's not my fault I may I may have
went one meter
interesting
I was teleported
to the right area
dad I appreciate
but I am right behind them
is this a stealthy thing or is this uh
let's [\h__\h] go kind of thing
is
are they right next to order
see two dots but I only see him oh wow
self
Trevor never goes job yeah it's really
not much like him
he has a grenade launcher since when did
I get him a grenade launcher
proof his weapons too at some point
huh
there
hmm let's make it clean
Michael the guards are done
okay okay get to the single box see this
actually saved us a little bit of time
of the time that we've been wasting
elsewhere
all right I'm here track's been flipped
Michael where are you
just like me for real for real I also
never know where I am wait for a train
to stop in the sightings
yeah
but what did he just you
train he says but
I already switched it don't have to
switch it again
he's coming the train is coming
I already did it though
can't do it again anyway the game is not
telling me
any oh oh is it okay
all good
stop it I need a chopper pilot yeah
what how is he already in the chapel wow
wow wow I feel like I really made it
easy for myself
I wait chocolate without controller
I I don't remember how to fly it without
a controller holy [\h__\h] what a what a
helicopter
I wanna switch your controller but I
well it's gonna like [\h__\h] around again
with the audio
R2 press R2
okay okay
um
let's
see what happens
well
at least I still hear myself well
okay
game audio
non-existent all right
and let's fix this
I don't know if you guys heard anything
but I didn't and that's a problem
so okay change this to this
change this to this
and then
here we have
Grand Theft Auto
this please work like sometimes I change
things in this audio settings but it
does actually always switch back
to whatever the [\h__\h] it wants to it's
not working
uh
[Music]
yeah I don't know why it always does
this
I I changed it you know where you can
change it for specific programs only I
changed it to what it should be but
as being a real [\h__\h] about it
um
can I
go
maybe this one deactivate
[Music]
I did it okay but how do you fly again
it's been a while
take off of R2 and then I guess just
continue pressing R2
um
no triangle yeah yeah yeah
what about landing gear was that a thing
of helicopters I think the landing gear
is already out though
I think we're good we just
have to hover over something to pick it
up probably let's go
r2l2
oh
oh it's right there I didn't know where
it was so close
all right all right all right
look down
just don't break it
[Music]
[Applause]
never seen a helicopter like this before
by the way I guess it's really
specifically for picking up things
wow
where you want me where where where
I was basically on top of it no
I see the blue dot yeah I thought it was
on top of it
how is there like another button that I
have to use to like
specifically pick it up
okay
how about this
I'm trying to go back backwards
backwards backwards
press okay
activate electromagnet
[Music]
so close it even gave me the right
button prompt
oh well
I need to be on
so I'm just gonna pick it up properly
you don't you just mean like hovering
above it like one meter above it or so
right not like 20 meters or so oh wait
we're already here
already here okay okay
I'm here I'm here
no why not
it can't get smoother than this man
[Music]
okay
not so bad it took me only like two
tries
locomotion
impressive this must be really heavy
damn
it's okay
yeah
I didn't know this was a thing but okay
well
okay okay we're here we're here let's go
down
wait wait don't don't break anything
lower the engine onto the trailer
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
lower how Oh you mean lower
color
here here take it take it take it take
it
I'm on my way back
oh
pick up a flat bed Carriage aura
nothing I was using l1r1 yeah yeah
well my line will come on
foreign
time
smoothly now
why are there five
blue dots
does it not matter
what is a flatbed anyway
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
what's a flatbed flat then
truck with a long flat Trail okay
ah these things oh okay okay
I wish you could like kind of stop it
from moving so much
I got it
back to the Airfield oh I stopped moving
do I have to do that with all of them
that was forgiving don't question it my
skills my magnetic power is just so
strong
I have a magnetic field around me
is more powerful than any map that
you've ever seen
so where are we dropping this one
oh on top of that as well
where did you have a bingo
interesting
I'm getting used to it now wow
okay I didn't have to do all of them
down the helicopter now maybe
unless unless
we are now the proud owners of a freight
train excellent I'll let the others know
we have everything we need and we'll
meet in the strip club
of course the strip club all right maybe
should I go there with the helicopter
I can just switch to Michael right oh
wait this is Michael's let me switch
Trevor
where is he at on his home
that is General
what's going on
you good bro
[\h__\h] disgusting like how how do you
not get all kinds of diseases by living
in a place like these
things
taking a bath please please more than
just your head please do us the favor oh
what you doing
he's styling oh let me try that too
he did not miss
huh I did it I'm better than you
what you gonna do now huh apologies
she's so defensive he doesn't want to
fight with me oh he loves me
but okay what's what's Franklin and we
haven't seen Franklin at all today
I understand no
oh where is this is this
oh
Thunder
[\h__\h] was that sound
what was that
I see no Thunder
okay what was that
okay oh no
we are going not to the elbow to the H I
think H he's the closest
to the strip club so
maybe we're saving some time here too
[Music]
should we stop by a weapon shop for him
as well
the closest one is that a weapon shop
yeah that's that's one
okay let's go
give everyone a fair chance
at doing whatever we're doing
whatever we need all that [\h__\h] for
[Music]
good night good night I'll be going to
sleep
sweet dreams
everyone should get some nice weapons
okay we still have to have to do that
with Trevor uh yeah I hope we have time
for that
dude
like oh my God whatever
[Music]
hello kind Mr Sir friend
I
I don't know should I buy him the same
[\h__\h] like also
it's Under One Roof
he still has a lot of money as well
armor for sure yeah
um
Trevor doesn't need it he just flies you
mean in this mission
I thought maybe there's another reason
why you want me to get it some kind of
Showdown or so but okay
money is shared if only the guns were
shared too
what do we need let's upgrade
I was given this one that way that's so
expensive give me back I can't I can't
take it back okay
why did I give him that I didn't want to
give him pink so I can like see the
difference you know
it looks nice though you want to buy
that gun I don't know you tell me man
that's a lot of money man
[Music]
wow we're not gonna get that one though
and green because you know apparently
that's his gang's color and not because
they're
um
matching by accident because their
brains are connected
what else
anything else you
recommend me to upgrade or buy
never killed a man I won't tell honest
none of your business
minigun minigun minigun on this one too
you want him to have a minigun too no
no
expensive
I don't need so many rail guns
um
well
all right he'll get a minigun doesn't
look so many though
I also sell a kid for filing off serial
numbers
oh oh what would you use that for
how well for the gun I love the serial
number of the gun so when they are found
they don't know who was the owner
um
oh for crime
I recorded what you just said sir and I
will send that to the police
[Music]
were you guys in school like the type of
person who would go to the teacher and
rat somebody out for
saying something mean or evil because I
was definitely the type but that's
mostly because you know I was being
I was the most unpopular kid and people
were being [\h__\h] mean and to me and
bullying me so
that's what I have butts tubes sometimes
try to protect myself or pay them back
with some [\h__\h] Revenge
I ain't no snitch this is good stitches
well it was for a good cause
all right
foreign
[Music]
did you get stitches no no never got
stitches in my whole life
well done now
[Music]
I love railgun man I love it
amazing anime my favorite top free anime
railgun is in that one definitely
yeah that's the only railgun you'll be
hearing or seeing no
no no no
Phenom ammo I got ammo for the minigun
too
my favorite well done girl
up
I think back in the day I really liked
kurokolo
but now I might feel differently
[Music]
not sure I should re-watch it it's been
a long time
I bought max ammo as far as I remember
like salary don't know um but I did I
think there was wasn't there it wasn't
an index movie or a random Gun movie but
there was a movie with this like
um singing cute girl Frank good to see
you I liked her as well
does anyone
's name
hey so we really gonna get this [\h__\h]
cracking right oh yeah get dressed and
maybe you will
ready
let's go
all right I'm gonna meet my guy oh wow
they look fancy yeah
I got style they're dripping they look
like Men in Black
can I save by the way though okay
all right I guess we're taking separate
cars [\h__\h] you too Trevor [\h__\h] you let's
go
a big one
once again
well I like that tune I would love to
listen to that but I'm sorry I really
like this
listening to nothing
you're saying you're not capable we need
Lester in the air running comms and
managing the link up with the train some
rental Hood ain't going to be able to
handle Logistics t
v no I think this is why I also don't
listen to music in my free time a lot of
the time anymore
I just need it to be quiet sometimes or
all of the time just like talk so much I
guess during the day
maybe that's the reason
on it
same same I used to always listen to
music like on the side not anymore maybe
I wouldn't expect that it could be the
age
I'm going through the Vault wall
speaking of do you
know oh it's happening it's happening
hey so turn on the cutter blades hold W
to move the cutter torso or like for
example
where
where there
we opened the can we take out the beans
okay
yeah and do you do you speaking of do
you
what the [\h__\h] oh hey
um uh today in case you were curious
about that the do You choreography has
been uploaded to my
choreographer's channel
hey here we go
guys
the full choreo
I retweeted it
I think there were some people who
wanted to do a full dance cover Maybe
so feel free to do that now
hard to cut the out of the way by the
wall
hey cops will be here soon we gotta blow
these cages fast the choreo is really
hard and it doesn't only look like it it
is hard
Place explosive charges on the Vault
doors like a sticky bomb
is that what you mean
oh wait here
do they mean the sticky bombs okay we
got two cages to open
all right arms are in place
what is the detonation button again was
it f no was it e no
[Music]
should I protect
a defense Chef okay defensive defensive
[Music]
I'm gonna smoke when I'm done
I'm doing my best I'm trying
[Music]
oh oh
stay back
[Music]
I got the other side go ready to go
he's not showing up anymore
[Music]
you were
them
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry
we have to do that again
[Music]
I really don't know what kind of what
situation the only thing I know is if I
want to shoot someone who's really far
away then I use a sniper that's all I
know
foreign
[Music]
hmm well where is the end goal which way
will he be going
[Music]
is he coming he's coming
back to hell look
they're alive they're all alive they're
all alive they're all alive they're all
alive
[Music]
other side another influx of cops the
other side come on get the trolleys
where we need them
half the golden GTG I don't care
hey motor Metal Man
what gun am I using right now what is
that
how long y'all need
[Music]
[Applause]
another carbon right okay
I got them all
teeth ready to go for the Choppers at
helicopter inbound
's ready
[Music]
worked really well
um
felt like it was easy to control and did
good damage
more they're in the fall what in the
vault
yeah I should take cover oh nice just
get the bricks out hey the boss empty
already Punk
I don't understand
you chose the wrong option
we all are on the Run team
we're the good ones
it's just a matter of how you look good
at it is the glass half empty or half
full you know that kind of [\h__\h] oh oh
are they coming from the side too oh
the Metal's gone already
all right I'm taking this side you take
the other one all right all right I'm
I'm
I don't I actually don't trust you to do
a good job at that so let me help you
out here too although I really don't see
them from here
this thing
[Music]
a little [\h__\h]
oh I think I got a part of him
all right oopsie and then here
next we're switching
oh control
please and faster away all right we're
coming
[Music]
get out of here
yeah we don't have to ever
do crime again really good luck dog I'll
run
hi
Michael your turn again
guess we're out of the city why did I
really have a switch for that they could
have done that on their own
[Music]
whoa this is the way
this is Delaney you know the way you
seem to know the way pretty well
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh nice nice nice
[Music]
it's this way
oh he's not dead I think
you have been released from your
suffering because life is suffering
Chopper we're shooting that are we going
down
oh after doing the walk in the union
depository man it was a whole lot less
successful than your lick but we needed
to divide attention
we're in the same position man why are
we coming through
bad position let me go here on the floor
across the bridge
this is a [\h__\h] show
out the way okay we're getting out one
way or another
let's go
where am I supposed to go
here
you really want to die for these
[\h__\h]
stand and stop
let's go
oh [\h__\h] I'm I'm nervous another mini gun
hi gun where's my minion going where's
that I don't think he has it
didn't we get one for him too
oh
oh God I'm gonna die though
don't be a hero
Chopper
ah
I don't see anyone push through that set
the bridge across off the street
you don't want to screw with me
hey they didn't give us the goal it's
fun though I don't mind repeating
over here
what's your problem
[Music]
it's so cute everybody who sees my
minigun underestimated but now they
shouldn't
they really shouldn't
it
what's up
sweet raunchy Strat once again I'm just
chasing it man
they're doing the walk in the union
depository man wow what is so accurate
holy [\h__\h] less successful than your lick
but we needed to divide attention
come on
laying down
I don't wanna switch why do I have to
switch
well you can have a minigun too
in three seconds here is how you do it
life hacks stand aside
life hack baby
oh I'm so happy you guys told me to get
the minigun
we're getting out one way
oh oh I can't why can I not get out of
the way
I'm too close to the the
a point I guess oh you really want do
this
I hope I can't do Friendly Fire man
because they're always getting in this
way
my life is complete now that I know
about these things oh [\h__\h]
are you guys doing any damage at all
can I jump while shooting
don't be a hero
let's go up a level okay stairs right
here
hey let it rip
we're exposed here look out
suppose no problem
my specialties
stay on me
a scripted then they land there because
that was beautiful
oh my HP can I like hide a little bit
like and heal like
a bit
is that heels right yeah yeah yeah just
give me a moment
here
is that it will only heal so half
very accurate beautiful shots that you
see here
[Music]
professionals
oh nice shot
I'm the one who gets the kill you get
the assist I got the kill
foreign
[Music]
shooting
which one is the real gun oh my God I
don't see the wait where is it
whatever
ain't nobody got time for that
over here
did he switch weapons when I switched to
a different character on the minigun
minigun
20 rounds like how does this even work
what kind of shots does he do that'll
take us back it's not worth it it's on
his way
don't be dumb
what
[Laughter]
when there's 50 people in one spot man
yes
well okay now I know what that one is
like
oh on vehicles okay okay
I've been working it's super good too
let's go
hey on the right [\h__\h] they come oh love
they coming
oh
maybe you know why I want to get out of
this because you got a wife and kids
right you know
okay oh
[Laughter]
down here
you really want to die for these
[\h__\h]
[Music]
this is like a cheese man
[Applause]
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
out there
[Applause]
yeah
yeah next time
all right come here come here I'll wait
for you to stop Maybe
yeah oh is that the car oh they probably
brought it over here let's go
Why Don't We Just Kill Them All
oh that's not boring wait what do you
mean lose them I have five stars
okay I'm driving where to where to where
to where to
where ah this is the part that I'm
always the worst Dad we could have just
killed them all until we and then and
then you're late every single cop in the
city
uh
we gotta lose them
[Music]
maybe I should not get out of the city I
don't know should I
oh
oh hello
hey Nick of the metal let's go [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
I don't know
if I fail doesn't make me redo
everything or just like this part
okay okay okay once I'm past this point
I see no more dots so
if I just escape this seems to do the
trick
oh wait there's more right now I'm
losing them now though
can I go up here
so I'm so sorry you did definitely not
deserve that but this is a good spot for
me you know
hopefully the Choppers won't get my
scent but let me lose the stars please
it's like any score you just lose the
car
that's what I'm doing that's what I'm
doing
that's what I think I'm doing
oh I see that I see it
success
hey we're getting cold not now homie yes
yeah oh oh oh
showed up there
it's another one of those moments but
with this car it's really working well
where's the Holy Ghost maybe I'm the
goat maybe I'm the greatest of them
[Music]
and the goldest
but how long does this take
how much longer do you want me to do
this
[Music]
I can't do better than this oh [\h__\h]
they're following me
hey if they catch this man
region or something like that oh no oh
[\h__\h] but they're all coming from there
no
no I didn't know
hahaha
you got this right no
it was so close to doing it though but
okay this car is really good wow it's
like a mountain car
like a mountain bike but it's a car
okay okay
are they following me how's it looking
no they're on the street will they not
go off-road on unless they see me
is a good spot perhaps for now
[Music]
am i hidden it's just a little heat man
you can handle this oh they're over
there will they see me
I'm coming from over there
you shouldn't see me though
oh
wow funny funny
him
I still got the blinking stars though if
I understand correctly then every second
with a blinking star means I'm still
hidden to them
oh [\h__\h] oh no no
the [\h__\h]
no my car
oh my God
I'm so hot what happens if I lose this
oh no what happens so I have to redo the
whole shooting too
no never give up
maybe I can get another haircut with a
different character
never give up I'm Gonna Give You Up
Never Gonna add you down [\h__\h] the car
has been really like losing its control
at this point
and we're gonna run around and desert
you
and I'm gonna say goodbye
make you cry
oh sorry about that oh
[Music]
please don't I want to hide there
how about here
foreign
might be good
for how long
there's no one coming from there
I think this is good
oh
gosh I wanna go
[Music]
impressive what did he say located
it's still blinking
and they're like all in that one spot
but oh they're watching looking for me
on foot now
squamous day
stream sniping yeah they're watching my
stream oh [\h__\h] they're getting closer
and closer I have to go I have to go I
have to go to go I have to go
the car can't take much more though
I feel like it's falling apart
everything my whole life too
let's keep going but more or less
carefully let's try to be as careful as
possible this is a good spot too
cars are pretty far away
all right I mean I still like 200
million I understand that they're being
like this
[Music]
[Laughter]
gee I think we're in the clear we doing
all right
[Music]
yeah Hallelujah
I need to drink water
ah
okay okay thank god wow so
it really does take longer when you have
five stars follow Italiana Martinez
okay that's our as our friend that we
saved yeah I am
help us attack the trumpets by flying
close to marijuana keeping the chopper
steady
but we have to we're going
to wait
and never change but okay we're shooting
them down huh
fly steady all right all right all right
I have to follow them right try to shoot
them
down
exactly that
is
going down
this is dangerous though this is really
dangerous
[Music]
oh that one is still thank God that
wheel
Wheel of Time we missed um
[Music]
oh dramatic crash
drop the gold into the train car mm-hmm
is
the most difficult part perhaps
um
okay how do I drop in oh oh oh
it wasn't so difficult
we're good
all skills increase let's go
my job here is done
[Applause]
they don't know what happened we're
clear
[Music]
[Applause]
so proud
[Music]
stable man you know that don't go near
the Rockets again
those guns were so overpowered though I
feel like it's made of too easy
make it out
but at least this way we saved a lot of
time I guess
and don't have to
um worry about all the endings maybe
this is really in this way we can get
all the endings
[Music]
yeah that's big
ger
I suppose so now if only we can get the
landing right
hmm
because it wants me to go to a very
specific spot doesn't it oh no that's
good that's good
[Music]
yes R yeah good yeah
all right are we good
you are one serious [\h__\h] buzz kill oh
why not party mood where's the party all
right he needs a party hat otherwise he
doesn't feel like partying
yes both of you it's been a pleasure
working with you you'll get paid when we
get the cash
until then I want you to keep it on the
down low no new cars no vacations
come on sugar
this gas can't be in here
all right
beautiful last mission hmm
something's pissed me off but mostly it
went smoothly
just the beginning was rough
the big one has
dictator
mama
okay what now oh that's that's a little
bit too close to comfort my friend
we're going back into the city
safe now oh
okay
quick save I'll make another one
[Laughter]
so this is
maybe I'll make another one
there's a square
it gets important
how much more time from here on do you
guys have an estimate per per ending
what's with the green circle that's like
a side mission that I started but it's
so [\h__\h] I I gave up on it
really short
30 minutes for one ending okay can I go
to the Iowa meeting really quickly
let's do all the endings because 30
minutes is nothing and I think we're
doing good on time and BRB everyone gets
a toilet break as well I get an idle
break
see you in a second
or two or three or five
foreign
[Music]
I mastered flying vehicles you think so
yeah definitely need that PS5 controller
though
um
so
uh let's see what did I like get a call
or so did I do two saves
just for good measure let's do another
one so we have free saves one for each
um
for each ending I guess
yeah all right what's next
am I waiting for a call or so
I didn't expect a minigun to be as
useful as it was to you oh why not
it's incredible but how my aim my aim is
really good too but I felt like with the
minigun
my aim was even better it doesn't have
like huge bullets or how does that work
does it shoot like five bullets at once
is that one of those that's why it uses
up so much
I'm not going to L I had to F okay
I think my aim was good
um
it's very stable
whoa
it's just really fast ah
100 a second
really
my name was good I I have to agree
because even when I was not using it my
aim was really good
I have to say it all yesterday when I
was playing OverWatch holy [\h__\h] like
games like that
I wanted to say that my aim improved
through GTA but maybe not really
compared to like OverWatch that's just
like a whole nother story and also I
also don't really know how to play all
the characters I guess
um
but with a game like this it's easier
like I'm used to this now
OverWatch has no aim assist
oh
oh wants to be different
oh yeah well it's PVP and online and
everybody's jumping around like crazy
these cops ain't jumping around like
crazy
all they do is duck and then they come
back and they duck and they come back
and that's it
it's a whole nother story
Mountain keyboard oh no no I use
bouncing keyboard for GTA 2. just for
flying I would switch to the controller
[Music]
um
at my mom wasn't that good when she
started playing FPS all you need is
practice
yeah but I don't know it's not it's not
really
why what I want anyway
I don't want to necessarily get good at
over lunch or those kind of competitive
shooting games I had fun getting into
GTA really and I will
um try to get perms for other GTA games
I will look into that
for future playthroughs but I I don't
think I ever really want to take this
kind of Apex OverWatch kind of games
seriously I'm sorry to disappoint oh
nice car
so why do I have so many vehicles well
yeah
San Andreas yeah yeah I remember most of
you guys want me to play San Andreas so
I'm keeping that one in mind
I'm here
what now um
someone's at the door
who's there
I'm not buying anything oh it's me oh
sheesh oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] you got
your body guys
hey you got some coconut water or
something like that some electrolytes
am I supposed to kill you now oh no bro
not me
hmm
no
oh yeah
but that's my boy
That's my boy he has betrayed everyone
he's ever known he's got you and Michael
federal government and he's messed up
several business ventures oh did I
choose an ending just by playing
Franklin
but it is personal personal but the fast
man the feds have told me to kill Trevor
and I obviously can't kill them both
I own shopping malls I would not employ
those two clowns and and I make one
phone call there their careers they
listen to some 50 Grand a year pension
hunter or B a billionaire who even the
president lets finger his wife or C try
and be really stupid and save those two
idiot mentors of yours and have
everybody in the goddamn State crawling
up your ass hey can we just kill him
sometimes ticking pal
and your answer is why is that not an
option
man [\h__\h] you
Genius answer pal total genius but time
is running you think about it me I got a
triathlon coming up oh I see training
but bye
[\h__\h]
oh
well that is very
very hard to say blatant that choice
uh we will uh which will be
for me the most satisfying one I think C
so should we do that one last
or
and if I had to
wait is there if I played Michael is
there no choice of killing Franklin is
he completely out of that out of the
game just does no one consider killing
Franklin at all
he's the best boy
okay okay he doesn't deserve to be an
option at all okay let's do c last oh
what do you think what's the what's the
best or like the the most uh Canon
ending
but some say see less sometimes you see
first C is Canon okay okay okay
well let's start with Michael not that
it's my number one choice but let's get
that out of the way
maybe it will be sad because if Franklin
has to kill Michael he likes him like
how is that gonna go
Tony is
[Music]
Michael I'm calling you because I want
to kill you
sorry look man we need to talk but
somewhere quiet all right
um
You and Me we'll meet off Route 68 by
that fuel to satellite dishes
I just snipe him
I'm doing all of them chill guys I'm
doing all of them
the game will erase him
doing all of them going back to myself
hey T-man I'm in trouble dog I think I
gotta take out Mike are you guys not
good too listen yeah man look what I'm
doing FIB man they trying to get me to
clap you and Devin Weston he trying to
get me to ice Michael and I thought if I
if I do enter the stream now
what are you telling me this for cause
dog I'm doing this for us I thought you
could a million times
[\h__\h] you deserve each other
thank you
yes maybe we do
chill chill guys chill I'm doing all the
time
um
so Michael
where's that straight there wow that's
so far too
chill guys
so Trevor said no to helping me
that's okay I don't need him
I'm gonna kill him after this I wonder
if Michael would help me they'll kill
Trevor I feel like Michael would Rachel
but why reasonable why
we don't know why you not save the game
why are you so stupid why you make this
mistake
ah
I know that from Pomo yeah yeah speaking
of formula so we're doing the collabo
actually we would have done it earlier
but
um as you may know she's on like a
vacation right now
so that's why we're doing it at that
time I honestly could not wait but it
gave me some time to prepare some things
yeah like I commissioned like a
and instrumental so that I can sing a
song that we don't have an instrumental
for
because we're gonna
I thought you were jealous maybe I
really was
yeah because we're gonna sing perhaps
in the collab it's gonna be on VR collab
it's gonna be streamed on both channels
I think that's the plan at least so you
have both povs and if I can I'm gonna
try to get some help from Amber because
um mostly we're just gonna do probably
like the selfie hand cam POV but at the
end I kind of want to have you know the
the camera system
from Ahmed if it works is it going to be
of a froggiana costume
um I was I don't know it's in the middle
of uh the Frog week so and it's VR so it
would work I guess but no I'm gonna use
one that matches
um whatever promo is using
only so maybe I'll also switch in
between because you can switch in
between right
don't have to be the same all the time
no the last thing I have so many now I
have so many outfits in VR now I have
Cali's outfit
I have
I have the school uniform I have small
Wawa I have small lava as vampire
so many I can't even recall all of them
do I even have my own outfit at this
point
did we have a for the low poly ones
do we ever get our own
Santa so yeah Santa Santa outfit
no right we only have like each other's
[Music]
outfit maybe I'll use the idol outfit
then
idle wow
that makes sense I think
um
I have to show myself from my most
beautiful side you know yeah
oh [\h__\h]
reap outfit Kiwa is so cute right I know
I like seeing myself in that outfit it's
really flattering isn't it cute
and hot oh what's going on there
oh
what's happening oh I don't care really
sorry I'm busy guys I have to meet
my soul mate
Michael
[Music]
on my way to kill my loved one can I
just stop in the distance and shoot him
from a distance
you're so Savage
where is he
it's probably not how it's gonna go down
right I wonder I wonder do I even have
to do anything
what
I won't let you treat me like it yeah I
did the side quest too
well chill guys
no I don't have a weapon I'm unarmed I'm
good
police is not for me right
oh
um
hi
I was just here to help I hate awkward
silences why was that written down there
how do I get my reward
just be cool just be cool pull out the
railgun no no no no
[Music]
what's going on
if I had my gun out would they have
attacked me
hi hi
I'm so confused
anyway anyway
he's still roasting him
that was not Michael though
what happened to anti-climatic
how is it gonna go down shoot him while
he's on the phone hey baby what's up
oh really
Tracy
College our trees
real college you gotta be kidding me
Franklin I know you got a heart
you're really gonna do this let me talk
to you a little later all right how yeah
I just got to wrap up some business here
all right bye
Amanda
says she wants to be bringing around the
house sometime for dinner
one of these nights huh
I don't know what I did to deserve this
[\h__\h] luck got my kids back my
wife
I made it we made it you and me bro
how can you kill him now
I like dog and you know this I risked
everything for your ass dog what is this
look man
you know this [\h__\h] ain't over dog we
both really the [\h__\h] is this
you
oh no oh no you came here to [\h__\h]
where's the popcorn you
[\h__\h]
did I have to do it because I have my
hands on cookies oh okay okay no cookies
for me I'm hungry but no cookies for me
after the stream I'm gonna eat the rest
of my bow buns need some yummy
interesting food last night at three a.m
or no no it was not perfect
one or so we really going on a train
track huh
he's not gonna crashed crashed crashed
and crashed by a train maybe so I don't
have to do it that would actually be
kind of a relief
oh there's a train
[Music]
I was hoping it would be in the other
side oh oh it's going there now okay
oh didn't even touch anything do I just
have to what
I couldn't kill him
I see Invincible right now because we
need to reach like a specific story
finale
what the [\h__\h] was that
[Music]
all right
can I fail though so why is he not
shooting me come on man
used to Running Man come out
now he's killing me
why can I take damage but he can't
you're like a son to me [\h__\h]
you bro or dad
I don't want to do this I'm just doing
this for the sake of completion you know
oh you like doing this man
What if I
[Laughter]
can't do damage on him anyway so
Michael man I gotta look out for
me
for you dude that is it for the final
shot though
Overkill what if
man this was a hard decision
you little [\h__\h]
I love it bro
you're going up there huh
you're going up there um who made what
we're there okay
ooh dramatic see you two guys who had
like a big connection we should take him
out a lot of things going on it reminds
me of the ending of the way out of my
home Franklin yeah with my wife and kids
yeah
painful ending
very painful oh oh okay oh
come on you prick I taught you
everything you know should have used the
minigun
I was here long before you and I'll be
here after your hands but we'll see
about that [\h__\h] I'll take you every time
[Music]
foreign
by the way I say this a lot I think some
people maybe don't understand it's a
reference to pekular assembly in
Minecraft saying before
any [\h__\h] damn you
[Music]
just keep telling yourself that
it ain't gonna make you feel any better
that's right that's true Columbus homie
people don't [\h__\h] change you did
you two big gangster going three bit now
you're gonna
Gap the only one who was ever decent to
you
no
I took you in
treated you like family
really does not deserve to be taken out
by Franklin
Mike
if anything it would have had to be
traveling
hey you told me when the time came what
okay I'm sorry yo hit my crack I should
have clipped you when you broke into my
house I knocked myself
[Music]
oh God you made the wrong call can I sit
it doesn't matter
I changed my mind Michael love you but
I'm probably gonna drop him by accident
why dude why Michael
you could have lived
[Music]
uh he was too mad he was too angry
he was
[Music]
maybe we can hang out or something
I know I've been kind of caught up in
[\h__\h] man but shipping real crazy homie
but it's dealt with now
[\h__\h] man you know how it is homie you
just start running and [\h__\h] and all of a
sudden your legs giving you just can't
run no more
anyway man
I think it's weird because it's not
really in character or Justified or
rational like
he doesn't really have anything against
him and I don't think it's in character
that he would go that far
it actually makes no sense
so I'm a character
Trevor like okay I want to ask one more
time if I if I did not switch to
Franklin or does it always have to be
Franklin could he not end the story
unless you're Franklin
because I have not gone for Trevor and
he gets the same options yourself
it has to be okay okay she seems he
seems to be like kind of the neutral
ground now he's the real protagonist
is this dmca
I'm just gonna turn it off because I'm
scared I mean but at this at this point
it's too late anyway
oh
[Music]
oh well
okay that was one ending we picked one
up didn't even feel like half an hour
but more like 10 minutes
do you do you say you do feel the same
shout me like an ass I know I'll never
be alive oh do you do you say happy
decency
I thought you loved me I trust you very
very much oh
do you do you really want to kill me oh
no
yeah the stream is unmonetized it's good
it's good should be fine yeah well okay
I think it's good that we chose this one
because that's the most underwhelming
ending
and hopefully the next endings are gonna
be more satisfying can I skip them oh
yeah okay
[Music]
from the office of Dr isia Freelander of
client notes highly confidential this is
about me
so needy and vain
is this is is this like customized likes
to think of self as straight shooter but
doesn't see other faults likes to think
of self as Big Cheese
Miser Miser what is that possibly
repressed
is this does it depend on how I play the
game
what is not
that's mean hey I I played the game
probably way less aggressive than a lot
of people out there
see yourself a savior of women aren't
given certain behaviors
I don't see myself as a savior of women
but yeah ignores people closest to her
I don't ignore them
very into random speculation
okay maybe that's true vindictive bully
no not true probably not a full-blown
club today yeah I'm not into stealing
[\h__\h] you'll get wow it's not working
very well huh yeah great though I don't
like yoga not really into physical
fitness okay yes yes yes now we're
getting there avoids new experiences
okay yeah yeah in terms of like food and
so on yeah I guess so yeah yeah I never
tried
um drinking properly never tried smoking
and [\h__\h] yeah okay distracted yes I'm so
distracted all the time I wish I was
less distracted
okay some of these are correct some of
them are obviously like make no sense in
reality
[Laughter]
oh can you not please
please it's gonna pop up all the time
I swear I'll count
oh is this like an after ending barn
dance is over I guess
how should I go to my safe or can I
continue from here is there anything I
want to see now in the post game
anything I should check out
go to save okay so is it like now it's
like free world you can do whatever you
want
is that how it is
we might want to make some calls yeah
no I'm curious what are you gonna say
Michael's still in here probably no
one's gonna pick up hang out oh yeah
Michael how you doing
For the Love of All That's holy okay
friends will not always be available
yeah I mean he's dead
Franklin
oh hang out oh he's busy too good Lord
above
good Lord
you're talking man
okay I don't have his family on the
phone
all right
unfortunate
yeah I kind of would have wanted to say
like
how his family copes afterwards oh Jimmy
was Jimmy an option
does he want to talk
well
this big J AKA J Dog AKA dangerous J and
I should probably say like uh Jimmy De
Santa in case is in relation to a
doctor's appointment or a reservation
it's physique
oh it says his voicemail ah Mr Franklin
go to Max houses Franklin
okay
see you next time all right bye oh
is he coping
am I having lots of women over
is that his his way of coping Michael's
dead for real this time I hope you talk
weren't involved I transferred his cut
open dropped his family his fell as the
right thing to do I thought he was gonna
say trans with the cut to me
[Laughter]
yeah all right let's let's try
I am kind of curious so oh his house was
was it here
I feel like it was there
wow oh trouble
no need trouble
no man he's not gonna admit it oh
foreign
we're gonna go to the house
oh is that the cut from the 200 million
right
oh so much money
maybe it's time for yeah I'm getting all
Landings I already say if we're doing
we're done we did this the first one I'm
gonna go to the second one in a minute
but oh so much money I should maybe
change careers become a criminal
so much money but for what yeah I mean
he already had enough money man it
wasn't necessary did what you had to do
I understand it so let's move on
business as usual we never mentioned
this again wow
why are you searching me now I didn't
give you any reason to trust me
just a moment ago you were still like oh
I hope you two didn't do it now you
already don't believe me oh
Gavin
Franklin homie what's happening man hey
you know you sound kind of patronizing
in borderline races when you speak to me
like that I grow up is it more
patronizing than telling you to ice your
favorite uncle yeah I don't think so
how'd it go he's dead it happened man so
y'all got to get the FIB off my case man
since I didn't smoke Trevor for him
already done homie haynes's boss has
been spoken to all right so now what you
got a job for me I had a job for you
slick and you just did it let me take a
look down a list of your uses and oh
yeah we're all out of them I do have
some advice for you though
in school it worked out so good
if you want to know what's Franklin up
to after Story play today online
ah
is that connected to what you did in the
main game
what
well I don't I don't know where his
house is [\h__\h] yeah
I thought I had it I thought it was so
it's somewhere here though
one looks like his house
it's in a corner more Wednesday oh
this one
maybe this one
corner and then yeah
could be here could be that one
yeah oh Jimmy
oh chill chill good children hello yo F
you see my dad we've seen him for a
while uh no do not have it man
because my mom is majorly freaking out
uh
well
you know didn't y'all see it coming I'm
sorry man
totally was me he got struck by
lightning or so
I know man
I wasn't there I I do totally not
remember what he wore the time when he
died
oh wait that was not it either
that was not it
ah
wait this maybe around 2 it's here
keep going forever I'm close
ah
oh it feels familiar it looks familiar
but oh
there's been me everybody
's battling me [\h__\h]
I'm right there oh my right oh
up there
Trevor says I do not believe him
hello just checking up you know I I
would love to help you but I guess since
there's no like letter here
I'm not getting anything out of going
here probably huh
anybody home see I can't even enter oh
no nothing
anybody home
all right I think
I think we're gonna go the next one next
ending
oh load game
show I guess let's go with number four
oh should I
save two dog
I don't need that safe
cute oh
very
[Music]
um
very weird ending not the best one for
sure
all right we're gonna choose
to kill Trevor next
which might just be my favorite option
but who knows
I will admit that throughout the game
maybe I have
um
I'm going to f right maybe I have found
a little bit more
not respect but
yeah I don't know what's the right word
I don't hate him as much anymore but
oh don't think he should be alive
[Laughter]
observes to sympathy yeah maybe a little
bit
yeah
but I think he's a danger to society
and a threat to the world and disgusting
and stinky and yeah
just you
he does not help the World by being
alive in any way he does not contribute
in any positive way
that still hates Rich
well you know
there's different levels of hatred and I
went from very very very very much hate
this person to very very very much hate
this person
Trevor's loyal well
just being loyal doesn't make you a good
person if you're loyal to the wrong
people and for the wrong causes
my God you guys
Fanboys and fangirls
nice nice Cardinal nice muscle car
right yeah
loyalty is a really really really nice
personality trait and feature
but only if you use it for the right
reason so for example if you're loyal to
me
and watch my streams until
they're not there anymore
that is a good use of your loyalty
if you're loyal to me by streaming do
you and all my other songs
that is also a good use of loyalty yeah
if you're loyal to
I know
like some really bad person doing bad
things
yes
yeah what's up let's go in and now we go
out again
wait for it
knock knock who's there oh they're not
knocking they're just ringing
hello
here we go again hey slick it's me
[\h__\h] are you wrong you got my money Punk
oh man I got some coconut water this
guy's so obnoxious but I love it
damn it's got a sake of Comedy thanks
for the memberships you got a death wish
or something am I supposed to kill you
man oh no okay
kill
yeah
[Music]
Franklin what's up [\h__\h] what's cracking
home what's cracking we need to talk but
somewhere quiet all right oh he says
basically the same thing whatever you
need
all right homie look I'll meet you there
all right
that was easy too
um but I don't think Trevor can get me
with any SOB stories oh will Michael
help or not Franklin what's up big homie
Mike man I need to have a conversation
with Trevor you know yeah
all right okay look man the FIB dudes
want them gone and Devin Weston want
y'all gone you know how it is doll
[\h__\h] somebody gotta go well ain't
[\h__\h] me exactly man look we mean that
a burrow Heights so you think you can
help me
I don't know that sounds like it's your
thing Frank I'll see what I can do oh
that sounds a little bit um hopeful
uh
yes because I have other saves I think I
can say yes no
no okay no okay
yes
okay
where am I going
did he tell me where to go
[Music]
question mark no
why are we going
am I still waiting
tea
I
think
oh why is it so small and unimportant
all right something to take care of
Brown teeth oh [\h__\h] that's why it's so
small and other important ah
okay ooh it's fire
Shawna
finally
It's the final countdown
[Music]
foreign
why do I see so many muscle cars today
everybody's driving a muscle car ever
since I talked about it
people are like
oh that's trendsetters
she knows a thing or two about cars
yeah yeah a thing or two or exactly two
things
and one one of them is muscle cars are
cool and the other one is vintage cars
are cool but for some reason everybody
is going for the muscle cars so let's go
with the muscle cars
such a trends at all
another one
ooh Casino
I've been to a casino twice in my life
one time it was for like a Christmas
party for uh at my like workplace we
went to a casino but like I did not go
into the casino they had like just
dinner
and then afterwards I went home while
the others went into the casino
didn't feel like it
just wanted to go home get away from a
stupid Christmas party
did get free food though
thank you
I always look forward to when working in
like a normal kind of job I always look
forward to like company dinners because
then you'll actually get some [\h__\h]
decent photo ones for free
[Music]
that's dumb luck right there
once oh my God I remember one company
party that we had at one point was like
themed um
I think it was
they were the 80s or was 70s or
something probably the 80s being back to
the 80s so
um
the employees were encouraged to come
dressed up in that style
yeah some of them put a lot of effort
into it
but then you know
you know those cringe moments when
some of the employees they they like
arrange some kind of performance or so
but
it's like oh you're like really grateful
for the fact that it's happening within
the walls were only other employees are
in
but I they I think they like performed
with like the separate
um
branches
like this department this department
they all prepared some kind of song
performance
I think
this one of them was decent because I
think one of them was they were playing
instruments and that was actually pretty
surprising to see that some of them
played instruments something I never
knew well a lot of the other ones were
a little bit cringe but cute you know
that cringe is cute because
all these employees they're trying so
hard to perform
they should have let me perform I know
how to put up a performance baby
I know how to do that
I know how to dance I know how to sing
leave it to me guys
oh you know what that's so embarrassing
so I'll leave it to you guys after all
and then I laugh about it but still cute
though corporate cringe hey man how you
doing not sex at all the way you hold
the gun behind yourself peachy
I know what this is about oh you do of
course do you do it you're The
Peacemaker well I ain't having it all
right I ain't having it
I mean maybe when the heat dies down
I mean that's it right huh wasn't it
wasn't it but Michael ain't the problem
it's so aggressive yes you are the
problem you scared the [\h__\h] out of me
sometimes you creep me the [\h__\h] out but
but the way I see it the way anyone
normal will see not that any of this
[\h__\h] is normal man you're gonna get us
all [\h__\h] killed gonna whack me
huh me
I ain't been nothing but straight and
true with you
sorry man you have been true but the
truth ain't what I'm interested in you
[\h__\h] did it let's go Chase Chase
you're striving nice and slowly for me I
feel like what if I stop no never mind
that's gonna stop let's take it
seriously man come on
oh
come on
wait for me we can talk about it let's
talk about it
talk about it can we just talk
[Music]
maybe for him we'll also get in the end
an option
save him but he still dies
well I'll I'll I'll come over to your
side in a second
where's the next
oh oh here
oh oh he went up there
[Music]
should have gone after him the first
time I'm losing him I'm like legit
losing him oh no oh no I can still catch
up
is she there okay okay
that was a close one
[Music]
I apologize
let's talk about it
I don't I don't know let's take out
Michael together yeah yeah totally
that's what we're gonna do
oh can I just stop his car or just do
his wheels also have plot armor oh so
you're gonna run from me yeah they're
definitely a plot armor yeah
well these cars yeah
am I chasing him until a specific spot
you just have to get close to him I
suppose I
yeah that looked really unreal
unrealistic dead driving skills yo
you're cheating bro and Nolan
cheating
you know honestly this Chase should be
in the helicopter Travis Style
he should be in a helicopter I should be
in a helicopter
or in an airplane oh Michael oh where
are you man I'm chasing teeth through
the oil field [\h__\h] okay I'm not far away
try and stop him
haha and let's go we both hate him just
like me for real for real man
oh
like father
I don't know like son like father
was not gonna help killing Michael but
Michael will help me kill Trevor that's
so sad man so sad
Michael are you good oh [\h__\h]
gas
fire in the gas white do it
[\h__\h] did he like drink some of that
fired up yeah we all do this
[Music]
that must hurt I feel sorry for him
he's got like no one no
he's just so
so
what's the word pathetic like sad
do it Franklin
okay
oh there's actually no choice to just
leave him
oh
ah
you always like gasoline
man that was your best [\h__\h] friend
yeah you called him oh
you called him
how do you feel Michael you mad the mad
bro tough guy
it's it's time you grow the [\h__\h] up
yeah I admit I'm a bad piece of work but
that guy that piece of [\h__\h]
No Boundaries no sensor when to back off
no nothing yeah 24 7 Insanity day in day
out yeah
never regretted nothing they cared for
nothing
[\h__\h] him
why are you telling him though to grow
up then there's got to be a limit kid
you know a point where even [\h__\h]
like us say enough is he [\h__\h] enough
that's what we just said we ended it
human stew
that's my limit is that what we're
eating tonight
I know that now Trevor still
but they still seem to be good with one
another these two
but they were gonna I thought Michael
was gonna be like I can't whip you
anymore I'm sorry I guess that's that
then
it is what it is it is what it is oh
[Music]
I like this ending sorry satisfying
the bother is out of the way it's
certainly been an education and they're
good
surviving is winning Franklin hell yeah
[\h__\h]
can top this whatever it takes kid
survive
I Will Survive
damn straight hell yeah
what's a different song
[Music]
uh the previous one I could skip point
on this one
all right I'm building this
go next go next one more and then we got
them all
the free endings
the free endings of power
one can we make like a
saying like for the Rings but for the
endings of GTA
one ending to
to do this and that
can come up with something poetic
[Laughter]
one ending to save them all one ending
to rule them all
oh okay skippity scoop
whoever in the ending tweet whoever
comes out with the best one as a reply
to my tweet will um
get a retweet
yeah good luck Is this different now
oh this looks different dull but at
least they have insurance
like standing others ignorance faults
himself
um prone to bathtubs just self self
justification
but prone to about yourself insecure
hoarder
I hoard cat hairs nothing else makes
weird judgment calls about morals ah has
some moral boundaries it seems just
nowhere near
complaints nobody cares then avoids
family like plague ah no no no
no Falls forget rich quick schemes and
other easy way outs
what the [\h__\h] possibly worse Psychopaths
roast me roast me you know I was
actually thinking would be funny to have
like a a roast for like whole life
members like everybody wrote someone
else but I'm I'm guessing some people
would take it too serious and be like oh
my God I'm so mean they hate each other
well I I think it could be fun
uh yeah everybody gets on the in the
spotlight Spotlight on the
the little table and it's like so you
suck because you are this nap
I can't even come up with anything now
because everybody's so lovely
uh what else
only Rob's of good reason or with some
reason
that sounds good Keen Yogi you have to
be kidding me not really into physical
fitness
that's right worse I've come across okay
some of them didn't change but most of
them changed interesting just by that
one ending it changed so much
I don't know
why should I come across
hmm amen baby
good morning sunshine oh
oh
where's your wife
interesting now we start from Michael
again
not Franklin oh
I don't really care about like going too
much into the aftermath of this Travis
fell in another group I don't know
what's going on and I don't want to I
have split his take from the last or
between YouTube
what up
this time it's going to us oh thank you
I see okay yeah I don't really I don't
really care
oh the Michael's house was Franklin oh
he's power in line Michael's paranoid
a lot of extra money
ah he has no family it could go to oh I
guess so
yeah call my clothes Frank as Franklin
okay
this is still the same
contacts Michael
do you wanna be my daddy
[Music]
I don't know if that will work he's busy
oh no
he's busy
[Music]
I don't want to drive all the way to
this place again we did that before
is there like and his places are now
like a mission no not even that
maybe he'll call you okay I'll just wait
a little bit Yeah because last time we
also got like a couple a couple calls
and [\h__\h]
just you know out of curiosity all these
endings are
all these endings are really fast Joe
Devin Weston came to talk to me he
wanted me to clap Michael and let Trevor
go then you
man ain't something you and Dave can do
because
people work he's this close to discharge
with no pension well [\h__\h] is there
something you can do sure I can talk to
Devin he's licking his wounds after
Meriwether lost their license to operate
in the state he might need a friend oh
yeah okay she I hear it can be real
useful having an FIB agent looking out
for you hey your chips are cash pal
don't contact me again
ah rude
you can play Michael hair with Trevor
and just forgive each other
ah but Trevor's dead
you mean in the last ending or
well Michael also gets some calls if I
stay on his side
after see
um
meltdown oh
that's his movie right
he didn't get the memo
that sub line subtitle
was
so deep it speaks so many
words so many letters so many meanings
wow oh the things we do for our health
drinking grass really
hmm
what you doing
hello my darling wife oh hello Michael
why'd you leave when I arrived
what are you up to
well there was another explosion just
now did you hear that is she going for a
swim
oh no
perhaps not is that our
I didn't realize we had asked to
attendance oh what I didn't realize that
what
hi Jimmy hello Uncle T dad I I just
heard he's he's he's not gonna bother us
anymore thank God we're safe Uncle T he
was a good guy no no no he was dangerous
Uncle T did you do it did you Dad Uncle
T wanted to kill all of us Jim he wasn't
well Uncle team man [\h__\h]
I'm Michael and the chat is Jimmy
I didn't even do it though why is my
wife going
I'm stalking her
I'm gonna try to call Lamar because
someone said to do that
[Music]
um
cookie yummy
[Music]
um
Lamar right
I'm always like
this he was just a dog as his pictures
on I never realized it's him
what up bro you busy you want to hang
out all right full for show yeah but I
got a lot of [\h__\h] going on right now so
I understand if you need to cancel you
know just hit me up on my way
but we'll just give us
any like specific dialogue though
is that my hands
print meeting place at the ammunition
no
let's go
[Music]
um
best and yeah I think it's good that we
split
um this into two parts I couldn't finish
it last time probably
but this way we have more than enough
time
[Music]
all right I feel like I have a couple of
cat hairs in my mouth now
[\h__\h]
okay I think we're good
um I'm gonna go to my house again right
every single time
should I maybe just saved at my house
before starting that mission but oh well
let's look at the last ending
who here in the chat actually finished
GTA
cool cool
GTA 5 I mean
I didn't hear me I did oh oh so many of
you
oh did you also do all endings or did
you only do one I did one ending which
one
if you did only one tell me which one
he has free air out whoa
all all just see only see
only seen
option A up to see oh oh one a what
that's the Michael option
I'll understand that one at all why why
would you do that
but okay I'm looking forward to some
friendship Titan
in this last c ending
it better be good also I start moving
again yeah
it better be good never liked him I I
understand that Michael definitely has
some unlikable traits as well
definitely like he's stupid as [\h__\h] of
course he is
but if I have to choose between him and
Trevor Oh by Miles by miles am I going
for Michael
as I said the only decent person in this
game is uh Franklin
which makes so much sense now that now
at the end he is the main protagonist
who who has all the strings and all the
pieces in his hand and he makes the
decisions here because [\h__\h] everyone
else finally Franklin
is the one to pull the trigger
that's literally just figuratively
I think
did I say it right because he's he's him
I mean he makes a decision
I guess he also does pretty cool I guess
it's both
you won't you got my money Punk
that's some coconut oil skippity scoop
Death Wish see if I played this game on
my own without you guys I feel like
there's options C just by the title and
the icon would intimidate me
and I would probably
oh wait a was Trevor never mind someone
I thought that was Michael so I take
back what I said before but I would
probably if I played it privately just
go for Trevor because I feel like death
wish
it sounds so intimidating
as if
this is an ending where everyone dies
like it's a really bad option to choose
this one
frankly Master dog man we need to talk I
got a problem I need your help with Man
actually [\h__\h] it man we all got a
problem you can help us with calm down
all right come to my house
real evil who's been trying to control
us
and make our decisions
by himself
[\h__\h] bastard
all right
oh this car is kind of broken let's take
the other one
the real ending
oh you can do it
okay wait it doesn't show me where to go
so I have to figure it out myself all
right is it l no it's still not L is it
it's this l
it is Alpha Lester but not that one else
the other L okay
what [\h__\h]
okay another drive this might just be
our last Drive although maybe there's
another Chase
wait this is
our last Drive where we're just hanging
and chilling guys oh man I had some good
talks with you guys and uh driving
around was fun I'm glad I didn't take
the [\h__\h] taxi all the time [\h__\h] Tank
season this game
no I'm glad you all really enjoyed my
GTA play for so much you know I'm really
happy to see all the positive feedback I
mean
thank you guys for being part of this
as I said before I really did not
think about
um like finishing this when I started
out it all for me this was just like a
oh let's just get into it like once or
twice and [\h__\h] around
kind of game but yeah
you guys enjoyed it so I have and I
enjoyed it too so
yeah yeah and my mom enjoyed it too my
mom was been watching every episode
every single one and she says this is
like
one of her favorite or her favorites
games that I've played like in terms of
how I played it
oh oh and she did say Trevor is her
favorite but I think I told you that
before
ah
I'm gonna give Mommy a phone call gonna
say Mommy
and I'm gonna oh I would love to see her
not physical psychological report in
this game
see what Dr Friedland says about my
mommy after being on Trevor's side
unbelievable
no no Mommy
if I asked Mommy instead of Michael to
kill Trevor together with me
she would probably turn me down to she'd
be like my sweet sweet daughter you're
on your own
you you might be sharing blood with me
but
he will not accept this no no this is
your thing
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] as she likes to say just like
me
just like me for real for real but also
just not like me for real for real in so
many ways
oh GTA online that's not possible
because simply because you know we need
a like a PS4 or five right
because we can't play it on PC I've
heard that even on PC there's like a
[\h__\h] ton of like hacking going on
hmm
it was not good for
actually seriously playing together
what's the Panic bro what the [\h__\h] do
you think I heard even in problem is
it's a problem that will [\h__\h] things up
the worst anyway my mind is just racing
but you know I don't want to say
something that's really exciting and
then you have to act all deflated and
say no no it's just that somebody got
the same tattoo I got so why don't you
just go ahead and tell me some
[\h__\h] wants me to kill Michael
some other [\h__\h] wants me to kill
Trevor I feel I can't kill both of them
I don't know what the [\h__\h] to do right
now
hey
I can see that who are the [\h__\h]
who are the [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
from the FIB
um Devin Weston man you know the um that
angry Rich [\h__\h] from whatever holy
hibernates in exactly all right all
right I say
kill Michael
didn't kill Corona you little shits yeah
are you for real what did you say you're
[\h__\h] you know I I don't know
know everything dawg I know okay I'm
sorry I guess this is it you know I'm
doing my best man I don't know how you
can deal with both of them
just don't I know man deal with the evil
people behind it we're [\h__\h] every
single one of us is [\h__\h]
unless yes
okay yes Steve Haynes is under a lot of
heat because of the shootings at court
Center and Devin Weston's a known to be
a major [\h__\h] B known to be friendly
with Don Percival who runs Merriweather
I think actually Weston owns
piece of Meriwether look
right 11 pretty good for pseudo-liberal
owning a private Army so they would both
love to be involved in capturing the
bullion that we just lifted
that you boys are at The Foundry and
Marietta Heights melting it down maybe
maybe both of them will pay you a visit
and Bam we turn it into a bust yes I
ain't got no better ideas all right I'm
gonna get in touch with Michael and
Trevor
go to The Foundry get yourself set up
all right
the only reasonable
option yes hi Lamar
just saying goodbye man things are kind
of [\h__\h] up right now dog it's all good
[\h__\h] we better have in a [\h__\h] up
situation in the [\h__\h] up fool like me
man that's what the [\h__\h] I wanted to
hear hey look I'm coming to your crib to
get your ass I'm here
I thought it was gonna mean
fun with just the three of us
but it's gonna be four four we're
Blaster two everybody's involved it's
like a a goodbye sayonara party
you know
the king all together
I think this will be our last bonding
moment
and then no one will be
you know plotting against each other or
so anymore
no more of that
just live peacefully and enjoy life with
the 200 [\h__\h] million US dollars that
we got
even more than that when you have 200
million right like what what the [\h__\h]
else do you want
money can't buy you happiness
I can't buy you okay some pieces of
Happiness some pieces that help you get
happiness but you don't need any more
than that for real there he is
get in
where are we going we uh heading to The
Foundry place
yeah I don't think that the saying of
money can't buy you happiness is
definitely kind of [\h__\h] because if
you [\h__\h] broke as [\h__\h] hey look hear
me out man and like die you can back out
no drum hit me with it man we got a real
problem can't afford a place or so can't
afford food or whatever obviously we're
trying to save money for your homies
four tanks hell yeah I'm in
who want to clap your homies who don't
[\h__\h] these Chinese dudes some FIB cats
the rich white [\h__\h] who scams us on
the car Devin Western [\h__\h] why didn't
you say we was creeping on it we ain't
creeping on him [\h__\h] at least I don't
think he gonna be there we gotta take
all the heat he can throw at us before
we worry about how we coming back on his
ass
but you is coming back right oh hell
yeah we creeping on that fool
respectively we creeping on that fool oh
so you ain't the Mercurial [\h__\h]
you fronting ass huh man I'm just trying
to make something by myself dog that
will change who my homies are [\h__\h] it
don't change my family [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you
getting me all emotional now [\h__\h] might
have to stop me from sucking your dick
[\h__\h] please [\h__\h] [\h__\h] off
[Music]
somebody who want to clap yeah but that
applies to some fools more than others I
heard that [\h__\h] I'm talking about you
everybody in this town wanna take a pop
at your ass it's lining up camping this
[\h__\h] trying to take a shot at the big
shape ain't that the truth
nobody pissed off as many [\h__\h]
as Michael and Trevor dog [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you
play Big you stand and lose yeah ain't
that the truth
okay what I was gonna say is I guess
it's just a Coke
if you're trying to tell yourself you
don't need money to be happy
uh
but at least there's other things to
replace that at least maybe
money is definitely an option
look me Michael and Trevor they should
be inside can you stay out here and let
us know when the Bad Dudes is coming I
got it man I'll holler at you
Carla cause I ain't no hollaback girl
yeah ain't no hollaback girl
[Music]
all about girls
should I take out my gun already do I
have my minigun yeah
yeah I wonder if they have plot armor
too though
nope not oh oh I see someone up there
is that Trevor it looks like Trevor
oh it's him
I totally did not try to shoot him just
now no no no no
not at all
I did not try to lift Mouse click and it
didn't work unfortunately no
it makes me think this is a setup it is
something here
let me clear the situation
need to put it down it's making me
nervous guys
you're not saving me you're saving him
oh you're saving this God [\h__\h] I mean
y'all gotta keep y'all [\h__\h] heads
right and in this [\h__\h] if not man I'll
put bullets in both you [\h__\h]
hey they're here
huh
stop this [\h__\h] come on
we're a team [\h__\h] it
what
did you pull
like
whatever you want me yeah full of muscle
all right man
okay okay all right where you want me
you hold your position right there okay
I'm gonna go over there
it was about to
oh who's building watch your stickers
[Music]
can I can I uh but minigun will be
difficult to use though I suppose
all right
[Music]
stay up here forever
where's the party I'm right here
it all comes tumbling down
let me switch oh
let's go what was that I kind of
I'm putting him oh wait what am I using
what is that heavy sniper oh
not necessary
that music nice music
oh I don't see it more on the way
[Music]
you know what you're dying for
huh
let's finish this
okay okay okay we gotta help our man our
boy
he's the one he's the chosen one
I don't see
there's something there oh now he's
living he's on the move
don't let them clap you homie
what are you talking about
there's stuff in here not meal go to
Lamar hey
oh wait wait wait how where do I go down
uh
where's where's the exit
Twitter
I think that's the right way
go go go
go I'm here I'm here
hey LG just hold on man
[\h__\h] homie I'm trying to get to you
there you go it wouldn't be right if I
didn't have to save your ass
just one save me
[Music]
yeah I know I can't use it in clever I
know
back off my [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
what I say a [\h__\h] up homie for a
[\h__\h] up situation right on two counts
dog
why aren't you inside with the rest of
them
[Laughter]
and he ain't responding man I gotta stay
out here with Lamar hide a little bit
I went to Reckless
that was fun though okay I'll try and
find him
you want more
can you stop being an [\h__\h] please
[Music]
what what am I going somewhere
did you just tell me there's some
serious stop being a prick I go to him
[Music]
come in here
say something Trevor
you just said something
where was that uh
that y'all buy [\h__\h] that I had the rails
go off the ladder what's the problem tea
oh there you are you oh yeah
I took a knock I was sitting out a few
rounds I'm not good here if I was going
outside
but no you care yeah well don't do it
again
watch out another FIB team on the way
over here
if not now right
and it don't stop coming and I don't
stop coming and it don't stop coming and
doing stuff coming now
[Music]
you coming or what
are we clear yeah
here
I follow Trevor oh we have to Forever
all right
I don't know where to go though he knows
where to go I don't know where to go
outside I didn't see an exit there
should I just go outside with Franklin
is I know that way
I'm gonna go there
oh
anyway I will start laughing what the
[\h__\h] is going on out here
[Music]
good timing wait but I stopped moving
let me fix that really quick
[Music]
is that what is that
hey we'll get through this
[Applause]
let's wait until we have bigger targets
where do you need help I'm helping
well you shouldn't have come here
I'm putting him down
[Music]
taking him out
oh
what more
only five shots left man
okay
all music is over
looks like we did it now exactly for now
so what's next huh I'm just gonna wait
around until someone else comes to kill
us or are we gonna wait till this [\h__\h]
gets turned again fighting ain't anybody
getting turned again you know it
you got a lot of old friends I think
need to be re-educated a lot of friends
I mean things could get really messy no
we just gotta silence
let me see there's uh he's like
constantly on something we need him
alive why
so nobody [\h__\h] with us afterwards what
about that try [\h__\h] now where's
my mom thank you two boys it's dating
[\h__\h] you know he bound to come back yep
there's that well who's the uh the guy
who set up Lamar
stretch you want to throw him in should
Trevor throw anyone in just to satisfy
his bloodlust whoa hey it's called a
[\h__\h] Lucinda right now if we're gonna
be man of peace and Tranquility we tie
up Loose Ends
stretch has been a liability but then
we're gonna have to take care of our old
Pals Devin Weston and Steve Haynes [\h__\h]
what a mess man well let's get it
cleaned up how about you get Lester on
the line
Moshi Mossy
watch this
stuff hey it's me dog
no no but look I got you on speakerphone
I'm here and
on the ground Wheels
no we got some work to do can you get us
some whereabouts
I'll do Steve Haynes to start and Devin
Weston's ass and uh waiting
w-e-i-c-h-e-n-g waitang waitang exactly
stretch
yeah man look his real name is Harold
Joseph I don't remember who that is
tell you that agent Haynes is taping his
show over on Del pero Pierre she en
permit came up
I want to dice that [\h__\h]
oh I got him I got
her known associates
[Music]
okay I'll go ask his ass about his punk
ass when I find Mr Weston
oh this ending seems to be longer than
the other ones definitely
get rid of Mr chain
more of a pleasure than that
all right let's do this [\h__\h] one shot no
problem as long as I can use my minigun
because that's 100 shots
big brain outsmarted yeah game
get 100 shots for one
what a deal
special Michael first
why
did
all the same what should I stay if you
want me to save
I can't say now you want me to
uh he wants to take a stretch oh
what do you mean I want to save off this
is my last my last ending anyway why
does it matter
oh where are we
I'm more railing on ammo oh
[\h__\h]
now we're fine
don't need it my minigun is giving me
enough pleasure
oh there
easy
and then I have to escape oh uh what's
what's the challenge here
what is the challenge
where is the challenge
where's the last one ah I'm clear
he ain't a problem no more friends
ah sorry did I interrupt no
welcome
list okay should I give Trevor one of
those guns would be really helpful I
think
yeah I think I will because he's the
only one who doesn't have that uh where
are we all right they're so close to the
Target but
I'm gonna go back
you just need the sniper
well he has a sniper okay am I not
taking out like a million people
you know what would be stylish if I
could get up on the on the big big wheel
over there and then shoot them from up
there that would be so
[Music]
one snipe is not one sniper's shot is
enough okay
I'll just say I'll go here
oh that's are you still there
[Music]
Saints
city of Sinners and nothing in between
but the FIB
cut
this is crap
you got this framed right yeah you're
looking great is it chin how's the chin
look like a scumbag all right the
audio's clean nice so we'll say
something we'll cut that off yeah don't
worry about your chin yeah it's great
okay fine we're on I'm ready you ready
it's gonna be blasted all right let's do
this so let's go
I'm gonna observe that
is Los Santos a city of Celluloid a city
of scumbags the last great um
okay don't get too close they say but
yeah
oh but will people panic if I pull out
the gun
what do I care right or should I not be
seen
he's been gonna be difficult to see from
here
find a good angle far away
yeah that's what I want to do
don't get too close okay
and why did I go to this place I don't I
don't like this this position but let me
see what I can do over here
throw in a senior FIB agent and you've
got a unique look at what happens when
dreams and we
I want to listen to
listen to All of thinking
uh how do I know which one to see him
well we got uh 10 shots
oh don't worry about this
it won't read okay RPG
it's Trevor style maybe this one that
could be the one there's two people in
there oh that one no that must be it you
look like he's talking to someone
how long does it take to reach though
oh lose the cups
all right
[Music]
how good of an idea is this
will they find me if I'm done
you find me down here
I'll go in the water
how would they know
how do I die
all right
you could do that it seems so
it's the most obvious thing to do now
okay
yet
whatever I'll go up there and get them
easy easy
it's good that we used the RPG and not
the sniper because that was just
Trevor's style you know
thank you
the last important shot
he does his own way
write that Redemption
um maybe I'll look into it I know people
recommended it to me because it's
similar and it's with horses
but I I would already dread the oh did
they just hey the old man's here
where's my didn't I have um
I follow
where's my where's my big boom machine
oh well
are we done no
one more live where
[Music]
Escape time
where do I go
maybe that was a good way to hide over
there as well
maybe yeah
but it's just one star
up the mountains
[Music]
welcome back
blind style for killing like 20 people
right
oh are they coming up here
it might be
keep on moving hey I got all clean you
dudes ain't gonna have no more trash
coming out
unbelievable
is this the last one or the second to
last one
I'm going to his house that's so
Direct
are we sure about this
that's the last one oh
[Music]
I wonder how they think they'll get away
with this though because they all have
connections with these people right so
won't people be like
[Music]
sus well no one care about this and try
to investigate it
marry with a card hey unless you got
news from The Foundry team I don't want
to be disturbed
well that's what Dave is for oh
kidnap him
hey
how
do you want me to do that do I kill his
guards
oh
yeah kidnap not cute
Chris I have to kidnap if only it was so
easy
what was that what was the sneaky button
again
[Music]
what's the sneaky button
so do I need a
I got like
no like
suppressors and [\h__\h] I only have to
snipe them
wait does this one have a silencer
though
that was kind of loud man oh
gladly it's my pleasure
my pleasure
I'm getting kind of bored of killing you
pricks
[Music]
hi y'all where is everybody
no one's there oh
how much is [\h__\h] paying you I hope it
was worth it we'll go inside then
thank you
what does a guy like me and have your
outfit back in town
[Music]
huh
let's earn our paychecks protect DW
Aria
love still the left side okay okay
thank you
don't you feel sorry for me my heart
can't take it I'm here for you
one last
little bit of fun
come out
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] can I like you bleed like humans
but I know you're reptile
[Music]
I'm the definition of SP I'm the most
suspicious person you'll meet
why are you gonna be like that well it's
gonna be so difficult
combat situation [\h__\h]
easy okay we took them all down
all right I mean let's threaten him with
my carbine rifle and then
we good are you at
oh nice pool
damn the layout here is stick
is he chilling
all right I don't see him
I see hiding here
he's in there
wait wait
no more talking no no no no no no no
getting there
we should dress him up in a cute dress
oh
[Music]
go to the Rendezvous Point
around the boom oh what's that
I want to listen to that
I'll sing in for you I got Mr Weston
let's take him out of the city make him
disappear meet me on the cliff off the
Goa Mountain State wilderness
down
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
sorry man don't don't drive towards me I
can't go past you okay
moves like y'all go got the moves like
yeah
[Music]
moves like Yahoo no I think I moved
better than Yago come on you gotta give
me that much credit oh good morning
sunshine which would you like for
breakfast the other people that we took
down maybe
some scrambled eggs I wouldn't kill you
I didn't say anything about cutting your
tongue out
maybe we should
have you ever seen Malcolm move it well
yeah I like like normal like he wasn't
trying to dance I guess but I'm sure I
can dance better than him
I need someone like you in my
organization the CEO positions gonna be
vacant real soon slick I've got enough
energy
are looking at it rationally there are
people who are useful to you and people
who ain't and the people who wait gotta
go me I'm not rational I don't care if
you're useful or not I feel like taking
you out Devo that's what I am
serious offer we're on the same you'll
have everything once all I've ever
wanted is to watch you drift in and out
of Consciousness as you're slowly
disemboweled oh brutal but okay
understandable what kind of creativity
let me out of here look I got my own
company Trevor Phillips Industries
company
give you money to grow oh it's you heard
but I'm kind of gold Rich right now so
you got precisely nothing to offer
prepare for the end my friend
I Go Glow
well you're definitely not winning now
you can't do this to me that car looks
good this is why people want to kill you
you won't shut up
we're Trevor you're not one to speak you
don't shut up Beaver Trevor
all the time
so [\h__\h] annoying all of you also I
just noticed still
moneyed
sign back there
crash more all right
and I thought you was gonna say
something funny
okay
well you love Trevor don't lie no I
really don't
I mean right now he's quite funny to me
because he's doing the right thing for
once
more or less
but no I really don't
you're a dead man let me take your phony
prick
and we wrote take me home to the Grave
where he belongs
in love all those bastards I finally
dead now
take me home
to my homies
um sorry
take the money make me a job
pipe down
[Music]
and all the others whose name I
forgotten
because they're all irrelevant
they must suffer for the sake of us
cause we're [\h__\h] crazy wait let's
take the bus Country Roads
my friends won't be happy if I empty a
clip into the trunk no we're not taking
a bus never mind oh that's a cute Island
of course it's not kiwis
so many animals
it's a good song to improv to because
it's pretty slow if it's a faster song I
can't keep up with making up lines
with a few minutes for some one-on-one
time
oh nice Showdown area
yes
get into a shark have the shark eat them
do it
oh I was I guess picking up something
else on the Kiwi oh
around a little at Sunset romantic
never better amigo
I like this music
I'll be here
you just stop smoking
yeah I'm gonna kill yourself
stop smoking all right what's up
[Music]
ain't that a [\h__\h]
but we'll not talk about that I know
intelligent businessman like you but the
way I see it there's two great evils
there but devil American capitalism the
type that you practice
is outsourcing you paid a private
company to Do Your Dirty Work
company because you thought you were big
enough and bad enough that you didn't
have to play by the rules oh number two
offshoring your profits offshore oh it's
horrible you wouldn't want to be sent
offshore just to save a little money
would you T no I I wouldn't oh no
nowhere no see but we know your opinions
on the matter Devin keep your problems
the [\h__\h] out of America huh in this
instance when he puts it like that it
makes sense
even goodbye my old friend thanks for
all the advice
or so
it is boring
Wow
Let's go I guess
is she really dead because of that
oh okay never mind
that did the trick I think so now what
and how to keep a low profile and get on
with our lives as friends
do I have a choice no no
all right then oh as uh I mean awful I
prefer totally uncomfortable and poorly
matched friends I prefer if we don't
have to kill anyone perfect then we can
get back D3 capitalism we practice [\h__\h]
I don't know how much more better that
is than Devon's con ooh hypocrisy
Franklin
civilization's greatest virtue Jesus
your therapist has a lot to answer for I
know I still hate myself but hey at
least I know the words for it now yeah
but I hate you and I know the words for
it so does that mean I don't have to go
to therapy look man you too
[\h__\h] terrified me of that
middle age I'm good you're right to be
afraid Franklin yeah be very afraid
because this is how I'll be one day like
these two
if I'm older this is how we're all gonna
turn out they want the tea
no
I'm getting too old for this nonsense
[Music]
oh traffic didn't get a ride
oopsie
all right I'm just gonna end up drink
somewhere
[Music]
obviously that's like the best option to
have the free all of them still alive
you guys made me finger that was not an
option
I thought I have to
say goodbye to someone I thought it was
like a a way out kind of situation
but this is very satisfying
that's really satisfying as it makes
everything much better
yeah I wasn't even looking forward to it
that much when I thought that we have to
kill someone
This way everything is good everything's
okay
hmm
yeah we did all of them no and I think
that's good we saw all the options
in the original game there was only two
options what what's the original game
you mean on PlayStation or so is this a
I guess this is a port
wait
original have free okay that was
[\h__\h] that's not true okay why the
[\h__\h] you
booked why the [\h__\h] you lying why the
[\h__\h] you lying
why are you always lying
is he saying it's a setup it's a setup
it's a setup
it's set up it's just it was not a setup
why is he saying that
oh it's a setup it's a setup it's a
setup what
not a setup for us at least I set up for
or the enemies baby
is that what's going on in Trevor's mind
he's being really paranoid that was what
he was thinking when
he was there with Michael and Franklin
jumped in he was like it's just set up
it's a setup it's a setup [\h__\h]
Michael it's a setup it's a setup hahaha
so Trevor's singing this
oh Trevor got a good voice maybe you
should become a pop star
groupie
oh maybe he's actually saying eat some
salad eat some salad eat some salad eat
some salad eat some salad
yeah it sounds sounds realistic eat some
salad eat some salad eat some salad
sounds perfect oh no not the salad I
love salad
eat some salad salad eat some salad eat
some salad
I'm getting dmca for this anyways
DJ DJ DJ
can I stop it now okay
so
what happens next oh
koala is terrifying deluded lonely
desperate and vain
sees both sides of the argument and
can't make their mind up
that's not bad not necessarily at times
can really Embrace his hypocrisy oh the
the doctor friedlander can embrace my
hypocrisy well very nice very nice very
cost conscious oh
know it's true super silliest which is
ironic I don't know what that means so
you're not insulting me with that avoid
certain steaming behaviors unfortunate
on all of them it just sounds better
than the other endings
complain somebody cares and avoids
family like playing wisely invests money
in insane speculations
prone to random and futile outbursts of
violence
that's not true
true because whatever happens in the
usual room
happens through the usual room not for
my hands
only wraps with good reason or for some
reason devoted Yogi bizarre avoids
strenuous exercise doesn't mix well with
others as if that were a surprise
hey lazy in some ways I'm lazy and
always I'll admit that there's a lot of
help as do I
[Music]
stay true to yourself
Mr freightlander
I like you I wish I could have gotten
more therapy from you
all right how we doing all the money
what are we doing huh
want to see some after Story aftermath
save
oh can I oh
there's a teddy bear
on the front of his car
see that
you have a house
wait is it that one right there
is that my house that's not my house
oh no I thought it's my house
yeah I'm on the second floor right
my body is pretty much uh wrong place
almost almost so close
never mind
ah
wait don't just try to have two places
oh
awesome well for yourself yes
what are you doing here oh is that how
you greet your mother mother and father
it was Patricia I didn't know they let
you out so you never wrote To Me you
never visited well I
I bet you never found a girl he didn't
tell me
are you gay no is that what this is all
about oh
in fact
I've always wanted a gay son maybe he is
a son who wouldn't forget about his
mother but more but no but not about
mine
not a tape I carried you in here
I fed you I weaned you now look at you
you always were an ungrateful wretched
yes
you know it and I know it destroy him
there's always something wrong with you
ashamed of yourself ashamed of me of
your own mother
I've been here for hours and have you
gotten me a drink or a cigarette
or massage my feet
I'm an old woman oh [\h__\h] he's being
dominated the prime of life
have you nothing inside
I'm so sorry he's broken she broke him
so easily
there there it's okay son
wow impressive I want to learn from her
oh
exactly for everything
I'm an old woman Trevor I don't got the
Cockroaches I got money I don't want
your Goddamn money is that what you
think I am a prostitute still
you're sick what should I do
I'm in a lot of pain
I need you to get me some more delude
them all what's that I can do that a lot
of them a truckload literally and not
those weedy little ones the thousand
milligram ones and if you find me a
gentleman well we both know you need a
father figure
nothing
and this is another proper Mission I
don't want to do anything anymore
find a van
oh wait I think I know which band I mean
I've seen them around here yeah yeah
aren't there like a couple of those Here
No Maybe not maybe I'm mixing it up or
something
I don't have to
how many missions are there afterwards
oh they I wrote those Brad emails all of
them your secret to save with me now
calm the [\h__\h] down and stop being a
crazy freak and people won't try and
have you busted or so maybe
thanks Norton
I've never even finished it okay can I
can I just say I'm not doing that thank
you yo if I don't have to
I'm not doing it now I want to end it I
just want to listen to everybody like
you know
see what's up what's up Michael
apparently you're the fake protagonist
I'm disappointed Hey listen I believe
the new I gotta run now okay all right
bye babe
you're happy
we never played tennis hey
let's play tennis
give me a tennis match come on
let's go over how you swing a racket is
it better with a controller I wonder
anything to aim your shots
oh dear
oh [\h__\h] what
that game
go hey remember what Freelander said
about not taking it too seriously
sorry Michael it's a long time since
I've taken you seriously
all right all right all right
hey
I'm Liverpool
serve me [\h__\h]
do it
do it try me
oh wait I'm the one serving
I don't understand tennis
I don't understand it
[Music]
hey
that worry for your help
take this
small wobble when you serve unbelievable
I want a divorce
clay
tennis is not for me
change yeah that will change everything
and there's no serving
I like the squeaky shoes it's nice
tennis ASMR
oh my thumbs changing everything
got that's everything I wanted we got
one point
I'm impressed just by that where are you
going
[Laughter]
on just having a mental breakdown
because I said I want a divorce
mental gymnastics is what we're doing
here
you have to know your opponent
you have to know how you can manipulate
them
come on come on
Bring It On
show me what you got go
oh come so far
oh you're letting me win are you letting
me win so then I'll forgive you
coronary what does that mean I'm in his
own game point is she winning is that
what you're trying to say [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
at least I didn't make those stupid
mistakes she did
that wow
[Laughter]
it's not over yet boy
ah
that was legit for a fat old that was
legit
that's a four oh dear that's really long
wait
this is fun maybe I should play tennis
in real life imagine chihuahua in such a
cute tennis outfit huh
imagine
what
spicy I hope you're ready
quit let me let me out of here let me
out of there
hey you play it was fun though not even
that difficult with mouse and keyboard
not so bad
well Amanda
don't ever bring that up again
oh what's going on
crack crack
I want to trigger something I want to
trigger some dialogue or so
some some special after math dialogue
I'll try there
it wait
oh please for the love of all of this
holy stay out of trouble
of course I'm just gonna make movies you
know me I'm good oh is my car still
there by the way my dream car
why not I ever leave it somewhere else
my friends we haven't met but both of
you and your buddies have caused me huge
problems I can't see us establishing
much of a friendship but I will say this
who saved me a fortune
okay there seems to be still like stuff
to do after you clear the game but hmm
I think this will be it for me
I'm a garage oh yeah right
but I can't open my [\h__\h] phone I
don't know why on it
I'm pressing okay finally why does it
not work before
you saved me a fortune as I got to buy
back poor old Devon steak at a hugely
reduce cost due to Temporary collapse in
our share price you will make me a lot
of money you for that I thank you for
not having to deal with Devin anymore I
thank you do not [\h__\h] with me again I
hope that is clear no reply necessary
foreign
all right we will try to call who did
you say I should call Franklin
I don't want to talk to Franklin I'm
gonna you I can only hang out with him
that's like not really what we want to
do right
because that will just be like
uh
therapist
okay
this is Dr Isaiah freedom
[Music]
for me
you need to be flexible for me someone
like me
what you doing Franklin
am I you finally learned something
you're almost ready to start acting like
a [\h__\h] man
he's more of a man than all of you put
together
I think that's it I can do side missions
yeah but no I think it's a good place to
end it unless you know
anything super special that I should
know about
oh
Mike
I mean another kid nearly sent me insane
but we did it I hope you I hope you
learned something from hanging with me
and the maniac even if it was how not to
grow old you're my
favorite you're mine
yeah my friend for life I hope you know
that
oh so sweet like for Life what a journey
thank you for looking out for me your
boyfriend
oh
almost brings a tear to my eye
Oh Daddy
okay Mike what was named Michael
Michael love you
hey Mike it's me what you doing you want
to hang out uh yeah cool cool I'll come
pick you up
don't trust him you're a contrarian
because that's what you called that
because at this point obviously
he's not trying to hurt Franklin or
anything he loves him
whichever two can I hang out with all of
them
oh do I need my car
you I will never see Michael again well
who knows can you see him in uh
uh in GTA online
why am I running back up the mountain
pick them up on your bike yeah
yeah maybe
no not for now oh
I can just look at pictures of us
pictures of you pictures of me
[Music]
but yeah so can I also invite
what's his name again
do I not have his number
oh there it is
me listen I'm about to meet Michael you
want to join us yes yes for sure pal
absolutely yeah I'll be there soon
let's go absolutely like with the team
Capital like let's [\h__\h] go
I totally needed that right now where
where am I meeting them
yeah
are they gonna both be there or am I
playing taxi wait up turn around oh no I
don't think they're both there I see
another
another one of those icons on the map
okay
I choose where we go
well
where should we go
before we went to the movies and uh
kind of failed
because I accidentally skipped it even
though there was not my intention
I'm gonna try to oh can we watch
meltdown
is that an option
now that it's out
maybe this is Destiny
well all the way out there where his
home is
no [\h__\h] way can we not just meet at a
specific location
good to see you man
no I'm gonna put Trevor in the back seat
he doesn't deserve a front seat
I'll tell you what if we got through it
it was close we're talking we made it
the show I mean [\h__\h] we were real lucky
there
continue talking in a second I need to
get it here
we should have never managed that that
was crazy I mean even by my stand that
was easy though Crazy by Mom
yeah
you know Justice
just deserves to be served
on the big
fancy platter with some parsley on top
yeah yeah partially important
I just did that
just did what I had to do
more parsley
calm it down honestly [\h__\h] cooking
simulator I cook something much better
and much easier
last night after that
I'm never gonna get a game like that
make fun of me make a fool of me
undermine my abilities and disrespect me
as a person
I'm a busy man my time is valuable and
you're this late
ladies let's go get our nails done
should we
what's happening with my car why is it
so weird
okay we did it damn straight yes quite a
journey we robbed the feds we tricked
the IAA we boosted a huge pile of gold
and we defeated a private Army in its
billionaire investor that's the way you
retire but most importantly Frank is
that we learn to not be snakes yes after
being some snakes yeah yeah A and B
Because if you learn too much from
Michael and not enough from Trevor and
you're doomed for you know it you'll be
faking death stabbing backs and taking
plea Bargains yeah as opposed to eating
joggers smoking meth and molesting
Sailors
it's not molesting if they're lonely
it's patriotism you're not even American
I am [\h__\h] you yeah whatever you say hey
all right we're gonna watch a movie
where is the movie theater we're going
to watch the one and only well I don't
see it
oh
I can only go to the places that are
orange you know
it's close what
no I want an uncle here
let's go for some drinks then I feel
like at least with the go get drinks
we're gonna have more of a conversation
I wonder if the game made like scripted
conversations specifically for when
you're uh when you already finish the
story or if it's
always kind of the same
Tremor doesn't like movies is that why
let's go have some drinks
what a pink
you ssy
oh [\h__\h] little miscalculation there
happy hour at what
clinical those
oh wow you don't see them inside yeah
[Music]
you both hate me you both do I see it
now you pair of this is how it feels to
be drunk thanks you both Hate Old
Trafford Trevy Trav trap kind old track
have
Trevor
ation
[Music]
man that ain't true now who we will love
you too
you hate me you both hate me
both jealous of me you hate me because
I'm real
yeah they hate me because I'm smart
around either way shut the [\h__\h] up
[Music]
and then I thought we would have you
know like in Yakuza Yakuza when we were
in the bar
and they would talk
you know with a really chill atmosphere
I'm gonna show you my Pro driving skills
now
no one will suspect a thing
especially
if you just let it roll down the hill
like this
oh I'm done what
I'm not drunk is how fast that was your
fault it's over
easy
and I'm a bit disappointed in that
but oh well here you go bye bye guys
yeah we should do this again
you should do it again soon
it didn't look like he had so much fun
in his face also why are they going
there together
when leaving me out you're doing like a
second round without me
the last you will see of me for a while
because
I have a feeling someone else will take
over the channel
and yeah it was nice
it was nice spending these last moments
with you guys
I'll miss you guys
I'll miss you
I hope that you enjoyed GTA 5 with me
and uh yeah please support froggy Wawa
in her Endeavors next week
we're gonna read some super chats
because I have some left over I think
and now from the stream obviously but
from something else so we're gonna move
over and read a little bit of those
oh I just noticed there's um
some space down there and now I got it
to fill up the screen properly huh
that was a bit rough at the beginning I
think but besides that
yeah I had a lot of fun today
ah a bit sad that GTA is over I I
enjoyed it but we um perfectly filled
the time until although not perfectly so
like
probably like a month or so
until Pokemon right I'm not sure when
exactly it releases I think maybe in the
middle of next month
um
but I'm not gonna start anything big new
but you know frog week fails a whole
week and then we have you know Halloween
week where I'm gonna try to play some
on-topic games
yeah and then maybe we can play some GTA
online maybe I can organize a
collaboration
um
yeah hopefully I can get that going I
think I think time will pass by fast
enough so
yeah with the blink of an eye
suddenly
trust me
Pokemon will be there and then we have
something new to play for a while
um not to say I'm not gonna play GTA
games again if I get you know
permissions then I'll try one of the
others eventually but for now there will
have to be a break yeah
okay
yeah I've seen a little bit of Mikko
senpai's playthroughs in GTA Online and
whoo it gets crazy
yeah
okay let's move to my office follow me
[Music]
come with me
oh [\h__\h]
hi
I look cute with this hat huh
pink cute
cowboy hat
I wonder who that was who got sent into
the usual room
probably someone who deserved it don't
worry about it
let me turn on some music
do we have
something good
[Music]
started a bit loud sorry
something chill some Lo-Fi
[Music]
there you go okay where are you doing
which ones do I have to read I guess um
what what was that stream
what was I playing
[Music]
pray for Jimmy
which Jimmy
did I read the rings of power ones I
ordered I only have to read the cooking
simulator ones seems like it's only a
cookie simulator nice soon
I will be open an instant
[Music]
by the way I did not decide yet what to
do for
the members only stream I want to use my
frog
but it doesn't necessarily have to be
frog really maybe
I was gonna say we can watch a frog
related movie but if we just watched
rings of powers I'm not gonna do that
but
I'm just gonna play whatever or do
whatever
oh yeah we can play slate Aspire again
I'll think about it but um
yeah
for the other streams I wanted them all
to be frog related but for the members
only I'll do whatever I can
um
[Music]
have you seen the five minute Speed Run
of that game of what let's say the Spire
or GTA
[Music]
foreign
memberships
[Music]
yo
oh yeah hopefully everyone who gets one
really deserved it and will make good
use of it
otherwise
I have a gun
so many lucky happy chickens wow
can watch the members stream next week
too you better be there don't disappoint
me now then you got it you gotta be
there
[Music]
to there
foreign
[Music]
thank you for the insane amount of
memberships
wow wow
thank you thank you
thank you okay I'm gonna read the Super
Chat dolls
remove some things you go here and you
go there there you go will you go here
welcome thank you for
a rainbow oh that question oh
God says became winged once again oh
I see it was your anniversary of
membership huh it takes more than a
friar to keep me down now I'm supposed
to have a little Firepower so can I get
a deal deodorant what's good
well I'll become all
an MF flame for when and nobody will
stop me I'll burn the enemy so bring
them on
sound a little bit like Trevor but
Trevor wouldn't use the Elder end
so hmm
but I guess you'll use it for something
else on the serious note to think that
I've been part of kfp for over two years
now that is the longest I've ever been
in a single Community oh
hold on how come
[Music]
part thanks to you being sweet and funny
Phoenix attracts me like a champion to
the fryer part thanks to friends I made
here ah recently my chips have been
pretty bad with a lot of afternoon
shifts and limited remote Days by
accident I became so dependable and I've
been bothered more and more making it
harder to watch you at work but not
impossible
Experian learning that your streams help
me chillax at and after work from now on
it should be better for some time worst
case I'll just change jobs to one that
allows me to more freely watch you oh
I feel the dedication from that
statement whoa
wow
[Music]
priorities set straight
I like that
I still refuse to leave in any other way
than with My Soul on way to kupala I was
going to read Coachella it really looks
like it Coop holla
I only accept leaving after I've done my
warrior two TV thank you thank you for
everything wow I love you curse you hook
on for copy pasting emotes
Ah Ah that's the doll oh that's what
that is
[Music]
who has to watch me less because of
their job but what you said oh
very passionate thank you so much so I
can always count on you I guess
thank you you're the best okay
congratulations on membership for two
years wow please continue supporting
kiwawa I don't even have to ask for it I
think
ah thank you
[Music]
I found a job thanks to you so that is
only fair oh but then I hope thanks to
me you won't you know change it thanks
to me because of me
that would be stupid
I keep on stopping to move
um
thank you for the pinky this is a stream
where you can see attention's cooking
skills what kind of poem will you show
nothing I was not at fault for any of
the bad things that happened like for
real
[Music]
as long as the game lets me do a good
job I even wanted to do a better job
than it let me do
like what the hell what are those
potatoes
unacceptable
you guys need to eat potatoes
that are
fried with butter in the frying pan
not fried as in you know like a
like a chicken burger I mean like you
know just just you know have it all be
um
um made slippery with
butter and parsley chopped parsley
sauteed is that the word
more of a sweet potato type of chicken I
like
I like some blood
um
we call these
and we usually serve them with schnitzel
[Music]
I love them so much
so good
I don't think that would suit so well
with sweet potatoes but I've never tried
so who knows
anyway
I think you know he wants to stream so
you know no Pawn no Pawn
just chef
perfect yes
bread cooking
making you hungry yeah I'm making myself
hungry I I actually kind of want to
order food it's not quite too late
and now I should probably eat what I ate
yesterday but I have a feeling that it's
not so fresh anymore
but oh well now I'll eat that I have to
eat what I cooked
I think I should
[Music]
um
yeah the meat is probably a bit dry
[Music]
yeah yeah
I have leftovers but my boots so good oh
well maybe maybe maybe I can finish with
like before
uh like maybe half past and then still
have the choice I'll look at my food
that I have from yesterday and I still
have the choice to maybe order but I
think I'll be okay I think I'll just eat
what I have
yeah yeah I should be fine
yeah
um
[Music]
chef chef
soon
Gordon Ramesses
Vanishing for the pinky well my oh my
who is a sweet pumpkin pie and what is
this delicious food she's making are yo
Tien Gordon Ramsay rameses is so nice
why is he was so sweet
why are you so kind
oh wait you were sent a red what wait we
sent a red one and a pink two pinkies
what the [\h__\h]
who is this
who dares to bother the Great and
Powerful Gordon Ramesses I've seen
better cooking from my dying Jackal wait
wait wait what happened
[Music]
oh I don't want to hear anything about
cooking seals from a big flaming chicken
wait what happened
[Music]
what did I do to upset you what happened
just like a different person I think
it's a fake
that's an imposter but no it actually
isn't because it says here it's the same
account
[Music]
swings yeah
I don't want to deal with someone with
such mood swings that's Splash
I was talking smack about him
no no no if anything I was talking smack
about Gordon Ramsay but not Gordon
Ramesses wait they sent so many
oh
what
there's so many different Ramses though
thank you Egyptian Wando mwah
even though you confused me that
question for the support in the kitchen
and Chef Boyardee
which is probably also like this seems
like a famous Italian chef because they
they wrote something in Italian
foreign
[Music]
excellent
all of it I speak very fluent Italian
after all
no but this I really understand
[Music]
what it's an American canned food brand
but but
in Italian
I was Bamboozled I don't know that brand
we don't have that here
[Music]
is that good stuff is it yummy
thank you
[Music]
did you change your name already and
this is still like you were supposed to
write this as Dr Glenn Pierce
oh
Egyptian Gordon Ramesses for three more
orange Silver Shadows Chef golden Ramsay
Dan kitchen knife
your passion for Italian cuisine
Bellissimo would you ever consider being
an ambassador for my restaurant
[Music]
I I have my own huge
fast food chain why would I be the
ambassador to another restaurant it
doesn't make quite sense
I don't want to turn you down because
you're so nice
[Music]
I'm kind of busy with my current job
though yeah
it depends on what is included if you
include
lots of yummy food then we can talk
about it
yeah
let me test it first before I make a
decision I need to test if your food is
on my level
to satisfy me
Chef Gordon Ramsay dances
[Music]
oh blessing me for my sneeze
wow thank you
[Music]
very much
[Laughter]
so my fault the food was running away
from me
a few game bugs in the dish won't hurt
anyone
might add some flavor but yeah I guess
some people eat bugs but these were not
the right bugs no no no
because you're in the game soon
Jacob 47 Al thanks again
I was about to say that kiwawa is the
only one I know that takes cooking
seriously in this game and does a 10 to
10 job job until the pork chop instant
happens
well I took it seriously
I did the game didn't take it seriously
excuse me
[Music]
thank you
for the pinky
[Music]
ah
if you like Lord of the Rings or Game of
Thrones you might enjoy the game Dragon
Age
I know that one the setting is in a dark
fantasy world with its own nation's
poetic magic and wonders the a
Inquisition is easy to get into the
franchise but the a origin has the best
story
love to see you
play
um
[Music]
I think I ever
played it
oh yeah no it doesn't look the interface
doesn't look familiar
[Music]
probably not something I wanna stream
but in the future interesting
why can't I give you super chat I have
them turned off because I'm not supposed
to have them on during Grand Theft Auto
streams
um
you're welcome to donate in the next
stream though if you wanna
[Music]
stream will have donations open
so you can keep it for now
these streams deserve Super Chat and if
you think so as I said
froggy Wawa will surely wire the money
to me
will she will she will she
can we trust her
what's your attention
[Music]
we'll see
will she take it and run
[Music]
I will tell her to wire any money to me
because my channel
she listens
and that just shows how much you mean to
us says space wonderful thank you soon
[Music]
you will always be perfect in my eyes no
matter what nothing in the whole
universe will ever be better than you
are you're the absolute best Chihuahua
I know
thank you thank you for the sweet words
thank you very much
[Music]
what a charmer
thank you
[Music]
oh this is the one that I read already
in the Stream everything
me kind of how dare you slander my
oshiki wow what am I saying she's not
perfect love my attention please stop
insulting her so I can stop saying
cringe things
no more and more
I want it let me hear you say love
kiwawa let me hear you say hashtag well
cash a guilt
[Music]
oh wow
mascara
[Music]
Islamic fellow thank you for the red
super chat a very late congrats on 1.1
million do you know oh thank you and the
ground would turn the whole tongue yay
I wish I could have said something
sooner but my brain has been locked up
at work and they don't want to let it go
shh
how are you alive they took your brain
and they locked it up in like a like
some kind of juice
you have to take it back should I get
Trevor Franklin and Michael
I'm sure they can help you with that
they'll take care of that and maybe
brutal ways but in the end you'll get
your brain back surely
brain jail
I see work even in dreams oh
that is hmm I hope it's not bad dreams
not no nightmares
[\h__\h] I hope you got free time
more chillax time more time for yourself
you deserving we're lucky to have an
Osho can help us online despite piled up
stretch love Wawa all of you until I
really hope you can get some free time
[Music]
I'm really lucky with my job I can
decide when I want to work and when I
don't want to work
I do push myself to
work
as much as possible as much as I can
take but I still have the freedom
which some of you guys don't they're
always like this but it will clear up
eventually oh that's good
you take that thought as motivation
and fight towards it
yeah
motivational truth
[Music]
thank you guys Bryson half I'm born yeah
um
yeah take a good break
for yourself
spend it with something that relaxes you
like me or something else
oh we can choose Thank you
I believe in you to take a break if you
ever need it yeah I mean I can see
myself next year taking a one month
break somewhere maybe
or like a one month break where I stream
only once a week or so to keep you guys
updated
but
I think that's acceptable at some point
I I think I will need some
some time to shut off and find
inspiration again and [\h__\h] get some
topics to talk about of course
[Music]
um yeah I've been on the grind yeah yeah
I always feel you know like I'm on a
on a spinning wheel like a hamster
and I ran and I run and I run and I run
and I just can't I feel like if I stop
running
the wheel will get the better of me and
like kick me out throw me out
[Music]
um I was trying to keep up with it
at the moment
I don't know I still feel like I'm
in some ways I'm
not keeping up
enough not as much as I want to
but
I can't give up
there's always that
hope
that hope and that
dream
that keeps me going and I feel like
every single day
that I don't stream or don't try to
create content
would be a waste
I feel like I just can't
[Music]
slow down
it's not so easy for me
[Music]
I'm trying to keep up
vital I don't
[Music]
Patsy donkeys
we're done
all the GTA streams left us with uh
nothing to read
I've been reading less super chess than
usual huh
more time for chillaxing
wish I could tune in more but always
make sure to catch you in the weekends
thank you you're the best now that
you've ever been slow down before you
get too good and the world can't contain
you oh I don't think that will ever
happen
thank you
let's train on your voice yeah that's
true
[Music]
we've done so much this year did I
want to do more
[Music]
I wish I could have done more
oh well we still got time
[Music]
all right well thanks for the great
stream no thank you no you
[Music]
guys
my first year following you I think you
did a lot oh thank you
first here
for joining
[Music]
you guys wanna see
Frankie Wawa spoiler picture
[Music]
no of course you do
yeah yeah
[Music]
cute
it's me
I'm taking over [\h__\h] say goodbye to
your owner takanashikiwawa
you won't sit here for a while
let's read me well too though I'm better
than her anyway
[Music]
all right so I'll see you guys on
Tuesday
um I'll upload the updated schedule with
one small change on my community board
but yeah still streaming at the same
time pretty much
on the same days
I have no energy left because my throat
hurts but thank you guys so much for
watching and joining me in this
playthrough another one that we finished
and number one for the list of games
finished by kiwawa
the game finisher
oh yeah you'll see froggy wow one don't
you say yeah yeah yeah yeah of course
what else could that mean
um
hey I'm glad you guys had fun
[Music]
um
not many streamers who take on GTA 5 and
then finish it but I am one of them
yeah all right good night everybody
let's rest for a bit until
this crazy thing
attacks all of us and makes us lose our
minds and and everything that we love
and cherish
and in Germany we say I'll be the same
time
[Music]
what's
foreign
[Music]
no
movie always knows when my stream ends
baby
[Music]
it's like I still can hear her that's
because you can
you're not imagining it
[Music]
foreign
subscribe and give me a 10 out of 10
review on Yelp