foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
get down again
[Music]
hello welcome to the Stream
hey how are you doing guys
yeah thank you thank you welcome welcome
I'm nervous
um
yeah I'm also kind of tired
tired tired what's tired
I am tired
Mommy
I am tired I didn't sleep so well I had
many many nightmares or or one big
nightmare
uh
so tired
all the chat messages yet
oh no
yeah it was it was even about streaming
the nightmare was actually about
streaming
so it was very realistic
um
yeah it's okay no I didn't eat pizza
before bed but does pizza induced
nightmares
ah so guys uh I will I will repeat what
I learned like last in my last uh Korean
lessons
because wait we need bgm
because
um
I have now I have weekly uh Korean
lessons with a private teacher
one-on-one
um
wait let me say that I have weekly
lessons with my Korean teacher
weekly weekly private lessons I should
see it
Papa go go
challenge
yeah
every week uh one one day uh maybe 90
minutes or so
did you hear that I think you heard that
right
okay
[Music]
yeah but this week she's uh not
available so I thought I just learned on
my own this week she is not uh this week
is not available
[Laughter]
[Music]
Anita and I I will give you a rough idea
what I learned so far so first first we
started with
um the writing yeah
um okay so you know for the what are
they called the consonants and the
vowels and all that stuff so
like we did this and and we did
this and we did this oops okay
it's like this no wait no it's like this
and and we did this and we did this and
we did and we did
um
um oh God the writing order is important
uh I think no
that like like this is this this is this
is um
and we did
we did uh we did what did we do we did
uh good and we did and we did and we did
to
okay that was wrong too I think no no no
no it's like that no it's like that in
the writing order stroke order
um
yeah and and we did uh I know the book
and when I know the oh I also know I
also know this double is you know
and oh and I did I know this one look
oh that was the perfect writing order
wow wow
and then I know this is this is uh wait
okay wait so there's a there's s and
then there's
and then there's
uh
okay maybe that's that was maybe first
is it like this or is it like this
and then you can this one however I
think you can write somehow like this
I think wow
wow
[Music]
yeah oh yeah Korean devil consonants no
problem no problem and like for example
man this is this is easy to understand
you know we have ah but if you add
two then there's yeah
if you have
uh
over the table oh
then you can also have yo and then you
can have
wait we still don't have PTM I forgot
what's what's wait a moment in Korean
I feel like I heard that before let's
wait a moment
full Tetris ah it is Tetris
I'm late to class welcome okay audio
stock
we should learn how to write audio stock
in Korean okay here how about chill
Lo-Fi because it fits to the the
thumbnail
oh
Lo-Fi hip-hop for studying oh wait I
don't hear it
[Music]
is wait a moment
really
loud
looks like Tetris that's just because
recently whole life members are playing
Tetris so everything looks like Tetris
do you know
foreign
I need to remember that uh
I'm still way faster I think riding in
our romanized letters
[Music]
oh thank you
for the superchato
okay okay so then we have uh and then we
have you you know there's a pattern
there isn't there there's also a similar
pattern for example what I wrote before
I'm just flexing my skills now so you
know what I know okay so this is
this is good or like for example if you
write this this guy this is Ka and then
this is
cup and then
there is
a God and then there is
no yeah chat is cut oh yeah a little bit
a little bit
it's fun it's fun
wow wow perfect
what no
what there's oh is there no car why not
why not oh okay yeah and now that you
say it I never saw it before
[Music]
maybe there should be a cop
I just made that one up okay but there
is uh uh let's say let's say let's say
we make a uh
a adult
and then there can be uh
uh
a tall
and then oh [\h__\h] I wasn't uh
I wasn't looping
and then there can be this looks like a
face now
there can be uh
uh
it looks like a funny face doesn't it
[Music]
we can we can write Kotori
Kotori is a
wait oh oh okay well I know I know them
all like single oh this yeah I know them
like on their own now when we get to
writing them oh that's Acorn ah acorn
now why would we write Japanese words in
kick you're still I thought you were
gone forever
but but at least I know you know it's
easy to write Japanese words in Korean
remember when some Korean Bros are like
uh trolling Me by writing like in Korean
so I think oh I can't read it and then I
translate it and it's like troll
messages because they're using Japanese
words but writing it in Korean so I
think
no
my handwriting is so bad no does that is
in
maybe not is that what you would choose
because there's more there's like you
know
there could be more options than just
going for this one because there's many
similar ones oh is it okay okay
cool uh
[Music]
but look how ugly they are I need to get
like let's see let's say I can only
write in here
[Music]
yeah yeah
I wanna write a prettier
don't ignore my order I'm a struggling
[Music]
it's it's really I think I need some
practice to get this stuff to look nicer
um
because essentially
if you have for example
an ah
um this is this is that but let's say
you want to write
for some reason I don't know what that
if that has any meaning but let's say we
write
then you have to fit it all uh
in here
yeah so there's like
four slots basically or there is
this constellation or there is uh there
is this constellation I guess
yeah depending on I don't know if it has
any meaning I'm just trying to you know
explain there's like slots and you can
fill it up or or it's just two it could
also just be two and then but with two
you want to fill up the whole picture
I understand I understand oh yeah it
could be even four yeah yeah yeah so
um
what did you write
what did you write what was that what
the four
ah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay okay so oh really
[Music]
foreign
why is Korean love like I guess I guess
it's like the
um how some evil
lolies in animes laugh like
[Laughter]
[Music]
why is that why is it like that
it doesn't even have a wait I keep on
forgetting because my first language is
not English so I keep on forgetting it's
it's vowel the owl
or is that a consonant
foreign
[Music]
we're trying to sound smart here
you know oh wait ah here one one that I
don't see so often so I haven't
practiced it much this is this is Boo
this is and then there is
uh then there is
this is
this is p right
did you see where I'm writing
hmm
oh but that one is really no that's not
that's not exactly it no
I won't have a normal key is fun here
um
okay okay okay okay okay uh I would
maybe I mean it could be wrong but I
would maybe ride
he
um
[\h__\h] I said there's no
[Music]
no
foreign
[Music]
oh yes okay
uh
[Music]
something like that although like in in
in
I actually write
Double K here so but you guys said I
there is no there is no Double K why not
there's so many double letters why is
this not double
that's so close what
okay
what did I ever do wrong
yeah I think I got it right looks the
same
[Music]
oh I know Double K
oh by the way this is
NG but
uh not you're not always when you see it
because uh this is ah
but at the end for example
[Music]
um
I don't know where ah for example room
where is ah
here at the end we have the NG so it's
p a n g normally you start from a top
left and then you go to bottom right
like this basically
and if you have several ones yeah yeah
yeah yeah
okay so as you can see uh I'm totally
not avoiding this one
is this this is oh oh oh
is it all
I always confuse the pronunciation of
this one
it's just like all
all
or a bit different
yeah
I
yeah okay well I mean yeah of course
like this
[Music]
no because this
this is uh uh maybe this doesn't exist
with that maybe it's always just that oh
I said it correctly oh
okay oh
oh eyes I wrote um
okay that's what I mean
it's a cup vowel what does that mean
[Music]
because there is also there is uh also
on this one and this one is all this one
is all and this one is oh
this one is all this one is all
[Laughter]
and this this this one is like a short a
short sound
[Laughter]
yeah
yeah yeah yes yeah oh okay okay
[Music]
I wait
um
okay I'm just I'm just repeating for now
but I think I think
okay next page Chihuahua kiwawa practice
next page
let's um
do some some difficult ones
we I want I'm gonna write them down in
in domaji and then we're gonna try to
remember
okay how I would write it in Korean so
we have a
we have
yeah
maybe I should leave a space
yeah yeah
we have we have yeah
we have what we have
we we have
this is just sometimes I write it the
way like how I hear it rather than like
because you have to think about the fact
that I have a German brand brain
so some things just sound different
you know then how you would maybe write
it officially in English
and
[Music]
something like Uli and something like
a little bit faster we
okay okay so
uh easy easy easy
this one is
you didn't see that this one is this
this one is I
and this one is uh
this one is yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah of course eventually you would add
this but for now for now for now for now
just just okay
Phoenix silly exactly not phonetically
we ride it in Phoenix silly whatever
sounds the most correct to me
and then we have uh it is
it is like this and then yeah
do I start with this
oh
and then why
why
[Music]
is a combination of over the table or
and ah so it's like
but it turns kind of into a into w
ow
so Ina's greeting is what
Maybe
yeah yeah yeah yeah and then
um
where where ah
like this and wait wait wait
wait wait like this
yes okay and then whoa over over the
table oh no wait this is the the other
one this is
[Music]
and then we have uh
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
go back go back go back go back
I wanted to do
not this one
now here we go under the table
oh
what
yeah it looks like a table and a chair
um
remember last year I was trying to teach
Korean to myself
and remember we were doing Duolingo and
they just throw you in there without
proper like starting training like
explaining everything properly and I
needed to make myself in German
some some kind of hints on why what you
know why this sounds like this
and I came up with the most ridiculous
ones yeah Ninja Turtles and the ATM yeah
yeah a lot of interesting ones but to
this day like the other ones I I got to
leave my head but this one
the over the table and under the table I
still have to tell myself that
maybe eventually
I will be able to get rid of that
um you know ninja turtles yeah
freaking green birds no green bird as
well
I need to cancel my subscription to the
green bird
okay well now we switched we switched
so this is uh
[Music]
can it be this is this what I'm looking
for yeah okay and then
um but then there's also Lee
foreign
it's so similar
eh
um
it's so similar there oh oh my God okay
so we practice here like a proper
student write it a million times is wait
was it like this or was it like this
was it first the long ones
what was it like this
[Music]
ah okay for like this okay
[Laughter]
doesn't matter no it matters myself
rip my head off if I if I write it wrong
she's like always looking when I when in
the middle when she's teaching me
something and I'm writing something down
while she's talking at the same time she
looks at how I write things yeah she has
a an eagle's eye so in that case this
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
maybe okay how about we try to stay in
here
in the boxes let's try to stay in the
boxes
okay beautiful and then yeah
[Music]
yeah
yeah okay perfect some of them look like
birds look funny these parts look like
beaks to me now
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
okay anyway
and
oh no space Oh no space
ah no space
ah
wow
what what
and then way
[Music]
this one's easy
it's again a combination of two
different ones where and
wait and then what
uh uh oh under the table and oh
gotta be careful to not write like this
no no no no no no no it has to be
the chair has to be under the table
because otherwise what the hell
this is not how you clean up in
restaurants no no no okay
wow
okay and then
[Music]
same here
and I'll leave it at that and then
[Music]
a few of these
do I really need to practice writing
those it's just two strokes okay wow
look it looks like I'm a student looks
like I'm practicing what happened to
stay in the Box I don't see the Box
sometimes you have to think outside of
the box sometimes right right that's
what life tells us
think outside the box
oh
[Music]
um
would be more like this one I would say
okay
um
now what I learned
last time where you know song something
was like okay kiwawa you are doing great
you already know how to write everything
more or less
um although these were just like some of
the examples
um she said okay let's go I will teach
you subject markers object markers and
verb endings you know when I posted on
Twitter
the Beautiful
subject
oh okay so basically basically let's
repeat this repeat repeat
subject markers
[Music]
when making a sentence subject subject
marker
[Music]
by the way I find it interesting how in
in
um romanized letters we don't give a
[\h__\h] how you how the order is of how you
write it like I write I write and wait
how do I write an e no I don't write it
like this
how do I run an ink like this I don't
care if you write it like
like this or like like this or like this
I don't know I don't care we don't care
but in it seems to be important in in
you know Asian languages
[Music]
yeah the stroke order anything goes as
long as it looks like somewhat accurate
okay
so we have uh thankfully not too many
different ones here so it's it's okay I
feel like I can remember when
um
what I feel I don't remember any of this
I don't remember this
so for example when we have
um
[Music]
ah
Tiana
[Music]
so we could write kinara
or
none
and
ah yes yes because Kiana ends in a vowel
ends in a vowel so I can I can use
and it doesn't matter so much which one
said my songs but God is like when the
focus is more on the subject of the
sentence and noon is more when you when
the focus is on the verb of the sentence
but you know
it's okay use when oopsie
use one use when the word ends in a
vowel now let's what's uh
What's
um
a word that's not ending in a vowel
son Let's how about Mountain I learned
Mountain Sun Sun the mountain
the mountain
the mountain uh Sun Sun
is when it ends in a consonant it's e or
un
so
or sun
mountain is big for example
um
right
when
ending in a consonant
[Music]
wow
see I'm actually just trying to repeat
everything for myself but maybe some of
you guys are learning a little bit too
yeah
yeah I also thought that the God is kind
of like similar to in in Japanese but
um
[Music]
actually yeah so some similarities to
Japanese she gets it yeah yeah I get it
I just get it and then for titles
if we want to be really nice because I
mean in Korean it's also like there's at
least there's not so many titles
in Korean as there are in Japanese
um there's only two so we could say
he ah
[Music]
she or Kiara
uh
name
and maybe that sounds familiar because
we have song Some name and what do you
guys call me
the name is already in there because
well some words they just come with this
but you don't say you don't say
Angel you just say songs
don't
foreign
yes
the problem is I guess
well it's not really a problem I suppose
when I when I end a Nim then it's
automatically the consonant when I end
in sheet and it's still the vowel so I
would say Kiara Shiga but when I say
Kiara Nim then I say
[Music]
um
right
yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
um
yes genius genius
these are pretty respectful titles both
of them but my Samsung name told me that
Nim is the more respectful one that you
would use for a teacher or a doctor
Etc and she you maybe just use for
everybody else
like um a friend
I mean if you're really close friends
you can maybe get rid of the she
um
yes yes your name is like Japanese
summer
okay
although I hmm
yeah yeah more or less hmm
okay okay and now we have
object
markers
in order to make a sentence we don't
only need subject markers we also need
object markers
so for optic markers there's two
there is
one and two
one is
a rule uh
oh God but this one is so hard to write
because it's so length so never L and
lengthy I need to how to fit it into the
box
I can't why is it so long
why is it so long
[Music]
do it and then there is
okay this one's a bit easier
okay and and again we use
[Music]
um
actually
this comes after the after the object I
guess yeah uh and and this is this is a
when a vowel when the word ended in a
vowel and this is when the word ended in
a in a croissant no in the consonant
[Music]
okay
dude and uh no
[Music]
okay and then one more thing we need for
the sentence
is the verb endings
[Music]
verb endings
mind you my teacher just started telling
me about sentence structures
um I have yet to learn like Words
vocabulary properly they were like some
words already that maybe I picked up but
uh
I like she didn't ask me to learn them
yet now she just wants me to get like a
an understanding of how a sentence is
formed
and then we practiced some sentence
building
but
I don't really know
many words yet I just picked up some
random ones yeah verb endings there are
um
there are I guess free
or four maybe it depends on how you see
it or two or four
so maybe you heard it before but many
sentences end in knee
da
Nida
like
and then some this is very polite this
is very polite
and this and then there's another one
this is Yo
a middle polite verb ending
not so polite as Nida
and then when you wanna
ask a question
this is really scary for me uh
I don't want to say it because
I don't want to get clipped out of
context
uh I don't even want to write it in
romanized letters just I'm not gonna say
it like this unless I have a sentence or
so uh yeah it sounds like a word that I
should not be saying
yeah
um but this is for for questions okay
I'm not gonna say it now because uh
otherwise people gonna clip me okay but
I know how to make a question
[Music]
okay and so we have
um polite
light
um
mid point
and uh
[Music]
yeah this is important for building a
sentence now
[Applause]
um
I want to do some vocabulary later too
but
yeah okay I have some
some
example sentences
that are really easy
that I learned already let's let's go
[Music]
here let's write them here look this
looks so cute doesn't it
and for some reason the textbook that
we're using
uh is giving all the people in the
example sentences
either English or Japanese names
at least they sound very Japanese like
Sato and Yoko
and Richard
these are the people that will appear
for us
I don't know why why are Japanese names
the subtle is definitely a Japanese name
Yoko too and at least from what I know
Sato and Yoko
in the Korean textbook
what is Richard doing in Korea well I
mean
only an English teacher
[Music]
Okay so
for example we have
a sentence let me write it down without
thinking much about it first and then
we're gonna try to read it again
maybe maybe the chat can give me a
similar uh easy sentence
uh
[Music]
Sato ends in ends in a vowel so
ga
this is the subject marker
foreign
uh John
it sounds like um
but
um well
this is another thing I learned
Germany
when it ends in the Poo It's actually an
um or oh no not really but you can't
really pronounce it like that is what my
teacher said so it just ends up like
that
this is the verb so we end it with a
knee
[Music]
da
um
right
yeah
wow wow
Sato is sleeping
now another sentence how about
Yoko
um
yo
Yoko
what is she doing ah oh
we have a verb and an object in this
sentence
[Music]
um
she's eating rice
up
that's the object that's rice
and then it ends in a consonant so we
end it in UL
um
[Music]
don't look don't look
um
come up
don't look don't look don't look
what am I writing
sounds like an um but it's not an um
and then the ending
um
[Music]
foreign
okay
next a person to appear is Richard
has a long difficult name that little
[\h__\h] how dare you how dare you make me
write so much
[Music]
um
what are we gonna make him do we're
gonna make him watch
uh movie
[Music]
is a movie
what is this
[Music]
I can't read my my teacher's writing
huh
ah it looks like a cup
no she wrote it a heart it's hard to
read
okay
Young
um
this is
this time we need the little it ends in
in vowels so we need to do
[Music]
how do you
make possible
I'm trying my best here and then
[Music]
this is awesome why is this also so long
how do you write this
[Music]
hmm
we charred
uh
[Music]
why am I running small and then big
glitter
okay
[Music]
yay poop it's pop but you were riding uh
you say it as pum because it's
impossible with the combination of the
needle I guess if you say only only
watching only the word then I guess you
would say pop
yeah that is difficult to understand
um
[Music]
okay okay
I'm today since I woke up I have a not
much breath
ability breathing ability
it's really hard breathing today
sorry
I feel
I can't breathe
shortness of breath very strong today
it's like I'm constantly out of breath
[Music]
hmm
yeah yeah it's okay
well I want to change bin Jam the Lo-Fi
is getting repetitive
I want more Lo-Fi
wait we have a
we have don't we have whole live Lo-Fi
but that's gonna always make me wanna
sing maybe that's not a good idea let's
go to audio store girl
give me some Lo-Fi
[Music]
so we need new Benjamin I'm going bgm
shopping now here you can choose with me
um I need something that Loops though
[Music]
oh
that's gonna make us fall asleep though
oh wow this is like it says it's
Japanese style Lo-Fi
oh
let me skip a bit
[Music]
yeah
what is so pretty I didn't use this
before no no no no I didn't what are you
you're just did you watch someone else's
stream and they used it and now you
think you claiming that I used it but in
reality you were just like just outing
yourself that you watched someone else's
stream um
I see
foreign
[Music]
maybe it was Santa's bgmo really
okay I like this one
no no from an anime I swear are you sure
you think animes are using uh audio
stock
[Music]
okay is it so quiet
this one this one has been demo the
previous one
getting distracted yum sorry
visual novels use it
I can imagine
[Music]
okay let's write another sentence
how about
well the child listens to music now we
don't have a name we have an actual verb
unbelievable
it's
[Music]
um
ah and E
h
[Music]
Aika
what umak music is umak in Korean
[Music]
ah the writer link
with this
[Music]
because it ended in a cane
Buddha
and listening is
put
it up
[Music]
hey okay so we have cup we have oil we
have
and then we have
the child
a e
[Music]
um
and
food
I can't fit
with a cute word
[Music]
um
okay okay we're gonna leave it at that
unless give me uh Korean Bros give me a
really really easy sentence and I want
to try reading it okay maybe I will not
understand but use easy words maybe some
words that I know
um
or maybe we should first practice some
words
I have some words that I want to
practice
reading and writing oh
okay okay I have I will stop stop stop
stop
and
okay what is this uh
[Music]
um
that
dark dark
what's that what's that are you trolling
me you're trolling me probably
what was that what did I I don't even
know what I'm reading
I should write it down for you guys wait
a second what is that you definitely
trolled me
[Laughter]
it's just trolling me
okay okay another one what's this one
the meaning of the coming sentence is
Piada is cute oh
[Music]
Queen
he Queen
um
our sentence
[Music]
what is this
yes oh
Jordan
what's genius jonan is me I Kiana
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
words have never been spoken before
foreign
[Music]
you guys
don't
know
okay
okay I can read sentences let's put this
aside I want to learn
um my my teacher left me with some pages
she basically just like
um I don't know if this is legal when
she
um they didn't make me buy a book she
just uses her own book and and um
scans and copies the pages
and gives me them I guess we're saving
money
I would buy the book but you know this
is just how we're doing it I guess and
some of these Pages have like pictures
and on them
and and then the Korean letters and I
have to practice how to write it and how
to read it like what it is and what it
means
I think that's legal is it it says the
teacher so maybe maybe it is okay so for
example
um
we have
[Music]
this is an apple okay sagua I remember
this one
um
[Music]
I can read it too
sagua
Apple
okay
let's practice
good
okay
okay now oh okay next one is let's see
if I can draw this
um
[Music]
how many legs does it have six oh I
didn't know what is this
this is
apparently uh this is a
get
[Music]
ah
okay
a crab cute
Connie Connie Connie now becomes gay
[Laughter]
[Music]
silver let's practice
again this is just one one syllable so
that's
pretty simple
[Music]
oh God okay kill crab
how about you get a Kiana
am I making sentences
I wouldn't eat a crab probably I don't
really like the taste or the texture
but the sentence worked out right yeah
yeah okay next I I don't I don't know
what this is
I don't know what this drawing is
but the word
the word is
uh
doctor
to go to the doctor
I think what the drawing is is probably
the doctor's office oh no company
a quit
Lisa is Dr Jose's company okay
company answer this is just a company
building
[Music]
um
here company building
oh what it is when you know what it is
that's how it is
uh
is
company
[Music]
and
point
song
[Music]
not looping I want to look the other one
holy oops
yeah yeah okay
no I'm not eating the company Kiana
how about Kiara is going what how do you
say going to
[Music]
going to
how do you say that kfb hoi song
[Music]
each comma Court must consume
cup
Nida
uh
Canada
[Music]
saying one breath what's up what's up
okay nice nice
next I think maybe Church judging by the
uh drawing by the illustration
um
Windows yeah must be Church
so that would be um I only see the
Korean writing now so let's see if I can
read it
um
uh over the table yo yo yo
[Music]
yo yo
coin
is that what you said
you're fine
[Music]
it sounds like the German word for it
almost
[Music]
is it did they take it from like a old
Latin word
sounds like German almost
okay
in Germany
yo
[Music]
okay
um
well
[Music]
it's the same word as Japanese
that's a bit different but it starts
with guilt kill
um
a a church
okay come on let's practice
oh look at that handwriting
looks like a Korean person wrote it's 10
out of 10. oopsie
what is that what is that
you
[Music]
what that's enough that's enough
thank you
ah it shares the same it
etumology
[Music]
interesting you write better than I do
don't say that no no no
no what is this this is uh
who is this what is this a doctor or
what
and
I'm trying to read it um
[Music]
they use like an English word for winter
um
waiter
wake up
wait
e
top
no wait yeah
wake up wake up what's little not white
wouldn't wait wait also see it's
intercepting
why is it not way down
what what
[Music]
wait on him
way to see
so
now let's make a chicken out of it
[Music]
transcribes to
oh
yeah it's good here
and wait on name
wait don't wait on you
um
wake her I think I can hear it
yeah I think I understand
[Music]
wait
oh
later okay
[Music]
one more because this one's kind of long
yeah yeah
left vowel not round like
yeah I need to get used to the
difference
um
well I think we have the word for
a bird I don't know if it's bird in
general or this specific bird
[Music]
um
I love that and this is a
step
say
all right
yes yes yes
[Music]
any bird in general okay you said
I am eating eating poop Kiana is eating
a bird yeah
uh how about
ah how about
well we are at animals we already know
this one and
[Music]
Jay
this is a rat mouse
wait I forgot the big ears yeah I'm
doing
a rat or Mouse
[Music]
oh my handwriting is getting better
yay okay okay that's Bales yeah
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no please no
I don't want to
doesn't taste good I'm pretty sure
how about oh
um
what is this stop Target what's a gage
it looks like a building a house but
[Music]
what is this okay
what's that supposed to be
a shop ah okay that makes also sense
um
oh no I wanted to I wanted to have
uh
uh different colors every time
I have to try it again
hey FP
okay
um this one is
okay this one's easy too
okay
and we only learned how to go right what
was what was going
um probably don't know I was going
going to the store
[Music]
um
no
got it I want to go to the store though
how do I go to the store
yeah
[Music]
Gaga
is there no two like specifically a word
that says two
[Music]
ah
um
[Music]
oh oh see I see okay the teacher didn't
teach me these kind of words yet
[Music]
maybe I will learn it later
shop
okay we do next one we do is
I I'll stop practicing now
this is a scissor
um
ah
we go we
going
we
can't write
God
[Music]
scissors
thank you
[Music]
go away
are we
are we up for me it may be in English
you write w e
but I'm I have to remember I have a
German brain yeah can we
can we can we can we
[Music]
okay yeah yeah that's okay that's okay
and let's one more here we have ah
oh wait it's very similar to ear cup we
scissors and
GUI is here but I'm not gonna write that
one down one
this one is a doctor how about this one
what's this one
[Music]
and
what what
[Music]
snacks cookies
and we can make the sentence again with
uh
next yeah
I don't know what that is but
it's just some snacks okay and
watch out
[Music]
snack snacks
wow
Etc Okay so
let's say with some vocabulary beautiful
some easy ones there's some more that I
have to practice there's like
uh
uh baby probably is
and then there's a
[Music]
Pudu is the grapes
and then we have I think meat or steak
is
cookie
ah
no cookie cookie
a country
Nala
shoes
who do Bridge
Daddy
tree
nah
Nam
U namu
and
ah pants
party
uh cap
or hat hat is
[Music]
um
and woman is your job and bus is
[Music]
pizza is pizza who would have thought
train is
[Music]
Etc
okay
now
that we learned some words
I have some more I could learn some more
words
I know I wanted to I wanted to do one
more thing
with you guys so
let's figure out how to write countries
so
I write down some countries and we try
to figure out how to write it in Korean
Austria or or city names
um Austria
[Music]
Berlin
how about
America
[Music]
um yeah wait wait wait let's first write
some down I know it's not a country
countries and cities
[Music]
um
Mexico oh I wonder how they write that
in
do they write Mexico or Mexico
give me give me some City oh it's how
about Sydney
Sydney
Indonesia oh
[Music]
how about Maldives
how about
Chile
Canada
give me more cities though
it's a Canadian city oh
Canadian city
Seoul okay
um
[Music]
okay okay let's go with these for now
okay uh how about
over
what
[Music]
uh
how's it
awesome
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's what I meant that's what I meant
there's no kangaroo yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay Berlin
yeah
would they write pear ludin or pudding
foreign
[Music]
no wait what heading
hey what hey
[Music]
I don't think
oh okay okay okay oh nice thing I feel
like there's like several ways of how
you could ride it so we have to learn
the correct one
[Music]
okay America
um America is it just America ah
oh no I finally wrote it correctly
um
[Music]
ah you have an actual proper word for it
um
America okay America is America
huh
um
[Music]
I think I've wrote it like that
whoopsie sorry I forgot one stroke
but I I wanted to write ah
me [\h__\h]
ah you have your own yeah for some
countries I guess you have your own
meguk miguk oh
me
look
what
[Music]
what what is that
me look
[Music]
good
beautiful country oh you're being really
nice to America
ah if you want to say the continent then
America oh and if you want to say
country
okay yeah Mexico do they say Mexico they
can't I don't think they can
make do they say make Mexico Mexico
how about that
make make
Chico makes ah they can do Mexico make
Chico
[Music]
no Mac make we want to add the cook milk
oh she
[Music]
all over the table make sure you call it
okay yeah yeah sometimes I think a
little bit I give it a little bit too
many syllables
like in Japanese but in Korean you can
give it a little bit
lightless
Sydney how about [\h__\h]
NE I feel like you could do it in two
syllables
Sydney
foreign
you could do it like uh oh wait is there
she don't can't you do like this [\h__\h] me
Sydney
why not like this
why are you laughing
why can it not be like this
They're laughing at me Sydney
me
okay but actually it is
cheese
doll
me
he had a bargaining yeah I have to
finding a better way
because then we don't get all the
syllables yeah I feel like you do Sydney
Sydney
I think
this this one should be it
because
[Music]
here I feel like you are
missing the soft d
ude um
[Music]
Indonesia in in
um
[Music]
oh it is
it is over the table
[Music]
oh
indoor
window
[Music]
see
foreign
chimney ah
I guess yeah because I learned that the
pups what was it what do you call the
ending thingies
certain ones they all turn into the same
one
I wrote this down somewhere
[Music]
um
is it correct now you're right Indonesia
oh yeah
Indonesia it sounds like England is four
o'clock in Korean ah
in India
oh in India it's four o'clock means
Indonesia
when I was in the Maldives there are
many Korean
um honeymoon couples so I think Maldives
is really popular in Korea
how about and
[Music]
um
more
[Music]
um
more blue
model
and oh no more
I'm still thinking to Japanese
[Music]
freeze free
um
and then more deep
oh
[Music]
one people
I wouldn't have written it like that
I see him
okay what about Chile is it is it the
Chi
um
children
[Music]
no
it was not Chile it was Chile
ah ah because
otherwise it would be more like
but if you put ah my song Something
taught me like
a different case like this where you
want it to be clear that it's an l
rather than something in between an r
and an l and you can only do that it was
close yeah you can only do that when you
put
another L here which forces it to be an
L or something like that Chile
hitting you
[Music]
LR
um yeah yeah
L is double our arm
s
so so
[Music]
oh
so how would kiwawa write this so uh
so
oh
is that how you read it
so
[Music]
but this part was right
the second part was right
so so
no no no no no no no no
sorry
okay
this okay okay okay
Toronto
[Music]
thought
oh
no
[Music]
I feel like the end should be here
but how can I do three of them in here
check how do I do wrong
how do I do wrong
what oh
yes I'm left-handed
hey so it's not
it will get bad today
it is no space it's too long hold on
hold on
oh
wait wait wait wait wait wait where's my
mouse where's my mouse
soul is still wrong wait wait wait wait
wait wait somebody wrote
raise that comment
well Toronto is correct okay Toronto
Toronto is fun
[Music]
no
says
solid is
this this
is sold
[Music]
when confusing Wikipedia
so no solo Korean writing here there we
go oh
oh no no
um
[Music]
that's how I wrote it no
ah
bro hmm sexually
so over the table under the tape under
the table
um
so
so rude
[Music]
ah
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
I snorted
are you okay
me in Korean oh my God I can't believe
it
it's triggering me
snort chill all right all right we have
some more space we have some more space
here if if only I didn't
um
let me get rid of this
why is it so difficult huh
I thought oh with my Japanese skills
this is gonna be a piece of cake no no
no no no no
so
much fun under the table
okay okay
[Music]
let's let's add one more roll of cities
and and countries
um
how about
Brazil
in Japanese is
[Music]
London ah my teacher already made me
write this one before London
Lawrence woohoo
fancy
[Music]
oh it's Florence yeah for Lawrence
New York
this is gonna be a long one
and oh
what what's up I don't even know how to
pronounce it
that's gonna be an issue okay okay here
we go
Brazil so in Japanese the syllabus
in Korean okay how about you guys just
tell me the amount of syllables three or
four don't tell me no writing yet don't
tell me just tell me one two three four
how many syllables how many little
pieces of the puzzle I need
free okay
let's see can we make it in free
[Music]
now
why not
why
hey hey first
no first I wanted to I was thinking
about it I was like no
hey
I was gonna do that first
I was gonna I was going to but then I
doubted myself
oh so close but I'm proud I got the rest
right although I guess it's is it more
is it this or is it this AKA
this
[Music]
is Jill or chill
should be Doom shouldn't it be this one
it looks different in the chat but I'm
it's the first one right
yeah J sound
not true sound
okay okay okay okay okay
London how many syllables
London probably two right I think we can
do it in two
uh over over the table
[Music]
two okay long
long done
houses
London
seems right
[Music]
what oh
I had so much confidence
[Music]
oh no no
hi hi
[Music]
it's pretty similar in terms of
pronunciation
[Music]
um
okay Florence
how many syllables
oh
free maybe
you free
four four
words you guys are not sure about it huh
ah
foreign
let's go with four okay
but oh wait but there is no
it can only be put in in Korean too so
cool
[Music]
oh
put on
[Music]
then
how does
laughs
it's four I made it four
ah
ah there's two ways of pronunciation
foreign
[Music]
which one is the right one
we are talking about finances oh
ah you give us the curry and the Italian
name
but let's say we would have written
Florence like the English one
would this be
how you would spell it
it's probably not poodle oh
[Music]
okay thank you trash human
lens oh
class
pretty close to me
huh
cool cool
bring the r over there to make it an
actual l
um
I did that I did that I did that and
then I did I did this too okay
I mean I feel like this is not
necessarily my fault you know any of
these like
ah because it could work either way
[Music]
yeah you could do the same with Brazil
probably okay New York
new I think we can do new in in one
letter even
can we can we do
you you are
under the new
new
hello
New York into New York New York New York
New York
oh
ah
New York
[Music]
They're laughing at me again
was bullying me again
because
in patching is the same right
mm-hmm
it's the patching problem but the the
besides that it was fine yeah
yeah okay okay Warsaw I wore so I don't
even know how you pronounce Warsaw War
so well more I don't even know how to
pronounce that in English
let me see or so
also
Warsaw Warsaw Warsaw Wars
[Music]
Warsaw four
um
[Music]
two or four well we'll go with four four
nah this one's breaking me this one's
Breaking Me No One what is this no
[Music]
I wanna
I wanna find out myself but
um wait which one would I use for what
maybe
[Music]
what
whoa
yeah but am I not
I could do this in two whoa whoa
foreign
[Music]
what's up
also
or was for
no
you are you the police name
[Music]
what's Warsaw
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's completely off but I feel like
Warsaw Warsaw we could have written with
two I don't know if that was like how
you would do it but okay yep
huh
oh yeah
with a Y in there
all right
[Music]
it's very
difficult
[Music]
I think if
this will take me a while to just like
someone says write this country's name
or the city's name and I on the get-go
will get it right that will take me
a long time because I feel like there's
different ways you could
yell
try it and
you can get close to it but
[Music]
foreign
language description is a complete mess
yeah I feel like it's more difficult
than Japanese
but maybe that's just me being biased
because I know Japanese fluently but I
feel like I can guess even when I hear a
country's name or like a foreign word in
general for the first time I know how to
write it in Katakana in Japanese
immediately I don't have to think so
much about it
I feel like Korean is trolling me
crawling me
uh
okay
two hours that's enough practice for
today but I will read some super chats
Maybe
from this stream
thank you
but don't go yet
foreign
[Music]
and Kiana
you're good what's it good
but still good
a reading and what was the other thing
[Music]
you're good
um
[Music]
it's like future tense okay I'm not that
far yet I haven't even learned any thing
any proper vocabulary yet so yeah oh
well
and I'm just gonna read from this stream
only
and then because I think I finished
super chats the other day but people
told me I forgot to read the members one
but we have a member stream later so
we'll read members super chats in the
member stream
but thank you for listening to me
listening listening listening
[Music]
lights
out
[Laughter]
thank you for listen
[Music]
ing
baby we can do it again because my
teacher told me another date where she
whenever a week where she can't I think
help me but maybe like once a month
um once a month now let's
repeat this
once a month
[Music]
from books
too long
once a month okay
you come and help me so that my teacher
will think oh
yeah what was genius
all right we're gonna watch Star Wars
the SEC what what did we watch last time
I wanna watch the next one
for members I have to put up a
reservation hmm
you're doing really good today thank you
so
[Music]
well episode four last time so we
watched Empire Strikes Back tonight okay
Empire Strikes Back
only movie later
Empire Strikes Back for everybody I
remember who was like what the [\h__\h] are
we watching Kiana
this
is that the fifth one oh
okay okay super tackle
and
um
something something
[Music]
I'm so happy though now because like
when I was trying to teach it to myself
last year I wasn't making any real
progress I kept on forgetting because I
I didn't really push myself to do it
regularly I couldn't I didn't have the
time but now now I already paid for my
private lessons
so she's coming every week and I have to
learn I have to but she's doing a good
job at teaching me
after every lesson I feel like I got
much smarter hmm
she's a good teacher
very good very good once you get the
alphabet it's easy yeah I'm I'm I can
write it at least now so that's
something I was never able to do
properly last time and I understand the
system of how the letters come together
mostly
mostly mostly
so it's it's getting there should we get
a new audio how do you re how do we
write audio wait let me write audios
where's my pen
audio
10 of soil
okay
ah
I lost what how can it be lost I just
had it in my hand
and
sorry we cannot write I know it's right
in front of
my audio stuck okay
oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh it's not oh it's
not like all probably all how about how
about all
oh
the
it's definitely not correct audio
[Music]
talk
wait I can do that in one letter no wait
that doesn't work that's no way that
works Maybe
Maybe
talk
no
how about
how about this
oh
which one is the right one
I said I wrote the party wrong again
[\h__\h] pot team
patient
it's the correct one
eh
and close oh
over the table oh oh
what's the official one holding it
oh
so
[Music]
call
oh I wanted to do that but I thought it
looked too long
free on top of each other
audios to talk
yay not so bad
was a good try
try
audio stuck
in Japanese I think it would be
how do I write Japanese
cool
I think I forgot how to write Japanese
Korean is infiltrating my brain oh
oh oh
[Music]
this is how I write it in Japanese
and even though it's very confusing it's
very fun
okay
oh that's right
where's my papa go
where's my purple cool
[Music]
piano will read super chats
she
ah
super
chance
for chats
Super Chat
this is
the super chats
support
[Music]
foreign
I don't know what I'm writing at this
point
real good
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] me
[Music]
yay it's a sentence let's go
hey back
hey back stay back
[Music]
yes
okay I'll stay in the screen
for Siri we did so much we started with
this like repetition of what I know that
we did some Writing Practice then we did
the you know subject marker object
marker verb endings and some sentence
writing then we did some vocabulary
writing and and you know listening and
learning and so on and then we did the
countries how to guess how to write them
we did so much WoW
my teacher will be so proud of me
oh yeah audio stock let's get another
different
Lo-Fi can never have enough Lo-Fi right
how about a Christmas lover just kidding
[Music]
hey hey
we
win
this one's nice
[Music]
it's like they're having a lot of fun on
the DJ thingy
playing around with the track
with scratchy scratch
okay
[Music]
your boy Stephen Adams done
hmm game
um ghee
listen you guys for the pink Super Chat
oh what is this
over the table Cordy
[Music]
Korean
study
EE
over the table yo yo
yo
[Music]
over the table ah
m
what what what
is
[Music]
did you just mix English and Japanese in
there you little [\h__\h]
it's so confusing
that's so confusing
thanks for the pink Super Chat everybody
[Music]
stop
laughs
on
[Music]
um
I think that was right
thanks for the pinky again yeah Tetris
Tetris very Tetris isn't it actually
some of them
look very useful to make a cow emoji to
make like like faces face
cute little I think or if actually some
like some Japanese color Emoji even use
Korean
signs sometimes sometimes I see it
like the mouth could be a
a
sometimes to make it like a hirakuma
kind of mouth
and one thing I need to learn now now
that I can ride with my hand I need to
learn how to use the Korean keyboard on
my phone or how to use it on the
keyboard but
yeah yeah
What the hook
oh it's okay wait I want to make one
[Music]
aren't they like so perfect
for making
look it's so cute oh
[Music]
it's so cute
yeah they're perfect
I love it
thank you everybody now please teach me
next time how to write on my phone very
important because I I want to tweet
Korean on my phone brought epic2135.com
okay
oh okay for writing it in in Japanese
too so I can read it better
cold thank you for the pinky
I've also been studying English to watch
your streaming I think it's really fun
to learn another language
over the table go
Puma
oh yeah
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait this is one
thing that we didn't uh I didn't repeat
actually this time
[Music]
you're welcome and thank you as well
please continue coming to my stream and
studying English
fighting fighting
what my teacher told me
[Music]
is you're welcome
why are you laughing it's a bad what
it's just oh
what
puppet help
you you're welcome
to my nail that's what I was saying you
know that right you know that you know
that someone else
you have to understand
um
[Music]
I was not trying to install me okay no
I wonder what I said
um
oh I love this bgm
I cursed
I think what did I say like you're a
little [\h__\h]
funny maybe that will actually come in
handy in the future I
think
slack for chickens
perfect so
oh
that sounds perfect
[Music]
I was like
welcome back I'm happy to see you again
thank you I'm glad you're still watching
kiwawa sometimes thank you
[Music]
what was that
you just like me you're struggling to
put the
single letters into one proper
um I feel you
it's difficult
thank you thank you okay
[Music]
don't leave me again say hello every
once in a while
please how's progress progress was
really good
oh it's so small uh over the table
Garden Park
hold on
holiday
[Music]
thanks for the pinky this is taking me
back to living in Korea oh you lived in
Korea before and learning Hangul so I
could write the metro and stuff like
eh
and
dog
so I could find restaurants to serve ah
yeah those are very useful words I can
imagine
kimbap I know how to write kimbap I can
write kimbap now I want to eat kimbap
kimbap
um
but even more than that I want to eat
Korean Hot Dog
please
yeah street food in Korea really good
well actually did that did I ever tell
you
when Nabi mama and me were uh
I think we're looking for a very
specific Korean street food uh running
around some popular
[Music]
area
in I don't know where it was anymore but
I was sitting on the ground eating some
street food and then some foreigners
like tourists
like a small group of tourists
they they were like
Kiana they know me I'm like
Prince recognizing me but Taurus being
tourists in Korea we're like oh yeah
yeah
that was interesting I never told you
home
I wonder if any Koreans recognized me
and just didn't say anything
um
oh how much is this my I was just eating
my food that was embarrassing
eh you stopped yourself from asking but
you saw me oh yeah
[Laughter]
I mean generally
if I
um it depends if I look like a
in that moment if I look like a homeless
person
if I look like [\h__\h] then maybe don't
talk to me because then I would be very
embarrassed about talking to you or
being recognized
like messy hair
like weird not cute clothes and no
makeup and sweaty as [\h__\h] I don't know
if I look like that then don't say hello
but besides that we still have that that
myth that
um in that big Temple
that I visited with Nabi that the guard
recognized me you know the one the chat
who was like I'm one of the guards and I
saw you I didn't I couldn't say anything
because I was on duty really
really I still don't know if that's true
I can't believe it the spare yeah spare
KFC really
really I mean
yeah generally
you can say hello it's okay if you if
you find me if you find an orange bird
on the street
you can generally say hello
but this orange bird doesn't go outside
much so good luck with that ah
oh my God
oh
okay sometimes
we don't either
just let me for real for real
um
I think I need to sneeze again huh
well that was four times I think
[Music]
you for the pinkies
thank you
thank you for the Super Taco donation us
soon
and I don't really celebrate Easter but
I have some Easter eggs in my fridge I
mean not not these like proper eggs but
painted proper eggs and I bought some
Easter themed chocolates yeah but I
don't really celebrate it
um
a great orange bird if she's not in
homeless mode exactly
maximum
[Music]
what
[Applause]
[Music]
yes thank you I am fighting
every day
every day is a fight thank you soon for
the support and watching me learn Korean
and this guy is going somewhere it's
getting somewhere we're learning things
yeah we're making progress
I'm so proud
even though I I didn't know how to write
a lot of these things correctly I had an
idea of how and how it could be there's
just so many options
I've studied Korean for 10 plus years
and I still mix up subject markers oh
really
[Music]
Han
you know one thing my teacher always
corrects me flip is like the difference
like for example of pronunciation for
example
uh
God
and
cop and
oopsie
like this
I think these two
are a bit difficult for me
to differentiate and like several of
these
where
for example
and
oops
I mean
okay this one's maybe still somewhat
manageable I think there's some that are
more difficult
um
foreign
yeah those differences are
[Music]
difficult
yeah my nose is running now from all the
sneezing
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
better catch it
oh I don't want to lose my nose
I had chose the first Super chats of
people now whoa thank you
super Chapel
from blackpink they have the normal do
and they have the double the
dude
I wouldn't know which one is which
yeah
um
what the [\h__\h] can't wait to see you at
the karaoke later today at Anime Boston
don't stress me out it's I'm not on
today I'm not on today I'm on Sunday
what what kind of okay
what did I not get a memo or are you
making up things
I'm not on here anyway Boston's are
there right
thanks for the pinky here's some simple
Korean words oh you're definitely
trolling me
I feel like this is a troll
eh eh
under the table uh
three
it's not it's not so simple clean
uh your
um
you're calling me cute
he
he Wawa sometime
[Music]
oh yeah
no what what is that what what's that
what's that mean oh
what is that
explain
what is this bgm uh it's number
one one two two uh one one two two two
for free on audio stock
this is the usual room
oh
[Music]
I can't read that my brain is broken
kfp
[Music]
I can't anymore one more salary oh good
that I can't read that I don't know
I don't understand sorry I don't
understand Korean yet
um
sorry
I can't understand
um I will practice more Korean maybe one
day I will understand
no no
no no I don't understand
sorry
I do also not agree no no no a
convenient yeah I mean I really don't
understand though
don't cry
[Music]
do you mean soy milk and you do means
chicken
[Music]
do you say you
yeah you told you a soy milk soy milk
say
Chicopee feel the same
oh no
is that what you guys were hearing
soy milk soy milk say chicory feel the
same
[Music]
that's funny
true
[Music]
thank you
ale
my check I saw emojis flying around
because I'm not using hyper chat right
now what
[Music]
what thank you thank you
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
lucky lucky
[Music]
cookies
for the pink Super Chat
[Music]
no no no no
is cute he says
um
thank you
you're cute too you're pretty cute too
[\h__\h] you chicken thank you so much
for the support
agrees and coffee
[Music]
and crayons 80 thanks for the pinky
I killed yesterday was my birthday oh
yes you did okay you're saying that
because I always ask them after two
years you're still my Kami honestly oh
don't I admit I joined DDD again what
then how can I be your kamioshi
I guess okay yeah
yeah here's a little funding for your
planned practice this year because more
Cubano content is what I want as a
present thank you yeah I got really
excited yesterday because I got a new
demo track for my album which already is
like it sounds like pretty like finished
and Polished
um
and one I already had since like months
ago but I wasn't sure if I could really
have that song If it was within the
budget
um but it seems seems fine so now I have
two
already I will not tell you how many
tracks there will be but it's I'm not
sure if we will call it a mini album or
an AP or even a full album I'm not sure
yet but I I have a plan of how many
songs there will be and who will produce
which songs there's like different
producers and all that
are absolutely incredible like for me
absolute bangers
um one is like a summer banger and the
other one
I'll keep a secret
I'm so hyped too like they both give me
ear worms
um
so excited I want to make 3D music
videos for them
yeah
promote them but also just to show them
off because I feel like I need to dance
to them I have to
more news coming at 12.
wrestle free donation and
mean
um
[Music]
York yo yolk your cook
okay soon
and
difficult very difficult jumping queue
thank you soon thank you
jumping
and I can't get started with Japanese
because it seems so much harder than
Korean it doesn't have kanji for one
yeah
but at least in Japanese like you don't
I mean yeah you will need kanji
eventually but you can write every kanji
out in hiragana
worst case
then
when
[Music]
Maybe
that's enough to get you by yeah it
looks like as a base and if you want to
learn more then learn more afterwards
one
me yes you
yes
yes yes yes wait I wanna hear it
[Music]
okay
yeah
Duncan for the pinky
[Music]
um
hunger
on
girl
no um oh
um
[Music]
or on the thumbnail no in the tile
so I'm so slow
what
oh you're breaking me
you're breaking me
foreign
[Music]
you're always here you're not only here
when I study Korean you're always here
and I know that I love you
thank you my my sweet sweet loyal
chicken
I want to give you a kiss but it's not a
pink Super Chat you get you get half a
kiss
there it is
no no folder yet but I know I know you
yeah
[Music]
Dora thank you soon Red Ring thanks for
the pinky did you change your phone no
wait no I just know you more from
Twitter that's why it looks so different
red pink
[Music]
and
if you can read this that means you
started quite well okay okay okay uh
what the [\h__\h] it's so small though
it's so small
let me size it ah it's a it's a oh wait
um
well well done
Kiana
it's English
[Music]
English but written in Korean ah
if you can read this that means you
started quite well here's some allowance
money as the reward oh and would you
consider telling me that it's okay to
use Art Attack 2 for the Korean
reviewing fan vids or just use KFI tan I
think kfp tag is fine I checked the kfp
tag a lot as well like every day
oh
I think
that would be fine also I have to change
the Art Attack now anyway
well done
thank you for trying to teach me very
helpful thank you songs I mean you're
also songs
for the pinky thank you
now actually I have to refresh because
there were many more Super chats after
that what the hell
okay
refresh
was that a mini yawn I don't even
remember anymore my
I saw the pizza you made
it didn't look very Italian to me but it
looked good and I'm glad you tried out
the corn on the sides
said the Art Attack is changing ah it
doesn't matter it's just a tag
yeah it's just so annoying I don't see
that kind of spam in my other tags so it
must really have to deal with the art in
it
my pizza was very Italian you little
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh that was my first try you guys never
go easy on me
oh
foreign
[Music]
are you saying that just because of the
Corn crust
or is it something else
this is the corn crust orange meat
Italians don't have my back I can't
believe it
[Music]
I tried so hard I tried so hard and gone
so far but in the end it doesn't even
matter hmm
[Music]
why don't they like my pizza
no I've been fill the wood well [\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] yeah it wasn't whatever how many
dollars or Euros on the like legit
restaurant quality oven
okay whatever today I'm not trying to be
Italian anyway today I'm trying to be
Korean
Jay I am a Korea boo so it doesn't
matter
what
waffle maker is enough yeah but it's not
a waffle maker though okay I have a
waffle maker this is not a waffle maker
I would know
why do you not have Ramsay living in
your kitchen are you even trying eh
Ramsay would mess everything up in my
kitchen he would just make it everything
worse he doesn't know how to make
Italian pizza either
I know how to make Italian pizza more
than him
the pizza chamber
ah not Versace oh
I want to see
[Music]
where was I
focus focus focus focus focus focus
[Music]
John
um
[Music]
what
Kiana
what I
mean
what a fire bird
[Music]
okay that was on me I'm I didn't read it
right buy a bottle
ah yes yes yes yes yes
Firebird I mean you could have said
Phoenix that would have been a bit more
accurate but at least you could didn't
call me a chicken so that's pretty
decent thank you
[Music]
hmm
[\h__\h]
son
thank you
the one who draw the the thumbnail thank
you so much oh I didn't because I didn't
tweet it properly this time I think I
didn't give credit I have to do
afterwards
I'll put you in the in the description
of the of the video okay
[Music]
but thank you for drawing it I think
it's it was really nice to have this as
a thumbnail very fitting
and mood wise also fitting
um
um genius
[Music]
oh
yay again it's really linguistic genius
I'm trying I'm getting back my
confidence when I was trying to learn
alone I was hopeless but now I'm fine I
think
hmm thank you thank you so much for
drawing me so many times thank you soon
please draw more and more and more and
more
CS Lim and
yeah
for the pinky but that's a really long
text I will put that into Papa cool it's
too long
oh
yeah it's words are different from
Hangouts so they cannot communicate with
Korean KFC employees I felt sorry for
this and learned a new 28 letters and
the chickens were grateful and sent to
protest ah
I learned I learned to learn
I wanted to be able to communicate
better with you guys and give back for
the support you guys gave me since like
last year or last last year even
um
thank you for watching kiwawa please
watch more quinoa okay
not only clips
not only Kitty Nookie
thank you for the support
yeah he could have kicked my Korean in
high gear
oh yeah I want to sing K-pop properly
too yeah
be able to read the lyrics more smoothly
but that will still take some time I can
read them slowly but not not so fast
for the pinky but like even when I read
when I sing Japanese I
I often just sing while looking at
romanized lyrics even though I could
sing but when you sing
you don't want to use your brain too
much for reading so
even for Japanese side yeah
there's no way
[Music]
they added new jeans on to Color Fun
which one new teams
although I can't find it
wait wait new jeans wait wait
slow
huh
wait it's not working
no names
maybe I have to write it in Korean you
know
my kind of fun is not loading
hello
what's your mouse
OMG and ditto ah
okay okay oh my God
I was really hoping that you will come
through don't say anything
London
okay two songs please add more I wonder
if they added new jeans maybe they also
added maybe a new twice song or so
hmm
oh that's that's nice
cute someone's really based in the
cutoff on
yeah I want attention and I want hot boy
please hi boy
I know what you like boy
I can't look like
[Music]
or please I need a
need option to call me as a guest this
year so I can sing Korean songs on stage
because last time I could sing twice
and I can't I can't do that on stream
ironically I can do it on in conventions
and Stage performance please
Korean
cookie Wawa
please please please
pong
yeah so popcorn can we go again please
it was so successful last time but maybe
they want even if they invite us maybe
they invite other Holo Live members or
not me but I wanna sing Korean songs
again please
oh yeah oh yeah I really like uh
Moonlight sunrise
maybe let's do it all night they have a
um another new song though that one's
the English one
and they have set me free
set me free
and they have an English version to that
song too
but the official version is Korean
only old songs for twice yeah please
more what the hell
help I beg you
beg you um
[Music]
congratulating you for the amazing
performance in horror Fest so slow are
you slowpoke it was amazing on both days
and concerts so please keep being
amazing as always Wawa kfp loves you
forever for a Spanish meme can you say
Feliz whoever's Feliz
Feliz whoever
let's say it right
Feliz who are this
what does it mean happy first day why
first dance first day my dudes
yeah thank you thank you so much I'm
glad you enjoyed the concert even though
you're a little bit late on it I don't
know why you want me to say that but you
say like Oscar it's a meme
Burger
Feliz Juarez
happy birthday why
Feliz
like that
I don't know why you have to explain
that one to me
happy birthday
we first say to you I guess whatever
it's been two years Kiana oh never been
committed to anything as I am to you wow
I fixed your commitment issues but I
mean who could resist that sweet but
even sweeter personality you've grown a
bunch and I'm so proud of you I know I
don't talk much but no I'm here till the
wheels fall off thanks
two years also can I get a huggington of
a kiss and let me get that oh free one
one for my chicken number please oh yeah
you can have that I don't know how to I
don't know how to keep hug I don't have
them
I I can give you I can give you um this
behind me
oops
I guess that will do
that we'll have to do
that's the only thing I ever I don't
know where the hug is anymore
[Laughter]
a hug hug the mic
I'm hugging oh wow it actually sounds
like
thank you so much for the support for
two years oh love you thank you wow wow
wow see the difference wow I was like
right on your ear
laughs
it does sound kind of like it wow good
job good job sure sm7b I squeezed the
the the fluffy foam
I'll take it yay
you'll get a kiss anyway
oh that sounded interesting I'm almost
new
friend zone
Duncan uh
um
oh my God
what was that I was holding and then
it sounds like maybe kisses in your ear
thank you for the recipe
oh
red
an
foreign
[Music]
with my microphone
and a pinky from
Jean
are you guys are losing it yum
[Music]
hey
thank you for the pink Super Chat pink I
unlocked something again new new kisses
uh Pink
oh it's just pink
super tattoo
[Music]
and give me that thing
thank you thank you soon
[Music]
uh what for me
under the table each year
[Music]
oh
sure
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah I had eat turtles
you love honey churros
Maybe
I don't know
honey churros I prefer chocolate churros
oh no chocolate
G I have read this one before
and over the table salty soapy
um
what does this mean
are you asking me to go to a gym
champion
and now
no no celery no
no no no
thanks for the pinky that was pink here
the album let's go let's go you will
love it but I mean you love everything I
do right
thank you so much
I hope you guys can get a listen into it
ASAP but you gotta wait more more more
please wait
foreign
oh my God it's a lot of text can I just
put this into Papago as well
otherwise it will take me a whole day to
read this
manager I'm studying English to make
your broadcast more fun how did I study
English I want to be hired or how did
you study English I want to be hired
someday when I have kfp oh I I just
study in school
not any more though for a long time I
was just I think our
teachers know how to teach English very
well in Austria
and so everybody can speak English very
well here
um
it's not so difficult
for us to pick it up maybe also because
it's like
um you know our our first language is
not an Asian language
that's not even it's just that's just
wholesome that's not even horny wow
okay wait I'll get there
I think
if you want to learn more English
then
for me now the one one let's the
one-on-one lessons are really helping me
the private lessons
but if you're done with school then yeah
maybe if you're not satisfied with your
English skill then go get some more
lessons and or go overseas if you can
because if you're suddenly in a
situation where everyone around you
speaks English that's usually the most
ideal
fighting
[Music]
thank you for the support
maximum
thank you
yeah I want to watch your live but in
Korea every man has to go to Army so I
couldn't watch your life for a while but
in Air Force I can use my phone shortly
oh were you first in the normal Army and
now you're like in the Air Force I'll
watch your archive
that's ironic because I feel like you
would be in the sky and then there's no
reception but you're probably not always
in the sky
at least you get to watch me a little
bit thank you fighting fighting
how much longer
how much longer Max came
you're really lucky you can watch today
huh
even got to send the Super Chat wow
it's buying
you're flying right now
don't don't use your phone now it's like
when you drive and then you use your
phone to text message two years
21 months oh I wonder when you started
how much more time
you have
chihuahua has to stream forever so that
everyone who's in the Army now can come
back
to koala wouldn't it be so sad when you
you're done with the Army and then and
then you go home and then there is no
Chihuahua no all alive nothing
[Music]
that would be so sad
I'll try
to stay as long as I can so all the Army
Bros have something to get back to Don't
Cry
oh oh I'm sorry
I know and yet I am sadistically
laughing about it
nice Gordon Ramsay oh
thank you for approving my pizza thank
you soon
[Music]
what is this
oh
that's how you write thank you then
oh thanks sure thank you
I need to put on my training wheels this
is too much for me now oh thank you for
support
thank you
[Music]
on the table
June
but wait no so
[Music]
thank you and Mom son
hey
now we don't need you thank you for the
rest of the chat
yeah that's embarrassing now you're
making this is when I like when I
started giving kisses for the first time
hug the mic tells everyone
's gonna be okay
wow that's like ASMR
oh
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
new power I put some skill points in the
new Power new Talent new skill
s
he's Beyond okay now oh no
I opened Pandora's Box
[Music]
oh okay wait one more refresh and then I
think we're done and I can take a break
and eat something and then I'll see you
for the movie
oh no I have to refresh one more time
laughs
hey Savannah another good thing about
Super Chat ratings you only get ASMR
Kiana and Super Chat ratings can you
believe it
can you believe it and
[Music]
oh new friend Bird friend
or under the table
[Music]
sorry boo
on me
[Music]
any plan starting Korean on the member I
don't think so at the moment because
like
there's not many who are studying Korean
and then even if they're probably on a
different level than me
[Music]
I had the court to travel to Europe and
I'm leaving for Canada
you went to Europe first and now you're
going to Canada or you don't you you
Canada is not in Europe okay
so you you went to that's what you mean
right you went to Europe first and now
you're going to Canada right
oh
they was but I don't know about now was
she at the level I am at recently
I feel like she's been studying Korean
for a while
I'm living for Canada soon to study
English and do an internship just like
you I was studying Korean I would study
hard and watch the stream a lot I love
you
well that's a great
see this is how you can almost guarantee
that you will learn English properly
wrong translation
or maybe the translation is off y'all
but the gist is you're going to Canada
for an internship I think you will learn
muchos muchos English
so fighting good luck with that maybe it
will be a bit scary and overwhelming at
first but I think actually you chose a
perfect place Canadians are known to be
extremely welcoming and nice and
friendly and apologetic
just super nice right so I think you
will be treated very very kindly
actually no need to worry at all yeah I
think so I've never been to Canada but
it's just like everybody says so
everybody says one of the nicest
countries in the world
so I think
um
[Music]
thank you for
you
Han
[Music]
book
s
I don't know how to say that this is the
doubles
foreign
[Music]
I'll hold my breath until you come to
Korea oh no oh no
out it it will take a while I will go
this here though okay
I mean for a vacation but also it's
until
I will I will I will visit maybe and I
want to go maybe in in fall in Autumn
maybe not in summer I don't want to go
in summer
and hopefully besides vacation maybe
Korean Bros can message Korean
conventions and tell them to invite
takanasi Kiara please
can I say it again please contact Korean
conventions and ask for
convention is
we can do meet and greet and we can do
uh
singing on stage
[Music]
yeah please please please please
chunk rain thank you for the pinky thank
you for Korean stream Don't Damn name
I'm looking for your uh Korean version
and yes I think there's a distance
future from today but after singing do
you in Korean do you have any thoughts
on singing you other songs in Korean
people night maybe yeah if you guys help
me actually I still never tried it
before should I try now
uh can someone send me the final version
of the lyrics
I would have to practice I didn't
practice it I'm so sorry
does someone have it like right now
we can try
wait actually I think they made a
YouTube video
with the pronunciation
Kiana do you Korean
here there's a guide
[Music]
now it's so difficult
oh girl you'll know it I just can't
resist you hey baby
[Music]
you know play the game
foreign
[Music]
sure
because it was probably out of sync even
though I was also singing out of sync
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't ever let yourself violin you got
it
thank you
[Laughter]
[Music]
song
if you know play the game baby
[Music]
I'm always coming back to you
soy milk soy milk
[Music]
okay if if I get invited to a Korean
convention this year I will make this
perfect
it really feels like Kpop yeah I will
make this perfect okay and then I'll
perform the perfect version at a Korean
convention
in the end in the end it's just so
[Music]
thank God for the vegetarians
thank you thank you thank you for making
that I'll practice more hmm
looking for the top Junction
what
what the [\h__\h] looking for the tub what
the [\h__\h] does that mean
what
are you doxing my PC
what does that mean
who's that Super Chat mean
now
no no
not for turquoise no no if you want ASMR
It's gotta be more
the new tickets eh eh maybe maybe they
did go go go go
huh
oh someone is trying to say so
new new tickets for
whole life
not yet
where did you get that info
2.5 hours
okay guys be ready
be ready
oh two hours okay okay all right anyway
I gotta prepare it
thank you guys for watching today
thank you and members only later we're
gonna watch
Empire Strikes Back
yeah even though I only watched a movie
yesterday and I had so much popcorn so
much nachos holy [\h__\h]
sometimes like normally when I watch a
movie
I will eat
for the first half of the movie and then
I stop because then I'm not hungry
anymore then I just don't feel it
anymore but this time maybe because the
movie was more like a little bit on the
shorter side
well I just kept eating since before
since the advertisements until the very
ending I was just eating forever I was
really hungry
oh damn
yeah I watched the Mario movie yesterday
but I will not spoil you yet don't worry
but we have to we have to talk about it
so please go watch it please so we can
talk about it okay
um I want to watch it one more time in
like different
there's I think there's a 4D version We
I think we have a 4D version probably
where maybe there's like some the chairs
are moving a little bit and there's like
some air and I'll watch the German
version because I already watched the
the English version in normal Fernie and
I want to watch the um German one
because no it didn't sound so bad and
honestly it was such a good movie I want
to watch it again I was so happy
watching it the whole time I was smiling
it made me so happy and I was surviving
so much the music was so good I was so
hardly vibing
I was in car last week please comfort me
attention to you mean a car accident
car accident crash
ing
can you know
I was I'm okay I guess that makes it say
something else I mean I was vibing
hardly no I was vibing strongly
yeah in the end I really enjoyed the
voice acting even even Peach
um but Chris Pratt was amazing like I
didn't even in the teasers I was still
like hmm but in the actual movie overall
he gets a 10 out of 10 from me
um
I don't know where you're really where
are you or no
oh no you weren't in a car accident you
were in the car so you couldn't watch
until now is that what you're saying
huh well oh well I'm gonna go now I'm
gonna go I'm gonna go gonna go see you
later guys
um bye bye and in German we say happy
nothing
and you guys say oh
[Music]
the person living says
I wonder how you write that in Korean
I would write it incorrectly probably
[Music]