I have this blockage now ever since that
accident that was crazy man yeah the one
of CI really crazy accident that was
terrifying and gave me pts deep on my
life with skiing that's actually
a miracle that I didn't break anything
and in hindsight I wish I would have
broken something that would have been
finally the first time in my life that I
broke something that was the one time
opportunity for me to break a bone in my
body and I didn't I didn't you don't get
it guys you don't get it y'all are
saying that because you probably broke a
bone before but I'm like I never broke a
bone I never had a cast before I want
that let's break some bones sticks and
stones and chains and whips excit me
what