[Music]
YOG
Maki Rock,
Paper, Scissors, Rock, Paper, Scissors, Rock, Paper, Scissors, Good Evening,
Dododo Hololive 4th Generation Kazumaki Watame,
Everyone Today,
This is the Square, Rock, Paper, Scissors Dojo.
Thanks to all of you, we've reached 1 million registered users.Thank you very much.
So today I'm going to play rock-paper-scissors with square rolls, and
I'd like to play Convex 3D.No
, I'm waiting for Convex today, and I'm thinking that it would be nice if
everyone could come and play Rock-Paper-Scissors,
but I was thinking,
Why do I have to wait for Convex?  It
's the second time today, and the first time I
was jealous of that outlaw band, but it's already like that. I wonder if
this pounding in my heart will come again?  I
can't stand this excitement any longer, so I don't have to
wait for the convexity
anymore. But now that I've done it, there are a million people,
so
today I'd like to try my hand at waiting for the convexity. No,
everyone is coming.  It's a little bumpy, but
since I'm asking you to play, Makoto's corner wrap. Now that I've opened a rock-paper-scissors dojo, I
want to play rock-paper-scissors with everyone.
But the BGM is huge, so I guess it's okay.
Can I practice a little rock-paper-scissors with everyone first?
Is it okay? You
can have me try a little rock-paper-
scissors for a moment. Hello, I'm worried that I won't fail because everyone from home came to visit.  I'm so nervous,
don't worry, poop, so you don't make a mistake,
okay, let's practice.For today, I've
created a rock-paper-scissors-rock-paper-scissors system for my breasts, and then we'll
go, everyone. Decide what you're going to serve.  Please,
okay, okay, let's
go, rock, paper, scissors, let's go, let's go, rock, paper,
scissors.  I
did something similar when I was spreading 3D, but this time I did a cat and it came out like
this, and the cotton glasses that came out
were all videos, so it
looked like this.  I
wish I could do my best and come out on top,
but I've been doing a lot of rock-paper-scissors today,
but as an imitator, I
think it's normal for me to win, so if
I end up losing, I'll make an announcement at the end of the stream
on the foot mat.  I'm going to do it above.
Wow, it's simple. I'm
going to ride it for a moment. I'm going
to ride it for just a moment. Now here, I
actually have a leg problem. I'm going to ride it for a little while.
Hey, just a little bit, just a little bit, it
hurts, it hurts, I don't want to do this, I don't want to do this, it
hurts just to ride a little bit,
but the sole of my foot hurts, but it's like this,
hello, hello, please come to the convex today.  If someone
loses, I'll
make an announcement on the cat's ice bot.I
don't want to, but I'll do it.If I win, I'll
make an announcement normally,
so please enjoy it till the end.
Yeah, okay, let's start now. I don't have to
wait. I wonder if someone will come. I wonder if it's okay. I'm
nervous.
But I wonder if someone will come. If they don't, I'll give them a little
something. Everyone, everyone, too. We're
all busy, and we're probably at a loss.  Because, you
know, there might even be a conversation like, ``Who's going to go?'' There might even be a conversation like, ``
Hey, healthy people don't have any pain.''
Eh, I'm a health paid child, but it doesn't
hurt at all. O, the
challenger is a super teacher.
Kaman,
ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo can you speak from Japanese to Japanese?
Okay, uh, I'm a
member of English's Kasuru no Shi.  I
'm Sana, please. It's
nice to meet you. Thank you very much. At first, I
didn't think it was me, but no, I didn't expect you to come.
Congratulations to 1,001,000,000,000,000,000,000 people.
Thank you. Congratulations. Thank you. No, I'm happy.
This is the first time I've talked to Japanese members. The
first time is my senior, and it
's my first time.  I
'm a first-timer, I'm a first-
timer, so please do your best in the Japanese issue.
Thank you
very much. Please teach me next time. English, yes, TEme. English please, Wawaki Pai Waki.
Yes, yes, armpit pie is the best, right? Yes, the universe has turned it upside down.  Rock, paper,
scissors, let's do rock, paper, scissors I know, yeah, yeah, I know, I know, I'll do it, I won't lose, I won't lose, I've already decided Let's do rock, paper, scissors, yes, I'll do it Okay, let's go Rock, paper, scissors
Start rock-paper-scissors
[Music]
Start rock-paper-scissors Pon Pon Go
Pon What did you put out? Pon Eh, uh
Hand ah hand ah paper Kapa hair paper
Paper Yes,
par
lost
Taya Ta
lost Tat you're
so strong You're so strong Sa-
chan Rock-paper-scissors strong  Neaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa list of lang
rock paper scissors from uh ba senpai um I
studied um I studied maki Jakete Jake hai
yea yea live for Wible
Um, it's going to be a live show, so it's hard to rehearse. I understand. Well,
even if it's a rival, it's rock-paper-scissors, rock-paper-
scissors, rock-paper-scissors, bread,
etc. Well, I'm happy,
Sana-chan won.
Sana-chan is unpopular.  To
loose
Wow, let's play rock, paper, scissors again, uh, let's
talk together again, let's talk,
uh, I love you so much, let's talk.  I'm
happy to be able to talk to you, no, I'm happy too.
Thank you. I love your voice and your singing, and when you're kind, you
think it's fun, and you make a mess of it. Thank
you. Let's do a collaboration next time.
Thank you. This will continue to be delicious. I
look forward to your continued support.
Thank you.  Thank you so much! Thank you,
thank you, Senkyu.
[Music]
Thank you, Sana-chan, for coming. Yeah, I
did my butt for the first time. I've seen your debut stream,
but this is the first time I've used my butt.  I'm so happy that
everyone is complimenting me so much. I'd love to do a collaboration. I
lost at rock, paper, scissors, but the pressure point on my foot is
getting closer. It's scary, I don't want it, I don't want to do it. I don't want to do it. I don't want to do it. I
wonder if someone will come and save me.  I
wonder if anyone's going to come. It's going to be bad if we don't win. I'm
asking if anyone will come. We're
losing. We're in trouble. How many people are going to
come?  It's
so scary. Let's believe in fate. Yes,
everyone is a little busy today. There
's a switch, there's a lot of things like that, and there's new things like that.
Oh, the
next challenger
is alive. Everyone who came.  I'm here.
Welcome. Thank you very much.
Welcome to the rock-paper-scissors dojo. It's so gorgeous.
Everyone was
looking at me. Thank you very much. It's
so cute.
[Music]
Hey, if I lose, I get 4 cups.If I lose, I get 4
cups.If I lose, I get 4 cups.If I lose, I get
4 cups.But on the other hand, if I win,
everyone makes the same
move.I don't know what the moves are.
If you can't do it, you can
win, and it's okay to be sure, and the
risk is going to decrease.  I
've decided, I've decided, I've decided, yes, I've decided
But it's only just started to appear This
one is going to collapse I guess it's over I wonder
if it's over I'll do it now It might be in the net now I'm going to
cry, it's going to be rock, paper, scissors
Let's get the sign. Let's win. Let's go. Rock,
paper, scissors start corner roll. Rock, paper, scissors start.
Eshi, wait a minute, what did that say?
Nepo laura
la goo, it's Bogu from Nepo Labo.  Oh,
I got it, oh, I got it. I ca
n't make a profit. I can't make a profit. I'll convert it to "I can't make a profit." I
'm a senior. That's why I'm a senior. Pames
has a really kind junior.  I'm so happy.
Thank you very much for your victory.
Thank you very much. Thank you for being so
busy. I
apologize for the inconvenience. Thank you.
No, Zero Shop was in danger. Now it's time for 5 cups.
Let's drink some water and calm down.
[Music] It's
dangerous, fuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu.  The
challenger has
arrived. Who
is it? Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
Name. The second member of the Hololive family
is Inanis.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you. I'm so happy. No, I
've said that we're going to collaborate with Ina-chan, but it
hasn't been decided yet. Oh, that's right. We'll do something. Let's
do it next time. Let's do it. Hey, what do you think?
I like games, what's up with that
? It's my senior's favorite game. It's a book.
Next time, I'll invite you to tell me the
illustrations you want. Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes. I did it. Of course, I did it. Tell me.  I
want you to teach me how to write ``pi'' from now on, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, please teach me from the basics.  Please leave it to me. I'm
losing, but I
'll play rock, paper, scissors. I'll definitely play rock, paper, scissors. I'll
win. Yes, I'll win.  Let's
play rock, paper, scissors, let's do it. What have we decided to put out? Ah, it's gone. Okay, let's go. Let's go, let's go, rock, paper, scissors. Start rock, paper, scissors start.
Ai, I opened it. I
won.
A
loveloveto, I love you,
I love you, Senpai. Thank you,
yes, I won. I'm looking forward to the live show. I'm so
happy. I'll send it to you.
Thank you for the ticket, I'll
send you the distribution ticket.
Yay, thank you, I'll send it to the book. Yes,
yes, thank you, bye-bye. Bye, bye-bye, Ina-chan, that's
a bit amazing. It's so
cute that this girl is coming. I'm so
happy. Who's the challenger again?  With the results
[Music]
High! Congratulations on the anniversary of your victory.
Congratulations
on the Arigatou-chan. Thank you, thank you.  I
came here because I wanted to play rock, paper, scissors, but this is so funny.
Should we really fight rock, paper, scissors? There's an option not to fight, but I also want to flirt normally. But right now, I'm losing, right? Oh,
well, if I win...  Is there a reward for Wata-senpai
? Yes,
if you win, there will be no rewards.
If you win as much as you can, then you lose.  I
can't announce it if I lose. I'll announce it while hurting my foot. Whoa, what made the decision? Who
made the decision
? It's scary. I get
it. I get it. Ah, then I
win.  Please give me words of love, Yowa-senpai.
Words of love from a senior picture. Yeah, yeah,
if I win, then who wins? If I win, then oh, okay, okay, okay, but
I'm still in love.  You
want to say the words, or both of you.
Yes, either is fine. I'll say it from here. Well, I lost. I
want that. Okay, okay.
Okay, I'll win. Yes, I'm going to win too. I've decided to win. I've decided. I've
decided. Okay.  Okay, rock, paper, scissors,
let's go.
Rock, paper,
scissors, yes, yes, square roll, rock, paper, scissors start.
Makimaki Kinkin Pom Ponchokig
Yo
Kataiei
Congratulations Thank you so much, what do you mean? Ki-chanma Yes, yes, ah, I'm saying that, yes, that's right. Yo, okay, Jesus,
Liebe, what does that mean? Oh, love me in German. So, that's what it means.  Guzabye Bye Tom
-senpai, thank you for your hard work.
Hey, let's collaborate again. Absolutely. Promise,
promise. Thank you for your promise, bye bye bye. Bye. Did you say it in
German? I heard it quickly.  I did
n't understand.
[Music]
Oh, I received a video of Vivi.
Hey, hey. Hey, I hear the
VTR is coming, so the video
starts. Hey, let's go. We're going to start the video.
Jake Chiki It
's time for us to do it all for money. Congratulations on
reaching 1 million people!
Ikaku Drill [Music] Keep up the good work, do your best. Thank you,
thank you.
[Applause]
The two of you
took the trouble to take it from the Cinderella switch and send it to me,
but it's crap. I
lost to Karasui-chan,
but I
wonder if I won against Miko. I
lost again. I lost again. And this
VTR, too.  I didn't see it beforehand,
but the staff sent it to me, and the
management sent it to me, so I just watched it for the first time. Hey, I
lost
again. Oh, I lost again.
Thank you, 3 wins, 3 cups. It's a
good match. It's funny. I was planning on winning more.
But it's
weird, but it's
getting more and more interesting. I think I
lost again in the comment section. I
lost again. As expected of an elite person.
But today I had a live show at Cinderellas,
so I received a gift from two of the best idols.
Thank you. I'm so grateful. I'm so happy. It's getting more fun. It's getting more exciting.  I
wonder if the challenger will come? Can I have a drink? I'll drink some water and take a rest.
[Music] Oh no! I didn't expect him to come out with all his hands. The challenger is coming. Come on! Rock, paper, scissors. [Music]
Whoa, who's who?  Who is this? Who is this? Who
is this?
Fu is my senior.
[Applause]
Fu is welcome. No, it's
rock-paper-scissors right now. That's a no-count. I'm panicked.  I was so
nervous,
thank you so much for coming. The
broadcast was really on time. Thank you.
I'm fine today,
thank you. It's okay. It's okay. Thank you. Yes, it's
okay. I'm happy. Besides,
Indonesia and EL.  Everyone was
contacted by that manager, and
yes, yes, but yesterday, in the middle of the night,
in the middle of the night, in the middle of the night, it became tomorrow,
but I hate how good it was.  I was
wondering if you could
come. It's true, it's coming. It's coming.
Of course I'm happy, thank you. It's
true that I might be a little weak at rock, paper, scissors,
but I lost about 6 times like that in Minecraft.  That's why I
saw that machine the other day, a
rolling rock-paper-scissors device.Oh
yeah, I lost about 6 times on that one.Oh, I
guess I'll let you win this one.What
should I play?
What do you want me
to do? Oh, what if I win? What do I want you to do?
Well, I want you to do something like this on the wall. I want you to do something like that on the wall. It's okay to
play on the wall. If you buy something called Don, what should
I do?  I'll
give it to you, Oa's
confession.
Yeah, okay, oh, I'll win. Let's get serious, too
. Decide what you're going to put out.
Let's go rock, paper, scissors.
Okay, okay, okay, ok,
let's start rock,
paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors, start, start.
Come on,
rock, paper,
scissors, start, start, rock, paper, scissors, start, rock, paper, scissors, start, roll, roll, roll, roll, rock, paper, scissors, pon, pong, rock, paper,
scissors.
One more time, one more time, one more time,
please.Jake,
start, rock,
paper,
scissors, start,
roll, roll,
roll.  Yeah,
yeah, what's the difference between that and that?
Yes, if you ask me, I'll do it seriously, seriously. Yeah,
yeah, to my beloved senior,
thank you for always helping me with my errands.
Thank you for being with me.Thank you for
inviting me to play with you.Thank
you for always helping me when I was lost.I'll love you even more in the next year or two, maybe
three years from now.  I
'm crying, but I
'm crying because I'm so happy.
Thank you.
Thank you for always being there for me. Thank you for always being so good to me. We're collaborating next time,
aren't we? Next time, we're going to sleep together, right?
Well, let's do it in October.
Thank you very much. The rest of you are also waiting,
so maybe you'll come after me. If you
come next time, I'll
be grateful
.  That's good,
wait. If it doesn't come, come again. I
definitely
want it. Let's play
rock, paper, scissors again next time.
Thank you, everyone, for bothering me, Neji.
Hey, I'm so happy that even Iofi came. It was
amazing and everyone in Indonesia
came. Thank you so much for coming. I was
wondering what I would do if no one came. But the challenger has arrived.
Hey, Robo, Robo.
Congratulations to Roboco-senpai.
Thank you, Roboko-senpai. Congratulations to Roboko-senpai as well.
Thank you for your congratulations. Even if you
can't win, go ahead and say thank you.
Yay.  I wonder if it
turned out to be a song like ``Yay Roboko''
Yesterday, I actually posted a song called ``Konohate'' so
please give it a listen Wow Wow
Wow I'm so happy I heard it! Mei Wata is amazing Roboko It
fits your senior's voice.  I don't even know how to sing, my
heart is so full, wow, I'm so
happy, I'm
going to tell you to come soon because I was listening to Ibi's story.  I
forgot all about it.Esuma: I
was so surprised at how kind you were.No, no,
please listen to it, it will also be streamed, so
thank you very much.Everyone was released without permission.I won.I
still don't win,
but I won.  No, I'm sorry, I came here to win,
but I don't mean to win, I actually won quite a bit
in the Minecraft world, right?  It seems that the
same machine lost quite a lot, but Roboco
wins quite a lot,
but it's so good that it's so true.I
got it, but I couldn't get the robot to win earlier.But I also
added a
square drill.  I'm wondering if I should get a reward for sleeping with you,
but is
that okay?I really want it, but if I
buy it, you might give me a deep kiss.
Is it okay if I get a nochis?
I'll go, but I won't give in.
Okay, let's go, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper,
scissors. Tanda's roll, rock, paper, scissors start.  Guho
, it's safe, it's just one more time. It's just started,
so that's right. Let's go. Come on,
rock, paper, scissors lie.
Two rolls and
rolls, rock, paper, scissors, pom pom, chopsticks,
oh, you can say it one more time. What did you do? You gave out. Wow, that's
bad. That's strong. It's strong. I lost again. I
lost. Oh, I still lost. High performance.  Well, it
was a high performance. It was a high performance
final. 4 wins and 4 losses.
But congratulations and thank you for your help. I
wonder if it's going to be a hit.
Thank you. I'm happy. Thank you. Next  Let's
go challenge it. Thank you for the orchestra.
Congratulations again.
[Music] It
's
funny. I thought I was strong at rock-paper-scissors after beating Miko.
But maybe I'm
just normal.  So,
don't be timid.Win, definitely
win.I
wonder if the next challenger has come?
No, it's either, it's either.
[Music] I
can really hear the live show's idol color in
the corner.
Please celebrate. Thank you. Congratulations on reaching 1 million people.
Oh, maybe this too. That's
right. I just spread the word, Wow, senior.
Today, there's a new one at the same time.  Yes, it's the same time. It
's a celebration, so congratulations.
I wanted to see you, but it's just now. I didn't
think I'd be able to see you. I came to see you. So
cute.
Thank you, I'm so happy. What kind of animal is this? There
's a flying bear, and there's also a squirrel, but
yeah, that's amazing. It's a nice match. It's dressed like a bear. It's
not even dressed up. It doesn't look like a bear. It's a bear.  It's a festival, isn't it? The
hairstyle of the one from before that looks like a mine suit is a
sheep room, but that's a bit of a joke.
Yeah, that's what he said.  I'm so
happy to see you all in the same set. I'm glad you came. I'm glad you came. Yes, thank you. I'm glad you came. I'm so glad you came. Thank you very much. I'll
win at rock-paper-scissors, but no. The
festival will win now. I'll win.
Leave it to me.  Please, I've already decided not to
do it.That's right, I've
decided.Then I'll leave it to you.  Rock, paper,
scissors start One roll, one roll, one roll, one roll, one roll, rock, paper, scissors, pop, punch,
punch
[Music]
A, please say it one more time,
Moe, let me say it one more
time.  Well, what did I put out? After a while, ah,
uh,
goo,
goo, I was already
defeated. When I thought back on it,
it might have been a little goo. Maybe it was goo.  It
's okay to lose. It's okay to lose.
You're cute, so it's okay to lose.
Thank you very much for coming. Congratulations on
reaching 100 million. Thank you. Let's
play next time.  Hey, let's go to Okagegistat.
Well then, let's go. Hey, I see,
Manet-senpai was the type of person who could eat at Jiggisu-kan. Or
maybe I should just say that he has a busy schedule.  It's
scary, it's scary, Nechi and Abibi, it looks like some kind of video
has been received. Let's
take a look at the video.
Who is it from? I do
n't know who it is.
I sent out a tiki congratulations on 1 million people
Thank you Sora-
chan Da Sora-chan It's a bit of a video
so I can't have a rematch so I
decided to draw and save.
Thank you, thank you for the video, but it was a Meiji
Restoration mission. I'm so happy. Thank you.
No, how many wins and losses are there now? This is bad.
No, I'm losing. 4 wins, 5 cups. It's a lie. I
'm losing, I'm losing
. It's bad. Yo,
this is bad if we don't win next time.  It's
too late, it
's too late, it's too simple, it's too simple.
Oh, the
challenger has arrived. Hey, good evening,
good evening.
Me-chan Good evening, whoever that is, I
'm Aani Amelfissa, a Holo ID student.
Good evening,
Ani Good evening, Chan, Good evening, Acha.
Thank you
. I'm so happy. I'm losing a lot. Wa-chan, no, it's too bad. Please lose a little.
No, I'm losing. I can't lose.  Ni-chan, yeah, she
won't let me win, no, that's
a little bit, yeah, it's just a little bit of pride.  That's why,
as an
older sister, I see. As an older sister, it seems like you're sleepy. Well, as an older
sister, you seem to be sleepy. That's right, as an older sister, you seem to be sleepy. Well, now that you're sisters, you're right, so
we're like, well, you're going to let us do that. Yeah, no, there
's no bus.  Okay, let's go to a serious game. Let's
go to a serious game. Let's go to a serious game between sisters. Let's go. I've
decided what to serve. Yes, I've decided.
Okay, let's go. Rock, paper, scissors. When will it be?
Rock-paper-
scissors start Roll-paper-scissors start
Roll-paper-scissors Roll-paper-
scissors Roll-paper-scissors-Pop-Pan
Paper-scissor-pan Pan-oh, it's
okay to say it one more time.
What did Mr. Kakumaki put out? I
thought he was good at opening things, but
now he's got some chops.
[Music]
Taare, yada, yada, yada.
Dasan, this probably means you lose. It means you
lose, you lose. Is this a negative thing
? That's
strange, isn't it? It's strange to say rock, paper, scissors, etc. That's strange. It's definitely a dream. It's a dream. Yeah, it's
definitely a dream.  Yeah, I guess I'll go to sleep
, and when I wake up, everything about today will
be gone, yeah, it'll be
gone.
Let's talk
Yeah, it's over now. Let's play. Let's play. Yeah, let's play. Let's
play next time. Good luck, do your best, thank you, thank you. Senkyu, thank you, thank you, Senkyu. Looks like the next person is already here. Who's who, who's here, who's here.  It's here, Name, it's here,
it's here, Rosé is here, it's here, it's
dangerous, it's Buwa
Mukiroze, it's Kama, it's Kakumakija, it's Nemuki, it
's a bit of a legend, so I'm not going to go with this.  The
final boss has arrived, and I'm sure he'll never win. Oh, how
many wins and losses have we had so far? I forgot.  That's what I
thought, but I have 4 wins and 6 cups.I see, I don't know
what to do.I'm sorry,
but I'm still going to explore the stars.I understand.Watana
and Mukiroze, who created that together.
As a bond, yes, Mukiroze will
give out goo.Okay,
this is the first time, I got
it.I understand.I don't understand.It's that goo, so
yeah, it's goo.Without it, it
's a ceremony.  Because it's a joke, I
already know whether I win or lose.Okay, okay, okay, I got it.I probably got
it.Okay, let's go.Yes, let's
start rock-paper-scissors.
Start corner roll, rock,
paper, scissor start corner roll, roll, roll, roll, roll [Music] Rock, paper, scissors punch.
Power, I
think which one wins.
Rose, yes,
even if I win, I simply
lose. Dashi loses. That's where I want you to win a little bit.
Even if you make a hole
and you make a par, it's
unlikely because it will shatter your par.If you dare to
play a chip, you will also be crushed.A
forced loss event is coming.
No, but thank you for that time. No, no, I'm grateful for that. Thank you
for this event. Thank you for
not giving up. I'm looking
forward to it. Thank you. Let's do our best. Let's
play. Let's play. Promise. Promise to come.
Thank you for your help. I'm sorry for bothering you. Thank
you for your help. I'm
here. I couldn't beat Rose. I
never thought the final boss would come. I
guess we're going to have to close down the dojo. It's such a wonderful place.  Hey, can you hear me?
Who are you? Hey, how many shoes are you
walking in? Oh, hey, hey, hey,
do you know whose room that room is?
Well, now that I think about it, there's some corn, and
some tea, and some pots I
don't really understand.
Look, I
didn't do anything related to Nan-chan, so I thought it was a good idea to do it.  I feel
bad for losing so much Natsuki-chan, I feel bad
for Natsuki-chan if she wins against Shiraga.  I
was thinking of doubling the points, but
then I heard a voice from heaven telling me that I was sure to be punished for being such a loser.
Yes, it's confirmed, but I'm still in this
state, Netsumaki-san.
Yes, whether I win or lose, you
're the loser. If I win, there won't be 100 million cases.
100 million, right?
Mr. Tenno.  What do you think of 100 million books?
100 million wins, 100 million wins, 100 million no,
so it's hard and tough. Do you play rock, paper, scissors? I
'm losing, but I'm
losing, or I'm already playing a punishment game.  Yes,
yes, I'll just let you know. Yes, I'll
accept it. Yes, I'll accept it. I'll
come again. I understand. Please come back again.
Yes, it's there. What do you
have? There's a foot pressure point mat. There
's a foot pressure point mat.  Nema: It's
boring to just stand on foot pressure points,
so it
seems like there's going to be a Nemane concert soon, so when you
think of idols, it's step.  I see, it's a
nice rhythm.
Let's announce it while shaking your hips from side to side. That's
right. That's right. So that's how you're going to do it. Is
this really an idol step? Yes, please
shake your hips in a cute way. Shake your hips.  It's
squeaking left and right. That's right. That's
it, then please let me know.
Please, if you can't say it, please. It
hurts. Yes, it's time. You have to
stand for a while. There's a 10.  It's
getting old. Goodbye.
October 12th
. I don't save any fast live performances. I'll reduce the number of live performances.
[Music] I
can't remember.
[Music]  ]
It's 18 o'clock, 18 o'clock, 18 o'clock. It's 18 o'clock. You can
get off. It hurts so bad. No, you
can't get off. You can't get off. You're losing.  I
'm practicing hard, practicing singing, so
if you'd like, I'm selling streaming tickets.
Please buy them, please. It's just plain painful.
This is it.  I got it, so everyone's okay. I wish I had
gotten through the announcement properly. I would have understood if I had gotten through to this
one. Some
people said, "I'm sorry, I just found out that you bought it."  Thank you very much yes
So yes, when I open the Nemamo Dojo,
please submit an application to Shiragami.Yes,
there is still an application.There is still an announcement.Can I
get off?No, this is not
okay.Why next?  Sui-chan's
live performance is coming. Sui-chan's solo live performance
will be held on October 21st. It's
Sui-chan who sent me the VTR. It's
not a VTR, it's her solo live performance on October 21st.  We
have it, so if you, Su-chan, please
join us and buy it, I'd be happy if you could join me and buy it.And I'm
going to make a big announcement every day.And
today's announcement, the biggest announcement,
is goods to commemorate 1 million people.  However, I
made a stuffed animal, and it
hurts to be in the middle of the day.This
one is currently in production, so
please look forward to future information.I
think it will be released around next year, so
please look forward to it.
Yeah, I took the cotton stuffed animal today,
so I guess the second one is coming. But I thought I'd do a slightly different kind of test.
Yes,
please, I'm running out of time.
But...  Rainbow Uwame's picture isn't coming out anymore. It
's Riso Rainbow, right now. It's
being shown on premium from 10 p.m.,
so please watch it after the broadcast ends.
Thank you for listening to Rainbow.Thank you.Composed
by Deconina.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Is that
enough?I'm off.It's okay.Well
then, thank you too, Ho-chan.Today,
no, thank you, no, I did my best.I'll try
to win next time.Thank you.  You
can borrow here again next time. You can borrow it again. I've
borrowed it and you've given me permission, so next time I
'm going to wait 24 hours.
Thank you very much.
Let's do it for Christmas, let's do it for Christmas.
Hey, let's do it together. Shall we wait together? Let's do it together. Let's
wait together. Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you everyone and everyone who watched.
Thank you very much.
[Music]