[Music]
thank you
questions
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
Christmas
[Music]
ES
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hahaha
chicken again
[Music]
and wow
big
[Music]
it's about right and I see a little bit
of gray on the left
[Music]
a little bit bigger all right this is so
cute thank you
I did not forget about the props this
time that will be gym yeah the game has
a little bit of a bgm right now but it
will stop
it's ten thousand dollars
it will stop in a moment
because generally I think we always
played our own bgm because it's kind of
like nothing going on otherwise
hi
hi Mario it's too loud I don't worry
like when the video
ah hello thank you for making the cute
assets look I am the artiste wait a
second
water pouring
[Music]
ah yes I am the artist
wow so elegant wait what
since when is there so much
bgm in the game
that makes no sense
okay we can play that for a while
until you decide
[Music]
you you don't wanna
play for me anymore
[Music]
actually a bit more quiet
oh I exited
I canceled
[Music]
okay
Jazzy
yeah now it's a full ground music
foreground
[Music]
thank you for adding wasn't me don't
thank me I didn't I don't I don't decide
actually what goes on this because
they're made voluntarily
by my fans and oh sure they come up with
all kinds of crazy
oh
[Music]
wow okay you do you microphone you do
you well we haven't played this in a
while
I move my stuff around keyboard go back
is
tablet come closer
because today
I'll be looking a lot over to the side
which means
there we go okay I calibrant myself that
when I look at the tablet
I'm actually looking straight
nice
[Music]
Olivia's Olivia's pixel stuff is so cool
like
sometimes when I collab with girls
it's often the first time that they see
the loading screen
or any loading screen that I have
yeah and then they're like whoa what
cause normally you know
they don't see that part I mean even if
they would peek into my stream they
would probably peek somewhere in the
middle of it and then they don't notice
the the loading screen
yeah
already ending screen yeah
in the recent holiday was Empire said
that she really likes my ending screen
oh and I was like oh oh but it's been so
old I kind of want to change it I've
been thinking about changing my ending
screen
[Music]
somebody got confused with the giant
booty Dapper I mean I mean I mean I also
am confused by it it's it's it's
generally confusing not only to you know
newcomers
what is going on
yeah
what was that sound just now
we haven't played in a while I don't
even know what's going on like what am I
what does the game currently want me to
do they need to implement like a list of
quests that I currently have
George
ah he still bugged out with the pothole
[Music]
too bad
he's not approachable I remember that we
did this like
long Quest
some long quests remember yeah yeah with
the back and forth it was like RPG Quest
and then we opened up this new area that
was super far
did I wearing my teeth
back give it to me give what to you
Citgo
uh can you explain again
that's sick okay
maybe we should start by drawing that
but no
I don't want to put that much effort
into it
[Laughter]
uh
yeah I'll paint on this map
oh no see I was trying to sell it by
accident no I didn't do anything
what did you say
well I would have been interested
because she was freaked out I would have
been interested in seeing what she said
about it
okay close that
let's draw a sicko on top of this
Phoenix
Lower Town yeah yeah we already know
more than that I wonder if you get the
map now
oh I stopped moving
my cold resistance equipment yeah if
that happens too often I have to do
something about it
my app crashed
app
what was I saying
I wonder if you get the map later if it
will give you
a map that shows the other districts
okay here we go I'm back
[Music]
I hope you have fun with the game well
we'll see I I as a warm up we will do
something else
something with not too much uh
hell
yeah okay I
I understand can you guys give me a
moment unfortunately I have to do
something
like radical
it'll take a moment
at least here let me
let me do something then it considers me
already painting right
therefore more time
on the painting and then and then that
means
I will get more no but actually we're
not selling this one right we're doing
it for a quest so it doesn't matter
I am installing I'm installing new new
version
of application
which also unfortunately means that I
probably have to put the accessories
on again Highway and down
[Music]
take your time boss thank you
see now bgm is like
just
a string of uh
what do you call the big ass violin
you call that again cello
cello
oh yes oh my God I got it right
yeah a string of a cello or contraverse
is that the same thing thing
contrabass
cello fancy name for controvers maybe
oh it's ah
look
[Music]
I
know ah wait I'm loading I'm loading
we're not working I updated
eh
I updated you
are you aware of that
all I've crashed wonderful again one
more time I will I will drill you
until you work I help
I hope that
oh I think it works
I think it works
for sure
okay
uh I'm ready to show my face again
well I'm small there you go Maybe
like these
is back
let's hope that there will be no more
crashes
and no more freezes
please I beg you begging begging you
know
[Music]
bagging begging you okay a sick sick
painting
oh
why not why not working there you go
okay sick
sick they say I have an idea
[Music]
okay see now we need bgm
it hurts
now when you beat them until they get
louder again and then we I guess we
change your mind you're pretty sick
right now oh no any sick kfps here
I might keep changing though
[Music]
the window there we go
I'm sick as really really
mistake mistake not sick I'm sick
bad cold I'm sick with legume
black that's our Return of the flag um
that is unfortunate I I hope that it
will get better for you
soon
and for that cause
I'm going to draw
thick kfp Champion although I should
have done the background first
[Music]
you guys gonna be in the pink room
because it's cute
some paper I didn't see the crack it's
folded oh
actually hopefully she doesn't mind
[Music]
if she has any problems with it
well
how about blue bed sheets
thinking and eating chicken soup to
cures oh no I was gonna just make him
sleep
[Music]
on the bed
and then
a picture frame
of me
[Music]
I mean that's what all of you have right
on right above your bed
right
[Music]
we didn't get well soon gws
so this is two paintings it's a painting
section because there will be a painting
of me
you have a mural on the ceiling
happen
oh
[Music]
oh I'm so proud of you oh my God
congratulations you can do it
keep keep doing that
[Music]
this is something to be proud of
um you always pray to you Kiana Shrine
really I want to see that I want you to
record
um a video of your ritual
so now it is just an egg
so in case you guys are sick eggs
just take a screenshot of this and
basically now it's still a painting of
you
so because chicken thick the red thingy
is is hanging down am I not moving
[Music]
okay I'm moving again you you I swear to
God
wait
I I am confused
turn that down
moving I'm moving
range problem
no I'm not far away but maybe
it lost a track of me it could be
because I'm looking too far to the left
okay chicken
[Music]
I want you to be very round can you do
that for me
[Music]
with this I like to pronounce the
thickness
of this chicken
because the blanket goes up over here
hey
hello
okay that was no it wasn't the range
it's just the app being absolutely
shitty today
yeah
okay
where face oh my God it keeps on
stopping
I'm gonna have to use the other app but
then I can't use a smile my beautiful
assets didn't this the last time this
was so annoying and what happened
was I think also on the past part two
stream and then I was sad that I
couldn't use my assets
I think
useless useless
at least we have a backup
[Music]
always look on the bright side of life
and then this one
[Music]
oh my God
I am not who I should be
thank God I didn't accidentally show
s
uh yeah okay
[Music]
okay
Chihuahua change clothes too
why not
I'm sorry blue I can't use your eyes and
I will use it in the proper drawing
stream sometimes how about that
[Music]
hello hello
yo
okay
now Focus
Focus
foreign go back here
glasses is what I'm going too much okay
okay
[Music]
I was just gonna have your eyes closed
but
but then I don't know
it will feel so lifeless let me give you
a little bit more PN
see make you sad I'm gonna make your
sand
wait do I have some gray no
okay it's really it's really bright
uh dark gray by the way
why must we suffer I would have been
that thinking nothing I mean I think
when you're sick you have your eyes
closed a lot but uh sure
and what the
[Music]
and now because you have a fever I make
you very pink
and a little
I only see this in anime I don't see
anyone doing this in real life except
maybe in Japan
but like you know the thing that people
put towels little towels on your
forehead
[Music]
I don't understand that
um
you do that I really
you guys do not
[Music]
okay then then I don't feel like too
much of a faker
doing this
you're a little
[Music]
or it might even be a cooling pad who
knows
only when you have a really bad either
where it seems like this chicken does
[Music]
oh but now he looks kind of Happy
and because because even when he's sick
he's looking at his Wawa
[Music]
oh
see I'm putting out the feathers so it
looks like he's holding his blankets
his own thing is blanket isn't he cute
was there something missing to my
chicken is there something that I forgot
I think
but will she really accept this as sick
maybe not we will see
um
maybe maybe sick
because she says sickle she said sickle
and maybe that means there needs to be
some green in it
we'll just fake it
with the green and hope that that means
sicko for her
he wobble on a green screen
I don't have
um all the red colors but oh well
kiwawa on the green screen incoming
[Music]
yo I can never use screen whenever we do
something you know recording
um and they're like okay
we need you to use green screen for this
we will green we will chroma key you out
afterwards
okay I always let out a big sigh
that's me
hold on
[Music]
because
in my default outfit I have all the
colors
and it's really difficult
and then my other outfits also are often
quite difficult
one
I you can't green screen you can't uh
purple screen it blue is also difficult
because look at my my choker uh at like
light blue and dark blue pink doesn't
look uh orange doesn't work yellow is
you would think maybe that works but
yeah there is some yellow in my feathers
as well kind of my feathers already take
away so much oh and there's red in my
glasses but didn't really read uh you
know in my mouth and all that so yeah
black see black I've tried before my by
myself in OBS when for some reason I
just could I couldn't use the
transparent function that we have
thank God we have that thank God we have
that
and in OBS it worked kind of well but
when I when I had someone else attempt
that for me I think they used
um you know an editing software they
said it doesn't work
even when something works for me
it seems like it doesn't work for them
it's weird
um
now what I'm thinking often for these
recordings they're like
um
they're like uh meant to be
wonderful thermometer look like let me
look it up
often I'm feeling like it's meant to be
for like promotion so maybe they would
want me to be in my default outfit
and then my favorite my feet my favorite
outfit my my default outfit really has
like everything so
I'm like sure I can do that but you're
gonna suffer when trying to edit this
good luck with that
even the official the whole life
official Channel
tried it and they also failed
remember that program where they had me
on uh with then I think it was Lena and
uh someone else it was that the one with
the three people and and we were telling
stories was it Louis yeah we were
telling stories and I was wearing my
dandel in an official program for the
first time
and uh my
[Music]
my eyes were like losing its color they
probably
[Music]
I know what they did there I don't know
what they did there because I don't
think we even used uh green screen but
who knows what they did
yeah who knows okay this is the thing
but I thought that was too thick but
that's the smallest I can go that's why
we need like bigger canvas for like
pieces where we're serious about it
[Music]
um anyway how's that Chihuahua looking
low low low
effort kiwawa
does does it look like me I guess I'm
missing the feathers
I never forgive anyone who forgives my
feathers if you forgive my feathers I
cannot forgive you
where's the blue
where's the yellow
you can barely see that at the beginning
of it because of the green screen it's
very dark
big Wawa a young party that looks young
and party to you
really
I always was an artist because I always
had an artist beret
what was I saying did I finish my whole
anecdote I wanted to say that you know
I'm trying to use uh the default outfit
for like
purposes where I feel like they want me
to look you know official recognizable
even though I'm not a big fan
um but yeah you know you do what you
gotta do
[Music]
okay this is cute
maybe open mouth whatever
[Music]
okay
you thought is your favorite thank you
foreign
okay
uh yeah we said we're not gonna put too
much effort into this so this is okay uh
sickle chicken
if she doesn't take it I will sell it
but so far I feel like the quests they
always took whatever I gave them
[Music]
okay
wait here we go yes yes oh yeah she's
posting it on her social media
likes 2014
[Applause]
listen to the comments
so sick oh my God that's so sick plastic
move signal now that's exactly that's
you guys you guys are sick
[Laughter]
people really love the sink chicken
nine four thousand four hundred and
seventy likes I would say we got this
wait no the Australians
uses reverse tactics he just posted a
stick figure and got four bags
oh when someone puts even less effort in
but gets more come on is it ironic is I
will need a new stick it's so confusing
and but my my sticker was pretty ironic
though
this was not in my calculations time's
up how
it's a place
scripted
okay I got my money though
right and the stupid print of the post
with the most likes
oh
can I
why don't you give me that can I sell it
that's
that's the sickle
wait are you guys seeing this
wait
let me show you
so if this got so popular on the
internet we should sell it then that
looks like something Iris throughout
we should selling see how much it makes
but ironically it would be let's see
what no okay Gabrielle this says change
I think the game recognizes when you
just put out something that you didn't
draw
oh
[Music]
um
how about her does she also know
where is the love my sick chicken had
love
okay no problem
let me see if there was another Quest
that we kind of accepted and didn't do
um
so I guess they're all upstairs maybe
let's go draw a cap onto it
I think I'll just use the the canvas and
completely draw something else on top of
it
Prince Charles
endorsement
not so quick first I need to see your
potential someone may have accidentally
done some damage to one of the
chantelle's paintings
I believe it God's in the way of some
flying yogurt those things happen you
know luckily on men's 2 escorted out
safely without her nose perhaps you
could restore it so I mean the person
who's damaged it doesn't lose his or her
face
you're saying you just want me to fix it
so
so you don't see the yogurt
Cupid's art
gastro thank you that's out of nowhere
thank you thank you I'm glad you like it
yeah I guess I mean pitch I don't know
am I should we try to just get rid of
the stains and then
give it to him
and then we can draw you know
something we actually like
[Music]
like a whole life member
on their own just for the sake of money
guys I
I could watch look great for some reason
because they only like I thought the
first time I checked it two days ago I
thought it had more than just two
episodes I thought they saw it
I was like oh I'm just gonna watch two
now and more later I saw that the upload
dates I I'm not imagining it I'm not
hallucinating
we saw the upload dates it all said I
think 12 12 May
and then last night I checked and it was
gone it only had two episodes the ones I
watched
and now I'm confused because when I
looked online if I could if I could find
any
info on it
there was nothing
nothing
[Music]
late no no no that would already be
finished I'm pretty sure
[Music]
going to delay it but
um did I hallucinate Maybe
tonight
[Music]
right I'm pretty sure I saw it
in the end I just
fell asleep to Seinfeld again
oh my God what's with his eye
overall getting darker I think than it
was this whole painting someone punched
his eyes
oh it's so hard that it even turned
yellow
[Music]
red
there we go
we'll have 10 episodes yeah what the
[Music]
why why would I I'm watching it on um I
think it's called MGM Plus
they just changed their name apparently
and the first two seasons were not on
MGM on within Amazon
in another thingy another subscription
thingy and for me now
um the third season was not on that it
had to be within Amazon but on a
different subscription thing called MGM
plus and I swear I swear I saw it and if
Hulu has it
doesn't that make sense maybe it was
like bugging out
because Hulu has the episodes 10
episodes which I think is all of them
pool has it then I think maybe
maybe what I saw was real after all
actually we had this once where the
quest Giver was like hey this is not
enough so I think with like the the lady
in the in the really big mansion so if
if this is not okay they will tell us
[Music]
but I will give it to him like this
and that's not what he wanted
yeah subscription I think they're um on
purpose nowadays having like so many
subscriptions even subscribe to
this one
because Amazon Prime is already a
subscription and if you have Amazon
Prime you can watch a couple of shows
and then you need more subscriptions
unbelievable
[Music]
hmm
simultaneously eating a burger hamburger
oh more restoration
a tiny catch a bathroom
okay
[Music]
what so is the the red in this
Apollo you call this artist who draws
like this Pollock because I think it's
actually kind of cool
I wonder what the technique behind it is
because it doesn't look like just some
random splashes
[Music]
Jackson Pollock
I didn't know that person
DaVinci who
Polo cool let me look it up
[Music]
Jack Jackson wow
uh yeah some of his fans are over the
top
just too much I like the more simple
ones
oh
wow no most of those paintings are over
the top
in my opinion
at least from looking far away if you
look closer
I would I would say okay it's it's nice
to look closer but often you will walk
into a room and if you're like 10 meters
away from it and it looks well then
I think you already lost
the red represents the ketchup right so
are we getting rid of that then we have
orange blue and black
I I will just
do this for the sake of progress in the
game
[Laughter]
uh what kind of Finn
orange blue
with a nice blue like this
[Music]
yeah I am maybe but not Pollock
hey hey
[Music]
holocard
yeah yeah that's me that's mean
we're done I didn't spend so much time
on it
[Music]
oh okay I just realized I have no idea
how this type of art is supposed to look
would surely be this she can't tell the
difference either very well this is the
last one okay okay
[Music]
ah how this last painting got damaged
it's quite a mystery someone seems to
have mistaken the painting for our
coaster such a shame it is one of
Chantel's most precious oh what's this
next one
[Music]
the Mona Lisa is what you're trying to
tell me
Chantal painted the Mona Lisa
really
[Music]
and then you I think it's you you use it
as a coaster
it looks like a print to me
[Music]
this is difficult to restore
but I shall try
oh scary
oh dear
[Music]
at least like most of this painting is
so dark
it's kind of black
it's really hard to cover with a sponge
I wonder
if that's on me or if that's on the
painting
[Music]
you just gonna make it really really
dark in the room okay
[Music]
this one I have a Twist in mind for this
one
foreign
[Music]
guys
dark brown black brown brown
because like everything's so dark in
this painting right so it might it might
have been
um Brown
dark brown black
that Browns is their whole life member
with dark brown hair
remind me kindly
I wouldn't say it's dark brown
yeah dark dark brown yeah yeah I think
so
[Music]
let me check someone always looked more
like black hair to me but you might be
right oopsie
[Music]
yeah that could work
Subaru with long hair
it has an outfit with long hair
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah she looks very
sophisticated in that so she couldn't
very well been the model for the Mona
Lisa don't you think
[Music]
okay perfect
I found my I found my Mona Lisa
I don't just I just don't really have
the right tools
to make it look
more
like you know I originally painted this
I'm still gonna try to keep up the
charade of it being
[Music]
with being a realistic painter a
painting
boss art restoration gone wrong gone
viral
wait
[Music]
have you guys never thought of Subaru
as the Mona Lisa
[Music]
I have opened my eyes to it
oh my God it's so difficult
to draw this
the lack of pixels
[Music]
is disturbing oh my God
I can barely barely draw
and maybe maybe I should go home for
this because I have more tools at home
and let's just have a long path to come
back here
ah
[Music]
on the way we could see if there's still
some tools I haven't bought because I
certainly got the money
um
[Music]
oh okay
okay
[Music]
um
I want a fin
one maybe the autograph pen could get
pretty thin some some tools are like
kind of locked
in the minimum size
maybe this one isn't because it's
supposed to be really thin
I'll add the white brush
um
that will do for now
[Music]
um
no I'll keep the sponge I'll send by the
plane forever I'll take the autograph
them as soon
[Music]
okay
let's see how they work and maybe I can
draw my Cuba Lisa better this way
[Music]
oh yeah okay
I think the autograph pen is really tiny
I think
[Music]
I mean it's now okay it's not that tiny
but it's okay we'll make it work
[Music]
accuracy I'm hoping for it yeah but the
sound
yeah cause we're using uh what's it
called
um I know it's called autograph pen here
but I mean
and Tintin's uh
in
my language
now we're using the light brush okay
okay
[Music]
what a fancy name
foreign
[Music]
should we change her clothes too
but then won't it look like barely like
her
hmm
[Music]
oh it's
um
when I draw on this left side
it gets really thin it's like realistic
wow
[Music]
realistically angled
we need to do something about her eye
but the crayon gets really thin too oh
yeah I thought so but actually it's
pretty pretty thick
[Music]
okay I mean you guys are looking at it
smaller than me
and I think it still looks like the Mona
Lisa
[Music]
thank you
wonderful
no one will notice
everyone will accept this
as their new Mona Lisa
but it doesn't look like Subaru yet of
course I know I know
[Music]
um
the Hat
[Music]
maybe just a hat
but in this outfit she has a blue
brain
[Music]
how French of her
how very French oh Shantae
[Music]
if you are just joining the stream now
I will have you know that I painted this
from zero
it was all on me
[Music]
I'm gonna make it a bit dirtier
it can't the whitest color can't be so
so bright you know
brightest color can't be so bright
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
well you know
if I if I weren't so humble
I would I would probably lose my mind
and and I couldn't be this flawless
artist that I am today
[Music]
I just like to give back to my people
yeah I would like to help I would like
to help people with my art
and and I am absolutely
enthusiastic
seeing how you guys are
[Music]
so so
in love with me and my art I can't
possibly can't possibly accept
the 50 million dollar that you are
offering for my Mona Lisa
no
impossible how could I
[Music]
think sorry I'm late boss no problem
we're just chilling I put out the
schedule did you see guys
new schedule
this week of course of course we are
playing more
more
um
he oh take cat
oh CK
oh TK
and yeah Humanity actually I I didn't
even know about this game until
management was like Hey look at this
game
[Music]
but it looks funny
doesn't it
was like hmm
I'm gonna give this a try
[Music]
basically you try to control Humanity
thank you
by making packs for them and then you
let thousands and thousands of them die
probably but
you're trying to help them
[Music]
with the dog yeah yeah there was a dog
yeah
I never played Lemmings but
saw you guys uh comparing it to it no no
black and white unfortunately I love the
black and white
[Music]
your eyes
there needs to be in more colors
I would say
[Music]
does that look like Subaru
okay
I understand I understand what my
mission is
foreign
we must make it look more like our model
like our inspiration
so I will I will make that come true
[Music]
I hope they won't notice
Raffles this is like her her casual her
cute casual outfit so you know it has
some Raffles and it has more Ruffles
here
but all around the Mona Lisa you know
the painting has such a so many brown
tones I should probably try to
recreate that
why new job will be art restorator
wait what
a restaurant what
[Music]
the dog is from the game not from me I
don't have dogs thank God
[Music]
restoration yeah I'd restore uh art
restore conservative something like that
yeah
[Music]
it's basically what I'm doing right now
so let me apply for a job and then for
you know my examples of work I've done
so for my references I will show them
this
that would be a prank
[Music]
oh that would be quite a prank
yeah so I've actually been in charge of
restorating the Mona Lisa I don't know
if you've ever heard of her but you know
yeah yeah that was me
thank you
that was indeed me
if I'm ruining this piece now
it is only for the sake
of Subaru senpai
oh God
oh
[Music]
I did
hey croissants responsibility yes you're
going to work now I
just started streaming
actually oh it's been an hour already
has it
well thank you for coming you mean
improved improved
I saved it uh sure okay guys okay okay
yeah sure
I need more
I feel like I should bring out my
[Music]
my monochrome palette but oh well
you know but it's just dark in here you
know
that's why it looks pretty dark I don't
know what that comes across well
wait I'm gonna go get some more colors I
need the monochromes
that brown Hue I don't need it I'm
gonna go monochrome
[Music]
some of these Grays actually have some
brown in it too I feel like
[Music]
okay
Mona Lisa didn't skip arms day
well no she just she's just wearing very
fluffy fluffy moves
[Music]
I'm still not happy with these brushes I
want something that actually feels like
I'm painting with acryl
so far
I have yet to find something that like
that
I wanted to blend in more nicely
ah
but the the light brush takes like so
long
to do something
hmm
okay whatever
waffles
[Music]
I'm gonna
strand her hair oh actually
I should use the watercolor but the
watercolor is so Random
I know if you can see okay it does give
up a nice effect
um
this is kind of random it just goes
wherever the hell it wants
Mona Lisa but she's a JoJo character
because
my God I didn't watch JoJo but I think I
can tell that this this this is not no
no
[Music]
no no no no
besides the schedule I also updated my
playlist I finally made playlists for uh
tltk and some other things and I made a
playlist that is like
something you can show
someone's like hey I I am interested in
Chihuahua please give me something that
I can get started with if I want to
watch her streams
so for that I made a playlist that
consists
only of like
one-off games
or games
that I only played for like one stream
or games that don't really have a story
you know
and compiled it I went all the way back
to the very very start
of my
days
um
and it's called zero commitment playlist
yeah
because this is a zero commitment
playlist
[Music]
so feel free to use it guys
you are encouraged to do so
foreign
name right
but then if you feel like committing to
me you're always welcome to do so
[Music]
I think now it looks kind of like super
interesting but don't you agree
yeah very much so
nice
[Music]
the Red Ribbon is still missing
how long is this uh
um
[Music]
okay
that's kind of right
there's something darker
brown tones always work wow
what a ribbon looks good
Maybe
[Music]
that's the beginning of her skirt I
could still draw that but I need some
more blues for that like dark Blues
the dog is from the game guys
dog is in the game oh do I not have dark
clothes okay
challenge accepted
Richard thank you yeah I don't know I I
I was going I was going for my recent
videos and I I was making playlists for
you know the series that I've been doing
like Hotline Miami and all that and I
was like damn what about all these like
small games you know that I've only
played for one stream and they're all
not getting a playlist even though
they're good streams too I always felt
like making a playlist for that so
I finally do dude
[Music]
oh
it's kind of nostalgic I went for all
the videos I looked at all the fountains
looking at that it's like looking at a
gallery
of like history of takanashi kiwawa
I can recommend it guys it's like a
museum you could do it too
let me fix her fingers here
I've gone through looking for stuff
before
[Music]
every stream is like two hours long one
bit is like a playlist now two hours
very short I mean okay if you're if
you're not able when you're being
introduced to me to watch like you know
a little bit of a two-hour stream then
okay you're just not made for this
channel in the first place but okay okay
I have for that I have even shorter
videos you just don't go to the live
section you go to the video section
and there's like you know mostly clips
or order YouTube shorts whatever
either either the live section or the
the video section or the short section
I follow a really really small hunger
appetite
[Music]
see I'm gonna make her her hands even
more delicate
[Music]
okay that's kind of scary
I want to make them realistic
[Music]
thank you
oh sheesh my shading game today
is top notch
just gotta cover up all this
all these white blocks man
[Music]
marvelous
doing pretty good job thank you start
watching a lot more ever since the GTA 5
series thank you yeah man that's so
nostalgic
uh
good times good times
I hope they release GTA 6 live in my
lifetime man
please
I'm begging you
gosh her arms look so puffy but I mean
it's not my fault I was I just drew over
over the Mona Lisa what can I do
foreign
[Music]
over pretty much everything at this
point I might as well
paint a little bit over the face
carefully
[Music]
move it out so that we don't see her
pores
all the time
[Music]
she's getting airbrushed guys
wow like a supermodel oh
[Music]
I think it's hard to see for you guys
the difference is there
[Music]
interesting
she does not have originally she doesn't
have collar bones or anything like that
here I added a little bit
can we zoom in you want to zoom in you
can zoom in
a little bit of a zoom in function I've
noticed but like if you
oh I think only if you're like on the
phone
can make the the wide screen fill out
your phone
why does the Mona Lisa have no eyebrows
or does she actually do and I just got
rid of them
oh
excuse me I mean the the sugar Lisa
she does it right or like really she
pencils them in usually
you talk as if you know her
okay let's give her eyebrows then
um but
um
[Music]
they're kind of bushy
they kind of bougie
okay okay
[Music]
came into the stream 10 minutes ago or
five minutes ago
question for you
who does this remind you of
Doesn't Remind
quality
John Cena
in scientific duck
really really are you saying that and
you just arrived or are you saying that
because you came in here an hour ago
Chris Pratt
Lisa
hopefully Donald Duck hmm
female Yago
it's me
[Music]
he's pretty cute man
I'm fixing her lip because she got like
a white blob there too
thank you
she's got pretty lips
I've never realized this
looking at Mona Lisa uh
okay I wonder if they're gonna be angry
if the other blobs are still there so
let me let me carefully
[Music]
get rid of them
darker no dark Blues no dark greens
what's what's up with that
what is up with that
have to do it myself man
okay I think I'm pretty done with it
[Music]
foreign
gorgeous
[Music]
I love her
I want to show this to somebody what
will she say
[Music]
I wonder if she's still awake what time
is it in Japan pretty late I don't think
somebody stand by sleeps that late
cute
foreign
[Music]
can I rename this yes
should
ah I can't type my tablet is partially
on top
I want to look at the progress really
quickly
uh we're seeing we're seeing
I'm here
let's look at this
[Music]
uh-huh
wow
yeah it's starting to take shape
I'm fixing it
it's a difficult job but no problem for
kiwawa oh
[Music]
we just thought we decided to do
something with the cloves after all
we're fixing the hands
and now some more detail on the face and
skin wow and the background and there we
go
legendary work thank you
I'm gonna send this to Savannah senpai
okay let's go bring this over
I put too much
that's supposed to put effort into Quest
drawings it's a waste of my time
we saw they also just take some
scribbles
no problem worth it thank you I think so
too in this case it's just for personal
satisfaction
foreign
artist you have my endorsement
[Music]
and then they throw a vodka glass on the
ground and smash it
are you the one who holds together
ah endorsements from
everybody's cool okay let's go talk to
Chantelle
man likes buff women she wasn't Bob
it's just
it's just a floppy clothing
sandal
how can I convince you
oh she had lunch lunch with the castle
once really well how do I wait
oh did I already convinced her because
she's not giving me a question
[Music]
huh
so then the landscore guy I was thinking
anyway like we already did so much for
her
that must be
enough but we did that so early I
thought it doesn't count for the quest
but I did the hat and the violin
she was very picky about the violin
[Music]
now there is one more left to convince
doesn't be difficult what do you want a
rock Furrow her mind I've died this
dress is impeccable
stand here with excitement I have by my
own unwavering study of Master
Shakespeare's first year writing and
cover the treasure not treasure Beyond
proportion a lost screenplay that has
yet to Grace The Mortals and I know it
will be authentic
yes
[Music]
foreign
are you gonna give me those free pieces
I'll take it I guess oh I paint
oh
he said Lush right does that really
matter
[Music]
okay
bushes
obviously I mean could have been Stones
as well
so just green I kind of want to draw a
volcano but he sat Lush so he probably
wants green
maybe behind the bushes there can be a
volcano
[Music]
I didn't I don't have I don't have
big brushes oh well okay
he won't notice the
the volcano in the background right
right
and he will be focused on the large mess
in the front
we're just setting the whole thing with
a dark dark dooming background
[Music]
this tool actually works pretty well on
a big canvas
it's so easy
[Music]
ah I see it better on my obs
oh well
there will be a
volcano anyway
volcano how what what does that volcano
look like like a mountain but just with
um
with a lot of lava coming out of it
right
yeah okay whoa
okay okay okay
foreign
[Music]
I need to get better tools BRB
that is the biggest that that uh pen can
go and I need I need something
otherwise I'm gonna go crazy
[Music]
oh the path is so long
wow
someone needs to teach their dog some
manners
Happy Trees I could use the Happy Trees
maybe I will
[Music]
I mean what else do I have the three
stamps for if not for this
[Music]
10 is lush green 90 volcano
but it'll be fine I mean
you need some drama
that's right only the station May flick
as well sorry
okay here we go again
I brought some more
[Music]
you're sick because I it
even
ah because we're painting on this big
ass canvas
so we need okay we need to work with the
other tools after all
that is the biggest
the biggest it gets okay
that is that is the biggest oh my oh my
God
okay wait this one this one's okay
this one's okay I just have to look at
my OBS screen because on my tablet I'm
having reflections
I cannot see the dark
[Music]
now
I did it with a tiny ass pen after all
okay
and then lava is like yellow
the right
colors but okay
we'll make it work
yeah oh
that's mountain or Mordor you will
decide
which one it is
[Music]
I don't have the right yellow
good
[Music]
that is a shitty volcano
okay okay I don't give a anymore
I want to paint cool life members let me
just put some lunch trees
perfect
[Music]
some more or less trees
no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
what's that song I it's from the hobbits
one of the soundtracks
and Ed Sheeran sang it right Ed Sheeran
was it Ed Sheeran
[Music]
I love singing that encato
foreign
[Music]
see the top of it from this angle but
sick
within this
music the night is awesome
wait are we making more than one set
is it finished
there is a forest there is a forest
[Music]
maybe it helps that I was using the tree
stamps maybe the game recognized that I
used it gets you for life I could almost
feel the leaves wow they got pulled my
rosy cheeks to try up and dude so allow
me to set the next scene okay there's
more
uh castle walls
sturdy stonework a comfort or prison to
be revealed on the outside appearing in
we find ourselves when we find what we
seek inside okay
[Music]
a castle
Castle he says
[Music]
you are asking for too much sir
but once again the inspiration
has struck me
[Music]
we start off with a
a blue sky oh Mr Blue Sky
Mr Blue Sky I need a reference for how a
castle looks like
wonderful
oh that's gorgeous
let's see if I can recreate this
[Music]
wow this is a I'm using a UK castle for
Instagram ah inspiration okay I can make
it work
s
let's pass a little bit I don't know it
says 12th most beautiful castles in the
UK it the thing that really looked
beautiful to me now is that it has like
a
you know it's like surrounded by water
[Music]
and there's a bridge leading up to it
I don't know if I can do it justice but
I'll try
foreign
[Music]
UK Still Standing I didn't realize
everything
looks beautiful
oh Windsor in Windsor Castle didn't they
film them
that show there oh
[Music]
ah
bodium castle and East Sussex a castle
floating on water
bodian Castle
um
[Music]
Sussex Sussex
sounds fancy
[Music]
Saucy eggs
Sussex the land of Saucy eggs
never eat eggs in Sussex
they're very saucy
don't trust the eggs
I wanna go to another one of those
painting workshops with Cali
I'm actually right now I'm really having
this feeling
that I am in one right now
okay
um
laughs
don't put too much
effort we don't have all day
[Music]
pay together
calming music really helps
yeah
okay the castle outliner
um
foreign
[Music]
like this not really oh well
sounds like that
the full generic Castle
[Music]
yeah
hi there
it's loading on water
I saw on Twitter yesterday
after I was done streaming t-o-t-k
I was you know trying to get some
communication done replying to things I
should be replying to and then
I was sent two more demos from different
producers each
for my EP
[Music]
and I am really digging them I'm really
liking them
I listen to them so far they're only
like one one chorus one chorus
each like a verse and the chorus
yeah
and have no lyrics yet
so it's only in a rough State now no I
mean you
pretty
it was pretty far but
it just needs lyrics and the rest of the
song
looking forward to when it's all done
yeah I'm excited
but for for some of the songs I want to
have more control over the lyrics like I
generally
I gotta be honest I don't care about
like what I sing that much I care less
about the lyrics
most of the time then just about the
overall General Vibe of the song that is
like really important to me
um so for the other two songs that I had
so far
I didn't I didn't really give I mean
they are already before I could say
anything they already gave me the lyrics
but I said okay for the upcoming ones
talk a little bit about lyrics
lyric creation
together maybe let's do a meeting I've
never done something like this before
actually
I think what I ever only did was like
for for heart Challenger I said okay I
wanted to be uh like Valentine's themed
that's it
and yeah that's what happened but I
think besides that
I never I never really said anything
these two lyrics more important yeah I I
just thought you know I'll take the
opportunity I'll take the chance to
for once maybe
have it be
something uh that I decide
um
doesn't necessarily need to reflect
anything that happened in reality
anything realistic but oh sheesh
I at least I wanted to
um feel more like my thing
[Music]
why am I putting so much effort the one
other thing that I wanted to do here
with the front elements
[Music]
I have an idea
it's not gonna be bushes what did the
the guy say he said he wanted something
uh peeking
I think
[Music]
my volcanoes are my strong point hey I
could draw this better too if I just it
was more time okay
foreign
[Music]
will be
I made I think this the shape just kind
of reminded me of you guys but what do
you think
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
wow the two Jenkins Jenkins about to
enter the castle
[Music]
we might want to use some more gray
tones
thank you
mmm
[Music]
because he said Castle maybe the game
will recognize that I used many many
gray tones
[Music]
God I think think and work smart
yeah okay
from fire it will look even better trust
me
yeah fine find her the chickens are cute
my Scottish piece of land would not fit
even
a table maybe a chair maybe a small
small camping chair
I'm finished
yeah
when you hear me speak the name
then you only then you change the
scenery
mm-hmm okay okay
is this gonna be difficult because he
will say some like similar words
go for it buddy
started
I'm ready
huh
this is just gonna be out of nowhere
or
[Music]
can I talk to him
so it's like this no that's not it why
would this question make the master
proud of Bravery
[Music]
and I'm feeling it was
guys don't you remember didn't you look
closely
sounds German enough come on
[Music]
no okay it might be it's changing
can't see your phone oh that's my double
crochet
no no
tomorrow
[Music]
it was not high the right opportunity
will emerge at which hour the time
cometh save mine Leaf gray hats yeah
that's the same one I'll change it again
till then then I shall seek out refuge
in Yonder before or it's dark yesterday
we're back in the forest the patience be
mind wondrous because
delicious
but I am mad of my own word I shall give
you my endorsements I see your scene is
set all endorsements I met send my
regards to Adrian you ought to meet her
before she bores of you
German always works it was really true
it's just like where it maybe sounds
German to you guys but it really isn't
it
[Music]
oh you got the endorsement well done
you're in luck I have just the
opportunity for you I have a friend
visiting a marvelous man of great
dignity one of the finest art critics in
this part of the world
let him take a look at one of your
artworks a review from him would surely
make the curator Intrigue now you've
managed to bring attention to that
sucker Benjamin and his mediocre wears
all I ask for me is a small favor I need
you to endorse me and start using my
tools exclusively but doesn't she only
have like three and I bought one of them
I think oh
with my Superior ones but it's only
three tools am I not kind of like
it's not kind of shitty to be like
you know
and what if I say no well we were
getting along so well the offer still
stands okay it seems like we have to do
it
yeah we have to do it
yeah
[Music]
none of that Benjamin stuff now only my
face now all I need from you is a true
master
is it time for them
make sure you really take your time with
this one opportunity to get everything
you ever wanted your well-deserved Place
among the man a masterpiece cannot be
drawn on any canvas instead use my
master canvas
now go take your time and make those
Masterpiece my eagerly await the result
it is time for the Masterpiece the truth
is I actually had something in mind for
the Masterpiece I was not gonna draw a
whole life member uh
I was gonna draw Natalie Dormer as Anne
Boleyn
in a medieval portrait style kind of
like the Mona Lisa
uh
so
yeah maybe after that we can still draw
a whole life member
or before that I mean I don't mind
but now she took my tools
fancy camera
okay it's pretty big
I wonder if you can mess this up
wait her tools she didn't take my tools
uh I have to replace myself it seems
okay okay okay
[Music]
I could drop one more whole life okay
let's do
one whole life remember before we go to
our Masterpiece
[Music]
um
no trees
nah well that's probably sometimes
pretty helpful
no sponge
yeah
blindness okay and colors
I don't know who are we gonna try
I don't know yet
I will have to decide the colors
with that but for now I go with the Lush
Forest
and I want a big canvas
um is this big
that's pretty big
who did I not dry yet I could draw I
could draw weiner
uh I want to draw a Japanese member
um
draw pecula
draw oh mikoti would be cute
I want to draw Corner Maybe
or anything
[Music]
um
I think Martin would appreciate it
because she played passport two and a
lot and she knows you know
she knows the game
but I also want to draw corner
why are you guys all saying I want to
draw Kona
okay
[Music]
I will try I don't we'll probably have
with her colors she has like purple
and gray no dark dark dark black it's
more like a
yeah yeah I guess I could use black
[Music]
purple
her purple
her purple is more like a blue purple
not this purple
do I have any other questions
[Music]
maybe the frosty feels because they
always they look different
it looks different once you get to paint
with them
no I'm not gonna draw her dancing I'm
gonna draw a close-up too difficult
[Music]
yeah
yeah that's that's called work that
could work that's kind of like it
okay
um not the not the same color
I have to do the whole thing should we
do a background color
[Music]
um
what should be the background color
maybe maybe uh um
this blue
[Music]
oh I
am sad but you guys are spamming left
I'm drawing her now okay I know but do
you I literally retweeted it
and talked about it on stream
[Music]
when I want the one I wanted to draw for
now
okay
I'll test my
my lowly face drawing skills
non-existent
I wanna I Wanna Do Well
okay reference of black butcher let me
put my my phone there
have confidence is it
um
um I know how to draw her
just a simple
because the problem is the fast part two
still
uh
uh you cannot undo things and that's
that makes it very difficult in my
opinion
oh
yeah yeah okay just for the overall
overall face shape I guess I'll be using
this tool first
she has straight straight white hair
um yellow eyes big ass horns I hope oh
they're not really gonna fit on the
picture at all already at this point
[Music]
already too late
oh she has this like huge collar okay
I'll add that eventually
um
I like her hair the bangs I love the
bangs
[Music]
with the little braid on the side really
cute okay okay wait let's see what I can
do
um
[Music]
oversized loose balls I'm just gonna
draw her although wait she has a version
without the color oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah we've only she can take off
her coat
and it's pretty cute I'll draw her like
that
yeah yeah
lucky whole ax got like so many
like
variations or like things they
they could do
with their
main outfit
it's pretty nice
[Music]
like I think coyote can also take off
her clothes Lily can also take off her
code
you know how I think also can take off
her coat
oh they all can
[Music]
it's not normal not everyone
in the previous generations could do
that
I wanna kind of do like a
looking down on us
angle but I don't know if I can
good face shape
wait I will mess it up
[Music]
we'll be crying in the distance and I'm
crying in my room
[Music]
yeah it's a jawline
photos
[Music]
your eyes
ymj
[Music]
why why has no ymd hmm
okay
kmt Chihuahua detention
why else that you wouldn't say that to
me though
oh no no no no no no no no
[Music]
that makes no sense
okay I can't really do the angle that I
want to do
[Music]
hmm
I think one reason why I don't why I
always like end up hating what I do
because I always do this like big upper
lashes
maybe I I just try to keep them thinner
this time
[Music]
she doesn't really have lashes but it
doesn't matter
[Music]
is this already too much maybe it is
maybe the eyes
[Music]
you're gonna scare my cats
just kidding big dog you can't hear
the dog
[Music]
help you
it's weird to me
everything looks weird to me let me draw
the hair at one
[Music]
purple hair goes here
yeah and now we have a brain here
[Music]
I love drawing braids
it's like a croissant
[Music]
this is like a closet
oh little
elf ears she has those two okay okay and
then the long
Nash's hair
[Music]
and then
okay
I will not draw the bird so the bird
went somewhere to
annoy Some Humans
me or so I heard
this will be a pain in the ass to fill
in the color again
is this
an accurate thickness
about this much
also her ears are kind of straight not
upwards
[Music]
the hidden sixth member of uruturi I do
not agree with that
someone's mascot
cannot join Horror Story
a mascot
[Music]
okay
what do you think guys the the balance
looks okay I think because it's
confusing let me fill in the horns first
they're mainly black
foreign
did you guys watch the
um video that came out today earlier
today on the official Channel with me
and akuse
with the calories
yeah yeah
you liked it
Facebook recorded that for at least an
hour and of course you know it's always
it's always at least an hour of
recording
sometimes even more and then they cut it
down
so much
but I
I don't know if you guys know this but
did you think that I was really low
energy in this one
if you had that feeling then well
you're not wrong
hahaha
and I I think I told I told you guys
back then like at what time I was
recording that
um I probably also wrote when I finished
because we did two programs I think on
that day back to back
but it was somewhere really early like 6
a.m yeah
I I stumbled out of bed
I had maybe no breakfast maybe
and yeah it was oh
I felt like I think I felt relatively
awake but I just couldn't I just could
not get the
the energy out yeah I was hesitant about
it because I just
don't know
about calories
I don't know shut up I I first turned it
down I was like sorry I'm not gonna do
this I don't I don't I don't think I can
contribute
I don't know about calories
[Music]
but they were like please
doesn't matter
so I was like okay but then I felt like
I kind of had to inform myself so I
looked up some
like General things like how much Ramen
is normally like the different types of
ramen you know
it looks Step Up
foreign
oh
[Music]
your guesses ended up being pretty close
but I also feel like
the way they determined
how many calories these things have
yeah
uh like out of their ass
like how can I know so many of these
pictures that they used they asked us
for
um you know our our Creations or or
really what the
or anything that we ate
outside in a restaurant as well but then
how can they know like what was actually
used in the picture in the in that
cooking how can I know because I didn't
ask what I exactly you used in these
things
[Music]
um
and how much and uh
no they cannot tell come on you can tell
me
like generally you see a fish okay uh
but I mean you don't know what sauce I
used what what did I put into the sauce
and all that
[Music]
um
right
so I
don't know
it I I looked up some of my own uh like
how much would this be I looked up every
like ingredient how much is it zucchini
how much is mashed like or just I didn't
really do typical mashed potatoes how
much is like potatoes and and leek and
all that and I I added it together and
in the end what they came up with was
completely different from what I would
have guessed
so hmm
olive oil chicken one would have been
pretty easy Jasmine yeah okay that one
is simple yeah yeah yeah
but it's okay it was just for a funny
stream so I'm not mad or anything but um
I'm just saying that this would have
been really difficult to do like serious
guessings if you don't give them the
details
of what is
in these dishes
if you guys don't know what what we're
talking about uh it's a video that was
uploaded today on the official Channel
and it may be in Japanese but there are
always subtitles on these kind of videos
so my phone went black
oh
eyebrows
guesstimating
[Music]
moving the distance
did I get rid of my monochrome I need to
get a bag
[Music]
oh wow
[Applause]
okay excellent
she looks kind of cute to me for now
looking good so far one official Angela
do programs like this every any time
well I don't think we currently have the
resources and staff for it
so probably a no for now
you can't deliver the Masterpiece I
wonder if the game just ends or if you
can continue drawing with your
Masterpiece status
seems like I've reached the end of the
game
foreign
and I mean
we need these kind of videos right now
on the end Channel because
they're inviting en members anyway to
these things I mean okay never mind
they're really only inviting Ian members
who can speak
Japanese most of the time
[Music]
oh well at least you know it's some
extra content for kfp at least every
once in a while I think the next one
will be uploaded in June I was told next
one where I am in I forgot what that was
calorie one I remembered because it was
like
the other one I already forgot
it will be a surprise
that one will be purple I think
[Music]
looking back showing the necklace
shaft angle no I can't draw fan art
generally
um because copyright
that's what I know from art streams
the you know unless we have permission
for it specifically
like if I wanted to draw Zelda
I wouldn't be allowed
[Music]
although maybe you know because we have
like game permissions with Zelda maybe
at least
that could be somewhat applied but no
difficult if it's all difficult
draw player cosplaying them yeah I mean
I can always say oh this is just some
this is just play oh this is just some
random elf girl with blonde hair
I was actually thinking about this today
like oh kind of want to draw Zelda and
passport to I'll just say it's a random
elf girl with long hair elf girls often
have blonde hair you know you know
Ina kind of did that for her thumbnail
oh did she
I mean for thumbnails I feel like you
know
if you want to be creative and you do
something on your thumbnail that's
that's okay
that doesn't get like
looked at so strictly I think
[Music]
what does that sound
is that in-game
hello I heard a weird sound
also keep on hearing both sounds it
sounds like maybe my tummy is making
sounds but that's not the case okay guys
oh this one
did you hear that
it's like a tummy rumbling but I think
it's supposed to be both sounds because
there's like a boat close by
the dog the dog is very loud have a look
uh
probably fine
that's really fun
anyway I sat it on the stream but like I
until that day
I've never
looked at like calories on a product
ever before
and I will continue to ignore them but
it was interesting for once to
see
how many calories things have I don't
really care
[Music]
I don't really care is that what guy yes
it's gonna be wagah
[Music]
ymv
you guys look at
calories
with my portion sizes it's not an issue
I don't know I guess so I mostly eat
smaller portions but and I also eat like
outside often and then I also don't care
about the Porsche the calories
no I do yes
no no no most people know
I try not to have too much sugar
I don't know it just seems like too much
of a hassle to me just like how you know
I stand okay maybe if I want better skin
I should cut down the sugar a bit but
then the other day the dermatologist she
was like yeah if you want to improve
your skin you should you know no not
chocolate no this and that no maybe no
alcohol and all that blue and also no
milk products and that that's where I
was like
excuse me
in my mind
like uh okay
um you lost me I don't really consume
milk products much
and if I had to completely give up on it
I would probably
be fine but I just
at this point the things that are
supposedly supposedly bad for you like
even fruit that supposedly is good for
you has like a lot of
sugar
in it
so basically everything's bad for you
that's what it sounds like to me so I
don't care anymore I'm not even gonna
know
I am not gonna stop
concealing the things I like
just because everything's bad for me
then everything's bad for me
no no
I don't care I mean it's not like I have
like health problems that are caused by
food
so it's really just like more of an
Aesthetics thing of my skin and I know
my skin recently calmed down a little
bit
again so I think we could like whatever
whatever
and there was there would be so many
things I have to take care of right
my God
everything's on healthy
there's not a single thing
seems
everything in moderation yeah I think
like I I don't
I don't
um
consume that many milk products
so we probably good
probably good
[Music]
thank you
her eyes on
oh pretty much just like a
black to Yellow graduations
most people in my age group drink and
smoke and they look aged while I look
still look 20 years
oh so did you not
do not
smoke and drink much
only chicken breasts and water
wasn't Mr y'all that ain't nothing but
rabbits well but he was already like 17
years old and he was consuming
everything in a mushed smoothie form so
I think the reason he was consuming that
was partially because he can't really
know
anything anymore that has proper shape
and then it's easy to Mush and smooth it
smooth arise
vegetables
it did seem like a really uh healthy
person who likes to live
healthy so you know
[Music]
it was probably also paying attention to
that but I don't think that was the only
reason why he was doing that
[Music]
okay Yellow
Nice brush
[Music]
okay
whoa
[Music]
thank you
maybe maybe I'll try to autograph them
[Music]
mmm
see I'm doing I'm doing the eyes that
are like characteristic for her
hmm
I count calories because I want to lose
weight so I feel better and healthier
the better skincare sleep and all this
is our bonus well I mean if you're like
motivated for it and you feel like okay
with
you know doing all of that then I think
that's totally cool I just do not have
the motivation for it at all
what the eyes look good
since I made it uh
eyes so dark I think I can make the
lashes also pretty dark
right
I forgot these two are pretty similar
[Music]
welcome memberships thank you
giving attention to nutrition in general
is important especially in your later
years oh I never looked at that either
the nutrition details
never looked at that ear oh my God
should I should I well the eyes look
cute
wait right now she looks like baby to me
what the
[Music]
neon Beats art style
she does right like a lowly baby
oh my God what happened right
why did it turn out to I think it's the
the
eye is the the way of drawing the eyes
he draws the eyes
kind of like that like the inside the
shading right
oh it doesn't look like neon beat on on
LaPlace though obviously it just
happened my style
trying to imitate LaPlace and uh up and
ends up to be kind of like neon bead
cool because I like neon Beats art
so much
that's funny
[Music]
it looks cute right now okay
um so in order to make it not look too
much like baby let's fill in the
[Music]
strand
should help
[Music]
that helps I love how soft this art
looks yeah
yeah I agree oh my God I wish I could
draw like wait I am drawing like that
right now I mean
Loki Loki
we're drawing like that here I am doing
the pain
bro
okay I'm thinking we're getting really
close to the point where I can help but
I need to bring out my monochrome
palette I'll give it a bit more
time because I can work on the base of
the horn dating before putting
purple on top
oh that's not so smooth man
that is
better
[Music]
um
don't forget to add Squidward's nose at
the end or else it's not art what the
what are you talking about
the purple is still not the ideal purple
to me I wish it was a bit more like
grayish but that's okay I mean we can't
help it we have limited tools you know
[Music]
that's all right oh my God the eyes I
can't
everything I see when I look at these
eyes is maybe
it's freaking me out
[Music]
you see a difference is it getting pink
oh yes
[Music]
a little bit I'm only one a little bit
okay
[Music]
that one is a little bit too much
Gotta Have a good a good feeling
all right
[Music]
thank you
oh
hey
maybe I should just draw more
more cute cute girls okay not cute girls
like this
um do I have what I need
probably gonna it up okay let me
get which which palette do we not need
I feel like I'm done with the skin so I
could I could get rid of it could get
rid of the skin palette
[Music]
try and screw something here
I don't know what
whatever keep it like this don't it
up
um
ah wait her shoulders I should do
because she's gonna be wearing her
non-coat version
and then let's add a little outline
[Music]
you know what I was watching are you
gonna line up I don't know maybe not in
this game but elsewhere maybe I was
watching
um this is the second time uh niji Sanji
playing some game what was it called I
did like a big collab
[Music]
the Family Feud I think
uh Family Feud
where I mean you're supposed to play it
like in real life normally but so they
can't so that one person just puts in
everybody's answers and this time it was
I think finana but before it was someone
else who was doing that on their Channel
think of someone else maybe it wasn't me
I was thinking y'all this looks so fun I
want to do this with Ian
although it's like because
um you have to type it in
pretty fast and if they change their
mind then you have to go back and then
you run out of time yeah it's a fun idea
I was thinking about it already last
time when they were doing the
um
getting all 10 of Ian yeah the problem
is like
I mean it doesn't have to be all of them
you could try
nine with me and still no or four we can
do eight with me participating as well
we could even do eight four four
um
it doesn't have to be five five
[Music]
thank you
just an idea
[Music]
boy you know don't expect it to happen
immediately
I'm gonna be traveling soon
and faunas on a break and this and that
[Music]
so you know
it would have to be like a big
a big collapse um I need I would need to
be able to get although I could get some
ID girls in too if I have struggles
I ah
speaking of guys I have
an updates
um on on the scam
[Music]
remember that was that a ring that it
goes through oh
[Music]
um so I mean it's past the deadline but
finally DHL answered me they sent me a a
um
they sent me an email
they're like Miss takanashi here is your
bill
they didn't apologize for the delay it
took them it took them a whole week
okay
um
but apparently there is a bill
ion was legit I didn't pay it yet though
because there were many bills it was one
package but many bills for it and I'm
I'm not yet understanding what's going
on
um but but you know
you know what it was
apparently it was the later package
oh that look it's costing me a lot of
taxes
280 bucks
of taxes and it's probably the keyboards
so solely the keyboard that is driving
that up even though Wayne and marked it
as a gift
but that doesn't help
Austrian Customs are
and just
here to make me angry
hmm
[Music]
yeah but the bill was like it was it was
four different PDFs that they sent me
yeah but is that you guys know more
about keyboards that keyboard uh does
that make sense like how
I think she even like told me roughly
how much the keyboard
all together cost but I don't remember
what is that
would you say that it makes sense I'm
paying so many taxes for that because
the rest was just food I think
could keep it really
apparently
apparently could like a an estimate of
the value of this package
wouldn't it be based on weight no no no
no no no no what are you talking about
this is about Customs they don't they
don't charge you based on weight no no
[Music]
I'm confused
um
see I think
she put that in it was like something
like 300 something
but then 280 taxes
I don't know it seems weird to me maybe
I should
I argue with that
but they already passed that point
they're already sending me the demands
via the lawyer
can I even demand you know
[Music]
to
reconsider that because that's
ridiculous I think in my opinion have
you guys even agree yeah it's like 80
tax what the
are you sure it's legit yes DHL sent it
to me
after making me wait for a whole week
I don't think we're gonna get to draw my
masterpiece today
this is my masterpiece I should have
drawn this
on the on the canvas oh well
[Music]
yeah that was what I saw this morning
when I wake up when I woke up
I was like what the I I can't
I can't comprehend this right now
and look at this later
but yeah it was the kicking keyboard
apparently but I don't I still
I still did not charge me when it
arrives
yeah because normally you do that they
don't charge you afterwards and then
like how I that still they still never
um sent me any reminders me a day in
jail they immediately like sent me a
lawyer notice but does that mean that
there are also fees on there
uh that's what I was trying to figure
out looking at the PDF if there are any
fees of like delay of me not paying then
I would like to argue about that too
because I never received
anything before
but do they care about that because I I
can't prove that I didn't receive
something that I didn't receive
[Music]
late fees yeah
and I'm not sure because it was like
four different and everything four
different PDFs and everything had like a
different
a different
[Music]
um
price different numbers on it so I'm
confused now
I'm confused and angry
you should contact
UM
[Music]
okay don't say please anymore that it
sounds like a scam because it is not a
scam
might be Escape shut up
[Music]
you'll live your
wishful thinking
I had it all checked out I called DHL
then I contacted their their like
uh build apartment and everything you
know
turns out it's real but
is it fair hmm
[Music]
that's another question
don't think it's fair
foreign
Customs that's why I stopped ordering
things from from Asia in general because
they charge like Austrian Customs are
absolutely insane I don't know what
they're thinking
and they're thinking we're gonna make
money
and now it's even worse than it was like
years ago because they got new laws new
Customs laws
everyone over
hmm
[Music]
yeah yeah
I'll continue discussing with them but I
wonder if that will add on to my delay
fee
um
[Music]
yeah maybe it's a push for them from
from the country to make people buy more
domestic stuff could be
foreign
[Music]
I highly agree with that but I also
don't remember like it's been so long
when did I receive that guys I told you
when I first received it right isn't it
ages ago
so I can't really tell
if maybe I actually already paid taxes
when I first got it but I don't remember
[Music]
go okay I never received a letter I
swear
maybe one I would have missed
but all of them because they until they
go with the lawyer they would send more
don't you think
[Music]
it's normally I would think so
foreign
I don't want to just blindly paint us
man
it's so annoying
until if I if I try to discuss it
they're gonna take like two weeks again
to reply it
it's gonna be a long process probably
[Music]
your mistake or Miss remembering on my
part
[Music]
no
thank you
you got to decide if that's worth it I
think it is what
uh no you guys even said
keyboard shouldn't even cost that much
so
so I'm not buying it
[Music]
I'm stubborn
okay
become a Karen yes I'll try it's
intimidating but I will try
to unleash my inner parent
[Music]
s have to
I will not Bend
to the Customs will
so easily
welcome
thank you for the uh
[Laughter]
a text explained 50. he's playing 15.
Japanese Customs also actually I
never had a problem with them but I
didn't get so many packages sent
from Japan when I lived there
[Music]
I'm already white really
oh
that's three thousand oh my God that
makes no sense it just did you like say
something
maybe better at that point to send it
back because you don't want to like
start a whole discussion with Japanese
Customs where possibly you don't even
know the language
oh no
that is
troublesome
foreign
[Music]
what the
that then it would be way cheaper to buy
them in Japan I mean Japan
razors pretty cheap anyways
I don't know do the the American ones do
they have like a really good quality for
some reason or
for what
[Music]
you guys have like magical razors
the more color I put into this
the less good it looks
to me
[Music]
the green ones
brain worms good
preference
go to DHL with a broken importance later
returned to send that I'm not paying the
customs and ready for raining to repair
it and send it back
I think it's too late for that
but I mean normally they charge you at
the door and then you would have the
option to be like to be like no way I
refused but I didn't get that I mean
they delivered to me at the door I
remember that
I didn't pick it up at the post office
it was delivered to me at the door
I'm not gonna ask because for custom
fees
what that means that if they would want
to ask me to pay 2008 bucks for this at
the spot
I mean I would feel bad like sending it
back to Elena but I would be like yo
something's wrong with this let's let's
just send this to the post office first
[Music]
let's just act as if I wasn't home
because then it would go to the Post
Office
and then and then we'll think about it
I guess
[Music]
well it's way too late for that anyway
it's been over eight months apparently
unbelievable
[Music]
I want a mix of the gray with the blue
maybe I'll just I just put the gray and
then on the top I go with watercolors
again
[Music]
now it stands out because only that part
is gray but I don't want it to be too
blue
okay let's try it out
[Music]
um
yeah yeah that kind of works
in the UK they ask you to pay the
Customs fee before delivery too I've had
that happen once as well yeah yeah it
depends sometimes I just do it
differently I don't know
when or why
their eyes look like they blow
that's my favorite part
okay
but we should finish this at some point
can't be doing this forever
I'm waiting I forgot the yellow
um
ribbon scarf thingy
and then
oh actually
oh
I made a skin color and I I took
clothes away from her even more I took
away the under blouse
oops
I just realized I was gonna draw it
[Music]
Yamada
making you even more naked
I apologize
that was disrespectful
[Music]
let me give you a close
um stuff like here
yeah
[Music]
and then
weird it's kind of weird like a shirt
color
[Music]
first of all this
that
don't worry I'm doing this one correctly
[Music]
or is that the the problem that you have
now
[Music]
you didn't want it to be like this
lapless no
no although I feel like probably someone
already drew that I mean
surely someone drew that already right
for whatever reason
huh
[Music]
did I forgot any details
I feel like we're good but I want to
make this part fluffier
[Music]
thank you
I'm sure someone out there Drew every
single whole number in calcaneus
[Music]
exactly there's even the fan art of me
in the kaukini which was Commissioned I
think someone personally needed that I
guess
mm-hmm
I think I have it saved in my fan art
folder
in case I need it sometime
for for thumbnails
[Music]
okay
I hope you're happy with your face
because
[Music]
I need to be stopped you know
but the problem
is that apparently according to the game
I think I only have to draw the
Masterpiece and then we're done with the
game
or does anyone know if it continues
afterwards because I'm not gonna do
a whole stream just for painting one
masterpiece
[Music]
and now starting the Masterpiece now I
mean I could
I could maybe I will
come here
[Music]
is this in my space no because you have
to use a specific canvas with specific
tools
but
oh
I can't stop this is like me playing
tltk I have recently
I am Unstoppable
when I start doing something
I'm unstoppable have you noticed
[Music]
doesn't it kind of look cute sideways
actually
upside down is even cuter
now
Chihuahua and kodaks no I hate products
products corics or something
that I I cannot be bothered with
in totk unfortunately that's the only
thing
[Music]
you give it some softness you know
okay
[Music]
starting a chat
looking at you
[Music]
a party okay
laughs
[Music]
LaPlace titled
sure that would be your name
[Music]
I wanna watch the replay of this I don't
know watching art replays is so
like satisfying don't you think
she has a yellow glow I think it was
better without the yellow glow but mmm
[Music]
spinito
you don't like it
online
not finito
[Music]
it has been undone
due to popular or unpopular demand
foreign
[Music]
okay
I want to watch on OBS difference
I always start with the face the eyes
still uncertain oh but this now it's
taken shape already the hair the hair
really helps to make it look like
something proper
now you people already recognize slap
with us at this point I think yeah yeah
I'm starting to fill in the hair
[Music]
and the eyes oh this is the moment oh
baby
[Laughter]
holy
oh my God can't unseeing but okay
close
nice the horns nice hair shading nice
cute
this proves we need more Kiara ice
creams
[Music]
the yellow outline
it was there for a second a mere second
[Applause]
ah okay let's sell
[Music]
I want a good price for this
please and
um
[Music]
where are those three tools
holy
[Music]
I feel like that's already as good as it
will get but I will I will look at the
other ones
I don't even know what's normal anymore
that's it
[Music]
what what I don't understand what are
the three kills 300 no hell no
free hunt
where are the tools that I need to use I
don't understand
Harry
Harry offers again three thousand four
hundred
the razor tax
and
that's I don't even need that much money
that's probably As Good As It Gets
should I take it I'm just curious about
what the others would offer
does anyone who would offer even more
[Music]
if I
take it off the shelf and then put it
back again still get Harry till
bid the same again
worse guys there's also like George I
think who pays a lot often
so anybody who wants to bid more than 3
500 for Yamada
[Music]
what about our croissant man no not the
punk
[Music]
Seth get out of here get out of here you
have no chance
Benjamin did not even
okay Harry okay I love this painting
like I love the sea and my wife and kid
of course
okay you can have it
oh
leave my money in this game feels unreal
oh ah see they're rich people they take
so much time until they arrive
[Music]
I wonder
if they would have
hate more
I just don't have the patience to wait
for them but wait let me go back to the
lady is it like a bug I did not get the
tools like she literally said right that
she's replacing my tools
those three songs
and I still have the same ones
is it because that maybe I already
bought the tools that she
offers in her store but then then she
take away my tools and she really didn't
though
let me see what are the tools that she
sells I think I bought one but there's
Michelangelo's metal points oh yeah
these are just the same things
this is the fancier names because they
look the same as what you get in the
other shop she gave her the canvas yeah
DaVinci's chalk
I mean it's not necessarily those are
the sponges what not the tree one is one
I got for whatever reason I felt
compelled to buy the tree one
no no no no no
[Music]
yes
this box like I've had a bug in this
game before so
why
why do I have these tools
I wanna that is a real scam yeah let me
look up maybe I can find something about
it
um
passport tutu
bug tools masterpiece
[Music]
no I don't find anything
but there's someone
who played it
what and then I think they were painting
their masterpiece
no this person
seems to buy them
wait wait wait wait wait I just want to
say I just want to see if they like if
it works for them
[Music]
and that's not the masterpiece is it
search up how to get the tools but she
should have given them to me
[Music]
that looks like a masterpiece frame
oh okay
this person is painting with the
Masterpiece frame but uh seems to also
have access to all the tools
ah okay
didn't she say she's taking away the
tools and giving us them because this
person also I think bought them
them on their own
and it's just choosing them
in their own like options
right
oh and the game continues after that
still he's still drawing
he gets a ticket to the curator
hmm
yeah okay but it seems to have worked
okay so I do have to buy all her shitty
tools
uh so I think yeah the one was the trees
right that looks like
yeah the tree sponge
the Michelangelo Medal Point thank God I
have the money and the da Vinci's chalk
ah
they have like stars no it's just
because
how can I draw with only dad
um
but the colors are not limited
to replace the tools I already had with
her version I mean the the ah
the tree one that I already had
maybe maybe that's what she meant
by using a tablet yes I am
I used one of my tablets as a screen
normally
and then when I have to drop
and
just pull it further towards me let's
see
happy tree
I don't think I'll even use that one
okay so we don't make a mistake
we only have these brushes for real
thing wait didn't I already accidentally
used something here
[Music]
is that yeah bye
is that a problem but they if that would
like mess it up would they wouldn't they
stop me from doing it how can I I can't
I'm doing it hey
[Music]
foreign
will be fine
well let me get my Natalie Dormer uh
ambulance reference
if you type in Android Natalie Dormer I
will not show it on screen but you may
you may get an idea of what I am using
as a reference
uh it's the portrait where she's sitting
in front of a red curtain
and she has like a yellow golden dress
on
with the B necklace
[Music]
okay we're gonna draw
Evelyn
Natalie Dormer version
um
but with only three tools
are you kidding me right
just kidding
here it's not even the right bread in a
second
but I feel like she's they're both not
gonna be so serious about it hello
[Music]
I feel like my game crashed
I can't press Escape I can't walk around
can't click things it doesn't light up
when I'm around it
[Music]
yeah it crashed
that's the first time that happened
maybe it's telling me maybe it's giving
me a sign
oh
[Music]
not responding
maybe they're live fixing my bug
let me reopen
[Music]
we found the reference picture isn't she
pretty
isn't she gorgeous
they really nailed the look
I hope it's safety work ah
normally I think it saves automatic
[Music]
but didn't I I got a screenshots
if it didn't I'm gonna Rage Quit
what a scary thought
another person who's prettier oh
eh
[Music]
cause I have less money again because I
I bought some I bought two tools
did you guys
don't remember how much money I have
I spent like three thousand bucks
[Music]
this is killing me
no
I was standing in that spot no wait not
quite but I mean maybe I was standing
there when it auto saved I had around
10K when I started the game and I have
around 10K when I ended the game just
now
hello
[Music]
wait yeah I didn't have the frame yet
and here chicken
and
oh
[Music]
yeah okay okay we're fine we're fine
okay what was I doing anyway
um
the colors
[Music]
we're good we're good
don't worry guys okay
uh and Berlin it just didn't save what I
already painted but that's okay because
I didn't like it
I'm gonna use the trees
not in a very
free full way
but is it really
really not a so fancy name the others
are very fancy
but I do think it was one of the tools
this is gonna be
gonna explain this
I'm just doing the curtains right now
and I lost motivation now that I have to
paint it like this what the
what
lots and balls in
yeah I replaced she said she replaced
the tools too but I mean I didn't have
the tools that she was talking about
we'll give her the benefit of the doubt
you can do it because you're very good
thank you
[Music]
I think it's meant to be sort of hard
mode yeah
I can see that
yeah I have to prove
myself
well it would be so much better
if I could just use all tools well thank
you
these tools are annoying but I think you
can work magic with them
so so they're just making a tools were
fancy
[Music]
okay
okay okay okay
my beautiful wife
[Music]
let's draw my beautiful wife
I'm gonna try to make her look like a
real human but I I don't have
skills in that department normally
oh my God
maybe I should have made her face bigger
nah nah
there will still be hair up here
why so funny he's not even using
let's see
no I just you know he never changes the
brush actually
whole game is a scam because he's never
using a different brush look at him
look at him
he's not using Michelangelo's metal
points
I'm getting double scammed
and a neck you know real humans have
relatively thick necks unlike anime
characters
foreign
of her hair it's like dark brown
[Music]
still need to keep the hairline well
very realistic hair lines wow
not balding
this show tutors the shooters was
something I was so addicted to and
that's the cutest kind of got my whole
like
UK history
or generally European history addiction
started
we'll never forget that
[Music]
look how desperate I am I'm using a tree
stamp oh my God
[Music]
I can't believe it
history not Central
school I was already pretty interested
in history
but they mostly taught like
Austrian history I guess
oh wait she doesn't really have
[Music]
he'll be nervous you're doing okay thank
you can you rotate the stamp by rotating
the canvas oh interesting what a life
hack I think so
yeah
where did my
you could
[Music]
uh okay and then like this big thing
goes around here oh maybe a bit more
a bit more hair
[Music]
and I should write
um
Natalie
bullin
well my history stream one day I hope
probably never
probably never right unfortunately
history
the one who tells you about all the
things that happened many many years ago
in real life when we started out
could do some whole life history videos
why not
I mean
basically
I I basically do that in whole talk
[Music]
I would say like she should do it more
like general not not focused on one
member you know
[Music]
but more on how whole life developed
chronological history yeah a whole lot
of Errors yeah that too yeah
[Music]
okay
you can't talk about Real History they
will not allow it will I I yeah
never I never I never did did I no no no
I never did I don't what's history
[Music]
where would the eyes be
oh God normal human facial Anatomy okay
let's let's start like here
[Music]
I've made it bigger after all
oh no I'm so embarrassed
it's gonna look so but she's so
beautiful
how can I do that
[Music]
is it still anything no
that's the same color oh God
oh my God
trust the process you'll be fine yeah
well you know anime
character
[Music]
um
not comparable
what else do I have to talk about
[Music]
I talked about the official program I
talked about
scam
post scan that wasn't the scam
thought about my music
talk about so many things already today
boom oh oh
[Music]
you know
I have to say this now that I'm drawing
it
um in this kind of medieval shows they
always wear these beautiful
historic
corsets right
with all my respect
I have to say
the way it makes boobies look is my
favorite way to make boobies look
it is
um
the booby squish is my favorite kind of
Ruby squish
[Music]
were you thinking I was gonna criticize
it because no I was I was going for a
big big phrase I love
I love this kind of medieval courses
um
even even women with smaller boobies
will look so good I mean it's so
uncomfortable yes my European is showing
it's so uncomfortable but it looks so
that booby window
it's just marvelous
the way I mean I don't know some of you
guys are looking at the same picture
right now as I do right
whoa the glow
the glow
oh God woman
her booby window
it's beautiful
oh I mean generally I just love these
dresses in general
like in all of these medieval shows it's
always just such a pleasure
to look at these dresses
but then
there's a movie window that makes it
even better
better
[Music]
basically what I'm talking about what I
mean is you know
this
this oh here here is the Shadow and then
here it's bright yeah oh
it's magical
she'll get a necklace here so I can
actually
do my thing it's not like a typical like
push-up bra kind of push no the corset
push is a whole
friend push
[Music]
you guys understand
and then here there's also a squish here
that I love
[Music]
the oh my God I can't breathe
please let me out of this corset squish
marvelous marvelous
so far this part is looking good but the
face the faces what will devastate me
[Music]
no wait wait
foreign
[Music]
I wish I had a softer brush
make her Derpy face
never seen you try realism before yeah I
don't think
even in art school I don't think I've
ever drawn like a portrait of a person
it was always just objects maybe if I
would have stayed longer in that school
maybe then I would have had to do that
oh God okay
her eyes
the proportions are so important
[Music]
look around here
is that too high yeah
[Music]
thank you
oh God she scares me
that's only do some sculpting in art
school oh sculpting
oh that sounds fun too actually her face
is a bit too wide maybe or I need to
make the eyes
[Music]
this is already not
not realistic anymore I think
almond shaped eyes
[Music]
how do you draw nose Holes without
making them look like
oh
[Music]
pretty big
and it's pretty dark if I want to be
accurate I have to make it pretty dark
even darker than that
and then the nose flap oh God noses are
like the one thing that will up
your decent piece of art like a
realistic nose will you up
oh my God
[Music]
did I is it is it already like a piggy
terrifying piggy nose or not yet
what do you think
[Music]
she's a bit yellow right now but I I
can't help but this these skin tones are
kind of yellow and even make these in
realism art and passport too I think you
can we did that with Mona Lisa
but I had more tools
more tools that I could use
let me get that hairline closer
[Music]
yeah
okay eyebrows
[Music]
ER
it's dark too dark
[Music]
foreign
that's all right I mean that's not 100
her eyebrow shapeless okay
would you guys say Natalie Dormer is
like a famous actress I feel like I only
know her because of all those medieval
shows but she's probably not that famous
as she is I also I also never see her
like in like stuff like Met Gala or red
carpet it absolutely yeah yeah
oh she's famous now add Hunger Games
that's true the Hunger Games must have
helped her a lot but has she done
anything like big recently though
but I'm glad you guys are saying yeah
oh yeah wait what the
what the prawns
[Music]
from Hunger Games she was in Game of
Thrones so it's true
okay I guess we could consider her
famous but I liked her before she was
famous
I like to before that I like her lips so
much
the booby window is something you know
anybody could have but the lips her lips
are special you know
she always has this like poutine
[Music]
pouty face
I'm a true fan
before I'm Gonna Keep I'm gonna gate
keep that in the Dormer
[Music]
yeah
I wonder I wonder what's next in store
for her I mean she probably already did
something else and
I don't know about it
these pinks are not ideal
ah the lips
[Music]
your smile is more beautiful than the
woman in the painting
thank you but I want her to be beautiful
too
you can probably get those lips with
some surgery
yeah but also
makeup I've been watching a lot of
makeup tutorials recently because
YouTube keeps on recommending them to me
from a specific uh Japanese YouTuber
holy moly her Transformations are crazy
and I actually I love her attitude
like she will always show herself not
only bare face
a lot of people do that you know a lot
of makeup YouTubers show themselves bare
face yes but
I feel like she
she's just like she comes across so like
down to Earth because she doesn't only
show herself bare face but like she's
like this whole mess in the beginning of
her videos
she will look like she just woke up her
hair all over the place and and doesn't
have the most flattering oh the lips
look good I think it doesn't have the
most flattering
um like lightning setup to make her bare
face look more you know perfect like
those other Beauty YouTubers do it
foreign
like say oh this is like the model the
perfect ideal I don't know she's she's
cute you know but what I'm trying to say
is like
you said you see you say that she she
doesn't
um wants to fake it you know she she
shows a more realistic version of what a
face looks without makeup at first
um
yeah she's not trying to fake it and
give you the image that she's perfect
but then once she puts on the makeup I I
always was like like she has the
perfect face
the perfect canvas
for this kind of stuff
that's what I was thinking
such a perfect canvas for his face man
so cute I want to try her makeup
tutorials
but it will look different on me
I don't have an Asian face
hmm
actually this isn't so bad right now is
it I mean it does look why it look like
huh
hmm yet no it will never but at least it
doesn't look like horrendous
[Music]
considering the fact that I don't do
I don't really do realistic faces ever
this is like my first try
ever Maybe
you can see Natalie really
um Brimley are you just not saying that
mouth I think is really important I'm
giving her this little smirk at least
but um
okay wait we have to fill out the eyes I
guess
oh
let's start with the pupil
just make it big
and then we'll go around with the blue
[Applause]
whoa
I mean it does look like a medieval
portrait kind of doesn't it actually the
red is beautiful
red oh my god
oh wow
[Music]
oh
wait the eyes are decent
[Music]
hey I'm just winning today and recently
the dog keeps throwing you up
yeah looking pretty decent it's not as
cursed as I thought it would be it would
be even better with the other two still
she looks kind of cute looks like a
different person but also it looks like
she's looking somewhere else she doesn't
look at the camera oopsie
[Music]
um
I couldn't I can probably fix it
I'm gonna try
okays
needs to be corrected
being like this now now she's looking
more towards us doesn't she
think so
God wait I'm a genius holy
[Music]
very good setup as a family pick and it
feels gonna look Christmas just Blobs of
color
it's looking right at you
see I told you trust the process
yeah I think it's just
a bit too much to expect uh
for her to look like you know actually
herself
you know that's okay
[Music]
around
ah okay
interesting
[Music]
okay where is her face flowing kind of
on the
on the forehead
yeah wow
[Music]
and um
around the nose here
yeah realistic
on the tip of her nose
and on the bridge up here
whoa
okay I end of course on the police
I already did some
shine there
oh
wait she has really really really
defined
uh color called color
cool color Hollow oh man
I don't want to say color I like the
color I want to say color bone
man oh
[Music]
color
bone is that okay clavicles
what happens
yeah oh yeah
[Music]
let's call our bones are crazy
he's a different girl who whom I've
never met before
kind of cute
let's draw her headpiece
[Music]
now
she seems like a Carmen
what
nice clavicles my Vegas
amazing job on the nose thank you
he does have a pointy nose but as
actually a bit wider than how I drew it
maybe I'll fix it my nose is a bit wider
we're trying to get as close as possible
to make her look a little bit like
herself you know
although when I make it wider it might
start looking weird
happy treat them
it's half oh no it's uh what was it
South Park it's South Park kind of like
a NG topic guys
because the girls the other day were so
hesitant to say it they they wrote it in
the Discord chat instead
no
well yeah I mean I know they have like a
lot of like
idiotic episodes and topics that's why I
don't watch it
sorta kinda
with no reason hmm
it can be controversial as a show yeah I
can see that
like not that it would be like not okay
to mention it right well if if yes then
I up because I mentioned it ha ha
but I don't remember being told anything
like oh don't mention so far
really
watch yourself
oh
no
[Music]
I'm happy if she's happy
thank you
I'm a pretty girl
[Music]
pretty girl
foreign
[Music]
it's really tiny the reference
is smaller than what I'm drawing
like half the size
trying my best
how about
it is I made it a bit wider
and a bit more defined yeah she does
have like pretty strong Shadows there at
her nose
as a painting it's still you know a bit
more difficult
okay but I think that's okay
[Music]
let's define her eyes a bit more wow
maybe I should draw more hyper realistic
paintings maybe of all life members
okay that there's already probably
people who do that as well but you know
she actually her eyes her eyes are
smirking too
you're like
not as almondine
I drew them
there's a smirk in her eye
[Music]
you know I think I think she's smirking
a little bit
[Music]
and then we need them
Park
learning realism is always a good good
to do art wise anyway yeah probably I
wonder you know you know probably had to
do that too
but has she ever drawn like
realistically on stream before that
would be interesting I think she should
do an art stream where for once she
draws maybe even herself in a hyper
realistic way
she just poses realistic poses you know
okay but no no like for real like fully
colored faces did she
[Music]
move me through me very realistically
once
wait do you mean
wait
thank you for joining the stream and
being
straight away going to praising me thank
you hey
I'm doing my best here
also very curious about the Replay for
it
thank you
[Music]
man is the only one that throws
realistic animal ah yeah true she did
that yeah yeah Ah that's what you mean
she drew it like a chicken is that what
you're saying
doing her best kiwawa she could do it
yeah one thing not to do that I'll ask
her if she plans on doing something like
that because I want to see it
wait she has a glow
right here
it's those little like shading and
highlighting details which will make
a painting look more realistic I think
foreign
[Music]
probably one more issue
we're having is probably the eyebrows
because the tip the front part of her
eyebrows is more round
and
they're not as harsh as I drew them
[Music]
yeah more like this I think
thank you
oh my God my first fan art of Natalie
Dormer wait she looks like a child
the how did that happen
[Music]
oh
I perfected the pout
[Music]
I did
and the dog is in-game Ambience are you
guys as soon as Angela looks not mature
enough the jawline
[Music]
you know what we'll drop for now let's
draw the dress
I won't put as much details in it but
my daughter was pretty old when she took
this I think but uh and Berlin was
supposedly way younger
it was annelin when she died I should
notice but let me ask you guys can you
look it up really quickly
I'm curious how old did she get
wait I'm not done with the hairpiece
either
[Music]
40 what
no not not Natalie don't worry I'm
asking about uh and Berlin did I say
Natalie Dormer
29 or 45.
ah is it unsure
that might have been unsure yeah yeah
we're not exactly sure
confusing documents are soon
[Music]
thank you
I don't like it I don't like when this
drawing like in the picture
it's not so defined it has like a soft
shadow
[Music]
it's also these skin tones are too
yellow
oh well okay I made it a bit darker
maybe yeah
[Music]
oh maybe around here
that's not really supposed to be oopsie
a skin tone
but
it works a little bit
okay
[Music]
her cheekbones look too defined
more scattered like this
[Music]
oh and then
to Define her chin a little bit
gotta add Shadow underneath the lips
on the side only
see what I'm doing oh my God I'm such an
artist
DaVinci who I don't know
I don't know who this chalk belongs to
must be some random guy
working at the supermarket or so
I never heard of them
[Music]
oh I think her chin looks good now
Ashley a little bit more pointiness
[Music]
there we go oh okay her chin became too
big
that's weird I don't know how this has
happened
[Music]
weird
she does have a little bit of a
okay okay chills I inspire you to draw
really
you should you should draw two alongside
wow
I think the whole nose eyelid holy
I did such a good job she may not look
like herself
but she looks like a pretty damn cute
girl
and I've seen a lot of these damn cute
girls I I know a pretty damn cute girl
when I see one
whoa
[Music]
I fell in love
doing really good at realism for the
first time thank you
you were a doubter
yeah cause when you get started of
course it looks like
has to
let's get the trees to help me
well I imagine me painting all of this
and then the little tiny test stroke
that I did in the beginning when the
canvas was still white imagine that
being a reason for her to say sorry you
you used more than three tools on this
I'm not accepting it I
am I'm it's not like I could reset the
the canvas anyway
I'm going to never play this game ever
again if that happens oh my God
[Music]
I could have done this so much better
otherwise if I knew I would
have to redo it anyway
then we'll only get regular ice cream
from now on crying face I feel like
you're you're actually happy about it
but
honestly
I I like playing around with these tools
because if I would have just used like
you know a normal art program
I would probably always default to the
same two two different
um brushes
I wouldn't experiment with other tools
and I like the I kind of like the look
of
the art in this game
thank you
the traditional look
act right thank you
forget the critics
and what was her name say oh I already
forgot
I don't care Danielle Margaret uh what
who
who's the lady we're doing this for I
don't care I don't know I really don't
know
I don't recall
okay
um her dress is kind of like yellow
green
[Music]
I don't know about the colors for this
I don't know
[Music]
thank you
that's a shitty green I don't like it
do I have more fitting green I doubt it
let me see
[Music]
let's check the frosty feels in game dog
yes it's in-game dog
ah absolutely not what I need looks
completely different
than what I saw in the preview okay
whatever
I think I already bought like all the
available colors too by the way
how hard
how what her dress looks like
I'm gonna go with the blue maybe even
freestyle
dress is not even the important part
[Music]
thank you
let's get
it take a shot every time someone asks
us to talk is in game um yeah you guys
have some alcohol normally I don't
support that kind of stuff but
if you want a drinking game
there's one right there asking begging
for you to play it
I'm at work
[Music]
okay maybe not now
what should we talk about give me a
shopping guys are here lost I lost all
my tensions
[Music]
witnessing the birth of an art
masterpiece thank you
oh what
I don't watch Dragon Ball no
how's the weather I don't know of
curtains closed
something new from Hello beep no today's
Monday right tomorrow
I have to cook today though after the
Stream
how did you feel a girl sock went girls
talk oh I think was fun
I mean
I had to
bring the girls back to the OG topics
every once in a while but the sunset
actually about whole talk I am
I I don't know I didn't feel so
satisfied with this week's whole talk
maybe it's the fact that
there was no singing performance and
that kind of like you know now that we
had a couple
makes you feel like something was
missing but also
um
[Music]
ah I know
I think
you know me and Thomas and boy got along
really well when we were together IRL
but I I don't know I feel like we
weren't on that day
I feel like something was off
it was okay as an episode but I just
personally I oh no
something was off to me
so it's not like the perfect episode but
it was all right
it was good and fun
[Music]
questions like to death well I mean
oh I don't think so and I don't think
necessarily they need the death I think
there was death there though
[Music]
this is a huge pattern on here
she streamed before coming to hotel
maybe she looks like low on energy too
thank you
[Music]
everyone else who knows and I think I
mean I understand like you know waiting
for the
um
translation to happen to finish might be
like boring
and all that so maybe that had to do
with it
it's okay though
I'm sure
trying to make it look like her dress
what I like about toys her if extremes
and it's hard to encapsulate all that in
one stream yeah yeah yeah I mean
I didn't even choose any Clips like that
because I thought again it would just
like you say it would be difficult to
encapsulate in a short clip as well
um
but I think the clips were also okay
but yeah and I I did put a lot of
questions in that I had to deal with
with you know her being really good with
[Music]
um
PS games because that's a fact that's
like a big part the singing and
and the FPS I think is a big part of her
whole thing so I wanted to make sure
that that was mentioned
oh well
[Music]
I haven't scheduled the next one yet
but I think it will be at least
at least two weeks if not three weeks
until
the next one
[Music]
wait
I saw violets with an entire essay yeah
I saw that too I checked out every clip
but I personally felt that they would
not be
really a good choice they're good Clips
on its own
but I look for something very specific
when it comes to all the talk clips
thank you
[Music]
it's hard to explain though
but I tried explaining it before it
needs to be compact like something funny
ideally
that can be told in like four minutes
[Music]
funny and uh should I mean I ended up
using that one collab thingy but
generally it should be something that
um
focuses on the interviewed person
not too many like collab focused things
because I want the focus to be on the
on the person I'm interviewing
okay
no I think I think I'm doing the best I
possibly can here
[Music]
foreign
wasn't too hard to find a lot of good
Solo cups for her
[Music]
I looked at so many Clips man I don't
know I don't I have this problem a lot
because I I'm looking for something
really specific
[Music]
when I when I think about
you know whole talk clips
[Music]
maybe I'm too
too picky
yeah the B necklace almost there I'm
gonna do the B necklace next after these
little stones
pretty I like these headpieces too from
medieval times
[Music]
would it be better to have fans pick
them well I kind of like
have you guys uh helped me anyway
I ended up going for something different
though I really like the compilations of
Coronet yeah but that is I I would like
to do that more often but that is really
difficult to
I think if I I think it's
[Music]
um
I don't like asking my team to do that
for me
because it's a lot of work
and unless I give like really special
like detailed inter in in instructions
like I want this part from this stream
like from second so and so until second
so and so on I want this from this
stream you know if I want to make a
compilation that's gonna be so much of
that
and that's a lot for me
if I have to go through that and create
my own compilation
out of thin air
and it's a lot for the staff to
yeah but I think the Coronet one
I think I basically I said hey I want
something like this and then they made
it or even got permission to use an
existing one I'm not sure anymore
this looks like a real painting I am
referencing a picture that is
referencing a painting I think
Natalie Dormer as a ambulance from the
Tudors yeah yeah because I love her this
is my masterpiece
start a clipping Channel no thank you
that is not my job
[Music]
um
okay
I made an animation of human crony
and you mean just today or like
previously because I think I saw it is
this garlic phone
every time I see someone else play
Guardian phone I'm like hey I also want
to play on your phone again
I want I want
foreign
[Music]
was always a lot of fun
especially remember I feel like that was
absolute absolutely genius from me
remember when I got
some some fan Community artists
to join me on
garlic film that was amazing too
[Music]
do that again
yeah that was so hype and it was so
spontaneous so many of them just joined
so spontaneously I was like hi hi this
is really random but can you you know
[Music]
okay here we go it is necklace time
she even has like another weird
necklace that goes into our boobies
if I see it correctly
it's like two of friends
black looking balls and then golden
chains
[Music]
you can only see one here
two doors
[Music]
two two doors she don't need Jewels with
this amount of beauty
[Music]
you praising my art feels like you're
praising me
[Music]
okay okay okay we're almost done we're
almost done all we're missing is the
pearls and these pearls are also going
into her boobies
I see this a lot
and
[Music]
uh medieval
Royal fashion
[Music]
I'm gonna give them
a lot of white shininess I'm just doing
the base a little bit darker
[Music]
big
let's try something okay
maybe it was a
a thing they came up with for the show
[Music]
good thing they came up with why I
appreciate it
sometimes
you know when I think of
future outfits sometimes like I low-key
consider getting like a legit
medieval Royal outfit like this
because just because of the beautiful
corset don't worry I'm not doing it I'm
not doing it
it could be cool but not if I can only
do it like once a year
and hookah would probably be like
Chihuahua
are you trying to kill me
with these ideas
[Music]
but I mean he drew came a little before
and kimonos are really really detailed
as well
so I mean
okay
[Music]
it would be really unique yeah
it would be
I don't know if I if I stay
in Hollow for another five years I will
run out of ideas probably and then maybe
maybe then I would do it
gold
the B on her necklace
[Music]
iconic
five more years let's go spoil the eight
of your outfits
[Music]
I mean it's okay I also kind of spoiled
the 2023 one
didn't I
by asking you guys for your opinion but
and honestly I don't care because if
that helps me create something that you
guys
well enjoy even more
than hell yeah
let's go to
ask you guys for what you want
I did the same for the merchandise
what you guys did you guys say omo cat
[Music]
oh my cat once again is working with us
for some uh concert related merchandise
and we also have keyboards or key cats
not foam keyboard maybe I don't know
yeah I think the Parker looks really
nice
a hoodie
generally the art on it I really like it
I think that's my favorite merchandise
concert merchandise that we have for
this concert
gonna be honest I'm not personally I'm
not a big fan of that you know that
t-shirt that we have with the letters uh
the all of her names and different fonts
packed into a square
I was against that but it was very
popular with the other girls I'm like
really
here to you guys too thank you I thought
I was the only one because even Ina even
Ina was for that
weird fonts designed
but I mean you know we're a group we're
we're a democracy
[Music]
uh the one that gets the most votes
because we had a different option too
you know
the one against the most votes
wins
wearing a black hoodie in a salmonella
sounds like torture though
oh
doing for the omo cat one are they only
doing a hoodie and a
in the back are they not doing a t-shirt
what was the other one League
it's more like a basic one
you know
just with the names one under another
it's not a leak because it's never gonna
happen so no T-shirt they should make it
because you're right L.A isn't it
hot at that time
you're right that that's weird
that's weird
they didn't think that fruit did they
but if you don't order right now by the
way it most likely won't make it in time
so if you do want the hoodie and wear it
for whatever reason to sweat yourself to
death
um at the concert
you gotta order it now
or just get the t-shirt that will not
kill you
but has a back design that kiwawa does
not like
[Music]
but you know it's not it is an
individual thing not everybody can like
everything I guess oh wait the shadow
should be on the other side
[Music]
foreign
is there already like details on that
that you guys can look at because I
don't even know like what's the price
and is there even a full keyboard
version or is it only the key keycaps
I'm interested
[Music]
there's a site for it you can already
buy them the only keycaps oh so this is
really only for those keyboard lovers
who know how to put together a keyboard
[Music]
done
I think she's done
[Music]
please
finish it done my beautiful
lady
I think I noticed something that bothers
me
this
yeah I don't think I'll get it anymore
looking like her
but that's okay she's beautiful
[Music]
what's that okay we'll see
let's check how much people would pay
for this I'm not selling it because it
is a quest wait is my is my mask what
happens if you're selling a masterpiece
[Music]
oh is that allowed
do you do you get like a new masterpiece
frame can't buy this over get in trouble
oh they look at it but they're like
we're not allowed to buy this
not allowed
yes
offer me something
they refuse it when she's gonna say
something too
they won't let me I don't think I should
buy it
why no no okay
wait we should look
we should look at the process
[Music]
whoa and Tiny looks like her
it looks like her
okay
[Music]
oh the face shape very important the
hairline looks very good in my opinion
oh
scary face features
all pretty pretty pretty
not so 100 defined yet but already
gorgeous
or is that already the final version
kind of I'd already kind of is
wow
[Music]
amazing I'll upload these on Twitter too
so I think they'll be a bit bigger on
Twitter for you guys
[Music]
I own a dog now
amazing
didn't draw uh we only drew two whole
life members today but
you know I have a commitment
and that is drawing Natalie Dormer as
Ann Berlin as my masterpiece I said this
already ages ago tag her
does she have butter
maybe I will but I feel like a lot of
celebrities that have Twitter only have
Twitter for the sake of having Twitter
and are not active there they maybe
tweet or check it like once a month or
every every three months or so
is she active on Twitter I doubt it
I don't think she has an art tag
it's basically their manager
damn it maybe she's more active on
Instagram but then for Instagram for
Instagram celebrities I'm more like
they probably won't see it unless they
follow you
[Music]
the moment of truth is she gonna
complain about the fourth tool that I
supposedly used
let's give him some space so he can get
a good look oh she put it on a nice
pedestal it looks so good on there
dude eh
[Music]
but before I can show you we need to get
our promotional efforts in order nothing
big I just need a quote for you when you
think Adrians what brings to your mind
great upgrade Visionary shop owner or
Exquisite design
is this important
um
Adrian's great upgrade Adrian's
Visionary shop owner Adrian's exquisite
exquisite
oh good good we're looking at other two
suppliers would you describe them as
mediocre limiting or unfair
um
limiting but yours were even more
limiting probably then we should say
inferior
I have everything I need for now is
promise the article I think you'll be
happy take it to the curator I hope it
will be enough changes
and there's a platinum ticket to the
museum it gives you unrestricted access
now it's all up to you to show the
curator your metal
and I show him the same picture again
because you're not telling me that oh
yeah and now I make it mixes it
sponsored by Adrian um okay
will will he take my picture my
masterpiece and hang it up in the museum
if not
then what the hell did I do it for
I mean
who goes there me I have a ticket
welcome back to the Museum of mattress
what if he turns it down because that's
three and that that video that I watched
you know it continued even after the
masterpiece
uh maybe he was just doing side quests
before because it looked like side
quests
when you look here right now
is that the same guy that just looked at
our picture he looks different to me
okay but this is divine exquisite
famous kiwawa quote sounds a bit
different now
different person
see you again no same person I don't
think you've got the Masterpiece on
let's not insult him right we shouldn't
insult him
[Music]
I was actually made Improvement since we
last met but does it really have a place
in the museum do you belong here
do you do you say belong here yourself
eh
is there a right and a wrong answer
I just say confidently yes so we have a
little surprise call Adrienne ah there
we go hey hey Adrian why are you here oh
and all my other stuff it is only the
rich people though apparently because
only the rich people apparently are um
capable of proving my worth
what tells that about Society what what
what what what is that telling us huh
don't listen to the poor Fox apparently
only listen to the rich people who only
their opinion matters
foreign
[Music]
I'd be scared I think you're the one who
is afraid
I guess we should show the art nah who
cares about the articles
[Music]
I don't know
is this important
I think this is the only game that I've
ever played
that no one not a single person in my
chat has finished
you guys did not feel like this one
like you feel like
yeah
okay
[Music]
you don't have to be able to draw for
this game what what's this the spirit of
Monet reborn yeah
this is from the top art critic the
colors blend together like a vibrant
dance between a newlywed couple
artists oh the art critics says what
convinces you what the you must
become part of this museum at once okay
so just because you saw it was popular
with other people
so it is just the
the clouds that I have
such colors I'm glad that my Justified
rejection of your inferior past has
brought you back to me stronger it was
all thanks to me yes yes
[Music]
you didn't get impressionist vibes from
my painting
as the old Traders from the max will
once more open up to the museum to the
public but before we do that let's have
a small ceremony first approach to empty
slot and Reveal Your Masterpiece is that
am I finishing the game right now
Chihuahua
see look at that kind of stuff I would
have liked to paint something like that
[Music]
that house
looks like the house from Sound of Music
[Music]
um
wow
oh all nice paintings but none of this
is a
takanashi yeah
let me show you what a takanashi is
[Music]
it will remain covered by the club until
the public reveals ceremony okay
what are champagne here
drink
marvelous
[Music]
Exquisite thank you thank you okay I'm
ready I'm ready for the
[Music]
for the big ceremony let me do it flound
size
okay when does it happen do I need once
and then they leave too
I'll go back
well they're still looking at the just
at the curtains
when are we doing the public ceremonies
in the meantime anyone wants to see you
the lady gives me the shivers
another thing I will just speed draw it
in that situation
Adrian's back at her place I assume
because that was Chantelle
yeah we'll draw a stick figure oh
[Music]
it's so cool that it's open
Adrian's tools are so cool
yeah
a new shop you can use her tools too I
think you made them cool
no I am part of the city Society
made her spend a thousands bucks for a
tool that she could have gotten for 20
elsewhere
oh no
[Music]
oh wait in the cheap one
items can be cool like you and get
Rhymes at the Museum wait if they buy
the fountain that means that's enough in
the cheap shop no
because hers is not Firefox
will be good
[Music]
I don't wanna
wait where's she is she inside here
Adrian
okay I'm going here where's she
Square oh
[Music]
she upset that they're not buying it
from her
[Music]
the whole game is looking a critique of
how fake the awkward is
yeah
maybe a carnivorous I mean I don't think
it needs to be oh
[Music]
this is like a like a sad ending I
this is not what I wanted by becoming
famous with my art
oh no
where did where did my friend go when
welcome to Adrians
how do you like my new pop-up store
don't answer it's not it's impossible to
not like it New Era awaits to Adrian era
when it's time for you to start working
according to our deal what happened with
Benjamin
survival of the fittest my friend with
success comes expensive when people stop
using those food poor Benjamin couldn't
afford to shop anymore
excuse me
yes you're right so ineffective just
sign one and I'll make my work signature
no one will notice
oh wait maybe I should have said no
is there two Endings by any chance
a bad and a good one
Benjamin
Benjamin is that from the first passport
2 game
Benjamin I'll buy it for 5 million bucks
common boy cheap boys
nice to see you again
I couldn't afford it anymore
it was his way of making art through
others it was never about fame or money
we just wanted to wanted everyone to
keep painting but it's hard when you
also add the paint uh pay rent that
bills you had to honor my grandfather's
dreams and now it's time to follow my
own dream selling art has been other
than I thought
I'm so sad I kind of like ruined his
life by using his health
to become better
and eventually go to the rich people
didn't want this to be like this
that wouldn't feel right it's something
I've worked on before quite sometimes
oh
it's always been meant for you please
take it it's yours I'm happy for you
that you finally got everything you
wanted
oh this is terrible
no
what
could it have been different
curator needs me at the Museum
really
now
okay I'll go
you're Indonesia at the Museum
don't have to make my signature you can
still get the good ending
really maybe I do have to tell him to
off
can I swap the pig
oh my God
wait my painting is over there
[Music]
this this strut this
destroyed master
this it says destroyed masterpiece
[Music]
thank you
are you a hater
what the
excuse me
it once was a nice paint I mean it still
looks nice where is it broken there's
like a fence going through it but uh
what are you gonna reveal then anyway
this is terrible boy young Misfit broken
and it's only a message
and then he confessed at least I think
he did I have a hard time understanding
what he's blabbing about I think I heard
him say that he works on commission from
a synthesizer
could you talk to him
wait can I
um it says I have to recover my
masterpiece
I'll take it
take
banking new little I died
I'm sorry I not mean
ah the punk
same promise no more
says she said I destroyed sellout
artists oh banking
[Music]
always what she says in dark thank you
no see thank you pink old boring art not
you when understood so sad so sorry you
are not a sellout are you whoever
no matter thank you
[Music]
I'll just sell it instead I'll get more
money
choice
[Music]
good talking curinder he mad at me make
him not mad okay
thank you sorry
[Music]
okay wait I'll fix it
I'll fix it yeah
so since it's a person parents give
their kids to strangers names nowadays
welcome wait you don't mean Hyacinth is
she your daughter
yeah that's your Dell's daughter she has
made incredible contributions to this
Museum
I think we can just forget this
unfortunate situation it seems like you
recovered it
you just hanging on the empty spot as
soon as you can
[Music]
I mean I would say what I made is
definitely a masterpiece
but it will be a really huge gesture to
do this
but is there really two paths like if I
went to put up this my own Masterpiece
instead and sign those things
is that a different ending
now for the final flourish Pull the Rope
and reveal the art of the world
but is Benjamin gonna be here though
[Music]
I don't see Benjamin
maybe he will come in last or he will
never know
but it's okay
I totally Drew this I mean I believe me
guys I mean no don't believe me
just leave it up there because he
deserves it
he literally is the reason why passport
2-2 came out
[Music]
hello
Benjamin
I can't believe it you did that for me
people really seem to like my art but
what did you
say you're making the museum into your
final piece of art no
I've been using that true artists
existence everywhere Among Us not only
in exclusive museums
all things to you I wanted to ask
something it's the brush again and my
grandfather gave to me before events
knowing that you're using to create
Beauty will bring in Glide so I'm sure
thank you a friend
the ending for him
what does he say about that
what does this mean why did you not
place your heart on the slot it was your
start why would you if I would tear it
down on this one but these hooligans are
rooting for you I can't be the curator
of a Teenage Museum how's that you see
my beautiful Museum fall into the ends
of the common fall I have no choice my
future lies elsewhere Beyond
Phoenix
in a place you can change idea it was
always my city I mean
[Music]
bye more calculations you would have
been more famous if your art was hanging
on the wall yeah I guess so
am I still was hiding among us all this
time
next
[Music]
time it shows you have a good heart
and he spent so much money on me
Emily you're looking at the wrong art I
always knew Benjamin was a secret artist
how the markets react to the stunts you
play today oh they were right about it
in all the newspapers
it was kind of cool to see you go your
own way
yeah
answer the art I bought has lost value
by now
you mean the art you bought from me
nah
I'm still famous
I'm even more famous than not even
better reputation Now by by helping out
my friend
quite Brave to go against the system
like you did I hope it was worth it
[Music]
I still think the harbor is a true Gemma
Phoenix
agreed the museum I didn't realize
I've missed coming here until now
Minecraft
never been here before I didn't even
know there was a museum
maybe it's better to
close it down and do something else with
it
Bobby
yeah
excuse me
excuse me what
what rude
please
but you're in support of it aren't you
hmm
I knew he would be on our side
I knew it I the punks I'm not gonna
talk to them especially not sin
yeah
so what now is that the ending
what did they say didn't they say I
still have to do something I had
something to do
foreign
[Music]
I go to my house
oh the store is
[Music]
and Maggie is in it
hello welcome to Benjamin this feels
like cool here because new I'm shame to
get this old place back and he enables
me to take care of it I've always wanted
to be closer to Art so I'm like super
grateful
oh okay he doesn't have to work his own
store anymore he just owns it
and what is this game over
what Adrian do I have to go to her house
or is she because the curator went down
down the left right
I mean he left the island
oh big
okay I'll go all the way up again
she was at the Museum I didn't not talk
to her
oh wait they're going though they're
going home I see her she's up to her
house too
[Music]
um
what
okay we have to call her I think she
said uh could you assist please
we should Rob her place
like Robin Hood
grab all this and give it to the other
artists
inspiring artists don't you think
is the sun extra bright today
is
there to understand its purpose it is
only Annoying you could help me out
though I have these special Pennsylvania
sunglasses that really do the job but it
doesn't matter
dominant in Superior
I shall reward you with a unique Marvel
canvas that money cannot fight this game
is not done
isn't it weird that you're still making
me do things else would be a nice way to
end the game at the stream
especially because I have to record
something tomorrow at 7 00 am
foreign
[Music]
she wanted it to what be
edgy or
Master brush oh yeah right I got this
from
where
I don't care about this I don't want to
put effort into this
is it over yeah is it just for Cycles
Papa
[Music]
no credit yeah right it can't end
without credits right
yeah here take this
I don't know what it is
I don't know I don't care here there you
go okay
Pennsylvania eyes here we're in
Pennsylvania pencil vanion
eyes hurt right here
[Music]
what does she want
can we make it pure black
he does not like it
it was too cheap
should it be because she's kind of like
golf
[Music]
maybe we make it look black purely black
burgundy
oh
try
um
[Music]
that's burgundy right
don't forget the edges okay and then
white
[Music]
maybe around the eyes
make her eyes pop more
and ideally some purple I guess because
like she's also a bit purple
[Music]
looks like a
a wrestling yes wrestling mask
s
I'm done with this for today if the end
is near I might play it off screen if
it's worth doing another stream about it
we'll think about it
I don't care anymore
[Music]
it was supposed to be a short frame and
now it's five hours again
have I ended it already
is it gonna be put on on on my chihuahua
finished games list because otherwise I
am not happy
I just got here thankfully
you missed all the masterpieces I drew
today every single one was a masterpiece
it's just post game from how it looks
um okay okay
[Music]
we have this here thank you
I love the shibalista yeah that one
turned out good too
LaPlace it was just until I'm not this
unhappy with my art today
surprisingly and maybe it will change in
an hour or so
yeah where are the credits
I need to see the credits
maybe if I exit
whoa
[Music]
can you try to sell tonight I should
maybe they'll buy it now also and my
picture is still not there is that
normal
let me try the salad though
no credits what did you look it up
if there will be credits
I'm surprised or just always there where
where maybe the red credits are the
chat messages
you guys do look like you could be
credits
see
it's text that goes up
you guys look like credits you guys are
the ones I want to cry
okay
um well let's place the father rich
people
[Music]
what do you say you like this one didn't
you
um
perhaps you should realize that this
shouldn't be
well
but the whole museum deal is done it's
over
[Music]
really you're not gonna buy it
maybe the other is what's happening I
guess not I guess I can hang it in my
house forever
hmm
but then they'll always wander around my
house looking for something to buy and
then they'll be like Oh I'm not buying
this though
I'm buying this though not buying this
either no no
hmm
let me try again here
maybe they have a different stance but
I'm guessing not
I can't buy this from you okay
okay well I mean a masterpiece maybe
should stay in my own hands anyway until
I die and then you know the historic
people they'll be like oh wow wow this
this Picasso heart I'm gonna make
millions of money uh out of now after
he's dead I don't know if that really
happened but
Benjamin Benjamin
no Benjamin
I don't know where Benjamin is
it was oh there he is he was happy
though
he was very happy
birthday
to take care of it properly so now I can
focus on doing what I love and that's it
okay okay
[Music]
hahaha
I guess I mean
it would be weird if the game just ended
there because they just gave you the
master brush so you should be able to
use it you know somewhere
you have to cook and sleep yep yep yeah
um
[Music]
okay thank you guys for watching my bro
my throat is kind of dead I feel like
the air was dry and I talked I tried to
talk much
[Music]
go try to make some food now
yum
you guys for watching hope you enjoyed
it a very chill stream
with me proving that I am a real artist
after all oh my God I'm lagging let's
close the game
I'll see you guys uh
tomorrow or the day after tomorrow I
ended up taking tomorrow off right yeah
okay oh yeah but I have to I
7 00 am
recording a little program
[Music]
yeah you guys will see it later on I
don't know when
but later on
the last artist was Benjamin all along
oh is that what they're trying to say
that's sweet yeah
[Music]
I think it's nice I mean you know we
were in the same position of like an
underappreciated artist just like him
and he was kind of her sensei in the
beginning
um so I feel like our character also
deserves all the all the appreciation
and accomplishments
but Benjamin of course
deserves it too although my art was
objectively better
yeah no he deserves it to be in that
museum yeah yeah more than me yeah yeah
yeah
thank you guys for watching energy and
I'll see you guys on Wednesday for some
Korean study and I think I'll I won't
have that stream
um be too long so I will read super
chats after it ends and hopefully be
able to catch up um
thank you
thank you finished pieces on Twitter so
go check them out you know in their full
Glory because they look a bit bigger I
think uh in screenshot for him yeah
yeah good night
it was a pleasure uh Yours Truly kiwawa
Da Vinci bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
what's going on
um
yeah I think I also record my singing
Tomorrow Rick
singing very important
[Music]
foreign
come on
[Music]