[Music]
um
uh
[Music]
oh
i'm going to
i die going to die for sure
i am going to die for sure
[Music]
why is my
um
[Music]
oh
take a sip of that monster energy drink
the most
[Music]
um
i found my hat about my hat
do you guys know that feeling when like
the the middle of your
chest feels like uh
really like i don't know weird pounding
and when your whole body feels tingly
it's not
love it's i don't think this is love
okay is there an echo still
um that's still from the last stream
[Music]
how does this work again
huh wait let me go over here i think
then i know how to do it
ignore that
i forgot how to do it
oh
ah echo sounds nice
should we go to the echo for an hour
help amelia
amelia have technical help support
please
emilia she's still there you slept slop
sleep sloppy
amelia does get there
out blue and you're very confused
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm really like so
tired i
i remembered how oh my gosh
[Music]
this was not this wasn't how it was
supposed
to be i was supposed to be like really
really uh energetic in my
first stream after the w like originally
i was planning to
sleep after my debut
until the collab and then
do my soul stream and then just go on
normal
but after my like you know
before my stream i the day before my
stream
the night before my stream i guess i was
so nervous i
i couldn't sleep like but i was like
really scared and nervous
it was like a bad nervous anxiety thing
but the night after in my stream which
was just
now and i was
like so happy that i couldn't sleep
i know
so i i i've been away for over
24 hours
now i will play i will play
blah how was my first stream everyone
sorry i really want to be more energetic
oh my god i think the collab took the
last energy out of me but
a lot of
until uh the collab with cali i still
don't really know
at what time that is but was it good
you got that ah
thank you
i'm starting to speak in my native
language i didn't say a word
in my native language which is of course
bert
[Applause]
the reason why i took a slot at this
time
because my stream was like like
at a certain time that was bad for other
people
i figured okay next dream gonna be at a
time that is better for those people
for who it was bad well it makes sense
and i thought i really thought i could
sleep after the first stream but that
wasn't ridiculous
i was like on reddit
for maybe an hour and yeah
you know i was so worried so i really
wanted to know what you guys are
thinking
but like everything was so positive i
didn't expect it so
i was so happy i couldn't stop reading
sleep stream can you imagine my first
stream after devio being a sleep stream
oh yeah yeah but since i'm so tired i
i i i wrote down some things i want to
talk about
maybe it was just maybe 30 minutes fall
guys and 30 minutes talking if that's ok
is that okay good idea
gotta drink more monster
i feel like the monster is making
everything worse though
water is next to me but i still choose
to take the energy drink
by the way amelia you deceived me you
have deceived me i know you like iced
tea
i know you i know you like iced tea more
than i know you bamboozled me by riding
only tea
but i was thinking you just forgot to
ride ice
there i was thinking we're talking about
iced tea
i was thinking was iced tea or water no
i was like oh for sure she likes iced
tea the most
just like me
bamboozle me this is my favorite word
i've been using it maybe
50 times in the past two days
ah we we do love ice tea don't we
mmm really good
after the first stream i have reached
100k subscribers
18 months
[Music]
yay
yeah you're probably good at fall guys
right you seem like
someone who's good at pockets will be my
first time
[Music]
i was like really uh worried
um about everything panic
real panic mode but
um it went so well
i'm really happy i was really glad
actually i thought that
like right before the stream i was so
nervous
however eh i really thought it was gonna
be like until the end but
soon after i started it was just
i don't know i think the nice comments
really just overwhelmed me and then i
was like
this is a good place to be
um
tomorrow
[Music]
right now i didn't want to um
i didn't want to overlap with her stream
but when i
took my uh slot
she was i would never overlap my stream
with her on purpose
and fight
i mean i always watch some backlash and
by streaming archive
because i kind of like um i usually
watch them like before i go to sleep and
those are like times where she's
often not streaming so and i watch it
like for hours like two to five hours
per day
um
um i'll be watching an archive
i'm sorry if i could ask him but he
didn't wanna
overlap i'm so sorry i love you
[Music]
um
i can do her her angry
yells they sound so scary
like when she's really angry i don't
know how she does it
all right she really rolls the r2 like i
should be able to do that actually
because
like in german rolling the r is like
totally normal
but when i speak japanese it doesn't
come out so easily
doing personal hair laugh i don't i
don't want to like try it and then
fail me
maybe it's like
[Music]
i'm not trying
it doesn't come out anymore
wait that was my natural life sometimes
like my
my laugh can like really change like i
have
i have so many laughters i i've realized
sometimes this
see
it's so it wasn't really so good well
i've been watching
oh my god you know actually i i
at some point like since i don't watch
your streams
i've been watching streams um on archive
always so at some point i started like i
don't
want to see like every stream from the
beginning of her time
so i went i i listed uh his streams
in order of like uh the oldest to the
newest so i started from the oldest
and now i already reached the news i
pretty much watched everything
[Music]
especially the minecraft streams are
like so
i don't know why i can watch them for
hours because originally i never had
interest in minecraft
i i really didn't like have any
interest in minecraft because like i'm a
sucker for
games with like good graphics
so like games like that usually turn me
off
because i like rpg games you know like
especially the new ones
you get what i mean but now that i
watched like
probably a million hours of her stream
i felt like i want to try it too so
eventually i'll probably be streaming
minecraft as well oh shots fine
[Music]
oh oh [\h__\h] will you play against an
impact
oh i'm i'm planning on it yes
i'm planning on it
um
games that are in like an anime style
especially like normal rpgs are fine too
yeah i guess oh yeah well i prefer that
anyway i'm yeah i'm like
basic
oh yeah and then since uh actually rise
ryza 2
is coming up soon i uh yeah i found my
hats by the way
after the arizona 2 is coming up so
before that releases i wanted to play
out atelier rizza
and because i actually i played a bunch
of italian games but i didn't
uh i didn't touch atelier ariza yet so i
thought it would be perfect to do it
like
right before the the actual release of
atelier writes that too would you like
to see that
i feel like atelier games are
[Music]
i like playing them because they're like
relaxing
but i don't know about streaming would
you enjoy that
i don't realize
actually like i wanna i still like
didn't play xenoblade and i was really
interested in it so actually i
i'm i'm like having this crisis
like wanting to watch your stream but
also don't want to get spoiled because i
want to play the game on stream
eventually
[Music]
because
oh i never played the persona game
before
never where's the fall guys oh yeah we
have decided on starting fall guys
uh in the middle of the stream because
i'm dead but i'm regaining my energy
right now that's pretty good
ah i didn't really take a look at that
game yet
but also um i played like pretty much
every tales of the game
so i don't know if i should what do you
guys think about um
if i play tales of games that i already
played
it's probably not interesting generally
i also don't enjoy replaying games that
i already played
so we gotta i think we gotta wait until
one comes out that i didn't play at
anyone
and also taste of cilia too
um dark souls
ah i'm not sure i never took like a
a close look at it but
i think it's like probably too dark for
me
i'm brightest as the sun i'm in phoenix
so i gotta play bright games
okay guys oh ah yeah there will be an
archive stream
actually
i don't think my account is ready for cc
so i'm not sure what to do about that oh
near automata i bought that game
but then like i um i
never got beyond that point where
i probably was still like the tutorial
or something
where you reach that like you know when
you run in that
little in the beginning in those ruins
the whole time
and then there's like this boss
i never was able to fight that boss
why is it so hard
yeah there are no checkpoints i had to
keep on like starting over and over and
over again it was so hard and then
eventually like after trying again and
again
i was so sick of it like the game is so
beautiful but oh it's so hard i need
easy games
there's cheeks for that eh
tomato
anyway um i'll get into four guys now
and uh
look let's go i guess
i've never played four guys before
24 hours so please
forgive me for not being at my best
wait where's the chem key oh you'll see
the screen for the first time
[Music]
yay oh the bucket is behind me
you shall go here i always have chicken
ready to eat
oh guys about the bucket oh i feel like
throwing up oh my god
about the bucket um before my debut
stream
already like actually i made this bucket
like ages ago in preparation but like
before the stream like uh
uh when i released the twitter and
people um people actually designed their
own pockets for me and i was like
guys how do you know that i made a
bucket and why are you making better
buckets than the one that i made
[Music]
they even had like really similar
designs to mine so i was like wait that
looks like mine
just better i guess
i don't need my own bucket anymore i can
just use yours why did i even bother to
make my own bucket
i didn't think you guys would make
buckets for me
but it's kfp okay well there were some
really good buckets man
really good [\h__\h] hell did you hear
the music how does this work
oh oh window mode oh i need to move
stuff
i have this on window mode okay i
usually don't play games on
i haven't actually i honestly haven't
played uh like a proper
game on my pc for ages
oh i want i really like
yeah i don't know where it is so i'm
playing with keyboard i i heard it was
fine with keeper
where you can follow your controls move
right
d move left hey out all the basic
controls
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] so much oh i need a control next
time
what if i get used to that ooh you can
do emote
this is really like i i watched some uh
paul guy streams
also of course from pecora senpai
i kind of know what's going on wait so
space was jump right and sea turtle was
wait what was your girl
oh we start from here guys i really
never played i wanted like the first
impression of it to be on stream
crap move across your microphone let's
let's not grab anyone yet because i'm
not used to it
i forget like so quick but you have to
keep in mind i've been
i've been awake for over 24 hours
they'll kill
i can't remember those buttons those
three buttons
jump and dive do i even need that let's
just start out with jumping only only
wait how
again
i thought i could get out of the
settings
i'm such a noob wow
well that's all right you can go again
[Music]
guys
oh that's me i'm pink but i want the
chicken outfit i've seen a chicken
outfit
okay i fly
i fly high
dizzy heights how to play navigate the
obstacles and race to the finish line
well i've seen all i think i've seen all
of the stages before in um
in other people's streams
no wait i want to change the settings
this is weird after all this feels weird
can i change
settings
i want the arrow keys instead give me
that
only we'll have to do this will be a big
fail
ah
okay
as bad as me that's impossible
[Music]
is that lagging i feel like maybe a bit
laggy
okay oh we can do it there how how oh
yeah it is
well i mean what did you expect
oh yeah okay i have to say like normally
i really only play like ipg games i
don't play these kind of games
is there any comparable game like this
that i might have played before i don't
know matt
next
i might have to change the game settings
somehow to make it less laggy i don't
know what settings work best
and noob slime clip oh no i've seen this
is horrible oh no you died so quickly
here i've seen like really
a certain person dying so quickly
no no wait who am i oh
i was like why did i change my costume
oh
i'm sleeping i i have to say again for
everyone who just came
i've been awake for 20 20 for over 24
hours
i thought they were just going to send
me off to the next game right away like
to the next like round
not round for like the other group like
oh my god
yeah bye bye
big brain oh and maybe deciding wow
whatever you know
you know how i'll be better next time
i don't need sleep
hurry up i need to win
guys how i was thinking of like next
time i stream fall guys i'll do an rta
until i get the chicken costume how long
does that take
hello nobody wants to play with me
20 hours seven week watch
for it hello
hi there oh the worldly gig
oh this is no problem
it doesn't take that long depending on
okay
maybe not the second fall guy stream
maybe if i get a little bit better we
can do an rt
by the
a way
what was he talking about oh i was
pushing the rocks
oh thank you is that the right direction
though
how do i grab jump and do everything at
the same time
oh nice nice that was what i planned
can i change the camera how do i choose
oh the mouse
ah the luck is with me okay so i've seen
that like going in the middle is not
such a good idea
you're gonna
okay okay i want to try the middle it
looks like fun
[Music]
tata
well these people really have to wait a
long time for me to get through hot oi
stand up
[Music]
ah
um
much better than the beginning look out
there we get there
what was my question oh wait we have to
get out of here i remember i was going
to stay again we had to get out of here
let me get out of here what was my
question oh yeah so there's a new season
starting right on
fall guys does the chicken costume
disappear with the new season
oh let me out here
oh hold your hand
you think i'll be better after i slept i
highly doubt it
it will disappear not if i unlock it oh
no i have to get it
on
japanese comments that uh no no wonder
she could manage to get out of the
tutorial of near automata
we'll get there i'll i'll get better oh
i still didn't change the statics
level 25 28 that will take ages wait how
much more time do i have
level 28
you can back out oh
thank
i feel like i'll feel more comfortable
if dc
said where was it right i [\h__\h]
probably right yeah we left
he died
[Music]
i kind of i think i want to change dive
it's kind of like a bad spot
i think i want maybe like here
can you find that one no you can't use
that one
let's go with one it's already assigned
oh
no cancel oh well i don't need a mode
soon
oh yeah whatever don't need to move
anymore
oh no
oh yeah how did we get i don't want to
leave again up over here
let's go you don't like my controls
what's your problem with my controls
are you going to jump in
it's space yeah
but you will be fine that's over the
shore
what left-handed keyboard no but
i don't know it feels easier yeah i'm a
left-handed person
it felt so weird what i did just now
that's why
you gotta use the mouth
ah indeed cannot use mouse it's okay i
didn't have the
time to use the mouse anyway
this is a very chaotic
we can do it without mouse i just have
to stop if i have to
uh adjust it
how much time do i need to become level
28 though
my control's changed oh wait camera
ah
oh
this is the worst this is the worst fall
guys stream
i have ever seen okay so this we do
i think
oh is that not grab did i not is i know
one ah cg or else
this dude
hey he has the chicken costume
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
with every other um fall guy stream that
i have seen
the stream snipers are like bullying
the streamer but you guys are helping me
well like you're waiting for me that is
the sweetest thing i've ever seen
that is
let me out here i don't have time this
is so funny
okay it's so hard with keyboard though i
i
um i realized that uh
okay oh i'm such a shitty gamer
[Music]
uh i have regret
everything i did so oops now
let's let's not make into this again
guys
and then mouse uh i'll try before i
didn't even have my hand on the mouse i
will try to
reset i guess so i didn't even have my
hand on the mouse
because i yeah
but but those buttons are all too close
like i can't
do jump and grab at the same time
grab is left oh
oh that's smart
grab this left click what take it
it it didn't it doesn't take it
oh i don't have to set it it just does
it
guys what is your impression of me right
now with my first game stream what's
your impression of me
it's left click on the fault oh that's
awesome why didn't you tell me earlier
on
let's go one more my impression of you
is yes
that is wonderful
uh okay and right click was the diving
thing
left click is grabbing right click is
diving
impression is do your best
you need sleep that is very true
i don't know but right now i feel so
awake again
i wonder if i can sleep like i actually
i really need to sleep
i hope there's people who help me again
in this round how do you guys even do
that how do you
manage to get into where i am
you guys are lucky to meet a majestic
phoenix in action
okay with the mouse i think this will be
so much easier here we go
oh oh grabby grip i want to go okay
this is so much better
[Music]
you shall not pass
i will pass i will pass very much see
this is
this is an easy stage
movie
i wasn't even that bad
so like
it was just a problem of the controls to
be honest like for real though for real
yay my first qualification
papa
[Music]
m
uh grab use how to grab a tail wait
which one was grab
i think oh no this is difficult i'm just
gonna run
wait why don't i have a tail from the
beginning
i feel like someone will give me just a
tale out of being
kind maybe they already stopped being
kind to me
no no i've come so far
oh my mouse is kind of like
i wanna i wanna see the last stage okay
oh
okay today go i will stream until
i mean there's only eight minutes left
but i'll stream until
oh i thought it got i was doing once
i get into the lantern oh my oh my god
you shall
[Music]
yay
energy
boy
oh i can remove the cursor now
i did not qualify today let's get out of
here i'll press delete
i didn't in that last moment i
i made it
cool oh this is uh i just have to
remember or follow everyone else
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
you'll go i can do this oh i'm really
still in
i thought this was the end okay the
mouse is so weird
what what what uh look look
grapes i think oranges which is like
glad girl
oh right oh grapes and oranges
this is that's um i forgot what are we
looking for
uh where were the grapes
grape banana that's all i can do
watermelon grape banana
huh
that did not
orange grape cherry something
and the watermelon i cannot remember
that orange
grape mango cherry is over there
orange grape mango yes i remember this
one
yeah oh bye bye losers
flawless victory my stream fans
nice
all right is next the final
[\h__\h] brain galaxy brain
no okay well i think we still got far
but let's don't let's try to get into
finals
rock and roll work together oh if my
team is good
then i'll get into the finals just like
push it right just push it
when i'm in the middle yes i will take
responsibility
of these bowls these follow
okay we need to do something here like
no
but with that yellow
[Music]
no no no no no
no no no where are my stream snipers let
me win
come on come on yes
yes bye blue
it was my destiny
hmm
final wow that was easy it was just a
matter of the controls
then you see pro gameplay
hey do i get the b the b states
but that will be hard give me an easy
one oh
oh this honestly every time i saw
someone else do this i
i thought it was like looked so
oh i'm on it what if i just stand on it
the whole time
a big friend let me stand on you
america doesn't
this is like this is so much fun this
reminds me of
no no no no
that reminds me of my childhood whenever
that was five million years ago
you know that game where you like jump
over rope i think everyone knows what
the hell why am i even asking
is this dude trying to lose y'all better
try to lose so i can
no no no no no no
i'm so young
was a good introduction to the game i
would say
wait that was the final though right i
made it into the final
nice wow
but i mean huge improvement from the
beginning
i was so funny i was laughing at myself
because you were so ridiculous
i can sleep finally after a probably 26
27 hours
how how am i even awake i don't
understand
don't do it okay now
now this game made me so excited again i
was so tired when i started this dream
and i'm so excited again
i'm not even tired what the hell how
can someone just punch me
[Music]
one thing i wanted to say that i didn't
want to forget i got some
uh i like a lot i not a lot but like a
few people said something that my
mic is [\h__\h] and which i'm confused about
because actually
uh this is a really good mic and i
probably just messed up like some
settings or did them wrong because
actually
uh kelly the
super professional rapper gave me this
mic
and it's actually a really good mic
i just don't know and probably did
something wrong with the settings
it sounds like it has a it's a really
good one it's like an expensive
blue mic
[Music]
i'll have to figure out like uh what are
the right settings but for now please uh
deal with this it should be a good mic
it sounds okay like so many people said
my mic sounds like [\h__\h]
it was like eh i i got that because my
old mic was [\h__\h]
it's a balance because this is one more
thing i wanted to talk about because
like
some people are also confused because i
said um
uh i will be using a little bit less
japanese in my normal streams and then
i'll be doing japanese only streams as
well
uh so yeah i don't know what's today's
balance good
is
it's actually like really hard to uh
realize yourself how much you're
actually speaking into each language
it was okay okay so would it be fine for
you if i continue on like this because i
i'd really like to like um have like a
worldwide audience you know
and i and i just enjoy speaking japanese
and i enjoy like
like i like like the english audience is
really funny and also the japanese
audience is really funny so i want to be
on both sides
get the best of both sides
[Music]
my
german is so embarrassing
but um i just felt like people asked uh
for german streams a little bit but like
i feel like most
german speaking people can speak english
anyway so
i'm like is there really a need for it
but maybe like at some point maybe just
like
once in a lifetime but i have many
lifetimes
maybe more than once in a while nine
nine nine it's magnesium nine nine
nineteen
[Music]
then i'm really actually i'm feeling it
again like my body feels so weak
i don't know the adrenaline came out
again with four guys that was really fun
i'll play it again
uh in my next stream i didn't uh
schedule yet i was thinking
what i should do um would you like
to do a like a q and a like a
marshmallow thing
[Music]
maybe if i'll see like how i feel
tomorrow and then i'll decide if i
stream tomorrow
and then maybe we can do a marshmallow
like uh if you i don't know if you know
what that is it's like sending questions
anonymously
okay uh if i do that i'll open up a
marshmallow and let you all guys know on
twitter so everyone follow me on twitter
and
[Music]
so let's have some more talk when i feel
better and
energetic actually i'll see you at cali
stream
all right okay
okay thank you everyone i still need to
think of like an ending greeting
if you have suggestions let me know on
twitter about the end decorating
ending greeting i can't speak english
anymore
good night
oh yes
[Music]
i love you subscribe
good night the phoenix
is now going to die
cinemas i can't leave so much fun