[Music]
thank you
hahaha
questions
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
okay
hi everybody
Welcome to day two of The Marvelous
Adventures in Anime Studio yeah
things have been improved since
yesterday because well first of all
we're not playing a game we're not
trying to capture I mean we are
capturing two people but
I'm a brought down the uh about her PC
over huh so now we have two pieces and
more power and well speaking of The
Marvelous amen do you wanna
uh
[Applause]
[Music]
hello hello puppet this is the puppet
just any normal puppet with light sticks
even oh
yesterday we were just talking about it
like oh I wonder if we can do live sex
version of the Amelia puppetson that
looks better than the the the sock
puppet that I made of you there's been
there
thank you
[Music]
oh can I also say it because you just
mentioned task I didn't even ask for it
but thank you so much because like over
the night husk fixed my skirt
um yesterday I have to say the physics
you know especially when jumping on
trampoline were really cool like you
know flowy but this is a tight skirt
right so it's not supposed to go like
the hair should be like that but not the
side skirt and now look
it's staying on my butt as it should and
there's maybe you guys know this the
Collision is gone
freaking genius for continues
didn't even ask for it
look at my skirt I'm in I'm trying I
can't turn that way look
beautiful I like it oh my God
[Applause]
oh
yeah thank you thank you thank you and
so one more difference yesterday is
yesterday we just didn't have hand
tracking on and today you know because
we recorded the motion capture for my
upcoming music video we're gonna say
upcoming it's like two months away or so
so you know don't get excited but
um yeah because of that we wanted to try
to get the finger tracking going but in
the end we gave up on the end and
actually this is not even proper finger
tracking but yesterday we just had the
the hands completely turned off so now
I can go like hmm
Loki Loki finger her tracking right Emma
yeah yeah yeah
it's better than yesterday big
Improvement and no legs
amazing food yeah it really does 60 FPS
sexy FPS
yeah it is it's really 60 FPS are we
streaming in the 60 FPS
[Music]
is there a 60fps option I'm using a
60fps capture card especially working
I think it looks pretty damn smooth
can't get much sooner oh yeah they say
yeah wow
amazing I'm a studio
I'm a studio best studio yeah yeah we
recorded already some stuff today so I
have to say I'm pretty kutakuta pretty
exhausted already but I at least don't
have to sing because here is a
disclaimer for today's stream I was
smart I pre-recorded the audio but I did
it kind of okay style there's no mixing
okay it's just like I took it in one
take and that's what we'll be playing
while I dance and I act as if I'm
singing live totally live hit the gritty
I heard that recently yeah what's
hitting the gritty how does that you
know that uh you like put your hands up
and then you put your hands down
what do you like do like robot up in the
sky
and now bend down no no bend the whole
back ah what bend my back yeah you did
that do like this you like this
Ah that's it is that it is that what it
is I don't know is it like this
I just recently heard about it no no
this thing is not pre-recorded this is
wrong that's wrong
um somebody said I'm hitting the girl no
no I'm not not hitting the gritty damn
what what is it what does the word
gritty mean
was the word gritty mean
uh it means I think you're Grody Grody
means like gross but I don't think Grady
means that hold on look at how gritty
like a grid of like a like a like some
some grid on on the floor or
just recent I think wasn't it even in uh
didn't they even mention it in the
spider-verse movie
I'm not sure oh oh
NFL best of the Grady yeah
what does it mean to hit the Grady how
do you hit the girly in real life next
question Zach Wilson
catches TD and hits you is it like a
sports thing
ha play it play it play it which one
this one
um
yeah
okay how does
how does Zach hit the gritty oh this is
uh not baseball what do you call this
again oh not the soccer football oh
wow
is it like this oh my God
that's nothing special
it's like when he's really excited I
guess
I may do that too
well you have no feet and that's a
really important part
hit the curtain hit the green
man
[Laughter]
it's almost like the number maybe that
was inspired by the real runs
I normally don't know where don't run I
guess similar actually yeah
Okay so
yeah
um by the way that's fine
is my background music
[Music]
is that Harry Potter
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
change the station so yeah
um I just want to say okay for you guys
maybe it's cool but I'm kind of a
perfectionist so just want to say
disclaimer this is not the best version
of me dancing against upcoming songs
okay
um well and then a lot of these I
learned like 10 years ago
and I tried to remember them yesterday
it turns out it's not like bicycle
riding oh almost but not quite so some
parts are a little bit iffy I even
forgot how to dance the first song which
we're gonna dance now which I talked I
remember before right so I'mma should
know how to dance with you
[Music]
you saw me dancing in VR before here
comes the real deal
okay uh you can make the chat like
thinner on my screen
make them thinner make them
blue yeah beautiful okay
yeah
I actually want to move the chat a
little bit more like
it
yeah and guys um rides in the chat if
there's a delay or something
or if you hear audio down below if it's
allowed to quiet I made in front of the
PC so she can take care of it anytime
yeah it's moving it's moving it's not
moving on your side no huh
it looks ah good it looks different on
my side
is that supposed to mirror what I have
on my screen yeah oh it's coming back oh
I think it's a placement you see how I'm
a muppet is going crazy [\h__\h] that's
that's her touching the mouse
there's a naked hand
I saw them on my pretend now now okay
for now
Okay Okay Hand reveal it was naked
Asana
we gotta close the curtain oh man
all right all right I'm ready you ready
yeah warm up this is just a warm-up song
okay guys
okay
here we go
[Music]
out there
that was just a test tell us guys what's
the problem
they were saying some stuff I saw that
uh
what muffled
audio sounds like underwater Oh
laughs
kind of low
the music is a little low but music low
and muffled
was it going for the wrong
no lag but audio was low
muffled
aha
[Music]
um
it was it uh maybe in
um I'm gonna check the monitor ring of
the audio input maybe I don't know what
I'm not an OBS so monitoring
of the audio input capture or is it
going through
which one is it supposed to be going for
we'll figure it out it's not being
monitored
does it sound guys like it's coming for
the microphone
vocals will clearer than the song I
think they're just saying the music
sound like is coming from an 80s Boombox
well
it's it's it's
cheap instrumentals
um
it's coming from my headphones uh-huh
oh really
um
walkie-talkie Kiana
okay everything's fine right really
I think so really yeah
she says it's fun
okay I heard
pretend like I was singing but I forgot
it first okay okay guys
okay I'll I'll I'll try to not break the
immersion
okay should I start again yeah but don't
forget to cheer too okay
here we go
[Music]
hello
okay
Young
[Music]
mama
you know
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
imagine me again
hi Kelly
yeah I saw her in the chat that's why I
was leaving
did you see guys I was hitting the
greedy because it was fitting the lyrics
actually oh Bale's best too what the
[\h__\h]
Studio
[Music]
I was just a warm up it was just a warm
up
again I know this I noticed that I think
I need to move the
let's swing down a little bit okay
the one song that I taught you girls in
VR chat
remember
yeah I still I still remember how it
goes
well it's a classic good old classic
okay
what's the checking looking good right
yeah
it's so good I'm gonna make the most out
of it today even though my muscles are
[\h__\h] dead after these days
audio kind of low raise it 10 somebody
said okay really really
okay okay
should we shall we do another one let me
drink some water
out of uh we are chat mug
okay
sounded good really it started good but
it looked like everything was red on our
side oh well okay we're raising it again
hi everybody
okay what should we do can you show me
my folder and what songs I have
um
okay let's do
oh did we not download the last one well
I I have it oh okay somewhere
I downloaded it okay oh maybe
we shall do that one
maybe or we'll do another one first
while this is downloading
depends on how much oh
really it's really fast
it's really fast okay
um let's do
um
your mouse was on it the last one yeah
yeah
a calm one this one's not so difficult
oh it starts immediately
ready yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
sucking
sucking news
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
la la la
[Music]
because
foreign
[Music]
now I got it
[Applause]
but I can't do the hands oh
yeah
you have to imagine the Killer I mean
you know that song no I've never heard
it before it's just a classic from my
cross
um
and I was secondhika from a good old
Macross from Diana
[Music]
simple chorus like she's just singing
now maybe you want to see something with
more action action
more action
okay okay
remember
my Rococo
my home pretty uh karaka stream where I
was like trying to dance and it was all
right but I was feeling so frustrated
that I can't show you the real
hip first
yeah the upcoming song has
a lot of hip thrusts
um but don't make it weird okay
so let's do
jeans Masala Masala Masala yes
oh
okay here we go ready let's see if I
remember this let's go
[Music]
imagination
my eyes
[Music]
foreign
illuminations
[Music]
my mommy
Mommy
[Music]
foreign
why the [\h__\h] did it end early
what the [\h__\h]
well it's almost all very good
it continues right a little while but
it's supposed to go well that's weird
that's actually the second time or
something
is wrong with the video but
let's not send anyone to the usual room
yet
I gave
bring in my power
to make that look good though
how did that look guys
I put I put so much into my hip breasts
I'm feeling a little bit dizzy it's
[\h__\h] hot in here
Eric air conditioning non-existent
thank you
honestly Muppet I'm gonna do hip rest
no no no no no no no no no no
no not don't blame it on Amazon
it's so hot I'm gonna take off this
super sweaty
once you catch a suit huh
sweat
not time to take it off yet that's a
dance mom I have to dance also guys I've
been trying to keep up the face capture
but don't hate me and sometimes I just
because I move my head so much it just
stops capturing my face guys okay
doesn't mean I'm not singing I'm trying
yeah sometimes it will stop capturing
the face okay we just have like one
camera here breaking your immersion
right now but you know
it doesn't always capture it can't keep
up there's too much movement going on
here
Ah that's a little chit chat before we
go on to the next song turns out you
know yesterday I mean I watched
for how long
two hours
and I was waiting
I was laying and I was like hmm well
should I walk over because I was getting
really worried at some point
um but
uh then I just went to get breakfast at
Denny's so that was really good Denny's
breakfast
I want to go to Dennis again
yeah cause like the first I had
breakfast on the first night at my hotel
so it was kind of bad kind of nothing
there so I went to denny's oh there's
like everything and they have so much
sweet stuff too and they put so much
fruit on top
it's really good actually like very
different from the Denny's in Japan
I mean did you go to a Denny's in Japan
yeah oh yeah we went together
too I'd probably waited for like an hour
to get in
was that the Denny's yeah yeah
but the food was really good
what do you prefer a Japanese or
American Denny's
because I you know I always go to
American days not always
studies
it's really yummy yeah like American
then uses breakfast filters but Japanese
dinners is like everything yeah actually
there barely is anything like breakfast
related in the Japanese Denis it's
mostly like lunch and dinner yeah
American breakfast is pretty different
too yeah I was so surprised I was
looking at the menu and like pretty much
like all the sweet options like the
sweet pancakes and so on they all come
with like eggs and bacon on the side so
there's always something Savory with the
sweet stuff and hash browns and stuff
yeah yeah
yeah I could choose between different
yeah meat options
I thought you know you have to order
that separate but no it just comes as I
said and at first I was like
um
something sweet with bacon and eggs now
I don't know normally I wouldn't mix
these things but it was really good I
just ate it separately I didn't combine
it but you should have a bacon pancakes
bacon pancakes
how's that look is the bacon in the
pancake yeah they put it in the pancake
no
oh it's really good I mean actually I
haven't tried it before but this song If
you haven't tried it before you're
eating it and they think that was good I
do want to go to Denny's again they have
a dessert that looks so yummy
something's like apple crumble something
like that it looks so good I want to eat
everything
okay well so we didn't watch the second
movie but
in in the future maybe someday
no I mean you can go watch it alone
because I'm going home
or or you wait until it's like somewhere
available as a streaming service and
then we can watch it then like together
it's a watch alive
right the track's gonna spoil it
but I didn't like the first one I did
like it it's pretty good yeah it was
good I was like you were you were even
watching sometimes you're just petting
my cats well no I was watching Always
you were even looking at it
no no I was
I was just looking at my cats sometimes
because they were doing funny things
like licking your feet
eating your feet
I'm so sweaty
what what's with the motion what nothing
well you were sweaty is that what you're
saying a little bit I know yeah I guess
maybe they like the the saltiness
something is sweat
[Music]
all right all right what do we have as
options hopefully the next one doesn't
cut off somewhere
um how about
the last one
[Laughter]
one this time this is the audio version
of me singing in energy
welcome to the gym
you can imagine that part but yeah this
is a collaboration with an entity
was that doubling no it shouldn't it was
just two voices singing it okay
and Kiana uh late night circulation
Danced by me only here we go here we go
come on and down and welcome to the Sun
or the other way around
[Laughter]
and I'm done
[Music]
[Laughter]
here
[Music]
[Applause]
I know
[Music]
[Laughter]
good afternoon
foreign
[Music]
oh my full body
Arena
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah thank you then it's you somewhere
out there
in Japan for singing that with me life
totally 100 live
yeah
did you watch that anime
[Music]
is so good
and this song Everybody Knows yeah
yeah I see the animation it looks really
nice it's so good yeah it's like very
focused on uh like a dialogue they talk
so much so I really have to focus when
you watch this anime app it's so high
quality I've been waiting for a million
years for a new season to come out new
season yeah I'm still hoping it's been
so many years though even for that
moving it's there's even movies that
were in the cinema at least in Japanese
Cinema
yes
it was good should I give up hoping guys
what do you think am I am I coping no no
they
don't think they said the plan is to
animate every like novel that they have
and they're not done yet if you think
about it that way
yeah there could still be more yeah so
I'm not giving up it's a promise they
made maybe maybe they'll put out a new
season in 10 years I'll be around I'll
still be here
uh yeah did I misunderstand that I don't
know
shaft angle shaft
shaft angle this is the famous shaft
angle
[Music]
yeah it's hard to tell
when you're in that form maybe you
should go back to a wooden puppet
from yesterday
you feel more
less less stiff right now don't you
you're ready
can you put your arms on my arms
I want to hold
um I want you to be in my arms
turns out there's another arm
I will I will get
um I miss arms amputated I'm reputation
replace These Arms get new arms
better arms upgrade
upgraded I'm oh
maybe you can cut my arms I'll just
stand still here
okay let's do a wave uh
[Laughter]
I'll hide I'll hide let's go like this
hi everybody how are you guys it's so
nice to see you
so I have fake news today's announcement
there's an announcement announcement is
done I cut off on his arms and they're
mine now
doesn't it looks so much better now
wow new arms and they come with a muppet
oh my gosh
okay can you wave it the can I wait for
them
they're a bit uh proportionally too big
for me but uh
I'm strong
but maybe I should get rid of this
did that Muppet just kissed me
so cute
[Laughter]
oh nice
oh
brutal it sounded like a kiss to me yeah
maybe I'll miss her well okay
my arms are back I think oh are they
is there does this look normal I think
it's normal
yeah
it's clasping them behind me okay
let's do another song
what should we do
let me look on my list
when when Amma has her Muppet iron
figure it out again
it's good
okay
yeah
okay are you ready to cheer ameth yeah
and what should we do how about
ah shining power this is from my
favorite Idol group uh some of you guys
maybe know it from an anime old old
anime old song okay here we go
[Music]
I
mean
[Music]
thank you
together
[Music]
Daddy
look forward
[Music]
foreign
see me
[Music]
good evening
I feel like
[Music]
[Applause]
it's a song about Bento
that's what all of this is about make me
hungry and me too this is the shape of
the ventil they're singing about
the pencil that you made for me was two
two levels high and it's so yummy kind
of like that
my Bento is the best I know it's so
I think I will win with this bear until
I don't know it's from like they made
the song for the ending or the opening
of an anime
called Inazuma 11.
you know that one
right yeah no I think it's oh can I
still hear
him
[Music]
does Callie not I wonder does she know
you have to sucker anymore yeah yeah and
probably in the anime the moms because
it's like kids playing soccer and things
the mom's probably oh yeah the student
who loved that I write that really fast
to the point of the obsession oh
yeah I only know because my favorite
ever Idol group
saying this
couple
song I don't learn how to make Phantom
[Applause]
Arigato
what does Kelly say every English
project
that there was was about that show
what your English projects were about to
show and if she means like students or
something ah like if they have to ride
something
less homework or so
or presentation
[Music]
yeah I think it's uh what do you call it
you call it the Shonen anime
yeah
oh my God
[Music]
America
United States of Amelia OH
is it is it like noon now I think 12 41
noon yeah yeah
um
I actually swim at American Prime Time
yeah
in a million years no actually never
okay let me dance something cool for you
stay everybody stay I want to dance
it's a uh also an idol song and it has a
even though they release it when they
were like 11 and 12 years old the choreo
is like super cool and intricate
so please enjoy
lunchtime or lunch break good time
I mean you ready
oh [\h__\h] I'm gonna mess it up let's go
[Music]
now
[Laughter]
I'm ready
[Music]
foreign
come on
[Music]
foreign
it's only
now
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I Will Survive
oh
[Applause]
who's Dancing Queen
thank you I am the bouncing Queen
[Music]
if I run out of water I'm just gonna
drink my own sweat
that's okay
it will still be cold was it tasty did
you try I want more of it I only takes
up two sips
and the ice tastes so good guys
oh I was speaking of brown lemon
you know the most American thing
happened to me today
and I see a single girl with a little
table
selling lemonade
one and I was like
I mean look I'm gonna look she's selling
lemonade
and so what did we do I said I mean
let's go let's go we want some lemonade
so I went down to the little girl she
was like this small this small this one
her parents also are also there
yeah and I was like oh what are you
saving up for because I'm I was guessing
you'd do that when you're like saving up
for something from [\h__\h] money that's
what I thought too yeah but she said she
was like smiling like I don't know
she was happy though because we like we
were like gonna just walk by with your
American yay we're gonna walk by first
but I really wanted to have this
American Experience
so she had nothing particular to save up
for but ah I gave her a dollar
and she gave me a cup of the yummiest
lemonade
I have ever tasted in America
yeah Emma didn't have a sip though what
is poison
well
yeah maybe she spiked the drink is that
what you're saying
you're fine right
I'm fine it was good yeah had had
lemonade from little girl on the
roadside
hmm have you guys ever seen that like
somewhere in the IRL before because I
only saw it in like TV before hmm
cute story right yeah it was cute when I
was younger the only thing I did to like
um make a little bit extra pocket money
you used to be
haha I can imagine
I can imagine that
right yeah
what I would have done or what I did is
like
um at the closest supermarket I would
like put a blanket in front of it
um and then sell like my old toys and
stuff and like witch magazines Barbie
magazines all that kind of stuff or like
uh the uh what is it called the duck the
duck books you know what I mean
yeah really yeah because I loved reading
the little books yeah and I had so many
yeah the DuckTales stuff like that and
now it's salad there in front of the
supermarket and normally they wouldn't
get mad at me actually I think in
several times and it was never a problem
because we were just kids yeah yeah I
made a little bit of money I was
actually thinking back now I was only
selling like
useless stuff it's actually surprising
that people would even buy anything at
all
How would how would little Amy make
money back in the day huh
how would I make money
I don't know yeah maybe candy at school
sell candy at school
maybe I didn't have any ways of making
money the other way what is that on the
way did you mow Lawns ever no friendship
what's
the 400 poisons
you can't oh but I know what you mean
um um oh my God they're yeah back in my
days there were several ways of making
cute bracelets Ebert is normal Fred or
my favorite thing I wonder if you notice
I'm a you know the Scooby-Doo
um Fred's they're like out of plastic
and they come in all kinds of colors and
then you make like little bracelets and
keychains with that you know them
Scooby-Doo yeah friend
yeah Scooby-Doo like
it's plastic but yeah it's like
I've never heard of that in Austrian
they called it Scooby-Doo but ah they
may have a different name here
but there are the plastic did you never
see something like that plastic bags
maybe
yeah there's like all kinds of like
different patterns so like I would go to
school and my friends would be making
some cool pattern and I
see you in girls talk ma'am but like
yeah yeah lanyards and everything you
can make with that and there's different
patterns and then and then my friend
would make like a a really cool pen and
I'm like how do you do that teach me
teach me because it can go like even it
would be just like a like a like a
square a long square or you can make it
round or you can make it like like a
dragon like twisted and stuff it's so
cool
it's so cool I love the feeling that
yeah
Emma do you want to come to girls talk
sometime
you have a lot more fun listening and
yeah
mommy said the same thing but she is
contributing
you once did my makeup I would say that
is very girly of you to do my makeup
[Music]
I think I even wore your clothes
oh yeah yeah why did we do that so that
I could look more normal guys because we
went to the arcade yeah to look to look
different because I guess all my clothes
were kind of like flashy maybe yeah
yeah I felt very edgy on that day
that was cute yeah I haven't had someone
do my makeup in a long time I was very
special to me you did a good job right I
think so yeah now remember smudge again
yeah
normally I don't smudge but I like eye
stuff but you were smudging it makes it
look extra edgy
[Music]
Mrs Muppets and I'm out of water okay
thank you
oh guys I think I still have like a
couple songs left so
hope you're gonna enjoy the rest too I I
always say like a little bit of a break
in between otherwise I'm going to face
wow
I keep on like feeling you know there's
a lot of Velcro on me oh I'm like
dancing really aggressively that things
are sticking
to Parts where they shouldn't be
sticking to
gets me worried I'll rip something off
geez she's doing something ah
that was like I think one hour in
but I'm gonna apologize a lot
I'm listening go off huh yeah sorry no
problem no problem
wow let's do another song is Coco
let's do
oh
let's do Viva happy
I don't think I can I don't remember
this one so well guys so don't judge me
okay
be my happy here we go
[Music]
Michael okay
nothing more
[Music]
no no no no
no
no no
hey hey hey hey
[Music]
comedy
movies
[Music]
happy birthday
foreign
[Music]
yes
laughs
why is there so much bouncing and
jumping yeah
[Music]
something that was singing along you
know that song huh baby me
banger
happy
I am also Viva Villa happy
me it's supposed to be dance with two
people
yeah
I guess you were yay
thank you thank you
yeah listen book a lot
we shall go back to
my beloved hell project
uh
all we have one
two
more songs well thank God
fake [\h__\h] God
oh you know this was like
I'm here and I'm a studio just because I
need to record motion capture for MV but
I thought you know I have this chance
often
so I might as well you know do some
dancing so I just got all those old
dances out of my repertoire hmm
oh only Tom I'm sorry
but I can't dance forever I'm so tired
and my muscles are so sore chickens
massage me
I'm in Muppets and massage me okay
thank you massage me
oh
[Music]
yeah
you're massaging my feet can you do my
shoulders
they're not non-existent body
oh yeah yeah yeah
my hips yeah thank God I don't really
have hip problems yet thank you oh thank
you
well I'm getting all the service I could
possibly get here well luxury
[Music]
now includes a day spa service massage
service okay yeah I'm totally certified
and
thank you more later more massage
the first a shower
very necessary yeah okay
guys we're doing
um
all Japanese people know the song ah so
feel free to dance along
Revolution
21. hey yo there's some cool rap from me
in there I was just uh mimicking the
producer tsunkusan who you know he often
puts like some
you know weird voices into the Idol
songs you maybe remember my sound cover
with Kubo and vatamel where there was
similar stuff in there too and yeah I
had to mimic that because it kind of
belongs into the salt so don't laugh
though don't laugh yeah from the
Christmas song yeah I'm laughing already
can't do anything but laugh with that
face
is there ever a sad Muppet
no Ryan always happy
okay but you're laughing with me not
against me
yeah yeah yeah okay okay here you go
we're in a revolution need to reach
[Music]
oh yes
tell me
baby baby
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
you know
baby
[Music]
thank you
tell me
right
[Music]
baby
drop it
[Music]
all together
foreign
[Music]
hello
bye
I'm gonna tell them the story what what
story and your story uh oh hey guys uh
did you guys know that uh Bigfoot is
real and uh you better watch out because
if you live near the woods he might come
and find you who's real Bigfoot ah
you know big [\h__\h] yeah Sasquatch
Sasquatch yeah oh did you make a
different kind of story I'm not anything
[Music]
because I ate them when they're so hot
yeah I air fried them actually it did
not bake the cookies
you clearly do own an air fryer yeah
that's good can you make more I gotta
make a new batch dough but I could yeah
we have time I'm so good yeah oh what's
your favorite kind of cookie
I like chocolate chip cookie but I also
really like uh I like the white
macadamia nut oh
why am I good I never had that cookie
before damn it Subways oh
yeah
it's tasty but there was one time I went
to Subway so there are ants all over the
cookies but they're so tasty
I mean that's why the answer did right
because they're so tasty they're so good
oh what's your go-to drink at Starbucks
a Starbucks
I never had Starbucks well I had it once
yeah it had a Starbucks donut in Japan
it was really tasty what I don't like
coffee
we never but I always drink Frappuccinos
there's no coffee in the Frappuccinos
usually really yeah oh I saw that they
have like a melon one in Japan I want to
try that so bad oh yeah that's probably
seasonal so cute
but my go-to is usually like either a
vanilla Frappuccino because they always
have that on the menu
and then I put like
some cinnamon powder but I noticed
recently when I went to Starbucks
I didn't have the cinnamon powder
anymore no yeah what the [\h__\h] man
and then and then and then sometimes
there's other good ones new ones
seasonal ones
um bring cinnamon back because normally
you know they have cocoa
and and another powder that you can just
add onto your drinks
[\h__\h] out I'm having like a heat
stroke
uh-huh
[Music]
well the last one is kind of like in my
blood
it comes natural to me the last song I
heard you singing and it was it's gotten
stuck in my head since you recorded or
were you you were singing
but you know do you know it yeah I think
so it's a classic yeah yeah many
Classics today I'm not for blood
if you want to see four Bloods just
re-watch my my birthday concert from
last year yeah literally recorded here
yeah it was like I don't know I don't
want to lie about that no I listen live
no of course not yeah but there have
been made many upgrades since then yeah
it's easier to uh dance now here
yeah thankfully yeah thankfully last
year she was dancing on a piece of
cardboard literally yeah
I try it because like otherwise it would
have been like carpet and that was
really fluffy and then the cardboard was
like moving around when I was dancing on
it
so both both was difficult
well now staple ground
hooray
professional studio I mean totally just
just Place some new flooring just for me
right
I'm great hmm yeah no it's really it
looks so professional it's like really
freaking amazing like I'ma puts together
I don't know how you do it girl look at
all the duct tape out there you see it
where
everywhere
in that thing why not chicken tape
[Music]
chicken tip is even better quality than
duct tape
ha ha
asean belly laughing
like sideways yeah turn sideways
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh you know like okay here's here's the
Idol idol game animation okay
oh like Idol that's not even like oh
this is how I would do it um
really heavy breathing
does this look Idle No and it looks like
you're doing it jellyfish the jellyfish
is like we're like
I don't know
what what kind of idol animation
do you like that like fighting game Idol
animation
but I have no weapon right now but you
like use your fist
okay fish right I forgot about this
stuff okay
oh
you don't have this some I don't have
fingers
they're just attached with hot glue
probably
well those those are at least I mean you
could say those are lightsabers these
are um
oh Emma you gotta set up like a
lightsaber fight here
yeah we can do that one day
next year yeah
okay guys
are you ready for the last song
and then I will retire forever from
dancing
[\h__\h] that thing man [\h__\h] it
foreign
I'm so dead it's already been one and a
half hours anyway what the hell
okay
that would yeah how does it start with
this I think so yeah all right here we
go
[Music]
foreign
trying to be back
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
I guess I can just revive I think my
body is officially broken too just
because I'm rolling around on the floor
ah
thank you guys to Phoenix town I'm dead
yep yep but you're in Phoenix so you'll
come back right uh
yeah tomorrow on Anna's Channel yeah
around noon time okay yeah we're gonna
do what kind of stream I'm in
shooting star
yes not pretty we're doing handcam kind
of
tomorrow tomorrow I'm wasting no time
guys
no time shooting stream and they will
teach me because I watched that that
wasn't that your birthday streamers of
Christmas a Christmas yeah you were
shooting I was like
damn she's so American
my God yeah I guess airsoft airsoft I
already tried out yesterday right and
actually I hit the goals yeah she hit
the target whoa it's not so difficult so
be careful guys I'm better at FPS in
real life than in games so don't cross
me yeah
yeah will I yes oh do I have to yes is
that like something you have to do if
you're streaming on something like that
yeah
[Music]
proper safety okay
otherwise do we lose the the airsoft
perms we don't have any Airsoft
nobody knows what it is
oh yeah oh yeah I'll be sniping some
some goals and stuff yeah on this
channel tomorrow earlier tomorrow
so yeah guys hope you enjoyed me
um dancing again dancing myself until my
absolute [\h__\h] limit
never again
thank you so much for providing the
studio and for setting me up thank you
so much
refreshing energy filled dinner and
Einstein
thank you by the way Kyle carrot for
well including helping me out with the
preparation yeah good chicken and and
thank you for ask for fixing my skin
yeah thanks everybody
subscribe like leave a comment
[Music]
thank you for watching thank you today
yesterday to the outfit doesn't I feel
like I forgot yeah I did I remember
because I said right after two oh okay
well we'll do it again
um
I should think of like a choreography
for uh that first yeah yeah do it do it
how about
[Music]
um
and in German we say
oh
my God I'll forget that Shirley and then
say I was being a Zen remember yesterday
I was saying like a chihuahua sleep well
and what was that oh
I want to sleep
guys so much
what's going on
tomorrow I'm a channel oh
more and more
[Music]
I can't just need to do that okay
yeah yeah
chicken dance really quick okay how did
the chicken dance on the
um
yeah does that and then you do like
different directions
and then
I don't know that's the only part I know
really okay
[Applause]
oh my God
[Music]
foreign