[Music]
so
oh
[Music]
do you feel the music baby
[Applause]
keep playing
[Music]
but when i see you
soon
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
so
okay
[Music]
i don't
of you
[Music]
huh
ah
[Music]
hello
it's been
84 years
hello
did you miss me
i missed you guys
it was um
weird too ah green line
eh
it was weird to not stream
for so for so long i'm saying but
in reality
it's only been like
three days or so
but then like in total
i haven't i just i forgot to tweet i
just haven't been streaming
much
uh overall right so yeah i need to let
people know let the people know
let it be known
uh
it has begun
coming
um
thank you
you're not looking bad either
um
sorry um
so
update on my health
i'm like like
mentally and all that i'm doing great uh
i don't really feel
sick um like last time
uh after the last stream i got a fever
and had a literal fever night let's go
string streaming fever night so strong
that you get a [\h__\h] favor
um
uh
yeah and um
and then i don't know the following day
uh
fiona was already gone yeah um and i've
just been like low-key sick
but i realized i need to
wait until it's
completely healed and
i mean
it's maybe not completely healed
uh
i still like cough a little bit and i
have a little bit of a
stuffy nose which is why i might have to
blow my nose sometimes but
i think i got my nose in a state right
now where it's not running so i hope oh
the moment they say that i felt
something running
um
but no i i definitely feel like i can
stream so i have the energy
i feel like my body has the energy so
i think we can do it and i want to i
want to
explain the nasal ah my voice doesn't
sound nasal
today more than any other day
does it
you can hear the stuff he knows no
it's not so bad right hey really
yay nasal kiwawa
a little bit really
oh
hey
a little nasally really
i don't really feel like it's so
different um myself but if you guys say
that no no no i just opened the game and
it's asking me to answer time
does it mean it got rid of my progress
because it does say in steam that i have
four out of 11
achievements and 2.9 play hours
does it always do that
put eight is that an achievement to put
eight a.m
it asks every time ah okay okay okay
okay okay
yes we're gonna continue
stanley parable and sorry guys that the
schedule for this week is pretty much
[\h__\h] all over
um
[Music]
i
will probably uh no probably i should i
will i will take tomorrow off again
because um i want to give myself you
know some more time to recover and learn
dances i've been doing pretty
pretty good at learning the dances
and
then on saturday i'll stream wind waker
that's my current plan
uh and then on sunday i think i
will
have to take another day off maybe or do
a short stream because even if i wanted
to do wind waker
i really sound nasally on k r that's
funny though
isn't that nice to have a have a
different kiwa for once
uh
[Music]
yeah uh so
because even if i did windbreaker
normally on sunday i think i would be
maybe overlapping with foreign's
birthday maybe maybe not i'm not sure
so we don't want that uh
we might do a short stream
and oh yeah sunday uh like it's
confusing to me for me
gooda's
birthday stream is on monday in the
night time i think
but i will be calling into that
so
yes i'll stay awake for that yeah yeah
so many birthdays oh my god what about
super chat yeah oh oh i turned them off
oh
i don't know i did a super chat reading
on monday i don't know if we're
so
so caught up that i can afford turning
them on again
what do you guys think the people who
follow my super chat progress
i will read them i really read some more
uh
no you dare i right there
um i'm not there now whatever
yeah well i'm on hey
well turn them on
how else am i gonna feed my cats guys
and pay for my medicine
uh super chat super stickers there we go
i dared i did you dared me so i did it
yes i saw i won uh maybe that's because
kfp is always winning are you guys
really surprised that we won the wwe
thingy that good idea are you surprised
beginners amateurs
you're new here
are you new here
of course we win we always win
and i mean
kick
okay here we go nose is running
maybe i should mute myself when i do
that
and some i know in some countries in
some cultures it's very rude to blow you
know
[\h__\h] you know what i really hate
i i really this is the first time i'm
like properly sick in many many years i
never get sick i get sick once in three
or four maybe even five years
and i hate it when you have a stuffy
runny nose and
you know that you can't breathe through
your nose
but you know that your your body will
once you're asleep
snort it all up and then breathe through
the nose forcefully
and then completely [\h__\h] up your throat
because all that snorted uh
blah will go into your
b i don't know somewhere in your skull
fill it up and then
it's disgusting i hate the thought
i hate the fun and then then you wake up
and i'm like okay
my nose is like relatively open and i
can breathe with my nose oh i know
exactly what happened i must have i must
have snored so strong during the night
ew i normally never snore
i really never snore like arena
and cali and so on they all told me i
don't snore
thank you skye
thank you
thank you brief with the map well i
tried to but i think my my body once i'm
asleep i can't control it so it will
just
you know
yeah
yeah a snoring woman is a hardship
do you snore at all no i don't as i said
i don't okay
i forgot to say
kick it again
[Applause]
what do you mean i said it
now i said it
okay
i shall
yeah don't mind my cops i'm fine this is
just a
little little
bit
it's more when i talk but don't worry
i'm fine i know how to you know
um
i i know how to
einstein myself
my throat doesn't hurt that's the thing
so very good do i need to enter the real
time
someone said 8 a.m so let's do it that's
8 p.m
okay so 8 a.m whatever that does
evaluate yeah i know to evaluate and uh
as i said i'm taking tomorrow off so
we're good
powerball
hang on hang on uh
yeah
was this like this before
before i get started can i just say
something
i don't remember this
thank you
thank you for actually setting the clock
both times you've put it up the game
you're welcome i mean i didn't set it
correctly now but i said it currently
last time
it's not muted it's just uh there's no
sound
a lot of people don't take that stuff
seriously they just leave the clock set
at 12 and call it a day
[Laughter]
yes but you're talking to kiwawa here
you're actually taking the time to set
the clock and i appreciate that
oh see i couldn't have gotten that if i
cleared the game in one one go
because it needs me to set the time two
times
ah
that's how i know that you care about
this experience you're paying attention
yes
i don't even have any way of knowing if
the times you're setting are correct
i feel i wonder does does a game
have access to my real computer time
does it
is it like does it have hacker skills it
does it can
then i
uh i'm scared
tell you what i'll make your deal
since you've been so cooperative next
time you put up the game and see the
screen just set the clock to your
favorite time oh
i don't have a favorite time though
[Music]
go ahead pick whichever time you want
even if it's not the correct time you've
earned it
all right i'll let you get back to the
video game now thank you
oh how nice what a nice surprise
to begin the game i want to continue the
game
okay
the end is never the end it's never the
end
this is also not the end you have a man
named stanley
do i get an achievement for listening
again stanley worked for a company
where he was really starting from here
i wanna start off where it was last time
he sat at his desk in room 427 and he
pushed buttons on skipping is fine
orders came to him through a monitor on
my desk it always okay okay
where will i be hey but i'm here
i got an achievement for coming back yay
hey
i want to go into the big room again how
do i know how to get there
you guys said it saves my gamble
just how do i
i don't remember him his co-workers were
gone what could it mean it doesn't
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room it doesn't remember that i was here
before
it saves endings your reach
i think
oh
but he's talking to me as if it's new
that i'm new
is the new content room there
it's there okay oh good you noticed my
sign yes why is my mouse very exciting
go so far outside of the
outside of the game oh wait huh
i don't remember do you know the way
guys your content
ah
let's go
love your new look yeah thank you
is the is the sound fine now
uh
yeah uh-huh elevator elevator you see
stanley i've been reflecting
understanding
and about how roundly disappointing this
ultra deluxe version has turned out to
be
you're having an insane existential
crisis again i feel so sorry for him
he's like
looking so forget this ultra deluxe
nonsense
one step even looping the pressure which
is why i'm very proud to announce for
the first time ever
the stanley parable
and that's not a surprise to me though
but okay i think this is where i wanted
to go yes you see isn't this far
superior to a measly re-release with a
few minor additions of all the new
territory we'll cover with a fully
fledged sequel an entirely new my mouse
didn't do this last time it's just
normal that my mouse just like decides
to go to my other screen
when i'm in i'm i'm in the game
i mean i have it windowed but still
maybe i need to maximize it
it just goes somewhere else man
change the sensitivity
oh
like lower
maybe one
second
experience built from the ground
because like every time i want to click
something
i don't know where my mouse is so i have
to like
press the windows button i think i have
to
out tab out and in
might need yeah i guess i'll make it
full screen
[Music]
i need to see something
apply
big
oh [\h__\h]
oh
it's making me lag a little bit don't
know maybe
maybe it will fix itself [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
i tapped out because i need to find the
chat
okay here we go
oh my god okay
let's see ah we should be fine all right
hey my mouse still goes outside
my mouth still goes outside is that
normal
i've never had this issue before
what
gently tell the cursor to behave i guess
i'll restart the game
this is weird man i can set my favorite
time
i guess
all right
[\h__\h]
kusa
have you fed the mouse
all right let's get my favorite time
what's your favorite time
[Music]
you're not funny
oh sure
okay now it starts with being windowed
interestingly
okay
the mouse still goes out
[\h__\h] annoying mate
you know what
i'll try to deal with it
[Laughter]
it's kind of annoying but okay at least
it's not like a shooter game or
something
um
favorite time
is like
i would say
my favorite time maybe it's like
2 p.m
because then i'm like oh
i still have
a lot of hours left in the day
that's nice like later in the day it
will stress me out because yeah i'll see
that i don't have much time left
2pm is a pretty good time no i don't
wake up at 2pm anymore then these are
old days of kiwawa this is a new day
new age of kiwawa
okay
we'll deal with it
i might just have to you might not
notice it but i might just have to
several times
um
push
the windows button and try to find my
mouse
hi 2pm your favorite time of the day i
guess it is
or could you simply not resist giving me
the correct time again no no no no
no no no that was really actually a fake
time after all i know how much you
enjoyed sending the time correctly
wait that scares me does he know does he
know that i didn't said it correctly
last time
i feel threatened
and cornered and pressured and
blackmailed
okay now i'm curious how accurate 2pm is
let's use another slider to find out
how accurate
uh
if this is 24 hours
and now it's actually
7 p.m here
how
how where is 2pm on here if this is 24
hours then maybe 7pm is around here
and then 2pm is like
here
eighty percent
i you're you're calculating it
differently then
it
twenty percent wrong
no
it's 2pm in brazil okay
uh
and i can what what
well i say
well if this is 24
hours and then the middle is 12
p.m
so
2 p.m would be around here
i think
let's go
you know can i just say regardless of
the accuracy of the clock i'm having a
great time adjusting these settings
thank you me too me too actually
i feel like i'm learning more about you
and how you like things to be said
i like you is this is this the dude
talking to me though because he doesn't
have a voice now he's only
writing to me is this a different person
is this not the narrator
it's good to collect data
oh [\h__\h] they're collecting my data oh
that's not a good thing
i wish we had more sliders but we've
gone for all the sliders i have
see if we wouldn't notice if i didn't
restart the game again this is amazing
all according to keikaku
yeah perhaps i can invent some
newsletters to grab a new date on you
shouldn't be too hard yeah let me whip a
couple new ones up oh dear oh dear
next time
now i want to put up the game again
oh
now i'm going to put it up again
i want to see the sliders
let's see the sliders
show me
what do you got for me when you got
prepared for me now i'm like reopening
it on purpose
please adjust the slider until the
computer is barely visible i thought
that's a boring slider i don't like the
slider until the computer what if i what
if i make it like this though
now but i'll be honest i'll be honest i
like this exercise
maybe around here
he wouldn't know though he wouldn't know
how my how my screen settings are to
myself
okay
this is more
uh accurate yeah we want to be accurate
please adjust the slide until the dog
and the cat
[Music]
i have the right thing for that
until number five becomes number nine
oh i gotcha
ah there it is what are the others
what if i do that and i'm really funny
[Music]
well
well look into the whole of the nine
guys i still got you
i got you
there it is
i'm a good girl please just decide until
you stop it just again
[Music]
what song is that anyway i can't stop
we'll be here forever i just like the
slider very much
it's pretty nice nice slider wow
i like that
sound that it makes so you guys probably
don't even really hear
this is this is high quality gaming
important data is important
slides in your dms oh
zeus
like this nah only in your dreams
you hear it
[Music]
ah the smurf song
holy [\h__\h] what
the more singles the more blue i turn
[Music]
so you guys have the same smurf song
because someone said it's by some german
guy
oh is it the same
sensational i know
wow
okay
what do you say about that which is the
two made-up worlds below is most
appealing to you
hell yeah
please don't adjust the slider okay okay
okay
do you know what time it is right now
on gaming time
is is the time that is it is right now
the correct time
you mean the time on my pc yes
i mean but it depends
wherever you are it might not be the
correct time because time difference
but for me it's the correct time
[Music]
what is the time menu
i'm a bit scared
he scares me now
well what is time but
yes no
yes
is there anything about yourself that
you haven't told me oh yes so much
keep on asking
i'll talk with you i will help
is he okay
yes
[Music]
will you come back to visit me
oh
wait i i
i'm scared
is this like um what's that uh yeah ddlc
yeah
yeah kawhi
yes i don't know if i finish the game or
no yeah no
i might not today might be the last time
i play this game but don't tell him
oh
what if i said no
if i said though what if i come back
again
i'll come back
i'll come back i promised him
i promise he scares me but i promised
him
so
hello
i'm back
oh this is so fast what time is it
there's no
does anyone really truly know oh man
you're
the depressed
game code aren't you
oh no
of course they don't nobody knows
anything
no no we know because of you know the
sun
and ancient
rome i guess
they decided
because of the sun
but in theory time it's just a concept
i guess
so
um
i guess we could go without time yes
somehow it it's a human construct not
exactly because i mean the sun you know
there's a whole system there when it
goes up when it goes down as we can see
but but we decided for it to be a thing
we could have just ignored time and went
on with our lives without thinking about
time
wow
philosophical phoenix
why are you so depressed bro you and i
don't even know each other we're like
strangers
yeah but that's true yes that's true we
can get to know each other you and me
so i've adjusted all the game settings
to your exact specifications but who
hasn't
oh
well you've been a little bit more
specific with me than others
i'll give you that
it's just what i do like a day job
and now the job is over
not if we not if we change some settings
you know like my mouse still needs some
fixing
maybe you can help me with that
my mouse keeps on leaving the screen
yeah
there is no more information for me
together i've collected all the data on
you that i can
oh trust me there's more but there wait
there's more and you don't even know the
real time of my pc yet
that's better
and i still don't really know you and
you don't know me
yeah
[Music]
it's okay bro i can tell you some things
about me you tell me first who the [\h__\h]
are you
neither of us know what time it is
[Music]
i guess some settings are just unsettled
is that a real word
yeah but if i'm being totally honest the
clock doesn't do anything in the game
anyway
that's good to know i was
i was wondering about that you won't
have me here when the game starts next
time but that's okay really
no i was just about to go back to my
happy face now you say something like
that
how disappointing
video games are meant to be played alone
no
what about mmorpgs i love mmorpgs
[Music]
you like being alone don't you
oh
oh well i mean
i don't know if you consider it being
alone when i have two cats with me all
the time in general i like being alone
even when i'm with people i prefer to
have my own hotel room for example
or
my own bed
um
an airbnb
and
i like going shopping alone because i
don't want to waste too much of your
time
unless you really want to be there and
you can carry my bags
but i feel
better alone because then i don't feel
judged by
the clothes that i
am considering
by your eyes
but
i like being alone yes
that's maybe the only information i
really learned about you oh
yeah
it's time for me to leave no don't
are you leaving because i said i want to
be alone
but no i never said that to you directly
don't leave you don't know if i want to
be alone unless you're listening to what
i'm saying right now
there's still one more setting that we
need to adjust but it may take a little
time before breaking
oh my god
it's not really in my job description
but that's okay
perhaps you'll see me again if you can
find me
are you in the game
talk soon you're missing two words
talk to you soon
talk soon yes
monica
can i
can i talk more with you
last time okay
i mean it sounds like he won't be here
this time
but
oh he just means the system settings no
restarting simulator
okay
he's not here
my friend
friend
where are you
it's not you
[Music]
okay
i guess it's time to begin the real game
[Music]
this is the story of the game okay
my [\h__\h] mouse oh my god i guess i
could get used to this
okay
because
his co-workers were gone new contact
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room stanley is
[Music]
you got sick because you didn't wear the
mask
oh no
see i really wonder
i've been really wondering but in the
end it doesn't matter but i've been
really wondering like where i got sick
was it dokomi or cali
um
but
never mind it doesn't matter you see
stanley i've been reflecting but if it
was dopamine then i wonder if you guys
got sick too who were you
deluxe version has turned out to be the
original stanley parable was a landmark
and any new context
but she recovered way faster than me i'm
jealous nonsense i say we take it once i
think recently my immune immunity which
is why i'm very has been pretty much
ever like in the stanley parable
it's been better
i definitely had i used to have a
stronger immunity system yes you see
isn't this far superior to a measly
re-release with a few minor additions
into the sky
will cover with a fully fledged sequel
entirely
this is what fans have truly been asking
for
um
you're just getting old hey
[Music]
it goes out so far it's just so much
catchier than ultra deluxe don't you
think oh
ducks what does it even mean yeah but i
need to use the mouse to move though
now
it's an artistic statement
right there it's future oriented it
screams progress and innovation and
maybe term franchising potential can i
make it faster instead
maybe i don't know
uh this is
better i think i think it will go less
out of my screen now to be clear i
haven't quite nailed down what exactly
the stanley parable 2 is going to be but
let's take a look at some of the does it
show me yeah and i can interact with
something i forgot
that if i can loosely organize a handful
of interesting concepts that surely the
game will sort of naturally spring up
around them it'll all work itself out
what is this about it is much more of a
fuzzy magic than anything scientific or
logical really let's just show you
huh what did i ask
okay okay
sequels are good oh yeah we saw this
before we've been in this room before
that's why i'm kind of
uh running through it
new content oh new content buzz let's go
let me in
huh
i'm not supposed to go for the new
content bus
i guess i was here before but i don't
remember this looks like netflix
i think i said this last time too
wow we're back here
here we are go on try out some of the
new features okay
okay okay okay so last time we went to a
hole we went to the bucket i don't have
my bucket anymore it's kind of sad
let's see no screenshots
in
office no that's where we were already i
guess
got the bucket again
okay go get the bucket do i need the
bucket
do i need the bucket
[Music]
was that it was confusing and
paradoxical that it engendered a chaotic
sense of reckless despair in those who
played it well
i'm happy to say that after much
consideration i've engineered a clever
solution to this fundamental problem
with the game
it's the stanley parable reassurance
bucket you see stanley i see nothing
holding the bucket a sense of calm and
ease
[Music]
disorienting contradictions of the
stanley parable feel perfectly normal
and perhaps even comforting can i take
it you may even come to long for the
gentle embrace of jarring cognitive
dissonance while the bucket is in your
arms i want to hold it gently it's a
much more convenient solution for me
can i put it on my head to be less
uncomfortable can you imagine what a
pain in the ass give it to me yes the
bucket is the perfect solution come on
give it a try
in the face of crushing despair must
already be sweeping through your body
just pick it up come on
i do believe the bucket lends you an air
of charisma as well no i'm fine with the
validity
has made you the slightest bit more keep
on clicking outside of the screen
the benefits of the bucket seem to go on
and on
all this and the bucket have some places
to go in the stanley parable too which
will never come probably
the button that says the name of the
plane is the most enjoyable bucket in a
video game
that really should be an award if it
isn't already i want to press the button
but i'm worried like does it like say
the name of the system of my computer or
so
what name does or the steam name
for the stanley parable 2 i asked myself
what do players really do save okay and
of course first and most obvious answer
is that they want to be individually
recognized and validated as people
so with that in mind my first addition
to the game is this button which speaks
the name of the person playing the game
isn't that wonderful
i mean the one in the middle really just
looks like someone's freezing
i would say the big button is nice too
but you're right the just right button
is really just right
oh
okay wait what was something here now
okay
wait there's a door there's so many
doors everywhere it doesn't open okay
no
what is this
name here yours oh what's my name say my
name say my name
sorry
[Music]
here we go let's take a deep breath
clear your mind forget whoever you are
and simply become a person named jim
i want you to imagine yourself living as
jim jim whoa whoa whoa
i wasn't finished that was by accident
if you don't properly roll players jim
then you'll never understand the impact
of this button otherwise it's just a
stupid button that says somebody else's
name exactly
that's what it is we're doing it again
and this time you know what we're doing
here we keep on pushing buttons and we
keep on listening to this dialogue
like last time jim
imagine yourself driving to work as jim
playing frisbee
developing a crippling substance
addictions oh no that's not me i'm
straightened discovering yourself
through fringe religious groups
could as jim
dying a slow death at an old age
surrounded by members of your cult as
yeah kfp cafe would surround me your
soul are you really pray at me jim right
now
if so then
step forward and press the button it's
more like a me but you gave me a
different name that's all it really is
[Laughter]
yes you'll see what a thrill what a rush
that was you the button described you do
it again do it again
[Music]
teddy it's even harder the second time
if this were the thing your name
narrative
by any chance still be worth the money
because you got really excited about it
i'm too emotionally drained from all of
this personal validation
what if what if i press anything oh
there cowboy sometimes a person can be
too much jim i'm putting the gym button
away otherwise soon you'll start to lose
all sense of who you actually are jim
jim hey
hey
how dare you wow they just this is why
we can't have nice things
man
[\h__\h] this room
[\h__\h] it
that's not a button if i can't press it
it's not the right button
i can't press them
i jimmed it too much not
that would actually save me the work of
finishing this feature
a whole new office looks pretty much the
same though
what
what what's that sound did you hear that
it's like a phone
too close to something
sound
alright where are we going next
yeah my phone is not here though my
phone is not here
my phone is very far from here was it
was it part of the game
let me see again
if i go through here
wait it happened again at the same place
wait wait wait a little bit
huh
wait
oh
hey it's in the game no
it's in the game
[Laughter]
is it only here
it's messing with us
like i was like hey i don't have my
phone here it can't be me
let me try again
for science
i see you again
i hear it i hear it
come on
no it's i was kind of gone
it's the bucket
no don't you dare
don't you there's such my bucket where
am i going which way uh jump circle it
will hold a button that says the name
okay wait did i get everything
oh
that's new what's new
wait wait i'm gonna go over there
i'll get there
that's a jump circle that's infinite
hole
brainy's achievement
we did that collectibles
oh what is this collect them all can you
find them can you find them can you find
them can you find
here find them can
what
wow
whoa am i supposed to
collectible stars no it's a real video
game in the stanley parable 2 you'll run
around gathering up these miniature
stanley figurines
and what's truly innovative is that
there will be no reward for collecting
all of them wow
that's so rewarding joy of watching a
number go up you simply collect all of
them and then you move the hell on with
your unremarkable life
[Music]
but wait what figures are the stars the
figures how do i collect them
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] game like keep on tapping
out
how do i collect i can keep going i'm
scared though it's so black
i don't know what i'm seeing this looks
like people
in a circle
it's kind of scary
oh there's a figure and they all want
the figure they're all trying to take
the figure
but i shall be the one
to take the figure
wow
it okay
i got it is it in my bucket it would be
safe in my bucket but it really is the
worst when you collect everything in a
video it's not that type of personality
a big fancy reward for it absolutely
tragic can take him
no
that would be good if i could take him
all right and what else can i collect
you only had one collectible is that the
thing because you don't like it when you
have to collect everything and then get
one reward so you only give me one out
of six things
okay well what else do we have did i see
everything
settings world cha
settings
settings settings
where is that where is that i see it
here but where where am i looking at
right now
exit is there
where's the settings
it should be
it should be here and left
big red i know i saw the big red arrow
but i don't know
what direction
wait i need to figure this out so the
exit is behind me and here it is there
so
yeah okay yeah
through there through
through
what's dent
it's that is merch okay so it's like on
the other side of the merch
like
i was right it should be here
settings doco in here but we were
already okay i'll be honest i haven't
yet decided on this one
i think that in the new version the
office could use a bit of decoration
like balloons but i'm undecided on
upstate
someday now we have to do this again
though
we already did it
see now i'll go this because i know
you'll choose the other one
wait i tapped out oh sure you know
sometimes when you solicit another
person's opinion it makes you realize
that you knew which one you actually
really wanted all along
get well someday
[Music]
yeah guy well that's exactly what i need
thank you maybe i should have gone with
no no i've made my decision we're moving
or did you
did you make the decision or was it me
all along
how do i get to the second floor that
one or
is there other stairs
what what is
what is this
what is this number
like that
check the merch ah
okay i feel like i already like walked
at it but
i saw the new content
the end is never the end again this
shirt is the best new feature
uh-huh they're back two doors let's go
i can't go inside i can't buy anything
that's my brain by the way very pretty i
know it's um red and black yes
merch what does that is that actually
like does it bring you to actual
merchandise
i don't have my phone here to scan qr
codes right now
what is it individual the qr code
there's a video i don't have it right
now i don't have my qr phone
qr focus
uh
that's new
that's new x i think we're gonna go to
the exit
way it took i think
i found stairs i think
yes
oh
[Music]
what's this all right have you seen
everything you wanted to no i'm ready to
move on i want to see the settings
is this the exit am i going for the
accent
that's the x oh no
i can't find the
settings huh
i can't find it
helpful
exit jump circle it's not written
anywhere i've been through here
help us bucket bucket is so useless
right now we need to fill it with some
chimkin
and it wouldn't be more it would be more
useful then
what about here the whole uh
and here is that is that the whole thing
oh yeah
uh go to gym button on the way
there's a door gym button
gym button jim jim jim button
jim button the button that says my name
over here
on the way there's a door
like
this one ah this one this
a one
an epilogue would be fun wouldn't it
stanley yes yes it would go at the end
of the um
well we'll figure that out later the end
of the end
i already know that
oh
second floor
ah this is how you get up here
champion
is this what i think it is
well he said you have to find me again
what
[\h__\h]
it doesn't open
that doesn't mean i'm not the world
champion
you need to become the settings world
champion to enter the settings world
champion room
settle settings every possible huh
ah a just
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
what if i what if something doesn't need
adjustment
okay
eh one handed walking
hold left and right mouse buttons to
walk
in i guess we'll go
i don't know something i can read yeah
german deutsche yeah
uh house
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my god
you guys remember my original settings
you changed this before
[Music]
yeah okay
[Laughter]
um
else i have to change this too
oh [\h__\h] y'all
huh
oh [\h__\h] hell man
again
i forgot that was possible
okay okay okay okay
oh dear i don't have to remember this
right
okay okay okay did i change everything i
think i changed everything
i think i did
so look
that's spin fought sets and callie would
like this she was so excited about
german
einstein
inverted [\h__\h] last michigan
i didn't get an achievement
when am i getting the achievement
you need to send every single selling to
every no [\h__\h] way
no
like if it's from 1 200 i have to set it
no [\h__\h] way
no who does that
who does that
no i'm not doing that i don't want to
meet this person that badly
bless
but it's just the answer yeah
[Music]
sensitivity i guess
here
okay
give up i give up you got me
i don't want i tried i tried okay you
can't say i didn't try
just drag them oh
just slide it
i i don't have to like
i can just go like
swoosh swoosh
swish swish
is this enough swish swish swish
nothing here
and
[Music]
nothing here okay
i didn't get it
i can't move
okay okay is this normal
they're more hidden ah yeah okay but why
can't i not move
uh
where was
on
there we go what is this translation
labels
wow amazing
all my key bindings oh no there we go
uh
hidden hidden
i like this this sounds when i press
everything
you know i got it
you're into deep
yeah i can't back out anymore
controller i don't even have a
controller
well
resolution
and lat ha
ha
but
what do you mean what
hit
oh you mean
okay
medium large very small yes what um
medium
oh my god
this is insanity
i got it
i'm the settings world champion
uh
wwe and settings world champion wow holy
[\h__\h] i'm like rocking it while i'm sick
um
getting all those achievements
now let me in
oh you [\h__\h] idiot let me in
it doesn't let me enough to restart the
game
after i start the game
it doesn't let me in
walk away and come back okay
oh
hello
i can see you've gotten the settings
world champion achievement well done
translation experienced every setting
travel to all corners of the settings
menu there's nothing you haven't seen
so
just for you in the stanley parable too
i'm including an entirely new setting
something called bump scarcity oh what
exactly is bump scarcity
i haven't quite figured that part out
yet but i just know that you'll be able
to adjust it on some sort of slime
and that it'll be available from the
settings menu we'll sort the rest of the
details out later i hope you're looking
forward to trying out every level of
bumpscarcity in the stanley parable
it's mine
can i take it [\h__\h] windows
i can't i can't take it what
it's worth nothing if i can't take it
like my bucket
kill me
i want it i want it when this room is
not very special
congratulations settings world champion
oh thank you
what a scam
check your settings now oh my god
where is it
is it like how i bump off of other
things
doesn't do anything
huh
but
it doesn't do anything
these [\h__\h] these [\h__\h]
it doesn't do anything i was scammed
it's a scam
okay i think i've seen it all
i'll go to the exit now
where is it
i've been there before
or maybe when i jump
you know what stanley i actually think
the jump circle was a pretty good idea
i'd like to hang on to that for the
sequel i already heard that
real gamers always use frozen bum
scarcity
yes yes oh i'm not insane i would do
over 9000 if i could
what over 9000 these are not real
elevators
i know a real elevator if i see one
these are not they don't even have a
button to call them what the [\h__\h]
the [\h__\h]
exit doko
exit dogo
now this will not
get through
the security screening my friends
because oh
i was gonna say because the accident is
not marked properly in big leather
somewhere but it isn't it's this should
be green
yeah i think i think um
you know in public buildings like this
the the exit sign has to be marked in
like a lit up uh
like knee and whatever
that lights up at all times
because
um so that you also see it at night
because this if the lights were off i
wouldn't see this exit sign
i wouldn't see it
yeah i am an inspector yes i am
yes
i turned into a steam review
[Laughter]
oh is this a guy from half-life i don't
know i feel like
you know i never played half-life but i
feel like
looks like
looks like him wait let me go
half-life
oh that's stanley oh why did i think of
oh no
what was this
nice room
that's a big hole so stanley what do you
think do you like all of the new
features no yes i know it's not exactly
clear yet how exactly these features
will come together as one single
coherent video game but i can feel it in
my soul it's going to work there's
definitely a good game in there
somewhere say let's do an experiment
i'll arrange these new features together
and we'll see whether or not it coheres
into a meaningful gameplay experience
[Music]
are you ready
here it is
i give you
the stanley parable too
wow
well um i mean there's potential here
right it's sort of okay never mind it's
tiny hold on let me do a different
arrangement
okay okay okay impress me this is much
it was something good something new here
we go something refreshing
[Laughter]
am i kidding stanley
this isn't a coherent video game at all
[Music]
i wanted more than anything to create a
sequel that would capture all the magic
of the first game i wanted fans to love
it no matter how good these gags are
they wouldn't stand on their own they
would need the structure in the gameplay
of the original
wait
maybe that's it
i can take the original stanley parable
and simply well
insert a few of my new features into it
peacefully of course with respect with
care for the vision and integrity of the
original game
would it possibly work
i suppose it could but it would need a
really really tremendous title screen
maybe if you act jumpy
i would be happy just by that this is
the standing terrible that would be a
good reason to make a stanley parable
too
just for the jumping all right perfect
go ahead
take a look
oh because that was the exit
wow
oh
that is
that is quite the title screen
[Music]
the way it moves like a snake
and a red light oh
that's
pretty impressive good job
oh
i like it
do i get something if i look at it
forever where does it go
is it a loop
good job noraelia for once
for once you did something good
you thought this is a dlc
i think again yeah now with this title
i am convinced
whoa
that was actually cool good job um are
there new settings
how about we i think you know it was a
little bit too much bump viscosity
it should be like
what is this
what is this setting
like i can do these properly
but this goes from one uh to twelve to
fifty to seventy six two hundred two
thousand
is there like
is that some kind of like multiplication
thingy
i hate it
okay let's begin the game
welcome to stanley parable 2
was simple he sat at his desk in room
427 and he pushed buttons on the
keyboard
orders came to him through a monitor at
the desk telling
buttons to push how long to push them
and him wow
this is what employee 427 did every day
of every month the loots are blue
when i started
i'd have considered it
stanley relished every moment that the
orders came in
[Music]
all right um where are the balloons
wait well i guess we've we're done with
the extra content unless this is still
extra content but my balloons are here
this co-workers
kid will someday wait for something
decided to
when am i getting better
[Laughter]
i want to get better now
[\h__\h] mouse
this triggers me so hard it's [\h__\h]
moms you guys you guys have no idea how
triggering that is
i feel like if i restarted my pc
it would work but look at my button and
my my bug could book it stanley picked
up the bucket
he did implement all the features into
the main game the balloons are there i
can't jump though
and the bucket is there what about the
pillow can i have the pillow no
okay it's exciting
now bucket can influence all endings
really
i [\h__\h] my mouse [\h__\h] it
where's the new content wasn't it here
it's gone it's now in the game it
doesn't need its own room anymore
is everything different now
stanley clutched the bucket tightly to
his chest and entered the door on his
left uh-huh
did stanley really do that
i don't know if he really did that you
like foreshadowing i don't like
foreshadowing
but okay i'll see where this goes
he did really
what did he do now
someone left on their pc it's kind of
[\h__\h] bright
oh
meeting room meeting room
still no one was here except me and my
buddy needed the buckets warmth and
comfort now more than ever perhaps his
boss's office was where he'd find
answers the voice lines changed
no no no how to solve a dispute use the
bucket put the bucket on the top of the
head of the person you have a dispute
with that will solve all the problems
partelli pie chart prophet's cute
cute
okay brown glasses
what happens now that i have the bucket
oh stanley can you feel it yes the broom
closet it wants the bucket you can feel
that can't you the aura of jealousy it's
as clear as day this broom closet
believes it deserves the bucket
i can really feel it now you can't take
it away from me it belongs in a broom
closet that's what the broom is trying
to say here it's supposed to go with the
other cleaning supplies
you gave it to me as a reward somehow
yeah i know how hard it must be given
the pressure that the broom i know what
this is this is a reverse psychology
thing this is your bucket yes this is
your companion and lifelong friends no i
agree with that you can't hand it over
no no i'm not heading i'm calling now it
seems is this how low the broom closet
has sunk that it has to resort to this
stream of petty insults simply in order
to get you to hand over the bucket
stanley i never liked this broom closet
for a variety because you couldn't
control it i had imagined
and wait
now the broom closet has the goal to
imply that you and the bucket are not
truly deep and lasting friends
but your relationship is purely
superficial and convenient that your
life is super null and meaningless that
you feel the same sort of kinship
towards any inanimate object which
happened to lay in your path in an even
partially enticing manner well i've
never no you can't make me hate the
broom closet lay into it no really tell
the broom closet off for its demeaning
comments expand on the wide variety of
experiences
you and the bucket have shared together
go through each of them point by point
share your journal entries detailing the
rich emotional landscape of your
feelings for the bucket as they have
changed and evolved over the years
you're kind of intimate and private
well there was this one time
where
my
okay something which i think will help
settle this debate once and for all okay
good thank god i didn't want to say ah
no
no more debate no more discussion
take a hike broom closet with all your
meandering philosophical diatribes about
the nature of cleaning supplies and
their relationship to broome closets in
the natural order of things
thank you wow
because i think it's appropriate
you see i feel that it works because the
sticker is also a bucket
that way if you're ever unsure whether
the thing you're holding is a bucket or
not you can look down at this sticker
and say to yourself oh
it's a bucket
okay variety of applications for this
sticker wow can i put it on other things
and make it a bucket too
like the broom what if i put it on the
broom can we put it on the broom
you know what i could take the name
calling and the dismissal of your
kinship with the bucket but now the
broom closet is just giving us a silent
treatment to be honest i'm sick of the
pettiness on display you can stay here
all you like but i've had it with this
impetulant room of cleaning supplies
easily the most childish room i've ever
been in i'll see you outside and we can
get on with the story about you and your
bucket uh hi see
you want me to leave the room huh
well i don't want to live the room
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
i'm smarter than you i'm smarter than
you i'll stay in the room
let me um just close the door here
well here we are back in the closet
[Laughter]
um
so
um intimate stories of my bucket um
yeah so
there was this
this one time
when
um
the toilet was broken just kidding i
don't know
i can't say it no no no no
what
i can't leave this room
[Laughter]
ah
is that it i want more oh so it doesn't
need this this room doesn't need a
bucket it has this bucket this is kind
of a bucket too
right
[Music]
all right bye-bye
i think
i think i can't
i can't fix this
that is a bucket yeah
yeah i got my stickers yes yeah my
sticker makes it very clear that it's a
bucket there's no bucket sticker
on that bucket is there
maybe it needs a sticker
oh but it has a fun image of
a person
trying to
like do a sick jump into the
ocean if that's if that sign is supposed
to be the ooh slippery sign
then there's that's a lot of water for
that
all right all right all right
sick chop do a flip
let's go all right coming to a staircase
stanley and the bucket walked upstairs
to the boss's office we did we did do
that yes i remember that very clearly
like this morning's breakfast
it's our favorite room
because here comes the elevator and
oh but what about this room
oh
i never saw
[Music]
only the intrinsic creature of a job i'm
not doing it for the sake of collecting
them they god knows i've tried i'm not
doing it for any reason to savor each
and every moment you'll come across one
of these beautiful figurines i will
savor it
um
that felt so
good
yes
because the bus knows that what the bus
says goes if the bus suffered losses
then that's what the bus chose
because the bus knows
that what the bus says goes
if the bus suffered
losses
then that's what the bus shows
so so true
so true
i nailed the dough
can i go
no
extreme bathrooms
and time but time is a concept
all right oh nice we got a collectible
so you're telling me that there's even
more collectibles
and i have to find them all oh my god i
don't have to i guess because there is
no
reward for finding them i guess
looks like you'll need to use the bucket
again then it was once again stunned to
discover not an indication of any human
life
crushed by the weight of this revelation
stanley may have broken down into an
emotional dumpster fire if not for the
soothing presence of the bucket
even now in his darkest of ours did the
buckets warmth and guiding light pierce
the dark clouds of confusion and chaos
it would be with him always
the button would
and he knew it is that
a marriage with me in the bucket
stanley was so absorbed in the tender
spiritual connection he shared with the
bucket that he didn't notice the keypad
behind the boss's desk
nor in his bliss of simply being near
the bucket did he have any notion that
the pin number for the keypad was two
eight four five
i don't know that like you just said i
don't know that
oh i wonder what the number is i need to
figure it out maybe the family just said
around two years
i mean maybe the books will tell me it
since he could never possibly know that
the combination was two i couldn't how
could i know impossible
maybe the bucket knows bucket and do you
know you know do you know the number the
code two eight maybe it's down here
hello
there's another here
[\h__\h]
i don't know ah maybe
[Music]
maybe it's
what could it be
here but it turns out that the panel's
emergency override kicked in and the
door just opened all by itself
you can't control my life
[\h__\h] you
i was trying to live my old life is
controlling my life
god damn it
it's the [\h__\h] illuminati this game
they're so easy to find
another miniature story figurine this um
you know there really must be a snappier
name for these things what about
minister ministers stony figs um what
about stanlerines yes i think i like
them no i like mini stamps
i need to save you the moment
that was good that was good
good stuff
good stuff mate stand
chihuahua tangents
let's go down
what if i go up again then we do all of
that again maybe he will say something
else because now i have a bucket are you
guys prepared to suffer again for all of
that [\h__\h] that i did last time the
elevator raced downward plummeting
towards an unknown fate
it would be all stanley could do to keep
himself together if not for the bucket
soothing him comforting him reassuring
that in this darkest moment
now oh my god the bucket is here for you
stanley
everything will be fine that's a relief
in that case if the bucket is here with
me then i feel like we're good to go and
again
another ride you know bucket wants to
experience all of that
can we go back up yes when i was
pressing those keypad buttons there was
something very intriguing about the
number three i want to go back so i can
try pressing the number three again
maybe i want to press number three
the the bucket agrees with me saying
nothing is a sign of agreement
free yeah
free
kiwa says
with the letter f
free
for free
free for free here we are said stanley
now i'm going to try out that number
three button
he took the bucket over to the keypad
and began absolutely slamming on the
number three over and over and over
that's the number three if you calculate
every number together no
okay
three
well
he said the number three is such a
special button i'm having the time of my
life
[Music]
had had enough of the number three he
got back in the elevator
what happened to one and two
three
free free free
three three
three
free
be free free be free break free free
free food for free
how long can we do this until he kicks
us out or will he never
yeah she's so sick of me he can't even
keep up with me
lame i'm so disappointed narrator
what about what about other numbers
is there a secret code that i haven't
tried yet
wow
can we do it yeah for about three hours
three years
[Music]
i want to break free this is the part
when i say i don't wanna i'm stronger
than i've been before
this is
the part where i break free cause i
can't resist it no more
[Music]
i've been before
this is
the part where i break free cause i
can't resist it no more
okay i give up
you got me
it's not enough content my dear narrator
son you should have prepared more
content does that trigger you when i say
that
i think it triggers him very hard
for sure
bucket had missed something
perhaps it had not seen how much joy
stanley got from slamming the number
three repeatedly
i could get some joy out of that
cope and see narrator let's go up again
content
content no no no no no you said stanley
to the bucket you can't go on yet not
till you understand how much the number
three means to me you and i have been
through so much together and i just want
you to see what i see feel the happiness
i feel
he smiled at the bucket
and the bucket said nothing
that's because bucket is perfect
like it doesn't need to say anything
[\h__\h] its existence is enough for me we
understand each other without words you
know
unlike you narrator all you have to say
is words words words words words
that's all you can do this time i'll
really assure you he ran to the number
three [\h__\h] and began to wail on it like
a musician on a beloved instrument
waving a concerto of truth and passion a
chapter did the number three like a fine
artist would wield a paintbrush he
taught stories through the number three
stories of his dreams
[Music]
the bucket conveyed absolutely nothing
at all
only silence
crushed by a wave of dejection stanley
returned to the elevator
will it trigger you if i leave it like
this
unfinished
just the number three
oh my god
oh no she didn't
yes yes yes it will oh wonderful
all right let's go down [\h__\h] it
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
mouse
stanley and the bucket was so close
they've always been there they love each
other certainly could the bucket not
connect with this passion of stannis
the question of course
are you when you say the bucket's name
are you talking about yourself a way to
get through to the bucket to communicate
fully with his dear friend surely there
was a solution must there be every day
always be with you
fear my friends every day night
always be with me
[Music]
i know how to fully express this feeling
in my heart
he decided right then and there that he
would hold a press conference where he
would speak to the public on all matters
relating to pressing the number three
sounds amazing where can they get a
wrong picture elaborate fully on what
the number three meant to him and why he
felt so alive when pressing it
then the bucket would be able to see his
love railgun by the way love it favorite
animation we'll react to this discovery
of standards
and it would be through the public eye
bucket would finally understand
you
[Music]
is this the real bucket ending
for months he advertised and marketed
his press conference building excitement
around it developing and rehearsing it
until he couldn't be refined a single
measure further did we also get to the
press conference room last time we kept
on getting going up and down and up and
down
for anything in his life
it feels so new to me
that means they actually really
succeeded in
you know making it fresh with new
content it feels so new
[Music]
again
free again
so many freeze oh
golf
congratulations stanley remember where
you came from your co-workers
i wish i remember where you guys are
where the [\h__\h] did you guys go
is that where they are like in the
mountain
[Music]
breathe
free
three
oh my god but four two seven
four
four to seven what does that mean
hello
come on
are we back
you know
the ironic thing is that obs let me know
that it disconnected in the exact moment
when
uh the narrator said there is no one
here
when i walked into this room and he said
there was no one here that's when obs
said bye bye
it makes so much sense because you guys
left me for a second how could you so
to press the number three on a keypad
over and over you're back though he was
unloved
uninteresting he was a failure no and in
that moment stanley knew that the bucket
would never again take him seriously he
wants me to leave it though
no connection no deeper understanding no
the bucket merely sat there in his arms
indifferent
and so it began that slowly over many
years
the two of them grew more and more
distant no they spoke less and less
neither wishing to state the obvious
that any sense of real respect between
them had eroded since that day at the
press conference no there would be no
more games no more long conversations
about passion and pursuit only a silence
that consumed the space between friends
and stan
discovered the warmth and comfort of
true companionship
was cast back into the unremarkable
normalcy of loneliness
free
okay
oh my god that was really an ending for
once but the end is never the end
no
oh my god
[\h__\h] it all of his co-workers were gone
what could it mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting
perhaps he had simply missed a memo
is it
isn't this where the bucket was
i can't pick it up anymore
next room oh okay
figurine find this comedy
meeting today in the meeting room what
i'm part of that
oopsie i'm part of that committee
committee committee com coming committee
comedy comedy
what the [\h__\h] is that over there stanley
lifted the bucket into his arms and a
wave of comfort rushed over him
you're back and the stickers are on it
too
awaiting input
gonna give more input
out of the game
and for some reason
i managed to get because i keep on
tabbing out i managed to get to the
wikipedia page of
gold
s cr
no get a gold src like a half-life
something engine
because i keep on tapping out and then
clicking on various things i miss your
popsicle sword
i haven't been using it much let me put
more
and this is
ocd inducing
who farted oh
that cup
would be good for
callie
alright
i guess that's it then
i can't input more unless maybe i can
input on other computers
[\h__\h]
zapped out again
oh
i turn it off
turn it off
i'm gonna turn it on
maybe try turning it on and off again
[\h__\h] mouse
i'm going insane
it's okay calm down kiwawa at least you
have the bucket stanley clutched the
bucket tightly to his chest oh he's good
he's the door on his left all he's good
as long as he's
fifty percent of thanks
[Music]
i feel like there's like so many endings
that i still haven't seen
but um i know
how to
get to them this was not the correct way
to the meeting room
[Music]
i want to go back the employee lounge
was simply the place to be oh sorry
i will i will uh
i need the meeting room is that where
the figurine collector is meeting is
and here it was had the bucket turned
out to be correct was this better than
the meeting room yes stanley thought to
himself yes perhaps honestly no i wanted
to go to the figurines meeting i forgot
i'm sorry
i can go back but i guess going
backwards there's no option in this game
never mind the bucket was wrong yeah
stanley took the door on his left
it's all your fault
ah
i can go now
meeting room
so the two of them detoured through the
maintenance section and walked straight
ahead to the opposite door yes yes yes
we did do that because i need to get to
a meeting very important business stuff
you know
how can we find him oh oh
it's like you know we're looking for
missing from missing person what we know
small things have appeared across the
office we have to synergize our
resources to ensure the retrieval there
are many uh questions there was no memo
from management [\h__\h] management
agenda how can you tell you spotted one
what makes them float in the air who
took these pictures of them a good
question he's in the toilet give him
some privacy
i already got that one though
please are hard to feel decided on
failing huh follow clues provided by
employee 416 we can do it red room
red room
red room question mark who's 416 though
thank you good luck thank you
smile
uh-huh
oh my god it's
clues my clue dot jpeg
where are they please now leave the
office before reporting back on any new
findings teamwork and communication are
great importance during this
unprecedented
precedented time of investigation
help i'm a post
oh
artists
huh get covering
uh-huh
or the fig lease
maybe we are the correct one
maybe the real collectibles was
that we met along the way was us
source of limitations
i managed to pick up uh sounds unusual
to our regular office ambiences or local
audiences using an array of microphones
analysis of the recording allow me to
triangulate the source of the strange
noise data shows that in all likelihood
it's coming from a dark area behind a
very warm place i also picked up what
looks to be reverberant of a porcelain
surface anyone have any leads on this
wouldn't you like to know
what do you like to know
where it's spinning figurines oh
saw one in cargo room oh thank you
remember that
guys write it down
[Music]
ah
it left me again i want to sneeze again
it disappeared
logarithm okay
do we need contracts for them what no
potential liability can we sell them
more money money money if sold together
yeah collectibles yeah sell there's a
collection how many are there six
[Music]
how do you know that there's six when
you haven't found them yet
there must be someone behind all of this
why do they look like four to seven they
don't look like four to seven what the
[\h__\h] oh you mean the employee four to
seven
why floating magnets
our quarterly success yeah they're
flirting because of the quarterly
success and dreams should we make finn
what make them lem
lim
little entrance
employees
interns yes
cured
trust the completionist instinct
why wouldn't they just tell us something
will happen this investigation this room
they feel pointless to be honest no no
no it all has a point
the point is finding them
oh [\h__\h]
it's like the x-files
they should say oh
welcome back welcome back welcome back
welcome back
welcome back hello
obs is not doing so well tonight
uh i was saying that i think red
something red and blue seems sounds
familiar and the cargo room and the
stairs i don't know
i don't really
i only remember the stairs in the in the
dlc room
um
there will be a reward for finding them
all lies
there won't be i was told there isn't
but maybe that's a lie
because they don't have enough rewards
to give out to everybody so they tell
them there is no reward in the hopes
that no one will try to
no one will try to find them i did
notice i did uh i didn't notice guys i
was waiting for you guys
i need to
blow my nose
okay
all right i'm going to find them kind of
room it is
oh is there one in the broom closet
oh no okay what
that's kind of really i'm not even
sneezing stanley and the bucket walked
upstairs to the boss's office
so i wonder if i go down or is there one
if i fell up
i don't want to go to the boss's office
again ew no
i hear it i think i hear
one
[Music]
name of these little stanley figurines
and now i'm torn between stanlarines and
figlis i'm a collector now
what name better encapsulates the
intrinsic it seems like you've already
decided to figure it out seeing a small
number in the corner of your screen go
up by one let me sit on it i'm sure i'll
sit on the figure
okay we got another one
feels good
i guess we're going this way
i don't i feel like we haven't been here
much but stanley just couldn't do it
he considered the possibility of facing
his boss admitting he had left his post
during so scary yeah
and in such a competitive economy why
had he taken that risk all because he
believed everyone had vanished what if
we take this car that's crazy and then
something occurred to stanley and go so
maybe you thought to himself maybe i am
crazy
in his arms am i crazy he asked the
bucket
the bucket i didn't ask that but said
nothing at all i'm not crazy that's
strange stanley thought usually the
bucket is a source of guidance and
wisdom for me in difficult times such as
these it never was really held the
bucket closed my own none of it's
familiar reassurance income i know that
and that's when stanley realized
this isn't my bucket it's just a normal
it is my bucket it says property of
stanley oh
why is this music so scary with someone
else's bucket this is all terribly wrong
surely no good would come from this who
knows what sorts of bizarre
hallucinations stanley might experience
without the psychologically grounding
presence of his bucket and indeed now he
noticed that the rooms were repeating
which was of course very odd
and now he felt himself floating off the
ground
oh gracious he exclaimed without my
bucket i've gone truly mad where is it i
must find it far off in the distance now
he heard it calling to him
stanley it's me this is you
could it truly be he rushed forward from
room to room passing by one bucket after
the next none of them were his none of
them i'm not rushing
come to me
find me you're exaggerating all of that
he had to return to his old friend it
was the only way to truly restore his
sanity and then suddenly he froze dead
in his tracks
he knew where the voice of the bucket
had been coming from
the real bucket was inside of him all
along my god when did it enter me
stanley doubled over in agony i'm black
the [\h__\h] ending's so sad
this is a story of a woman named
mariella
mariela's parable like any other she
arose got dressed picked up her bucket
of comfort and security and walked to
her place of work
but on this particular day her walk was
interrupted by the body of a man who had
stumbled through town talking and
screaming to him
and then dead on the sidewalk
right away she knew what the problem was
he needed a bucket this man had no
bucket yeah of course he'd gone mad
ranting and raving about a narrator
describing oh my god and how everything
is predetermined and free will is an
illusion and it's all just a video game
it could all have been prevented if only
he'd taken his bucket with him
realize he'd forgotten his bucket at
home in the first place
no how cruel the world can be
and she hugged her own bucket even how
about you give me the bucket
excuse me we can share maybe for a
myriad of confusing problems she would
soon have to confront at work for which
her bucket would provide absolute
guidance and total clarity on everything
oh come on
what if i ran faster all of this would
have reached a bucket what could it mean
that was that an option decided to go to
the meeting room perhaps he had simply
missed a memo
the confusion and the chaos all seemed
to melt away standing no
it just loops okay
and
[Music]
what
i want more adventures with the bucket
but that's interesting wait so was there
that ending before
without a bucket or is that ending
completely new because it seems like the
last ending that we had with the speech
um
we had before but without the [\h__\h] yeah
oh i didn't see that one that was
completely new to me stanley clutched
the bucket tightly to his chest and
entered the door on his left i did enter
the door in my left
i did indeed
see we got one more okay i want to go to
cargo
if we uh follow what he says is that how
we got to no if we don't follow what he
says that's how we got to cargo i think
or red and blue
too late for cargo in this run ah okay
okay then next time but blue and red
how do i get to that let me try to get
there
ignoring the
bloom closet for the first time
stanley on the bucket walked upstairs to
the boss's office both are right thor ah
damn it okay
[Music]
wait what if i go down now it's not the
exact same path that i chose before will
it still give me the same ending i just
got
cause it's not exactly the same
this time i went left immediately
same
okay okay
then let's not waste our time
what is there to do ah how about we go
to the elevator and then actually don't
write it a million times
stepping into his manager's office
stanley was once again stunned to
discover not an indication of any human
life what's the number crushed by the
weight of this revelation stanley may
have broken down
again whoa what's going on today
oh
actually actually look
cool
we're back
hello
[Music]
um
oh
he's back
i just read kelly i had problems too in
her members stream yeah cause it's
actually not obs right now
that was
and the one before
i think was also youtube
oh
too much bomb scarcity [\h__\h]
should a bay stream was acting a blast
really
but since last night really
oh
my looks
significant issues for a while
[Music]
youtube found no no the thing is youtube
doesn't have a bucket
that's the problem
okay into an emotional dumpster fire
well welcome back everybody
clouds of confusion and chaos
it would be with him always
the bucket
and he knew i know the two of them were
inseparable
at this point stanley was so absorbed so
dirty though i want to give it a
manicure i shared with the bucket that
he didn't notice the keypad behind the
boss's desk what the [\h__\h] is the number
one is bliss of simply being near the
bucket did he have any notion that the
pin number for the keypad was two eight
four five
open
open up
but stanley guessed the correct code by
sheer luck
this is certainly the most logical
explanation let's go
i want to ride the elevator i want to
ride the elevator i want to write the
elevator i want to write that
this time we don't annoy the narrator
for once
let's see
whoa
okay
stanley and the bucket walk straight
ahead through the large door
mind control facility
uh i feel like also here i've done both
before but not with the bucket
see i don't want to escape because that
would risk me killing the bucket
let's go here let's try to keep the
bucket safe
what yeah
what's this again
turn the light on
[\h__\h] tab doubt
on an enormous room packed with
televisions wow what horrible home live
headquarters like me and the bucket both
wondered to themselves more like youtube
headquarters maybe we don't have that
many members
oh
wait why is there nothing on the screen
turn something on i'm bored
let me try all the netflix shows that
are existing
at the same time please speaking of
netflix shows i tried i watched i
started a new disney plus show yesterday
disney plus really has only shitty shows
i mean
except for
scrubs but
i saw that they released
how i met your father
apparently recently in january
and i was like i'm gonna binge watch
this and then it only had three episodes
because it's still like putting out new
episodes every wednesday apparently but
i gotta say it's pretty bad it's not so
good not as good as the original
uh very disappointed
has a british guy
in it but the character is stupid so
that's dad
that's kind of sad oh parkour
how did i do that
but just as stanley was about to proceed
further into the mind control facility
he tripped and fell over the railing and
into the dark void below
thankfully he fell directly onto the
bucket he never had this before
cushioned his fall
now what to do next stanley wondered
stanley and the bucket could find no way
out of this enormous pit and so
eventually they decided that the best
thing to do would be to simply get
comfortable down here yeah it's a hole
so they set up a little couch and
relaxed
it really wasn't so bad down here
cold perhaps
after some time ago oh hell yeah
shells as well and a sort of kitchenette
that was useful for when the legs i
don't have legs
oh my god but it wasn't until the rug
it's amazing
that it really started so
in fact after some time stanley realized
that it had been ages since he had even
thought of the mind control facility
he'd never gotten to fully explore what
was up there i don't care i'll say on
earth the many mysteries of the mind
never saw this before
i thought for a moment i thought i eated
it i found a bug soon he was dwelling on
his regrets and the state of their home
slowly decayed stanley became withdrawn
and neglected the cleaning
me
i think it was the bucket who neglected
it stanley wasn't usually like this
the bucket tried to reach out to him
again and again but to no avail no no no
no no i think i'm the only one doing
[\h__\h] in this house okay
was going back and he only wanted a band
how can a bucket do anything
it was a mistake besides rolling around
it was a mistake it was a mistake i need
to do what the narrator says i need to
see the true ending what is the true
ending made no sense at all it was a bug
in the original oh
down
here as possible they put something down
here what's unconsolable
this is just a hole in the ground we
like holes we've established dads
true it wasn't an end there it is
lava and maybe possibly if we accept the
reality of things maybe this will become
an ending eventually
it's what the bucket was killed where
did i go
the truth of the world
i'll do everything with the bucket
all of his co-workers were gone what
could it mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
you know what we'll do now
we'll go get the figurines let's go
with the bucket in his arms again he was
home desk for free
three four two four
oh it ain't here
i'll remember it
[\h__\h]
cool
let's go
stand there
talk to me this was not the correct way
to the meeting room i am looking for the
figurines i have to you placed them
there how else am i supposed to get
there employee lounge was simply the
place to be
[Music]
turned out to be correct was this better
than the meeting room oh yes
i'm going the right way right you can't
get the red blue of the book okay okay
to the meeting room because the bucket
just keeps me too sane is is that it
uh that's where the that's where the
cargo is
where is the figure no
said the bucket don't go to the meeting
room go somewhere else
the cargo lift yes go there because it
knows that a figurine's
smart bucket i'm so proud of you
so proud all right
it could be it makes a nice sound when
you get close to it
is it up there
is it down can i even go down there no
right wait oh no
oh
parkouring time let's go
was this here before
oh my god
me and
[Music]
and then the first number will equal the
second number and that will be it
we'll be different people by then
different in the sense that we used to
have none of them
no we have them all yes you'll conquer
that different timeline ziggler and
marines
what the [\h__\h] is that name
and larines
drink the water
what what where do i go from here
whoa is there a hole
that's so [\h__\h] dark
i'm scared
it's an ending
no it's not
what new round let's go
what is that
ooh-hoo what's this
uh-huh
i vented
i haven't played the moguls in a long
time when i'm playing
my people with members
these are from my music video
yeah that's sparks that's heart
challenger
that's favorite night nancy no tony
there's so many copies of it though
somebody bought like a [\h__\h] ton of it
thank you thank you for buying so many
straight favorite nine
straight favorite nine string paper
okay it says narrator dialogue but it's
clearly not that it's a favorite night
oh
can i take one of them
nope
literally a new phone who it is
[\h__\h] hell tapped out again
okay
i'm going here
wow wow oh it's so old uh time to wake
up no no no no no wake up darling no no
no no you have to insert one of these in
here
[\h__\h]
if only i wouldn't tab out all the time
oh my god
okay
this
voice is
take note
i don't even know
i've lost track
nothing feels real anymore
the longer i study this bucket bucket
the less sense
anything makes
that's not the narrator
sounds so different yeah i feel
every time
i pick it up it's me wait it's me isn't
that me many times i've done it
it's always the same feeling
and the emptiness is in my chest when
still
haven't figured out why i see the world
so differently i think i'm insane in my
arms
why everything feels so i'm scared
don't get so close do i do with this
treasure
i can
i can yeah sell those voice packs let's
go merchandise
yes
it's unthinkable the amounts of money
people will pay for even just an hour
with the bucket
what are you guys gonna do with the
bucket no i want my bucket for myself oh
no i'm not gonna [\h__\h] out my bucket
no because as soon as this gets out
there's going to be a target on my back
holy [\h__\h] even now i don't know who
might be trying to get
what's that
who's that
don't
[Music]
[Laughter]
he's not talking to me
go to free for a free desk where is that
stanley had never seen the office this
brightly lit was it a sign of something
at least it was
super late much that it was
this was someone's job
just
the pencil sharpener
four three four with the bucket
oh wait that's uh
ah there that one what the really okay
what the bucket can i go back
stay open door just getting the bugger
stanley picked up the bucket and smiled
he'd never be alone again not truly
alone not with the bucket around no
without first yeah well now i already
have it
but how did they hold the pencils it
for
for free for
i'm here
what'd i do
you can do it what am i doing
what am i doing here
can i get the balloon
glitch out the window
do i get another glitch ending
oh my god oh
yes whispered the bucket into stanley's
ear we've done it we've escaped from
that dull office and that pesky narrator
at last out here in the white void we
are alone now and for the first time i
can reveal to you my true self reveal
yourself yes tell stanley of its life in
its history of the countless wars it
witnessed desecrating the land and lies
of untold numbers of innocent humans and
the buckets only complicity therein of
sadness and regret and the many years it
spent dwelling on the actions it might
have taken so much taste and the decay
if only it had been stronger no you're
strong you're an iron bucket what else
could you be stock of life for the
common man to manifest justice when none
existed and the bittersweet reality
halfway meted out in parcels like
charity and abandoned as soon as a warm
glow of inspiration
the opportunities to do so much more
there was so much it could have done
perhaps the bucket wondered to itself
perhaps if it had seen its own darkness
with a clearer perception
this was way too much for stanley what
are you talking about he screamed
to this the bucket furrowed its brow
now
not since the evil wizard gambharata
first ensnared me in his machinations of
payback for the sacred amulet i stole
from his treasured vote i was young is
this just a narrative
stanley screaming sounded like this
[Applause]
[Music]
the bucket revealed its true form
transforming into a mighty beast of
untold power its fangs glistening like
you're fighting
what did i kill the bucket
stanley you did it you saved us from the
bucket thank god you already had all 12
emblems of sages and knew the
incantations to summon
i never want to kill the buddies easily
been overwhelmed by the bucket's power
okay you've demonstrated such bravery
here today come let's restart the game
and we'll agree to never again go
trifling with this
bucket i can heal it magic cast away i
can give it my
oh why would you do that
this game is just
suffering
why are we here
just for suffering oh my god the bump
scarcity in here is absolutely
overwhelming a thousand
you people have got to be nuts how can
you stand this much bump scarcity i
really didn't change anything to be
honest
thanks for the comment though that makes
me happy that i made it so high
i guess i wouldn't have gotten that
comment if i didn't keep it on a
thousand huh
ah there's so much drama yeah drama baby
what if i do this whole thing without
the bucket
like it's a nasty
at first stanley assumed he'd broken the
map exactly until he heard this
narration and realized it was part of
the game's design amazing well once you
praise the game for its insight where
you may be just too lazy to trick the
issue
and it's examination of structural
narrative tropes so now that you're here
what do you think isn't this a fun and
unique place to be
why don't we take a minute it's
flattering honestly to my face because
the light is so bright here
now what do you think are you sick of
this gag yet no
oh
wait can i
uh no ah then in that case we'll
continue but now here comes the real
question what's the real question what
would have happened i know the answer
that you want forty two stop do you
think it would have been particularly
different would i have taken the same
idea but rephrased it superficially to
fit that answer what perhaps you never
would even have thought of it if i
hadn't brought up the issue in the first
place oh now think about it will it be
worth it for you to restart and then
come back here just to do the other
option perhaps yeah
this gag takes some time what if the
other option is even longer how long
people literally want me to do all
endings so
oh and this is rich perhaps you just
played the other option and now you've
come to see what happens in this one no
no no that was that's the key
which choice was the better one
imagine if you had selected continue on
your first playthrough how tantalizing
it would be not knowing what happens
when you pick the other option indeed
you are one of the lucky ones
well if the other option is really
miserable to listen to then perhaps
you're not i'm probably not going to do
it again i'm just going to say that no
one who's listening to this is lucky um
well now i've built up the other options
so much
[Music]
or just sit in this spot forever and
ever
jesus cheers
come find
okay some water then
wait so i have to restart the game
someone who said in the chat i have to
restart the game really
oh
it seems i really have to
i can't push anything
huh
it's a special in which you have to go
to the money to restart to get out
hey
or sit here forever and ever
so many options
i never saw this before so dramatically
red
[Music]
decided to go to the meeting room
perhaps he had simply missed him now i
want to do it no matter how hard stanley
looked he couldn't find a trace of his
co-workers now i'm intrigued
do it do it and don't wait do it do it
let's do it and do it and do it and do
it all and do it and do it
but first stanley assumed he'd broken
the map until he heard this narration
and realized it was part of the game's
design all along i knew it he then
praised the game for its insightful and
witty commentary into the nature of
video game structure and its examination
of structural narrative tropes so now
that you're here what do you think isn't
this a fun and unique place to be
[Music]
okay i'm over it now what do you think
are you sick of this gag yet yes
well i don't know how to say this
lightly but you could literally just hit
escape and restart the game any old time
you want like right now you could also
end it for me like you did in the other
time so i didn't even want to end it but
you didn't give me a choice so how about
you give me no choice now either but no
you gave me a choice this time
why would you do it last time i'm
enjoying what seems to be an internal
conflict going on where you are
literally unable double standards
narrator to restart the game so just to
push the envelope i'm going to try and
make this as miserable as possible and
see how long you can maintain
uh so you have challenged me there once
was a man named stanley
who people considered some men i'm a
girl but the truth must be told he was
not very old and was quite
particularly gangly
what stanley liked most was buttons
he pushed them like some kind of
gluttony i don't like them yeah did it
all day
in a meaningful way
but his brain had long ceased to
function
excuse me why he is in this parable
and lives in existence quite terrible
and if you are not strong
and keep playing along
you too
will become quite unbearable
[Music]
that's all you got
gonna sing it again
you're welcome to do so
i'm
listening i'll stay here
[Music]
are you not even singing
weak
it was a nice melody though
[Music]
could fall asleep to this
there once was a chihuahua
who was very very sick
and she couldn't stream like she used to
and she missed her little chicks
oh yeah
but then
she took the energy
much energy
from her little chicklings
they gave her so much love
and with all that love she gathered
she became
full of
i don't know
yeah now she's healthy again
healthy healthy joel
just how we
love her
the most
thank you tencho
wow one more time
thank you
[Music]
sick timing mate
oh
all according to keikaku
wow
it ended
[Laughter]
he's tired of playing
how about you play some favorite knight
thank you don't stop the music
please don't tap the music okay
i give up
thank you
all of his co-workers were gone the good
old bucket
[Music]
why is it like this
where are the balloons
try opening photos okay
[Music]
i think
yeah yeah you guys
everybody says try opening four two
sticks have you not been here last time
i've seen it last time
i've done this last time you guys don't
remember huh because you weren't here oh
you want me bucket plus dog ending
okay
maybe the bucket likes a dog
i want to hear dark sounds
only press the bucket upon every little
thing in the office
nothing responded to the bucket's touch
but it did little to discourage
stanley's belief in the magic of the
bucket
magic
the gathering
[Music]
tightly to his chest and entered the
door on his left
oh yeah we got it and i had my hand up
so
the
germs didn't go to you guys let's go
success the success story of takanasi
kiwawa
[Music]
which door do we go to where can i see
something new
this is different than before anyway
though
uh
thank you
oh
right left right
right
right for blue red but uh didn't i
didn't i have to leave the bucket for
the blue red thingy
right door
ah jump on the mail okay the correct way
to the meeting room but stanley had felt
the bucket calling to him telling him
that the employee [\h__\h] is lying
[Music]
all right
okay and here it was had the bucket
turned out to be correct was this bad
the bucket was always right yes danny
there you dumped the bucket yes it truly
was how
thank you you have a nice bucket too it
was wrong this is blue stanley took the
door on his left to go back to the
meeting room
take the elevator for happy life
the two of them did this one through the
maintenance section
get ahead to the opposite door
this one
are you talking about a different one
we've been down this one before but i
think without the bucket wrong one
no not this one oh you mean the one in
the in the office
where i kept on going down and up and
down and up
no take that one take that one with the
[\h__\h] trap the bucket
[Music]
disneyland welcome to disneyland we're
going to disneyland
oh good stanley i'm glad you found your
way here i knew you'd find this place
eventually
that's new
have i been here before i thought i went
here before
you see your friends and i are concerned
for you stanley my friends we've come
together it's an intervention
it's this bucket you're carrying around
everywhere
the bucket isn't even from the original
stanley parable it's just secret you're
not gonna say anything about the dogs
the ones that matter stanley classic
characters from the first game like the
adventure line
because that's what fans want from a
sequel they want more of their favorite
jokes not this bucket that they've never
seen before
yes i know i'm the one who gave you the
bucket but you're spending too much time
with it
don't you want another story involving
the adventure line sure
somewhere new yes yes that's what the
fans want let's do it
how about a collaboration between
adventure line and bucket you know i'm
just trying to see you know what's
possible
that's a low quality fire and if uh
phoenix tells you that then it must be
true
yes i'm married to the bucket
that's why the ribbon is on that side
where's that table
what is that table what room was that
brown closet wait can i go in oh
it's another brown closet
what
but it's a fake one
it's fake
i don't believe it i don't trust it
all of this is fake oh this is not real
it's all fake [\h__\h] you i don't need you
i need any of you
huh
okay i'll follow the yellow line
at least
[Music]
silly music as well yes yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is what the stanley parable is all
about don't you remember all those great
jokes from the original dialogue also
stanley is addicted to drugs and hookers
excuse me it's as classic knowledge it
was back then let's do it for the fans
stanley let's give them more content
exactly like this but if we want to do
that you're going to have to give
something up
i'm going to give you up
i'm not going to give my bucket up never
going to let my bucket down
then we're going to run around without
the bucket and desert it
portal
this portal it's portal welcome to
[Music]
let's
go eric welton married
he didn't see that one coming he's so
pissed now he left me
[Music]
where are we going
nice detail
the sound of the
ah well finally release for spoiler-free
yes
mommy i'm scared
mommy
don't you get it stanley we need to get
rid of the bucket no that's why i'm very
proud to introduce a brand new character
a character this is the bucket destroyer
nah
nah i think it'll make a wonderful new
addition to the rich lore of the stanley
parable true it also was not in the
original game but it's such a well
fleshed out character with so much
personality that to me it already feels
as though it's been part of the cast all
along don't you agree
i hate you
can you guess what the bucket destroyer
does
surely you don't need me to spell it out
it destroys my heart go ahead now
stanley heart destroy us stream it and
then pop it into the machine when you're
ready
i'm not ready
what if i'm not ready
can i turn it off
oh what
thank you
thank function
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] dabbing out all the time
can i just leave
can i turn it off now listen to me it's
crucial that you give it the bucket i
don't know what the bucket destroyer
will do if it can't destroy your bucket
destroying buckets is all it knows that
is its singular personality trait sure i
can hear you saying how does a character
with only one personality trait deserve
to join the
pendulum characters well you see if you
were to really explore the bucket
destroyer you would see that it's
designed oh my god
it's intensely loaded with complexity
and nuance that it's really like ten
personality traits what other object in
this game can you even say that about
the broom closet certainly not i wonder
what's inside the bucket destroyer
merchandise the fans will be clamoring
for after this did you hear it okay the
bucket destroyer is getting very upset
now you'll have to hurry and feed it we
can't get back to the classic stanley
parable characters like the adventure
line or the bucket destroyer until you
crush that damn bucket quickly now the
fans are waiting do it the fans tammy
give the fans what they want
no
i'm
[Music]
in love with the bucket you're not gonna
take that away from me you inhuman piece
of [\h__\h] the bucket destroyer
my prized creatures destroyed itself in
the end we were going to do such
marvelous things with you tell such
spell binding stories about you all of
its squad now
goodbye
new friend
for the moment in time that you are here
goodbye magnificent
not really
i'm i think we did the right thing
yeah i was stronger than that [\h__\h]
oh
i need a bucket for kfp
look at all those buckets in the chat
what would they be without a bucket
just a loose bunch of fried chickens
people would have to like pick it up
with i don't know their own bags they
would have to bring bags from home
who would do that that's ludicrous
ah no one would do that
i mean obviously it would be the next
step to a cleaner environment
but not can no no can do
it's been a thing for a long time in
supermarkets you can bring your own
[\h__\h] bags
still so little people do that
so it's not gonna work that system is
just not gonna work
so we have to provide the buckets
but just for this one time i'm not going
to take the bucket what could it mean
because i decided to go to this
perhaps he had simply missed a memo i'm
sorry bucket
i'm sorry but just this once i'll have
to go without you
okay
i have to do something i'll be back soon
i'm going on an adventure on my own
well i'll be back remember that okay
i'm not forgetting about you so you
don't forget about me okay
i love you
guys
was it stanley cage
he entered the door on his left was it
right it was red right uh the blue red
was right
was it right right right okay
this was not the correct way to the
meeting room and stanley knew it
perfectly well
it has done so much for me have you not
heard
the emotional support it's been giving
me
okay what now
standing now in this incredible room
stanley for the first but eager to get
back to business stanley took the first
open door on his left so i guess we're
not taking that one
congress jump onto catwalk okay okay
stanley was so bad at following
directions it's incredible
oh but i've been really bad at this
before
i can do it first try let's go stanley i
think perhaps we've gotten off on the
road sideways sideways i'm not your
enemy really i'm not yoko
from the whole you're trying to trust in
someone else can be difficult but the
fact is that the story has been about
nothing but you all this time
there's someone you've been neglecting
and
someone you've forgotten about you
please
in the middle of something do you have
zero consideration for others are you
that convinced that i want something bad
to happen i feel like i might have said
this last time i don't know but i played
kooky yummy one two and three i do want
to at least
mildly consider it
something beautiful look let me prove it
let me prove that i'm on your side give
me a chance
take a chance on me
[Music]
ah
what would happen if i come here with a
bucket
what happens if the father never come
here with the bucket
you said i have to go without the bucket
okay i guess we'll go here again
okay
now listen carefully this is important
stanley walked through the red door
uh where's the figurine uh they're both
the same aren't they isn't this
never mind
the last stigly wiggy
this is doing something just for the
sake of doing it yeah so many people
expect to be rewarded for the most
trivial achievements you've insisted
that a job well done is its own reward
exactly i don't need the overwhelm but
i'm proud of you for collecting them all
but that would be like a reward and we
can't have that i'm the stickler wiggly
monster and i'll just say it's done
we're all done here nice and now we can
go to whatever the hell you were doing
before you hunted for figurines okay
really
that's it
there's more to that right
there
there actually is more to that right
well now we can restart
there there was it was that
where the meeting room right meeting
room can i take my bucket
okay
[Laughter]
you can't do that to me
what is this
stanley i'm sorry but i have to put a
pause on things it's just
it's those figurines oh those figures
what i haven't stopped thinking about
them since you nabbed every last one
here's the problem just the most
intrinsically fulfilling life didn't it
fill you to the brim with inner richness
no
yes i know we're supposed to be telling
a story but won't you please indulge me
with one more trip back to the memory
i would love nothing more than to
revisit the figurines oh one more time
i'm gonna celebrate oh yeah oh yeah all
right one more time stop the dancing
[Music]
it's like the legend of the phoenix
and ends the beginning
and keeps the planet spinning
[Music]
that's something like a bucket
last night i had to dream about you
in this dream i'm dancing right beside
you there's nothing wrong just a little
bit of fun we were dancing all night
long
oh
i don't know what to do
about this dream and you
i hope this dream comes true
one more time
oh yeah all right one more time sorry i
really love this remix so much here's
where it all began galaxy brain
collectible but then we have no idea of
how many of them we'd find yeah
six right there on the screen but how
could we know for certain you're gonna
give me a seventh one
we'll never be like that again stanley
oh my god
okay oh hell yeah
but i can't take a seven point it was
six out of six you're gonna destroy it
and make it seven out of six you can't
do that
what if i don't take it
take it take it
it's okay for me to take it when
everybody else wants it so badly
maybe the others should have something
nice for once whereas though is me
taking and taking and taking and
receiving and receiving and receiving
really
[\h__\h] what do we do now it's seven and a
six that's not right something's wrong
with that
tamida
i took it but he didn't tell me to not
take it
what do we have here
oh yeah oh
ah we're looking at all the places where
we oh
but then we're going to 12 aren't we
cause i can do math
we're gonna collect everything again
here was a second standard that was
independent this one on your own just by
poking around in the boss's bathroom you
did that stanley i did that back then i
had no faith in you to find any of them
six but you continued they were so
easily placed sort of mundane
unremarkable ways
but dude i'm getting 12.
is that really okay
you should have reset the counter
okay let's do a little quiz which of
these rooms was the room you found your
third mini stand can you remember
under the stairs
i
think
the third one
did i even find anything in the boxes
office
oh i guess i did oh [\h__\h] i almost would
have got what happens if i go into the
wrong one i almost want to do the wrong
one oh okay okay okay thank you
thank you our fink i needed you guys for
that
thanks for closing that
hey
that's exactly right it was here behind
the boss's office
that you had three of them
i shouldn't be surprised after all
science tells us that it's impossible to
forget your third time doing anything i
forgot that [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you
it's as if he's hearing what i'm saying
[\h__\h] you
let's see what came next
this didn't come next
no no no no
no this is new but i like it wow
an apple in like a pink
weird building
oh yes we found a fig in this pink room
no oh well i can't actually say i
remember being in here yeah i would
remember this moment it's nice
so it must have happened
chad
what i don't
no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
[Music]
i can't help it you guys are dreaming
about me aren't you
i'm even in your dreams you love me so
much and you're dreaming about us being
in the pink room picking up figurines
ah yes yes yes yes no that's that's your
memory because it was a dream of yours
because you're so infatuated with me i
love you too guys but i don't
necessarily dream of chickens okay so
maybe you need to take a step back i
love you but take a step back okay
all right
since this is fake i shouldn't pick it
up
this didn't happen
it didn't happen
ah
should i
am i doing the right thing
she really forgot the pink room huh nah
i did i did not there was no big room
there never was a paint room
take it
pick it up anyway okay
got to catch them all right
shanina
look he's so sad he's concerned because
he doesn't want me to pick it up pick
him up
no no no he wasn't there sad about it
[Laughter]
no no no no no you can't film me
here
this was it
and this one was really something
special
i remember it so clearly when what
because this is really the fifth one
that we got
then what happened with the fourth one
where was the fourth one
pink no no no in fact
special to me i need a little you're
gaslighting me
huh
no
[Laughter]
no no no no
no that's because he also made a weird
comment didn't he
no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no okay you got me
for a moment but no no no no no no enjoy
for a moment i doubted myself
let's go all the good old times oh yes
oh yes this this is amazing this is what
i remember from the old youtube times
yeah yeah it was right there
it wasn't i don't know if it was really
five but mine might have been
oh look at it oh wow yes high five what
a class with a moment of memories
give me five stars on youtube please i
think back then the wood stars you found
it dude
[Music]
oh
he's behind all of it best boys very
style excuse me why am i only staring at
you back doesn't it i spent a lot of
time making that i love that it was
eight minutes i wouldn't have spent on
anything else i love it
what's that sound
but the pink room
didn't exist
stairs what no yeah the stairs he missed
the stairs
with the pink room
wait maybe you guys
huh
maybe the third one was the pink room
after no no
what no what what what what no what what
then there was no pink
what's this one
[\h__\h] you
you're you're it was narrator
oh
i can't trust you guys anymore and then
stanley then we came to the last
collectible oh my god
right here by the red and blue doors all
of you your memory is the most distinct
and clear remember all of your sassy
[\h__\h] it was the one that happened
more recently than all the others
who can truly say how the mind works all
i know is that this is the moment where
you picked up a fig and i thought to
myself yes that's all of them they're
all collected no but it was a moment
unlike any one on the stairs except for
the other moments picking up figurines
which it was exactly like
can you go back to grab that's a good
question
the stairs led to the pink room
no they did not
no they did
no
[Laughter]
we what no
oh shut up no
[Music]
oh
no we're clearly missing one
i mean when i'm is
replaced one
unbelievable you guys are unbelievable
you guys are really like really really
really into it aren't you
you're so committed to this
oh
is that jumpstarter
no it doesn't [\h__\h]
that's so lame
i'm in the present there was no more
because we've caught up to the present
moment wait why why am i trolling what
oh my
there was no i would [\h__\h] remember
that pink room if there was something
go go
stanley
parable
delix was there a pink room
there's a reddit
post
click to see spoiler
so one of the endings the collectible
one there's a pink rim of a statue in
the middle of it i noticed there was
whispers coming from the statue anyone
have any clue what oh
that statue in particular was whispering
something i didn't listen
no [\h__\h] you no you didn't get me i don't
believe you
nothing left
move onward
[Laughter]
[Music]
me neither there's some way we can stay
here keep enjoying these figurines i
need closure
we'll do the memory zone again from the
opposite direction see how that feels oh
right 12 18 so we're gonna get to 18.
are we gonna get them from the correct
locations this time
hi it's this one here the room with the
red and blue doors he's trying to
confuse me
i must say of all the figurines we've
looked at in our initial tour of the
memory zone this one is the most
distinct and clear in my mind you said
that before
you know the most distinct to me now
is the one on the stairs that we never
got
no
you're just acting as if that never
happened why
why
and here's where i made that video don't
you remember the video we watched i
remember the video it was awesome
speedrun
yeah i like it it's very nostalgic thank
you very much for that i should make a
video like that for my next outfit
reveal if i ever have one again
good idea it can't even [\h__\h] post here
you probably couldn't get any [\h__\h]
posterior and well you were wrong
let me make a video with windows movie
maker next time
[\h__\h] this room this room no
remember the pink room stanley still no
memory of this one yes so a solid ring
exactly see he doesn't remember either
[\h__\h] you guys
i guess it is uh whispering something
[Music]
but i think it's just
like just trying to make you think it's
whispering something but it not really
is whispering anything in particular
what if i don't take it
[Music]
i feel like i'm being manipulated
by you guys too you guys said i'll take
it anyway but
but the collectibles
taste the food and fruit
ah completion is instinct i don't really
have that though
you guys forced me to have that
not really
personally i would take it
[Laughter]
i don't care what you would do
personally
well okay i do
uh
i remember this from the bakery
[\h__\h] figurine
ah
there's no special dialogue for nothing
i don't know if there have been any kind
of reward for finding all of these it
really would have muted the intrinsic
joy of collecting them i'm very happy
never been a completionist
next one next
next stigma figurine
uh-huh
um nose is itchy oh
i did
you even told me if it was up or down
you don't remember
well now i'm disappointed in you guys
you guys told me down i was like we are
[Music]
why don't you know don't you know don't
you know
what you know
[Music]
don't you remember yes i remember it too
the past is truly a wonderful thing why
does anyone ever choose to leave
keep going
i'm not on meds now
no no no
17. yeah one more
until this insanity is over
ah
this is it the very first one we found
in the exhibit where i introduced you to
eating this narrator have you gone
insane have you gone mad me i want to
keep going what else is there what came
before this
nothing
nothing came before this
some things came after this but i don't
know why you keep on insisting on the
pink room though
maybe you should be
have you gone mad no have you gone mad
see this is
this is what i'm talking about this is
an exit sign that follows the law
this is how it's supposed to be it shows
me very clearly in a dark room where i
need to go to the exit
if only there was an exit concert behind
that that would be amazing what the [\h__\h]
is that
oh it's
oh yeah
oh we're back here
the big one
maybe he's behind all of that
this big one
and honey
can i collect him now
actually
well actually an exit sign should be
mounted in pairs with one on the bottom
of the door way to meet regulation
well actually thank you for that
look it's the terrible new content that
we were originally sold on
i remember hating it back then but time
does put a rosy filter on everything in
fact i dare say i'm actually quite fond
of it now
look how much fun the past is i want
more
i'm worried about him man he's so like
stuck in the past you need to move on
dude
you could
you want me to jump i still have some
jumps
there you go
it's really um
that jump feeling though
it makes me feel like i'm in some kind
of like 2d old ass pixel mario game
because it makes you like boom boom
the it makes it drop so fast
all right i guess um are you gonna show
me a [\h__\h] of nostalgic old things now
the doors wow surprise
really oh yes the two
a doors memory this one
you never played how do you know how do
you [\h__\h] go
how do you know which games i thought
you know i'm a boomer you always call me
boomer anyway how come that you assume
that i didn't play
any
old 2d
pixel mario games ah
had a game boy color
i had a game boy advance
i had all those tiny whatever things i
had a nintendo 64.
did you have it zoomer
[Music]
rude
ah
okay can i calm down no you calm down
no you calm down your little [\h__\h]
it's my office oh
and before everything else there was
your office now we're back in the
beginning
is there anything else was there
something that came before your office
no i was born here i feel like i can
remember i was created and born here
remember
settings i'm remembering something now i
remember before this whole story got
started back then i was
i was different
i used to make big decisions i was
passionate i was skeptical i weighed
each decision with profound
thoughtfulness and then somewhere along
the way i stopped making decisions
i became lazy and i came up with well
came up with a character named stanley
to do my thinking for me he would make
the decisions he would decide which way
to go huh i would cheer him on as he
collected figurines for no reason
how did i invent stanley
was i lonely yes perhaps that'd say well
you didn't invent stanley maybe you are
stanley and stanley really did make for
a wonderful companion even if he was a
fiction
i suppose it's grown old wait he's
saying i'm not real stanley's not real i
want to go back to how it used to be
according to him now i can be on my own
again i can do it it don't erase me
i'll take care of myself i don't need
stanley anymore
oh but
you're an
independent narrator now huh what are
you gonna narrate if you don't have
stanley
an empty room one more good memory let's
go back just once and give stanley one
more run of the office and then i'll
retire him for good
enjoy telling his story one more run all
right i can take down them or read super
chats that's actually good this is the
story of a man named kiwawa
[Laughter]
it's very interesting
it's very interesting i i feel like
we've come to a good
lower part
all of his co-workers were gone what
could it mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
is it
how do i ask this question is this now
just
main what
set up the opulence
ah
should i
epilogue is
like what plays at the ending right i
would like to see that yeah
and that was a regular reset oh okay
[Music]
okay just
how do i epilogue is now available in ah
on the main menu
oh
oh bucket
i just want to touch the bucket one more
time
where are we going today the bucket
asked stanley just smiled anywhere they
went together would be perfectly fine
with him
ah one more ending let's do one more
ending what did i not do yet
um the bucket wants to go somewhere
we're taking the bucket for a walk let's
go
[\h__\h] tighten it to his chest and
entered the door on his bucket very
happy to be very tight on my chest
starting to [\h__\h] chad oh all of kfb
wishes to become a bucket well then join
the membership now
after one year of membership you too can
become a bucket filled with fried
chicken but that's even better that's
like an updated bucket
all
[Music]
ride right
cargo lift ah that was all right right
this was not the correct way to the
meeting room but stanley had felt the
bucket calling to him telling him that
the emp is there something like
completely new
like a route that i
really haven't taken yet i feel like
i've taken it but there must be more
endings right
ah thank you
seven months oh so close
was this better than the meeting room
twenty one months yeah already 12 months
already bucket nice
how insightful the bucket turned out to
be
fake out the doors
someone up ahead is all new what what's
that mean
thanks members buckets
being here with the bucket was a grand
adventure red and blue door
reflected on earth
no never mind the bucket was wrong
stanley took the door in his eyes
after the cargo
two more days until back in oh so close
oh look at all these members oh nine
months very close eight months also
close put me in the bucket you gotta
wait three three four more months
i became a bucket and i've never been
stronger it's all thanks to joining him
i was membership
wow
i'm [\h__\h] only hurt a little it's a
good kind of pain
so what did we say uh jump off the cargo
level okay
there's something up there i need you to
do
stanley did not question why or how this
bucket was what about the pink room man
i feel so of course because buckets
can't talk but stanley chose not to
think about this obvious fact it feels
so wrong i'm convinced that the bucket
had spoken to him right all the way
thinking we haven't done that in a while
jump ah it's too late
i i thought about it
in here said the bucket go into this
dark room over here
stanley once again obeyed blindly which
dark room
dark
that room isn't dark it's lit
what do you mean bucket john tell me
you already did all the endings here you
had to jump off yeah but i didn't do it
with the bucket
i didn't do it with the bucket
now pick up the phone
pick up the phone and it will take us
back home where we can go about life
together
what oh okay
is this our taxi
and you tried to stop me from that
ending it's a happy ending with me in
the business is the sad story of a man
named stanley and his bucket
stanley a bucket because i thought he
was lonely and could use a friend he
took it away from me then very
distressingly he began to believe the
bucket could speak to him
but it did
wait this is new
this is new
you guys try to keep this away from me
i think
oh nice i mean comfy
i like the floor
nice floor
nice nice
weaving
weave weave bucket
oh it's a
bucket
with
made out of
fur
so it's a fur kit
there's no time setting
that's not gonna make the setting person
happy
hello sally it's me and [\h__\h] prince
cute to take me to work with you ah
to work
that sounds like
it's
gonna restart everything i don't want
him to stay here with you
ah
a rat yes rather [\h__\h] all right let's
go to work we'll [\h__\h]
the stanley parable reassurance bucket
was merely meant to provide the
comforting glow of companionship it
doesn't literally talk and give you
orders
whatever stanley is hearing the buckets
say to him is just in his head
no you
yeah my new outfit i'm glad you like it
i like it too
where's the bucket
where am i okay
hello
press auto take me back home let's go
home
shift is over just arrived shift over
lady i've been cons
sorry my humidifier is going crazy
you're free to formalize someone's won't
be in a bucket anymore ah it's so that's
so soon too has seems unreal the second
year oh my god
that does feel
like hey i thought that would never
happen as i said sometime before
so weird concerned about him wouldn't
you be concerned as well to see him
delusional like this obsessing over an
inanimate metal object i want to say
something to him but i don't know how i
can convince him i don't know if he'll
listen to me
[Laughter]
there you are you went somewhere else's
time you scared me
now i have to press why do i have to
press y
oh i'll try anyway stanley
can you hear me listen to me it's just a
bucket someone talking
about whatever
[Music]
so i guess we'll have to fill it with
sounds on our own
bug
yes you and me together forever i i
understand now why you guys told me
to go somewhere else because there's
nothing new there because you're jealous
y'all are just jealous you didn't want
me to have this happy ending with my
bucket
you tried to keep me away from this new
ending
and try to have me continue continuously
repeat other endings other scenarios
yeah admit it
this is the real happy ending we're
going back home see the bucket loves me
property of stanley i wish i could put
a sticker on myself that says property
of bucket
because that's basically just like
putting a ring on my finger and putting
a ring on the bucket's finger which
doesn't have fingers so i have to use
stickers obviously
yeah
but don't worry i'll make a sticker for
you bucket
to ensure you're you so you don't have
to be insecure
about who i belong to because i belong
to you and you belong to me and together
we're
[Music]
he's not listening he's still taking
orders from the bucket you know once
upon a time it was me he took orders
from me he trusted and listened to now
all he cares about is his awful bucket
this stupid hunk of metal
[\h__\h] it
there's this bucket but that's not the
same
ah here oh
almost at the seal
just have to ignore anyone in your life
except for
under the bucket
[Laughter]
let's go i suppose he doesn't need me
anymore from now on he's just going to
cling to this bucket this cold empty
bucket this sort of shiny bucket hmm
well i'll give it this the bucket does
have a nice shine to it
it's on the pc now it's so fun you see
it's so playful it's so cute
i love you
you believe i'm real don't you stanley
press stay there go back let's go
[Music]
you want me
forever together doesn't quite look like
your average hardware store bucket
it's just a little more um what am i
trying to say
sturdier more capable of transporting
liquid
like it would be better at moving an
amount of water from one room to another
press out to relive the same day with me
i'll hand him
beautiful
oh my god what am i saying
the shadow is so scary as if the bucket
is about to kill me
why do i feel some need to point out the
ways in which it's
so much more than just a regular bucket
land
let's say to go home to work to home to
work to home the end is never the end
work to home to work at home and
i'm having feelings
for the bucket no [\h__\h] you no no no no
get out of here not having a triangle
relationship with you say do anything it
asks what's wrong with me i don't
understand perhaps perhaps if i had the
bucket this would be less confusing yes
okay the bucket could tell me what to do
in this think about it a coffee mug is
basically just
a bucket
with a handle
oh yeah
all right a bucket is in the next room i
guess
oh
my
my oh my oh my
oh that's romantic and creepy
but i guess i should like you know think
positively in
spicy
[Music]
nice closet oh been built oh damn nice
all right
i just felt like for a moment i was able
to go up
[Music]
oh yes i want to be on the bed hold the
bucket
let me try to glitch
onto the bed yes yes
i love you
i love you bucket
you know you're also kind of a hole
but you have a ground
at the end of you
aren't holes supposed to have no ground
then the hole that we saw
last time wasn't really a hole what is
the definition of a hole
isn't the hole supposed to you know have
no
ground like bottom
anyway
why are these in the frying pan
all right [\h__\h] it let's go
you ready
to cover your asses privacy please
privacy
stand me give me the bucket of hell no
give me the bucket stanley i need it
give it to me now give it
go back to work stanley
okay
what
ah
someone was following stanley he was
sure of it if he checked over his
shoulder now he would surely catch them
i was in faster than you and i didn't
catch anyone it's scary scary scared
this is the bucket
[\h__\h] it
my one and only true love a good bucket
stronger strong
a bucket of culture and distinction my
beloved bucket
we love bucket where are we going bucket
i thought i wanted to end it
but where where how did we get to
our
lovey-dovey home again
stanley clutched the bucket tightly to
his chest and entered the door okay from
here on it seems like
is it gonna be like not connected
anymore
just a normal restart again
get two packets how do i get two pockets
unplug the phone phone
you mean in the room where
i picked up the phone
last time
that was an option
oh
i don't want to be with the bucket
okay i think i was right this was not
the correct way to the meeting
but stanley had felt the bucket calling
to him telling him that the employee
lounge was simply the place to be
and here it was had the bucket turned
out to be correct was this no never
how is this not a normal ending what is
a normal ending and why do i need to do
a normal ending
this is good too
this is good
what even is a normal ending no i've
done normal you mean without the bucket
i've done plenty without the bucket last
time
you're just jealous
jealousy is not good for your skin the
cargo lift yes go there good said the
bucket
now ride the lift all the way to the top
there's something up there i need you to
do that's just bucket less behavior and
why or how this bucket was speaking to
him it should have alarmed him of course
because buckets can't talk but stanley
chose not to think about this obvious
fact he was firmly convinced that the
bucket had spoken to him and he
unthinkingly did whatever the bucket
asked i love you
love you buggy
yeah said the bucket going to this dark
room over here can't deal with the
bucket list people play blindly
let's go [\h__\h] they don't understand
us
but that's okay you know not everybody
can understand us if they don't have a
bucket
i'm not getting jump scared
the phone said the bucket pick up the
phone and it will take us back home
where we can go about life
hold on why did you unplug the phone
were you trying to resist the bucket's
orders
i was joking
obviously the bucket isn't talking to
you and telling you to do things buckets
can't talk it was a joke don't you get
the joke it's funny stammy a talking
bucket
ah
can't you see um oh goodness i would say
up the delivery if you actually took me
the voice that i'm hearing from the
bucket
is about as real as the voice i'm
hearing in my head from the narrator
seriously what do you say about that huh
should i have paused for longer or
spoken quicker
comedic timing is so difficult i wish i
were better at it but there isn't
exactly an instructional video on comedy
that one can watch to fully oh wait yes
there is oh there is um it's sitting
right here let's take a look
windows movie maker again what is um
how long should it last huh how can it
be used to effectively go to work
political animals and more importantly
can it be taught in its entirety within
90 seconds okay
thankfully the answer to all of these
questions is 42 yes
let's dive deeper
if you've ever told a joke or made
someone laugh in all likelihood you did
it while standing 50 to 80 centimeters
from there well actually i'm a virtual
youtuber six degrees fahrenheit with one
of your arms raised straight upward at a
15 degree angle from your body
these are the optimal conditions for
good comedic time i cannot either begin
the joke start by stating and spelling
your name
next okay
synopsis of the joke including the
specific times at which the recipient of
the joke will laugh and then
spell out your name a second time
step all right
it's time to begin the humor ah let's
begin the entire joke in no more than 18
seconds and no less than 13 and a half
included it is customary to inform your
listener that the joke is over by
declaring in your loudest possible voice
i'm dunny
let's
[Music]
[Laughter]
this saying is a perfect example of
expectations management which is the
cornerstone of good comedy
finally it's time to hand out surveys ah
collecting hard data from your audience
on how rap they were throughout the joke
hey
[Laughter]
that was the funniest part
[Music]
[Laughter]
so how is it
yes
very funny indeed
is the only way to grow or learn as a
comedian
an effective survey should be no less
than 10 pages long and should include
the same question reprinted several
times
just to ensure that taker is actually
paying attention and not simply filling
in answers at random i hope you're not
and that's all there is with these
strategies at your disposal you'll have
audiences
[Applause]
[Laughter]
who threaten my very existence the
flannels smoke crates die in a hailstorm
of bullets and mandibles that's good for
your health man be prepared to give out
a lot why does one have a human leg
and their children after them god's
speech
i think the fundamentals of proper
comedic timing are still as relevant
today as they were back then so with
that in mind i believe the only way
forward is for us to return to the two
doors and walk through all of this again
so i can try telling my story that was
so worth it comedic delivery come along
let's head back that was so perfect are
you
done with the funny name right now
that was so funny
we really going back this is taking me
back
that never happened before that's
revolutionary wow
i can feel it um
really going to nail the delivery oh
[\h__\h] you those stitches
[Music]
the king of comedy that's what you all
call me thank goodness we have the
instruments
otherwise who knows where
well i wouldn't be the king of comedy
that's for sure why is my bucket sticker
the bucket spoke to stanley hmm
the bucket spoke
oh i'll figure it out on the fly no need
to overthink things
okay
he took my sticker next he's gonna take
away the other sticker
oh it's closed here too
[Music]
sticker
he's forcing me all the way back
okay you good
don't be scared
as long as we're together
all is good only safe
i'm with you
uh-huh now people suppose not i still
know i know he's trying to confuse me
he's trying to make me think it's not a
bucket
here we go you ready when stanley and
the bucket came to a set of two open
doors they entered the door on the left
[Music]
choices
really
right
okay
okay okay
oh when you
visit the telephone room again
we're back at the phone already yes
surprise
there was supposed to be several rooms
leading up to this oh yeah yeah that's
why it felt great up to this point the
dramatic display of remarkable comedic
wit which culminates in this scene with
the phone
true it feels incomplete
the joke will never land well not the
way it was meant to no it's all my fault
i must have forgotten that the phone
room comes immediately after the two
doors yeah what did you do you [\h__\h] it
up
i've made a fool of myself
i deserve the title of king of comedy
i'm nothing
not even the lowliest joke telling will
you suck boo
throw the tomatoes i think i need to go
back and re-watch an instructional video
yeah i guess so
sure take some notes
funny
here we go are you ready
when standing in there you're really
watching a set of two open doors they
entered the door on the left ah
[Music]
what do i do
i wish i could do
both left okay more people say left now
okay
no no no no no you were supposed to go
through the door yeah you didn't give me
the damage
this time
did you not even look at the
instructional video i think this is all
covered you didn't show it to me this
time i can make the comedic timing work
now
sorry
i messed it up your fault stamina this
is my fault
i want to go back to this room i'm going
to be shamed at every one of our
meetings from now on all because you
couldn't watch a simple video and take a
hint are you sorry
sorry
are you proud no i'm not
i didn't skip it oh my daddy you love
the bucket so much it's like you um
it's as though all of your other most
prized possessions pale in comparison
yes
let me try that again stanley
i heard that you are pale with shame
over how unabashedly in love with him
watching him being humiliated
is it the delivery
pale with shame pale with shay i
finished a new concert
true ending
no
no no no we're getting away from making
fun of stanley's obsession with the
bucket which was the whole point of this
i'm just i'm no good at these jokes
i need more instructional videos that's
exactly what
we did we broke him we completely broke
him he's doubting himself and his comedy
skills everything
wow and they said i sell the bucket i'm
not sure if it's a bucket but i still
have it
whoa
i can't stop playing
man
now there's some interesting stuff on
the floor
oh
[Music]
what could it mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
what does this mean i missed a memo
how could i miss the map
i wonder which one i miss there's so
many
uh
he always says that though oh man is
this one the green one
i can't take it
well too bad
of course i missed it when the game
wasn't programmed then i can pick up
everything i can only pick up certain
things
those you
ah
the embrace i got the sticker so it was
a bucket after all
test of time
how many comments does he have about me
picking up the bucket
yeah i want to do the epilogue
but
[\h__\h]
i'm hooked oh this is where it ends
what what does this mean
does this have a meaning
sticker disappearing might have been a
bug really
you can still do the heaven ending
heaven
how
tell me
local heaven
not no meaning
catwalk ending with the bucket is that
the heaven ending
oh no i haven't brought the bucket to
the no buckets allowed sign was that
where
[Music]
i had to jump off
yeah i think so
stanley clutched the bucket tightly to
his ending in pink and entered the door
on his left
i still have not been living well i have
been to the pink room
i i've been there
but it doesn't exist in reality but
stuff of this game bucket calling to him
telling him that the employee yes we
look at the think room again it this
makes sense how would i go to the pink
room again i can't go to the pink room
again the place to be
[Laughter]
had the bucket turned out to be correct
no
never mind no
stanley took the door on his left to go
back to the meeting room nah
okay wait nothing said the bucket don't
go to the meeting room go somewhere how
would i go to the pink room yes there's
no opening there
there is nothing you guys
all right we're doing this good set the
bucket now ride the lift all the way to
the top there's something up there i
need you to do she forgot how to get
there
and he unthinkingly did whatever the
bucket asked
hey you're not surprised at me jumping
down here
we're going to the
blue and red thing i think no stop look
there on the wall you see there's a sign
right there it says no buckets past this
point oh man how could you think it was
okay to bring the bucket here no no the
chat told me to go here you actually
don't know what is a bucket and what
isn't a bucket i suppose that would
explain a lot about your behavior up to
this point which if that's true well my
goodness would it still be a bucket if i
removed the bucket sticker
i think we have to do something about it
this misunderstanding could have dire
consequences on the entire rest of the
game if not addressed quickly and
properly okay so much of the images
on your understanding of what is and
isn't a bucket
please step in here for a moment
is it gonna be a a test a quiz
don't take my bucket
don't take it
oh it's a game show
now then i'm going to run you is this a
butterfly
and you'll tell me whether or not the
thing i'm showing you is a bucket i like
this studio this should tell us
everything we'll ever need to know about
what is or is not why is the stage so
dirty is that blood
yeah yes
is this a bucket yes there's a bucket
that's a bucket i got it right
this is a hologram of a bucket i know a
thing or two about holograms i would
know that
i'm i'm something like a hologram myself
actually
is this a bucket
can i have a joker audience
joker telephone joker something 50 50
joker
uh
[\h__\h] i think it's a bucket
ah
incorrect it is a 3d printed recreation
of the bucket not an actual no that's
still a bucket because a bucket is
defined by its shape i would say well
let's go on [\h__\h] wikipedia
bucket
what is
a bucket
a roughly
cylindrical open container with a handle
made of metal plastic and used to hold
and carry liquids i would say the 3d
printing material is something like
plastic so
also i would say it doesn't have to be
plastic or metal i've seen like other
buckets before i think
bucket definition and meaning
a typically
typically cylindrical vessel for
catching holding and carrying liquids to
solids seven resembling motors which is
the scoop of an
excavating machine one of the
receptacles on the rim of a water wheel
in any case it's a bucket
it doesn't matter if it was 3d printed
the hologram okay i'll give you that one
but this one no
this game is rigged there woulda buckets
definitely is this a bucket
well by your logic
what if i go no now and then you're
gonna be like haha this one is actually
a bucket
[Music]
ah this
this one is
this one
i mean it doesn't have a sticker you
know that's the problem we should put
stickers on all buckets
um but i'm not part of your system this
is a bucket
[Laughter]
[Applause]
this is a bucket when i go no right
you'll [\h__\h] it
under pressure
i guess it is a bucket
are you hallucinating this is attractive
it's an enormous machine that kills the
earth i thought this was a gimmick how
on earth did you manage to screw it up
absolutely
i went for your stupid login
to the next one i tried to see through
you
all right
[Music]
what
is this a bucket
this one's gonna be a bucket right
oh [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] yeah i think you
lose [\h__\h]
how is this
[Music]
i hate
you item six
is this a bucket this is so [\h__\h]
random no this is not a bucket
trick question
both gotcha
why why why
item wait hold on i can't find the next
one no more buckets it should be around
here don't take no don't take mine don't
take mine don't take mine
what
oh
that's not a bucket because there's
nothing there
what does he mean mine invisible bucket
but he didn't ask me it's just a bucket
he didn't do the line he didn't say it
there is no bucket
thank you there's nothing here of course
it isn't before me both know full world
nothing isn't a bucket wait when i say
nothing isn't a bucket that makes it
sound like i'm saying everything is a
bucket which of course is not true
unless is that what you think thank you
felix
are you trying to tell me that you
believe everything is a bucket no
no
you know what i'm too confused to even
sort it out i've lost all sense of
perspective what is
do any of us know what a bucket is i
know am i a bucket no
you're not a budget danny i can't keep
doing this ah i'm losing myself and
myself was all i ever had to begin with
i'm afraid the bucket is threatening to
tear our relationship apart no that's
you you're doing that but i'm going to
erase all buckets from the game no okay
not before i end the game
i'm gonna do it
i'm going to do it i don't care i'm
going to do it
and then i watch the epic look
i yeah i will not let it happen
now
i kind of want to see the end of that
ending but the end is never the end
anyway so [\h__\h] it
you won't oh oh
don't you dare me
this ending is important
but the punchline
i know
but
[Music]
who's gonna take it away
oh
here we go no
okay
what happened is everything gone why did
everything disappear wait
was everything a bucket
every single thing in the game was a
bucket
oh my god i had no idea
how could except for you because you're
still here i'm not so i guess that yeah
that's clear that cleared your
existential crisis oh not a bucket
either i guess so this is wonderful news
we're not buckets so can i have my
bucket back you're much more pleased
right now it's delightful to get some
clarity on that issue but it doesn't
change the fact that we haven't got a
game
so tell you what
i'll reset everything we'll put back all
of the buckets okay
and we'll know that it's all a bucket
but if you run into anyone else maybe
don't mention that who knows what that
information might do to a person all
right here we go
[Music]
let me just check out the bucket this
door all of his co-workers were gone
what could it mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting
the bucket made stanley want to be a
better man and a better co-worker in
time perhaps he would become both of
those things
okay
i'm happy
i'm happy with that
i think
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
many many years later
did my co-workers come back
um hello
uh i think it's about time that i take
my lunch break uh
[Music]
so i'm gonna
head out yeah
where's the bucket
and it would be nice to have a bucket
now the sand is so [\h__\h] hot
i could like sand in my bucket and jump
with it
[Music]
oh
that's nice
[Music]
got some wood
oh where did i get the wood from
nice
[Music]
pretty nice guy oh lena would be so
impressed by the stars
oh [\h__\h]
uh
why do all these games end in
apocalypses
[Music]
chocolate
we can't be on the chocolate
whoa
oh i like this lighting
i hope there's no lions to eat me
oh but that looks um
amazing
nice
it's like a montage
nature montage
it really is so cinematic
well i oh
that place
natsuka
um place of memories and nostalgia what
happened
this sunk
into the sand
hello
what is that machine
what's that do
so
we're not getting stanley parable too
the sand feels nice in here because it's
not so hot
but it's still coarse and rough and gets
[\h__\h] everywhere
ah
you're playing it no i'm playing ultra
deluxe excuse me
is this
is it a review
news article
cookie nines blog review oh is this a
good one i hope it's a good one so that
narrator doesn't get really mad
review the stanley parable too like so
many i enjoyed my time with the original
stanley parable which underscores how
truly this
disappointed i am with its sequel where
the first game
teamed with originality stanley parable
2 was dull uninspired and often
installed into its fan base
ah it's not good
that's not good rather than expand on
what made the first game enjoyable the
sequel veers off into territory nobody
asked for
that's not true
an infinitely deep hole
who cares i care where the new endings
there were a lot of new endings what
about enjoyable bits from stanley
parable one night adventure line i saw
it
but i never played the previous stanley
parable so i guess i don't really know
the difference that much
instead we get an uninspired side quest
collecting figurines even this diversion
feels incomplete collecting all the
figurines gives you nothing
i must say though i found the bucket to
be quite comforting
[Laughter]
ten out of ten
i think we all gave the bucket a ten out
of ten no matter what happened
i miss it
and it's so self-hating self-deprecating
oh name buttons
i can press my name again wait that's
not my name that's not my name they call
me jimmy
they call me jim i saw my name that's
one not my name sounded parallel no more
spin-offs no more sequels when the
stanley pair belongs to massive success
in 2014 its creators made plans to build
their property into an entire franchise
but a disastrous critical and commercial
reception to the stanley parable to has
pro and i would actually like to look up
the actual reception to the new game
it's probably really good
it's outlined in the press release they
published it it's clear that more
stanley parable is just not what the
fans want where's the press release we
thought that we had a vision for the
series that players would be excited
about yet it turns out this could not
have been farther for the truth press
all the buttons
that's right it's difficult
i pressed them all
the unlit ones i can't press
i think
i pressed them now
as you go along the room okay uh the
press release goes on and burns and
reverses
oh there's more
oh
gotta attach them all
tim
guess what
jim
oh my god maybe it is my name
let's go to the gym no [\h__\h] you i'm not
going to the gym
i'm sick
off the gym
and just sick in general
you can't make me
you go to the
gym you be jim
i don't have to go
i'm already fit joe
i'll do dancing nowadays yeah yeah i
have to study dancing
it's that stanley
what no
which one what the [\h__\h] where did that
even come from
huh
it didn't say stanley
it said jim
i never pressed that one i would have
noticed
i never
i never this is just like the pink room
thing that we have going on
this is why you wanted me to press all
of them huh
no no no no no
[Laughter]
but good to know there is a standing
button look at my fingers
one and two
20.
this feels wrong
at least we're not going into the fake
pink room
25 5
yeah 25
huh
wait that was
seven
huh
what no
and there we go
weren't we at 18.
one two three four five six seven eight
that was huh
huh
what
anyway
eight
why was it eight
thank you for enjoying the new content
you're welcome
where do we go now
why is it so dead here
oh
roll the crickets hello
[Music]
i love you hello i love you
it's terrible to learn that there will
never be another silly parable game
oh no
did you read what the developer said
preserve the integrity of the franchise
what nonsense the stanley parable is not
sacred we do not need to protect it
screw the legacy
let's keep making stanley parable games
until the sun explodes let's run this
franchise into the ground let's drag it
through the mutton back oh dear what's
your problem with it and if people hate
it who cares
you see that was the narrative's problem
he was so obsessed with what people
thought of his work oh that is true
that is true i'll give you that don't
make his mistake don't cling to the
legacy let it burn
as a phoenix i agree with that actually
it's not hard in fact let me show you oh
together we are going to make the
stanley parable free
free is a good number as we've learned
it's simple all we do is change the
number in the game's title screen okay
we really uh we also really need a
really dumb subtitle for the game
something loud and goldy
go ahead try combining some random words
together to make a new title for a game
oh selling parallel free
um
[Music]
these are not so good
part five
tuesday
[Music]
where's the bucket
i don't like them i don't like these
options can we get some new ones
i like this i guess
and then
choose it's tuesday annette
the stanley pebble free part five
tuesday it's absurd i love it yay
every time we restart the game we'll
advance the number of the sequel by one
and then we'll pick a new subtitle
sounds good to me
that way stanley parable will never end
and nothing in the game itself will
change when you do this either adding
more content sounds like work no need to
do that hell yeah
it'll just be the same content recycled
again and again and again with a new
title screen
okay i would like to roast uh
some game now but i'm not gonna do that
and i want to be mean
hahaha you guys
that's not even a game that i was gonna
roast but okay
i think that sounds good to me
what do you say should we go forward
with this plan
you know i'm really hungry i just want
to read super chats or eat super chats
now if possible i like it but i want you
to have a say as well thank you let's do
it
i disagree a new sequel every time you
start the game
and you know what since you've put faith
in my idea i feel like giving you
something as well oh
see i'm noticing that narrator never
found a way to give you the broken
achievement did he
oh
yeah there was something there yeah yeah
i think yeah
of course not i would expect him to know
i wouldn't expect him to know how it's
been bothering me let's fix it oh
all right there the achievement machine
is all fixed oh
you see i'm on your side we're in this
together are you are you the bucket
we're going to keep this train rolling
my thought of train
standing parallel cannot end it can only
spiral in on itself forever i must keep
the wheel turning oh
i'm ready are you ready
great there's only one last thing we
need to do
please
i will be very honest here
it's
uh
[\h__\h]
what
10 28.
i would never lie to you
please adjust the slide until the
computer is barely visible
yes there you go
thank you please enjoy this
there
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
amazing
wow
welcome to stanley powerball free part
five
to stay in it
it hooked at me
wow he's trying to pick me up
[Music]
what is it looking for
hi
okay guys i'm so hungry we need to read
super chat so that i can eat something
after that oh i'm so hungry
ah food food food
[Music]
thank you everyone for watching the
stanley parable 3.5 tuesday uh
yeah i had fun first time streaming
properly to you guys in a while
something that's not a collaboration
something that's not
dook of me and whatever
uh so yeah uh feels like
all is good again yeah the universe is
is how it's supposed to be again
score out of ten ten out of ten
um
and he's jumping though
so
i will read superchats in my office now
you may join me
if you would like to
stay close to me like the bucket
[Music]
i might need to sneeze again
and i put in the chat once again
we are cosplaying bucket this week what
for real like at a convention
cosplaying a bucket
oh man
what this world has come to
there it is oh yeah looks so weird
why does it look so weird
what
passing through
why does it look so weird
i dared it was kind of broken
okay shut up now
shut up
shut up makes me crazy
okay i didn't did i i didn't get the
broken achievement tonight
where's my achievement
i do have according to steam six out of
11 achievements though
that's more than half
and i didn't get it yet whatever it's
okay i'm i need to eat so i'll go eat
some super chats also this is ignore it
it's so inaccurate at this point
although tomorrow uh friday i will be
taking the day off because actually
today i didn't get to practice my
choreos
sad but i'm pretty far anyway
i have
um
most of the songs down that i want to
like dance to and then the other ones
will be kind of like freestyle um
yeah hopefully it won't be too cringe
freestyle kiwawa
um
there are some weird spots on your
screen huh
what
i don't see any
what spots
what do you mean
go along with practice thank you
ah
yeah that's the screen effect you mean
all that
that's supposed to be like that so it
looks like a screen reflection
why is chat disabled behind the chat oh
that's a different chat
chat section
there we go ah now there we have it
wow
in the middle of your face where you
know
you little [\h__\h] miss fist
you little [\h__\h]
oh my god i made myself so big i
disappeared what the [\h__\h]
it was wait i really
oh there i am oh my god i had to reset
myself didn't know that was possible it
it's possible
i never had that happen before
but here look at my nose
that's not the spot as my nose
okay let's get into position i shall i
shall put on my jacket
uh
sure
because when i look professional in here
maybe take off the boobs
yeah and you want me to live out
i prefer about the flowers but some of
you guys said you like the
version without the flowers
hello i look like a mommy now
me too
like all versions of you thank you
mommy sorry mommy
yes
yes my child
what do you want
dinner go make yourself your own dinner
you're old enough
you must make your own dinner now
i feel like my head shape is kind of
box shaped
when i don't have the birds on my head
so
i'll put them back i liked him
it looks weird without the flowers
though
oh let's put the flowers on
all right where did we leave off last
time guys
you guys know
ah
oh genma thank you
um
at the tacoma collab or the irish co-op
no i think we read
iris yeah okay okay okay not so bad
not so bad then
let me get some music
[Music]
okay
yeah
what do you want to listen to
i'll pop on this one again maybe i guess
[Music]
i was loud
sorry it was loud for me too
[Music]
it could have been louder
it wasn't that bad nah
hololyzer
where is it here
[Music]
let's go
i'm gonna
um consume some
fruit
lucky candy
[Music]
and then
this one
nice
suppacha
[Music]
i wanna get this done so let's get it
done
shall
[Music]
everybody got their brackets
they're comfort buckets
let's do this yeah
we're gonna get through this in an
instant so that i can have some proof
i need to cook though
no
i don't wanna cook but i have to
i have to i think
[Music]
i got a bucket in about a month nice
looking forward to that
aren't we
i don't have a bucket i am the bucket
yes that's right you are a bucket yes
believe in yourself
[Music]
you're real you're real you don't need a
sticker your bucket nobody can tell you
otherwise
what will you have for dinner of
sausages
yes i still have a hell fresh thingy
from last week even though the ones from
this week already came
[Music]
but i still have some sausage dinner
thingy
the sausages should be easy but the
sides are kind of blah
may look sad
[Music]
and the day before yesterday i made a
one pot
uh
tomato pasta which was actually really
good and really fast
hello fresh has some one pot
dishes dinners too it was really good
yeah
good outfit hencho thank you
nice typo should potential
ah
i've been trapped in the ui since then
you know my heart ate collab i got bored
and painted the pink foot
no no no no no no no
uh
[Music]
what is the type it was a typo
yeah okay human extension thanks for two
pinkies and two
uh yellows
after using him i was supposed to be
deaf but instead of after dokomi i'm
dead
i'm too old for this [\h__\h] then we're
gonna travel 10 hours by bus and train
again next time i'll take a
i plane
so much fun to pass on it next year i
already missed kfb ah
that chicken mask purchase turned out to
be hella worth it i won't
myself redox that easily but i'll never
forget that meet and greet even if i was
nervous as hell
after i left i remembered all things i
wanted to say that i didn't say i love
you aw
so i'll fix my mistake and say it now i
love you tanjo but you messed something
up with that super chat i think thank
you for connecting us together because
now i remembered what i wanted to say at
least now i have something to write in
the letter oh yeah
good reason to write a letter also shout
out for someone's keyblade who one time
got out from uber to street stood right
in front of me and said i'm here
i think we all know what happened next
[Music]
no
ah that joke
hi here did they say hi here
really
didn't he really do that did that really
happen
[Music]
really
so fast my brain wouldn't be so fast to
say that in time probably also because i
don't make dad jokes i make
high quality
jokes and when i'm done i say i'm danny
with the funny
did he say his dummy with the funny
because not then they're still laughing
to this day
because i didn't know the joke was over
and that's just
torture
so that's keyblade did you tell them you
dunny with the funny
oh wait it wasn't sort of keyblade i
guess so this kid maybe didn't do it on
purpose
the one doing the funny were the ones
saying hi here
[Music]
oh yeah did you give them a survey too
can't do the funny
[Laughter]
all right well thank you very much for
coming i'm glad you enjoyed it
definitely write that letter write it as
early as you can
so i get it soon
i'm waiting for it
and yeah um
10 hours travel i totally get you i used
to travel like
like eight to 12 hours to conventions
but yeah i wouldn't do that anymore
too much
but again i want to say
um
i don't think it's realistic
to think that there's a third time
so
[Music]
please
don't already book your trip
okay
it would be
not very smart
to do it
okay just saying
[Music]
you can't stop us no
just wait
just wait please until something gets
announced maybe we're gonna do other
conventions okay
we will be there either way oh man
[Laughter]
oh man well how can here's a kiss for
you
wow
thank you very much
we'll make a third time happen with or
without you so it's not even about me
anymore
wow
it's kind of sad well you do whatever
the hell you want then
i don't need you even no i don't need
you i love you
all of you i love you all of you
no gold
taught them the true meaning of
conventions
i guess so
i guess so if you just want to go there
for fun sure
i guess so
but how can you have fun without kim
hawa huh
[Music]
sounds difficult
the k in documentary stands okay
no man let it go to confess
yeah i would say the smart thing to do
would be to just
wait
i'm sure there will be conventions again
next year where i will be but
you can't know now
if i'll be there
next year okay
don't do it too early
[Music]
yeah be on the lookout that's the safe
side motion thanks for the pinky later
but i had a great time at the convention
meeting all the cave people i knew
online plus watching you perform was a
treat
not to mention how fun the call itself
was wish i was less awkward during the
meet and greet but the enthusiasm helped
me a lot i was pretty unsure about the
trip since my first time flying out of
the uae but by myself and not going to
america and i didn't know how kfp would
be irl but all that went away when i met
everyone great fans you got there yes
thank you
thank you thank you i'm so happy you
came too
you know i just was thinking
i don't know uh i don't remember sorry
because brain small and many presents
were given to me
during the meet and greet uh everybody
tried you know showing them off in the
[\h__\h] two minutes guys next time we
have a meet and greet
don't use up your precious two minutes
by taking out your presents one by one
and explaining them to me
you're wasting your time
but in any case i wanted to say emotion
it would make so much sense and it would
be so funny
if you gifted me a bath bomb
with rose scent
and you know why
that would be actually such a big brain
move i wonder maybe you even did that
maybe you are as big bright as me and
you would do that
[Music]
shoot i should have done that you're so
stupid how did you not think of that
oh my god
i'm sorry but
that's a huge opportunity you missed out
there
oh there's 100 i'm sure there's like
lush bath bombs that are
uh rose scented
oh my god
we share a single brain cell no that's a
taco that cheese
that is big brain is you i guess so oh
man next time dude
next time
you better bring me that rose bump
giddy dankeshan gd dancing
travel g
one two three four five six pinkies
are you okay
[Music]
and outlook
this pasta coming weekend was awesome
firstly reflecting on the mean and great
it was very difficult trying to quickly
pack out something to squawk about you
i appreciate you pushing me to speak up
i'm just not good not good at those
self-imposed high pressure
quick time events i'm sorry i'm such a
turtle
i love and treasure uh the moment all
the same so thank you oh and during the
meeting great i asked but didn't receive
your approval from my customer badge
number is it kiwawa approved oh
wait which number i don't see it here
as for the concert eden's new stage is
fantastic it looks exactly like the ref
you gave
ah yeah he posted that
man
that was that's a bit embarrassing
then when stellaris girls came out on
stage i got so hyped it was so cool
they were so good very cute too i have
it already oh okay good good
very cute too your setlist was of course
fire but journey like a thousand years
made me tear up oh really
that may or may not have had something
to do with knowing i would get to meet
you later that day at the meet and greet
heart challenger took the show for me
not only did we get to see the choreo
but i don't believe a single chicken was
hard from the towels the guys behind me
wearing the towels made a nice breeze
that really cooled me down from your
flaming hot performances you were
incredible more so knowing that the prep
situation you had sasuke on my oc thank
you
oh wait one second it continues all in
all saturday was a crazy day but this is
a rainbow
somehow
your concert was so good being in the
audience joining in the pen light chance
i could feel everyone's enthusiasm it
really was a special experience and i
hope all of kfb can join a live kikiti
concert
one day wait one second i forgot to put
up the thumbnail
a second
there we go
cute art
uh
overall photography i may not have had
many cafe interaction stories as i went
into the event in cognito but it was a
fun experience and a nice vacation and
i'd love to do it again next time i'll
introduce myself to some chickens you
should finally take a moment irela
reunion let's go
rainbow without the red yeah but you did
the the pinkies though thank you
yeah i was wondering why because i think
even at the meet and greet i asked you
like did you
did you like make friends with the
others and all that and then you were
like no i'm
i'm like why
why you so shy i think people would have
been so so so [\h__\h] hyped but
as far as i know you weren't able to
contain it anyway in the end
yeah
but not not all of you
seem to have met you that is sad
but it was so nice to meet you it was a
pleasure
really it was great
you're so sweet
just like in your super chats
sasuga
thank you soon very very very much for
coming and i wanted to say about the
towels yesterday i was practicing my
choreos and at some point i got really
sweaty and hot
um
so i got a towel and then
i was wiping off my sweat and then i was
like remembering you know what you guys
said about the the wind
creation by the towels
uh but mine was you know just a normal
bath relatively small though bath towel
like you know the ones for the hair
uh and i tried to swing it like you guys
but i kept on hitting myself
it made some wind but i i couldn't
twirl it continuously you really need a
proper
towel
that's like made for this stuff
i was wondering how you guys managed to
do it so well considering that probably
a lot of you
had
not the perfect shape of towel
need like a really small one or like a
lengthy one i don't know but i kept on
hitting myself in my face
now that made me
made me respect you guys a little bit
more
[Music]
we don't have noodles no no no just the
other day you guys admitted to having
new limes after all noodle wings
yeah
guests tell us what you're looking for
i'm glad that that seems like some of
you chose the right towel
and didn't seem to have issues with
like rotating it
[Music]
i feel like i'm reaching my
my
uh limit soon
with uh throat wise and nose wise
thank you travis thank you so much
you soon really was a pleasure i hope
that will be another time thank you so
much
hope your trip back home was nice and
comfy and safe too
uh
[Music]
the two people who motivated me to turn
my life around back together again oh
let's go can't wait for the stream and
the stories that will come out of this
trip enjoy your time together can't wait
to hear about kelly's reaction to
meeting the cats oh yeah
yeah she really liked them a lot she
played with them
and
she cuddled them a little bit but more
she played more of them because cuddling
i guess
is a bit difficult with my cats
you have to like join them
like by like chilling
in bed falling asleep and then they'll
join you actually
yeah
it's a bit difficult to cuddle them
um she left jonkers and she loved both
of them
but yeah she said that she likes
chunkers more a little bit a little bit
it's really nice to have someone so
excited about my cats
she praised and she praised them so much
and she did really quickly
like see the
big obvious difference in them too
because people often tell me they look
the same even though they're orange and
turquoise
people have to tell me they look the
same
[Music]
now
but she figured it out very fast
thank you typhin
[Music]
bunny game thank you
felix
thank you for the ride super chat thank
you
[Music]
ah
loser who couldn't come gang you mean to
talk on me
don't worry about it there's always a
next time and like other conventions
perhaps
i'm not saying dokomi
ah yeah
there might still be conventions this
year who knows
[Music]
maybe you can go to that um
don't give up i want to see all of you
all of you
chianacon would be great yeah
we're going to do for me
[\h__\h] you you can't go when i'm not there
no
no you should go only when i'm there
so that they know that these people came
because of me
concert at the pink room
a convention you mean the pink room
pink room doesn't exist
gatekeeping oh yes i will
i will keep the gate
[Music]
yeah so felix says uh thank you sorry i
won't be here live but i'm so happy that
we have another tv stream of kelly we
have a saying in chinese that goes like
moon
[Music]
oh yeah yeah i can kind of see
what the last two letters mean
which pretty much means getting together
after long separation is better than
newly getting married
what
guess that's the case here huh
i'm not sure
i'm not sure about that but thank you i
hope you got to watch the archive felix
and enjoyed it
here's a kiss for you
did you catch it
[Music]
thank you so much
thank you for watching
you always seem to like um be busy with
link stuff so you can't watch them live
but you still try your best to catch the
archives and i appreciate that thank you
lexington the lion thank you soon
general
now because i couldn't last stream
wasn't a plane during it ah thanks for
making dokomi amazing i was there from
5am to get a good seat in your concert
wow wait at the venue you were already
at 5 00 am
you know in hindsight
the earlier the better because we saw
what happened if you arrived
around 9 00 am or so 10 a.m um
i mean it was amazing talking to you
made me very happy now i'm home i miss
canopy and dopamine
also you said i look different than you
expected i'm curious how did you expect
me to look before you saw me in the meet
and greet
[Music]
yeah
i don't i don't no i don't want to say
anything like i don't know
weird so
or like um
uh
i have to say
no
i don't know
no not like an otaku
[Music]
i thought you would look like a chicken
like a chicken
did you expect a beard
maybe no not necessarily
older
maybe two
i don't know i'm just different
[Music]
oh come on
see
i don't wanna
no no we're not getting into this now no
no no we're not getting into this
[Music]
picking this up of hr oh come on
i am hr
[Music]
oh sorry about how lufthansa canceled my
10 20 flight rebooked it to 7 25 in my
sleep
made it
they made it three hours earlier
these [\h__\h]
woke up at 6 20 panic rest in the
airport and attacks in 11 minutes oh
thank god your bags were already packed
ran to the cake by 7 25 and a delayed
no [\h__\h] way delayed back to 10 a.m
[Music]
what the actual [\h__\h]
was that like a
uh like a direct uh long distance flight
or was that like a first flight with uh
a short one within europe first because
i heard that we have some uh problems in
europe right now with the flights also
i'm getting husky voice again
that's so [\h__\h] up is pyro hokula here
oh yeah lights in munich for my
connection usa
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] that makes me so mad
i would have gotten a heart attack
and then even though they they delayed
it to 10 10 am they probably still would
have required you to like um check in in
time
[Music]
oh i wonder if they delayed it because
lack of passengers because so many
people were missing because they didn't
see the delay
i wondered maybe we're like okay
sasugani
we cannot leave
50 people behind
because they didn't see a delay message
[Music]
thunderstorms near munich oh
okay
oh man that's so [\h__\h] up i'm so mad
[Music]
that makes me mad
all right well thank god you made it
anyway
spanking time thank you for the red
super chat mom mom dad i'll be on vaughn
duty for this but i hope you guys have a
blast the stream so i'm glad this is
happening the kids send their regards
oh thank you
yes
my kitties send their regards to
they've been very very very very sweet i
played a lot with them today
they had a good time today i think
[Music]
okay it's everywhere this is the airport
total chaos honestly for me it was so
easy and totally fine like i was really
stressed out
did i tell the story
did i
did that tell the story already
i think i wanted to keep it for
windwaker
[Music]
remind me to tell you
my departure uber story
yeah
i think i didn't tell this one in
particular
[Music]
yes yes i need to eat yeah and my voice
is [\h__\h]
yeah yeah but it's it's it's kept up for
a long time i'm impressed mm-hmm
so thank you so many kiss for you
i have many uber stores yeah honestly
all almost all of my uber drivers in
dusseldorf
were crazy
or weird
or just they all stood out
and this is not the first time last time
i wasn't this enough i also had a lot of
weird
uber drivers right
i told you guys last time too
that one that was like kept they kept on
trying to flirt with
us
yeah
but like oh star is not as beautiful as
you or whatever
ah what's going on man
are there no decent normal uber drivers
left who can mind their own business
i mean no there are there are some but
recently i've been meaning a lot of the
opposite
i wish the uber driver would flirt with
me oh
no
i've met um
i've
in the lifetime of me driving with ubers
which by now must have been like at
least
over
200 maybe around 200 rides
i can remember
[Music]
free maximum
free women drivers
shocking huh
[Music]
yeah every time i seen it i'm like oh my
god i've just encountered a rare pokemon
like for real i'm like oh
wow that's rare like i even say it to
the lady
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] it's a shiny pokemon
woman in the wild
oh
[Music]
i'm not on the hunt no no
just surprised when i see them
yeah
quite surprising
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
sorry i just broke some hearts in
japanese
[Music]
and an orange one thank you very much
cheers duncan maxwell the first dungeon
[Music]
flora john thank you thank you in
florida
squidward squid duncan for the red super
chat with no words
is this a death beat
thank you here's a kiss
second editor 77 dungeon
j p r s n s
have a red super chat with no words
thank you
also that pete
chad
thank you very much for coming by the
names seem new to me
[Music]
thank you for the ride of the chat it's
not often i see off collapse i hope uh
both of you have fun during your time
together i'm excited for more chances of
collapse with others in the future
also congrats on your show and talk to
me one day i two wish to my um
sorry to meet my favorite idols and meet
up with kp friends yes
that would be great i wish that for you
too
i think
you know even the shy ones who made it
to dokomi
the ones who actually managed to talk to
some other kfp
they say
you know they really enjoyed it and now
they're like even less lurkers i see
some some people came out of the shadows
are more active now
within kfb and really made some great
memories there so i wish that for all of
you
[Music]
it will happen i'll make it happen yes
i hope so it's really really nice to be
part of a community and if it like
actually
becomes real
instead of just being virtual
that's such a special special moment
yeah
i even use twitter now nice
became way more active yeah i was
talking about you
people became more passionate after you
know meeting me and meeting the others
that's nice to see come to america
yes okay
okay
i will
when i don't know but i will
eventually i
[Music]
will to uk
oh okay i will
gonna win but eventually i will
oh thank you angel thank you
[Music]
yes okay i will
eventually i will
[Laughter]
yeah we know some places i wanted to go
someday anyway no
canada
france okay i will
no i'm not gonna say that to everything
no i will actually come
[Music]
yes i will
scotland hell yeah i want to go to
scotland yes
i can speak in their longer language
after all
[Music]
canada loves kiwawa really
i don't see many canadian viewers in my
chat liar
[Music]
could be more
ireland hell yeah
i want to go to ireland but why you're
not even in ireland are you
you're not even in ireland come to italy
okay
i'm coming hello
i'm on my way right now
yes i will come to italy italia bella
italia
yes
[Music]
okay okay i will go everywhere okay i'll
do a world tour
perfect italian accent ah godzilla
godzilla
i know
are you joking though
singapore well no but to singapore but
i've heard it's good for shopping it's
expensive
and fancy
[Music]
i think the architecture is nice
he is joking no i couldn't be joking i'm
exactly talking like you lord evoke
of course that's a perfect italian
accent then mama me
mamma mia
[Music]
new zealand oh hell yeah i want to go
new zealand beautiful
[Music]
these are clearly canadian dolls i'm
giving you
[Music]
is that not a vpn
just kidding i'll believe you i guess
you're canadian eh where's the maple
syrup huh
to go with the super chat i can't eat
the super chat like this
anyway mundo gets a kiss
[Music]
thanks for the pinky my head is starting
to hurt oh damn i think i can only read
this one
these super chats
so awesome to have a new takamani off
collab glad you to finally get to hang
out in person again hope you're having
an absolute blast thank you
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah kelly came to austria i was
able to show her quite a lot so i'm
pretty proud of that um
thank you jim tracy
thanks for the red super chat glory to
takamuni yes yes yes no sleep now
thank you let's just stay up for the to
watch the collab
it was pretty late so for your time zone
i think holy [\h__\h] oh like more like
already morning time thank you
[Music]
thank you nice to see your name again
how you doing
thanks for being there
lexington alliance
alita thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
no text just hearts
i'll see love and dance
with zion
oh [\h__\h]
uh romanian deadlift sangashin senguinus
[Music]
how do i read this not in japanese right
we're getting closer to the end
the greatness of takamori is here great
to see you two getting a chance to hang
out a bit but we got to know cali how
many we but we got to know kelly how
many ribs did can i crash with her
phoenix hug
seriously have fun guys thank you
thank you very much
for you
[Music]
thank you
i don't think i crushed any ribs but
yeah i was very excited to see her again
yeah it was like
i know even though we haven't seen each
other for such a long time the moment
the moment i saw her
it suddenly felt like no time has passed
at all
in between
[Music]
it was also really nice to meet
somewhere else besides japan
i felt a little bit nervous about
whether or not she would like austria
[Music]
but yes she ended up liking her very
much
[Music]
and thank you thank you for the red
super chat
[Music]
thank you very much for the pinky it's
five am here but for this taka money off
collab i can't sleep as stencher said
i'm going to sleep after dead
oh no i can't sleep if i die i will
become dead beats so is cali waxing
today ah
yeah you see i didn't end up doing the
waxing thing because while
cali literally came first of all after
immediately after i came back from
dokomi pretty much
so i don't really have much time to
prepare things
i already i also had to you know prepare
other things
and clean my apartment and i had that
recording on the day
i think
when on the day when kelly came
yeah i had like a four hour recording in
the morning as well
and yeah but my original plan was to do
the waxing with
with um mummy
and then you know when i knew that more
people would come i was like okay i
guess i'll wax you all but then they
didn't come so
yeah i felt like it would be fun to have
to do it with
like a group of people or so
so i can wax more
um
yeah i just didn't end up doing it
because lack of time and then as well
like originally the plan was for someone
else so
yeah
yeah yeah yeah did cali either leave a
kiss and ah that was the only thing i
couldn't get her to eat because of like
lack of time with us eating in other
places
yeah
yeah that's unfortunate but maybe next
time
yeah that's
unfortunate uh but but she got to eat so
many other great good stuff i'm really
glad because you know with restaurants
it's always like a hidden mess and the
restaurant where i took her to eat
schnitzel i didn't go there before i
just went by recommendations and even if
you go to places that have high ratings
and it can still like be kind of like a
miss anyway
uh but this one was amazing like we had
really good schnitzel
so i was really really happy about that
let's move to see a mice oh the thing
that she liked the most was definitely
the schnitzel she inhaled it literally
like
i liked it too so i was eating fairly
fast myself but
she was done
eating it after like five minutes it
felt like five minutes
nah i was not that big those big
schnitzels there only served that in
that one restaurant
[Music]
still need to find lingenberry jam one
place where i think you can find it is
ikea
because they sell it
definitely
for eating it with credit chef
[Music]
it's not the most highest quality
lingonberry gem because it's more like
[Music]
jammy
and other high quality lingam mary jams
have like more of the berries actually
in it
but it's definitely an option
definitely an easy to get anywhere
option because i know lingonberry jam is
not so common
in other countries
outside of germany and austria i think
so
yeah
yeah that's where you can get it
[Music]
we can't get gucci i'm jealous you can
cook it it's fairly easy
yeah
the red room dunking [\h__\h] maple leaf
2501 dungeon
a cool make to sundankeshin
the booty called kufulu dunkicin mr
gameboy duncan
ellie smith duncan vivek tankishan
um cabbage i'm gonna say duncan but i'm
not gonna read the super chat but thanks
for the red super chat
video
officer
no duck attack thank you thanks for the
red super chat takamoni forever it's
great to see you both back together
you're both great entertainers and you
helped dispel the the presto espresso
and despair eclairs
wow
you added one onto that
oh
i like that
press of espresso is
kind of my thing i didn't think you
could come up with something similarly
nice
the pres
despair eclair i love that
thanks to dokomi and for preparing your
koi for live performances glory to kfb
viva la hot wings have to go guys thank
you thank you
yeah in hindsight i
i feel like maybe i should have given
her some advice for the meet and greets
too
not only for german speaking
because i heard that uh heard from
management
that they were
yeah since it was her first meet and
greet
there were some
[Music]
it didn't go as smoothly as my meet and
greets go
yeah
maybe some awkward silences
here and there
because
person being a great person shy
yeah
yeah yeah
i should have given her some advice how
to
handle such a situation
net
yeah i didn't i
realized you know i thought yeah but uh
maybe i should give all of whole life
members whole life english members
like
a lesson and meet a great
[Music]
you tell her to talk about the weather
you know what she probably ended up
talking about the letter
she only sat online 10 times during the
concert oh yeah yeah yeah
but she did great
during the concert
i was listening while doing my makeup
yeah yeah
[Music]
i thought you both mentioned that the
fans should plan something to talk about
yeah but then there will still be people
who don't do that and you know i know
how to deal with a person who comes in
and it's just so like even if they
prepare what to say they might be so
nervous that they like mess it up and
forget it all and all that
or yeah or they didn't prepare
and yeah i i kind of know how to control
the situation there
[Music]
i'm sure that the second meet and greet
will go much smoother
shy this seventy-seven dunkin when i
think i forgot the kiss stuck attack
[Music]
i'm really prepared because i messed up
anyway
oh you saw the future
[Music]
thank you for two red super chats
woke me up for my slumber a bit of a
story it was the tacoma eclipse that
brought me into whole life oh my first
livestream remember was a takamorika
okay before you left japan
oh
i binge watched all the piano clips and
vlogs i could be i could to be up to
date but i didn't know anything about i
was obitus so i thought you were
graduating
ah
during that cut out again i feel like
you weren't even the only one who was
thinking that
cause when i said yeah i remember back
then when i told people i'm leaving
japan
so many were like assuming that that
means i'm leaving hollow which made no
sense because there's so many other
whole life english members even at that
time
who lived outside of japan
yeah remember
there weren't some who fought that oh no
i guess kiwawa was leaving all alive oh
sad
[Music]
let's
see foreign
[Music]
that's the point you can do it
everywhere as a virtual youtuber
at some point there were people who
fought all of her and lived in japan oh
yeah i think yeah that was the thing too
people thought europe was just a nice
way of saying graduation
europe does not exist after of course it
does
i'm here aren't i we met at dokomi
i mean me and the people who entered me
[Music]
oh man
rental gymnastics are insane yeah
anyway
[Music]
your lots are too [\h__\h] cute gonna
give me an art attack love i swear
[Music]
is that you
imitating
uh
like a british scottish accent or so
even though you're canadian or are you
doing a canadian accent i don't know how
they speak
[Music]
or you got licensed to be that cute huh
right
[Music]
jackson fba sent that super chat you got
a problem with him huh
[Music]
[Laughter]
i just want to talk
[Music]
why it's perfect it's a beautiful super
chat
[Music]
we gotta warn jackson jackson doesn't
seem to be here jackson hide from
pudding
[Music]
with these super chattels
thank you very much for your support
everybody
thank you very much appreciated
i'll do my best to catch up more
sometime at some point eventually
i guess i'll have to do
a super chat rating sometime next week
somehow somehow
i don't know how but
yeah uh sorry sumima sorry canopy song
the fart supers on kelly's channel ew no
how's your front feeling i'm just a
little bit husky but it's okay
it doesn't hurt
um
are you done with the bunny i guess i am
done with the funny
no
i gotta make some food now don't
cook it's already so late man
too too late i think to order food uh
i'll see what i can do
tomorrow
uh day off i'm sorry but
i i want to stream but i have to focus
on you know
what i'm doing behind the scenes
yeah i'll record something tomorrow and
to dance practice you know what i have
to put that in my schedule
to record
something
for a video even on my on the days off
where i'm i'm i was or so i'm sick
a little bit um i was
i was not only resting i was still like
dancing as much as i could as much as my
body would allow and to be honest i
think it partially helped you know to
get
like the sickness out of my body they
say you have to sweat it out don't they
um that's what i did
[Music]
yeah oh sure let me put this in the
candle
and uh did some recordings that were
necessary and the meeting
and actually
yeah on on monday after the super chat
reading i had a meeting and then
after that meeting or during the meeting
i started feeling really bad and that's
where
that night was like the peak
but i'm glad to be
past the peak
it's good to be somewhat healthy again
[Music]
yeah
i'm good i'm like actually pretty
energetic in general you may have
noticed today
yeah doing pretty good
i'm happy to be somewhat back and i
apologize
because
until
probably shortly
a few days before my birthday
i'm still gonna be
very busy and not gonna be streaming
that much
yeah i'm sorry
really sorry but
you'll you'll
you'll get a great result
out of it in exchange
hopefully doing my best to make
um
something great
out of
the means
and
tools that i have
for the friday birthday um
i'm gonna do my best
yeah i need to apologize thank you
thank you well but it's also for myself
like i miss you guys too you know
and
i feel
like
you know even though i'm working behind
the scenes this is like the most obvious
work i can do streaming
so
not doing that feels like i'm
i don't know not doing work like i don't
know
even though i am doing work
yeah
but it was also nice to have like a few
days off
somewhat off
yeah
didn't feel so stressed out anymore
besides i mean still i didn't feel
stressed out about learning the choreo
but now i'm pretty like
um
confident that i can do it
with the amount of time that i have
should be okay so i'll go get some food
now thanks everybody for watching
[Music]
love you guys thank you very much
extreme favorite night to keep me
healthy get me healthy stream favorite
night shin kyoku if i
[Music]
we're so happy to see you again thank
you
[Music]
do
you