[Music]
he
oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] damn it oops okay
okay h
k
k YouTube is telling me that YouTube is
having
issues and that you guys might
experience
buffering how is it are you guys
experiencing
[Music]
buffering looks fine so far okay okay
well um
it better be fine because today is an
important episode it's the last one um I
was uh trying to prepare I didn't have
much time I did a little bit of
synthesizing like some materials I I
made uh some new materials and uh uh I I
rebuil my stuff which is insane quality
now
uh but I don't know I guess it could
still be better um I guess we have to do
the the whole armor building together
and uh I was like trying to get through
a few skates on my own because it's
quicker but uh I stopped here because I
this seemed kind of interesting to me I
thought you guys might want to see that
cuz it seems like Patty and her father
are getting into a fight and I thought
yeah what could be
interesting
oh I hope that we will we'll get the
materials for better weapons in the
final dungeon anyway oh oh maybe we
should synthesize them once we get into
the final dungeon then but anyway I
um I what what was I going to say yeah
uh I wanted I wanted to do the armor and
all that beforehand but I didn't really
have the time sorry you know hold time
talk and all that but I hope we can
finish the game today anyway um I've
heard that there's really not much to
go
so motion what do you
think you think we can do it we got like
what 12 hours or 12 hours 10
hours so there's a dungeon and a half
it's to me that sounds like totally
manageable also I heard that the last
dungeon is short so shorter than the
others so it all it all just really
depends on the difficulty I guess the
difficulty of the last dungeon but I
think 10 hours should be
[Music]
easy
should be fine yeah the only thing I
have the questions done for holot talk
the only thing I really need to do is
pick a a clip that I want to show on
holot talk or one or two clips which I
will do later when I take a break
between those two streams and if we have
more time left then I might take a nap
before starts from me at 1:00
[Music]
a.m.
so uh is that BM too quiet I feel like
it's too
quiet or how is it
guys
how about this I I I raised it a bit
oops uh oh yeah anyway we're running to
a Patty
now
[Music]
okay we're starting off right with a
fight between Patty and her
dad
scary
oh that no no way that that is true but
okay
uh
oh
honey there she
[Music]
goes the music is so dramatic no
she's scaring me the way she talks she's
like really scary right
now he's like starting to doubt himself
oh you can't see can't
[Music]
see
yeah I know parents generally always I
guess try to do the best for their kids
and kids often don't understand it but
parents are not always
right
[Music]
why he scared me
for
[Music]
a r are still listening
though
[Music]
ding she's already pregnant
sorry don't tell her dad he's going to
go crazy he's going to kill
[Music]
tell
yeah finally he's
[Music]
ja
the ass cracked
[Music]
out no bonking the audience you're not
supposed to do a face when you see that
ass
[Music]
crackk
okay well welcome uh we started with the
skar but welcome back to ATA 2 the final
[Music]
episode uh so let me show you just one
thing um uh uh wait how do I open my
[Music]
inventory uh uh equipment uh Risa uh
look the staff I I uh I rebuilt it the
best I I did everything possible really
the best I got was trump card L I don't
know it doesn't sound like much but hey
it's SN 600 quality now it's better than
before now what we have to do is I mean
her her armor is I guess actually not
that bad who we could actually
genely I think Rya is not doing that
bad what do you think a lot of attack
nice
okay that's better than before M you
remember how it was
before uh so for her we we want to get
Claudia some nice armor too this is only
C did I make this
one or did I find that
one
so something for her and py also has
okay armor oh but only has a level seven
weapon okay okay write it down write it
down we need um Patty's
weapon this is level 50 but only seem I
don't know what should we keep that
one that one is fine that one is maybe
fine too yeah the weap Patty's weapon
very important and
then uh another accessory for um
s and oh another weapon even though this
one is a
[Music]
quality H but uh it's way to low level
so we're going to get new weapons for S
and Patty yeah okay but should we do
that once we enter the last dungeon with
those new materials I guess maybe I
don't know I feel like we could already
do it now why is the game kind of
[Music]
like actually no maybe it's smooth I
don't know I guess it's
smooth okay level not important for in
the
trash no I think I think we
should I think we should definitely make
you weapons those are way to low level I
mean we can the quality was okay but we
can still get something so much
better okay did we finish the dungeon
last
time oh we didn't finish it yet
what where did we stop did I have to
make some
item does anyone
remember did I just stop
randomly didn't I need to make some
item after the area zone three of three
didn't I have to make an item the quest
item yeah wait a second I think I
saw recipe Why is the game kind of
like did you notice that there was a
weird like
stutter I don't
know
again did you guys see
that the frame no what what restart wait
let me let me save it mine also be
because of
the
um resolution but it's not even that
high I have it a 1,600 900 window what
the hell should I make it even smaller
also I have a the settings is high but
honestly my PC is not that
shitty I don't get it should I just
restart I think that will fix it
maybe
[Music]
let's
see also I got the best friends forever
achievement with uh Claudia and Risa
sorry for not doing that on
screen uh but it just happened it just
happened out of
nowhere I was trying to save some time
by doing some skits uh before starting
the stream but hey we got the most
important thing on stream like the one
with the
bracelets that happened on stream so
whatever okay okay okay okay we're back
in the
game hopefully it's not lagging
anymore
[Music]
okay I don't know I can't see an
improvement yet but we will
see ah it must be this
[Music]
right pretty sure cuz this
Dragon it must be this
one uh any Dragon Meat one one is
fine how about this one
it didn't drop this time looks good
okay uh it need's only one what a waste
but okay let's take one of those
[Music]
four okay that's it I don't need the
quality hi
okay ooh the the bottom looks
fancy Dragon device blood so with that
we will get to the last stage of the
dungeon
what
sh no it is
blood it is
[Music]
blood me and Fe will probably never be
friends oh I'm not sure about
[Music]
that
oh what we went straight
there wait no that's a the
different oh I remember
her ah
Anda went
there can't hear you emple speak
louder can't hear you
[Music]
li I can't hear her even now you muted
turn on your
[Music]
microphones oh my
God what the [\h__\h] okay now I can hear
you
[Music]
again I hear I know that
voice where do I know that voice
from
that voice reminds me of
kby I
think am I going crazy now did I make
something
[Music]
up last time I said
okay please Google and tell me what the
biggest roles of that uh voice actor
actress
are please tell
me annoyed
from I'm really curious
now anyway what the hell they should
have told me the whole
thing okay um we did the
so we're going uh no not not here we're
going to the Dragon Ball Valley
again okay
uh wait let me look at the map
[Music]
uh
I forgot how to look at the
map wait
what no no wait
[Music]
I help wasn't it like long pressing one
butt download
thank uh and then uh there okay
um guys is there a
shortcut I feel
like U we need to go back yeah no
shortcut okay going
back and
go I fluffy monster thingy let's
go thank you I don't need those I have a
[\h__\h] ton of
I have a [\h__\h] ton of those uh
ingredients okay how to
find
[Music]
remember could just throw my
bum I'll throw my bum let's go let's go
it is Rose bomb
time go let's see how much damage that
does even though they're weak against
the other one
oh surprise surprise they're
[Music]
dead overpowered match but I don't give
a
[\h__\h] I will continue using it I don't
see it that much is cheating like
especially for the boss
monsters it will not one hit
them
so yeah I'll probably still struggle a
little
bit but I think it's okay what do you
guys
[Music]
think it's in the game that means it's
okay to use
it but I mean generally I wouldn't use
that uh fre but
um I I I know it's Buck like if you
really really really Max it all out but
I didn't max it all out so it's still I
think
acceptable and for these little enemies
it's just nice to like end the fights
earlier cuz they are a bit annoying
sometimes I use the bump a lot I am
not uh judging you for that
throwing at them
go bed as in it does so much damage that
you can one hit bosses I
guess that that would be crazy I mean I
wouldn't want to do
that okay I have
arrived
[Music]
sty how is it what do we do the blood do
we just throw it at
[Music]
it oh it's magical it flies on its
own
wait that's scary though do we have to
fight it isn't that probably the last
bus in this dungeon was it really a good
idea to revive that I don't think
so I didn't we do this in the first
place p p how help py what the [\h__\h]
she's right behind you she's dropped to
the ground you're not helping
her
[Music]
okay if you say
so moving yeah okay where is where is
the the
[Music]
inside uh ah ah there okay I have to go
down
[Music]
so
let's go I don't want to fight right
[Music]
now I think generally to is a gentleman
yeah but why did he not react to uh
Patty on the ground just
now that is a bit
shocking am I on the right path yeah
okay
oh Patty has noodle arms too just like
me yay noodle arm
buddies too interested in the dragon
heart you should you should care about
the girls heart not about the dragon
heart he can't have children with the
dragon after
all can he build a family with the
dragon I mean Shrek taught us that
anything is possible
indeed but I wouldn't really apply Shrek
logic to ryen
logic you
know I
mean uh a donkey and a dragon head kids
so
yeah where am I
going
okay
now it's not the same universe exactly
exactly so to get your eyes off of the
Dragon it's not going to
work although the the donkey Dragon kids
are really
cute sorry are you guys getting dizzy
because of my riding
skills mean
[Music]
um
okay we're going
in into the mouth of a dragon is that
really a good
[Music]
idea
got and we don't have super Chats on God
damn it they would have sent R Snee
chats so Riser you're not getting any
sneeze chats
[Music]
unfortunately
thanks guys I'll give those to Risa
later
[Music]
do you guys feel like um this is such a
weird
question do you guys feel like I'm I'm
looking uh to the front more today than
usual like am I better position for you
guys cuz I moved my
camera cuz I was sick of always looking
to the side yeah
B
yes wonderful I noticed that oh
okay okay I'm also looking down more
rather than up I think usually I always
look a lot up to the side and now I'm
only looking forward
into more down a lot I think
but I think it's better
right gamer hands yeah let me turn on my
gamer hands let them facing fres should
look good too one
second it's the chance for the gamer
hands let's end this quickly I want to
use my gamer
H hey easy free dragons
down level it up 62 oh my God can we get
to 69 before we end the the
game okay gamer hands bring it on
um
[Music]
hands are moving of course they are I'm
always pressing
[Music]
buttons okay uh wait I heard I heard a
bunch of thingies close by okay there's
one right uh uh there noise wasn't there
one in the beginning too
probably no way that there is
[Music]
none okay nothing
okay fine with me oopsie I'll let me get
those
books pressing more buttons than in the
fighting
[Music]
game I'm a I'm a busy woman
um oh look at those huge mushroom
thingies hello a
[\h__\h] I feel like for the last dungeon
I'm going to change everyone back into
normal
clothes wait P is like
dying
they didn't
die that on them let's see they can't
survive
that okay dude what the
hell quick kill him
nice oh Pat oh I got two nice
screenshots I'm
s yay I thought it was going to weat it
with the last hit uh let's
heal
[Music]
uh
okay back to
[Music]
business
give me some high quality materials
please damn it I can't get up
[Music]
there tell yeah the shape doesn't matter
I
guess what why did I try to burn those
ancient
fting no I want to look at it okay
whatever if I have to fight you then I
don't care no no no oh
[\h__\h] I hate that the the bomb BR makes
you stop and stand so
long ouch what the
[\h__\h] what your
[Music]
problem
manager enma's name on
YouTube isn't it the ancient
ones Emma never shows up in my chat only
at Ina's chat but it was something like
the ancient
[Music]
ones
can I not go
[Music]
there ignore me being
stupid what
[Music]
I thought that was
water
[Music]
[\h__\h]
fore
hey you guys didn't
know okay now you make me feel conscious
if that was a something
I I shouldn't have
said
no I I I don't know maybe I'm I'm
wrong maybe maybe I'm wrong she go away
go away go away go you want are you sure
you want to
[Music]
fight maybe that
one it's it's it's probably
[Music]
d
R wasn't there an old game called
Ragnarok what Ragnarok
online did you guys play that wasn't
that a
game wasn't that like super
popular that's really nostalgic isn't it
oh my God it's killing me what the hell
why is my HP so
low am I so weak what the
hell my armor isn't as good as I think
[Music]
y
oh yeah we might improve everyone's
Armor after all can I when I rebuild
items I forgot uh can I uh go to like
the next recipe recipe more or was that
not possible with uh
rebuild yeah I can't right damn
it but I have to start from scratch
again
[Music]
well can't help it it is what it
is
huh there's one over
there more when reing damn
it
yeah oh another trans
chance
try to Wolf oh wait that's
for
Patty Patty but I don't know is that
better than what she has now at least
for now no wait not Patty
uh wait who wields two weapons tow oh oh
I'll give it to
him there you go we won't use you in
battle but still and who was the Ragnar
R for
lent or l
r
yeah well a fancy weapon for
you it's just decoration though won't
use it in battle sorry sorry about
[Music]
that oh [\h__\h] I didn't want to use that
one you know what this looks like
doesn't this look like
a the map look I don't know I don't want
to say anything
stupid does the map remind you of
something
[Music]
guys yeah like a pelvis yeah yeah yeah
and and yeah yeah it looks like wait
maybe that is on purfect
because we are inside of a dragon's body
after all but it might looks like a
human
pis
[Music]
what what if uterus maybe I don't
know why you why are you laughing and
did I say something
[Music]
weird what what what is it what what did
I say
[Music]
wrong Swan di the bottom left what did I
do no what about that was weird but
palis is not any anything weird right
it's
just what's what's weird about saying it
looks like a
[Music]
bone
n
[Music]
it's
Anatomy oh wait there's a there's a
battle
there am I
[Music]
healed could use a little bit a tiny
heal boss fight coming maybe
can I save while I'm in the
dungeon
uh I don't even know how to
save let's
[Music]
go
yeah so let's [\h__\h] steal it I
[Music]
guess wait this isn't the
beach weird we came here with swimsuits
but I feel like we're at the wrong
place at the wrong time too uh-uh
[Music]
uh-uh
oh
some big boy
just Dro from the from the
heaven oh you look like an angel could
you dropped from
Heaven no
[Music]
problem no problem fight
me move [\h__\h] get out of the way get out
the way [\h__\h] get out of the way
yeah do you think he will like my rose
bomb he looks like he's kind of he
doesn't give a [\h__\h] about uh fire so ice
bombs would be good too
probably I do have ice bombs with me
[\h__\h]
uh nice
defense okay I'm going to throw my rose
bomb oh what the
[\h__\h]
resist throw it
anyway
go how much
[Music]
1,800 total damage oh wait that didn't
do
[\h__\h] oh
uhoh that didn't do
much maybe maybe when he's broken oh
[\h__\h]
A that
was I stopped defending I was like [\h__\h]
I can't defend right away but don't
worry I got it last second she attacks a
lot oh my
[Music]
God what the
damage
[Music]
okay
I said I went to FR more damn it oh well
resistance and speed down okay that's
probably
good what what
what oh [\h__\h] if I'm already have in
trouble with this
boss that might not be good but we can
do it we can do it I've been in I've
been in worse uh situations don't break
me [\h__\h] he broke me
oh no oh oh he R is back
attack why couldn't I do
that let me try to fight with her a
little
bit what is he doing what's he
doing okay I'm going back to
R
[\h__\h] no I went I want to my B for God
sake but okay we still have time and
that uh already did a lot of damage on
its own okay 2,000 okay he's broken down
nice nice
nice nice let's
go oh 8,800 there we go that's what I
like to
see oh over 9,000 over
10,000 yeah wait can we do more n uh I
canot right
now I don't have any more
to I think there was a title in that
dude's name fing want the right
Phoenix it doesn't look like that's for
[Music]
sure oh oh he's doing it
again not on my
watch damn it di no no no should we add
the rose
bom why
not 13,000
22,000
[Music]
23,600 24,000 oh he's almost down okay
okay okay okay okay
nice I would like to attack him
please hello let me attack thank
you oh he's using his attack anyway I
didn't break
him okay no we're still all good and
Alive what is he doing oh
okay who is this
[Music]
I'm shook oh my God what the
hell what
happened
he's broken now
though let me do a bit more healing and
then we're
fun a wait I don't have
CC give me those give me those CC give
[Music]
[Applause]
me
swords and shields guys show me your
swords and shields I'm missing one I
I'll throw it anyway I'll throw it
anyway I don't have time I don't have
time he's almost out of his broken
thingy uhoh uhoh here he goes
defend okay he's he's almost
dead
[Music]
die eat
this that was anti climatic I thought we
were going to kill you now okay well
let's finish it off with a rose bomb and
an ice bomb and another one a wait ah
there we go I didn't do the
[Music]
wait is this how I use the for sty
Ora no wait I'm not using it I don't get
it
whatever I forgot how to use it but we
did
it I was a bit scared in the beginning
cuz he did do a lot of damage and he did
attack many times but lowering his speed
and all that o was that two level
UPS
that's oh my god
[Music]
wow that's what I like to
see nice thanks guys on first try yeah
of course I'm a warrior who do you think
I am maybe only part time Warrior but
still oh
EA so this boss is
down we probably get
one prefinal boss and another final boss
in the final dungeon I I could I would
guess or only one more final
boss fast
[Music]
quick sh
let's make this quick
guys those dragons they have a huge
wings and I keep on running into
them they're in the
way anyone think Siri looks like Tano if
she had white
hair I do not agree with that but I wish
it was true cuz Siri is hot I love her
she is so
cute Sher is gorgeous almost said
Sherry
alcohol she's hot
yeah oh is that deling rose again nice I
love those dely Roses I need
them I actually made my first
um off screen I made one of those uh
delin Rose uh fabric
things which is another um higher fabric
types maybe we can use it for our armor
more who
[Music]
knows Siri has a nice voice that is true
too yeah she's lovely I love
Siri she's like in video games she's
just my
type okay I have
arrived let's see what Fe will let's see
feel
better feel
better
[Music]
wink
okay why is R touching why is R touching
it
though
yeah R probably shouldn't touch it she's
going to turn to a monster or
die wait is is Fe going to be like a
villain
after and he's happy but he's going to
kill us now is going to kill us
Fe is the final boss that's what what
what the fee stands
for what
happen better get away from fee he's
trying to kill
us
[Music]
we should leave he here just trust me
he's he's
[Music]
sus
a okay to the
underworld oh wait we open the
gate oh [\h__\h] so we're getting the the
Fila and all that
[Music]
back
wait actually why did you bring me back
home I wasn't done collecting the shards
What the
[Music]
fu oh my
God oh my okay my cat um did stupid
thing
um wait
[Music]
wait
for
[Music]
sorry my cat is crazy she cat is
strong she did something
stupid I I got some iced tea let me open
My IC tea this baby the final pause it
was
smoothie can't open
the I usually make other people open my
bottles when someone's
around
[Music]
okay Peach
icing
[Music]
yummy yeah
I'm shut
up let's
[Music]
continue
that's why I said we shouldn't give a
[\h__\h] about
fee
fore
[Music]
fore 's design is missing uh the
yellow the yellow thingy he has the red
the blue and the green one but he's
missing the yellow
one
saying pay attention to it next
[Music]
time look
H nobody likes yellow is that why cuz
yellow
sucks sorry I'm late no problem welcome
we got a
[Music]
neutralizers
for
yeah that's the end now me awaken the
fua of
course we get
[Music]
it
it's your fault
yeah thank you
[Music]
Fe I always had this
feeling
always
I knew
it okay
[Music]
okay the
gate hello
baby chunkers has joined the chat hello
TK
b b
b
Bab
baby now I feel
stronger okay so we check out the new
dungeon I guess and then we get some
materials and we make new weapons and
new armor and then we go fight the boss
but wait but wait we didn't
finish this one what the
[Music]
hell
finish maybe is it
[Music]
actually
but I do want the
SP even if it is
optional um where am I missing
some I could go could jump down no no I
can't that's uh the way
[Music]
back four more I didn't even
see
okay I'm on my way let's finish this
dungeon that we started a long time
ago in the other
[Music]
stream also we got to change
clothes uh because I
cannot look at her butt going from side
to side like that
[Music]
anymore
it is it is nice
but I can't look at it
[Music]
anymore oh something new white moon
Frost
oh
oh I can get something else too oh but
uh we do want the light Moon fresh maybe
only
that
and that
one wait how do I
get
[Music]
huh
what
huh wait there is uh some weird
[Music]
path here I'm almost didn't see
it
mhm there's a little boss over
there I guess we fight that one
[Music]
too leave me
alone let's see if you'll like
that gas for talk tomorrow uh uh sweety
why did that barely do any damage
[\h__\h] you didn't give a [\h__\h] about that
b yeah maybe I should use the C drive I
forgot how to use
it
uh
anyway oh what the hell that kind of
hurt me
dude wait is that the boss monster that
was on the map
I can't can't use
those and the reservation is already up
too
[Music]
um it's already prepared I got all the
questions ready I'm
excited because Su sire is so
interesting she's another one of those
members who has done like so many
things just so much
experience so many things to talk about
you made so much music up until now so
we're going to talk a lot about that as
well I have a lot of questions about
that and about like other things like
her old
Avatar her old model
and yeah about the band I'm going to ask
her about the band as
well I'm going to ask her about h house
as
well
oh wait that really was that boss
[Music]
monster this whole do yeah it might be
another one of the longer ones on the
longer
side cuz I do have a lot of
questions
[Music]
sh
okay now I
use
this I pressed X so that it would use
the the the four Aurora thingy I'm
confused you have to press X
twice but animati I'm honestly not sure
like what to ask like I know she has a
sister but well she probably
[Music]
she's wow lots of
damage okay it's actually good that we
fight some of these enemies
because maybe we get to level
69 the vine liquid
[Music]
ooh
oh there it is I was looking for that
[\h__\h] this freaking
[Music]
sharks mama please help us find girls I
can't help you that I'm already
girlfriend isn't that good
enough I'm already watching movies with
you and stuff you're telling me I'm not
I'm not
enough do I not satisfy you you want
more than that why why # R #
yolk one
[Music]
more it it's not
here where did I miss one
[Music]
I am so sick and tired of
you okay that wasn't at
[Music]
me should be on my M if it's new I know
I know let's check it
again level 67 wow getting so many level
UPS we're really going to reach it
soon let's
see where could it be where did I miss
[Music]
one M can I just jump down
here oops see I keep on using
that
[Music]
yeah
I I didn't collect the blue one at the
top okay I'll check it
out stop attacking
[Music]
Patty she's
pregnant
[Music]
okay uh let's go to the top
then what what is it guys why are you so
shook
again
[Music]
yeah she's in an early stage but you
still have to respect
that and be kind to
her so was there really something up
here oh wait huh I didn't even see that
what the hell that was just like in the
[Music]
wall
okay
wait how do I open the thing there we go
we are
done okay I'm missing something here it
is a recipe for medicine strange symbols
there we
go yay
complete and then this
one I'm not done with that one oh we're
missing a lot here Eternal land power of
Stillness Eternal land power of
[Music]
Stillness uh Immortal and eternal no
emotions that's me and CI but there are
emotions lots of emotions love and
passion change for Demon's
[Music]
Eternal cage what cage for Demon's
Eternal
seal Frozen Moon Source of
[Music]
Life do the last dungeon have this F the
system as well do I have to collect
stupid shards again in the last dungeon
which is live white moon of uh
immortality yes it has damn
it okay but at least it's smaller right
it's shorter the parture of the witch
out that
[Music]
will
uh the part of the witch outside there
we go
[Music]
complete
Y
and then we can go to this
one
um lost place of
[Music]
origin seeking magic origin of M Alchemy
magic origin of
[Music]
alchemy oh that's
it that wasn't that clear which you left
magic not
mastered which left magic magic not
[Music]
mastered
are you guys checking with me together
or are you just waiting for me to finish
it Mage manipulating the
[Music]
Stars me thank you just
chilling I'm here for the ride thank
you sorry bu I'm working no thank you
for being here even though you're
working offering two
[Music]
heads offering two
heads one more B St
Dragon this one
no this one y one
[Music]
left okay this one is
left okay let's do it Manel reason of
prosperity there we go that wasck go
with M two dragon
[Music]
head playing the game while I'm watching
you play it oh you're playing with me
are behind me or uh uh F on me even
Stones Mana flowing through the
hole uh
there we
go behind oh well then you can learn
from what I do power of the Frozen Moon
fragment to seal demons but I'm glad you
watch it anyway even though it's
probably spoilering you I appreciate
[Music]
that they're all really really similar
losing fragment in
and into the vessel power of the Frozen
we did
it we finished the dungeon now there's
only one
[Music]
more
this yay that's the all complete
nice now we can go home or go to the
next dungeon I guess but let's go home
once I
guess and think about uh the SP what to
invest it
into skill Tre o a rave you onlyi
hurricane that's oh core drives
oh Eternal Loop Angelic Embrace gravity
press so
many but this is this partially not only
for me but also for the other
members any
chance uh let's do rebuild level Plus 8
maybe I don't
know and
uh lunar lamp I don't know what is that
good Genesis
hammer what's that only Hur
in give me
something I don't know what is good
should I get the core
drives get the Gathering
rank my cat is purring nice cats and
love cat fluffy
love po talk will be as
always it will be like
50/50 as usual right translate what the
Japanese Talan
is wait a
second should I get all those core
drives I don't really care about them
Holo
targeting Hol
life
what targeting staff
quality not much use for C drives
honestly okay you don't need them okay
nice
nice uh a wave then let's do the goddess
cup whatever that
[Music]
is GIC Embrace we don't need that that's
the cor D wait I got almost
everything
I think
I I can get the windchills
recipe I
guess okay Chad please read the rules I
love cie but this is my stream thank
you wait I think I activated everything
except those oh no wait there's more
here I I didn't see that evolution
[Music]
think okay let's get more of that R
level plus
[Music]
eight which connects to that quantity
plus one I want that I ran out of
[\h__\h] should we get Evolution like what
does that do is that
good never mind I'm getting
it oh you guys don't even shut up about
it even I said uh shut up
okay okay
[Music]
cool uh so we did
that this about the thing that I just
AC oh my God catch him jumped on my
chair give me
[Music]
shock Evolution link using a reinforced
multiple cauldron what a name will
unlock the evolution link
[Music]
option Evolution link lets you combine
accessories and items with other objects
activating special new e EV
effects
e effects are powerful effects that can
do multiple things try different
combinations to create more powerful
items there are even some items that can
only be created through secret
combinations
ooh but I need gems again for that I
really have a problem right now with
gems cuz I've been um copying a lot of
it multiplica a lot of items and uh I
keep on running out of
gems anyway
[Music]
uh you guys are asking for it
somehow my
god do do I need to time out
[Music]
everyone I don't want to time out every
everyone uh so
we just I guess going to go to the new
dungeon first and see what it looks like
how do I get there
wait where is the
gate anyway we need to hry to check the
gate in the m m with fraternity where
the [\h__\h] was
that ah here that
one let's
[Music]
go
oh
rest in peace
neck want a new neck can I buy a new
neck
somewhere
Last I See the
end it's probably that way
and that
[Music]
way a doctor you think a doctor can give
me a new neck that would be
dope I I need a new shoulder too while
we're at
it the left
one the right one is also not perfect
but better than the left
one oh yeah it's open was that not open
[Music]
before by robot
neck I become
robot I'm so sorry I don't know why the
robot thing is always so noisy but are
you awake
now are you awake
now robot
Daddy
that's what you get for not reading the
rules I break your [\h__\h]
ears I think if we just barricaded with
a few chairs and all that should be fine
don't you
[Music]
think
or I synthesize a door I mean I've
synthesized freaking Bridges
before I can synthesize a [\h__\h] door a
magical door that stops the
fua
f
with then because free has the man in
there bye sacrifice sacrifice
me for the greater good
I'm sure he he would be happy to do
it is that a reference to the first
game I like
[Music]
that yeah let's go we're going in
right o oh I love that
purple Castle Church Vibe damn you
know so magical but what what are those
statues they're looking
angry are they going to blunk
me yeah I like the aesthetic
though so materials please what is
that nothing
special
but there's something there wait a wait
a
second what is that
n is that for my for
[Music]
my how old is that fluid good
question I don't want to drink
it my bom is
[Music]
bad portal
ISE ah purple is the MMA affecting the
the world but that sounds like it makes
sense you sound really smart saying that
rise out what the
[\h__\h] don't don't just go through there
alone she really can't hold herself
back
Dam
[Music]
r i me with B BFFs I'm not sure about
that even though she's similar to me
like don't people usually try to like or
end up being friends
with
like sorry I keep on pressing that
uh friends with someone who's not really
like you but more
like like a different type and opposite
I
[Music]
guess I don't know do I have a friend
that's super similar to me
who would you say in Hallen is most
similar to me amen am in am in guda
maybe maybe are they
s a little
bit all in whole life Japan
[Music]
generally
notal okay give me some good materials
oh Treasure
Chest what's
inside demon
Ender
sounds
[Music]
goodia oi
Marine I
actually I
mean I'm not sure if I would agree with
M by I I I get where you guys coming
from because of the
less no no no no
[Music]
no don't Pon okay you want to fight P
let's fight I need your actually I'm I
don't have much of your jelly right now
anyway
I see some similarities maybe
yeah
who what you're still alive what the
[Music]
hell guys just
chilling
[Music]
with the power of Satan and
friendship they're still alive what the
hell black Ponies are tougher than I
thought cannot underestimate those
P my ice BBS are bad I know I mean the
rose BMB is just better but
still level up almost
69 almost
70 nice thank you for the K
balls
[Music]
H not not so
many materials oh [\h__\h] I ran into a
pony almost n not Dan guys you got to be
patient
stupid no I will not let you
[Music]
wait she
didn't she didn't do the thing did did I
activate
it did I forget to
did she do the aora
thing is it because he
[Music]
died I
didn't I didn't I felt like I
did let's try again
but he died for me I can never use
it congrats on reaching the freaky level
not yet not
yet got to be
[Music]
patient okay anyway this room sucks I am
leaving uh where's the
[Music]
here
um
first residential area was I here oh
yeah that's where
I is it where I
came let's go
here new
material don't stop the please get me
every
time
[Music]
okay go come on give it to
me show me what you got there we go
first B
round that that's the one yeah o oh
that's a big unnecessary
[Music]
explosion okay now give me that
material ah resentful
[Music]
scream we get more of those resentful
screams
why are you talking like that [\h__\h]
pleas I think this one gives me the
level up though oh wait did I did I
already get the level up St did I miss
it did I miss it did I just get to level
up I did I missed it what the [\h__\h] I was
I was
distracted I'm level
oh oh my god dad how are you
alive Immortal
[Music]
Queen
thank
it was too far
away
stupid actually you know what would be
cool like a bean bag uh
chair looking like a
puny that would be so easy just buy a
normal bean bag and then like put the
face on it which it's just two eyes and
a mouth that'll be actually really easy
just got to get the right color of the
bean back
chair I like bean bag
chairs did I level up
[Music]
again I'm getting Level ups every time I
I have a fight
[Music]
no
no okay
level 70 damn the EXP in here are
crazy oh he's not attacking
me that was a short time of being nice
yeah it felt nice being
nice it's over now oh
no
Immortal Knight
ridiculous I forgot to
acent I wish it would do it normally
when you fill it up why does it not do
that oh he still got a lot of damage
though oh he's mad mad we've triggered
[Music]
him
what just happened oh they killed him
oh
wow well at least it's quiet now and I
can already
got py don't even think about
[Music]
it next up I guess we got to teleport
back because there's a dead end here
[Music]
proceed oh wait I wanted to change the
clothes remind me next time I go to the
atere to put on some
clothes please remind
[Music]
me
oh
because I don't want to be the last
final battle to be in
swimsuits don't question
it oh even
older it's like the home of some kind of
magic Demon
Lord
culture things make you stronger
[Music]
do you wear underwear while trying on
swimsuits Ki what a
question why would you why do you want
to
know
I
mean I I I hope that everyone
does I
mostly I think up until recently I
ordered most of my swimsuits online
rather than buying them at a
store
how do you know if it fits I look at the
measurements and then just hope that
it's
[Music]
correct most of them are stretchy
anyway
yeah but with buying clothes online I've
had many bad
experiences and I've bought a lot oh
my
okay let's
go H what kind of experience is well
like even ordering from the same
brand I've had like
50% like of those gloves be good quality
and the other 50% be like really low
quality like some Fabrics are really
thick and nice and somewhat high quality
and the others are just like what the
[\h__\h] did you think when when creating
that kind of
disappointing um but yeah
that's I ordered a lot through um t
bow I haven't done it in in a while now
but I used I used to order a lot from T
do you guys know to
Bell because it's so cheap there there's
so many cute cloves cuz I really can't
find like the clothes that I like much
um like in actual
stor how about is like the Chinese
Amazon so yeah there's a lot of cute
brands on there that have really cute
clothes that you would never find in
stores which is why I would um use that
and also because it's
cheaper but
the problem is that the
quality is often really
shitty and the other problem
is
uh that shipping takes a long long long
long time to other
countries uh
and and uh then also like depending on
which country you're sending it to
having issues with the Customs I had so
many issues with customs in Australia
but R I was living in Japan this one
year actually had um quite luck because
sending something from um China to
Japan the Customs doesn't give a [\h__\h] I
don't even think it had to go through
any Customs I don't know it was never
stopped it was in Japan so fast I never
had to pay extra meanwhile in Australia
I often have to pay Customs that are
more expensive than the actual objects
and shipping all
together it's
ridiculous and even if they Mark the the
the the package as like gift or or take
up the tags or you know doing all these
kind of
things and especially recently I think
recently or or they doing it soon the
the there's like um new tax
uh regulations in my country or in my uh
in the in Europe coming up which will
make it even
worse so I stopped ordering from tal
[Music]
unfortunately oh
[\h__\h]
Australia I I did order quite a lot of
things while I was still in Japan so for
now I'm fine I have enough clothes but
and I guess I'll just recently I I also
kind of changed
[Music]
my my style I guess like I've been
wearing very different [\h__\h] I forgot to
activate it I've been wearing different
CS than like a few years
ago so personally I like just uh you
know more simple kind of clothes from
Zara
and and similar
stores Zara has really cute clothes
sometimes they're simple but really
elegant and
cute but I wish I wish I could just um
that there was this this one favorite
brand that I had on T
Bal and I I wish I didn't have to order
online I wish I wish I could just go
straight to the store look at the
clothes directly and and feel them and
choose them so I I want to visit that
that Brand's store one day and just buy
everything at at the spot rather than
online sorry I'm getting lost I have to
go
here I wonder if they even have a real
store there or if they only do online
shopping
what what the
[\h__\h] yeah that looks like
f yeah but but no the to the why I
ordered from townell was not only
because I had no money but also because
I just liked the clothes well now I
don't know it's just annoying to wait
months for the clothes to arrive
especially with the Customs like even if
everything else is okay and I pay the
Customs it still takes like sometimes
it's just even if it's already in my
city they stop it at the Customs for
another 1 month often sometimes even
longer sometimes for no reason
for no reason it's so annoying like the
shipping to here already takes well
depending on what service we use but
maybe let's say one month and then it's
there at the Customs for another month
so by then you know summer is probably
over and then I already need clothes for
the next
season got to plan ahead I guess yeah
it's really annoying the customs in my
country are so [\h__\h] slow I've had so
many issues with them ah
do you guys have that issue too when you
order did anyone hear order from China
to America before are they custom [\h__\h]
as well for you
[Music]
guys I order Christmas presents in July
thank you no yes yes no have no issue
took like two months to get something
small American Customs don't exist wait
there's no one stop the packages coming
in oh my
God wait what the
[\h__\h] resist let
second you
okay I want I want to don't
kill what the
hell
[Music]
okay damn it let me use my [\h__\h]
skills you
bastard wait I want him to break
first he why can I not use
[Music]
them I don't want to use
item oh there uh
two okay uh oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
ah well R biscuit is better than the
asro
milk she doesn't have
enough
[Music]
wait come on what the [\h__\h] is this
battle okay go go
go what's going
on okay it will be better
[Music]
okay healing everyone
once and now we're back and everything's
[Music]
cool
oh I broke one of them or two of
[Music]
them
okay now we're
talking you'll need to craft better
swimsuits you couldn't armor what your
normal armor wouldn't
do I think she
needs
proper armor not a
swimsuit okay they're dead I don't know
why I had so much trouble
[Music]
there okay they're
dead
they are these are the toughest enemies
in the game
[Music]
really
fore
spee
[Music]
fore yeah
probably all right time to level up
let's get level
[Music]
100 C looks good with you know his face
being
I like his
hat swimsuit
[Music]
outfit
just like how a Phoenix's instinct is to
look for a
death I can't help it's my
instinct
what
the what the hell was that
[Music]
scene
she's not that dble not that dble
clenching her face like
that
chill okay I guess we are going through
[Music]
there wait no no that's where you just
ahit do we have to go
here that's where it came from
right
oh the music ah no that's where I came
from and then they teleported me over
there okay very confusing game why do
you do
that they're probably super strong wait
there's a treasure chest over
there wait a second wait wait wait
heal I probably need some heals don't
I
actually actually no I'm
fine
another weapon I guess oh that's for um
I want to no I don't want to fight I
don't I wait I want to see what the best
[\h__\h] okay let's
fight you don't look like a rat kind of
sus you say You're a Rat
but I think that's a lie
oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] one
down they're
fast
Casper Casper looks cuter than
that they're weak anyway I'll just throw
everything at you have
[Music]
fun
what that was exp what the hell was I so
underleveled
[Music]
or I missed
it okay I do want to fight one of those
other boys uh
did I didn't fight you let's fight one
of those they look so
[Music]
pretty what oh we have to go home once
uh wait
wait it's
beautiful
okay let's see how much damage it does
even though he's
resisting oh broken yeah broken at The
Right
Time
Explosion
o ooh some cute fishies wait what should
we get right there uh ah some of
that
yeah now we're talking okay I have to go
home once I'll be right
back I'll be right
[Music]
back
okay straight
back ah thank you I would have forgotten
[Music]
again okay I want
to oh should we give her this outfit nah
it's cute
but my favorite is
[Music]
still wait orange
since have we always had this option it
looks so new to
me wait we have that had that I like
that
one wa oh now I like
it
orange
[Music]
that okay for
you let's give her like the summer
style oh don't care about
him but this bothers me when he's like
in the
[Music]
skits let's give him
that she needs more outfits that's
that's the normal
one that's give her this
one let's keep him in
that oh I love her original outfit so
much which color fire rat or dandelion
or
Nightfall we had Nightfall for a while
let's do either fire rat or dandelion
fire red
dilion red okay I like it
too
cute come
on okay
saving from 61 up to 70 something
damn okay let's go
back no time to
waste wait H it was
uh oh no it was there
right
lonely
residence
oh oh I don't have a shortcut over there
yet
H do I have those special ingredients
already that I want to use for the
armor not
sure like it seemed like most of the
things were just the
same
I want to see you end this game before
sleep well then just give me a few more
hours actually it doesn't feel like it
will be so much longer cuz this is the
last dungeon I can't imagine it taking
so much longer my gathering tools are
too
long oh I don't want to miss out on all
of them I don't I don't need
them I did get one on the world
Crystal
H should I go make some better Gathering
items okay
okay I mean we still got
[Music]
time
okay should I I can just rebuild them
though
right cuz they don't have any like morph
anyway
[Music]
fishing rod Grassle for example I have
the
[Music]
off a Gold version of the items e
really okay okay for example ah Master
bget Divine fishing rod ah okay well
let's start live uh oh I can't even do
that with cutter
ja a start live
the welcome new thank you for joining
the membership oh no I'm running out of
alchemy strs wait I did I make them
myself should I whatever I'm just going
to make new
ones
but do I think I need more anyway in the
next yeah yeah I need more ahuh here we
go again we're in the endless
synthesizing loop
again I need Alchemy uh
[Music]
fibers
I don't have many of
[Music]
these make polishing powder
okay thank you for telling
[Music]
me
what's that by the way ooh mushroom
forny
Embrace oh
[Music]
one oh another member thank you welcome
to the
membership actually
wait de whole talk yeah thank you
looking forward to having
[Music]
you nice
mushroom
that's already pretty good oh I don't
need
that this is already
[Music]
perfect uh
blue something with threee perhaps there
we go there's
one okay okay that's
perfect and not expensive skill charge
yeah why not critical
[Music]
yeah oh that was
good yeah three units only I want
more wait can I get more
[Music]
please okay what was the other
thing what was the other thing I forgot
I forgot polishing powder
right oh there we
[Music]
go what am I making I'm just making
stuff for other
[Music]
stuff
green one green one
green that's per that three w i really
get the hang out of it finally I'm so
glad I understand UNC me now I don't I
don't I don't know why in previous
artill games I was just when I was
playing it on my own I don't know why I
was never able to properly understand
what the hell I was
doing I look I made some nice new
neutralizers by the
way
[Music]
um I'm proud of you for coming along
long way with it thank
you normally I I feel like when I play
something alone oh wait what did I do
that when I play something alone like
without an audience I feel like I can
focus on the game more but even then
with like acular games playing them
alone I still never
understood um how they work I mean I was
able to play them fine I had some
troubles I was weak I fights were were
tough but but I was still able to play
them the baby's
here hello
[Music]
baby I got one
more oh wait I forgot the the upper
part I no we filled it up
okay
[Music]
chat taught you how to play yeah I don't
deny
that defense charge Speed Charge skill
charge noce
okay five minutes okay that's
good okay I'm going to duplicate them
anyway how many do you think we need
[Music]
okay she doesn't need chat I do need
chat motion let's be
real and I know I'm running out of gems
I'm always running out of gems it's
okay okay so let's make I guess let's go
with this one now what color's axe let's
make uh the golden one it seems we're
making the golden
one where Where is the
recipe here
okay punishing
[Music]
powder thank you thank you guys
what what happen with the baby
again that's such a waste CU it only
fills
up
well for a
waste of
potential we have to use that also use
any of
those
M oh one of those oh this one has four
perfect okay let's
go we're going for the golden
a capable chopping proper chopping let's
go for proper
chopping
[Music]
um
the system yeah it is I would agree it
is kind of complicated there's a lot of
things that you have to pay attention to
when you're
[Music]
synthesizing
I mean this is probably already good
enough isn't
it why would I need more
quality this is already good enough
right
more that's an insane
one I don't even need any of these
effects these are all useless for this
kind of hello Kat
hello
[Music]
baby
what we got one look at that that's such
good quality baby
[Music]
baby
baby baby so
soft baby what are you what are you
looking
at something is interesting under my
table
[Music]
a
You're
buring So Soft with a
baby did you hear it for a
second I think you
did honey
where is the J Japanese Bros
[Music]
hello for Split Second you were blessed
nice that's hair
everywhere now don't touch your face
it's too
late it is too
late wait no let me undo
that
[Music]
wait don't I don't want
that that
one and see I made this sorcery
Rose my cat just keeps on walking around
under my table and under my chair what
are you looking for oh hello
junkers they both came from my
[Music]
attention
B
[Music]
baby oh [\h__\h]
oopsy oh I picked up
junkers
oh
baby junk how you
doing how you doing
junkies what no no no stop pressing
buttons
[Music]
junkies
baby
oh so many hairs
yeah oh my God what is it I they really
want my attention right
[Music]
now
okay what are we looking for threee
green there we
go I can't help it my cats are just the
cutest who
this where we're going we're going uh
here
okay do I need gold for that one
too we
need there we go I haven't sneezed with
a we re in a long
[Music]
time
thank
you I almost accidentally um had the
robot effect on when I
sneezed I turned on my FX and the robot
was still on and while I was about to
sneeze I turned the robot voice off
quickly I don't think we want to hear a
robot sneeze do we maybe next time it
would have been very very very loud and
cursed robot
sneeze anything
[Music]
is oh I only have
one I hope I don't need
[Music]
more
oh wait no I can't do okay well Dad has
to be good enough I mean it's at least
better than what we had
before okay we got the master book
Catcher
too get me some of those cute bug
Pokmons then let's make the bump
[Music]
run h no wait no no no no no no no
no I know I can check what the effects
do but is there really any effect that
would help uh uh an an item that
collects
uh I forgot I forgot the
name what's the type of
item what's type of
item
Gathering
it one of them affects the Gathering
rank
oh oh
well oh
well got to go
here
oh wait do I need bombs for the next
stage
[Music]
though oh wait what did I do why why why
why
green
and the will we are we are not getting
underw why
not why
not oh wait I can still
continue um making better bombs ice
bombs think the rose bump won't Carry Me
Anymore my hand to clip
yesterday it was
[Music]
clipped oh I can still rebuild it I can
still improve it the the the the do I
need the the the bum rod for the
crystals
I can still make it
[Music]
better H not much Choice
here I don't know which one to
[Music]
use
uh well anyway that's that I can still
add some more
here
[Music]
ging okay I'm fine with that is there
really
anything anything of gathering
doesn't look like
it
okay oh it's blue
now
Aon okay let me change those out for now
equip uh
items grabing tools up the golden one
and this one and this one and now we
need the
sickle sickle sickle sickle oh wait for
the staff one I can't make a gathering
staff right she just
uses her own staff doesn't
she and and the staff Gathering Rank and
all
[Music]
that why are you both
what wait let me look at my
cats what what's the
[Music]
matter yeah I don't know they really
we're craving attention I
[Music]
guess they really want that attention oh
I feel
bad what taboo drop what the [\h__\h] where
do I get the T
drop is that something I
can
synthesize tuo drop tuo
drop I make it t
tra ah there it is I no wait that's
[Music]
no taboo jop worth it did I miss
it there it is poison I can make it
thank God
it
[Music]
really and I really make it
no oh I can't I need more black Muk
where the hell do I get black Muk from
again
wait
let's check it
again black
Muk which one gives me the most I wonder
ah is that from the water under the
water
ah
maybe Capital outskirts had the biggest
water
no
oh he wants
something what is it
[Music]
L I really like this uh color VAR
variation
[Music]
too where is the water wasn't it right
over
there oh
yeah can I dive in that no wait this one
is not made for diving I got the wrong
one I
think
Romy I don't know I don't know where she
[Music]
is cute BB
wait there a
[Music]
oh the
B angry B why
angry is it because called him massive
beak well you shouldn't name him massive
beak oh they're so low
level that's an insult to birds if you
call them massive
beak a
[Music]
I oh this must be a a side thing from
from like the beginning of the game cuz
they were so
weak
oh
baby it's going to fight us
again save the
[Music]
day thanks l
byebye those po poor BS I feel sorry for
them oh
uh is this
going to make me spawn in the cafe after
afterwards I'm not afraid of
you don't
worry okay oh thank God we spawned here
uh where on the big water
what is that
Romy who are
[Music]
you wait I can't I can't talk to her
like
that
no
[Music]
okay so maybe up there cuz there's a
[\h__\h]
oh one hit
[Music]
k
no okay isn't it like over there please
tell me it's there let me
dive
please that looks that looks somewhat
deep no wait that's not the spot
either do I have to go further like is
it not not actually
here
[Music]
maybe
maybe go to the second dungeon and exit
back to the
lake second dungeon which one was the
second
dungeon I don't remember which one it
was sunken city of
[Music]
stars
oh that could be it oh yeah hey that
kind of reminds me of like back in the
day like um
when I was like uh there's some friends
at the lake we have some really
beautiful lakes in Australia we really
do okay give me some of that black mud
please oh we got some new stuff too
richy
KP oh even more stuff here demon crab
and black Muk seaf soil okay nice I need
more of
[Music]
that
more give me
more oh something new
here what could it be jellyfish mushroom
jellyfish are so pretty I remember I
once watched some kind of anime that was
about a jellyfish girl or so that was
that was
cute maybe you guys know about
it oh lots of mug
m
m that's exactly what I needan yeah
[Music]
yeah not but I I know that one but I
think I never properly watched
it
we already got enough
but let's see if we find some more
stuff wow she's really never out of
breath
huh professional
diver
I've never been diving in my whole life
by the way have you guys ever been
diving I want to go to the fake
Australia and go
[Music]
diving in Florida yes o snorkling I
haven't even ever done
snorkling
I don't dive I only
sink I was certified rescue di what that
sounds so
[Music]
cool that's
cool the way you pronounce snow killing
is
why is that how you how it's supposed to
be
pronounced no
[Music]
killing skydiving that's awesome too oh
my God you've been on I'm so
[Music]
jealous that is how to pronounced
o snow killing no what the hell
[Music]
well once traveling is okay I want to go
somewhere where I can go
diving some nice place like I don't
[Music]
know
have a nice
vacation I don't want to follow you I
was trying to get to my freaking aier
and now you bring me somewhere else
again why every
[Music]
time GRE seems like a good spot
too they have beautiful islands
the IGN hav expressed her desire to dive
in the water like other birds
of oh hey tow we got a special tow
[Music]
scene
cute he looks good in this
illustration you shouldn't ask about the
looks uh Patty don't don't don't ask
about
them is that is that tell sub story
complete the end of his
character sorry I never really paid
attention to your
[Music]
tell
at least we saw the end some justice for
[Music]
t
what a
[Music]
nerd I'm the nerd
what done with that Arc so I'm done with
to and
Claudia Cloud yeah Claudia Claudia is
I but the others I wonder if we can
finish the other ones what about Patty
maybe if I go here maybe we can finish
Patty's
Arc so many things to do before we go
into the final
[Music]
dungeon no no no no scratchy chair no no
no no no
no no why you do
that
now she's like stuck
[Music]
stupid did you hear her
me she was hanging on my
chair
and I was
[Music]
junkers isn't she
cute
junkers has a way softer meow than
smoothie smoothie is like really
obnoxious whenever she
[Music]
meows yes it was
fake
[Music]
so the girl on the
right
yes mov is the door
[Music]
opener and junas is the lazy
one also junas is uh is really scared of
everything when I turn on the um hair
dryer chunkers will run away meanwhile
smoovie doesn't really
care even worse with
the vacuum
cleaner as soon as I turn on the vacuum
cleaner chunkers will run into my room
and hide under my
bed even if I vacuum clean like two
rooms away from
[Music]
her
no it's embarrassing
has
happy
[Music]
end
cute that's so
cute because you're
love how I know
and
[Music]
now both of you it's it's free
actually
[Music]
for okay that I got an achievement for
that too we cleared Patty's story arc
too wow good
timing good timing at uh finishing all
these
arcs by I've had that uh his sign and
actually Aris out the whole time but
every time I go there nothing happens
nothing
happens why why does it not get
activated did he want some item from
me Pro of chest synthesize the Tre uhhuh
okay I always wondering what that was
for you know what let me make
it maybe then his Arc gets finished as
[Music]
well
this thing to keeps me motivated a thank
[Music]
you I glad to hear
that okay I'm
done
[Music]
have fun with that
Clifford ear clip of the crapp version I
hey that's not completely
true he looks damn cool
[Music]
though
are you so
[Music]
[Laughter]
happy
lifford on his nipple
[Music]
bags oh I love this
music
[Music]
Wild
West oh
yeah I love that I would like to listen
to that just in my free time that's a
really
[Music]
good
shut up I said OST which is always te
shut up why are you laughing
huh shut
[Music]
up okay
no achievement oh that was not the
finish uh Last
Arc what I thought I I got no
achievement for that or did I I don't
think I did anyway I came back here
to to make the
sickle wait why is it so laggy what the
hell should I restart the game it's kind
of laggy it's
crazy what
Embraces her western side oh is it
better
out no oh God okay restarting one
[Music]
second you didn't save I did
save I
I did
save what no I I did is there all save
in the game
[Laughter]
there's
this game is not a safe feature okay
when did you save after the after
[Music]
after dia to all of shut up and now
okay hey my controller is not reacting
anymore
what okay quake
[Music]
uh okay I think that's saved right after
the cut scene
[Laughter]
oh my God okay so it's not lagging
anymore good okay uh never do that never
give me that shock ever
again so I brought a [\h__\h] have this
disgusting black muck with me now please
tell
me that that is
[Music]
enough
um oh sort by
quality and something with three red
there we
go and this one flow I need more of
that
but for now for this recipe it's
[Music]
enough oh wait I didn't need to do
that David thank
you thank you for everything you do
[Music]
David honestly it's probably fine like
this but okay let's add a few more
things why not we might use it for
something else after
all add some fancy things some fancy
tonic
water
[Music]
um
give me something with free red please
okay I'll take the this
one thank God for a
Saia I would be [\h__\h]
otherwise I would have cried because I
don't even have time to waste that I
can't replay everything I just
did m
[Music]
wow this is actually turning out to be a
really good
item we all would have
cried okay do you guys think I can
finish it in the next two
hours I think I
can actually I don't
really
yeah no
idea I think
so
probably okay if I keep at it okay no
more cats
[Music]
distraction if you're finishing in the
next two hours then I have like 5 hours
before
um uh Hol talk which means I could take
a nap which I would be very grateful
for so finally I should be able to make
this
tickle is's the
recipe here
[Music]
okay
oh
that would be great for me too do you
guys need a nap too before H
talk
yeah I don't know why I made my schedule
like this I before before I started to
stream today for a moment I was thinking
what if I just stream R tomorrow on
Sunday but I'm reading super chat
tomorrow so that's that
but low key regrets everything I
did is free a.m. for me oh
no let's all grab a nap before her talk
yeah like you know how like in
kindergarten when everyone takes a nap
together oh those are the good times
napping as part of school like I mean
kindergarten wasn't really school but oh
that was
nice I remember that getting up on those
bunk beds
[Music]
M the good
times okay I I asked this before but
does this transfer over if I fill it up
does it transfer over to the the the
silen
CLE you get bed down there uh yeah I
think we had beds and some people yeah
some people also slept on the mats
yeah nope it doesn't okay then [\h__\h]
[Applause]
it
no hi
Chun chunka is walking behind my
monitors right now and sits down and
looks outside the
[Music]
window
they really like just watching outside
they'll will be be really happy I think
if we move cuz I got some nice
Windows uh at where I'm uh moving
to I don't want to I don't really want
to use that I don't care about the trade
slots to be
honest I want to keep the the food drop
for something
else
electricity yeah they don't matter that
much
anyway I'm done with this almost I'll
just great effect too we want the second
effect at
least thank you for the membership
welcome egg egg egg
egg expert cutting should be I can't get
it anyway
I'm
[Music]
done okay now we have everything finally
now we can go back to the
dungeon we need at least
expert
what I made all these new Gathering
items and they're not good
enough
is that what you're telling
[Music]
me I didn't get the effect one
notes
expert did I even have the right things
what
I got this
one I can't get that one can
[Music]
I didn't it say not enough
before
[Music]
o
ex oh
because huh but why can't I put it in
[Music]
now I just make a normal scker oh come
on hey why can I not use it need more
gems
okay let's get some gems
going what do we sacrifice oh we have a
lot of
[Music]
those
so get rid of those dragon wings
you also don't need the bomb Rod anymore
but I I'll keep it for
[Music]
now I think I need to take a few days
off to cuddle my
C they they miss
me they're really used to being like
cuddled to death after El Phoenix cans
so it's no problem for
[Music]
them well tomorrow was like kind of a
break day because H talk for me is still
like kind of
today but I'm reading super chats
so that's that but that's okay it's okay
that's just reading some super chatos
having some conversations with you guys
and thanking everyone it's very very
very important for
[Music]
me one thing that I hope that I never
like I never want to change one thing
that I aim for to
always
um stay is being grateful I always want
to show you guys my gratitude for your
support no matter how many super chats
come in no matter how little time I have
I always want to take the time to
properly say thank
you I don't want to take it as a given
you know
[Music]
okay uh uh wait uh
rebuild
[Music]
pop your sickle H why do I need
more it don't I think it only says
[Music]
one do I
more need more of the Ole a come
on
why how many it's at least she four
[Music]
what the IGN Alan thanks her flock for
being by her
side
what at least four the flock is in turn
cause a massive uo by flying in an
orange heart
shape four four so I I duplicate
three wait
[Music]
um why do I need f
welcome
back I wa you
want wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait oh [\h__\h] wrong
one or element value okay okay okay no
problem I can do that
ah that one okay one
and and
two and
three and four x calling do we do we
need the effect two as well I can fill
it up
[Music]
you
okay now that is a beautiful sickle if
I've ever seen one
okay I love this game so glad I CLI cat
the end well thank
you items it's already equipped okay
well then I think we are finally ready
do or do do you guys do I need to
upgrade these ones
too they're fun
right oops what the
[\h__\h] I just pressed the button to open
the at RIS
manual
[Music]
H
oh wait wait wait wait okay
you good to go then let's
[Music]
go there's cat hair in my
face den of the
wise what do you mean it's dangerous we
got to
go
okay
L
[Music]
sideen should just sa in case not
remembering her last mistake unlike a
good gamer what I feel like I read that
sentence wrong
[Music]
you have hairless cats you have those uh
Sphinx
[Music]
cats
oh he's been lifting those
[Music]
weights I don't really see much effect
though he literally in Japanese said
training in the sense of like you know
lifting oh he got that Ragnarok
sword oh you got no chance against
Landon it's okay it's not your
phone what you have to watch SP cat CU
they don't have
hair ironic
somehow thank you for the membership
[Music]
welcome oh you got a lap cat that's nice
I want a lap
cat give them B baths all the
time do they not like clean
themselves like what's there to clean
[Music]
anyone very gentle baby bath shampoo oh
wait that's so cute they must feel like
the baby's
B Maybe Baby free will be a lap cat I'm
hoping for that
yeah I mean my current cats are also
like super
cuddly but they're not
[Music]
laats
I think I need a idle meeting
[Music]
break
okay H did I save
no not no Fe shut
up
safe oh I I just pressed because
it's h I thought I save back then but I
guess I pressed no so stupid
[Music]
okay
fore
[Music]
for
foreign
[Music]
hello
hello somewhere
here
okay also let me open this snack I got
some Kinder Bueno I don't know if you
guys know that but super yummy popular
choc chocolate
snack it's again Kinder Kinder chocolate
is just the absolute
bestest time for a
snack
M mhm
[Music]
everyone loves
PAB
M we already are snack
[Music]
oo
M don't question
it
m
[Music]
for do I get new things
now
or just more in higher
quality why they look really fancy they
got gold and all
that oh you want to bite oh
[\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh
[\h__\h] FY
F I don't know I don't know why I got
that now I don't know where that came
[Music]
from
you guys don't even know what that was
that was spergy I think it was was it
London
Bridge level
up no lent was not part of the battle
but okay
[Music]
oh his sword really looks dope though
wobble
[Music]
wobble yeah
oh you your home is a dangerous place
huh well they're fancy cuz they have
[Music]
gold
these bebers are all over my recommended
don't fight
it accept
it but
same yeah well Clifford is now the only
one wearing the
[Music]
swimsuit he's like he's just here in
like vacation mood he doesn't even want
to
[Music]
fight
recommendations are crazy in general
Honestly YouTube
says don't worry Risa we didn't have the
rose bomb in Risa one in Risa 2 we have
the rose bomb
will all be
[Music]
good where should we go right is a
continuation but I'm going to go left
[Music]
first let's get those Treasure
Chest no let me
no no no no
[Music]
no I don't want
toight Shadow Vanguard
ooh oh wait s what the [\h__\h] why did you
get some oh [\h__\h] okay okay we have
to F quick and
fast I think we need those levels I
guess so and we need
[Music]
um we need better
armor it seems after all there's nothing
we can do about
that but the one we have currently isn't
even that bad see we got more on the
welding crystals
nice I guess yeah yeah that's the reason
to fight a good reason to fight more of
these
enemies oh
no let me hit
[Music]
first oh wait I should have healed sir
[\h__\h] can I let me just throw it already
already
now
oh are you telling me that kills
everyone and I don't even have to do a
single hand
uhuh y yep yep yep that's what I like to
see easy
clap ooh more underworld
crystals
e
[Music]
these are all the same materials where
are those fancy materials you guys
talked
[Music]
about
let's make it quick ain't nobody got
time for
this I'm a busy very busy part down
Warrior the reason why I'm not full down
Warrior is because I have a
business W I love to see that
damage I didn't finish the one no need
rank free are you kidding
me are you kidding
me I need rank three for the
Axe
really if it's fine if you have enough
materials to make you have enough
material to make better items okay
cool at least the SLE is good let's get
some good sickle
[Music]
stuff hey
oh can't get inside okay what did we
just get out of the treasure chest I
didn't pay
attention when are you making new music
I love you songs well um I'm currently
working on some
covers look forward to that uh and
original who knows who knows when there
will be something new I I am not
sure even if I was I wouldn't tell you
yet
[Music]
a sword for Patty
yep
[Music]
[\h__\h] I ran into him okay that means more
Crystal Frost hedge interesting
[Applause]
name any transform rock metal music no
that's not my type of music
sorry the only metal music that I like
is baby
metal that's something I can get
behind if anything it would sound like
that yeah let's get some of these
materials and then go home once and make
new weapons
Maybe
should we fight
him give me those exp
dummy a baby m is dope b
[Music]
m i mean interesting concept
uh but
like I I don't the thing is I don't
really like scre Mo kind of kind of
stuff that to me is
nothing but I do like
[Music]
uh
you like that
dude he's from fake
Australia who's baby M you don't know
baby M look it up I don't think you'll
regret
[Music]
it
kill him
Qui go go go go
go sharpen sizzors what kind of name is
that also he looks like one of those
Ultra
Pokmon
I'm might to help again don't wor is
here to save the day have you guys seen
i' I tweeted about them on Twitter have
you guys seen those Ki Minecraft
videos those are so [\h__\h] hilarious
and there is so much work put into those
videos like getting all of those phrases
honestly I I I I feel like we should
collabor
don't let yourself be held back by
having to go through millions and
millions archives if you want me to like
let's collab let's make one of those
videos for my
channel uh and I just you write a whole
the cup Z you write a whole script and I
I I record it all so then you have
freedom you can do whatever the [\h__\h] you
want let's do a collab let's make a
whole movie
I love that Series so much even that one
video where I was just waiting and doing
nothing even that I don't know I even
that was hilarious I don't know why so
cute but honestly I really had that
thought um
oh I really had that thought uh last
night I was like damn we should just
collaborate
and do a whole
script and I'll just read it all off
whatever whatever it is
so he can do
everything unlimited
possibilities Siri is like
dying
y he going to
die [\h__\h] why did I use that
skill
anyway
go underated chicken no Phoenix gosh
that video was so funny it was so
[\h__\h] funny I was like how the [\h__\h] do
you get all of those phrases from me you
must go for like millions and millions
and millions of
archives how do you find what you're
looking for it's fascinating to
me let's uh no never mind
[Music]
mind that's half the fun yeah I mean one
one charm of these videos is of course
as well that you know it's like
oh it's a clip phrases to give a made
into a video that is of course one of
the fascinating things about this in uh
in the first place but still I feel
like it would be fun to have a video
where it's just me actually voicing
everything so he wouldn't be held back
by
limits
stupid shut [\h__\h] die already oh I'm
broken no no
oh he's like one hit go okay cck the
other one oh he still has so
much what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] dry biscuit fora why am I healing
myself twice this is not even a boss
battle I was doing pretty
badad
[Music]
ni fire ooh
butterflies okay he's broken let's quick
quick quick Frozen
[Music]
items
my first voice actress gig of clubs that
accepts I guess
so but you know I still have that goal
of uh me wanting to be
like
uh like voicing some anime or something
English English dump that would be so
cool that's why one of the few goals
that I was not able to fulfill yet
[Music]
it's h first of all how about we safe I
don't know why not
I feel like it's like not super
impossible but it's just a right people
have to like find out about
me and then I think we're we're good
once the people who make those decisions
find out about me then I think we're
good
anyway we need P let's make patties
first which is
uh Index right this
one and then we go for piercing blade
and then even further I hope I have
enough materials this might be another
one of those moments where we have to go
back again make some new items and
continue and continue and continue but
first of all we just rush for the
recipes okay
hello
cat wants me pet but it's like a bit too
far away I I would have to get up from
my
chair okay and God I don't have much of
that
oops
H that was
smoothie she just drops like the moment
I touch her she falls over on her
belly to get
pets I know exactly when
she's a she just flops it's so cute like
I cannot resist her she's the cutest
thing
[Music]
ever no yeah don't have
time wait I
Needum
uh should I copy that one or should I
here we here we go this is the the the
starting let's make some new studium I
guess why
not but from the others see I have a
free in we don't really need much inot
free free oh y I have to make some
copies of the these
two okay but other than that let me make
this one
quick uh
[Music]
it's going to take a while guys sit back
and relax and enjoy the beautiful
background music and my
voice I don't know if it's really that
enjoyable but that's what you
get that's what you get when you let
your heart win oh
oh that's what you get when you let your
heart I've drowned on all my
S that's what you get you your heart wi
w w that's param
[Music]
yeah uh uh what what what what oh wait
no we're just making
[Music]
stud
MC soon I'll make
a uh an emot that fits
that we really
need I can make good use of that and you
guys
too album has started to call for
[Music]
dmca but the IGN album is smart and
every time the dmca gets close she um I
can't speak in in the smart language
that you use David but like she she
Dodges it smart
[Music]
B
a c em ah good idea how would that look
like
[Music]
though are are we okay with that I guess
we
are 100
[Music]
% okay whatever I'm going with that I
don't care about the
others okay now we're
talking now let me make some copies
here oh we got three of those
me so
many there we
go and
let's copy
[Music]
a few more of
those is that enough I
wonder and the golden
one which cost a [\h__\h]
t Okay a red circle of C's outline drawn
inside of it
how would that say that we're not a
cult are you going to make gold weapons
I don't know maybe if we get
there I don't
know the IGN album uses her 12 level
intellect to avoid all Hunts by a DMC
with skill but more often than not luck
she has been killed
twice what no but not by dmca Dam it you
got it wrong you got your facts wrong
I've not I've been killed a few times
yet but have not never been killed by D
MCI they can never get me
down my Avid level is too
[Music]
high um let's add
string DMC is afraid of hot wings I've
heard of rumor yes well I've heard of
rumor have you seen the that Netflix
show
uh what was it called Umbrella Academy
that was pretty good that was pretty
good the the thing I just said reminded
me of
that okay recipe
more whatever
[Music]
we need to
go
here
oh you want that gold huh but I know
wait this one would work too nice
M no I'm using the Ingot for this
one oh wait no I need more
oh I guess I'll add another one or
should I use the
gold
no there we go I think this is the one
she currently has no is is already
better than what she has right now now
we're going for the loan
arer which is uh
here no this is the lowan arger but
we're going for the N
Circle buy more ingots off of Dennis
yeah I guess so yeah we probably have a
lot of money that we're never going to
use otherwise but I just feel like you
know it's always better if I sympathize
myself but you're right yeah because the
gem reduction o i I just don't have
enough gems so coping it cost so much
especially for the gold ingot did you
unlock the ingots on Dennis yet actually
I don't
know I ignored the shops I hold a lot of
money yep yep uh what am I doing sorry I
got distracted by the
comments um what should we throw in
let's just throw in that
one
and
trats oh you want the golden one that's
[Music]
okay let SK it the
stadium wait I don't even no I have to
go up okay that doesn't transfer right
the attack would would would it
transfer we had this
before I will be dare to see it
we'll see about that
David that one
does but
whatever ooh amboli only one one one
thingy each one KN that kind of sucks
but okay and now we go for the
golden ooh Dad I'm making nice nice
weapon for you no I'm still not
done hell
[Music]
yeah oh look at the Quality it's almost
like over over
900 wow F we
[Music]
s
uhhuh
uh we're doing pretty damn
well oh I Ed a lot of gold for that but
worth it question
mark But if I use one more
gold that's my No I can still copy it
okay and one more let's F that one up to
two two two two two two two
two not
where get I
Max look at me filling up maximum
quality okay I'm
done I'm done holy
[\h__\h] wait why is that still level seven
I'm so
confused but it is better than what she
has currently right why is it only level
seven why is the weapon only level
seven I mean I guess it doesn't
matter I thought that like each uh
recipe morph like each weapon is a
higher
level because of the
rebuild
oh okay anyway uh moderately increases
incre
15% ah stats power or skill charge
cuz this one increases all stats and
this one increases skill
power I feel like stats power might be
pretty
good okay holy [\h__\h] that's better than
RIS
weapon yeah don't use her skills that is
true breaking the limit I got an
achievement I broke the limit
yeah
wow Patty look at look at that look what
I made for
you holy [\h__\h]
Patty now you better not die on me
during during the boss
fight oh oh I actually have two because
one of them I guess I just got uh in a
treasure
chest W wo look at those stats going
up
m M that's what I like to see that is
wonderful
okay
hey okay um the thing is now I used up
so many
medals that uh for uh sir's weapon I
probably need to make some
more I can copy some of them but not all
of them let me try to make some ingots
quickly
[Music]
quick quick
clck armor I know but like I don't know
I don't know I I'll make one more weapon
and then we'll make
armor this might not finish in an hour
after
all cuz I'll be spending a lot of time
crafting
[Music]
ahee
h
let me check Discord one
second
[Music]
oh
oh one
second
[Music]
I'm just doing some holot talk
stuff okay that is
[Music]
done okay
okay effect effect
effect today's
h a lot of you guys are looking forward
to it aren't
you
[Music]
say say best girl by the way I already
decided who's going to be the guest for
the 10th episode let me just say 10th
episode will be a special
episode I'm not going to spoil anything
yet I'm just going to say it's
special
[Music]
baby
hello baby's trying to keep me from uh
finishing the game
today no baby baby's on my lap now but
she will not safe along cuz she hates
being on my
lap it's a chunkers don't go chunkers
no there she goes okay this is
done oh wait
H this is fine
whatever or high
quality let's throw in something
blue
yeah I don't know why they don't like it
honestly I can never understand cannot
comprehend um
whatever oh [\h__\h] I wanted the stats
charge [\h__\h] okay we got we got free of
those we need some more
gold let's try to make them on my own
save
some
gems what else we have that's gold for
anyway uh
green
it what is that honeyball is that a
[Music]
rare hope it's
not never I only only have one of
[Music]
those
it's not that real
okay no my
lap my
lap you make it sound like my lap is
constantly sweating lft don't say it
like
that I'm currently not sweating
okay you make me sound disgusting to the
other people
do I really want to throw that in there
Golden Crown I can get a
crown I need gold anywhere
else ah yeah for that one you know what
let me take that
back let me take it back and go
here sounds hot not going to
lie you
just
kidding that's not
[Music]
hot what a waste for one more nod
wasting my golden
KN I need more oh that's it okay well at
least I didn't have
to copy
[Music]
it ah what did I
do greatly increases old
stats
attack charge skill
charge what I do want uh the stat stats
[Music]
power okay three
more
[Music]
ah what about duplication
huh uh can I maybe duplicate ah
gems okay let me let me quickly get some
[Music]
gems or or make them my own okay I'll
make it on my
own let's get that uh wait there is no I
was going to say Alchemy level higher
but there is no Alchemy level it's not
even worth it is it I don't
know
it's taking a lot of time but oh
well still have uh five six hours to H
talk
so it's all good and I have more than
enough of this
material so I might as well just do it
on my
[Music]
own
SP at least right now my brain is still
focused I can still comprehend
synthesizing at some point and whenever
I play atar after a few hours I cannot
comprehend it anymore so it's good that
we're getting it done
now better do it now than
later and that dungeon is small anyway
as I been told so we might we might not
even be that far away from the final
boss hopefully
probably probably need to sympathize
another Quest item but that sounds easy
enough you're very close to the final
B what is there some kind of like after
after Story or
anything it feels weird to finish it so
soon oh I don't even have to do the I
don't have to do the memories
I don't really need anything from the
skill tree anymore
so actually you know what I might not do
them that's that's good we we we're
going to save a lot of time I don't need
those SP
[Music]
anyway
sounds good to
me oh there we go I finished it it's
only be with this will go up right skill
charge yep there we go it's a now Speed
Charge creamy
yeah
no okay well that should be enough right
no
but wait oh my God I need more of those
for armor don't
I or do I only need fabrics for the
[Music]
armor anyway for now we're making we're
making the weapon for
S this
one how do you think you would react if
you rewatch yourself doing rise one
Alchemy I probably wouldn't react
much let me turn on the light in my room
one
second but it would be interesting to
see
indeed okay much
better it was getting dark again you
know how people are like against um
Daylight Saving Time a lot of people in
my country are sick of it but I think it
makes sense and I really don't mind
it so many people are like why don't we
get rid of day s they're so annoying
yeah but it makes
sense because otherwise it's so dark so
early yeah I think it makes sense it's
the worst why are you guys also so
against it first world problems kind of
yeah I kind of have to agree with
that I mean it's just 1
hour
changing the only time that kind of
bothered me was when um whenever the
time would change uh when I had work or
school on the next day and then I
already wouldn't get enough sleep like
only 6 hours and then still 1 hour for
me then it's only 5 hours yeah that that
used to be annoying
but I feel like it's worth worth the
sacrifice or should I use those crystals
no not
[Music]
yet wait let's L this
one you get yeah the other time you gain
an hour and then I was always happy yay
I can sleep 1 hour longer yay yay
[Music]
for I don't know some people say that
they're they really have problems when
that time changes but it's just one oh I
don't know I don't get
it I don't get
[Music]
it wait why am I going there I want to
no no no no no wait wait wait what am I
doing which ones are the one that I
really
need these three and I need to go left
oh sorry I got uh distracted focus focus
focus focus
focus
no uh do I have enough
Stadium I'm going to be mad if I
don't we are going that
[Music]
way
yeah I know I need to just get closer to
the recipe I
know let's
go no not
done do I look like I'm done to
[Music]
you running out of stardium again soon
okay wait wait which way are we going
we're going
uh wait did I not even need that
one to go that
way oh wait now I know what you mean
ah I see oh
well oh well oh well it's
okay
defense I want a lot of
that
oh yeah let me use that one damn you got
six hell yeah since this one does
transfer as far as I know and
think and we're on the golden side yeah
the golden AG no I'm not
done throw that in we're almost Max
quality oh we're getting there we're
getting to Max quality again what is
that ooh that's the last one I probably
won't get there and I'm probably going
to be fine without
[Music]
it throw in a dragon
egg and one of those no wait that's my
last
one it was so good I don't want to
I'm going to sacrifice the gold gold
gold gold gold
[Music]
one or I stop it here then copy the the
studium salum stardium and then rebuild
it just throw in what I have now and
what I can give now it's already maximum
quality
anyway I do want that
though but I I could get that with a
normal Ingot too I don't even need the
gold you know what I'm going to stop it
here and then rebuild
quickly uh attack
charge that's
charge
greatly War God's power greatly in
increase
greatly greatly increase whole stats
increase his whole stats no no no don't
scratch J no
no no don't
baby
baby it's your fault why you meowing at
me you're stupid
baby oh my God baby she's so stupid baby
why do you do
that she did it again
she gets stuck in my chair she has her
paw up like really really high like as
high as possible and then I want to help
her like by raising her paw like 1 mm so
that she can like get her uh claw out of
it babbe then she goes like like I think
it hurts but like girl you got to get
out of the
chair anyway I think I'm going with that
one like double stats increase
[Music]
what do you think
motion yeah you want to help the cat but
she's like no
mama War God's power is better than
attack Plus+
oh greatly increases greatly increases I
mean it says the same but I'm going to
trust
you it sounds
[Music]
dope e
uncle that's not bad actually we
couldn't even keep it like that we don't
even have to do a
realu
damn I guess I'll just keep it like
that
um where
oh they started
fighting they're
wrestling get some ingots okay you you
keep on mentioning that so I guess I'll
do
that wow look again look again at that
stat
increase okay
St five bucks on
[Music]
there's it never really seems like
there's an actual winner I don't
know no one's ever winning it's wait
it's 1:00 a.m. I can't go
there or is he also open in the
night at least for fora I feel like he
would open up fora in the
night hello
[Music]
e
whose birthday is
[Music]
it my R had four HP left after killing
your last boss oh my god did you have
better equipment than me probably yeah
right
[Music]
did you have the happy birthday Ricardo
did you have the rose
[Music]
bomb four bombs but you had better ones
didn't
you I had a 900 what you had that c Rose
bomb and you still had
issues can't be worse than your last
boss fight in R of one do you think
so I definitely
have more
skills better
equipment and better items than I did in
Rise of one
ever
[Music]
true I was also on the level now I'm I
think I'm at at an okay
[Music]
level what's the boss
level
[Music]
LEL what oh
hey I do have
[Music]
that if that's what you're looking
for I have enough of that will that make
him sell me some ingots and stuff does
he already do that I
[Music]
wonder
hio uh one second
guys
[Music]
asked for it so I'm gonna
uh accept and respect
it no singing
[Music]
mhm okay
wait what what just
happened so can you sell me some stuff
oh he does have only England and
[Music]
Stadium oh wait I need some of
those you only came get me free what the
hell but he restocks daily probably
right give me those two
give me those two thank you I actually
really do need those thank
you I'm going to get some of
those I'm going to get everything you
know what I'm going to get all of them
because those are shitty materials
anyway I'm going to use my own for the
higher level
[Music]
materials
but for the lower
ones where I just want to fill out the
freaking
knots I'm going to use uh the stuff that
he has okay okay let's go to my
place BL what is
[Music]
it music is so triumphant
o always busy busy bus is Lady br
I'll take your entire stocks
yeah maybe I need more actually or is
that the last
[Music]
one those abs don't look so sad now they
look like they painted on with make
[Music]
a lot of people have said thank you I
think
call
[Music]
spee
fore
[Music]
David you cracked me up
David pain his cheek scar every morning
oh my God we were roasting and exposing
lent I feel so sorry
[Music]
now
very
[Music]
true you're
welcome
bye-bye I can really
L is it because I'm relying on you and
appreciating your support in RIS
and her FL crawling out L for just
trying to have some drip and play the
game but no that's not allowed David you
out of character what the [\h__\h] get back
into
character I'm calling you out for not
being in
[Music]
character what am I doing ah should we
make Qui quickly try to make um some
armor but help me
please I need help I don't know which
one to make like there's different ones
and I don't know which one is
good should
[Music]
I like we have we currently have the
radiant plate and a pretty decent
one should we try to go for the Fortress
armor but I don't have Master Le lever
how do I make
that fair cloak is good and
leather
quickly making equals 2 hours yes
unfortunately but then then we'll one
one hit kill the boss did I just read
Keys kindy yeah the first time I saw
that it really threw me off
to I guess you are German I had the same
reaction start from the base yeah but
from Rich Bas like they're they go into
different things no partially like h
can patty just sell sell the final boss
maybe I went for the club Amor ah okay
so H club or so either I got I start
from Noble tunic or for the leather
protector St from
CL ah no wait I guess it's a Travelers
code
oh
okay and then just use the same for
everyone just oh yeah I guess we can
copy that one we don't have to make free
of those we did that
before Oh wait I don't need that
sorry wait where are we going we're
going
there yeah okay let's see let's see how
far we get i'll dup it all
[Music]
okay
will I need more fluffy
[Music]
W ah the problem with these clothes is
that they only fill up one no no no no n
no oh
well we R out of fluffy W will I
probably yeah uh let's hope we don't
need it later on
I need
more I'm curious too to see how well
I'll do with the
boss to the right
[Music]
side it seems I'm trying to defend his
character the flock has turned hostile
towards me I better reintegrate using
their Sub sub to Long
language I love David that's like my new
Casper yay you make Fair cloak from the
point oh my God oh my
God Is it okay what I'm doing now is it
okay do I not have to throw it all
over I just do what I'm doing
now uh the recipe is up
[Music]
there that's the only thing I can
say some Japanese comment asked me if I
can speak
Japanese the
French
[Music]
no okay this time we're going to I don't
even know what this item ends up
being oh we're going here again after
all okay radiant plate okay do I have
enough creamy
Nia
ah in the end I really need those Metals
again oh wait I don't have to start
there though though right I can just go
here that's what I've
[Music]
learned wait actually
no
[Music]
use
um this
one and this
[Music]
one we're going to run out of it
I I need some
copies ah yeah uh also yeah what is that
wait we're going to run out of what is
that material that they
need what is
that I need that first of
all pony
letter
what Mas letter ah do I get that from
[Music]
pon
no elro
coat tearing off pun skin wait don't say
it like that I never thought of it that
way is this
where got it no way that turns
into a different friend one ah py
leather P Leather and
then the other
one skny the P oh my God what is what is
even inside of a p isn't that just like
py
jelly squishy py jelly and we're ripping
off the skin of that and oh my God
ew that sounds
terrifying
what I only have one where did I even
get that
[Music]
one
uh I don't I don't don't I I do need
more slime bus can the big Pon
bus okay guys you got to help me where
is the big p
boss wait let me
[Music]
see what it doesn't tell
me are coming from digging on
Mount digging where have the mount where
Capital Oscar
Highway really
so here we go
again have to get we have to uh gather
some materials in order to make uh an
item to make another
item this is what Atelier is all about
[\h__\h] why did I do
that there's a digging spot here really
anywhere or some specific spot it's the
big boss marked on the m
oh yeah but I thought digging digging
works too wait I found some other
stuff
[Music]
nice go to the Big
Bus ah that
[Music]
one
uh okay on my
[Music]
way mhm mhm
was that a py over there the the big BS
[Music]
there well he really digs up
anything yeah that
one a it's not even that big I imagine
it to be
[Music]
bigger big
pony give me your
balls
yeah only one where's the other
[Music]
one
I'm
sorry I'm
sorry I'm say it I'm say it I take it
back
yo I came for the second
[Music]
ball don't hide oh he's so
shy he's so
[Music]
shy also can I skin you as well I need
some
leather that would be really
dope a he won't let me skin
him
is is that I have three now is that
enough is there any like around here to
dig or do I only get them as a drop from
from
[Music]
him see I guess this is one of the one
interesting part about the game is it
makes you go back
to all
areas old areas from the beginning
you can take them in high L one's hole
and yeah it makes it go back and and
just look for stuff even lowlevel
areas okay is that enough what was I
doing who am I
wait uh do I have gems right now
no I want to get more of uh these these
two
sword by obtain gem okay
[Music]
W making Pony lever and then mastera
lever and then we go back to making the
armor and hopefully that is all the
items that we're
[Music]
lacking
does anyone know if there's any other
special item I will need later on while
I'm while I'm uh re uh while while I am
morphing recipe
[Music]
morphing don't think
so okay I hope so hope that's hope
that's
true
[Music]
did I hear meow hello oh baby I have a I
have a parer lying on the ground so my
baby of course chooses to sit on
it but I don't have a problem with it I
love it she's so cute she always like
sits on any like even on the on the
couch like there's like pieces of paper
on the couch she chooses to sit exactly
on those pieces of
paper it's so
cute it's so cute cuz the couch is C
huge and so
comfy oh baby oh now she changed to sit
on my
bed she has a favorite spot on my
bed I love
her
[Music]
cats love rectangles I guess
so but she's just weird she just wants
to sit on
[Music]
something that she's not supposed to sit
on cute why are cats so cute explain to
me maybe David can explain cuz he
watches animals
right David can you explain why cats are
so cute I have a
question why are cats so
cute I'm waiting for the
[Music]
answer I hope I won't miss
it guys tell me if I missed it at some
point
[Music]
give me a sec okay
one he's getting serious he's like
pulling up his sleeves and he's like
okay okay she gave me a Quest I have a
mission and now he's like aggressively
typing he's like this is my passion this
is what I was born to
[Music]
do good that we have a professional here
who can really tell us the real
reason a professional
statement why cats are so
cute curious very curious to hear what
he has to say maybe we should get David
into Hol
talk but first he would have to join H
life David ateno in h life how does that
[Music]
sound
yes please second bur girl after
theago okay this no more no more or more
always
[Music]
more
okay
40,000 and I will run out of it
immediately
May because the gold one takes a lot
let's see let's do this
one
two nice and
then oh I can I can even copy the ones
that I bought off of
[Music]
David
two okay I I need some more gems later
when I'm going to copy the actual armor
so
I will stop here maybe well hey the stum
no I have the stum okay okay
okay okay did I say David I meant I
meant
Dennis
okay
okay oh there you go the f c stringers
within the Mind cute characteristics
that make sentient wants to take care of
them by
releasing h a chemical IAL reactions in
humans and in the IGN Al
yay thank you
David that is I want to I want to cut I
want to print it out and then put it in
a in a
frame thank
you thank you for teaching
me I appreciate
[Music]
it okay
yes we're making Pon
[Music]
Le please please tell me that this is
all I need please I'm getting
sick of this soon
[Music]
soon wonderful
wait let me go back cuz it only needs
three and the other one needs four so
I'm going to do a smart one use the free
one on that and then
yeah wait that's all I need right but
I'll make it I'll make it
[Music]
good I no wait I need to go there I
thought I needed py lever that's not
true I need to go here okay
okay GRE oh wait that's not that's green
[Music]
oh dread leather oh God do I need that
later
on please tell me
[Music]
no you guys said no I don't need anym
stuff it better be
[Music]
true later on you already at the final
boss I mean I mean for the armor that
I'm synthesizing now trying to
synthesize now if later on I need that
letter as well hopefully
not four
fire well I can use up my good items now
[Music]
right
okay that's it that's all I'm putting in
there uh
[Music]
4% uh skill
charge actually not destructive but at
the last one I won't get
anyway oh God for for like 2 hours now
um outside of my room my roommate has
been cooking and it smells so [\h__\h]
good it's smelling inside my room
too smells so [\h__\h] good it's killing
[Music]
me but I think she actually cooked for
me
too I just can't eat right now
[Music]
both
p
h
whatever I think she cooked
the uh
[Music]
schnitzel okay uh
okay what was I doing I lost my focus
fuckus I was just talking about me still
being
focused now I'm already not focused
anymore I was making
[Music]
um I am now
making we
making this
one no not
[Music]
my ger is better to be real quiet
now don't don't expose me
[Music]
fore it's not like I cooked it
so
wait why did I fill that up I was sorry
I was confused don't fill it
up wait that's already enough
okay no okay and now we go up
[Music]
here is this really where I need to go
yeah uh two I got you fam
morph noise no not done now we're going
down here okie
dokie after we're done with that we can
go back into the dungeon and kill that
[\h__\h] boss I haven't seen him yet
but oh wait wait I don't even need that
oh start so
here
sorry I keep
forgetting
and
one
[Music]
more I can go to the P Lev El
too it's okay now I don't have puny l
so and I'm too lazy to get that I have a
lot of metals
so that's what I'm going
[Music]
forh okay um next this one okay but I
start
here okay now they're starting with the
metals I need need a fire one actually I
can use one of those
hell
yeah oh I'm running out of it is it
still going to be
[Music]
enough
four okie
dokie
no where are we going oh I might need
more wait where are we going which one
are we doing wait is Fortress armor the
one that I end up with yeah I can't go
to this one anyway I don't have uh
whatever that takes I don't have
it oh this is what I'm ending up with
okay so we can worst case rebuild it but
you know what I will have to copy that
Master
Level so let me fill up what I can over
here and then I'll rebuild it maybe
we'll
see we'll see what we end up with we
might not even need to rebuild I don't
know
I need a blue that keepes me free is
that too much to
ask it seems
so I know it wasn't a fairy cloak gr I
thought like people gave me choices if
go this way we'll go that way and this
is the way I'm going and I hope it's
[Music]
okay sorcery
Rose okay
effect three death +
death okay
wonderful enhance done
oohoo
[Music]
oh a green
boy
[Music]
that seems like a waste but
okay a it's okay David doesn't have to
be a member
no one has to be a member if you can't
afford it that's totally fine or if you
don't want it that's also totally fine
even if you can't afford it you might
just not want it that's
[Music]
okay okay I'll I'll I'll stop it here
but it's already
oh
oh oh
[Music]
oh
ah ah
which oh huh ah which is the last skill
I should go
for lended awakening stats power greatly
increases oh but which one do I U maybe
not this one this only says increases
death and
speed it's not that much I
guess
o
lent pretty oh my
wow wow I don't even need to rebuild
that
w we did it guys high five
he I don't know how I just high-fived
your white hole in the controller but I
did it maybe that was my foot you just
got high five by my
[Music]
foot C of course of course do I have
enough gems probably
not I need
a one takes
177,000 you know what the good thing is
we're probably not going to make much
more stuff with this cauldron so we can
pretty much throw up
all the [\h__\h]
things obtain gem okay what do we throw
out uh let's throw out some of these we
don't need them do we it seems like I
didn't even use
them but you know one thing that I'm
still lacking is a good accessories for
Ev Patty or
uh
um I forgot her name
well but I think we'll you'll be fine
without
[Music]
I'll throw in some more of those aori
AI she's lacking The Goods the good uh
accessories I throw in some more of
those okay that's
22,000 that should be
[Music]
enough that's
nothing w did you hear that catching
catching
sound okay now no one can [\h__\h] hurt
me okay
oh girls I got some new clothes they
might not look super cute but they are
[\h__\h] strong so you better wear
it I'm not taking a note for an answer
wait why is risea no never mind I was
looking at the wrong thing okay holy
[\h__\h] wow look at those stats going up
o the HP even is going up a
[Music]
lot wo wo big Improvement forever
everyone now we are [\h__\h]
ready uh cloudia I maybe have something
good for her
too yeah I can give her one of those in
case she gets switched
in which could
happen okay I'll try I'll give it a
try the only thing that we could still
improve is
accessories and uh the ice bombs and
stuff
should I try to at least make another
awesome ice bomb I don't know do I even
have the materials for
it um I
do I could also make a Clyde ice
bumb okay cide ice bumb is better than
the normal ice bumb
right we can try that
[Music]
one
I didn't save again oh well uh I'll save
in a moment
um
[Music]
greenen I can use the good materials
now I still feel like I don't want to
waste some of them but it's like the end
of the
game go for it
Ki glass flower uh no that one that one
down there
[Music]
okay
go for hot wings thank you thank you for
the
[Music]
support free
green there we
go uh
blow
mm that's the right one right yeah cide
iceball I'm
what's the weakness of the last boss is
it ice I would be happy if it's ice
otherwise there's probably not a meaning
of me making this
bum is it ice ice ice
[Music]
paper weakness is getting hit weakness
is Phoenix shut
up
oh to make this one ideal I guess I need
some ice bombs huh I
understand uh I'll first make it
uh I
[Music]
cannot copy that glass flow can
I can I that's just a item that I picked
up somewhere
right was that something I
can yeah I can I look up the ones I have
here I can copy that one okay then wait
let me just fill out the pon balls and
then rebuild but for real this time I
rebuild for real I'm not going to be
satisfied with this this bump
yet not
[Music]
yet okay for now
uh I don't
know
uh I don't know critical
plus what do you have down there Merc
strike these ooh
40% what's single
blast
[Music]
uh it cost 4 CC well it will maybe get
better after rebuilding
it make sure to keep the CC low well how
how
what it isn't maxed on the levels what
do you
mean thank you for the Jeff the Phoenix
ton
what thank you for the membership what
the [\h__\h] I love that try to load the CC
now before rebuild it
how
[Music]
I don't have
the why why why do I need to do it now
where is that anyway ah this one cc
minus
one but then I lose the glass flower I
can't do I can't do that afterwards
anyway you
[Music]
know
I don't
know I don't know which one to
use help
me this one power frow that wait power
FR you can but the item level is going
to be very
high
oh oh the top T BS of a note for that
that reduces CC usage
[Music]
mhm ah for bosses it's good yeah that's
true that makes sense cancel this and
copy your glass for
now I have GLS of
okay I'll copy the glass flower and now
copy the the ice bombs so that I can put
all of
them W I can only do one see I need gems
again but let me unequip the ice boms I
have now three might be enough three in
total
[Music]
um I
how do I unequip it I I'll just put
something else in there for now
whatever wait does anyone else have a
ice bomb too
no no
okay
uh David became a member what the
[\h__\h] how did that not show
up what are you Jeff and then J your
name
again how did you get a membersip and it
didn't show up in my
chat I've been a did you use a sub
account what
what
or
what well thank you though it didn't
show in the
feed wait if I have
two two streams open and someone becomes
a member does it show up in both chats
or only like in the specific stream
which you chose where
[Music]
like hacker it's a hacker B ah
okay anyway anyway anyway
[Music]
uh
once
again once
[Music]
again how many do I
need now that should be
enough
probably and
whatever whatever this is going to be
okay okay okay okay we got to go we got
to go it's 8:00 p.m. already let's go we
don't have time to lose ice
bomb for all in
there where's the recipe it goes uh down
[Music]
there
speed about 2 hours I have more than
about 2 hours left
but yeah at least right now I'm not
tired but I'm going to get tired after
the stream the good thing is actually if
I take longer with this and don't have
enough time to nap
then I just won't nap as long as I'm
streaming I don't really get
tired uh
was that a good idea to use that
[Music]
item I'm not
sure whatever use that one yeah I have
to eat too that's
true but a nap P would be would be
nice I love naps I want know nap while
cuddling with my kitty cats cuz they've
been
like please love
me why did was it necessary for me
[Music]
yeah I am not going to do finale part
two no Over My Dead
Body it will end
[Music]
today
such a
[Music]
waste we got to go down here though I
have
[Music]
to okay we got the minus one cc what's
that one super
fancy it's just quality + 20 what the
hell pink
ball wait no
wait there's another oh wait that was
not the oh that's the one
should I rebuild this
one uh few bonus plus plus
60%
oh what increases item power and he r
with few targets M do they they do sack
don't they should I get two extremely
devastating no it's
fine
[Music]
H they stack should I get two of them
and
then
oh I could get this one
[Music]
too or extremely devastating increases I
30% well this is basically the same
thing but heal single bonus triple stack
thank you for the membership
welcome
okay extremely devastating would have
been better you sure it's okay still a
great great bomb better than my ice
bombs should I try to copy that so I
have two of them or should I should I
duplicate the rose bomb
actually so I can throw two ice bomb H
roast bombs should okay tell me which
one ice or
ice bomb duplicate cost cost me oh oh
not even
that not even that
expensive takes a ton of
CC yeah
[Music]
well Rose
bomb oh it did end up with
999 that's actually better than my rose
bomb but the rose bomb is bugged so it's
better
still I like 7,000
400 you know what I'm going to do the
Ice bump cuz it takes uh
less less
CC oh oh should I keep ah I guess I
should keep one like cheap to use bomb
so I can yeah do the core
attack
true but I have four slots anyway H but
I want one slot for the for the Revival
thing okay okay
okay you shouldn't
always want too much right we have to
stop somewhere and think smart so core
item you can take one of uh those ice
bombs back I guess
and take this one beautiful wonderful so
we can do the core attack with those
free and we can also still have a
Revival item in there which by the way
it would probably be good to upgrade my
nectar but
whatever for now let's see how it
goes we are well prepared I
[Music]
think dragon's
coffin I did save now
right up the core Drive I how how how
how how how what how
how
how cor and ah ah yeah that was a
thing
[Music]
um
uh uh
[Music]
do I want ice too now cuz I have an ice
bom thank you for the membership
mersh glass is
[Music]
out what I don't have two slots what I
need the other slot what I don't know
what you mean ah ah I need that one
oh
oh wait I'm not sure what I'm
doing this will enhance all same
El would I just use ice here on that
one ice on
okay
[Music]
okay I still I have a lot of
them I can do one get both on level five
at
least
yeah
okay what do I have
to do how do I put the ice in
there H it's said X
ah okay now we're good
right I'll save
[Music]
again I am
back and now we're done
playing
I also don't care about any of these
materials anymore actually cuz I'm done
crafting as
[Music]
well
o
[Music]
done playing soon to find no no no
that's not what I meant what's in here
something useless right some weapon that
I don't need Divine Branch okay that's
actually something
else uh okay
uh oh another
[Music]
one oh wait that the final um item for
um Siri but it's [\h__\h] quality anyway cuz
it came out of out of a treasure chest
how ironic these are really
useless but okay
uh oh now they want me to go there
okay anything
here okay you want to be peted oh good
boy good boy good boy good boy oh good
boy I sh oh
[\h__\h] a bit too late on my
side I always like I don't know it's
just a reflex so mine I always go with
the the skill that's on y first even
though for example before it said he's
resisting against that one but I can't
help it it's just I always press that
one first I'm also poisoned I
think you know what let's see how much
damage that alone
[Music]
does nice
nice
wow d didn't even need the rose
bump found another level up wow wow
anything cool here no probably not
bye-bye we're getting like level ups
every freaking fight there's something
new that I kind of
[Music]
wanted oh no actually that was my
imagination I'm going to fight you I
think I feel like fighting you let me
just heal Risa I think she needs to
heal let me use the the toast it looks
yummy looks like a toast but I guess
it's
[Music]
[Applause]
not
okay
imag
it's time to fight sharpen
scissors
okay okay now I try to go for the skills
that are uh that he's weak
against uhoh no wasn't that me e
fight me don't go for this small cute
[Music]
LLY the way he's looking at me I feel
like he's asking for a
[Music]
bomb Patt with her 999
sword
yeah Power I feel it that's what I
wanted
power more and more and more
power can't get enough of
it next fight level
up I like
[Music]
it hello
fight sorry I couldn't turn on the river
was too lazy was too far away
oo that was not that much damage cuz
they are still resisting against it you
want to attack me
no thank you guys thank
you oh no he want to
[Music]
death
still
resisting
[Music]
anyway the plot
o should I take the challenge of
explaining the plot or do I leave it to
you
guys
um I'll leave it to you guys
it's basically just Raa and her
friends like finding each other again
after Risa won in this new
city then to was like [\h__\h] I'm I'm
addicted to checking out ruins and stuff
I want to see more and then they find
fee uh and then Fe feels like he's not
doing well so fee we need to take care
of fee basically while exploring uh
ruins to um keep tow
entertained I feel like that's pretty
accurate isn't it so then when looking
for staff of fee we go through all these
ruin and now we found the source to feel
Fe better but by giving Fe that Mama
[\h__\h] it open up a portal to the
underworld again just like in Raza 1 and
the Fila are now trying to get
us yeah they're like we opened the
portal so before they getting out we are
now in there trying
to stop them and kill them I think
that's honestly that's pretty
accurate yeah actually I think I hid uh
the nail in the coffin or something like
that not sure how that saying
goes
uh
sounds about right nice job remembering
honestly I was uh I'm proud of
myself that I was able
to put that
together okay what's up here oh oh no I
need to explode it synthesize something
to make it go
[Music]
boom
what's hiding behind that could it be
the final
boss
fore foreign
[Music]
fore
uh
if we burn some Divine tree firewood I
think there should be a furnace for it
somewhere Divine branches I think I
found one Divine
Branch so wait did we find the furnace
no we didn't
right by the way look at those statues
are those
dead oh that's one of those that I F
didn't
I wait let
me
I want to look at the
[Music]
material you disturb
me actually as you can
see yeah I can't I can't do my thingy
anymore from the beginning oh well um I
passed only ey is that that that single
spot that I missed was like whatever
it's not nothing's nothing interested
interesting is going to be there and
turns out there
is God damn
it
[Music]
or I'm on the level
really I mean Ian they do give me a lot
of
XP maybe that one I can get in
peace
uhhuh I'll get that no no go away from
me go away from me go away from
[Music]
me
nice okay but I don't need any of these
anymore
K stop you don't need those oh wait hey
it leads me there because probably the
furnace is there
haha or or is that where I got the
Divine tree branch
[Music]
it you'll be fine when you reach the
boss I hope so but I'm going to check
out if I missed the something here oh oh
no no nothing really
oh this just a just a
shortcut what was that room
for what a useless
[Music]
room okay no I don't I don't want to
avoid all of them because I do still
enjoy getting the
EXP but I don't want to run straight
into you
okay A Memory Shard is there ah oh I
guess
so well we will not be getting any of
those because I don't have the time for
it see how they're getting much much
less damage s and
Petty they're way more defensive than
before I'm happy to see that oh perfect
guard they used to have huge issues with
that they will be not able to tank
anything at all so big Improvement
there oh the wond is that good armor can
do right
okay
[Music]
byebye
right left and right
[Music]
and up I think and
left how did I not see the furnace there
before I was
there
Ah that's a furnace oh I was like why
can't I go in there
I nothing's happening but
the the blue thing is here what what do
you want me to
do what if I fire the bomb BR into it
does that make it
burn I need to craft something first oh
oh of course I
do do I have the
thing I picked up that ancient Branch so
the Divine the divine yeah there it is
top uh bottom bottom right I think top
bottom left bottom right
whatever a this
one probably I need this one
again pretty sure pretty sure
that's what I
need I I made that one before didn't
I
[Music]
I mean I might take a little break I
might not start it until I move because
I wanted to calm down
first uh and until then we're going to
do some shorter streams maybe
[Music]
perhaps we finish near AATA and Risa in
the same week after all that's actually
surprising so next week I just going to
I'm just going to do a week without any
big RPG I
think and maybe like two Minecraft
streams uh maybe
Sims we could play Sims
again and I think I have shadowe stream
next
week Sims what should we do next in
Sims create a happy
family
[Music]
that get get maybe some
Pets the
wedding
wedding yeah that might also make its
way into my schedule next
week
[Music]
ah
what just happened sorry we need to move
forward I don't know Miss okay I'll just
go back to the spot where I was before I
guess let's see it seems like the door
has opened
maybe
[Music]
hopefully
I like a dragon yeah cuz we started that
one last year that's crazy to say that
we started something last year last year
like in winter time we started Yakuza as
a sponsored stream we had one stream but
I enjoyed it so much much more than I
thought I would and we got permission to
continue it
so
let's do
it and now I have a much better PC than
I had back
then so remember the issues we had with
like loading times that was so
embarrassing because it was a sponsored
stream I I felt so stressed out I was I
was panicking I was panicking before the
stream and during the
stream that was tough I was so scared
like to get in trouble or so but it was
all
good I didn't didn't get in any trouble
but still I feel like so bad about
it that's it right that was was that
where the door was just a moment
ago how did that stone wall Disappear by
burning some
[Music]
incense
magic it was an illusion oh H because of
the The Fog well if it was an illusion
why couldn't I just walk through
it I can I can fish here e what kind of
disgusting poison fish will I get
[Music]
here but normal boring
stuff
that's
it that's actually
lame wait I can't even jump into the
water which door do I want to go
through I guess both could work maybe
they both lead into the same
map ah that path is important for
memories only okay thank you for letting
me know oh no no door
here
the middle door leads the B wait that
behind that is already the
bus
fore
ouch yes really wow that's really short
the
[Music]
dungeon
and I'm
scamed wait he's kind of tough damn
without the bombs they're really uh
tough to
defeat you know what I'll wait a little
bit
stomp cute
cute
[Music]
well that's thr it
whatever take
this yeah okay he doesn't really do much
damage but he's really
defensive
okay demon
blood excuse me just want to get to your
manager um I don't want to talk to you
idiots but I'm I'm a bit
scared wait
[Music]
uh everyone's full H except
Siri okay
okay
uh
[Music]
Karin yes
go is this really it oh there's some
weird
dust
[Music]
it's still a little bit to
go you know what I'm just going to go
straight to the boss there or should I
should I find that little small boss
okay as a warm
up what the [\h__\h] are you oh [\h__\h] I ran
into it another color variation Shadow
eater want to
fight oh cute
no it's like like cute Nibbles from like
a
baby you can't hurt
[Music]
me
oh he does not like ice bombs or they
all don't like ice
bombs yeah
30,000 total
damage almost level up let's get level
80 before the
[Music]
fight hello uh oh here's your
boss yeah that was
close renal
fiend wait
what is that weird
[Music]
or gold oh he's turning
Patty should I heal
her still sorry
yby yeah that's all we need for
Patty
attack when is the right timing for the
bombs see I really pretty much figured
out the crafting system but the fighting
system there's still some things I'm a
bit unsure about
like when it still s resist it does less
damage right so but sometimes when I
throw them it breaks him so instead of
waiting for him to be broken I could
throw them and then break him with the
bombs and then do more damage but I
don't know I I I don't really
know what is the right
tactic does he break every time I throw
those
bombs throw the rose Bomb Blast what do
you me mean
last I want to use them during the break
yeah so I guess I wait
[Music]
still like now now now would be a good
time to throw the bomb I think because
if I don't throw it now he might do his
big attack so he's not broken yet but I
kind of have to do it now but maybe
without using the for
Aurora that's that's how I understood it
wait he died from that oh oh what what
what okay I was too
strong what no need to worry about
anything at
all he he got wrecked oh my God I got
gold from him
noce um let me get that treasure
chance thank
[Music]
you [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] we don't want that
no no no no
no no no no no no no no
no nope no no no
no no thank you this place place will
forever be cursed with uh lost memories
and
[\h__\h] wait there's another the boss
already
respawned and he's right in my
path oh come on oh I can't go past him
but how did he already
[Music]
respawn it seems like they gave me no
choice
for
Fore
[Music]
fore
okay I'm on it
[Music]
Patty them okay it's time it's time to
move
[Music]
on by the way do I need heal someone
need
heal Yeah Siri needs
[Music]
heal
oh
Treasure
Chest oh we got
a
cloudia okay and then through the
middle woo wow wow wow it's not looking
good here
Y no no no should we get one level up
though I think we're close to the last
level up to get level
[Music]
80 let's fight these I'm not
scared
who okay that's too
much it's
[Music]
over y I'm going to heal them of
course we
[Music]
explosion it's the big bang fairy
you're not
dead
soon thank you
Patty level
eight damn we leveled up 20 levels in
this stream we started out
[Music]
[\h__\h] I ran out of CC right yeah okay
well we got to heal well in the battle
that's all we can do is this is this uh
is this
it let me drink some ice
[Music]
tea
this is it
maybe oh
wow I think this calls for a
screenshot before we kill the last boss
I think I need it
nice screenshot for
[Music]
Twitter oh time of day can't even be
changed
[Music]
here okay rise out po ium battle
poses they kind of at the end
[Music]
though
M where are your battle
poses we have the stick yeah that's kind
of
cute oh let's go with that one and then
an angry one deter an angry
determined
one and we get her closer here
how do I change the camera angle
again camera control mode oh that
[Music]
way something like that go back to
characters let's get in the girls all of
the girls only the
girls here she is doesn't have much many
clothes on
but oh I love her bows looks so
pretty battle P oh
yeah pies up a lot of
[Music]
space okay and then wait Risa Maybe a
bit
more over
[Music]
there and then
Patty come here little
Patty let me show what kind of poses you
got fighting poses this time ooh look at
that beautiful epic
sword
oh that covers up her face even though
it's so
cool
M difficult I like the pose
but okay let's just do that
one I don't want to I don't want her
sword to be that cut off but also don't
want it to cover up
[Music]
S angry okay and then s
going to be on that
[Music]
side ah she doesn't she only has that
bracelet so it doesn't really stand out
[Music]
much that's
cute no I'm going to do that one
cute
okay that's basically but maybe they
should get closer
[Music]
together bit more over there
okay the balance is important
guys cloud
uh bow takes up so much
space now I don't like that pose anymore
sorry Risa we got to change it oh in
your
face ah
difficult h you know what I don't like
to face
anymore serious yeah let's go with that
[Music]
one sorry I'm so focused now this is
important
uh okay I think I'm okay with that
[Music]
and taco UI which one is
that there we
go
oh screenshot
time
oh
oh photo mode it's a photo of they all
just came here for those Instagram shots
you know just coming to these locations
these beautiful tourist
attractions for the screen for the uh
Instagram photos
[Music]
in can you focus on them that would be
nice how do
I death F
fielded off there we go ah
[Music]
no okay I think I'm
done yeah okay let's go now I'm ready
sorry to keep you waiting D me
okay did I heal
everyone I couldn't heal everyone
completely I
think yeah we got a deal of this it is
what it
is ah
[Music]
kaai are you ready
guys for the last fight it has been
quite a journey first Raza one then Raza
two
is this the only game where I played
like a prequel and a
sequel for
[Music]
now oh skit that is the portal to the
underworld so far
yes ah yeah Okay cookie me okay
[Music]
okay
oh
oh let's do
this oh will the enemy come out of
there
cracking my
[Music]
fingers she's
I
see because it can't be close so they
have to close it by like building a like
a
huge building around
it to try to thr it oh my God what's
coming out of
there oh
[\h__\h] well hello are you the manager you
certainly look like the
manager ooh I like the design pretty
cool but bit
scary oh God I'll probably fail the
first
time
a
[Music]
[Applause]
minute I'll take it
crown
we can't close it how would we close it
yeah what the
hell just
down free will do it what is what else
is free useful for anyway it must be the
key to the
story here we
go
[Music]
for S I miss
you let's
go fight k KY let's
go VI glory to
KI oh God oh God oh God I cannot leave
my let my people
down no oh [\h__\h] I should have okay
already first mistake look at p is thep
I got to heal
her
[Music]
uh-oh I uh I need to heal I need to heal
I need to heal I need to heal I need to
heal
oh I'm like already [\h__\h]
up the music is
Chill why is the music so chill it's so
calm like
romantic Cafe oh now it's back okay wait
I'm
scared oh yeah rock and roll holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay
okay
okay element domination oh what the [\h__\h]
what what are you doing
n what what is that is he getting into
his Second
[Music]
Face a second face already okay that's
good he's already at half oh come on
ridiculous
you go let me attack let me attack let
me attack let me attack before he
attacks oh [\h__\h] what is that what is he
doing oh that ah he's like loading up
wait
okay okay
okay that was
close that was
close
Okay what do you say about that huh
weave have all skill nice Patt
[Music]
nice he's almost dead oh but he will
probably Rea re re revive
himself okay thir form that was easy up
until here was easy easy as
[Music]
[\h__\h] no there have a phone
right no no no no there's
more there's more
[Music]
right
nah wait I was doing so
well there were like there was one
moment where
um he was like really close
to giving me a really bad hit like when
he was about but but right before I used
my
items I was waiting for that moment when
he was broken and not before he was
[Music]
broken
what my timing was really
good
yes get rid of him
wait I have this would probably normally
normally be sad but I have absolutely no
emotional connection
[Music]
to he can't be here he probably ruins
the the balance of Mana in the world
was that really the was that really the
final battle that were that was easier
than like the normal mob
[Music]
somehow
yep RIS doesn't
care RZA wants him to leave
too n no that's that's the only point
where we're not on the same
[Music]
page but
byebye
Fe I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry
[Music]
but he's never going to be a
partner why is everyone so emotionally
attached to
[Music]
Fe
M why does everyone care so much about
[Music]
me bye bye Fe you were cute and all that
but that's your
home
a a
okay that's
sad oh oh come
on that makes even me sad no she cry no
what the [\h__\h] no R okay that got
[Music]
me
byee Mama Mama Mama it's like you guys
saying by to me to breaks my my heart
okay get it okay she hatched him after
all Riza is me B is you
[Music]
guys okay I'm
s
[Music]
okay I'm not crying I hate whatever
[\h__\h] I don't
care I'm I'm just sweating sweating from
my
eyes that's
[Music]
all I was so sad because it reminded me
of you guys and I didn't want to say
bye-bye to you guys but I don't give a
[\h__\h] about just to make it clear
[Music]
okay
I'm just
[Music]
sweating
is it
over I got to be honest the boss fight
was
some it could have been so much more if
I was less prepared I should have
prepared
less and hey what about the person who
said he only had 4 HP left at the very
end but it was was higher level than me
and he had a 99 999 Rose bomb and here I
am risea had like uh almost full
HP okay Ry has to go to every freaking
spot yeah I mean yeah but still like we
Ed the rose bombs on other mobs this was
not only the rose bump this I have to I
have to say this was also me using the
bumps at the very right time and using a
good batt tactic now we got to be honest
that was that that is
true if I would have thrown those right
in the beginning then maybe wouldn't
have done the same
thing the the timing was very important
the timing was off the Essence no that
is that is 100% true
yep it was of course also the rose bump
and the the ice bumb too and the
equipment of course like okay but all of
that took work and time and hours of of
uh farming in the crafting
so it was my
effort too strong I'm just too strong
I'm a and part time
Warrior
she's going back
to oh she's going to change her mind and
then we will have Raza
[Music]
free
where do you want to go
l
[Music]
he everyone comes back home
after I guess
[Music]
that's it's like
me in the end I came back to Australia
after all the travels and all the things
that all the adventures I've been
through after all that it leads me back
to
Australia oh what else is in the
cafe are
[Music]
you I got slime stuck in my throat
now
if there's a Risa 3 though they'll
probably make her even thicker cuz they
upgraded her from Risa 1 to Risa 2 can
you imagine an even Freckle rise of
3 that would be
crazy oh yeah I ate a pony
[Music]
I'll miss your face cuz it reminds me of
my
[Music]
papa oh she looks like she's
out
a I'll come back and check this place
out again
sometime Dennis
Workshop I don't really care about you
Dennis cuz we didn't really have much
interaction cuz I skipped everything but
[Music]
whatever
you'll be fun without me what the
[Music]
hell
you can literally literally create
anything with Alchemy as we have
[Music]
seen
you're
fine you know what Risa fre might just
be Risa side character just like how
Leela and emple were in Raa too but the
main character will be someone new
maybe that I could see
it her being like the mentor to someone
as usual with
gam maybe like
a would be cool if she had like a
smaller sister a younger
sister yeah she's so popular so they
they'll definitely want to milk her for
that popularity but I would prefer if
she wasn't the main character again like
they I like I
um I there's characters so much that I
just really enjoy
[Music]
having so many shut up new characters to
look at cuz their character designs are
so lovely so I really want to see
something new now Risa was great but
take that greatness and do something new
with it
[Music]
please that's my opin
p p i don't want to leave
Patty wait also I didn't really finish
Siri Arc did I that's
[Music]
sad did I never find the flower for Siri
that she
[Music]
want I want to see the final art that
you get with
Siri motion send it to me
please I know you didn't like me Patty I
remember I haven't even done s's final
[Music]
story
I said are you have it I want to see
it
[Music]
like she has money and you don't rise
up no no there's no fre no announcement
or anything like that no no but yeah
it's just a high possibility that
they're going to do something with Risa
again but someone mentioned Claudia I do
feel like it would be cool to have like
a side Arc a whole
game where Risa could still be there but
I don't think a ever did that like make
a whole new game where a side character
is now the M main character I don't
think they ever did
that don't whisper like that it's
embarrassing
[Music]
that was that that made even me feel
weird she's
[Music]
embarrassed okay as Central District
Central District
you
no are you
Romy sorry I ignored
you
[Music]
R fre is r
me traveling as the main
character and R being the side
character you heard it here first guys
you heard it here
first you know what Romy has potential
with a new new outfit a new hairstyle
she has
potential she's no alist well she can
learn it from
Ron
anyone can be an alchemist right there's
no like
specific magic that you have to be born
with Ry sounds
cute a living Barrel as a
party
[Music]
T
barel well the lag is back
oh wait it's still the same
[Music]
area okay who's next ah
Claudia
St it's uh maybe actually not Time to
Say Goodbye maybe we'll go back home
[Music]
together Liza hi B
fore
[Music]
fore come with
me
[Music]
for
speee
[Music]
Fore
for oh [\h__\h]
you [\h__\h] this
[Music]
[\h__\h]
spee
[Music]
fore
even though I said your name wrong so
[Music]
often I know
Callie I know I know you're
[Music]
busy
Ash
CLA official couple
hasht or Ria CLA Ria which one is it
guys CLA or
Ria oh my God
[Music]
right
oh
[Music]
oh okay nothing is more painful painful
than that one
so guess we're saying goodbye to to yeah
tow take care of Patty take care of your
children your future children
yeah
spee
foreign fore
fore
I honestly have to say
Risa like this seems out of character
for me I feel like she would go on more
adventur which is why we will get Risa
fre she'll go home and she'll be like
[\h__\h] I'm bored
again I want to travel
more If Only They had smartphones and
PCs back
then and she would probably be fine to
settle down she would start streaming
she would probably join
whole
fore
[Music]
for Fore
fore
oh that's
cool you'll marry Patty I
know
[Music]
oh wait there's one more
here I must be
Bulls let's see what we have to say to
Bulls Bulls was one of the characters
from RIS of one but they brought him
here too which I feel like was maybe not
really necessary but
okay hi
Bulls you two are of the same mind yeah
kind of I really feel like I'm similar
to
Risa but I'm unfortunately not as
positive as Risa I wish I was h
[Music]
as nobody's as positive as R yeah
this is just like an
inhumane uh positivity that only game
characters and anime characters can
help
oh
okay
[Music]
now if actuallya 2 will hit me with an
ending credit screen where I have to do
endless
Alchemy in order to kill each name on
the ending
screen I am going to burn my
PC and can't what what what what what
what do
[Music]
sorry smoothie just walked in my room
meow three times looked at me with a
drop of water on her
chin I'm like what is it did you are you
telling me that you just drank water
good job
baby she always after she drinks she
always has this drop of water on her
chin
always
n telling me to hydrate oh maybe did you
drink
water
was a pretty cool
[Music]
charactery oh my God now that you say it
[Laughter]
[Music]
you're making me
curious
[Music]
d
haa all right we're almost done
guys one left is it the the farming girl
no wait Siri what the hell what about
Siri is she here there's two actually
farming girl and
[Music]
Siri okay there is a farming girl here
let's do very
[Music]
lost you can come we have lots of fs and
[\h__\h]
too
[Music]
fore
okay oh she's with them oh is she going
to join them
[Music]
she would fit in
well
[Music]
fore
too much F in one
scene
true they are implying that there's more
game
seat is it because I didn't finish her
character
act would you say something else if I
found her your stupid
flower or does she just never end up
never finding it
[Music]
ever wait wait do we get a different
around no flowers that she's looking
CL it would have been different
[Music]
no she doesn't find them either
way it would be different okay
good
[Music]
foree
El Miss she was a cute
character okay let's pack up our things
and
leave oh is she actually packing or she
looking for something doesn't really
look like she's
[Music]
packing did did she
pack left the pony up at the b top
left
hit that
[Music]
okay a
hia
[Music]
screenshot
a it's going
home it's bye-bye
time
[Music]
aee fore
spee
fore
speech
foreign
huhe
[Music]
fore
for no not scratch it down no
no chunkers one's
[Music]
cuddles
fore
[Music]
spee
for no smothie don't Scrat
[Music]
oh she's crying her voice is
crying Chun is not in front of the
camera
Forint
hint a byebye fee
oh don't cry again
[Music]
Ry oh my
God
for
[Music]
foree
I don't know if I should smile or
[Music]
look
the song literally just sings this is
not the end there is another beginning
waiting the song spoilers
[Music]
itty PTY PTY clap
clap anding
credits oh a back in at the island
[Music]
for
adventure
[Music]
for Fore
for [\h__\h]
[Music]
AE
should I mute this oh whatever it's not
not uh no super chats
[Music]
anyway
well that
[Music]
was oh beautiful singing
voice oh I like the
song
[Music]
ah
well I have to
say uh all in all I guess it was better
than rise of one but not all of
it I turned down music a little bit
more for me it was uh definitely the
battle system was better um than in Risa
one and
uh possibly many other parts but the
story yeah the story was much better in
Risa 1 I think I feel like in Risa
2 especially today when I
explained uh what the plot
is I realized there is really not much
special plot like they go in a little
adventure and all that but there's no
real big deep
reason and
it all just starts out of a
whim while rise of one it seems like
there is much more
purpose
and however it didn't ruin the game at
all it still wins over rise one it still
wins because everything else is so
strong and the characters that the new
characters that came in are also so
strong like they leave such
a
um deep image and connection cuz each
character is fought through so well in
my
opinion yeah so they make up for it I
guess for the yeah a lasting impression
I guess too they make up for it and the
battle system definitely also makes up
for it maybe there's some other things
that improved I guess like Alchemy and
all that but I can't really judge it
that much because those are some things
where I just fck that in Risa one
because I didn't understand it that well
even at the
end but I guess Alchemy maybe improved
as as well I'm not sure I can't really
judge
that the systems are different and
um
yeah I guess it was better in some way
maybe easier in two maybe
maybe
really can't tell much the photo mode
was fun too yeah actually that is
true and I personally love the graphics
and everything I know that there is
games with better graphics but I just
like the Aesthetics of well all AA games
in general there's no big Improvement or
anything between a RIS one and two one
was already beautiful now for two I also
have to say this Fe thing was
unnecessary uh
oh that's R's
necklace thank you for the membership
welcome well I hope f is
Happy
[Music]
um
uh mhm sure uh wait a sh oh
[\h__\h] I ta out I
guess there we go yes I
guess why
not new
one a c CB C thank you for joining the
membership oh my God I love your videos
I love them so
much let's do something together one
day let's
collab and you've played the game which
is unlock the following very hard
charismatic and legendary
difficulties they have a lot of high
difficulties don't they they make it
very
difficult and
extra what's
extra what is that
voice is that baby
r
who what
[Music]
Fe what what is it what is this what is
this ah it's the artworks oh thank God I
love those oh there's ah there was a
variation
oh a a i love that moment that was
dramatic movies ah model view
oh
oh now concert hole a concert H adding
music and
bonus oh it's the voice
actor
[Music]
for
hello
wow okay I'm not going to listen to the
other ones now but as you can see
there's a lot of ooh a lot of even from
the side
characters nice okay well I'm going to
take a break because H Holo talk is
waiting for me in 3 hours um um this is
the end of the rise of series I hope you
guys enjoyed it hope you guys had fun um
we've spent many many many hours uh in
this
series together you and me uh I want to
say thank you to everyone who spent
their time with me with these games
although many of you probably um maybe
are not interested in these games that
much but you watched it because of me
thank thank you very much that means a
lot to me and I hope we can play more
games like this in the
future
it's a really cute game and uh I'm glad
that I was able to play it on stream
with you guys it helped me a lot because
you guys help
me and
yeah it's the first time that I really
felt like I really really played an a a
game to the fullest
potential and yeah that was very very
enjoyable M thank you
guys ah ah thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you I'll
um I'll leave you guys and I'll see you
at Hol talk in three
[Music]
hours
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you it was a lovely
game thank you kcho for the um
permission to play it thank you and with
that I say goodbye to Risa maybe we meet
again there were a lot of hints they
kept it open they kept the possibilities
open definitely not sure if they're
really going for it but
I see a future with
Risa and if that future ever arrives
then we want to wel welcome her back on
our Channel I think
again
so goodbye
everyone
and in German we
say
Al
byebye
Risa byebye I'll miss the game maybe
I'll play a different at game
privately there's a few ones that I
haven't played
yet
byebye see you later
[Music]
what
n
[Music]