DET
OG
OGtil
DET
H
Yeah Ah
Yeah
Ga
Waami San
Mina
Hello America
and
Hello everyone, please wait a minute
Hey, my wife is
really sleepy The background music is
a little too loud Oooooo Maybe it's okay
Maybe
How are you doing with the book?
How's it going? [Music] It's so early in the morning
in America. What time is it now? It's 7 o'clock.
Calliope is at 7
o'clock. I'm glad it's good. That's
more than anything.
[Music]
Hey, Hey
Debbie, I'm
sorry. Calliope's Japanese has
gotten really bad. I don't use it at all,
so I'm sorry. I want to get better at it again, so I'm going to try streaming something like this
in Japanese. English
is prohibited
this time. English is prohibited this time.  Saekari-chan,
thank you!
Thank you for listening! Thank you for watching. Thank you, Ki-chan. I can speak English,
but since I'm doing a challenge like this, I
'll reply properly in Japanese.
Hey, it's not Japanese. Sorry,
hey, hey. Hey, it's not Japanese. Wait a minute. It's
not Japanese. I think I'll try playing Totsumachi today.
Well
, this game
is called Clubhouse 51 in English.
Hey, everyone, I, Calliope, was
going to do Clubhouse 51 and I was going to do it in Dekomachi, so I
told you to come and participate, but I guess that
Japanese member was
wondering what Clubhouse 51 was, so it was called a play tournament.  is
Yeah, I didn't know that in Japanese. What
is Clubhouse 51? It
's true that everyone has it. It's gone. Calliope. Well, I can't help it. It's called a tournament.  I
understand that it's a different game and a tournament.
Okay,
Calliope. That's right, Calliope, so I'll just wait a little bit. In the
clubhouse, let's
gamble for now. Let's all gamble while we wait. Let's
play Black Jack.
Wait a
minute, I made a mistake, I want to make a mistake, I want to make a mistake, I'm sorry, but I'm going to
make a tiny baby Wait a minute, that
's not Calliope,
this doesn't look like a temporary bride, wait a minute.
Wait, wait, my
Figure Connecting
Yeah, Wow, I'm flying.
Do you like blackjack? Do you like blackjack? Do you
do blackjack? Hey,
ham beok. This is English. It's messed up English.
Skip. Oh, let's try 5 Raz. Okay, yes.
I understand. Do you know the rules of blackjack? Do you
know?
I've done it before. Play 5.
Jesus knows it, I know it, it's good
, it's good, it's good, it's good
, it's calliope. I've gambled because it's a real song. I'll
do my best. No, it's no good, so what
should I do?
[Music]
Do, that's really ginger  The
player without is the king
, so don't worry, everyone, don't worry, let's move on to the next one. We'll
definitely win this time. Calliope is okay, okay.
[Music] Oh, it's
not 20.
No, no, I really want you to stop.
No, it's okay. This time, it's definitely okay.  I'm going to win
because Calliope
30303030
Dao
30 It's not grass, it's not grass, everyone
Hey, it's not fun
Double
Down Please bust it
Please
[applause]
Ah, I do
n't have 40, I don't have it, but you
can do negative, negative,
so wow, congratulations to Black Jerk, muff hit!
Feeling
Yeah Stand
Da Stand
Power
Biu I won
[Music]
Yay, I'm glad I'm number 2. Look,
Calliope might be good.
No, I do
n't want to read Revia. I don't want to read it.
Hey, I'm waiting to see if I can do it again. I'm sure my friends will come to visit. I'm sure they'll
come to play.
If they don't come, I'll just gamble. I'll
gamble until the night.
Calliope, I'll be waiting for you.
Dando
Power Wow, I was surprised, I
was surprised, I was surprised, oh, oh
Senpai, wait a minute, wait a minute
Gambling Gambling Gambling
Thank you very much for coming.  I'm sorry to
disturb your gambling time.I'm not going to
stop it.I'm going to stop it.It's
not fun, it's not fun.I'm looking forward to it.No
, I'm looking forward to
Kario-senpai's game.Yeah,
yeah, yeah, I'm looking forward to it.I'm
making it.I'm going to make it.No, I
'm waiting.  Come to think of it, Kao,
senpai,
yes, Nba Love, thank you, I forgot, but I forgot,
but I was practicing so much, so it's cool. It's
cool. I'm so happy. Thank you. I did my
best.
Taeka-chan is blink bang bang bong Uh
wait a minute I'm not singing with Kao who was singing
Ooh I want you to try it I
want to sing nnnn I want to sing
Plagg and rap Eh what game should we play I'll
leave it to you  Leave it to me, leave it to me, uhm
4 How do you say this in Japanese?
Connect 4 Connect 4, okay?
Yes, I'm good at it. Big Bray. You're such a
genius, Kao.  You're so
bad, you're so bad, so go
ahead and
get eaten. Let's go, let's go, let's get eaten. Let's go! Calliope, Calliope,
give me a red color. Oh, it's red. It's a good image. Yes, it's red. It's a
good image. Yes, it's a good image.  I wonder
if you're concentrating like crazy. How are you, Kinkade-chan? Oh, you're doing well.
Hey, Calliope too.
I'm fine,
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, it's early in the
morning, but oh, you're early in the morning, Calliope-senpai, yes, you're
very good at Japanese, thank you, that's
not the case.
Oh yeah, this is no good, it's definitely
not good.  I'm
not an idiot, I'm
not an idiot, it's okay, it's okay Senpai, I'm fine, I'm fine. Hey, I'm not
an idiot. Please stop it. You're
being stupid. One more time, one
more time. One more time. I won't lose, so I'm going to
play Calliope. No, I won't lose. Call me a guy who won't lose. Hey,
hey, it's okay.  I'm going to beat you up, I'm
going to beat you up, I'm
going to beat you up, I'm definitely going to beat you up.  I'm
going to beat you up this time Yeah. The intonation is cute. I'm going to beat you
up. Intonation Intonation It's weird, but it's funny, so it might be okay. I'm going to make it pop. Oh yeah, what should I do
? Well, I see. Calliope is
going to block here.
[Music] Is
one okay?  Is it okay to have one
? Oh, I see. Oh, I see.
Oh,
oh, I made a mistake, no, I made a mistake, yay,
yay.
[Laughs]
Please don't be happy.
[Music]
Pipipipio No
Senpai
Uwa
[Music]
Uh hey hey scary scary scary scary scary scary
Calliope is scary Shinigami is scary
Stop Stop Stop Look, I'm
not concentrating right now so I'm strong I
might die or I might die Senpai is strong
Yeah, I'm getting stronger. I
made a mistake. I made a mistake. No, no,
no.
[Applause]
wn
Calliope.
UN You're an
idiot. You're an
idiot. Shall we play another game?  It's a
frustrating draw,
so I'm going to have about an hour left to
stream my craft.I
hope you enjoy it from 11pm.Thank you very much.I can
play, I can play, and I can play boxing.  It's
fun.
There's no mercy. There's no mercy. Pa-
pan. Just because I'm Pan-pan senior, I'm going to give it my all. So I'll give it my all. I'll try my
best. I
kinda forgot the controls, so I'll
just take a look.  I
see, oh, I get it, I guess I get it. I'm going
to really beat you up this time.
Come on, give me a punch. Come on, give me a
punch. Shinigami punch, scary punch. Hey, ga-ga-guard, guard-oh. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
over there. There's a UFOUFO over there. There's
a UFO.  Stop it,
wa
tawa wa tai oh yeah, of course you should do it
one more time
uoo There was no U over there.  It's
funny, I asked you, Ra-chan, where's La-
chan, Ihuiofi-sanfu-senpai, Fu-senpai,
where's
UFO,
Sussu-swiss UFO,
stop it, hey, UFO, look, look, it's
Hoshimachi Mizu, look, look, it's water, it's
Mizu-senpai, look
there, look there, it's over there.  Asui-chan, you do
n't have a senior.
Kastawa, wait, wait, yay.
[Applause]
Okay, congratulations. Thank you for the good fight.
It's fun, it's fun, it's fun, it's
a draw, it's a draw,
yeah, let's do this, this is my favorite calliope, are you
good at it?Are you good at it?
No, I don't know, let's have a match.Well, I
think it's good, but yeah, I'll lose.But I don't think
I'm good at anything.  If you think about it, you'll definitely lose.Oh, then I
wonder if you can win.No
, no, we haven't started yet.Wait a minute, I'll
protect you, I'll even protect you.Ah, Noah, I'll protect you.
Yay, oh, Calliope, you're so bad, you're so bad,
you'll definitely win. It's a difficult calliope, you're so bad, you'll win. It's
strong,
bumpy, bumpy, bumpy,
bumpy. It's become extremely difficult. I'm
watching it on the board next to you. Kumokumokapu-senpai, over there.
UFOU is wrong. There's no UF, so you should stop.  It's
difficult, wait, wait, no
, no, it's okay, it's fine, I can afford it  I can
afford it, I
ca
n't afford it, I don't have
it, I don't need it [Music] No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's a waste.
Oh my god, no, this time
it's blue, so I'm not lucky Calliope, ah, it's red.
No, red is the lucky color.
So
this is true evil. Blue is the worst.  It's
getting hot, it's getting hot
Wait, wait, it's a different story
It's a really good match It's a good match
No, it's a good match That's a good match More than anything, I'm being
too lazy. No stop strike. No, it's definitely not a match. Calliope
is so messed up.  That's why clumsiness
and tenbo are also crazy
Oh wait, there's one more point Ahhhhhhhhh I
guess I won. I won. Yes, I
won.
[Music]
Taei It seems like a good fight.
Thank you. Thank you very much, Gayobe-senpai. It
was fun. It was fun.
Thank you for coming. Let's collaborate and
sing together again. Of course. I
want to collaborate. Yay. I want to sing with you. I want to sing.  Well,
Kade-chan's singing is really good,
so I'm okay with that. Senpai is also great at singing and rapping.
Thank you. Let's definitely sing together someday.
Of course, I want to do it
. It was fun. Yes, it was fun. Thank you for listening.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, do your best, bye-bye, see you again, peace-bye, Kanade-chan, Kade-chan, you're cute, cute, playwith, stop, stop, it was fun, it was fun, it was a good game, everyone, I
was surprised, it was so much fun, I'm
going to gamble, I'm gambling, right? Or practice?  That
's fine, but I don't know if it even has a CPU.
But, uh,
thank you Jajagal, Kachan. It
was fun. It was really fun. Heung-boa. That's
nice.  Let's start
over, Calliope, it's a bit clumsy. Everyone is seriously clumsy. That thing can't be helped. It's been clumsy ever since I was born, so it might never change. Gambling, this time I'm 80. Stop it, stop it. This is the worst
hit and
power.
Yeah.  I did it, it's so good,
Big Manny, I
poop in this house. There's no water, there
's no water,
but it's in the sink. Can I
drink it? Maybe I can drink it. Calliope.  It can't be
helped because I love Bottle Bottle Mizu, but I'm shopping at Naiaa. Maybe the stores aren't open right now. Are you serious? Hino, stop it, stop it.Water.Water.
Tap water in America.Tap water.It's scary.It
varies from week to week.For
example, it varies from week to week.  Florida is okay,
maybe you can't drink it, maybe
Texas isn't that bad, I
don't know, but I don't
think Texas is that bad.  I don't
think it's a problem, and I do
n't think the
water in California is that bad either.Sometimes, the water in Florida tastes a bit like
stone.  I do
n't know, but it definitely won't be good.I
know Calliope because it tastes like ``Unstone Stone.''
Wait a minute, have
you ever tasted that when you were a kid?
Mostone is a hit.Maybe
it's a stand.I've had Nestone before.  I never
ate that when I was an adult, or even as an adult, but when I was a kid, I ate it
just once, and
instead of licking it, I
licked it, and I thought, ``This is the taste of stone.''
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
lick it, lick it, lick it,
thank you, no, but my calliope
's Japanese is so bad, I
don't use it at all, so please
stop.  Looks
like I'm licking the stand licking Good evening Good
evening Good evening I'm fine
Calliope I just woke up and I was in bed
No, I really wanted to die But I'm
glad I had a good fight for money I'm feeling really
good right now I'm in a good mood I'm in a good mood
Oh
my God.  Everyone is a blackjack master. I'm now a
blackjack master. I'm
waiting for 5 more rounds.  I'm
waiting for the members to come. I'm waiting, I'm waiting, but the other members are
streaming right now,
so I don't know if they'll
come or not. I hope they come, I hope they come, I hope they
come.  Maybe it's not happening at all
40 Likes Please stop liking 4
Please 15 and 16 are
the worst
Yeah then Calliope is the secret
Oh okay okay okay from now on
Calliope is
60 all en
In other words
Oruesia
All
in Yeah, the members of GP are shy. It
's okay, Calliope is also really shy, so that ca
n't be helped. The Holomen are shy, so it can't be helped, but I
did it. Taun won. It's okay, Calliope will wait. I'll
wait. I'm
sure.
Please listen to it when the broadcast is over.
Please, from now on, Calliope will be concentrating on gambling,
so it's okay. It's all good
now.
[Music] It's
blackjack. It's really weird.
If you gamble, you'll get blackjack. If you gamble,
you'll get a little more bonus bonus.  You
played chips, that's amazing, that's really funny.If that's
the case, it's a tie, so I wo
n't get the money.I won't get the money.Oh, you're so kind.Clubhouse
51 play tournament is messed up.It's so kind.It's such a
kind world.100100
100, yay, yay, yay, I've
been to Las Vegas.Yes,
yes, that's
scary.  I was
a bit
scared, so I might not go back. But I've
done it once, so I'm satisfied. It
's more than enough.  Is it
okay to say it only once in your life? Yes,
but if you like gambling, you've
only said it once in your life.
So maybe it's better to say it, but I'm scared. I don't
think it's that dangerous.  But if I'm with my friends, it
won't be a problem.Mom, I think I
should study a little bit of English.I played Double Dada Da Double Down.That's
right.It's fun and safe when you're with your friends.
Yeah, it's pretty interesting, but maybe you should study English a little.The
reason is because there are a lot of those suspicious people out there.Be
careful, be careful, I
did it, 410, and I got really rich.Wow, that's
great, everyone.
Wow, that double down
was really lucky, wasn't it? Yeah, it's
really
strong. I'll
try playing blackjack one more time with Wanire, and I'll try other games solo.
Waiting.
That's right, I thought it would be better to do it a little later.Well, the
Japanese Deb Beats are also
calm after work, so I
thought I'd do it for that purpose.Today,
today is Tuesday
or Tuesday.  Cat Good
evening
Good evening, I'm calm and relaxed.
Thank you, thank you, no, no,
this
is me. Yes, I've had dinner. I wonder if Calliope is eating breakfast. I
'm not eating breakfast.  My
stomach
hurts like hell, so I ate breakfast and thought, Wow, I
like
chicken doria. Wow, maybe it's not American chicken doria. No,
no, no, I want to go back to Japan as soon as possible. I
really want to go back to Japan. Japanese food, really.
American food is not that bad depending on where you are.I
think there are some delicious things like kage,
fried chicken sandwiches,
sand sandwiches, etc.
Even if it's the best, I prefer Japanese Lili's
Lili cuisine
Cooking looks good.
Rice's
dishes, such as tonka and cutlet, are also delicious. I'm
disappointed because it's Ace. Seung Woo Ji-chan's Wow, he's so cute,
stop it. He's Unlucky and Biji-chan. He's
cute, but he's not English.  The members of the group can
be called Bibu.Yes, Bibu.
Who is Biju
? ​​Biji is someone I don't know. I
know Bibu.  I
'm a friend of mine. Who
's name is beauty?
But it's 10, so what
should I do?
Well, well, double down,
baby. Hehehehe,
safe
. I won't take it off. I've always said it like Rusty Lusty from Ako 6.
That's right
. I
won't take it off.  That's cool Rusty
Rusty Co I love sex It's coming soon
Everyone Elden Ring
is going to be a DLC for Elden Ring
Stop it, stop it Oh no it's Ace No what do I
do It's scary  I'm
scared of stars, so yes, that's good. I'm glad I
stood, but I can't help it.
That really ca
n't be helped, that
really can't be helped, IW miss.
Gambling is fun, it's too much fun It
's not too bad, but it's a game, so it's
not really weird, so it's okay Hey
Halim, what are you going to do with the solo?
Piano,
wait,
Pia
[Music]
Baradankao is good
Hey, listen to this
What
's this? I don't know, maybe it's not good.
Stop and leave it to me,
shake, shake
.  I see the
screen.
Yes, yes, yes, so-so. I
can't touch the screen, so I
can't really use it. What is this? Well
then, Kao should play Scene Gully.
Fishin-Fishin is also good,
though.
Boxing CPU can't be really difficult
Normal or O, then I'll win for now
Gumornin Good morning Good evening
Everyone Ah Guard How do you guard No no No, you're a small fry
Small fry Small fish Small fry Small
fish waste Waste Look, it's
blonde
So waste waste waste Ai I'm
Dio Deo Dio This is Dio
[  [Music] I
made it harder and harder.
[Music] Look, it's
hard mode. It's this dio.
Let's go
dio dio deo.
Excuse me, but please die
No, I'm
going to get hit Guard Guard I
'm going to win, I'm going to win, I'm going to win, I'm going to win, I'm going to win, I'm going to win, I'm going to win, I'm going to win, I'm going to win, I'm going to win, I'm going to win, I'm going to win, I'm going to do it,
champion.  It's
Poupo who is really concentrating.
Oh, it's Poupo.
So wait, Kira. This dio is
amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing.
Thank you cuu cuu Next up is
Impossible
[Music] I'm gonna do it. The
last one is
[Music]
[Music] I don't know if I'm
studying or not. I'm not studying. I
was studying my punches. Hey, he's really smart. He's doing it
one more time.  One more time, one more time, I
'm sorry, but you're so smart, you're so smart,
stop being so stupid.
Calliope didn't punch at all, so I
did it, or should I say it was
really temporary, so I'm
sorry, but it was
fun.  Yes, I have a friend who loves Majin,
but I don't understand the rules at all.
[Music]
Yeah, it's so difficult.
Yeah, game, game, game,
game.
In English, it's called Sally.It
's called
Sally.I like the game Kia-chan.So this
game5.Hold
on a second.Hold on a second.How do I
do it?I'd like to practice a little.Gift
membership.Thank
you.Thank you.Gift
membership.Oh,
how do I do it
?  Are you 5?
Thank you for giving me this, I'm Takakia from Hololive Japan.
Hololive Japan or Japan. That's
great. I'm
Japan. Yes, I'm Japan. Yeah, I'm not Japanese,
but I live in Japan's underwald.
So, I
'm Hololive Japan.  Yeah, I
love Japan so much that I became JP.
Yeah, I'll make a Robbie, thank you. Yeah, that's because I'm
doing it all by myself. I
thought I'd help you. Thank you for helping me.
Yeah, other members are probably streaming it.
Right now, right now,
it's the busiest time. I think it's a little bit
late. It's been a long time since I last played this game.
Wait a minute. Yeah, I'll be waiting. Yeah, I just
came home from a nap.  I
did a little bit of work
on that mailbox, and I went to the post office and got the
postbox, the postbox, and the box.I
got home, but it was so heavy that my
arms felt like jelly jelly.I'm
tired.I'm tired.Thank you for your hard work.  is
Yay, I'm playing online with
Friends. I
think it's good if it's Katakana. I think it's Japanese. I'm
playing
with Friends. I think it's Japanese. I'm playing with Friends. Oh, wait,
wait. That Nintendo
SWITCH subscription has
expired.  Well, you have to pay,
right? Just buy it and
look at it. Why did it get cut? Slowly, okay,
oh, that's it. That's it. I get it, I
get it. I get it. It's a different account.  I
see, it's okay Kari-
chan, how are you doing? Well,
I mean, I may not be feeling well, but
yeah, I can't help it. I'm not feeling
that sluggish this week, so yeah, I
can stream pretty well, so I don't think it's a problem.
But yeah, I won't force it, I won't force it, I won't force it, I won't force it, I wo
n't force it, and when I
looked at the schedule on the Goog calendar, it was all over the place.I
love kukuku streaming, so no, I really
love streaming, which was so boring.
But I also love my body,
and if I
love my knees, I have to take care of them.I'm
eating that super healthy food, and I'm
just walking a little bit, but it's
a bit like Japan.  I have a Cain to say in Japanese,
but uh, what's that? I
know, but it's
not Bobo, but it seems like he's walking around using a certain kind of thing.  It's
like a grandma's cane. Yes, she's a
cute grandma. It
can't be helped. I
have to walk. Yeah, it's important.
But sometimes,
when I sit, my knees hurt.  But it's
going to hurt, so I wo
n't push myself too hard. I don't think the stream will be that long.
Yeah, this week's stream really
might not be that long. I
'll stream it every day. That's right. I hope you
enjoy it.
Something's going wrong with my Nintendo subscription
No, it's sad, wait, why, why,
why, why, I have an account that's being paid by the person who's paying for it,
but it's kind of expensive.  I
don't have any money, or I'm poor. Ah, no, it's
okay. I might not be able to play the game. Yeah, if it doesn't work, I
can't help it.
Ah, N Switch Online, ah, nice, nice,
wa, nice, hachama, hachama, hachama,
please. Please, please, please, please.  I
Just saved me, saved me,
thank you, thank you for coming. I
might come back later. I'll be
waiting. Bye bye, bye, bye, bye, it's a mess, it's a
mess, oh,
what should I do with this? What should I do with this? Yeah, yeah.
And I wonder if it's an
Arend, right now I'm
friends Let's be friends
Let's be friends
Wow, I'm looking forward to it I saw Haa-chan waiting for Saa-chan
At the time Saa's voice was so scary I wonder if I can go?
Yeah, I was worried, but then it
was a different day. It was a good thing. Yeah, I'm glad. My
voice is still okay. I
can't use it. Take a lot of rest. I'm feeling better
. It's good. Wow, I'm glad. Yay,
yay game.  We can play games together.
Send me the code or code.
Okay. That's the friend code. I was
just talking to Kia-chan. Yeah, that's
right. That's right. That's right. That's right. That's right. That's right. That's right. I was talking in Japanese. It was really
interesting.
For some reason, I can speak Japanese. Yes, I can speak English.
Wait a minute
Neka Lend Code
Thank you Okay Okay Um, it
was really funny, but what were you talking about?
Calliope recently had that surgery, so
thank you for talking about that. Thank you, don't push yourself too hard.  That's what I
was talking about, but I'm not pushing myself. Ah, I see. I'm not pushing myself. I'm not
pushing myself. It's
okay. I'm glad you're fine. My
knee hurts a bit, so I'm tired.
Yeah, it hurts because I had knee surgery, so I can't help it, yeah, yeah,
yeah, that's right, my friend, don't
move too much. Don't walk too much. Yes, I'm
sure. Yeah, I'm
not pushing myself too hard. Yuko, take it slow.  I
have it, so there's no problem. I'll send a friend.
Please wait a moment. Aze,
water, roo, hun,
hun, reest. Okay, I sent you a friend.
Thank you.
No, okay, I'll wait in the lobby
Hey, Gorilla Gorilla
, Gorilla, Gorilla, Gorigori, Okay, I
love Donkey Kong, Donkey Kong,
Donkey Kong, you don't like Monkey, this is a gorilla, lol
Thank you for your help,
Gorilla, wait a minute, okay, my voice is a little
low,
sorry, it's Nesoka-chan's voice.  It was really big,
so I lowered it a little bit, but it's okay now.
Yeah, this feels good, it feels good, the amount is good.
It's because it's big, yes, it's true, it sings, it sings, it sings, it's good, so it's true that the quantity is really good, so it's amazing.Online friends are amazing.I choose this or that.I'm looking forward to playing this game.I'm looking forward to seeing what games I can play.
Okay, what
? Let's do it. Okay, let's play. What game do I want to play? What should I do? What should I do? I
can do it. I'll leave it to you. What game do I want to play?  I'll
leave it to you, but I like sailing the most.
But how many times have I done this? The
first round is the one that says, "
I've only done it once."
Even if it's true, the rules are correct.  I know,
so I can do it.Okay, this is
luck.It's definitely management.If that's the case, then it's
the worst.Do this, do this.I
want to do it.Okay, let's do it.But I guess I
forgot a little bit.It's okay.  Let's
confirm, confirm, confirm, ooh, yeah, that's it.
Slowly
and finally, finally, finally Oh, okay, oh, wow,
wow, wow, wow, I
have my 456, no, 456 is true, ah, I'm
worried, I'm worried, I don't know
what to do. This is me, worried.  Oh,
wait a minute, wait a minute,
it's Calliope.
Um, are you going to play it in 444? Wait a minute, no.  The
strong A4 is really good, so it's gonna be bad. Yeah
, Hudai 4's Hudai, yeah, yeah, CC
C Okay, sure then, 4 Fufufu A4,
okay. Go ahead, wait, wait, you
can do this 3 times. 3 times, 3 times.  I
chose this, ah, I didn't know, it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay.  Don't
miss it, don't miss it, don't lose, don't lose, don't lose, it's too bad to lose. How do you
say that in English?
Course ah coos, ah that was was
estrate,
yup. Nice, Wow, that's good. Senpai, it's okay. I won't
lose. There's no way I won't lose. I won't lose.  Soooo
nice
666666, oh 6
and
let's go 66
Owamowamo
Nice
go
Maga again 235 It's the
worst
hacha 6  Let's
put it out 111
So 3331123A3 I do
n't understand,
but this is a rule, but Calliope is
a bit clumsy, so it's
blue, blue, blue, blue,
so if you don't understand, let me know. I should have
made it high. No problem.
Ok.  I'll definitely win, no problem. Do you
think Chama can win? Nonono,
Chama will win, but I don't want to.  It's
still my second time, so I guess it's okay. Good luck,
Senpai.
[Music] You can
aim for a straight, starting from 12341234.
Even if you stop, you can still S straight go go go.
Well, okay, yeah,
yeah, 5, 5,555,
2344, yeah, yeah, maibibi,
straight.
Yeah, I'm in trouble, it's true, I'm in trouble, I'm in trouble, I'm in trouble, I'm like a Shinigami, I'm like a Shinigami.  ]
Please, I won't stop.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's this one. This is amazing.
Okay, wow, oh my.
Gulley is amazing, he's so good, he's so strong.
Woof wan, what should I do? Woof wan, woof, woof, wan, wan, wan, go, go, go, straight.
Seriously? I
didn't know, I can go! Oh, I'll
give you 5 of the same numbers, 5 of them.
Eiwakapi-chan has 3 aces.
Oh, I'm sure. I wonder what we're going to do.
4455445
444544 Can we
make it to a full house? Let's aim for a full house.
Boxing, uh, boxing, um,
cann4, 4, 4,
4, 4, I don't know.
Arranging them, arranging them, arranging them, ah, I see, that's
right, that's right. Well, I
did a lot of air brushing.
It was a lot of fun. It was fun. It was fun. Yeah,
what should I do? No, this is really garbage.
1216 is true. 66 has disappeared, but 6666 has also disappeared.
But yeah, Huda  I heard it might even become a full house.
What should I do? It's okay,
Gimme. 1234 Wait a minute. I
made a mistake. I made a mistake. I made a mistake.
Ta-ah nice nice nice nice oh that's great I
don't really know what to do
But yeah, that
's right, I don't have 4, so I
still have chairs left, so I'll leave 66 and
roll another number, so if it's a good number, I'll choose again.I see.
A full house is also a full house, it's
true, then 55555566
Hugo, stop
it, please stop it, stop it,
oh, it's the worst,
no, it's really
the worst
, it's a lie, stop it, stop it, stop it.  You
can also choose a stop or a chair. Is that a
good choice? Let's just choose a chair this time. It'll
be a good point, right? I'll
choose. I don't know yet. 64 and 62.
Yeah, that's right. Oh, it's scary, it's scary, my seniors are strong.
Hey, it's 6.
6666  Yo, I don't want to take it. It's a waste of stuttering.
234 Yeah, do your best. Good luck.
666666 Wow
[laughing]  I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.  I'm
here again,
there's
five left.
No, no, this is this,
this
is a temporary reverse, it's a temporary reverse, isn't it?
Eh, that and that, but now that I think about it, Calliope, maybe she
's M?  If you'll
excuse me, please die,
but I'm not sure if it's masochistic or masochistic, but girls are usually masochistic.Yes, it's true that
sometimes, yes, sometimes
there may be a great s, but yeah, that's true.  I
got attacked because I'm a M, oh yeah, it's
like a naughty, naughty story Oh
my gosh, I'm so excited Furuha Is it Full House
again, but I don't want Full House anymore There's no
more, there's no more 4 is a lot 44
4 I like it, I like it  It's the same, same as
Calliope, same, same, I turned 12, now I have
3 thoughts. Is there a
bonus? When you
reach 63, you get an extra 35 bonus.
Oh, I see.  You can also
save up a lot of the upper part of this and
get a bonus. Ah yes yes I see.
That's a bit strange and strange.
Well, I'll do it with 5 Ogo O 5. I'm
sorry for Gochis,
Fubu. Wow.  I don't have 33 yet,
so I'll just go with 3.
Treat 3, that 4,
Oo 4, there's no more, there's no more
,
right?
Okay, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!  My
hand hurts. Are you
okay?
Is it okay? It's a shame. It's a shame.
Gogogogogogogo nice go go go go
Nice go go go stubborn, even my luck
is really good, my senior is good, good, good, right,
right, right? What should I do?
Now that I've run out of luck with Pechan, that's right, I'm
sure it's quite expensive. That's
amazing.  Chao Let's
Goretz Goretz Goretz Gow
Ooo, I can do that full house
Allas or canon
kang, but I was a sex
Stop, nana, no zero, no,
no,
point, Calliope-chan is alive, yes, Haya-
san, yes, it's okay, it's okay,
that's fine, that's no problem,
that's a little, that
's a great face, but
that's dead, don't die, don't die,
please don't die.
I'm alive lol I'm
alive I'm alive I'm alive I'm alive
Live
Nice, I don't have to worry about
it anymore It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous  It's so
bad, Momo, it's so bad,
but I'm
also Seth, so
wow, oh my gosh, why didn't I choose it?
What is El Straight
El Straight?
El Straight 2345 Yes, 2456 or
12345 Ah, I see, I can go with 1 or 6.
Ah, oh, this is good. I can wait for both of them. I
did it. It was a shame, but it was 1. It's such a shame. It's so bad. It's
amazing. It's
so bad. 30  That's the point.
Nono, this is strong after all. It's
going straight. It's coming! Don't do it. Dodge and be careful behind it.  I have to be
careful.
Okay, 2222 That's right, I don't have 2 yet.
Hey, Wow, oh my gosh, I'm still going. It's so good, I'm scared. I'm
scared. It's so boring.
Why
did I erase the straight B earlier? No
, I can't do it. If I get it, I can go.
That's right, Full House was the strongest
. It's the 4th house. It's really tough. It's
really
tough. Akadosu is the one who shakes everything. Yeah, that's
true.
Ono,
no, it's okay, it's okay La
Kirakira Kiraki ki Oh, I'm here, please
God, please, please, I'm here
now, I'm crazy right now, do
n't mess around, I could have gone
[Music]
But that's not there,
haha  I'll take it in 1. I wonder
if it's coming. I wonder if it's really
coming. I might have to wait a little longer. Yo,
this is really fun. It's
fun. No, no, I'll do it
one more time.
Ha,
no, I won't do it one more time, but I'll lose.
This is really interesting, showdown, showdown, come on, come on, come on, come on, it might be impossible, maybe it's impossible, oh wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wan possible I'm going, oh, I'm dead, I'm going, I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead, I think I'm dead [laughter] This is it.  I wonder if I can overkill, Oba
Kill overkill? I want to do MAGA. I
want to do it. I'm
here. I'm almost there.
This is too extravagant. Hey, hey,
hey.
Hey, come on!
Strikes and keys are fun, but if you're too strong, it'll turn against you
. It's fun! Wow, that was fun, senpai.
Congratulations! Wait, wait, wait, wait,
this is just too cool. I
want to play Calliope-chan's favorite thing.  Oh, wow, that's amazing. I
know Black Jack. I've heard of Black Jack. I'm sure I
can do it. I'd like to check it out just once.
But I checked the loose rules.
Congratulations!  It was really fun, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was
awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome, it was awesome.
Jack
Bra, that's cool, oh, that's cool. The name is
cool. It looks like Calliope. That
's right.
Okay, God's favorite game. This is just the last minute. It's a
tiki race. It's the last minute. But look, I'm aiming
for the last minute.
Looks good, so let's go. This guy
lost. Oh, we lost. We lost
because that dealer got that 2121.
Yeah yeah, that player got that 20,
so yeah, it was a little low. Yeah, it was
lower than that deer's 21, so yeah, that's
what I mean.  The dealer is strong, the
dealer is trying to match the dealer's numbers,
yeah, yeah, that's what I mean.Okay, okay,
okay, but Deira is heavy and I
have to stop.
Well, the rules of this game are
a bit weird. I've played this before.
Okay, weird, weird. Let's go. Okay,
so Calliope is all
in.  I'll
do it in units of 10, all
in, yeah, oh yeah, all in, oh yeah, it
's not bad, it's not bad, it's
low and low, it's better to hit it, wait,
wait, wait, this is the hint, the hint is low, no.  It's
better to wait and head again. That person is 10 or so. Yeah, it
's still a hit. I want more of this. I can
go even further. Wow, stand. But
what if there are 20 people in 20? I'm
definitely going to stand.  It's better to stand. You
can't beat people in their 20s. But you
're right. They play a lot of coins.
Yeah,
right. Nice nice nice yay. Wow.
Amazing Una Nauna Fufufu This is also luck, luck,
isn't it? Calliope once again
stole Calliope-chan's carp.
No, it's a real song, so she won't do something like this. No,
this time she's Orun. Why are you going to do it? All
in, why are you all in?  It's
negative. It
's negative. So I'm 100. Is this all
in?
Yeah, okay. It's a chance. It's money.
If it's 11, I think it's better to double down,
but Dao, oh, double down. It's
not that bad, so it's fine. It's still hot.
Burst. What's the
burst you want? Is that dealer going to
pass something like that on 12?
Yeah,
if it's more than 22021, it'll be useless. It's
true that I'm going to the stand.
Bust. Look, for example, this or this one. Ahh, it's barely
safe. Yeah, it's just barely safe.
Safe, minus 200, uh,
okay, no problem, strong, no problem,
strong, lucky, lucky, F-word.
Wow, I'm dead, Bakiol
Best [ __ ] Boy Ah [ __ ]
Boy [ __ ] Boy Good Word, it's everyone,
so everyone is Fukuboy.
Oh, it's no problem, I'm all in.
300 Okay, okay, if you're going to go all in,
then I'll go all in. Oh,
of course, let's go let's go meme.
Manny, mama, I have
n't been able to make it, but
ah, it's better to do a good stand at 18, no, I
'll have to attack a little.
Leave it to me I'm going to do it. It's a no -hit hit hit hit stand sun, so I'm going to go back
Ok, it's already a minus.
From now on, the minus final round,
final
run.
What should I
do? Please, Nada 15, what
should I do? 4, oh, I'm so
strong,
Raki Wowhi
, oh no, it's too close, do
n't do it, oh
, yay,
minus 400 MYS.
400 What
was this? It's so bad, I can't help it. We
lost on good terms and lost on good terms. That
was blackjack. That
was black. It was fun, black, it was fun
. Hey, senpai, thank you for playing with me. Kao,
Chanka-chan, I
want Chan to buy it.  I want you to buy it. It's okay.
The other day, when I was doing something by myself, I was
buying so much. I was buying so much. I was
winning so much. I became rich. It's
okay. I'm glad I'm rich. It's okay.  I've
been playing Convex Town for quite some time today,
right? Yeah, yeah, I've been doing it for about an hour and a half,
but I'll do a little more. I
thought it was someone from earlier, so I checked it out. I see.
Yeah, that's right.
If you're not the same person, I'll stop for a moment.I see.Okay,
okay,
yeah.Thank you for coming.It
was really fun.Thank you.  It's an incredible stroke of
luck. It
's an incredible stroke of luck.
Thank you. No, no, this time, let's
talk in English. Let's
stream in English. Let's
stream in English. See you
soon, see you again.  Bye bye bye
bye acha chacha cha acha maba
bye machi
maji macha maji maji macha macha
That friend request was from Chiara Let's go
Kiaretz
Go, it was a new account, Takakarika-
chan, and we weren't friends yet.
Yeah, yeah, check it out. Please wait a little bit. Hey, it's a
request.
Please be my friend. Orama pink. Is that a
llama? Oh yeah. That's right. It's not a llama. It's an
alpaca. Yeah, it's an alpaca.  Think of it as an alpaca.I
want it.Yes, it's an alpaca.Yes,
it's an alpaca.I
love it.Have you ever touched an alpaca?
Yes, that old lady.
My grandpa had a ranch,
so I had a parka.Oh
yeah, that's right.That's awesome.That's because they
made that kind of wool.That's right.That's
right.It's nice.It
was really soft.Yeah, that's
nice.  I went to an alpaca farm in Japan, and a
baby alpaca threw up on my face. Oh my
god, it's
so cute!
No, it's too
smelly, that Kari-chan, that alpaca's saliva. Have you ever sniffled at that alpaca's spit? It smells so bad, you really don't notice it at all, and
when it gets on your body, it never goes away. The smell
stays with you forever. Seriously? I don't
know.  It stinks, it stinks.
Oh, I want to see you again, but I want to know a little bit.
Oh yeah, I want to ride an alpaca. Hey, I
can do it.
Humans can do it, but adults can't.  I
think even adults can go there,
but I'm riding Minecraft, so it's playing Minecraft. It's a
great game.
Well, what should I do?
I don't know much about card games. Other than black tea.
Other than playing peacocks, what should I do?
Tennis.  I'm good at boxing, but
that's the left left,
but that's right, right left, right right right right right or
5th right right or 5th.  I've
forgotten how to compare them, but I'd like to
try
Japan's Japanese Connect 4, but it
's Connect 5, so I'll give
it a try.  I
think this game is right. It's an
easy game, Miko-senpai,
Suba-senpai. I love you so much, so I'm going to play it. Does it go first? Okay, okay. What should I do?
Come on, come back,
beat me
up. Hmm, I see.
That's right,
Kari-chan, look at the Shogun's army,
Shogun. After Fallout, the Shogun looks like that.
Where's Amazon Prime? The Shogun is on
Disney Plus, oh, Disney Plus. It's so
good. He's really good. His
crit is really high. His crit is high.  -Eh, a story about a samurai.Well,
there's a little bit of real history in Japan, like a samurai, but yeah, yeah,
yeah, it's not a true story.Oh, seriously,
what should I do?Ah, I've seen Japan  There are some
Japanese people who are interested in that.I
recommend Kana Sono Shogun.People who like history
might be interested in that.That's
interesting.That's why that
actor is so Japanese.  Yes, there are Japanese
actors. Yes, they are Japanese. That's great. That's really good. It's
beautiful. Look at the beautiful elephants.
What should we do? Oh,
how.
It's popular. Maybe more people overseas know about this drama about the general. It
's on Disney Plus, so I
feel like people overseas know about it.
Yeah, that's amazing. I think it's Goth of the Sea.  I
love that kind of game, so I
'd like to point it out. Yeah, that's good. It seems like a good
match. The history is interesting. The Japanese language is
really interesting. The Japanese language is really interesting. It's
really interesting.
Act's Japanese is a native.  or native
Of course, yes, I won.
Nekari-chan won.
If I were to put a tag on it, I would have talked about it so much. So,
congratulations. Thank you.
Let's play darts. Let's play dois. Yeah, sometimes,
so we'll watch it on Netflix.  I was
watching all those movies, and sometimes I'd see
that Japanese act speaking that Japanese, and I'd
think that the person over there isn't a native speaker, and
lately I've been watching something like Jiwoo, for example.
Yeah, I thought that was going to happen,
but it turned out that they were all Japanese.The
main actors, San Hai, and the other actors all
said they wouldn't do this job unless they were Japanese, so they all became
Japanese.  Oh, I see. You're
speaking Japanese properly. It's really nice. I'll
check it out. Yeah, that's really nice.
Nice. Yeah, I chose this or that.
This isn't bad. This isn't ad.  I'm
good at this too, so I'm good at this too. Seriously? No, I've
played it before. I've done
it before, but I'm a bit bad at it. It
's easy. It's easy. It's really easy.
It's easy. It's a children's game. It's a children's
game. It's a low-budget
game.  Yeah, it's a low-budget game. It was a long time ago. I did
n't have the money. So, what should I do?
Is this the right one? I see. I see, I'm doing the same thing.
Stop,
stop.  Even
if I stop, there's nothing I can do about stopping there.
No
problem. I don't know. I know. Yeah, that's it. Do you remember that box? It doesn't have to be that box of mine. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, okay, I know
.  Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
this is the time of preparation, right?
Okay, is this good? What should I
do?
[Music]
Who is this? Let's
sell it now, try it, try
it. I don't know yet. I don't know yet. It's
a little too early.
No, no, no, no, it
might be Kari-chan.No, no, no, no, it might be Kari-chan.No, Kari-chan is kind of blue, so it's super
hot, so oh yeah, that's right.It's
not, and it's hard to
do it while talking like, oh, I can't believe it.It's really
difficult.
Hey, hey, it's
wrong,
stop it,
stop it. I'm watching anime right now. I
'm watching anime. What anime are you watching? Monster,
monster, monster, random monster, oh
8, what the hell are you watching?  I
've forgotten Japanese for a while,
it's really interesting Kushiro, so I know Baku Monogatari,
of course I know, I've seen it, I've seen
it, I've seen it all, yeah, yeah, no, I have
n't seen it yet.  It
hasn't been out for a long time, but it's finally coming this summer. I'll
see, I'll see, I'll see. I
didn't know that I watched Chanba Monogatari that much. I don't know
if I really like it,
but I just like it and
think it's interesting.  I really love Araragi-kun, so
Araragi-kun is my favorite,
so I guess who's my favorite out of all of them?
It's a lie, it's a
lie. My butt is also Nadeko. It's true, it's true.
Nice Yeah, there are a lot of people who like Chibahara, and the same goes for Hanekawa, but there aren't many people who say they like Nako the most.I don't think so.Actually, I really like her voice, too.Yes, I'm happy.  The diapers are the same,
right? I
used to watch a lot of them when I was in high school. I want to see them. I
also like Kula, which comes out a little later on.
That silver gray gray, yeah, yeah, I'm
sorry, I can't concentrate for a second,
please stop talking, tell me the presses.
Who do you like next? I guess I forgot. I
know that. That guy's
hair color is really cute.  I think he's
saying something like "Peace Peace Yay Yay",
but his voice doesn't have any emotion in it at all.It's
so cute.
That's right, it's cute, so no, I'll stop. Also,
Kuji-chan is cute, right? Give
up, give up. Snail Snail is cute. Well, let's do it. It's over. Oh, wait, wait, I see. Oh, let's
start. Let's
start.
Even the opening is so wide. It's
amazing the difference.  Over I should be
able to stop at some point,
but I can't really do it. Let's go! You spoke English. You spoke English just now.
This game's delivery failed.
Look, this is a safe place. Where is the safe place? I don't know.
It's over, it's over, it
's over
. But I've already won. I
bought it. I can't help it. You did it. You did it. You did a good job.  The way he
speaks is
so shitty and
empty.
Well, I can't help it.
No, no, this last one is also Kia, right? Oh, that's
a little different.
Oh well, if you
leave things as they are, chaos will ensue. Even if it's pink or red, it's blue. That's why I made Kari-chan's pink color mine. Stop it,
stop it. From now on, Kari-chan
will have blue hair instead of that pink color.
No, it doesn't suit me, it does
n't suit me, it doesn't suit me right now, Okari-chan, yeah, I'm going to
prepare for my broadcast, so thank you for playing with me,
but I
can't help it.  I
can't help it, I'm pretty bad at my luck.Every
single one was fun.Playing,
that's right.I'm listening.Thank you for your hard work.Please do your best in
streaming.Thank you,
Kari-chan too.Take your time,
bye-
bye.  It was fun, everyone. I'm
glad I was able to do it properly, everyone. I
had a lot of fun with all the different aspects of the game. Oh, Calliope, I'm super sleepy though. I'm
sleepy.  I
wonder if I'll sleep again Even after the broadcast Hey,
everyone, that Calliope is a mess. I have some
news for you. As you may know,
Calliope's new album 2nd
major album is called Phantomime.
Please buy it.
There are all kinds of wonderful costumes,
but that calliope is the best so far.I
think it's a great piece.The song is really great.I want it
to be the best.Look at the jacket art.
Thank you very much for your wonderful work, Mr. Ray. Thank you so much for everything.
And when I bought it this week, there was one with that signature on it.
That
standard edition. That Calliope
website.
Yes, I can buy a new one. Yes, I can
speak Japanese. I can't buy a fortune teller for this week only. I can't buy a fortune teller
next week.
So I guess I should win soon. That
little sign of Calliope.
It's a little sign.
But yeah, I think it's nice. Yeah, it's
not the main jacket, it
's the alternative jacket. This is, um, this one.
Wait a minute, um, Limitaire. I'm
going to sign this or this. Yeah, it's tiny. I hear it's
going to be signed, so please buy it this week.
Yes, please check it out.
And then there's the
summary section below this video. Wait a minute, did I
forget
?
Wait a minute. I
forgot the summary section below this video.
It's in the summary column. I'm glad I remembered. It's correct. I'm glad I'm really bad at Japanese, but I'll get better again. Yes, check it out. Click on that URL. Buy it. Calliope's new album, and that
messed up. It's
so good.  There's a song in it, so I wonder
if the anime song is already on.I
want to see it just once.  I
want you to do it, so please. I'm
working really hard, so it's cool. Thank you. You're
really cool. Thank you, everyone. Thank you for
all the wonderful comments. I
really appreciate it. Thank you so much.
Thank you. Please look
forward to Calliope. I'm working hard on it, so there's still more
Since I'm doing that lesson, I have to record it, so I
'm still working hard on it.It's a really good
album, so I
want everyone to check it out.So
that's it, that's it for today.  I
wonder if I'll do a Kao broadcast. I'd like to sing in a laid-back, chilled-out kind of way. It's just a warm-up.
Yes, that's right. I haven't been singing at all lately,
so I'm going to do some other work after a while. I
had fun today, right?  Everyone,
thank you very much for listening.Let's play again.Also,
please look forward to Kao.Yes, it
was a mocha operation.Thank you for your hard work, everyone.
See you again,
take care of yourself, bye,
take care of yourself
Peace bye again
[Music]
Hey,
thank you, that's fine too, but pa
[Music]
HH