[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
d
clap your
hands clap your
[Music]
hands your
hand
[Music]
oh my God so
loud
[Music]
wait there we go
K it's not froggy W
waa
psych okay no it's still kind of loud
for
[Music]
me
H
settings where's
music there okay k
oh you thought I was gone
forever don't worry let me explain to
you what
happened this is almost like an April
Fool's joke the the whole froggy waa
week how did you survive okay okay let
me tell
you so last
week yeah when she took over basically
what happened is she took her water gun
and she sat me like I was already
sitting on a chair I was doing my office
work and she comes out of nowhere
somehow she broke out of her aquarium
somebody must have helped her must have
helped her and then she goes up to me
and she pulls my head back and she water
boards me with her water gun water
pistol who could have known that you can
do it with a water pistol
gun and then she thought I was dead but
I actually went into a trauma uh not
trauma coma I went to do coma for a
whole week thank God I'm awake
now can't believe that she took over my
whole Chanel for a whole week again that
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah are you guys okay has she
treated you
okay I feel so bad for leaving you guys
for a
while I had no choice I was in the coma
she came out of
nowhere you had one job excuse me what
did what did you just
say just a little shaken up she was cute
though don't be deceived don't be so
simply
deceived think with your brain not with
your
but uh I have seen that she has put up
froggy waa
merchandise The Audacity Of using one of
my threee in a year merchandise creation
slots using one of those up to make her
own merchandise when this is not even
her
Channel yeah the Easter event would have
gone so much better if I hosted it sadly
she took over that
too and thus the chaos ensued just like
last year how come she she managed maybe
last year she had so much fun in the
Easter thing where I let her out for for
one day I think then she was like oh
okay next year I want to I want to do
that again so that's maybe why she had
her aim on this week in
particular but I think her plan was to
never go back again
but I do not allow anyway I'm still
advertising the frogi waa merch because
you know as a little bit of a
compensation for the mess she has left
me with and for the
acts of attempted
murder that she thought
succeeded I must take some money from
all of this from this situation no I'm
not forwarding the money to her yeah to
me if that's what you mean
I mean it was going to go to my bank
account anyway because she she just uh
thought she can use my bank account no
no no no no no the froggy
waa this is not how it works it's not
her earnings no I I I created this
monster
so she will
have to stay in her glass container that
she fears so much much for a while
longer and perhaps we will have to think
of some higher security measures from
now on and yeah and those will be paid
perhaps also with the froggy wild and
merchandise speaking of froggy wild and
merchandise I don't have
um I don't have merch picks of
everything yet because I'm still trying
to improve the hoodie especially they're
sending me samples of how things are and
I'm like I don't want it like this can
you make it more like
this especially cuz the the color wasn't
really what I wanted like it was um way
more
uh burning your eyes
green than in the illustration
originally uh so we're working on that
but I got a merch pick of the keychain
do you want to
see
my
dream you want to
see let me show
you okay so key
chain cute look at
her it looks like this it's properly
seethrough
yeah she do be
dangling on on a really really thin
string AKA metal
but I have my eyes on you I will not let
you go you guys have to help me contain
her this another
picture totally Yo's Hands by the
way so yeah looks looks pretty I think M
cute it's pretty big now looking at it
on your hand
covering like I guess four fingers if he
would put them together or she I don't
know pretty
big maybe put it on your bag or
something link is in the
description please go get it I heard I
was told and I think yeah the the plushy
is doing very well but don't miss out on
the keychain and the hoodie either
guys already ordered thank you ordered
everything thank you shipping just got
cheaper
oh oh really why apparently shipping got
cheaper let's
go
didn't know you could see stats for each
item like that what what are you talking
[Music]
about get the thing in America open oh I
don't think so I don't think so
something happened with the shop and
some regions have better shipping now oh
nice timing it's more International now
they just made a deal do you think so oh
oh check it out guys
international
shipping what a de not Europe
though I'm so sorry guys I'm also in
Europe I I I advocate for you
guys there was a notice about oh there
was a notice about it
okay nice that sounds good okay so today
we'll play Holo X
break I have some tea here which I'll
probably
need trying to also fix my stomach
issues I've had stomach issues for like
a week now
damn but I had I had the
probiotic but in German we say multi
biotic uh
yogurt
uh hoping that will help and I've been
drinking some tea hoping that will help
too I might also have to do with um like
switching
Cuisines like when but you normally like
I don't really have that though I go to
Japan I eat
food it's okay on my
tummy I go back so same my toe my toe is
like only the tip of it is still still
purple it's really a small area I guess
the tip only the tip um but it's okay um
I can
walk I can walk I can
[Music]
walk those [\h__\h] strawberries
yeah those [\h__\h] strawberries I will
never forgive
them okay so we play this game I think
it might be a little bit difficult so
I'm a bit scared um wait are you
supposed to play this with a controller
I hope
not I guess even with Holo here it was
like oh controller is nice but you don't
have
to it's so funny to me that there's an
anop
phobia thing real bad lag what what do
you mean controller is
Banner keyboard's fine okay cuz like I
don't have a controller prepared right
now
U okay
[Music]
lagging in US
n don't don't lag EU is good okay for
once EU is
superior being treated better by
YouTube w j k l i j k l r o
j k l I
okay I didn't change
anything
dream
controller wait okay I have a
PlayStation controller right next to me
but the moment I plug it in it will it
will do something
funny okay which of these cables works
oh none of
these clap your
hands youb
[Music]
cable
okay had to get
unel sure okay going to plug it
in
oh and thus I stopped hearing the
music
yeah there it is I fixed it already
let's [\h__\h] go we can play the
game if anything else is weird let me
know did my microphone change I hope not
but then oh it's already working
whoa
uh is is X okay and this
okay then let's begin uh I know there's
no safe I know there's no save feature
voice is okay all
my you should change it to I think it is
PS layout or okay well it says those are
Xbox but can I change
it yeah it says PS5
[Music]
controller but then it's not a why does
it say a my
dream press a to join why why would I
press a
yeah so yeah it's a game that where you
can't join
uh where you can't save uh apparently
you can't I could have played this
online but I I I was like uh I don't
know I I I I I'm just going to play it
alone for
now
and and I heard uh and this speaks to me
very much cuz I was going to do that
anyway uh wait stop
moving
no how do I get to press
X oh there we go oh that was weird
something was
weird I was pressing the same button but
it went to the one below yeah I heard n
is the way to go because she can heal so
if you if you play solo she's pretty
good and I was going to choose her
anyway
so
[Music]
I don't really know what kind of game
this is uh I don't know wait why why two
players why I don't want two
players no no how to
start oh it's so confusing it
doesn't do what I wanted to
do uh
uh I I I do press X again and add
somebody
why square square nothing
happens triangle nothing happens maybe
this button
no this button
no I have a controller that's what I'm
using right now duh and now but now for
example Circle also doesn't work maybe I
should restart the
game
maybe it's like bugging around CU I
attached the controller in the middle of
the
game H your dual sense controller is not
supported by this game Steam input will
translate the device so you will be able
to play the game but you may not see the
GLS that's okay that match your
controller that's
fine
blowing the
cartridge I maybe they think it's the
keyboard
mhm could
be do I have to watch this can't skip it
I already watched it
before the same time news has gone
public about a mysterious group causing
havoc referring to themselves as hols
secret society they have announced the
initiation of their plans to take over
the world was there supposed to be sound
right now Escape skip okay oh I think
they're supposed to be sound it went it
reverted again I guess
why there you
go I hate my computer I hate everything
that has to do with computers
aha now it looks
different
aha okay how to play this game welcome
to Holo xra fight your way through the
enemies and stop the secret society
schemes press uh d-pad to move around on
the field well the joystick works too
right press X to use your normal attack
which I hope is really X okay joystick
works oh okay this is is this attack cuz
X isn't working wait wait a this is
oh nice
n oh nice AOE too like the hit hits like
quite a lot of hit
boxes no the coins the coin collection
sound oh you found the field weapon
field weapons can be picked up
immediately used to attack enemies hold
X to pick uh a field weapon up while
holding field weapon press X oh I have
to hold it to swing it or press a to
throw it
okay oh nice
song yagle
Missing You can change the PS layout ah
it's whatever it's always I always have
to get used to this field weapons have
limited durability so they will break
after a number of uses but they're
powerful never miss a chance to smash a
rock on an
enemy
so what's a what what what could a be
maybe oh okay found
it you have to turn
first you can't change direction while
you're hitting I think it seems to me oh
a considerable item that looks like my
sword but I don't think it is because
the colors are
different these are Health items that
can be used at any time from your
inventory wait who's who's whose weapon
is this m that's so funny cuz I just
dreamt about
M she showed up at my doorstep out of
nowhere crying and I'm like who whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa why are you
here and she's like I just I just needed
to go to
someone and then like she told me about
some some crazy [\h__\h] that happened and
I'm like oh my God okay don't worry you
can stay here for a couple days and and
I I'll cancel my stream or whatever
reschedule it or so
they try to yeah comfort her and take
care of
herh oh I see the kfp post are in the
back
nice the pitches must have been
bad we lost the stream oh my God come on
M yeah all the way to
Europe so and then use the lb and RB
button to swap between items then y to
use the selected item which maybe is
triangle you can also hold the Y button
to drop the current selected item if you
need more room oh my God
much Additionally you can set items to
LT RT buttons When selecting and I hold
the LT or RT button to set it to that
slot
uh what why do I have to do that once it
is sent you can press the respective
quick item button to use it
kill me muchto I can't read I don't want
to
read uh quicker
use two two quick
slots why do you H us not quick slots
then once it set you can press the
respective quick item button to use it
regardless of the currently selected
item what use these slots to yeah
whatever I I'll understand
eventually oh ability
[Music]
unlock oh Nissa had the same opinion
it's just like brain Overlord man
Overlord overload you unlock to Power
Attack hold the x button until your
character glows wide then release a
button the button to ex execute a Power
Attack every character's Power Attack
may have different effects and they may
save you in okay so hold the x button
whichever that is we'll find out um
oh wait what H that's not it right what
is it is it but she's not really doing
anything
different
longer how do I use the the item
now m z what are you doing here o
baseballs I don't know they weren't
really useful in Dave the diver
so wait there's no enemies left
ah
ah I did [\h__\h]
read not my fault if my brain can't
comprehended
she kind of dropped
backwards ah they can like stop me from
doing it
no shootting
again there we
go okay damn you really can't let them
hit
you they'll interrupt you okay I think
there's no more enem enemies or is there
Pebble scatters five panels in front hi
maai cute she's running with the bread
in her mouth oh this is this is this
gives me Yakuza Vibes like being able to
pick up items like
that oh
n this is Yakuza breaker mode oh [\h__\h]
no wait no I'm doing it wrong no
no leave me
alone there we
go dang my inventory is full though okay
how the [\h__\h] do I use
items yeah yeah what how I can't
see what
how oh
oh
uh okay
okay
uh ah
[\h__\h] oh I don't know what I'm
doing
Miss as you've reached level three
you've unlocked okay this first ability
did I get full HP now ability one can be
used by pressing the a button see this
is also a brain hurt because I I have to
translate or find out by myself what the
button will be for me x button thank you
I love you so
much press the x button for Ability one
after activating an ah that button was
empty anyway wasn't
it okay oh am I healing myself right now
amazing
nice I did hit someone with
that yo those
bodyguards recovers 25 HP okay nice help
how oh by hitting you I guess oh you
joined me let's go a kind of does they
play in her pajamas
cute I think those are um Cannon because
she
oo nice she drew them
before tell people what her pajamas
are what can I not see I miss Jimmy
there was a
chicken nah no
way where was it like walking past I saw
kfp that's what you
mean where ooh ah
ah ah Jimmy is
missing right next to
yo did you see p yeah I saw and I know
she mentioned me I was like oh
yeah uh oh [\h__\h]
uh no you can't turn like fast enough
nice oh yeah oh
oh
nice oh what I thought that works
differently what the [\h__\h] nice okay I'm
I'm getting the hang of
it yeah she likes me like when she was
asked which members besides pi obviously
that she knows she said oh yeah for
example MAA and Ki those are the ones
she mentioned first besides the her genm
of course what is
this rapid fire nice shito coffee M
increases damage by 20% wow healing orb
ah do I have to hit it I don't think she
watches me actually no no no but how do
you how do you use is
it that's my wait wasn't that my that's
my special ability so I used that up hi
oh my
godo
together oh cuz I'm full
ah but he
wasn't what is
this oh was that
healing oh boys love boys love come back
no give me give me the item I want to
see it oh we'll see it eventually oh God
more nice oh I like using these items
you get a lot of them
huh oh what was it we just slap him with
a
book hope so that oh what the [\h__\h]
equipment equipments are random gear
that grants different special effects to
change the way oh look at the the the H
promise boys at the
top those are
funny where's where is uh oh it's the
it's the host
club where's
cie or should I say what was it Kevin no
Calvin Calvin I guess and my honey is
not coming
out froggy wa must have used up all my
honey King this close
enough a SE
man uh uh change the your way your
character repl equipment will come with
randomized stats based on its Rarity the
higher the rity the more bonus stats it
will grant further more further more you
will be able to upgrade equipment so
that it will grant even more stats be
sure to experiment with different kinds
of equipment setups I'm sure there's a
meta
though they don't let him into the host
collab not after the incident oh I think
I've heard did you hear Calvin and ha's
new voices they're new I watched the
collab for like 5
Seconds just tapped into
it they sounded like always like the
same to me they have new
voices what they used AI
voices oh really what I mean oh I see
they Chang it in the middle or maybe I
heard the old one still the old one was
always you know the the the usual um
making your voice much lower with the
with the go XLR is like
very the sound of it is oh
heavy so if it sounds better now that's
nice they sound actually believable oh
[\h__\h] let's go so characters have six
following stats HP attack speed death
crit luck
okay I want to can I kick something out
maybe I can I can eat this pick up that
Reaper's cloak uh are there items I
guess because there's no saving and if
you die you start again from the
beginning that means that the items are
only in that very run that you're
in probably oh another one that needs
help let's
go ooh
oh nice this is fun so far I like
it oh ah wait this is how that works it
protects me from hits I
guess oh and I see it running out I
think oh let's go level up but then it
suddenly disappeared the the books
disappeared just like in Holo
cure Oh e be painting s i s by next to
her
cute oh already another one that one was
close to the other one hi oh my God it's
so
cute
hey yo cute Casino oh no oh this is
great the references are so nice so well
drawn as
well there's so
many oh oh you guys did everything for
me thank
you oh a cat pin reduce abilities one
cool why would I not pick it up give it
to me oops wrong button but yeah they
deserve some healing anyway so that's
good wait how do I
[\h__\h] oh there you go I didn't switch out
the Reapers cloak did
I is that Oh I thought it was cabbage
but it's trash
bags I was going to think say that that
must be like a reference to
something but what is
it a
y ah what is this
substance must be poison
better to be careful where I'm
standing nice so many
coins I I said not a said right no why
would you bring this back but wait does
it give you four attack
extra oh it would switch out my cat pin
right no [\h__\h] that no D cute Co love
cute for
Center cute ah alsoo now all the enemies
are her
coyotes oh no oh no we're at the end of
the map
already AB Abby leave me
alone give me some distance for [\h__\h]
sake oh wait that's it okay sometimes I
think they're the enemies too my
paa paa
dudes what's this secret society helmet
enemies are likely are to Target you but
you also uh would also reduce damage
taken by
15%
well pick it up to sell it later uh okay
what's a button
though my ex
maybe no that no probably
not is
it
okay then we good then we
good sell it later okay
m
wait let me take
the wait sometimes I forget how to use
this
no cuz there's you can do two things you
can just hit with it or you can throw it
wait can you throw even the bench though
really I like the Pebbles also did you
see what Holo Advent
did did you
see I saw it when I woke up like that's
the first thing I watched when I woke up
and I was
like okay what the [\h__\h]
a nice hat I love
hats does it so does it mean I have
death free now and it doesn't change or
does it
add I'll just use it because I don't
have a hat on right now new hat let's
go Square for that one thank you it adds
okay oh takamo
tamole where window shot hopping just go
in girls just go in oh
dear yeah ad been looking funny but they
didn't get like like life Tod things of
of that right it was just the video like
repeating
jibs cuz they look so
funny
it's just the video oh
man wa I want to heal you guys how did
that
work uh not like that I thought it was
press X
longer oh just tapping
okay I want to use this up so I can get
something new The Hope soda although
these are really nice
too I guess the Hop s heals as well I
didn't check now what it does oh boss
fight warning oh no bring five followers
into a boss fight yeah I kept them alive
oh my God COI
coai don't kill
me [\h__\h] she's cute she's raring with
some interesting mask oh God it's going
to [\h__\h] kill
us no no no no no get some G back here
uh any attack items no h this one uh
[\h__\h] no Aim
so what what what what what what okay I
ended up in the middle this is good oh
God I'm going to die uh holy sh holy
[\h__\h] Co stop
uh oh my God thank God I have so many
heal
[Music]
items wait she doesn't take damage right
now what the
[\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] she does she does doesn't dagger
stagger okay okay holy [\h__\h] I died is
this the beginning are we in the
beginning now but I have items
already good first attempt thank you
damn we almost had it though almost had
it you're back at the checkpoint but
without all my friends I lose them all
or is this like the checkpoint so early
that it was before I had
any
all right the
think a new
ability glowing means super armor ahuh
heal items on your shortcuts I don't I
don't know how to set
them but yeah okay that makes sense cuz
I'm like switching around switching
around looking for the right item cuz
there are so many I didn't think you
could have so many at
once starting but stage with less
resources pretty hard I can imagine yep
yep yep but now we have a second ability
that we can challenge her with otherwise
we wouldn't have had that we didn't have
that in fact and need to just dodge and
heal her minions oh really is that the
the the way to
go so ability to is the second ability
that characters can use they are much
more powerful however they also have a
longer cool down after using uh compared
to Ability one use ability to hold the a
button until your character to glows
wide then release the butt so we just
press it longer right and then we let it
go
later ah I think the Hope soda makes you
faster when it glows oh some clothes
cute heal HP every time ail is used ooh
oo there you go but uh bring with to
sell H oopsie
no inventory full is there
but so there we
[Music]
go and then how do I activate them with
the same
buttons
yeah
[Music]
okay okay one friend at
least
nice had them all in one
line ready to
go not bad not bad D this is a healing
item too right what what is
that get Fork oh is that nissa's fork
he's so
good but you got to have your enemies in
the straight line um anything I can use
Ed now no I have everything pretty full
snowflower hair pin that's SN work nice
so it's so helpful it's so strong
changes the power attacks to be able to
cause freeze ooh okay I'll gladly take
that uh do this and then
[Music]
switch oh a second one okay okay okay
okay okay
okay oh no they're going crazy
again I'm getting better at
this
ah is the bgm too loud by the way let me
know if it
is go help your guy I did I
did it's fine PPT so stylish sure yeah
they have so many dongles C Can I stack
them if I take one of these Can I stack
them cuz now I have no heal h no healing
items except for this one maybe I'll
take it little quiet if anything
okay they stack up to 10 okay uh how to
drop again I'll just use it
up
Mama Phoenix when well she was already
on my stream
before but am I going to go that far to
I don't know if she used up a a yearly
outfit slot for that or if she paid for
it completely herself but that would be
really expensive both cases I don't
think I would do that uh
personally Uber gozaru Uber gozaru Uber
sheep all the way
Uber shap all the
way oh they froze them
nice it's the
Rival damn we live in a
society what is this something new por
creates a stuff po explodes when
touched
CAA my minions are dying here have some
[Music]
health damn can I heal one of my minions
with an item probably
[Music]
not the Box H oh didn't see
it what's your new skill I don't know
we'll see I'm not going to use it up now
six
[Music]
dangos the dogs are
coming wait let's not let's not let him
die don't die
did he die
no
uh-oh I don't want him to die I need him
one is already dead no way but there's a
new one also we do get pretty much all
of them
back until we go to the boss again so
that's fine then that's
[Music]
fine
yeah I did see someone tweeting about
clet Kuran
today
uh nice
[Music]
exp just hit
him oh come here come here go into the
healing Circle you little
[\h__\h] wait I need I
need
leave him
alone I made him I can't lose another
one oh credit card oh no Super
Chat
oh is the next one the boss again oo
Golden
Apple increase healing all healing by
Reviving I think I I will just like sell
it
I put it in my back
right probably since I only have one of
the paa
thing although those probably just give
you money right but I might switch it
out with the
sword use super chat to heal
oh uh fro Super Chat to heal an ally fro
how how do I get the right one
oh oh I can't throw upwards can
I [\h__\h] it went that way okay okay here
we go wait let's get some more
ah I have the healing Circle too
though all right all right all right so
is the next one
the ah
oh the
boss
aler n Cheese N say
cheese not yet yes oh I also heal
between screens uh do they do full heal
though we'll see if it's the boss no no
I don't think
so and we good
I can do it K thank
you I think I can
indeed nut truck
union
interesting okay let me check this A
happy C automatically heals slowly every
time I think I I'll just take that to go
thank you and I kind of want
to I want to take this dagger with me
again
but we'll see we'll see I can there's
still more enemies coming right oh it's
already B [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] okay
then uh let me probably need need all
the healing items anyway oh god oh oh oh
god oh
oh it hit her
right yeah as long as she's on that
height throw it all at her yeah
okay
uh
I don't know what that is uh can you
not as my Beetle's attacking her let's
go I think I'm doing really good I'm
doing really good guys I'm so much more
like I know what I'm
doing why am I
exploding okay I'm
back oh I did it I wasn't even wanting
Yoo I can dodge R for that okay my first
pass let's go Yay good job guys good job
Yi Yosi Yosi Yosi Yosi fluffy Tail
cute yeah this time was so much more
smooth cuz I I I knew just better how to
use the items and
everything you have to keep in
consideration that was my first try the
first time this is my second try money
and some
claws demon dog claw blue they have so
many Advent related items nice increase
the effectiveness of ability to by
oh sure I'll still take it
though just heal a bit first I don't
know they might get a full heal when we
switch to the next thing but just in
case oh oh it's like an in
between nice we're
camping has that look water
mdal oh look at that dorky Pebble on the
ground look at that NY carrot ancient
ones when playing with friends
communication is important and anytime
during gameplay you can use up to 10
emotes by pressing the reme wheel
[Music]
button oops
oh no I do not want to buy your emotes
you should give them to me for
free I see I see good ass um Trident
inas tentacle and some suai sword
sticking out where's
mine just kidding okay you got
consumables here oh
party Phoenix sword l w there's a
phoenix sword weapon can cause burn Fox
King Burger nice oh I get so many items
already I think I'm fine but H what else
do I have the money for
huh
maybe I want to try the Phoenix
sword oh I just get one for o oh that's
expensive I
guess yeah get a h got five and then oh
equipment too oh
oh damn damn this feels like oh oh I
feel like I'm in an mmpg and this is the
cash shop for the only the visual
outfits upgrade the a better spend money
with Kyla okay
welcome oh yeah right ah some members
were asked to voice lines right ah I saw
a message about that I was like oh not a
message I saw a tweet about it like oh I
think Kyla gave like so many so many
voice
lines way more than it was asked for and
I was like
oh who who
why she's a NPC that's
why ah okay
upgrade so I'll upgrade something I
already have
[Music]
H the ones I have equipped have the E
huh heal HP
every let's upgrade like
this uh it just ah it just gives it one
more
death oh then this is more worth it cuz
yeah I got things I got things
this one this one thank
you a wait enhancing what what's the
difference between upgrading and
enhancing what I'm out coins already oh
[\h__\h] guess we'll never
know the gotcha there's got how do I
sell
cute how do I
sell equipment nice
anymore uh I'll sell that
sell I mean this is pretty
good but I don't even know how to revive
players also it's so cheap to sell that
so I assume it's actually not that
good we back ah I was gone what the [\h__\h]
which one this one no money oh still oh
oh 1,000 the 1,000 one I can a afford
how about this what what what does it do
ah does it give it another like stat
like this one has two because it's green
so this one would get another stat too I
guess
but is it worth it to do that with this
one
now maybe it gets replaced
soon some things sell low but are still
good okay I'll keep that in mind there's
only 42 chance to okay that's pretty low
not don't take all my
money oh we're in a bamboo forest nice
what I can take a full a whole
what somebody already ripped that out
right
oopsie ah what am I doing sorry I'm
confused I'm
[Music]
confused
noise no what am I
doing how do I throw it again there we
go
Money Make It Rain a fancy Cod wow again
we'll just take it with us to sell it
[Music]
it should I keep the Phoenix sword for
the next boss fight or use it now
hm also thank God there's so many
soundtracks it
seems so we don't get tired of hearing
the same one over and over
again
[Music]
swords are boss Killers what you mean
the one I just used now
too well everything is
useful swords better for annoying
minions like the green
[Music]
ninjas yours is really nice for bosses
okay and I'll keep it I'll try to keep
it which of your coing BRS do you think
gives of the most Senai
Vibes
well well obviously Co cuz I always uh
call her
Senpai oh I can use that several times
also the Yago stat does that give
money do do too she just has that that
aura
[Music]
um let me think oopsie oh what the
[\h__\h] out of my ID cool
eyes I
think just because I I already
interacted with them so
much um and have a lot of history of
them I don't really think they make me
feel
like they're my Senpai none of them like
none of the kis make me feel like
that but how how can I replace my my
Blue Claw with the red claw I even
upgraded it increase the effect
one can I not wear two Doos need two
claws man but I guess I'm going to use
it damn
red way better yeah but you
know I'm going to take him with me you
guys said he's missing but he's right
here he just he's just a little bit
stiff we can fix
that I can fix
him oh oh does he just never break or do
they have several frows
available
oh Yuki means yeah they're so cute
they're so fluffy and round so friend
shaped oh my
God taking it with me in my bag but not
going to use it oh heels oh me TI having
a little picnic and look at what they're
using a
fmis guess who else is using a fmis
right now
me guess what feris it
is yeah I need more items he
you yes the kfp ferace yay it's pretty
small so it's probably more for like uh
going out
usage not really at home usage but I'm
us using it
anyway M it looks so nice and and and it
it has a that that was my biggest wish
cuz there's some some firmers who don't
have the the lid as a cup but mine
functions as a cup so you don't have to
bring your own cup you know you can you
can let others drink out of the cup
too
o no if the furnace is big I will use it
at home too usually because
when I stream for 8 hours I can't like
continuously make new tea but if I just
make one cup of tea then it'll be done
immediately so ideally have a big ferace
jug right next to me not furnace
FMA shut
up and then fil my cup over and over
again I'm not going to say the word ever
again cuz of
you you know what I mean shut
up you unlock ultimate ability ultimate
abilities character's most powerful
attack these used once a character's
ultimate garge a yellow bar under the HP
bar is filled once it is ready hold both
X and A buttons for a moment is that
square and
X um use once in a while so be sure to
make it count I'll try [\h__\h] I'll make it
cun oh
nice yo the yukim me are strong
unlike in that other Holo fan game where
the yukim Min
were pretty low
tier oh theyve been dropping all those
heals for
me so
considerate they can heal themselves too
oh my God
op is it just me or are they dropping
way less items though than before
for do they want me to rely on those
jugs and
stuff ow [\h__\h]
you are you good over
there go go
go it's kind of random I like the tman
so it's RNG
ah think Po's fan dropping more no way I
got used to it oh but here we go here we
got some good
items M
okay nissa's Fork I got to say is pretty
great for bosses so I want to keep that
one M oh my God she looks so lost just
like in my
dream
just like in my dream are you okay M
don't worry I got you you can stay over
don't worry there's no pigeons mating
right
now that's the story of the
past well they're healing don't worry I
can heal you
[Music]
too can't be hat changes the power
attacks to be able to cause
burn oh that's amazing but my other one
is upgraded so for now I'll just take it
with
me damn so we have a waa waa sword and a
waa
hat
y she's she looks so
cute yeah that's a fake KY what do you
mean why they're the same level ah
oh okay I'll change it
eventually let's take the tree with me
still no Shield what do you
mean oh am I supposed to get a shield
like is that a
thing Dam so many heals all over the
map more Bab
baseballs you throw shoy I I throw
baseballs American
style why are you at the corner of the
map I can barely see you that's not
fair oh what the [\h__\h] was
that did you forget the shield what do
you mean the
shield what do you mean can
I
what is there a shield I item that I
picked up that I can
use H suers yeah but uh I don't want to
drop anything unless I can pick it up
again can
I Oh you mean the game needs
to I'm like what Shield as in like I
didn't see a shield in the game I
remember I have a shield but you guys
are asking
originally what like where my shield is
in the game okay the confusion
[Music]
I thought you were saying it like I
should already have it in the game wait
if I drop uh an item can I pick it up
again it drops holding the item use
button drops item
okay oh but wait they're healing right
now anyway they're aren't they fine are
they wait maybe they're not healing I
just saw a fat
Morana [\h__\h] I used the wrong
item I thought the switches immediately
the one that you pick
up yeah okay
um I might leave the tea on the ground
cuz we have so many heals anyway oh oh I
didn't know we can get one of you to I
thought this was all about yukim
means oh [\h__\h] I used it
again no wait what how do I pick this up
again like this
okay oh we're not at the boss yet
somehow I had a feeling that we're going
to the boss right now
okay easy no
problem
ah a it didn't hit anyone too
bad he looks kind of
heavy like his movement is so
slow okay pick up the
money
don't go away
[Music]
coins Pebbles function like a shotgun I
know I know I I love the Pebbles Pebbles
although I feel like they don't do much
damage but at least they scatter and
have like some AOE going on what is this
I can't see is it my sword or the other
one the m one it's the m
one and new happy coat no
need [\h__\h] why do I always do
that
I got to save the Yoki
mean come help me on my
mission this is so good this game is so
[Music]
good I mean the no save thing actually
kind of makes sense because in Holo cure
there was also like if you die you
die you can't like save and then go back
to your a current
run in Holo cure
either so kind of to be expected but no
there's no saving in beat them
UPS
not why is this by the way why is this
genre called belt action what what what
what's with the
belt stage 20 minutes as opposed to what
how long is this going to be I guess you
got to kill all five is that the
goal need to wear a belt to play this
game I it's okay I'm wearing a belt not
the classic kind of belt but
yeah took me 2 hours oh
[\h__\h]
damnn you good over there seems like it
with a lot of luck 1 hour two hours if
you don't die oh okay well probably die
before it
ends so no worries about that what is
this a shiny ring you know what I
appreciate it being something that I
don't have to think about whether or not
I want to use it or not
because I'm happy with what I have yeah
I know they're they're adding savings
still I guess they realize it's a little
bit too
long for there to be no
saving how we doing over here huh I have
no aim with this
stuff h
but you shouldn't be throwing this thing
either it's
sacred oh what the [\h__\h] is this is this
an
enemy he look like friends cuz he so
friend
shaped eat him up with the offering
boooks no no ah everybody
he
a
no a that makes me
mad
no no I used two shots of my burning
sword against
nothing for
what it gives
money when I throw it or
what
[Music]
it's all
over oh my special thing is ready but
I'm not going to use it
now
obviously let's go me and my minions are
going to do this mini has adopted all
the Yuki means and what are the paa ones
called Huka
oruo is that what they're called that
would be a funny name it's just a a
statement for a
name no ah oh Zane oh that's yeah right
I should have known that because I I've
read it several times Zane has joined
you that seems like a name of a member
of One
Direction
ah I thought it may have been a feather
of me or shoi but it's nous spend exp
gain it it it is wait but she didn't
call her uh mascot's dad because she's a
fan or so did
she wait it actually is though oh my God
I actually got that right just why
instead of an
i is your F in the game M I don't know I
don't know yet should I use this the
other one gives me a lot of stats so
probably not for
now IOP I doubt she knows who they are I
got to tell her that that's what I had
to think of when I saw her Fan's name no
I'm not ready no I'm not mentally ready
no no no no
no don't
no oh [\h__\h] already killing me oh
God
um I where is she
oh I said s by oh
[\h__\h] stat whatever shut
up
sorry I'm freaking out right
now oh no at least leave my yukim means
alone no
okay a what the [\h__\h] why was I in
[Music]
that where is she where is she so she
she like like all the Minions cover up
so
much oh wait wait I'm I'm I'm okay I'm
okay they're not okay they're not okay
oh God get out of there get out of
there h h
h no no no leave him alone leave them
alone
oh she's almost dead I can do
it
no wa I want to heal him
but I can do it I can do
it I didn't have time to stand still and
use my UL te I wanted to heal them just
that's all I wanted to do you guys but
wait why was I not able to use my UL I
guess I just used it
up oh I did it first try that was rough
cuz everybody all my minions were
dying ooh level two is green when
getting oh but mine is level three cuz I
upgraded it right when getting up after
a knockdown in vulnerability time is
doubled and also gain 25%
attack that's
good alt a tap twice Oh I thought it was
pressing longer sorry I
forgot I
misunderstood oh guys go get some
[Music]
healing this is super impressive thank
you I tried to dodge but damn I
shouldn't have let so many of them die
try it out now is it going to
be gone like the charge is going to be
gone when I leave the map also is n
sticking out her tongue like a dog
when she's in this
dance
like it will be gone oh okay uh uh
wrong wait
what you said double
tap
what square and I have right H who's who
the [\h__\h] said double tap I got one guide
it was this a it's a big
heel ah okay okay
okay back in the camp damn I got 10,000
coins good to see you again thank you
I'm also happy to be here happy that I'm
not dead
and so this n we wanted to
perhaps
use the kfp
Hat
um and we
[Music]
could I don't know what we going to do
were we going to use the feather upgrade
just one item yeah the kfb Hat burn is
better
okay
uh okay it it becomes speed
four and can we enhance it should we
enhance it too we got the
money but only
45 is this worth it with so little enh
hat first uh that there was an order to
do
that almost
50/50
success
woohoo I'm a luck
[\h__\h]
5050 chance
baby who taught you I've known that word
for a long
time I think from mm RPGs or something I
don't
know wait
uh okay this confusing I don't know
where I
[Music]
am
okay they should put in a selling menu
where I can just look at the items I
have and sell them not have to go down
here and then it's confusing
me uh
sell
goodbye was nice having
you fancy coat
goodbye um uh no
see agree agree death death Captain's
head would have been great on N oh
Captain's head oh that one on on any
heel share 10% of the heal to all allies
oh then gain gain a random amount of
holoc coins to
yourself that's pretty nice
sounding yeah I'll sell that one shiny
ring yeah
this one is interesting um I don't know
if
I should use
it uh it would be instead of this
huh I don't
know no space for selling menu it's
designed for four players like that ah
is it going to show up like next to each
other like in Boulder's
Gate sell it
don't know think
it okay
goodbye I
think that's all I
need there has to be a place to put it
though neow don't do much now besides
healing you oh okay okay okay okay I see
YouTube is apparently buffering like a
little [\h__\h] why would you do that don't
please oh you're right there was gotcha
I should have used gotcha you lose all
of it if you die okay then we'll just
not
die
Bach
wow oh dear
okay
uh ow please be nice what the hell I'm
alone still you have to go easy on
me
and again new
music yo we appreciate the many
soundtracks they really put a lot of
music into this
game um I'm going to
die
[Music]
I love that oh the taco D in the back
swimming I guess that where that's where
he belongs I guess I don't really see
takachi as things to find in the ocean
but I guess that's that's where it do be
I got to be more careful I'm like about
to
die so what's the specialty of
Nichi fans how do they help
me yeah they are supposed to be octopus
yeah
octopuses they had bang people great but
I seem to be getting a mix of the
minions again so that's
nice Su
duck H
he I forgot my
box thanks for letting me
know
[Music]
all
right oh my God they're
strong oh no don't don't [\h__\h] die no
no no no no no no stay stay stay safe yo
wait did I always only have two minions
I feel like I already had three but no
no I think I think it's to oh God give
me a super chat give me a super chat
give me a Super Chat no what is
this I only had two
okay wait I can almost heal it almost
almost almost
ni there you
go take this take my love take n's love
for her fans which must be so
strong hold X for ah yeah should I no
wait no no no why would I do that
now I'm going to wait for one more cuz
this is dangerously low Super Chat thank
you with your power I can heal the
[Music]
nickel he knows exactly no actually I
didn't intend for this to happen but uh
it's always a welcome
one I'm going to wait for one more yo
I'm so scared and I'm not going to lose
this nickel this currently it's so much
more
difficult the enemies are so much
stronger I have to be
careful one more oh thank you thank you
for another
one there you go
yeah that's that's looking better we
like to see it
[Music]
okay let's hope we can hit something oh
oh the most lydy couple of them
all [\h__\h] you all get out of
here
yeah they're so
Ted they're enjoying the sun just like
me for real for
real I have to say oh my God spring has
arrived in Austria and it's making me
feel so good
so much
better [\h__\h] winter depression sayata
we don't need you here anymore it was
like the first warm day that I
experienced since winter and oh it was
so nice you really feel a big difference
when you see that sun you feel the
warmth oh I was like where's goba oh
she's huge in the background
oh I'm getting my AC set up again I
really I really want AC
too I
wish I thought you like living in
Austria though I like living in Austria
yeah yeah yeah yeah at least it's not as
freaking tropical as in
Japan reduce ability is too cool down a
it looks so cute but it's not as useful
as what I have right now so we
good damn I I wish I could take that
item but we
good
goopa what are you doing back there come
over
here don't stay so far away SOS who drew
that
wait come over here guys I I don't want
this to go to waste here some I'll I'll
try to call for if he can join the fight
oh thank you for the Super Chat heal
there we
go that's what I wanted to
see yeah I got the baseballs actually I
like them in this
[Music]
game heal heal with the
heal
yay is that a soda can but it's an item
huh oh well is Alie buried in the sand
or did she lose her head which one could
it be which one is
it oh good trient is stuck
here you left your Trident if you're
going somewhere you shouldn't leave your
Trident out like
that
are you guys okay here's some
heal yeah don't make it go the waste
though oh no the coyote is
[Music]
back oh there's so many enemies holy
[\h__\h] uh
uh what should I use pick up oh wait I
can pick her up
a thanks Oli for the support he I love
her no not the Yi man not the
Healer oh [\h__\h] I just saw it ghost leave
the
planet oh I'm going to die on this level
am I I'm pretty sure I will oh I got my
Phoenix sword let's
go shindana bring the head okay the uh a
[\h__\h] o o I'm getting the right items
let's
go Oli you're coming with me aren't you
happy about
that I'm not going to leave you here all
alone
here oh [\h__\h] that's why I thought we
were just being
nice
a
uh just going to use up all the swords
now why
not she's supporting me she's so
sleep
oh I can use my attack if I wanted to
but I'm going to keep it oh what is this
a night maze L frontal attack maze
[Music]
mace truly all these
AI wow she's having a good time here
she's living the
life good for her there's a chicken in
the back swimming look at him
cute by the way ol like after the VR
thing oh oh wait what the [\h__\h] there's a
fish after the VR stream I DMD everybody
saying like oh my God I'm so sorry for
the SC but thank you for participating
BL blah BL just wrote them a personal
individual
message and OE replied and she was like
oh you know we're so grateful in ID like
that you like when people think of us
and then you invite us to your event and
I'm like oh
wow
okay I'm glad I did
it I'm glad I invited ID you know I
always love working with ID because
they're so like motivated and they're
always up for some fun and you know it's
just easy to to work with them and
they're always hype and always energetic
and always bring some nice energy to the
table and they're also really grateful
you know and you know you have to
consider they got up at a really really
early time for me or stayed up who knows
yeah yeah so ID is great and I
do um feel like I want to do more with
them I think I already do quite a lot
with them I always consider them as
great collab
Partners yeah I'm always happy to have
them
[Music]
around now that we don't have the Yuki
means I might have to focus on healing
here a little
[Music]
bit too bad Anna is yeah too bad
really otherwise I I'd love to interact
with her
more not that it really not that it
really matters what branch they are
in on your to collab
oh I love a fancy coat some more
baseballs but I'm good now I think too
bad I can't pick up those things uh
yeah
oh oh I'm
dying
oh
[\h__\h] oh oh [\h__\h] that was by accident I'm
I'm
panicking we're okay we're okay we're
okay we're doing fine somewhat fine
uh-oh oh my oh they're also not doing so
well yeah we have to protect them okay
I'm going to use more items I was kind
of keeping them but no use in keeping
them if my minions died yeah level
up what's happening over here don't die
minion
CH I will cry if you
die no one dies on my
watch I mean they do but I'm trying to
avoid it use skill
two
[Music]
okay you don't wear watch that is right
that is correct as
well
[Music]
shie I only know the first no I used the
the the bug a few times on the boss
fights yo I
did the sun is nature's watch oh that's
some deep [\h__\h] that you're saying I like
it
[Music]
yum oh two two more minions let's
go okay I'm not mentally ready for this
but let's
[Music]
go I'm just going to use my [\h__\h]
items
now there's still plenty on the ground
and
anyway
uh there we go there we go ah but I used
it to wait ah my bug is
useless wait take it with me go go go go
go no it's
gone
ow if I die and it's not in a boss fight
that will be so embarrassing it it
cannot
happen Okay okay we're feeling pretty
pretty energetic
o I want to pick that
up it's too valuable to leave it on the
ground
maybe let me
use oh
[Music]
nice what's that a the baseball
no what's that what's the other
thing ah what's that thing behind the
baseball you don't need all the items I
need them you'd be surprised how
difficult the game is for some of the
other girls I think only for if man you
finish oh okay well yeah see it is very
[\h__\h] difficult for me right
now I want to keep the minions alive at
all cost I need him to be my meat
Shield oh but okay we're good we're
good attack fetal
PE
yeah
I'll take you
down how my man
doing oh there's the
orcas what did I
use um get it what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] is that what item did I just
activate some is that amaz like
thing I'm a lens
Mayon oh what does it do it has a cool
down hold it
Apple a crit buff oh [\h__\h] we got to go
and use it but I need to heal oh my God
one one NE almost
died y don't die on me I'm going to stay
here and I'm going to heal them back up
May heals
[Music]
them
uh next boss I think is H what's that
mean that just heals me a it's only free
[Music]
too I think there was some better stuff
back
here angel star throw a star forward
that spins in place
five is the Oh you mean h h h is next as
in just telling me the boss is
next oh [\h__\h]
oh ah can shik is op okay I feel good
about it I'm going to give them one more
heal the NEOS seem kind of like they
have low defense or low HP in
general Mayo heals a lot it's really
good M but I
need I don't know the other items are
although I'm almost out of the dangos
that means oh [\h__\h] that's my only
healing item right
now I do have a I do have to remember I
have a big healing
skill a big one let's use it this
time the other thing was a baseball and
boys love should i dle h I guess yeah
free versus free
makes sense and
then uh wait how do I lock it in
again H I can't lock it
in lunch with
[Music]
me hold the trigger ah thank you
sorry let's put this one here
I'm not ready I'm going to
[Music]
die okay focus
focus get in there coward I don't want
to you got this fake be strong you got
this I don't know be you use Beetle and
ult okay
he oh that doesn't look like the boss
wait
NE we good it wasn't the
[Music]
boss ni okay o
chain uh maybe next is boss this one was
short
no we got more mayo oh five is Max for
this Mayo the boss should be thankful it
gets to live a little while
[Music]
longer gam it oh
okay oh
oh no here it is ah [\h__\h] ah which one is
it Lou I don't
know
oh
[\h__\h] I'm sure he doesn't like
beetles okay I
um just use up all the R
now
nice nice [\h__\h] Trident op get out of
there
guys oh she has does she have minions or
did I see something wrong oh she
does okay how's this work
wait where am
I
oh
oh [\h__\h] I'm like freaking out but she's
almost dead
okay I don't know what I'm doing
[Music]
ah touch her touch her yeah touch paa
you know you want to do
it I [\h__\h] did it
let's
go I was very focused first try again
guys first try again
y I did oh right I didn't use the ulti
again I should have I totally should
have but like oh my God I was like so
busy my brain was so
busy gamer of e my te oh God it's
spreading
I'm like TI oh I'm like
TI okay that was okay my
FAS my
FAS uh apparently only is enough for one
cup of
tea one day K would use it I did but it
was in a moment where it was kind of
useless yeah I mean I could use it now
right because it won't be there anymore
ta you know how it feels when you're
just overwhelmed with everything and
you're focusing and you're gaming
so small small te very small small tea
oh my God I'm so proud of
[Music]
myself why well I shouldn't be the one
saying that but at least I censored my
feet my foot oh man
damn
wow pump maker you're
here you must have been so happy when
you saw my foot weren't you on Twitter
you guys are missing out if you don't I
can't
move no what did my game oh no I just
tabed out I found my game
Crash yeah you guys are missing out if
you don't um if you're not on Twitter
then you didn't see
oh what the
[\h__\h] what the
hell okay I go check it there you go you
know you
know
um okay should we switch
something we
have nothing really that's that much
better better
what do you do first enhancing or
upgrading upgrading is the one that
gives it another slot right but we
already have full slots on this one so
don't forget about G oh
[Music]
yeah enhance first okay well let's see
what where's the
G Also let's look at the equipment
though oh
not consume one
use n hes are
back headphones oh they're also
back no are the book for the emotes why
why why would I do that I don't need
emotes I don't need
emotes they're just for
emoting right they don't do
anything oh
[Laughter]
no no no no you're not going to get me
to do that
no you little
shits uh well I'm currently using that
but I'm getting up after knock ah didn't
I want to possibly use
that what do you think is
better rip kada the Drew once for you
yeah
well of the artist if the emotes had any
other use I would consider
it she hates
us no I'm into to I'm in to win yeah but
I bought the froggy wild
merch that that you didn't do for me
anyway you did that for
her you don't really use power attacks
ah what do you
mean what do you mean what what is
that I can look at them without buying
them well there you go does that make it
uh less worth I think
so for me to buy them
wait uh wait I don't know how to get
there oh my God
sell
S I don't understand this I don't
understand this menu no where where
where am I here
okay where am
I how do I get to ah there we go sorry
confused because I thought the green um
Green Line surrounding the item means
I'm on the item for some
reason sorry sorry this this shows you
de this shows you de
almost sold my own armor yeah de please
do something about this do something
about
this my brain
hurts you're so
welcome goodbye cat pen okay I I don't
know you guys say it's not worth it for
me the aqua hat play tester waha I like
that job that's maybe something I'll do
after
Holo call you
shambles it's good right it sounds good
de is aware okay but but you also deaf
are you talking are you saying you you
as a death are aware even though you're
not involved in this well it doesn't
help me much you being
aware uh pretty sure headband is better
though better than my k hat the maid hat
is worth the kfp hat is not since you
don't ah the singing One aha okay that
is sad that is
sad ah Ah that's where the P cuz I was
like uh Power text and I was reading the
aqua mate hairband description I didn't
find that you meant the kfp Hat
oh goodbye
K my beloved you guys don't sell your
own okay you have to wear them I don't
wear it I have a different kind of hat
okay so we enhance
this oh wait 15% okay I think I already
enhanced it before then yeah yeah yeah
yeah
uh okay H from 198 to
269 oh
nice I can easily afford that how about
this I'll give it another one thank you
and
maybe but I'm not wearing this I can
sell this one too I I have I got a
second one that's what happened uh
should we uh enhance my
Chon yeah why did I not do that
45 oh thank God but
her her sound her voice is not scared me
I thought I thought it was a a fail
noise a failure noise
she she turned into you guys say gorilla
but it made me think of Tim
[Laughter]
Allen
uh
okay or should we do one more how about
this 17 no is there a way to guarantee
it
anyhow how about this thank you thank
you try it
well oh I guess I could have I could
have just bought a different armor if it
broke huh luck increases this chance
a try once oh no it's going to fail
though oh it went up to
18 well yeah cuz improved my
luck and
um it won't break it doesn't break ah it
just fails get some help ah get some
help excuse me KLA you're talking to
your
Senpai oh let's go that's so cute pum
maker I have confidence thank you okay I
that is very motivating for the upcoming
stages than I appreciate it we only have
do and laas left I
guess cute
and we get some extra death from that
let's go if it doesn't break then I I I
want to do it with the ma head B too no
pressure no pressure yeah this one no
pressure this time this one no pressure
oh my God
yeah
from a she's blushing this is this is me
and this is her when she looks at me any
give time yeah yeah yeah yeah see you
love emotes yeah but like I wouldn't buy
them if that's if all they do is look
nice
sorry than you I get knock
down get back up
again I get knocked down thank
[Music]
you H thank you I'm losing all my money
let's
go thank you okay I'm happy come again
soon I'm happy yeah I guess we should
use up all the money because you guys
you said if if I if I die then it's all
gone anyway what is
this what no it what does it
do I guess I pressed the wrong x what do
this what does this do oh I can sit by
it probably to
heal oh man I was sitting animation do
you heal when you sit here that would be
nice not that I need it right
now okay I feel very
pressured but let's do
this
oh we are in the air now this feels very
intense
oh
let's
go music is
popping it's motivating
uh-oh we got the mace again I think I
like the mace it's quite all
right Yay good
start both on stand by ah oh Nephilim
Wings Dodge action moves far and
extended vulnerabil okay um I barely
Dodge I know I should Dodge
more but this gives me a good feeling
that I don't need to use it because I
don't use Dodge much so I don't have to
think about
it but I'm going to try to use it more
often like now so much that you guys
start saying Dodge less not Dodge more
Dodge less yes now oh now you want me to
dodge less oh yeah I knew
it you can me come over here I want to
heal
you yeah no you were only in there for a
second barar and money let me pick up
all this
money for the chat will go to the usual
room that's right o Fox game burer
yummy roll no roll
this oh Al oh I can also shoes can I
really have them be able to withand
twice the amount of attacks before being
knocked down
wow interesting but probably I'm not
going to use
it okay let's
go
[Music]
Yi in Yi
in got to help out so it doesn't
die as in
protect
no no no no no you give me don't go
there no no
[Music]
no die
[\h__\h] not my Yuki
man I'm wait I'm I'm I'm about to die
too wait that was not a heal I thought
the Mayo was heal what the [\h__\h] is it
heal over time uh okay holy
[\h__\h] oh my God oh my
nickel damn this is bad this is pretty
bad this is pretty bad
this is looking pretty bad Mayo heals
slowly
a in that moment I needed an immediate
heal
so she lived but at what cost at the
cost of the nickele don't know if that's
worth it also H not the niele the Yuki
mean let me heal
you come
on ah beetle beetle yeah
Beetle s this
n let me wait for it to heal back
up you know yesterday on my day off
besides enjoying the sun I also was
really productive I finally unpacked my
second suitcase and I cleaned everything
I vacuumed everything I did my laundry
it was just overall a cleaning day also
I cleaned myself I went to take a shower
amazing
Yim went to Valhalla U also I watch a
bit of The Witcher a bit quite a bit
quite a bit a big amount
actually but it felt so nice and I even
cooked I even cooked quite late and I
didn't take a nap I kind of wanted
to but I felt like I was getting really
tired but then somehow I was able to
resist
what is
this oh I spread poison with that or
what a poison explosion kind of
thing
nice that sounds
good oh oh ni
NE what the [\h__\h] who's who's who's
making these explosions are
you oh my God
well I I don't think I can do it in one
run guys because the Neco dying so much
the minions dying so much me also not
looking so good anymore this is like
really o a tough
one let the chicken
cook me myself I made that choice
yes I want to pick up the Pebbles but
I'll eat the burger oh well yeah you
keep your level So eventually Oh I
thought you start from Level zero again
oh okay yeah well that changes a lot uh
but you only keep the level on Nei in
particular I
suppose the blue guys are grenadiers oh
look at that we have a bot on
[Music]
tempai welcome um I'm guessing they do
good damage
so
okay helping out
now nice it's like an extra minion I
need to keep that in
mind yeah they should
can okay good good that was better that
was smoother we like
it we pick up these some
chips be has good stun too oh moon blade
I really like Moon
blade ah a new
kimono don't need
this little bit of
heal did you guys manage to finish a
whole run
yet or not yet who managed to do it all
in one go
huh yeah
nice oh [\h__\h] that's powerful in a group
of
enemies but then they die and it just
stays there but now I actually saw how
it actually
works appreciate
that
anyone
dying oh I'm in I'm in I'm in
lens I'm going pick this one
up okay no one died right wonderful need
to sleep have fun good night thanks for
stopping by am I saw m holding the am
note for really long but damn it sounded
like a [\h__\h] mosquito
was painful to to listen
to I never thought I would say that it
was painful to listen to mum in any
context but in this context it
applies
okay the more heal the
merer okay let's go 28 of M's
blade that's pretty
good get out of here with your surf
boards go back to the
ocean you little
sh nice more shans hey
ooh that Shield somehow it makes me
think of Ark
Knights that kind of Shield cuz there
are enemies with that kind of Shield
too okay okay this is good this is good
I got the right items that will stack on
my existing
items I always appreciate that you have
an ALT too I know but I'm not going to
use it I need to use the beetle
again
welcome
what what what is he doing why is he
burning beig Tanuki he's so
cute he's so [\h__\h] cute so chunky I
want to give him a
hug uh what can we
use nothing really nothing interesting I
don't want to waste a shoy right
now maybe
later okay good awesome friend shaped
enemy
P what are your guys's favorite fan
designs besides obviously the chicken
it's a bath
bomb what's your favorite if you can
think of any that are not here right
now no I never paused the game before
I'm a gamer I don't need to stop the
game the ne go oh yeah it just looks so
funny with the scribbled
eyes tacos are versatile
noaki those poor noaki have no legs
man M tacis tacis
ssrb it's amazing how they yeah with
ssrb they made a bomb into a little cute
C cat looking thing gave it a little
pause it's
adorable oh [\h__\h] I used oh why I why did
I use that ah [\h__\h] I wasted
that wait I want to go here behind
them for the shooty
can Beetle time Beetle time
oh it was a fan M design oh
genius kind of
Genius fans are so creative we should
let fans do more things we should just
let them do
everything where's my Oh I thought I
picked up
oh
[Music]
whatever get those heels there's some
super chats
here but they're actually not so
necessary right now I'm keeping them on
pretty good HP right now o ears bunny
ears if a failed weapon hits an enemy
there's an a chance to cause an
explosion I'll do one more
heal yeah cuz I play nii how okay I just
realized yeah without nin if I didn't
have the ability to heal my minions oh
it would be so over I wouldn't have a
chance
I do want to play this uh in Co-op of
somebody I I'll try to set up a collab
for next week maybe do does it like does
the difficulty scale does it get uh
more enemies and all
that or stronger
enemies it does oh no I wish it
wouldn't oh n ref is in the chat n rev
worked on this really hard
while working on the Easter thing
too appreciate it it turned out great it
turned out
lovely stinky [\h__\h]
[Music]
Orca it's nice how they also involved
more artists This Time by giving them
the opportunity to draw stickers
that's really
[Music]
nice ah maybe the chips are not so worth
it I'll take the baseballs just to spam
them guys can you War me when I'm in
front of the boss because I need to get
mentally ready for it I don't feel
mentally ready at
all what I another Minion
okay now we can get a new one let's get
the bomb I like this one
oh go get
him kabwa kabwa
kabwa
always on five five yeah but I wasn't
looking at the numbers so I feel like it
it could have been anytime now and
surprised me out of
nowhere okay where are we
now did we lose a minion recently guys
or is this is this I'll be good did I
keep them safe did I protect their
smiles I'm on oh I'm on 44 so
soon if I would pause I would see it
I'm too scared I'm on edge I can't
pause yeah I guess I'll keep what I
[Music]
have yeah yukim me would be nice I don't
know if I'm getting
[Music]
anymore oh [\h__\h] what what am I doing you
have bombs I have bombs too
level up let's
go at the same time as I summoned my
Beetle send really makes you think it
sends us a sign oh new
enemy where am I
oh
uh
sure y yo y yo so many explosions
they're kind of
intimidating oh [\h__\h] oh it's like making
tornadoes oh
[\h__\h] look get out of the tornado R you
[\h__\h]
idiots a wait I barely got anything out
of
that oh my God the
tornadoes I don't know if anybody died
now uh it it it must have been
close [\h__\h] do
I
what is this the part
screen this is not my
chat it's not
it fake fake fake 1 hour 47 wrong I've
been online for 2 hours 18
minutes but why the [\h__\h] do I have zero
zero
subscribers
fake what am I looking at what I what
what am I looking
for oh it adds speed death and attack
soon yeah I am I think I'm going to drop
this and get the dangle do you think
it's worth wait it was only one why was
it only
one any more dangles here
no you can pinpoint my credit card too
bad I don't have a credit card oh
at the games instead what the
games
games mean the what potato chips
what
y guys yeah I'm so nervous I feel like
we're oh need a little B bit more heal
yeah chips are chips are better heal
them down yeah and it's like five yeah
okay I'm going to go get
him how do you pay stuff in Japan with
buy the credit card uh I just bring
cash Japanese cash and if I need to get
more cash I use my debit card at the
711 somehow my debit card only works at
the
7-Eleven yeah Japan is pretty cash based
also I just put cash on my on my train
card the sua or the Paso whatever a lot
of Japanese people just use that too to
pay everything it's like a cash card and
you can use it for the train but also
you can use it in pretty much every
other store too like in convenience
store and in department
stores everywhere you find your s cut no
that one's gone but I have another pmo I
think here in Austria that I can take
next time so sad I lost my Sila man so
sad especially when you came and get a
new
one um are
we four five oh
[\h__\h] I'm I'm not I can't I'm I'm not
mentally ready for this
ah I uh my items okay I remember I have
to remember there's baseballs back here
that I can bring I have a lot of heal
items [\h__\h] this was the hardest part for
me
use your Ting
okay wait it's not even FAL time
yet is it after the first wave I'm not
sure
ah
uh-oh
uh-oh uh-oh sorry I'm nervous I'm
nervous uhoh
wait
heal prare
yourself very hard for bullets spam on
tornadoes every no not the
tornadoes oh I got ah I got some more of
the of the needles of the pins of the
yeah wait I forgot
this thank you I'm going to die I'm I'm
I'm 100% going to
die [\h__\h] okay just I just I'm just
trying to um understand what I
have
okay yeah what I have in my inventory
okay think of your alt yeah it's it's
the two buttons at once right and I need
to use my my beetle
too
okay I'm gonna die I'm gonna die I'm
gonna die I'm gonna
die oh
ah
spam spam spam spam the same attack over
and over oh my
God spam spam
okay oh it's pretty good doing pretty
good
ow owow ow ow she almost
dead have no more weapons
though oh [\h__\h] not the
Tado go be
go oh [\h__\h]
don't where the [\h__\h] is she anyway ah
there no she's so fast she's so
fast no no no
no nice good spot good
spot
oh good
spot y let's do it let's do it let's do
it why is that so bad was isn't so
bad oh my
God holy [\h__\h] first try oh my this is my
second run oh my God the first run ended
really early everything p uh whatever
the first boss was I've already forgot
everything passed that it's first
try La plus is much easier than do as
long as you keep your minion you got
this though oh my God that would be
amazing
simp oh my God I'm locked in
you beat the first boss on the second
try yeah everything else's first try the
AL was very very real Tim yeah I was I
was trying to activate it at first uh
like like 5 Seconds earlier but then it
activated the the normal heal first
which is fine too double heal the morm
areia but I wasn't sure what I was doing
like why is it not working why is it not
working oh really just the same thing
again how many times have I gotten this
kimono okay wow I feel I feel so good I
will take this little sogui down her and
your her whole secret society wait I
just realized the way that
we spawn in is the same as from our V
concerts
a oh I have a little bit less money than
last time to see you again oh probably
because I didn't buy so much the last
last
time
uh uh this one oh oopsie what am I doing
[\h__\h] I was gonna sell
[Music]
it I'm just going to stay with my
current equipment so that I can upgrade
it
all love yeah okay it's not the one I'm
using good call yeah hadn't noticed it
yeah it's so sweet it's good plan
the shoes even though they sound kind of
cool would like to try it but
um I think we're okay what was this
again Dodge action moves further ah yeah
that's pretty good too but I'm kind of
okay with what I have which means we can
sell this one
too
okay
welcome uh we don't need to enhance
anymore cuz they're maximum enhanced
right so we're just going to
[Music]
upgrade cute she do be a genius a I love
her L we need to do the the Japanese
version of the Shark Tank
soon Kawai positive
genius is that what she calls herself
cuz that is oh
kpg very similar to kfp I like it how
about this 14 14 not hold this one thank
you thank you how about
this I got
thanks this one
M money already
[\h__\h] but you guys who else agrees that
that laas is easier than Lou Who would
agree with that your name's in the hair
color right like the oranges she has
pretty Orange orangish hair yeah I feel
like
visually when they become 3D I think
like we'll look pretty nice next to each
other no no
no the minions are harder I never got to
laas
oh laas is
strong laas is easier to read her
attacks oh hit boxes are huge her
attacks hit boxes or her own hitbox cuz
her horns are so big big and white her
alt is
crazy it's okay if I die I will accept
it if it
happens oh I don't get healed here
interesting I thought I would I did get
more perfect Dodges off of laplus than
any other
boss once you learn it's not so bad okay
but it will be a first try I hope I win
on first try oh we're getting deeper I
see I see I see like a whole like
like RPG style we start outside on the
grass and this and that and then we get
into the air on two a battleship and
then we get inside the factory destroy
the boss and then everything explodes
that kind of like run down I like
it yeah it feels familiar like in tales
off games you often end up in like a
factory looking place like
this okay no Minion Time
k k my
dream help
me thank
you
beo oh laas
horns did you guys see what I did with
the thumbnail I put her horns like I I
put everybody on the thumbnail I was
like okay where did I put lap blast this
is like unbalanced I have no space for
her so it's like okay you know what I'm
going to put her behind me so I have her
horns on my
body what is this boxing gloves
increases the damage of normal and power
attacks by 20%
wow not bad the ramen is good man you Bo
Ramen oh no I want to eat ramen oh it's
only one item
no I want to get the mace though now I
only almost only have healing items oh
well let me do up the other ones then
100% heal oh you like the thumbnail
y yeah I had to ask to get like some pgs
and stuff of the characters cuz I
couldn't find anything on Google not
even the logo as a PNG on Google guys
what are you doing what are you doing so
hard to create a thumpnail can't work
like
this but I was I was helped
immediately I got the
contact
stop oh nice level
[Music]
up
death
death it's in the steam files maybe oh I
never thought about looking there but I
also wanted like high definition um pgs
of the characters to rearrange it
because the pictures that are on the
internet on Google are either low rest
or arrange in a way that is kind of
difficult with the logo in a position
where I can't really put myself in a
good position you know it's really
difficult you know trying to make
thumbnails where there's a lot of
characters that you want to show and
there's a big ass logo and you got to
put yourself somewhere as
well so much to
consider wow where did that cat hair
come
[Music]
from
oh let me help you Yi
me got to keep this one alive yo really
important
that's
you so many enemies everybody is my
enemies such an edgy thing to say or
collap game 100% or multiplay Bo game
it's gotten a lot of phras oh is it
online co-op though that's always very
important a lot of games are just uh
local co-op but lot of Steam games are
online co-op thank
God
uh-oh Yi mean Yi mean Yi
mean Yi
mean Yi mean you little bu [\h__\h] stay
alive if you die I'm going to kill
you
uh oh Super Chat nice to let me use that
I don't have to heal you forever and
ever and ever and
ever take this take
[Music]
that
increases speed by
50% that sounds pretty cool but at this
point I just want to be able to heal
myself as much as I can to stay
[Music]
safe mik is in it and I swear too at
least one of the voices sounds a wait in
this game or what are you talking about
what are we talking about you don't use
Mayo that much that's
true but
but
still T is not a heal oh wait what was
the
T what does it
do give me die excuse me increases
overall damage oh wait I mean I like
that
too I might need that I I think I prefer
that over
the
um speed buff
are you ready yukim
mean another yukim mean this is good oh
[\h__\h] uh what [\h__\h] did I just
do I don't really want to use nissa's
needle up like this because I think you
have seen my Strat with the needle
Strat is pretty good pretty good
Strat
I like my needle
Strat please give me more
needles sound needle sound needle Wooh
with a fork yeah I can eat the ramen
with
that uh H oh
shiny o but it's just not it doesn't
even have any extra skills not this one
don't make this one shiny
going to make me mad that's
all 136 HP though yeah the stats are
good yeah but you don't give any extra
stats oh P Senai what are you doing why
are you looking at this Atomic
explosive jug eh you're eyeing it it
concerns
me
oh more
needles let's [\h__\h]
go they hurt me the game hurt me it's
like oh I'll give you I'll give you
exactly what you want who the [\h__\h] froze
me who did
[Music]
that I want the Pebbles too give me the
Pebbles
oh ni kind of wasted the beetle
sorry she's preparing she's she's she's
uh
researching I think I'll
replace with the bump I like the bump
quite much oh no the Pebbles
[Music]
too should I switch out the Mayo we have
a full heel and a dangle heel no I'll
keep it I'll keep
[Music]
itam a DLC boss that would be amazing a
[\h__\h] why did I just use by accident I
used the M but it's okay it's a it's a
heal over
time yeah yeah why
not
sometimes I just use items accidentally
cuz I'm
[Music]
stupid the coyotes they don't look like
enemies to me they look like minions to
mean like fans the good
ones cuz their color is so cute I want
to protect them I want to cuddle
them I can't differentiate them
where are we right now 52
okay oh [\h__\h] no I used the mail
again Mystic what's
happening hey yo there's so many [\h__\h]
baseballs wait aren't there what's over
there baseballs how many is maximum
stack for
baseballs let me just switch out to base
balls for now cuz we're still far from
the boss so I'm fine with these spamming
attack items 38 let's go 100 ooh do they
what the [\h__\h]
La what's that SM smile
eh get that smug smile off of your face
you dealing with a senpai you know that
right
little
[\h__\h] I kind of want the maze oh you're
still here I'm not anymore
oh
nice just thinking about
Earth I like
us s Critical Hits heal a small % of HP
mhm Pizza what is the pizza doing here
and the Phoenix sword oh wait I have
only one more or two more balls is there
enemies
coming
[Music]
yeah wait I want to use my no stop
stalking me
how we doing over
here another
nickel I will gladly help you out pza
heals minions oh not
all well I have no
space Oh
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I wonder how the other characters
attack Don't You Dare die on me
now cuz like n's attack is
pretty
small close combat so feels like uh
sometimes I'm just hitting nothing
what then uses a
gun
M I like all these items but I think
we're leaving the
area spoilers they're all cute a Oh wait
we're still staying are we
staying I think we're staying
yeah
right I should have healed them n died
died should have healed them before I
moved
on
um wait let me go grab
something don't don't don't do it don't
don't do it don't do it no no no Dodge
everybody oh
[\h__\h] no I lost two
more no it's so over it is so over I
can't even see who are the enemies
anymore I feel like my brain is hurting
no it's so over it's so over
ah it's so
over it's so [\h__\h]
over
ah probably going to lose another one at
this
point well I don't know I might get
another one wait even you in the last
pickle these minions are really strong
yeah ah
[\h__\h] at least I got more
needles I
mean I mean that's not good that's not
good at
[Music]
all of um weren't there more here
no uhuh uhuh
uhuh
a not sure what to do K and G yeah
they're really
tough this item really strong okay yeah
I am bringing that one but I wish I had
a few
more I mean I got some good stuff
here okay healing items on
there I wish I could bring
[Music]
more you can still beat Le I believe in
you yeah I mean the other bosses I I
didn't do too badly oh we're still only
at threee we can get some new minions
still possibly
then I guess I'll use my my Phoenix
sword a little bit for now a new ni
thank
you sheh that pretty
dramatic yeah we like
that
that's that's very epic when there's a a
group of enemies all in one
spot let's heal them even though there's
a lot of super chats there but it works
this way
too doio
[Music]
doio no no no no wrong
thing come
on
I wonder what does it mean when they
have like a yellow
outline the
[Music]
enemies oh oh
wait super armor okay
is my Yi me still alive
okay okay they're dead oh God there's
more oh
God oh God where am
I oh
[\h__\h] I need to heal
them why did I do that I don't [\h__\h]
know I don't [\h__\h] know I'm desperate
okay I'm
desperate I'm [\h__\h] desperate was that
okay to
do oh oh they're dead is that good yeah
okay I I need those minions I need
[Music]
them open the [\h__\h]
up all the swords what do I have
should
I I'll use the Pebbles up and then I can
get go back and get a sword
maybe okay another Minion that's
good a yeah feel free to attack
me
don't run out of there stay in there
yeah yeah yeah yeah good job good
job H wait I have one more but I'll take
this no not
that y what's happening over there I'm
coming [\h__\h] off fluffy fat
bird hawk is not in
demand at the moment at least
[Music]
no y give
meus oh my God come on no Y is going to
die
ah y mean big O big
U oh
no
holy [\h__\h] they're so
strong oh my God stop it wait Did
I oh no you're
here oh level up holy [\h__\h] this is rough
this is really
tough oh idle costume ultimate meter
charges Auto magly over
time I see I
see oh my
God I don't know guys I don't think I'll
I'll oh I don't think I'll be fine the
super chats yeah I can run back for
them I
mean I could also just heal them here
normally and take the Super chats into
the next
stage but what do you think Super chats
over a different item that I could be
bringing with
[Music]
me you know you don't have to one shot
every I want what do you mean what first
try would be
amazing yeah Super Chat are better than
Mayo Mayo might be a good idea sounds
good I don't think you'll have time to
Super Chat mid boss yeah that's also a
thing
[Music]
h i so worried that
my my ulti will not be ready when I need
it which actually couldn't I
wear for a little while before I go to
the bus couldn't I just wear this
now and then switch back to the
Cho
it's
that came at the perfect [\h__\h] time
that
item I'm just going to AFK a little bit
yeah talk time
easy um did you guys see the schedule
schedule looking pretty good we're back
to like a normal schedule it's not on
the schedule but I will be at a Bankok
event I mean from home I'm not going to
Bangkok and The takoni Fan event I'll be
there and oh my God so much nice cool
merch has been prepared cool art and I
think the same artist you know when I
retweeted isn't that the same artist
that D all the all the stuff all the
promotional art it looked like the same
art
style yakusa back on the menu
[Music]
woohoo 18 needles is pretty [\h__\h] good
the art was so pretty yeah climbing game
was a big surprise for me I thought
well flavor of the month I'm I'm here
I'm ready I might as well go for it why
not the AR here tweeted I follow for so
long the art is great oh
really I really like the art style so I
was really happy to see some more art 55
is next I know that's why I'm trying to
not go but my ulti is pretty much
charged up now
yeah Cy birthday yeah I'll be at K's
birthday I'll probably also call in
because it's at a good time for me just
say happy birthday once
again the train differences game ah yeah
yeah yeah I I wouldn't mind looking into
that game either maybe next
week uh we're going to wear this of
course
switch I wonder how quickly you'll get
fed up with tomorrow's game hm yeah I
rarely play those kind of games I never
played the what's it called the the one
in
the uh what do you what do you call that
one the one that climbs up they're
getting over it yeah never played that
one
before I'm so going to die I'm so going
to
die
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
or at least we got another Yuki
me so it's always first like a few
minions and then the boss
right I all these items I want to keep
for the boss so if anything I might use
the star if it looks really bad but like
for the minions then it doesn't look
scared she's really excited yeah I
switched the cost double
check
yeah yeah
K there will be kind of
oh
oh wait there's no like
oh there's not lap right
away
[\h__\h]
Kyla wow I guess yeah that's how you do
it before a final final Final
Boss you got to give him one more chance
to heal back up and everything yeah then
I didn't need to heal my ALT all the way
back up possibly I don't
know
wait eh is is there more minions
coming yeah
right oh [\h__\h] why is so in the corner I
didn't realize I was so far in the
corner oh oh no oh no oh this is a good
weapon not the [\h__\h] tornadoes again
I'll will take you down I'll take you
down and that stinky Ora together with
you oh he's already dead nice no more
tornadoes
oh die please just
die don't [\h__\h] freeze me oh my
God
ooh so many Phoenix
swords oh my
God
no not the Yuki me not the Yuki me okay
okay okay okay we live we live for
another day I know I know I know the
yukim is so
[\h__\h] easy to
die okay I dropped the
canata uh Stars I don't know the Phoenix
swords are pretty damn good too a there
she is I thought we were going into a
fire uh into a campfire
again the gloves
yeah keep the
star really star over sword
okay 25% chance to not consume uh yeah
Nar ah oopsie
uh taking it with me I dropped the super
chats
should
I
yeah have some super
chats don't throw them on the full HP
one okay maybe maybe h no Kyla doesn't
sell or maybe this time she sells
some consumables no but we can upgrade
we can use up all our [\h__\h]
money one everything
please this
one luck attack
death maybe all on that one oh I got an
achievement cuz I upgraded to
I'll just put it on on the maid headen
because it has everything I want the HP
the crit to death totally no pressure ah
I'm out of money now I wish I could sell
at her place
too no money no money
yeah
okay
ah well I'm not even full HP there we go
one more one more
and now do we go straight into the boss
or still
Minions Let me let me wait for my heal
thing a little
bit no rush no
pressure yeah let's wait for the ability
boss straight away oh [\h__\h]
La you have to be nice to me you stole
my uniform
before you you you have have to
apologize to
me okay I'm going to use my my needle
Strat I hope she doesn't move too fast
around shrank my
uniform I can't do it I can't do it I
can't
oh
oh a
[\h__\h] when she's on the ground it doesn't
hurt her does
[Music]
it oh
what Yi mean dies wait Super Chat I
don't have them anymore
right I'm not going to do
it damn she's got good
HP
wait wait what am I what am I
doing
ha so
over stps items let's
go
what's that what's that doing again oh
n get out of
there there super Chats on the
ground ah used the full heal by
accident
a
[\h__\h] h
sorry I'm like super focused there's
up
it's
over
foree
[Music]
speee
he
got
just in case cuz I don't want to
die
no wa
R I was about to say like oh my God I
died I was like I want to heal oh my
what I did it I did it first
right I'm [\h__\h] did it oh let's go I'm
a G yo that was so close at the end the
clutch I ran out of all everything oh
and I was like oh yeah those items like
I I got another bomb I got a can star
that's pretty good I can use that but
I'm dying I kind of need healing
on let's
go my God I did it oh and I think this
is overall first try because you can't
even consider the first uh [\h__\h] death
because COI yeah because because that
was I was just like learning the game
still oh my God
who oh my god did you did you notice how
[\h__\h] focused I
was
wa yeah the beetle thank God for the
beetle my real minion oh [\h__\h] timer redu
the charge time why do I still get items
isn't it over after this what happens
after this it's been ages since you were
that
quiet the ult but the AL wasn't so bad
ulti wasn't so bad I I also like like
how she brings everyone back in that's
kind of um sweet and deep and
emotional you you tapped back to see why
were you not watching a the boss
fight what do you mean 61 this should be
over now give me a
break damn you Dodges reg thank you I
tried there's still a lot that she got
me with but I I an attempt was
made I so sick yeah you joined
membership for that thank
[Music]
you no way I'm not ready for you unle
look at me oh
y okay okay you guys seeing the good
within the members of HX nipple extended
a friendly offer a the girls of HX can
join the be group and take over the
world in a different way
a do HX instead became a group of idols
and took the wild through the stages
dead yeah cute wholesome ending happened
in real life back in the office the
members of nipple andx received a
message and a massage hopefully they
were called to help save some fans
somewhere else you mean Holo cure and
and so nepple and Hol X joins forces and
heads off the do this as Idol wait is
this like the the prequel to Hol X but
aren't we forgetting something no it
doesn't like no Yago doesn't matter no
no no no no no no no no no no no you
don't need to bring Yago into this no
this is about us okay
no dislikes 211 what the [\h__\h] is wrong
with you
guys why what what makes dislikes the
times I got hit
or what is
that yeah crack that
spun getting knocked down I got knocked
down 211 times wow I got knocked down
but I get up
again total subscribers 18 18,000 new
subscribers that's pretty [\h__\h]
good yo I think I mean for me
like Yay who cares about the dislikes
yay 2 and 1 half hours you guys said
like uh if you're fast takes 1 hour
usually takes like around what two hours
I was like pretty slow I guess but I was
I was uh learning everything I was
taking my time ah
Kyla what do you mean I need to get some
help what do you mean I I just won I
don't need to get any help lot of AFK
healing time not not that much I think
it's it's a just a normal thing to do
probably
[Music]
anyway my first beat them up game really
what yeah I I don't have much experience
with beat them UPS is this a beat them
up this time she didn't need help y
remember to check out the two snacks on
the gold he this is amazing yeah this
artist is pretty cool she's about to
blow everyone up
damn H oh you can play them oh but then
they'll fight themselves or what versus
mode is now unlocked what's versus mode
Hard Mode no no thank
[Music]
you that's amazing the game is great I
want to do collabo yeah the art is so
cool too I have to say like both the
pixel art and this like main theme
art the gallery
yeah cute oh oh the aqua one
Andy she has
free oh table slam oh I like am table
slams God damn it the moim Miko art is
so [\h__\h]
good yeah the the bio one I just saw her
like this exactly like this in the new
video oh cute
oo oh my God fauna bald fauna she's real
I thought she was only my
[Music]
nightmares cooking hide hi hide do you
say hide or
hi
biscuit nice nice cute
emotes where are the waa emotes guys
hide okay oh my God the G
shark and the I dumpy it's so
shiny there it is
akashian oh I know these the bunk one
didn't that exist before the finger
heart I'm not sure about that one holy
[\h__\h] the gorilla one is
crazy ah cute I've seen those before can
I use them the prey one is really nice
although I want to use the the the
little [\h__\h] one it looks better than the
angry one that I drew actually wait we
have a little you little [\h__\h]
anyone we have our own now but this one
just looks like an angry one my angry
one I don't like so much the one that I
drew you know what I just realized the
one in the middle from
koni it her sleeves make me think of
like good or bal's
teeth also what the [\h__\h]
coobo coobo you're not supposed to smoke
what the [\h__\h] who taught her about
smoking who who let her buy
cigarettes what the [\h__\h] I'm taking
those away unless they're candy but why
are they smoking huh explain oh my God
oh my God the laas let's go it vot holy
[\h__\h]
sheesh damn these are
crazy ah ah the Nesta one I have I like
the m m
[Music]
one wa the Dead one is that paa oh my
God I like it oh my God the feet out of
all the nice stamps I got I got the
[\h__\h] foot can you believe
it
o wa
we only one
stamp Everybody Clap Your Hands the a is
one of the greatest H life fan arts that
was ever made oh that's it
nice flushed Su is quite something and
what beam cute what made on nice that's
one of the best ones I
think
nice this is good inspiration too for if
I ever want to get more or if I ever can
get new emotes cuz we're full anyway but
if I'm like oh what could I get but all
usually like a lot of these maybe might
not work so well like for example the
the dumpy one you would make you would
need to make a closeup of the dumpy
probably cuz like this in tiny version
it's not going to look so
good wait the
the isn't that like a Pog face or so I'm
not so sure like i' I've seen this face
before the one from hot man in the
middle but I'm not sure what it was
called is that POG or a Pog
CH it's it's it's a Pog
right looks funny the shark is so good
though nice okay wow I can't believe I
did
it wow and it was so clutch in the end
that was
exciting I almost died at that moment
the where where it freezes kind of I was
like wait did I die or did the boss die
holy [\h__\h] I could have easily died in
that
moment yeah game yeah we can put it on a
finished games list
[Music]
Yahoo um if I play
coab even if the other player has not
unlocked these characters yet can I play
with them anyway while they're in it
probably probably yeah
right yeah
okay high
tension uhhuh uh uh-huh yeah cuz it's
like Remote
Play okay I think next week we might
play this again with someone I wonder
who wants to play with me there's many
options going to invite
someone
yeah maybe maybe maybe someone who
played solo but not Co-op yet would be
good maybe cuz then they know what
they're doing but they also haven't
experienced Co-op
yet yeah I know narissa played it solo
uh like last night for
me so she's an option but maybe she
already has plans to play co-op with
someone else in that case I'll look for
someone else
I'll check oh there's a lag
we he'll be fine it'll be
fine n
n i I don't
[Music]
know no I don't want to bother
[Laughter]
her yeah maybe like ID
someone question mark question mark
question mark then it didn't get fire
what she's in the
game why are you getting shy for N I
don't know we haven't talked in a long
time
game I so thank God that I finished it
then I don't feel bad for ending it here
nicely and reading super chats and yeah
we have some
nice super chats to read
right did I finish the ones from the big
one the big the big one the waiting room
SL talking about the concert one did I
not
[\h__\h] do you remember where I stopped cuz
I don't let's let's quit that was a lot
of fun I want to say I don't know if the
if no ref and Kai are watching or
anything but just want to say great
great one I saw like a a tweet from Kai
about like criticism or so but honestly
I have nothing to criticize really even
the saving thing is doesn't bother me
really um
no the only thing is the menu of selling
items but the play uh uh anything about
like the the the the the how to say the
game itself nothing bothered me it was
great the uh soundtrack was great the
art was great it was a lot of fun it was
a good
difficulty there was nothing that I
would criticize
really David left what David you worked
on this too I'm so
sorry you're watching let's go it was
great like I really had a good time and
I'm actually feeling very
um like confidence boosted right now so
it it made me feel
good sorry sorry David you're here so
often I don't I didn't even realize you
worked on this sorry sorry sorry sorry
he brought out like every death and
every artist a teamwork that's so
sweet yeah you did great first beat
first try beat everybody yeah I mean
except for K but I mean that one really
like you shouldn't even consider that I
was literally this was like a tutorial
it was like a tutorial
okay yeah I can imagine they worked
really hard on it yeah it turned out
amazing it feels like a really good game
and like I feel like for holo cure that
was based off another game and like you
had a base and everything but this is
like completely I mean it might it might
still have like similar games somewhere
out there right cuz I mean the the
concept of it seems really simple but
they made it from scratch right so it's
amazing and it's free again why why do
you make it free again oh my
God I never lost a coyote no never never
never never I don't remember remember
such a thing
either beaten lups yeah of course there
are tons yeah but like I think hir was
very obviously very strongly just based
off of that vampire game thingy
MH to keep up the Senpai bit no no no no
I don't lose to my senis or my K eyes it
doesn't matter I don't
differentiate yeah they deserve
compensation and you sent money to
me you know that's not going to them
right you know
that thank you though I appreciate
it thank you okay uh let's go to my
office I don't know if it's usable right
now let's see oh looks
good uh let me
just find
the chat
there it
is good
question ah ah
uhhuh
C you know I wore my uniform today which
is pretty rare it's only because I
thought it kind of
fits um the vibe a little bit
which is surprising normally I don't
wear it much
so an empty TV spot yeah yeah I don't
know why it's empty I always I could
fill it with something but yeah not now
I'll fill it
[Music]
eventually
uh
bgm what do you want to hear
guys you see frogy waa is back spinning
for
eternity thank you for playing I'm so
happy you to see you had a blast game
yay I really did I didn't not want to
play it again I hope they add more more
like like levels I guess more bosses to
fight I I mean there was implied that
there's Yago and I guess the hard mode
could possibly look different I don't
know if it looks different or if it just
feels
different
yeah new story mode with fre gloss oh
they could do regloss versus Advent or
so I don't know just throwing that out
there I don't know maybe they already
have an
idea but I'm sure it took them a long
time to make this so don't want to put
too much pressure onto them
yeah okay guys I
recently cleaned up my download folder
right and I found a lot of unnamed audio
stock files in there and then I named a
few ones
but uh a lot of them are still
unnamed but I have some nice bgms I
think uh
wait it's not going to the
right let me detach the PlayStation
controller there we
go isn't this
nice do you hear
it and then I have some other
ones which ones are
[Music]
new comfy right yeah I have a lot of
comfy
[Music]
stuff here let me put some unnamed ones
in here what is
this
jungle this one's
[Music]
nice oh
nice o Loi
chill
wow battle they're all from audio stock
but a lot of them are often like
inspired by certain games
[Music]
yeah Eerie a lot all of them are uh a
lot of them are pretty suitable
for that's done so let's play this for
now and then if we get sick of it we can
switch it tomorrow we play a rage game
apparently apparently it's a rage
game here is schedule by the way we have
today Holo X break tomorrow a difficult
game about climbing which is the rage
game apparently members only I'm not
sure what we're doing yet I'm still
thinking about it release party
C should be pretty exciting um I'll have
a
guest on the stream
too and then we'll release the MV after
it I was told that uh the release will
be at midnight in every country
from Friday to Saturday midnight but
they told me that before and then still
it released early and I was like what
can we not release it simultaneously and
they were like no and I'm like but we
kind of did that before did we not
that's why I asked you guys in the
community board
yesterday and then then was like okay
maybe that did happen but they say we
never did that before like the music
department says that that doesn't we
can't do that we can't simultaneously
release unless it's like um
what's it called Universal or show but
then again we kind of did it did we
not yeah POV so I don't know they say
the releas is midnight
jst and midnight everywhere else like in
your own country like local midnight
yeah I'm being
gaslighted we'll see maybe let's just
say that for now and then if we're lucky
it releases everywhere when it hits
midnight in Japan
oh but the MV I will release um 1000
p.m. my time I guess so an hour after
the uh release party starts that's the
plan and then by that time you should
already be able to listen to it the
music in Japan on Spotify
Etc um where it released until that time
unless if it released simultaneously
then everybody can listen to it before
the MV
drops really depends what happens cuz
cuz not
sure
H we'll see I guess I think the first
and Friday times are a little off for
E are
they AR they are you
sure oh yeah
May um maybe yeah oopsie don't know how
that happened well you'll see when it
happens and then we'll play like a
dragon on the uh weekend I'm
also going to be uh at that event I have
to get up really early or stay up really
late for my panel and also have Mee and
greets that actually I do have Mee and
GRE don't I and they weren't on my
Google Calendar so I'm actually not sure
when they're happening
huh I didn't consider that when I was
making the schedule there's a small
chance that maybe one Yakuza stream will
be uh
cancelled because maybe maybe the meet
and greets are overlapping or something
like
that
for when are the meet and greets
happening
time I think there's meet and
Grace yeah for me in my time zone
there's a rehearsal on Saturday and then
Sunday morning like 6:00 or 7 a.m. or
something like that is the panel that
I'm doing with cie just so you know it's
like a fan event not not Fan event it's
a a Takami only event it's not in a
convention it's like its own event in
Bangkok and we are appearing as Takami
it's only Takami and nothing else pretty
nice we're feeling pretty special it's
like Takami
convention post pic yeah you guys post
PS it's basically the size of a collab o
I don't know about the
size I feel like it might be
bigger cuz we're also
like actually I have no idea what the
venue is
like they already announced the venue
I'm pretty sure so I probably could look
it up
too be you can't be there in person for
song CL yeah what is that like only one
day
or how does that
work I know it's like some cultural
event where you dress up nicely true
digital Park Grand Hall so it's like a a
seminar room of a hotel or something
like
that let me Google
[Music]
this oh oh it's definitely bigger than a
collab
Cafe
oh
oh what that's that's big there's
several
rooms so I don't know if there uh if
they have all of the rooms or just a few
or just one but they could in theory
have several rooms there's some
interesting looking
ones it's free days
a local Festival so nice yeah I wish I
could be there in person to enjoy it
locally at at the
IRL one day of playing with water but
people usually just do so all three days
yeah I sound like cuz like they put
water guns on us in the promotional art
and all
that looks like fun looks
cute yeah there's other activities too
but for for Stuff where I actually am
involved in and have to be available for
is like meat and green and
the and the like so to say panel
performance
[Music]
whatever but there should be more to do
for the
fans
yeah your wateran has a color scheme up
your sword yeah
it looks so nice can we make it into
merch oh oh
[Music]
was I don't have to cook because I
cooked already but you know what I got
to do I got to do something really
quickly I have to cancel an appointment
really
fast um there's an appointment that I
just keep on
cancelling over the course of several
months now it's not a doctor's
appointment um wait let me get my phone
really quick
[Music]
cuz have my
phone
now it's
um no it's pretty important but um I
keep on canceling it cuz I have to
prepare something for
it and print something out I think I I
need to print it out I don't know if I
could write it by hand but I think I
kind of need to make it look good and
print it
out um and my printer doesn't work and
so I was going to like go to the print
shop or whatever but then also like
preparing the thing also takes some time
and today I didn't get to do it again
again and I was actually I already
canceled the appointment like
appointment was supposed to be today
then I canceled it and I put it on
tomorrow and you know how many times
I've done this probably like 10 times
already and they must think like why is
this lady always making appointments and
always canceling it like a few hours
before midnight why why
why
well let me see
um I wonder if some one day they'll
[\h__\h] back me I just don't feel
confident that I can really get it
ready
until I try I'll put it this time I'll
put it like I think maybe on Friday cuz
the stream is so late I feel like I have
time let me
see yeah I should have time let's let's
aim for Friday how about
that cancel cancel so nice I can cancel
so last minute I love it thank you so
much so
easy they just make it too easy for
[Music]
me just get everything ready and dead
make it
a but then I have nothing pressuring me
but yeah I really got to do it like it's
been um like two months or so no maybe
even more I've been I've been making
appoint appointments and canceling them
over the course of like three months or
so well it wasn't pressuring in the
beginning but now I really should do
[Music]
it I didn't say what it is it it's just
something
something like bureaucratic
stuff it is important is it has to get
done at some point basically you
disappoint me wa thank you I disappoint
myself
too they would make back if there's
cancellation fees for real
if I could write it down by hand then I
think yeah but I need to probably print
out stuff
no no not taxes I'm so confused my tax
lady wrote to me the other day like
maybe 3 weeks ago or so and she was like
Hey I'm going on vacation on this day
and we really need to finish up this tax
year of
2022 I'm like yeah okay no problem um
there was just like two more things that
I needed to send her and I've been
trying to get a hold of these things
like the the males
bill for several times but like like
once I called uh I contacted the uh I
contacted booking first and they told me
no we can't give you the bill you should
go to the go contact the accommodation
for it and then I contact them and
they're like no we cannot give it to you
you have to contact booking.com and I
did that like several times I called
them I did it over email and so
on and several times they were like no
go to the the other one and there uh the
hotel was basically saying yeah you
booked it for booking.com so you need to
get it for booking.com because there's
different prices and I as someone who
worked for a hotel I can tell you that
that is true that is what we were told
to tell the guests if they ask for a
bill for a Booking.com booked stay we
need to tell them we cannot give you the
bill you need to get it from booking.com
that's what I was told when I worked at
a hotel that I was told this is how it
is because the prices May differ like
different
fees and uh the stay like booking.com
gets maybe a part of the money or so so
um the bill that we would be able to
print in our on our side would show a
different price I think something like
that uh yeah but but then po was saying
no that is not true you need to get it
from the accommodation blah blah blah I
went back and forth several times and I
told them well you know what they told
me they told me to go to you and you
telling me to go to them and then you
know that happened several times already
so
annoying and it took quite a while this
correspondence at some point I gave up
and then I now I tried it again because
she uh stressed me out about I was like
okay okay I'll get it done
yeah yeah I think that's true yeah yeah
but then I don't know why booking.com
was being like so annoying about it like
just give me the [\h__\h] bill you know
who in the end ended up giving me the
bill to
accommodation because booking the come
insisted on like saying no that's not
true you can get the bill from them they
have to give it to you and I'm like okay
but they don't want to give it to me so
you kind of have to hi Johnny tell them
tell them that they are allowed to give
it to
me yeah
finally they communicated with each
other and then I finally got the bill
that's one of the things I wanted them
uh I wanted to get for the tax stuff and
then I sent these things to her before
the deadline that she gave me several
days before it and it's been weeks now
she never replied to me so I'm like hm
did she take care of it
or what's going
on I don't
[Music]
know
no uh she might still be on vacation but
I I sent it to her like 4 days or so
before she went on vacation and I think
she must be back from her vacation by
now but whatever I did my thing I did my
part
whatever
you want to be angry for me for the
booking.com thing or for the text not
replying thing it's okay I mean the
booking.com just kind of pissed me off
because I worked at a hotel so I know
that booking.com has to give me the
bill yet they didn't want to give it to
me what's wrong with
[Music]
them but yeah it's not about that the
appointment is not about that I I'll try
to get the appointment for Friday can
you guys remind me in the and when you
reply to me
afterwards like hey make make a new
appointment can you guys can somebody
say that to me in the kfb hashtag or
something like that thank
you how do you guys feel being used in
this way Han H I wanted to say I wanted
to post a picture actually because I
finally got some
merchandise it's so nice that you're
sending a super chat so I can bring up
your name so
randomly I finally got um a lot of my
whole life merchandise and I got a lot
of fan letters and stuff and a few gifts
and so on and one of them was a polar W
of you signed by
you I think you were wearing a one piece
cosplay there's this one piece character
right with the with like a bikini
top I think I know her name even not not
the the orange haired one um the one
with the I think black hair
not
Namy Robin or maybe it was Robin h no
yeah boa hanock I think it's Bo hanok
you guys are misleading me I was about
to say something with Bo Bo yeah boa
hancok I got the Polaroid from when is
this how how late did I receive this
when was I supposed to get
this you look so pretty hone I finally
got that Polaroid better later than
never right
beat
scented ah last year like around connect
the world
time it's almost like having a Polaroid
of you H almost feels like I met you
it's so close yet so
far during AF in December wait why is
there different information on when that
[Music]
was
ah another one me your house yeah I also
buy your K thank you you mean the Ki
doll or the froggy waa doll cuz I got
new new doll right now should I put this
wait should I put it
here very cluttered screen
sorry
all of the
Dolls thank you so much honey the Cy
chicken oh yeah yeah yeah I received
that one too recently it's so cute it's
so chunky isn't it but look Han look
look look
look P waa
plushy now
available yeah frog frog Link in
description
everybody I'll make sure that everything
looks good for plushy looks so cute you
can take off the hood look it's about
the size of Dino gura I think should
[Music]
be I need to you
know get money for the suffering I've
been through by Froggy W's
hands yeah I know most of you already
took care of it and bought it if you
were able to thank you so
much I want to see cuz Dino gura also
kind of green looking can you put them
next to each other if you have a dino
gura at home
please thank you
[Music]
honey you're so beautiful you're so
beautiful
oh I have a cosplay a simple pretty
simple simple cosplay idea for
[Music]
you um wait I don't have a screenshot of
that right now do I I do did you see
this did you see this
new accessory of me the
Cape can you do this with
no
cuz
look
can you do this with no no bikini
underneath under Boop under Boop
please we have no yeah no cloes please
personal
request I think you have great potential
for under underbob
underbob it will look so good it will
look so
good just the cape I mean underne under
uh on the bottom I don't know you can
wear the jeans or whatever you
[Music]
want ask you for lose no it's just like
perfect for
her cuz
[Music]
ah she will look so good with the
cape I think she's
[Music]
motivated sorry sorry hone sorry sorry
Mommy
you're
SC looking forward to
it yes he looks good at anything that is
100% true I always love seeing Kan on my
Twitter
timeline it's like I
don't I don't follow many cosplayers on
my main
and like especially like cosplayers who
do more like spicy stuff I don't follow
really anyone besides Han but for Han
I'm just always happy to see what she's
up
to I'll do it X xas as a photo book
Christmas Christmas photo book let's go
okay that's a long time we have to
wait but it will be worth it y frogy wa
for
[Music]
Christmas yay I sometimes that spicy
yeah kind of spicy although like um the
Theus Theus lingerie that she
designs I feel like they are you know
they're so frilly and so cute so many
Frills and laces and all that it's like
um like a like a almost like an idol
outfit so I don't really see it as a
loot
thing but damn
got a damn nice figure I envy it so bad
holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] no it's 100% tasteful it's very
artistic like I just see it as art and
she makes all of those herself so it's
like she just uses it as a creativity
Outlet I really like the cute
designs I'm So based for that request
right I I
know I know things Iris hasn't redeemed
her Christmas steam present yet andless
to Tred to ask you about it there's a
clip why ask why ask me about it did I
did I not send her the
link or the code why would she need to
ask me about
it did I
not is she maybe CU I think one
person I think one person I didn't get
to send
a code because uh you know I was in a
clutch situation where I ended up having
to use honey bun
h no the bundle
thingy whatever it was called and the
game I wanted to give her wasn't on
there or so humble
Bund all right I'm just going for our
conversations I don't see a code so I
got to give her one at least she wants
it at least she wants
it I will hand made the cat don't
worry it will look so
nice I'm looking forward to it yay it
look so
good it's a recipe for Success trust
me cuz I I think I'm I missed out did I
miss out the time window of the steam
cell or did I just was I not just not
able
I think cuz we weren't friends and it
was like I had like one more
day and anybody who wasn't my steam
friend I couldn't buy anything for I
think that was my
problem
yeah and then everybody who wasn't my
steam friend which was basically
everybody besides myth I had to go for
Humble
Bundle
mhm yeah I look into it I don't remember
what I was going to buy her
I have to
check does she know she probably knows
what you probably told her you guys
probably told her and then she's like oh
I want
that metal wolf chaos
oh oh I'll go get it for
her
yeah
don't know if she knew only that it's
perfect for her oh so somebody told her
oh K gave you this perfect game for
Christmas and she's like what where
oopsie the US president one Ah that's a
crazy one such Crazy
[Music]
Games didn't Kelly or
so play it on stream like soon after I
did all of that go well done beating
whole X break thank you so much come
again oh yeah Kelly
did okay guys let's let's focus on super
chats
charby uh where did I leave off I
wonder yeah when I saw am and GAA play
that other game I was
like I want I want to looks fun let me
join
Richard what Richard was where I left
off or
what where was
I what
it wait I'm on the wrong one
here and Super
Chat he's a game character okay you guys
are confusing me
taimo
uh yeah okay could be yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah did I read the Typhon
one did I read it tyen are you here did
I read your Super
Chat let me change the bgm too since I
have so many
choices yeah I think so too I think I
did
then here we go Motion D for the
pinky is that is that a continuation
from a super chat or did you just start
the sentence like this Blown Away
period sounds like you cut off somewhere
Christmas it's not Christmas this
Christmas to
you all right I did mention suing
someone with his help that's right you
started it like that okay being inside
the concert hall is a whole different
experience for those kinds of concerts
right being able to actually Scream the
chance and have a whole building T along
it's different I hope n kfp notice how
much you killed it too I think I did I
keep on seeing like tweets that are from
um Japanese Bros that are like oh I
wonder when that song that kiata
performed releases I really liked it I
really died
it it does sound Christmas God damn
it how about
this successfully served
yay yeah so soon tell him tell him it's
going to be out Friday night oh
midnight Friday to Saturday usually hate
loud dark places but that
rocked yeah I'm sure it
did loud is loud definitely sucks but
when you're all like vibing to the same
thing and you all cheering the same
thing then it's it's it's the kind of
loud that you just feel a connection
with and you just feel like this is this
is your this is where you're supposed to
be then you feel comfortable cuz
everybody is like you know interested in
the same kind of
thing so you belong M so you can
tolerate the
noise yeah and the last sticks light up
the dark so no need to be
scared I'm so glad you went and I'm so
glad you had a great time it's a really
really special experience I hope many
people can make this experience in the
future
too thank you for going thank you for
supporting thank you for representing
[Music]
kfp
for free
rad oh G I'm so sorry ow I hope you're
feeling better by the time you read this
I have to say fifth Fest was awesome I'm
so happy I was able to experience it
even happier that I was able to see both
of your performances in person oh my God
so
sick um you are winning you're winning
chicken or I'm
[Music]
it was so hype I barely remember
anything aside from howling your
name did you just say howling because
there's owl in the world word word
because howling doesn't seem something
like an owl would
do and cheering as much as I could can't
wait for the vs to finally drop so I can
really live the moment yeah and get
pointed out by me permanently the whole
time I'm so
sorry
perhaps I've seen so many chickens
waddling around supporting you too even
SED to a couple and flew by some of
their events but I just watch them side
no not
[Applause]
again but when you talk to someone this
time right that's what's squawking to a
couple means you actually talked to some
this time right you didn't avoid
everybody
[Music]
right I hope so I think I'm sure people
would be excited to get to know
you don't be so
shy yeah
nice and overall this trip to Japan has
been really cool I've enjoyed trying out
as many waa food recommendations as
possible and could use some more still
have six days left oh that oh wow wow oh
damn so thank you w for inspiring me to
spread these old wings to fly and go do
new things and with the acrylic por
short as a little gift I'm happy to
celebrate my fourth birthday supporting
my favorite bird and most beloved ooshi
fling amazing and fiery hot Phoenix love
you wa I want more chimo a happy
birthday I love you too I'm so sorry I'm
so
sorry I'll try to not point you out
anymore when I see
[Music]
you at this point you're home yeah I
thought so but I was surprised you were
staying so long um next time next Fest
I'll try to make more even more maybe a
whole travel guide for you guys guys to
look into for your travels so you have
something to do I'll make you actually
we could even make that into a whole
stream making a travel guide for kfp who
go to
Japan could make a PDF or something or a
shitty PowerPoint presentation or
something like
that
yeah sounds great doesn't it well happy
happy birthday charity I want to sing
for you
cuz you sent free super chats holy [\h__\h]
Happy
Birthday to
you Happy
you happy
Birthday my dear
Trevor happy birthday to
you
wo
[Music]
sorry that's what you do after you done
singing
no wa there was no cake there was no
candles what was I blowing it
sorry fourth birthday already wow wow
wow wow wow wow wow thank you for
spending so much time here thank you for
not getting fed up with me
I was really scared I was really really
scared that you were maybe really really
really mad at me after the last M stream
and then you would leave the fandom I
was really scared so I was waiting I was
waiting for your reply but I don't think
you replied to my reply on the Twitter
on the on the YouTube comment section I
was like sorry and you didn't reply I
was like oh my God he hates me forever
but then I saw you um interact somewhere
somewhere else I was like okay I guess
it's
[Music]
fine yeah it's okay right you still love
me I love you
[Music]
too on to more gears together I did
reply but I'm not sure what happened
with you oh oh interesting what when I
checked it I didn't see her reply that's
so
weird H maybe it's here now maybe I need
to check it again thank you for being so
tolerant of
me I really appreciate it you're the
best thank you for
[Music]
everything
uh to tolerant oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] Studio no py D thank
you and Studio Rob thank you for the
pinky can you useful information time
useful shakespare yes The
Bard used the CW in his play 12 night
quote by my life this is my lady's hand
these be her very Seas her use and her
teas and do makes she her great peace
[Music]
no [\h__\h] way no way that
Shakespeare spelled
out I don't see the N but I guess the
end is the N I
know these be her very sees her 's
and leaving out the D her
te's thus makes she her Great Piece what
the [\h__\h] Shakespeare was Ry as hell but
like
[\h__\h] I mean maybe honestly C does I feel
like I heard it a lot of times in
medieval
shows if any anything I may have heard
it there more often than in other places
it it may have been more used back in
the day
no he invented a lot of words well he
didn't invent can't did
[Music]
he yes it's an old word right it does
sound old it has this uh it has this it
said a lot in game see there you go yeah
that's why it feels familiar it seems
like a like a term used more I mean
gimron is not you know it's fantasy but
still it seems like that kind of
vocabulary no no not the not the British
pronunciation of can no no no
no there's a lot of inua and Shakespeare
but a lot of it is hard to notice now
because the language has
[Music]
changed said more in BR than America
mhm yeah so um I don't know you say it's
useless information time but it's
definitely sparked
debate an interesting
discussion yeah based on War of Roses to
some extent
n [\h__\h] Love Game of Thrones H Jacob
[Music]
47 Soul you with the rainbow thank you
so much you make that stage on fire and
sweet love you wa oh sweet I think the
sweet is followed up by two hearts one
orange one blue one so I think it's a
reference to Cobalt M me and Cobalt
thank you for watching the concert both
the the concert excuse me
sorry sorry I stumbled all my
room what I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm
so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm
so
[Music]
sorry I was shy about saying about
before well I think I'm not shy about it
because it's just like it it it doesn't
sound like
a doesn't have such a bad implication to
me because it's just you
know it's just a random word to me it
doesn't mean anything to me cuz English
not my first
language I didn't drink the Red Bull no
but you know what I saw in the store I
saw Red Bull with like Korean writing on
it and I look closer and it seems like
some kind of
kwave version of Red Bull I'm like who I
can read
this didn't buy it though cuz I I don't
want to overuse energy
[Music]
drinks I I got excited to
see Korean writing
on Red Bull in
Austria
my Korean
revs I I'll be collabing with Goyle
surely soon so Korean reps will be
picked up again automatically for her
right no I didn't try a whole X energy
drink no no no no no I
didn't did you did Goyle answer you yeah
she answered me she's like um trying to
help me with um my suit like streaming
with it instead of just recording with
[Music]
it of course she replied to me she's
always eager to reply to
me oh see yeah that word in German I
would not like to say that I would
really not throw it around as much in
German at
all as in
English now that you say it in German to
me
I feel
flustered about saying
it that's a very I feel like that word
is more used in ger Germany than in
Austria
[Music]
though well yeah well yeah if that's how
if that's what you're hearing
well that is yeah okay that is
embarrassing
but but they say I served [\h__\h] so I
don't know it just changes it I think
it's good if we change the vibe of the
word a little
[Music]
bit we can change
it they already changed
it I I kind of get it more now if that's
really I didn't I didn't think about
that as the direct translation I just
thought generally about like like you
know the the V
word and then it wasn't so bad but if um
why don't I say you might think like why
doesn't she say that see I have a
completely different connection to the
c-word I just I just don't feel the same
way
about I'm too embarrassed to say the V
word also I feel still I have to like
really get
over
a hurdle to say the p word the p u SS y
word I I need to be quite Brave to say
that today I said it but uh I I it makes
me feel very anxious to say
[Laughter]
it yeah it's worse right yeah yeah I get
it I get it but
somehow because it's been used in slang
in a different way these past years I
think uh that's what makes me feel
like you
know it's
different but I own so many cats yeah
see even that that's interesting because
that doesn't make me feel more
comfortable saying the p word for cat
because I don't think it fits at all
it's just different it it's it's weird
for me I don't want to call a
cat that word cuz it's it's just
generally a stupid word I don't like
it it's not cute
either I don't like it at
all I'm so
selective it's just weird to call a cat
that I don't I don't think it's
suitable octopussy is something else o
excuse me octopusy is how you say
several
octopuses one octopus two octopuses that
that's just grandmar excuse
me it's just
plural shut up don't change
grandmar I like I like grandmar the way
it
is shout out to
Grandma
[Music]
shut up Ana thank you so much for the
rainbow it's beautiful just like you wow
smoo you C thanks for the red also for
your performance K you are the absolute
star of day one for
me why do I laugh like this
today so smug you're amazing it was my
birthday yesterday
19 damn
so I'm sending the super before I go to
Japan this Friday
9 oh I might not get to watch the
streams until I come
back
19 emotional
[Music]
damage thank thank you so much young lad
I appreciate your support of the Elder
L I wish you a happy birthday make sure
to to enjoy every day as it was your
last day because um you know I'm really
close to my last day already I feel so
that's how I live life and I I wish I
would have started earlier enjoying each
day as my last so that's what I want to
give to you as your birthday gift this
priority yeah this mindset is is really
important okay so I wish you all the
best I'm so glad you had fun in
Japan because Oh no you're going to
Japan after the Fest what you what what
that's the wrong order you you you you
kind
of messed up there um but enjoy your
time in
Japan and yeah thank you for the red
super chat thank you for caring about
your grandma
Takashi yeah thank
you you're so sweet you're so
kind are you still there I wonder you
got are you still in
[Music]
Japan this
escal you should you know people say you
don't ask a lady her age but I say you
don't tell a lady your age your own age
if it is quite below
seemingly um because it will cause some
serious emotional
damage don't tell the age huh also it's
19th month not 19 years
old oh
hallelujah how old are you then 18 17 16
are we going lower or are we going
higher but what a nice
misunderstanding well that is quite a
[Music]
relief oh
man what oh
emotional
healing no I didn't say the date it just
said in Brackets 19 which
implied they might be
19 but I guess it meant on the
[Music]
19 what I'm not in charge of those 12y
olds and I kind of doubt I have really
young people like that in the chat in
the Stream usually is anybody here 12
who here is
under
14 don't
lie you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] not a single one of you
no get out of here you m
[Music]
crazy people get out of here you're not
allowed on YouTube you're
banned I'll report you to the mods
Mist thank for the CH my
dear
[Music]
day one Expo and Stage free
only yeah yeah thank
you wow but that's so cool I mean you
didn't get the right ticket guess to see
my performance of
Kima but you still got to see some other
stuff that's exciting yeah as long as
you were able to watch on spawn
although cuz the thing is they the stage
one we're doing Expo right but stage two
like the evening ones were always after
Expo was over right so you could go to
Expo during the day and watch stage two
or stage free calmly at home but if you
want to watch the the early ones and you
kind of if you're also at Expo then you
kind of have to
yeah that's difficult that's to me that
sounds H like an unwelcome overlap if
you want to enjoy
both the international package was so
goed I'm glad it existed so I could buy
your stage yeah it seems to have been
like pretty damn good of a package I'm
glad so many of you guys were able to
make use of it and that it was actually
useful like I would have expected cuz
they added didn't they add wasn't it
including an accommodation but did it
include a flight no right no flight did
it include a
[Music]
flight they should have Expo end before
stage one yeah but then Expo would be so
short which already it was shorsh
considering how long you had to wait in
line for things
no flights but everything else yeah
that's really awesome I hope uh the
hotel was nice for you
guys what kind of Hotel was
it did everybody stay in the same
Hotel I wonder everybody who got the
that
package how many careers book to that
actually won the stage one and Expo 2
that's
amazing that's perfect
that's exactly what you want do you get
to like say what's your priority which
concert was different base of the
package ordered
oh I didn't stay at the hotel oh I put a
different Hotel so I'm closer to the
venue and didn't show up in the package
Hotel there are options for different
hotels I just stayed in my actual Hotel
the package hotels were far oh how far
are we
talking
I bought the package on depending on
what stage you wanted
oh we don't get to make priority but
most of us K guy W stage one
plus that without choosing priority or
so you get that just
randomly what [\h__\h] Goa lock
insane they had like four different
packages I think some in Tokyo others in
Cho oh oh yeah well the venue is in chba
so ideally you would want to be in
[Music]
chba kind of waited odds for that
combination to enter forever ticket you
want to attempt for the
lottery uhhuh uhhuh I was lucky to get
stage one and ex that's really lucky
[Music]
yeah stay in Shin e
e
anyway thank you so much I hope you had
a great time even if you couldn't see my
performance in person it still sounds
like still an amazing experience I hope
you made the most out of
[Music]
itk are you driving to work don't worry
about it drive safely I'm glad you're
listening am I your
radio better than any other radio
station FM
K yeah Asaka is definitely better than
Shinjuku in terms of
everything I'm I'm a Shinjuku
hater for people who don't know it's
like a a district in Tokyo that's it's
like a business district but
also
it can be a spooky like some places uh
in chinuku are
like you don't no it's not an otaku
District
no yeah there's
kuko maybe you've heard of it and a lot
of tourists go to
kabuko and I mean during the daytime
maybe it's not you know so intimidating
I find it always intimidating
[Music]
yeah I still end up going to Shinjuku a
lot of the time a lot of time anyway
because like a lot of things are in
Shinjuku a lot of things are in Shinjuku
Shinjuku is
big I mean there's nice places in
Shinjuku too but um I usually when I
think of Shinjuku I think
of like close the area close to the
station and the area around like
kabuka and all that and that's just the
yeah there's a lot of nicer places for
tourists in Japan I would
say just think Yakuza game
ah guys guys guys thank you for
reminding me of Yakuza
I went to
Yokohama on my last trip for the first
time in a long time and I got off at
Yokohama station and I walked towards
something and when I walked toward
something the scenery made me feel like
I was in a Yakuza game wasn't there
Yokohama um uh location in
Yakuza because it really looked like it
reminded me of
something yeah in
seven and I feel like I I walked over a
bridge and like a small bridge and it
really made me feel like I saw this
exact place in Yakuza but it's been a
while so I'm not sure if it's this exact
place or something else but I I feel
like that was the location I feel like I
saw the location
IRL I can't believe they made yaku into
a real
place is it in like a dragon yeah like a
dragon I
think yeah he's the hero of
yokoh no I don't think it was so plant
but it just felt it felt really familiar
from Yakuza I mean I've been to Yokohama
before but usually when I went to
Yokohama or like that area kanaga
uh then usually it was like
more or
so actual station Yokohama I didn't go
to that often
before maybe only once or
so first day was raining so much was
that the same first day for me um
because on my first day it was also
raining so [\h__\h] much it was
terrible but all the other days were
nice
so
Tuesday a lot of people arrived on
Tuesday
[Music]
huh
it's so exciting that Yakuza uses like
rare places cuz you go there and it's
like
oh oh [\h__\h] my shoes got so wet on that
day yeah me too my whole legs got so
[Music]
wet got so nice for fast and then cold
again that that sounds like a good uh
exchange good
sacrifice TWY ah T TW is also on my list
of games I need to
play y a tour oh yeah they should do
thatour ah you
think are the only pie aren't real and
maybe the name isn't real but they are
based off of real places I
[Music]
think yeah I bought w we such a cute
name I like the
abbrevation
abbreviation anyway uh Nathan thank you
for the pinky hi atten hope you're
having a good time in Japan despite
getting a little sick we miss you and
I'm looking forward to your new song K
coming out soon it really serves dot dot
dot thank you
H I miss you guys too and I'm I'm so
glad everything is over now like I'm not
sick anymore I'm home things are back to
normal pretty
much yeah really relieved it was an
exciting time though those were two two
exciting weeks for me I I did a lot of
exciting
things um the getting sick kind of
slowed me down a little bit
and made things a little bit more
difficult but besides that
really had a really
fulfilled two
weeks yeah there some crazy things going
on Fest made everything feel like a
favor Dre or I may have actually had
fever who knows who knows I didn't
measure
[Music]
it yeah hey nice
music Psy d Mo
[Music]
Sean d f the red chat what's this
picture what's this frog
doing I know you killed it at the
concert BS I still wait still waiting on
the vaults myself I have a question do
we have a new menu item I've had some
unusual requests from customers lately I
thought they were making obscene jokes
at first but
then
well yeah new menu item limited time
only during the promotional time of
[Music]
Kima can I get a uh um yeah what do you
want say it uh uh can I get a uh say it
don't fear say it have confidence can I
get it
[Music]
say it say it just say it can I get a
[\h__\h] yes yes you
[Laughter]
[Music]
can can I
get say it to my
face I love it I love this kind of
situation that we ourselves in ah m m
why are you watching M get out of
here again new voice packing coming nice
my order
is immediately
[Music]
servation it's really fast
service sorry don't get secondhand
embarrassment it's
funny
yes salvation I I coined
[Music]
word salvation too yeah I had that word
in mind while I was saying
that the
[Music]
piano let's go
oh
[Music]
this is fun anyway DCH I'm so sorry for
the confusion I'm sorry I didn't um you
know give everybody the the schooling
PDFs beforehand to inform you about the
new menu item sorry it came kind of like
a surprise thank you for the red super
chat though I appreciate
[Music]
it took you back to the 1800 saloons
let's go that sounds like fun come with
me come with me to the
saloon ja thanks for the
[Music]
pinky
for
per
he's saying he spoke to a lot of foreign
kfp at the Expo and had a lot of fun
taking pictures and he saw the
performance at the Fest and was like
really whoo glow
[Music]
away hey did you guys talk to Jack good
huh you met him he was really cool oh
really oh man so te [\h__\h] I wish I was
kfp fan I wish I was I mean I am a kfp
fan I wish I was a Kata fan I wish I was
one of you guys just one of you without
being me so I could be a fan of me and
then hang out with you guys I
wish sounds like so much fun man you
guys being
sweet hate
myself I don't want to be
me
be your own fan yeah but I still can't
mix in with you
[Music]
guys I wish I wish I could hang out with
you guys and cheer me on together with
[Music]
you yeah I got to get some
disguise
[Music]
thank
youe
I am
s sky for the CH keep serving thank you
thank you I I'm so so happy for your
support especially cuz English is your
first language and you still support the
new menu
item like okay I get it like you guys
pointing out like that it's like you
know it sounds like that word for me in
German and I'm like okay that really
makes it feel like I don't want to say
it but still you know I'm having fun
with
it so just bear with me until I move on
to the next
[Music]
word you spanking time thank you I I
appreciate the dedication and the
Loyalty very
much thank you oh thank you Chad thank
you R the pinky hello T hope you feel
better soon congrats on the amazing
fifth Fest performances you were such a
Bast during Kim and wild card I do 100
work segment of cool so cute too keep up
the great work thank you y'all man it
was so good it was so good I'm also
really happy
overall with that whole
[Music]
event
man but it's always over so fast you
know so much prep and then it's like
over so fast wow it's like a
bubble a soap bubble
popping and you're like
wo whoa wait that was so
nice why why is it so fragile and going
away so
fast need
more need more of
this but the good thing is we can always
look back on the Vault I mean for one
month and then who knows in the future
Blu-ray probably so you
know it it will always there will always
be proved that it happened that's
good yeah thank you so much rine for the
love and support cran D pyro d d d
always D Travis h45
danan oh yeah you are danan Roa dear sja
okay here we go all right thanks for the
pinky yeah let's say that you are sent
to a world where Mum and fauna are now
enemies aren't they already just kidding
because mum has decided to purge the
world of hippos while FAA wants to
protect them that sounds like a
realistic scenario what can you do she
get FAA and Mum to stop
[Music]
fighting what can you
do what can you
[Music]
do maybe we
can put them in
outside and make them face
corners and
reflect and then afterwards we make him
[Music]
hug I think that should
work and timeout yeah
put put him in timeout make him look at
the corner of the
wall then they won't be able to move
away from it until they apologize to
each other and give a
hug kiss and
makeup kiss and makeup o
y i then they have to they'll get put
into the naughty Corner h
[Music]
yeah done that was the easiest prompt
you have ever given me Rocka dear SRA
thank you it was even a realistic one
thank you thank you so much finally
you're being reasonable
[Music]
here he's losing his
touch no this is good let's keep it this
way
new persona Danish and San service
Danish thank you happy birthday belated
but still happy birthday Mr Kua J Dan
four years thank you that's amazing
beorn Atlant andar danash hi smovie
walking
by Golden I Dan rainard Dan for the
pinky I'm almost done with this yo your
first performances were amazing cimo was
so catchy and the
you know what while while I was saying
I'm almost done I realized you guys need
to remind me about
the the polar rides cuz I feel like I'm
done with them
because I thought I was done with them
but turns out I'm not done with them am
I because I'm I'm I was done with the
ones from before but yeah I know I froze
I'm fixing it right now I was done with
the one from before but I still have
yeah you you guys are also like oh yeah
right can you guys remind me I need to
finish those I I don't even think about
them cuz I just assume I don't have
anything to
do that's not
[Music]
good another reminder Maybe not today
though don't remind me today and not
tomorrow maybe on Friday or
[Music]
so yeah the white day
ones I just they're not in my mind I'm
so sorry I'm so sorry so your first
performances were amazing Kimo was so
catchy and the choreography and your
dance moves were so sharp maybe a bit
selfish but I really want to see you
dancing together in the future Fest uh
in the future fest with b and or L
Pulu thank you I do agree Kima is really
catchy I've heard it so many times now
and I still think it's really catchy and
really badass I love
it thank you I appreciate it I did my
this not tomorrow
today yeah I want to dance with them too
but there's also at the same time but I
want to do it but at the same time I
feel like oh
[Music]
man people going to compare us and
giving people a a direct
comparison like so easily like it's like
G asking
to be compared and I don't really like
that you know it's like in it's it
invites the comparison and that's so
scary to
me cuz I know I'm not as good so I know
I'm good but I know I'm not as good
so
H I don't know I still want to do it but
it's like well
you know you know cuz I know what will
happen I
know I know I know what will
happen but it will happen
eventually don't
worry D the
bgm well thank you so much though for
your support and yeah being so excited
about it thank you
rard
simply serve serve what money H serve
what star Shadow night thank you for the
red super chat your hips sent me to the
hospital oh what was the
diagnosis did you break your hips do you
need a hips hip replacement oh wait it
was my hips that sent you to the
hospital but what is your
problem what is your problem I hope
you're
okay I wish you good
recovery
please stay in bed take it easy you
already
know he got sered pretty severe oh oh oh
[\h__\h] but like what what hurts where does
it
hurt sudden blood L
ah I'm so sorry I'm so sorry for causing
that but um it's it's inevitable you
needed to be ready you should have gone
in there with like diapers for your nose
nose
diapers better luck next time you should
be prepared next time I am a t beep
thank for the pinky you were down on my
wa came remember rocks you rocked on
stage can I wait for the release thank
you it's finally happening finally
finally finally finally finally finally
W the MV looks pretty finished but now
we have to make a little change
unfortunately
[Music]
cannot change the colors of the idle
outfit even though it would have looked
so cool but we did not get permission to
do that so we have to replace um that I
hope he can replace those scenes without
having to redo the scenes like from
scratch or you can just like switch out
the
model like I can change the color of my
default outfit but not the idle outfit
sadly it looks so good though you guys
only saw like a little like hint of it I
think in the teaser from uh bird
POV so you barely saw it but it it was
really nice all the orange was changed
to um pink and the top is usually like
white but we made or kodu without me
even asking for it but it looks so good
uh he made the the shirt the top kind of
black and so it looked a lot more
fierce but I like the way it looks by
default as
well it's just we were hoping for
something even
[Music]
darker yeah no I don't think we can
share
anything it's not
allowed sad another reason why I need my
own kind of like fry idle outfit that I
can play around
with but I was thinking it might be a
pretty like pretty expensive Endeavor
but I I I think I'm allowed to just
commission my own 3D model if it's for
mvs I might only be able to use it for
that kind of stuff I can't like I
probably wouldn't be able to use it for
like 3D lives definitely not actually
but the same way I made
I got preu models made right um in the
same way I should be allowed
to I think if it's just like for mvs and
so
[Music]
on like if I can just get one that's
like somewhat versatile that would help
but I'm still like kind of like
insisting I
want I
I it's just um yeah MV is on its own 3D
MV on his own are already expensive and
I just wish I could get one through
normal measures within
Holo like getting a 1 million
wish or the other only option is an IRL
concert which is not happening ever
seemingly for me like a solo IRL
concert um and the 1 million wish I
already used up and I've been like
asking like okay guys I didn't know this
was even possible to get a 3D outfit
back then so that's I didn't ask way and
you guys didn't give me a list of things
I could do either I just assumed it
would be too expensive to ask for that
and back then I I don't think I had any
references of somebody doing that before
me like maybe simultaneously people were
working on it uh in the background but
nobody had uh used a 3D wish for a 1
million uh for a 3D outfit yet at that
point I think so I just didn't
know oh can I like in hind side please
switch it out and they're like n
probably not and I'm like please they're
like I I keep on
asking I really want to switch it out
because I really want a free
outfit we'll
see I'm still asking
again and if it really doesn't work out
i' have to look into commissioning one
on my own but I wouldn't be able to use
it for official purposes like
freedy Frey um lives
H cursed by too many early subscriptions
yeah I just didn't know my
options you get a free new 3D one if you
take part in ESC I don't
know I thought that would be a good
argument so I did bring it up but it
didn't happen so I don't know if it
would have worked I don't
[Music]
know yeah that's what I said like just
like don't give me a 2d outfit this Seas
year besides the one that's supposed to
be for last year don't give me one for
2024 you know but
whatever we'll see what can be
done I was also thinking about how Gus
group does it for their mvs and also for
their normal stream they always have
like different kind of cute outfits and
from how I understand it it's uh kind of
like public use such 3D outfits as like
fans or like just other people model and
they just download them buy them I guess
but they're not as expensive cuz it's
like like pretty
simplistic uh but anyway it looks good
enough for an MV or for like a little
stream and they put that on their models
I don't know how exactly works if you
just switch out your head or
something um but if I could do that then
I'd have a lot more variety and yeah for
me the most important thing is like to
get fitting outfits for the songs I want
to make cuz black and white W I don't
want to overuse it but it's like the
only other thing that would have worked
for Chima
besides um the I love it and even those
like all of that is not ideal it's not
the best
look for what I would have wanted so
blue I was thinking about doing blue and
changing the texture into like a
jeans
texture and maybe even take off the
sleeves I was already able to take off
belts maybe I can take off the sleeves
too but like I'm trying so hard to make
something new out of the things I have
yeah denim but like it will it will
reach a point where I'll have to make
songs according to the outfits I have to
fit the outfits rather than just make
whatever you know and that's just a a
dump that that would hold me back from
creating the music that I want to
create we I have a whole color palette
for real we'll have like
RGB
[Music]
w
yeah what else green
nah
yellow purple maybe some
purple like in terms of
dark Vibes it's just uh I don't have
much
Choice don't rip these jeans tar
recolor Yellow Ostrich streamer let's
go yeah I I I've been looking into more
options than I continue to look into
more options so let's see what happens
in the
future yeah continuing fa thanks for the
r of
chat T my dream come true I saw you
glowing on stage in person right right
Papa but I'm sorry I need to watch The
Vault a few more times my chicken brain
only remembers ice cream and Rave
penlight so hard ah a
Papa thank you so much maybe I heard
your scream maybe maybe one of them was
you thank you so much that sounds
amazing I'm so glad for you guys
Papa I hope you had the time of your
life I hope you interacted with other
kfp
too thank you so much for going out of
your way from traveling to Japan to go
to see me in person at the concert it
means a lot to
me it do be a dream come true thank you
well no thank you it's crazy like last
year already uh some of you guys came
but this year was definitely different
thank you thank you thank you thank
you gold amethyst
yellow gold sounds a little bit
interesting
[Music]
like shiny we can make it a bit more
shiny and make it gold I don't
[Music]
know oh they were giving out things
that's so nice
bling a NY gold
W bling
bling met some kfp too
y so sweet I'm sure they were really
happy to meet you too
FAA thank you so
much got to watch the VA as much as
possible Right fra stickers were nice oh
I didn't get one you know lunchbox than
Acappella official release sleep talking
Acappella Oh you mean you already heard
it before didn't you you mean you want
me to release it like as a as its own
video I'm thinking of releasing the
Chima a Cabella as its own video
maybe for sleep talking it's kind of
like out of nowhere if I were to do that
could do it as a member's only thing
maybe
those are so good right the acapellas
that come from working with kiaha angels
are so good right that's why I'm telling
you it's all about the backup
vocals it's all about the mega vocus
Arizona anime fan danin legi danin Jim
Tracy Danish bottom of sh's boots danin
thank
you a that's okay don't worry thank you
so much for the support
py than Egger
than high powerered lasers like those
can't this member uh or burn you thank
God that it can't dismember me I want to
stay a member of whole life but some
wind shine directly into your eyes can
blind someone for life so they never
need they need to never be aimed at at
the audience and managed really
[Music]
expertly interesting a quot
gas no I didn't believe her I didn't
believe her Alan Dan Eggbert Dan
again of display yeah yeah yeah but that
was uh was that before or after no it
was
before the dripped paint art yeah I I
think if they ask for suggestions for
next Expo I'm definitely going to bring
up that they should do like a creations
of the members thing again cuz I think
it was a popular thing and more personal
than just like having things there where
we're not involved in at
all yeah you guys also should put it on
the survey I especially for me who makes
a lot of like crafts and
stuff I want to put something out there
for next Expo please let me put
something cursed there I still have the
nail
please I think they didn't do it cuz
they had a
theme and they stayed close to the theme
with all the things they did but they
really missed out they could have kept
the theme by asking us to make um like
Creations that are maybe related to the
theme of traveling vacation beach
Etc you know I mean my nails wouldn't
have really worked for that but whatever
yeah mum has one nail it's okay she'll
probably take good care of it I don't
think she would throw it away would
she
H SP
[Music]
wonderful
that's it with those super chats and
it's pretty much midnight now so I could
cut it here we got over that big hurdle
wait I didn't even put the thumbnail on
the screen I'm so sorry ah VA gang
sumori py poy
poty thank you thank you go rest you
guys are so sweet you know what I love
you so much I love you let me eat
[Music]
you you know I'm really wasteful when
eating like chicken wings and
[Music]
stuff I can't eat it like the people who
leave nothing but the bones like really
clean I'm
sorry I don't know I know like some
parts are like kind of weird I don't
know you're that guy yeah eat all of me
don't cry that's exactly why I don't
usually go for chicken wings cuz I don't
want to be so wasteful I just go for
chicken
nuggets yeah the tendons and stuff and
the ew the cage [\h__\h] no
e cuz like that's so chewy and weird so
I just avoid yeah boneless boneless all
the way
yeah it's so sad cuz like they chicken
wings usually taste so good cuz they're
so so so nicely seasoned usually but
just I guess I just got to go for bonus
but I
rarely get anything but like chicken
nuggets
[Music]
anyway dolphin why why why why why
don't the sound that I
made nuggets m M the lowest of the low
I'm sorry I'm a white ass [\h__\h]
okay 54 chicken nuggets got to keep up
my daily
intake I know it's it's actually so
so basic of me I'm so
[Music]
basic go white girl
go wide how
wide want to measure my hips
huh dawn of the kfp Nuggets B you mean
yeah thank
you you're basic and we love you thank
you I prefer tendies over nuggets
tendies what what's that again like
how's that
different chicken tender it's like a
lengthy but
boneless
fried thingy right yeah the long nugget
yeah oh those are good too I like those
too long
nugget yeah I like that
no and you know those are even better
when um the coating the breading uh we
have okay okay here in Austria we have
oh listen you will love this we have um
um like a
salad with uh um those chicken strips
but the salad has a [\h__\h] a uh pumpkin
seed dressing and the pumpkin seeds
sometimes are also in the breading like
crushed pumpkin seeds in the dressing in
the in the in the coating I mean and wo
it's so good I think I showed you a
picture before but um let me find it for
you right now my brain is so empty holy
[\h__\h] what's called again uh
um uh uh uh uh what's pumpkin in German
uh uh [\h__\h] you see how empty my brain is
right now pumpkin in ger CIS
kis salot
uh
chicken
K what the [\h__\h] b b CLE a back candle
back candle
styish
styish can you guys notice how my
intonation changes when I'm trying to
speak Austrian like deep Austrian
country accent or does it just sound
like all my other German
teal for for example I say salad is just
very normal standard but then I can say
a candles salot it's very
country
[Music]
yeah there's a really really strong
intonation so what I'm talking
[Music]
about so it usually has like potato
salad in it too but not Mayon based um B
what's with
my what's with my pronunciation today
holy
[\h__\h] it's just
terrible okay so here are some
variations but this is not unusual as in
like how thick and big like it's just
like it's not a strip it's a whole
[\h__\h] chicken it's more like
this you see in the breading the the
pumpkin seeds this this is amazing and
then the salad with the um lettuce but
also with the potato
salad and then dressing is pumpkin seed
oil holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h] this is so good
you don't understand how good this
[Music]
is you went
FAA yeah chicken salad The Good the best
kind of chicken salad
like when you guys say chicken salad you
probably think of something completely
different but I think of
[Music]
this candy receips try this out guys if
you ever make like your own chicken Oro
try crushing pumpkin seeds into
the uh coating it's
[Music]
amazing
wow and yet I'm eating goulash today
which is fine I I made gash yesterday
with um hell freshh stuff
no it adds a lot of
[Music]
flavor it's not just texture actually
actually texture doesn't really change
much at all yeah gash with um uh smashed
smashed mashed
potatoes there's a difference between
smashed and mash it were supposed to be
mashed potatoes but apparently I didn't
cook it quite long enough it still
worked out but it's a little bit hard
the
potatoes can you see what mono is
cooking
what no no
what what will I see it if I go on
Twitter what's Gage it's uh originally
Hungarian food but there's a lot of
variations I made uh one with
sausages V just uh just really the basic
sausages and uh paprika uh bell pepper
so funny to me we talked about this
before I think but it's so funny to me
how you guys say paprika to the paprika
powder but you don't say paprika to the
uh vegetable where it comes from bell
pepper in German we just say paprika to
like both the powder and the vegetable
it's so confusing to
me I was have to think about it oh yeah
right you guys don't call it
paprika you could you could say Pap
paprika
[Music]
what what the [\h__\h] is capsicum what well
never heard about
that in the region too yeah cuz you guys
are smart that's why you say
papa nor regian smart what the [\h__\h]
capsicum what that sounds like Capcom
capsicum ah wait what do you mean it's
not b pepper bell pepper is that bell
pepper the long one no it also comes up
the same what do you mean capsicum
sounds more like a Latin name for bell
pepper
[Music]
so what's happening you guys are
confusing me oh it's a scientific name
and that's what I mean like it sounds
not like the name you actually
use ah you
guys let me go let me go let me
go if you love me let me go just kidding
I brought up all of
this going to eat my gash now and go to
bed had a good day yesterday too um I
feel I feel good yesterday was like the
best day off I had in a long time and it
didn't just lays around but exactly
that's what made me feel so good it's
the [\h__\h] winter depression being gone
next year for
winter tell me to take my meds tell me
to take those vitamins because it's
unacceptable to not take those uh Sun
Sun
vitamins during winter cuz it makes I
think a big change I need to take it
actively it's really bad yeah vitamin D
holy [\h__\h] like the difference it makes
in My overall well-being holy [\h__\h] the
whole winter I was just like Doom
posting whole winter every day I'm like
I hate my life life I want to die I want
to leave whole alive ah [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
ah suffering every day I want to stay I
love this but I also am
suffering ah I don't belong here H
everybody hates me the whole winter it's
so hard not to share it with you cuz I
already have this like problem of
oversharing my feelings and I don't want
to be too emotional and too
negative well was really hard to get
through
winter was so difficult [\h__\h] winter [\h__\h]
winter finally we are in Spring
baby let's
[Music]
go yeah seasonal depression hits
hard I really realized it yesterday cuz
I just I stand outside in the sun and
I'm like I'm so
happy why am I so happy now and also
just I think the relief of all the work
being done all the stress being over it
just all hit me so hard
[Music]
yesterday but you guys you guys being so
sweet and so supportive and my beloved
chickens you helped me for the winter
nonetheless I survived
somehow
somehow I had a lot of stressful
stressful things going on that added to
[Music]
everything ho [\h__\h] no I can't find
bangers right now I need to go I was on
my way out why am I changing
Ma I'm going
what what the [\h__\h] was that
though wrap it up please wrap it up okay
okay
woo
oh oh yeah I I I used this before at
some point I think so you heard it you
must have heard it before when I was
browsing I
think
oh
name that one what what do I name
it
oh oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
W oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] stop you stop oh my
God that goes too
hard goes too [\h__\h] hard oh my
God yo guys see you tomorrow difficult
game about
climbing okay bye
and I had a lot of fun
goodbye I love you
guys oh you you sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry I'm weird oh oh God I'm so cringe
[Music]
byebye oh yeah new members wallpaper is
in the community board go go go
download
[Music]