I
[Music]
one two say no
oh yes
[Music]
1 two say no
Happ
[Music]
why to
oh 1 two say no
[Music]
sorry don't mean to interrupt The Banger
opening but uh hi bom me
zo of course I can be sparkling G of
Hall I'm English a and today we're
playing Seven Days to
Die hi
hi I have a spawned in oh there's
someone next to me huh
huh oh it's f
f I'm right behind
you how do you type what's the type
button what's the type what's the what's
the type thingy what we're muted for now
cuz what's the talk button okay first
add all the
friends okay
what the pushy talk button
see
hello
[Music]
h no see is Crouch
hi oh yeah you can't tell but I
a oh I got a party invite
uh can you hear us yes how did you do
that hear the twins are you around here
what button is that
hello you scared us so bad using party
chat right now we're probably going to
use Discord pretty soon okay I am with
FL
M unfortunately what do you mean
unfortunately I'm beautiful what are you
talking about you're just you're just
you're just jealous of my nice beard
okay you wish you could grow an amazing
beard like me
I can hear you now I was excited the
direction of the
survivors okay let's do it wow you
buff yes I know I've been working out oh
yeah where where we
going oh yeah come to bble to
bble you look pretty buff yourself
everybody looks buff I'm
sure well I mean you have to be a
certain level of buff in order to
survive the zombie apocalypse I think
although this is too buff like you would
want more fat but maybe they can't
because they don't find
food to me hello
hello yeah oh nice everybody's everybody
that's huge overturn trailer whoa hold
up
hold is this mayy we should probably get
to
everybody there will be plenty of
trailers find you guys or am I going to
spawn uh you're going to spawn somewhere
random so come to bio and F
M well we'll meet where we're
at
uh meet at The Rock
The Rock The
Rock Let's plch the tree together
okay okay yeah beep this
tree yeah take the anger out on the tree
yeah already punching trees I see that's
good wait we're Gathering resources
while you guys try to arrive also did
you punch
me what are you
doing I thought we got all bloody from
punching the Tre
see can we
swim you know if we can
swim sorry my my was yes you're good
let's
go I tried changing Pusher talk and it
didn't work for oh I think there's no
like voice activation I think it's just
push to top
yeah no no I me I tried changing my key
I didn't realize you guys were in voice
chat
already actually we're using uh the
party chat probably move to Discord
afterward
okay oh I see took me seven minutes to
die did you die yeah I died like seven
minutes in ironically hilarious oh hello
everyone hello oh you're also big man
time for material oo big Burly strong
fortitude and strength lady wow you have
makeup on oh
M
wow
buff hello dear sir hello sir nice
beard nice
beard where is this coming from you also
very clean and nicely shaven I wonder
how much time that takes you every
day no I'm just naturally bald I don't
have hair on my
head could it be that the iname voice CH
has a long
delay a long delay theing maybe maybe we
should hop into Discord okay yeah let's
go
to okay let's go
Discord what the hell
now this is not a
now
the I didn't know I could actually punch
you I we're moving to Discord voice chat
hello hello all
right oh I think we're good
y much better not having to press the
the button I will say why is my mic so
low that's weird let me it's kind it's
kind of quiet oh God
R run iting volume t t
t can you hear
me you okay thank you yay we're figuring
it out together
together why is it so quiet all right
I'll turn up game maybe that'll help why
is it so quiet okay
uhoh eight Stones W is there weight in
too like like a a maximum of how much
you can carry in in terms of weight nope
sorry guys sorry oh so you can just
carry as much as you want that's great I
think so it's there's inventory slots
that are
finite wait there's a house over here
can we have
it the big goals for today are to find a
place to to chill out in
together um a base even if it's
temporary well yeah can we take over
this house this looks nice this is
actually a really nice house we did get
lucky The Walking Dead
house what is happening crouching I
don't think so enemies here though am I
crouching what happens if we die yes
youing then we respawn you want to make
a bed roll really
quick thank i v We live in this house
there's a PC set up I can stream from
herey streaming a
stream yeah this bad sounds huh watch
out there's zombies in the house though
there's there's
baddies I didn't think that
no I'm
coming yay zombie noises don't B me ah I
thought she was dead to Y do you want to
come with me to them uh I'm already
trying to make my way towards uh biu
apparently that's where we're meeting
okay okay so I'm I'm slowly making my
way there we we are in a big house that
could be our home base it could be our
home upstairs bab do you want to go
upstairs with me we should go upstairs
for okay what what are you scared are
you scared is that why
I call the bed but it has a giant hole
here I don't know I don't know about the
Integrity of this house I bet she didn't
go not sure we might just need to fill
the hole and be fine but watch out watch
out in here yeah that's
true boy don't hurt my new friend I'm
running out of s so
easy
close they're still alive fin they're
still alive but they're dead yeah there
a walking dead right where' they go
there I know he's got a bit of reach on
him okay it's just Dark Souls it's just
Dark Souls they oh he fell I get the
stones I may need them there a lot of
room
here the bunk beds down
here I'll take the
couch is there a way to improve the
stamina somehow you might need to level
up or something
oh it's just baby stop being jump scared
by me thank you
SC we going to upgrade on the C
there I'm going
to
Temporary the crap guys I'm going to go
on a little trip to find clothes I will
be back to the house our temporary base
you you can craft clothes by the
lake yeah I have all going make
yeah we don't have to stay naked forever
and I'm going to start cleaning the
house cuz you know you guys know I'm a
clean freak I'm sorry it can't be helped
yeah this house is very ni already I
found your bedroom house you guys can
come check it out it's we got really luy
come downstairs downstairs yeah what do
you mean like this is so
broken look at it
works it's so broken we're going to have
to repair it so much think we can find
can I show you look at this klie klie
look at this giant
hole it's your
bedroom there is a pool table that's a
good point that is a good point fun us
playing pool together yeah that would be
really cool I think you know what you w
me over you know a pool table pretty
good that's pretty good it's a fixer as
they say got to put some crates and
stuff yeah yeah a lot of blocks a lot of
crates snakes in this game snakes oh
yeah snakes and they're not zombie
snakes they're just normal snakes oh my
God yeah there's maybe I could blow it
up like in Shrek and make a balloon out
of it oh oh I have put that there and
then that's a big ho in the wall does
anyone know how to get plant fiber uh
smack grass yeah just hit it smack
it oh there's a water cooler bottle in
here that can we pick it up we can take
it to the water I think the one thing I
remember is that it's really important
for us to find water and not to like
save it like save it and not drink it
and figure out how to craft like water
reservoirs and water water bottle here
yeah murky water will give you tummy egg
probably but yeah it has denter in it oh
oh good back you think this will work if
we just down here too though but there's
nothing else up here down here what else
oh gosh
yeah Miss in the upper right yeah
yum still alive
dead see look we can totally block this
hole it's dead challenge is
done basic we have no wood left you see
what I'm where I'm getting right you
guys see what I'm getting at yeah I
think this is a oh I found $8 guys
anyone want to sell me something for $8
I'll buy you disent infected water e of
me uh can you can you can I buy wood oh
I do I have 12 wood built it no I don't
can I have two okay for
$8 wait let me double check if it's
two yeah yeah for $8 how do I how do I
drop something this's the Wind Block
Cecilia and I'm still waiting for you to
accept my friend request oh sorry
no accepted everybody and got everybody
except Cil and how do
I how do I split plugin holes a thing
like a stack I go like this did I do
something you craft more than one oh
nice how you split stackle yeah so I can
give you
two yeah oh I found it we're totally
going to survive how do you do oh hold
it to drop a SW okay here you go I
dropped it than look what I did I'm so
smart I'm a builder CeCe I'm a
builder oh W build already you need a
helmet this is not safe working
environment I do not I don't she's
already got
DFT just pluging up the
[Music]
Hol I guess I can craft
multiple
okay I already forgot how play this game
okay wood time see now the house is well
fortified cuz there's no hole
anymore nice wow this is oh my gosh this
is going to be our streamer house we're
going to stream from here and it's like
a dream come true it just had to have
apocalypse that we all have to share
there's multiple PCS here multiple even
okay kind of tough all the off collabs
yeah the off collabs
man
forever I'm so hype let me move my bed
roll I mean even in a zombie apocalypse
entainment is important yeah what there
where we can
[Music]
get such a good team no no never never I
need to
done make sure you guys do your
challenges by pressing y
why let's make the stone team made it we
made
it wonder if use my fish if we made a
stone a we should use it instead of the
one that we have Kiara and Gigi are
pretty far
away she's making her way downtown
walking fast face is past and she's home
now
[Music]
do I have to do
this see where we
are satisfying taking down the trees I
like the flowers we'll just work on
fortifying the base
here more
flowers I need to gather Pebbles Pebbles
give me yourselves Pebbles where are you
you can probably Salvage this car you
guys can salvage anything by the way oh
how sorry I didn't listen how do you
salvage anything anything just hit it oh
just smack it the stuff you find in a
crates I'm going to put some crates in
the house so we can put stuff in there
okay okay
okay keep out
condemned yeah yeah my
friend run away any more plants for the
I mean we can do whatever we want but
for the magazines I think it's probably
best to like keep them and then see who
wants to go into what because otherwise
there won't be enough like if everyone
just uses everything no one's actually
going to level any skill cuz they're
really rare and you need like 10 of one
type in order to get a level and stuff
sometimes so great let's have like a
magazine crate or something I
person welcome
eggs I am hello [\h__\h] there you go e it
to death guys there's a Farm close by
F I don't want the we have a bunch of
seeds yeah we have cfee din potato seeds
what do I need to build my first don't
need
anyting my first mys this is a good
spot potato myth dinner time baby
we can make a bone knife soon
too uhoh if you find corpses on the
ground hit them ladies hit them hit them
oh oh I
can zombie is kind of cute I need more
wood okay let's go need a little further
away kind of a strong zombie I don't
know let's
go by the way uh I have an
[Music]
infection how do
you fix the infection cut off the arm oh
you're
infected I am infected oh uh guess
bye nice you time to put the cat
down hey where are you hey where you at
where you I'm here wait where is she
where is here I'm here hello I'm here
here here where is here where is here oh
hi okay I'll help you with the
infection actually it might be worth at
the beginning she's wait where is she
going to respawn is she is she going to
respawn no
no I work so hard to be here okay where
where are you been I'll just tear off
that limb where are you we can talk
about it I okay listen no fighting no
fighting we can talk about it okay okay
listen I want to help I want to get my
tears I want to I want to help you guys
to fight zombies and behind you behind
you a
zombie knife oh we know the wait no it's
it's literally right there don't want to
sleep in the bathroom hello oh okay but
maybe you guys are NPCs oh well kaha
them
only that boy hear me I'm doing my I'm
crafting my my my
co get get get him you
guys get him in the booty we might need
reinforcement there's a
lot he punch
no we hear you we hear you can hear
you I'm not sure I have to leave a party
that I'm in I am
hurting we should heal
somehow but I made a a bow and I got us
meat you guys I got us meat so y wait I
have a question how do you actually wear
the outfit uh you click on the item and
press
[Music]
W our house
what you have the best house
ever freaking rocks just got to figure
out how to fix the door right
cck oh okay make sure we have I'm not
Naked Anymore yeah don't be naked
naked's
dangerous we can make it two two crates
this my bed now okay let's see whats and
than getting some cotton
plants could have sworn I made too oh
here we go all right I'm finally where
you guys are I think I I'm I'm there
welcome home yeah
welcome I see you she's here
welcome in here for now right yay is it
a like yellow the papa residence yes the
papa our streamer
house welcome am I closed all of
us now to
C I can make more
itage I need more need
more did someone put that building block
down there and I accidentally take it
maybe we pick it up just to block the
door
okay this even the are Dad here I don't
know oh there you go this place is
awesome so we put our uh bed rolls in
here somewhere did you girls do that
already yes you should K oh the beds
right anywhere there's actually actual
beds in here there are yeah that's
a oh wait did you build those beds or
were there just bunk beds by default for
us put your put your you have to craft a
bed roll and then put the bed roll where
you want to spawn
so I'm taking the master bedroom hey the
master
bedom I'm going to make it
too how do we does anyone know how to
make like chests or something yeah I
just made them they're in the living
room living room oh they nice thank you
I wonder if I can put right something
I'll just put all my garbage in here
yeah sure just materials and such oh no
maybe I should have on this couch you
get to sleep on this comfy bed
nice how do I put the bed
down uh I think I got a building Cube
from the house I'm sorry it's
okay I'll Rec I'll reclo it how do you
place the bed b right click right click
oh okay but I don't I don't know how to
turn
it can't be on the top bu no
oh oh I guess I can't place it on the
bed search
toilet
water if you guys find Murky water you
can uh you can boil it in a pot over a
fire to clean it what I see oh Network
time out I got kicked out did we all get
kicked out no no it said you
disconnected okay I'm going to sleep
next to the PC then I sleep next to the
laundry so I can put that I'm in the
washing machine we have eggs no don't
punch the stop that making
sure I think so maybe I do want to burn
some peee
water block we might need that would be
good there was a thing we could do
outside
oh visitor at our humble abod a
visitor yeah a good
one are they nice I don't know but
they're not
talking a Rand NPC uh is it the shieldy
group
shy F group did you just attack me I
like this room I've claimed the land all
night press e to use um
anyway we claimed this land with this
block uh what are you doing beautiful
G
A took us so while stop taging
me we have someone evil
[Music]
this I have no control I don't have no
control of my chos
hello you look beautiful look this is my
this is my PC setup do you like it oh
nice garbage oh I can sleep on top of it
actually opening theame okay or maybe I
cannot I uh got this place it's pretty
Co I'm going to find do you like it very
I mean yeah yeah it's co
the apart
yeah I like it I have some privacy too
sure I don't think we need it they
getting anything for me I don't know
does anyone want to come I want to go
try going to a farm a farm okay let's
go here really quick let's go okay I
come I
actually well then let's wait for shy
shy did you say you want to co you will
come with us or just said my bed roll
okay
okay let's wait a
second is there a Trader near here or
you guys Trader lless
pretty is there a Trader near this
house we haven't found one yet we
haven't done anything I'm going to take
off my hat I like that even in the
apocalypse Trend thing and we are
wearing the same style yeah accidentally
fashion even aash face by the way if you
guys open the map you can set a marker
for where home
is you can set a marker that's
[Music]
nice I'm sorry every time I I'll tap
back in I punch someone oh that's what
happened I don't needan it stay away
from me okay truth truth truth please
don't touch me do you don't touch me
truth
be careful don't H each
other I'm
sa probably
out
yeah we're crazy this way I think was
the farm Yep this way wait wait who am I
following everyone looks the same little
follow the follow everybody yeah follow
the follow this
the oh dead I'm
ad any point you
want there's corn
[Applause]
corn can we take the corn corn out of
this can we cook cuz I got some meat so
like dead corn and green corn I think
GRE
I'm get the green corn get
[Music]
the I feel like should probably be PL oh
they're dead let's go yeah there is real
corn M can we get can we get seeds to
replant them sorry stole that from you
we have po I don't know those are still
growing got be a good farmer I'll be
finding trous apocalypse with corn
that's all I need I'll survive most of
the Corn are dead though
I they just can't eat the the
people this one is different I mean
they're just zombies people yeah that
that is a shame that is a big
shame okay this this area has three
three skulls on it I don't know if we're
ready for that oh does that mean like
danger we're going to die yeah I see I
at the green ones the lot's probably
really good but I just don't think we're
ready just like skull images so I
noticed that the green corns actually
contain seeds too probably oh they do we
could there's a ear corn they have
something different we could set up a
little farm by our
home that feels like that's a seed we
get rid of the Dead corn what happen oh
there's a house over here too here yeah
I see got this is be careful this is the
three School area yeah it's a pretty
int there's zombies everywhere run run
run you got run what are they going to
do it's okay I'll be fine what are they
going to do huh much
[Laughter]
corn all right I hope the corn re like
resupplies maybe a farmer shows up and
take care of
hopefully so the the thatn doesn't give
you anything
yeah I don't think it gives you anything
can I eat okay we can eat wait don't
leave
me so we just need the big
ones or the green on I found
sand who wants to focus on getting food
maybe we should split into like yeah
good idea food gatherers this is just a
gathering and then stay at
home so far back time
let's there's I found a land claim block
we have to destroy this oh I think
someone put that down I just put that
there for the
Quest
for so if you put a land claim box down
apparently um it applies a hardness
modifier to blocks so it protects it
protects damage on something apparently
okay so like so like you're safe in the
zone I guess or something like that or
the player who put it down is safe in
the zone it's like you're
lag that will be by the house yeah we
have one of those I put one in the
living room oh
okay oh we're in the same uh Ally group
too so we should be good to
go it won't be harder for us to destroy
each other's things if we need to
exactly are we all in the same party I
have a question um no party s
how do you level up I'm not in the
anymore I think he going a kill oh
killing zombies okay yeah if we find a
Traer he gives Quest and he gives a lot
of exp from the
[Music]
quest with me on an adventure to see if
we can find the trader I
know I want to find I have one on my map
too yeah oh okay is it the wide river
yeah yeah
he this way point if he wants to trade
he should come to us that's right he's
not going to do that I think then he
won't have anys be our face by the way
or he's GNA stay
hello oh I found people
y welcome welcome welcome welcome wait
you guys are all wearing something why
aren't you wearing where's your hat a
there's a hat yes put your hat on what
you should probably
to kill
it I will
CRA oh oh wait no I see a hat oh thank
you yes put it on Oh
yay
civilized he's down down I think he's
not down
okay I need a Trader
[Music]
so I don't know how to share the way
Mark with you guys what what if you send
like a
screen I can send a screenshot gloves
I'm missing gloves pie oh
that eat the craft anything just yet
where do you have land claim box I
I can make a Char
meat meat meat meat is this oure this is
our base
yeah we should probably do multiple
campes what is this land claim
block our home base now basically
zombies won't spawn around it do you see
it I put it in the channel the map what
if we all put our land claim blocks like
around each other so they won't spawn
yeah let let's protect the house can we
get
so where can't do anything right how to
make land claim block this oh I have a
land claim block um I don't know where
to put it though uh it won't let me put
it
anywhere they claim this land claimed
yeah is there a maximum to can only one
person claim a land
cilia I don't how are you cooking this
is Mor that's meat oh here Trey maybe
right there TR to figure out where to
put this oh yeah I can't put the L yeah
it's a pretty it's a pretty large
perimeter put it here I am dying of
hunger oh I found a place
need all
right claimed this
lamb see if we can cook some more for
everybody
maybe here oh we need cooking items oh
we cooking oh I like the the placement
of this
fire
put anywhere these days is put in the
fireplace can't believe
it we should probably try to find um
like a cooking pot and a frying
pan
okay yeah oh I found found a I found a
cooking a grill outside the house I
don't know if we can use that anybody
house
honey water we have some water in our
inventory here near tree there a town
nearby uh there's a town very far
away that's
water oh that's the hill that's I I'm
going to eat scary food oh by the way
soon everyone um oh you guys have a nice
out here
wonderful the idea that I have is that
vc1 is for the home and then all the
other ones are for like going out on
different excursions oh that's a good
idea nice idea I think we're eating that
would be great sorry
sorry I want
eat
here cover the river she's here
what to
do FOC find I want to
[Applause]
go going into Vice chat too if anyone
wants to go on an next okay let's go
time stroll I'm going to collect items
I'm going to gather
stuff
wow night time stroll time yeah night
time
St
let's say say that I am infected so if I
die at any moment do you have a bed roll
yeah did you put the bed roll down at
the bed yeah yes indeed okay so yeah if
you die you'll respawn where you put
your bed roll down we're carrying a lot
right now we should okay maybe should I
die here then and respawn yeah okay I'll
kill you sir we'll
help you can put it in
uhoh no hesit
you're welcome it's fine anytime anytime
you need for help we'll help you don't
worry no hesitation at all
wow is there a place that we can put our
stuffs in our inventory yeah there's a
box here in the living room oh okay we
can we just put our stuff okay one
moment
W okay let's put it in there okay should
we check out the area East to where we
are it seems to have like a little yeah
[Music]
at the your stuff is where you died okay
I'm going to pick it up yeah that sounds
bad scary sounds all of a
sudden let's thank you for helping okay
I'm ready actually that's give me
seconds I'm just putting my stuff away
okay um should we try the one West from
us then theary
sounds okay
what ow ow zombie ah how could this
happen to me a zombie okay maybe in the
zombie game
no I hope is it inside maybe let's close
the
door oh oh he's in the house oh it is
inside perfect
for
where what somebody's on fire St back
like I'm just going to stab back I think
yeah it's over
yeah down I don't
know
yeah my breakfast it doesn't sound good
no how much corn do I have to eat to not
be hungry I think the corn just as it is
just heals one point so it's not worth
eating oh yeah yeah we need to make food
we need to like Grill it probably
okay let me check I have I have a few
eggs maybe I got some chicken soup okay
I'll just eat that there is a lot of zom
sound going on in the
can sounds yummy
sounds it calls me will
we okay I got some xeg
and don't think you can do anything with
the eggs yet we need like a pan and
stuff
yeah huh oh my gosh let's close the door
so no trees come through were we were we
heading out by the way we would kind got
scared a little okay don't be scared
let's go can someone make me a new um
wooden it is
time oh we need a new one is any can you
make you can you can repair your Axe by
the way oh we can yes let's repair it
then oh I can't oh we don't I don't have
the material we don't have the materials
right a second give me a moment we put
it all
away mhm we need some rocks probably
also if we had a torch it' be a little
bit easier to see things oh I can make
boiled eggs you should have one when you
spawned or is it a torch we have
one oh
clay I need clay oh gosh what is that
what is that help help help help help
r i
see no I got it I got
it don't catch the power
a let's take some of the rocks out and
then fix right now is it that I think so
yes thank you you saved me let's go
you're
welcome not you
B okay
we he the violence we
it
yay okay is everyone here yeah
this
way is in the house we in the
house okay let's try going for the the M
the area that is left of this down the
street okay watch out another
one we're going to be back up okay maybe
should run run away from
them oh he got me
they're fast I need more maybe to run
away from
them but run us than
usce does anybody have extra Pebbles I
want to make a spear we have oh yeah I
was trying to do that actually I have on
my inventory we are very hungry our
maximum status is stamina is reduced we
should have some of our food M down but
you don't want to eat it
my food
okay hungry still hungry yeah I don't
know the beginning is really hard
because there's just no food so you're
just going to be hungry I don't know be
hungry be hungry okay there might be
like a way to make food from the very
beginning but I don't know so
wa try finding stuff o cell tower number
one
what what's
it let's go on in are you guys are you
guys outside right uh inside the
building just if you're in the
party ra go towards the pink the
pink uh okay Pink Arrow can I can I go
past you please sorry am I in the way
thank you it's
okay it's okay Break Stuff I think I'm
starving I Cann there water empty water
nothing it's
empty it's empty water cool not was
scratching
oh it's okay you're you're a cat you're
on the
crow maybe the game has like
Communications say something uhoh I hear
sounds I want to climb on up oh I can't
go up
I'm coming oh there we go I think I
found you guys no this is how do I go up
the you just the ladder press
W be careful there's a zombie up here
though so just watch
out I going to get him I think lot of
zomes I think he ran off the cliff never
mind oh safe
upst ah my leg is sprained guys it's
over be
my leg is
broken my God house in the house in the
house is very
strong no no leave me alone I dog over
okay okay okay okay okay let me let me c
this be oh my gosh my leg is
broken we have 15 Health we're going to
die how do I climb down okay
you down look down is there outside I'm
going to fight them good oh
God CE CE don't go down don't go down
they're coming they're coming don't go
down oh my God
so we we kill him in the hole Yeah kill
him in the hole Yeah I'm on this side go
go I'm I'm I'm I'm okay not not a good
idea not as more
ID how do you go down how do you go down
just
oh I have I have six HP I'm going to die
go back up
no well I'm going to stay inside the
house let's break more okay it's right
there uhoh
yummy stamina really bad oh what's the
what's the little thing that says
it's not healing very
fast that
one I use a split do we have
one
no I thought I was zombie okay I have a
spear do you guys want a spear I have
extra one uhoh uhoh here they come can
we make
a I don't know how to do that take it oh
is that a weapon yes take it take the
weapon go down take the weapon
my uh me uhoh they are they invading
they invading they invading uhoh here we
go here we go here we go here we go
attack attack what the heck the door
the I
I'm going to fight you I really need a
spear okay a lot
of on on my bed on my bed on my bed
that's a big one I don't think we want
to go
back come on oh
no
thank I don't have any
stuff no
no inventory hi guys
hi I'm good I'm good thank
you don't
okay okay take turns take turns take
turns take
turns
yeah where are you guys almost
done this is one is very
resistant let's go get Stu from our
balls uhoh
for this okay
good okay finally
dead I'm going
downstairs where is the s coming from
let's hide in watch out ouch look that
that's in the meantime I don't have
anything to craft you got you got the
can we use the Rock
why you think one of them has red eyes
it's mess why does that mean because
it's night and they're stronger yeah
they're stronger at night oh they run
away from us
oh I'll try burning them yeah burn down
he's burning he's burning burn down burn
them die let's go if they come in here
what are we doing how are we escaping
this can't spawn near my it's okay it's
okay I'm okay rock burn
burn burn burn burning the full moon oh
oops burn no I'm
dead the night is almost
over I throw rocks they come down the
stairs I throw
rocks uh-oh oh God okay okay okay okay
got to run got to run I don't know I I'm
not sure oh it's that
explosion oh there is no door
everybody's
gone
door I don't know if is it safe here
let's I don't know we'll see those are
bad sounds those are bad sounds those
are bad
sounds I guess it
is not really no no okay no it's not
really safe ah ah uh-oh I died it
again okay I say a plan change of plans
everyone go back home okay going home
pick
up run back home okay running home okay
yes run back home pick up your backpack
don't forget to pick up your backpack
get a backpack it's gone does the
backpack gone at some point I think we
need to craft some better weapons before
going in
[Music]
adventure well it was still a nice
Adventure it was just not oh I haven't
said that it was not a nice
Adventure there's blood everywhere no
it's it's
nice it was
nice okay see this way
there is itting hey the sky is coming
upom Upon Us
yeah okay we need a door pink outside
there you go
okay I need to make did anyone find
anything was this like successful in any
way find but that's pretty much
it what did you find food that's good
yeah I found some juice and some
peas just going to take everything no I
don't want okay I'm going back to the uh
others okay I'm at home right now
there's still zombies out there let's
make our own w crate and put it
downstairs in our room and then nobody
will get
confused
yeah uhoh I can
C
arrows
arrows arrows maybe range might be
nice
no yeah
and then we can put that
there we should do it sooner than later
maybe maybe we should do it sooner than
later put the stuff on oh there we go
put the stuff on
in let's put the stuff on in quickly
in what's going go behind me let's put
it in just put it in oh if if we're at
home do you guys want to go back to the
main
chat the the where have a knif the main
voice chat okay cuz CeCe went
back okay that makes sense I okay see
you there do that in a second here too
cck did that work no no it didn't
work there go okay
okay
[Music]
hello I'm back I'm back the good news is
I found a house that I cilia oh really
yes why did you get back
I fought that was from the
zombie
inight no no I thought it was for the
zombie I thought oh my God this guy has
a lot of loot
wow it was me my it was still
decomposing I read your I read your
magazine again huh you read
[Music]
the if I find now you know if there's a
backpack that's
Well yeah if I if I find two more
magazines I'll give them to you I'll
donate them to you no worries no worries
it's okay I have a question yes how do I
get a iron how do I get
IR use an for IR not sure about that
probably have to find a rock and iron M
it maybe maybe like do I need a or
something in here or just a stone
pickaxe is fine your junk in there sorry
Stone axe I guess
yeah chest something
maybe oh I can make grilled corn now I
go find iron then how can you make the
grilled corn baby um I used a magazine
to learn cooking skill and now I have
cooking skill up oh can can make all I
want to find a magazine oh okay I I need
I need a cooking grill but if I we have
a cooking grill I can cook the corn I
think there was a leave the cooking
grill at the fire so everyone can cook
then yeah yeah I think the best way to
go about the magazines is probably to
like share them in the sense that like
oh okay one person does all the cooking
one person does this because otherwise
we're not actually going to level
anything okay if I have I have two skill
points in cooking already so I guess
I'll cook she's going to be all cooking
let me cook
[Music]
[Applause]
I have corn yeah so give give me your
corn and then I will I will the chest
the
chest who wants to come with me I'm
looking around Gathering
materal got
[Music]
the I'm going to the farm if anyone
wants to come to the farm with me uh
come to vc2 where I'm going to get
materials if someone wants to come with
me come to V
[Music]
nothing okay where was the
cooking what's the I supposed to be
punching corn do you think yeah yeah
punch the corn and then you get it I can
ask but they have like not dead corn so
the green ones oh God damn it yeah most
of them are
dead that one looks alive oh thank God
sure did you say we had a cooking pot
somewhere no I didn't see it okay um
I'll leave my corn here although I am
hungry okay do we have to steal a
cooking pot or something yeah yeah it's
necessary I think oh we need we also
need to find a source of water and like
to boil it with a
pot okay do you guys want to try going
to Theo my God okay I'm it turns out I
haven't read your magazines oh really
okay oh you can have them back here I
put them in this crate
here imag something that
anybody did they disappear afterwards
yeah they disappear
afterwards I see thank
you wait you know
what [\h__\h] wait I can't one sec whoops I
didn't mean to say
that I mean oh shoot oh
no oh gosh you give it back is this your
uh your reward you
cank SM together hey
big together O club is better know Club
cratic skill okay okay I'll go with kie
if anyone wants to go kie and I are
going to the
farm I'm not going to surv okay I'll go
to the farm too oh my goodness
can you guys
bring hello can we act as if this is a
this is a
walkie-talkie I on my way hello everyone
over uh which direction is the farm over
hi guys what's your favorite manga over
hos no Kuni over I love hos no Kuni so
much have you read up to the news um
uploads I'm almost at end I'm just
trying to be brave enough to read the
ending over I haven't even got I haven't
gotten to the ending either it's it's
it's despair but I hope it'll be okay I
hope so too
over okay over hi Callie what's your
favorite manga over was that please
repeat the question C over uh what's
your favorite mang C over it's a secret
C over it's a secret why over what do
you mean is a secret is it that type of
not manga no like that type of stop
outing me is
it is it bers bers it's berserk over oh
oh okay I heard also JoJo's over I
really want to read berserk over because
of because of Dark Souls I heard it's
related so I want to read it like over
but I I heard I might be traumatized
over you might over care but it'll be
like trauma bonding over trauma bonding
is actually very effective in Zombie
Survival especially
over guys I don't like zombies
over the Grim Reaper doesn't like
zombies either over do we really need
voice uh the walki talkies and we're
next to each other ladies over but look
how far away people is over can you can
you hear me I'm not not I'm entering a
tunel I can't hear I'm in a
tunel over oh my god oh this is a new
house I didn't go in here but um we can
check this out oh hello hello zombie
okay watch out watch
out watch
out watch out over there's a couple of
zombos this item needs I got your six
over I found I found okay so I have one
dream I want to pick up vehicle stuff
and uh maybe medicine stuff I want to be
a Healer maybe maybe uh so if you guys
want anything let me know and I'll I'll
I'll hoard the magazines for now and
then we can like exchange I okay I just
want cooking I guess since I'm the cook
now apparently I'm going to be a fighter
it's only two so if you don't want to
you don't have to but I like cooking
okay okay then I'll give you all the
cooking over thanks over give Mor
farming stuff and uh strength stuff okay
farming that sounds fun strength U let
me see I'm going strength fortitude
hammered okay
okay um ah ah I hear a zombie uhoh oh
they're mad I don't see it but I hear it
oh I see it I see it over they're angry
over oh oh he's big lady over big oh two
of them
okay C behind you kie another one
there's actually a lot of them
everywhere uh be careful over behind you
too over it might be over over no it's
okay we got this just K them kite them
yeah kite
them oh that's a
really it's okay it's okay we got this
over what if we lead them away and then
and then
scavenge no I think we we got them yeah
we got this just keep
kiting yeah there's one one's already
down it's the name of the game it's
called seven days to kite yeah seven
days to kite
it's true yeah Tiding I'm stamina one
second I'll just stand here for a
moment oh yeah
over
ow they're almost dead
over good job over nice ah but then
there's another
over you got this over oh jeez over it
it might be over for me over no no no
it's okay where are you I'll help
you are you inside oh there's so many of
them oh
yeah she's tanky zombies are pretty
beefy some beefy e that they still like
this tanky oh she's dead she's dead what
way to
die wow nice POS gang up on him a bul
and we can get him wait there one more
person here oh it's oh it's oh nice
crony let's go she's not in voice but
you oh a nurse oh doctor
doctor one more hit and it's over for me
over stand behind stand behind Okay
protect me
please okay that one knows how to
jump nice one should I Corney to jump
into voice or oh she's running away
should I okay never
mind it's fine it's fine it's fine let's
see what kind of loot we find in here oh
I want I think I mean this must have
been worth it right oh for sure found
some
[Music]
trash I meide over
here let's see must be something good up
here
parkour another
ladder oh maybe see other side oops
we're really
smart huge brain people
cute oh no a zombie a zombie a zombie oh
up here could hiding sorry I may have
hit you
ow kick him while he's
down how did you guys get upstairs
nice his
loot oh it's a blood bag ammo weapon
flashlight Mark schematic you can take
it really I found a bunch of stuff do in
the leather trunk there's shotgun shells
which I definitely will need uh there's
a first aid kit an instated oh the great
Heist volume two is this for agility
maybe we can give it to an agility
friend oh I'm an agility friend okay you
can have hello hello oh hi hi what are
you guys up to just killing
stuff I found a
shovel may I may have the agility book
please yeah sure let me find a way to
give it to you hold on let me drop it
okay agility and then I found a medical
journal do we have a medic yet oh I
wanted to do medic if that's okay of
course I'll give you I will not use it I
I'll wait until the until we reunited
with the others because maybe someone
else already
used you're welcome so you can keep it
for now Okie doie I'll hold on to it for
now okay do you guys want to try going
you know when you look at the map the
road do you want to try going further
East and see if we can find any
buildings sure well there's still one
house that we haven't looted that I
actually opened in this Farm okay okay
maybe we can hit that first that's our
BAS where is base and then we can go you
trying to head back to the base
crownster
yeah the base is um do you see the red
green square on the map where we are
like right next to it it's like a really
big
Square yeah yeah like a rectangle looks
like a Swedish flag or
something and then you follow that thin
Road the thin road to the west and then
there's one little building with like a
little Loop and that's where our
building is our house oh okay yeah thank
you I think I
know ladies if you want to follow me I
can take you to the place that I busted
open oh okay wait for me I'm coming sure
okay we'll walk slowly I have a cut on
my P walk our Pew walk so how long have
you been surviving in this in this
zombie apocalypse
over over oh man about 30 minutes oh why
am I not moving that's kind of weird my
body wow you must this this must be like
you you fell into a coma and then you
woke up because it's been 20 years for
me I found a pig 20 years in the zombie
apocalypse he Pig oh it's live it's
alive oh it's oh it's actually alive be
careful it's going to attack you
probably I'm going to need I might
actually be dead you are infected take
antibiotics to avoid symptoms uhoh um
where did you guys
go look for us on your map we're at a
big house I tried to break down there's
a sofa in front of it but might be able
to move it or I see I see oh there's a
lot of isn't this like a three three
skull area B yeah but I beat I beat up a
couple of the zombies that were here
already I'm coming you guys and bringing
a pig with me oh sounds fun is that a
pet is it is that going to be a pet um
uh s sir sir where you
guys having a hard time oh okay just
kidding the zombies have awoken all
right uh time to lead them out of the
house well we can like get the stuff
around the house oh we could try getting
into the house maybe one person can go
in try getting the zombies and then the
another person goes in and tries to loot
yeah sure sounds good do you want to
loot I can just lead him away I can
coral them away I'm curly in the
basement trying to be sneaky oh there's
the pig oh God yeah the pig the pig I
have 4 HP zombies and pigs okay to deal
with okay okay I'm coming
upstairs Pig please I have no quarrel
with
you stupid Pig hi stupid Pig ha yes
stupid dummy Pig hi
dummy stupid hi stupid Pig stupid Pig
can't even jump oh behind youie uhoh
There's a Zombie it's kind of a strong
one he needs a big b oh the pig's not
stupid the
pig oh the pig is very very smart oh God
he's after me a run pig is too fast kill
the pig first Focus Pig Focus P CL the
pig C the pig take turns take turns
doing shots
I will aveng
you use this I'm getting eaten first
that's messed
up maybe I can use this kit I feel bad
but oh I killed the pig I killed the pig
oh nice job three HP and a pork dream
going to get some bacon today nice you
got some good food
CeCe o so I think we need like a knife
or something to to get the meat out of
the pig so but that might be good food
source a bone actually a bone knife help
okay you should do it then I have blade
specialty now for
knives maybe you can get like extra for
it or something nice I'm getting a ton
of stuff off this pig though with his
knife knce we have food guys we have
food with the with the gatherers no with
the hunters Hunter Gathering yeah
hunting that's what we do all night okay
I'm going in uh
I'm going to try getting them out and
just
oh uhoh
I watch out behind thiso there's going
okay I do have four HP so I'm not sure
oh jeez maybe we should lead them out
first okay a lot of the doors are locked
it seems okay I'm leading them
outside don't detect them or they'll
lose um
aggro what also I'm pretty sure the head
is is like just like usual the weak
point no it's easy I'm watching over
your
body oh he's got some reach on
him no don't eat her you piece of [\h__\h]
don't eat me don't eat me or do eat her
so she'll be distracted
okay well you know what I'll I'll I'll I
can give you my my meat for
that I'm watching over your back you'll
get you'll get new meat anyway okay I'm
back yeah I don't like how they like
trick you into thinking that dead when
they on the floor like imagine we did
that like you get hit and you just like
classic move they shouldn't be smart
enough for that be careful there's a big
guy let's just ignore this one he's kind
of slow okay I'm going to go back inside
see try to kite them
out in the
basement okay so I got into a room o I
found a gun
magazine um may or may not oh my gosh I
found a cooking pot we can cook corn
when we get
back
did okay kiting kiting
kiting okay just got a kite so there's
three of them oh I can try taking them
on yeah and it's like a small room so I
can't like really kite them oh hello I'm
about to head towards your location hi
scce support us in our battles I found a
cooking pot so we can we can make corn
when I get that oh oh yummy corn I love
my grit we also found some
be corn pork tons of food oh pork
finally
meat but we need water I think it's now
the issue oh I see there are zombies the
room what to do about that to be honest
yeah okay I got
up ah there's a bunch of
people okay okay there's a lot of
shipping crates up here there's a lot of
stuff so if we can get them somehow
so I'm King them outside so if someone
wants to go all the way up there's like
a lot of stuff I'll
try hiting them because they on the roof
right now did you guys finish looting
the farm out of
curiosity uh no one of the houses but
like there's a lot of zombies around are
you okay okay I see I see never mind I'm
skipping to
far well that's bad okay actually maybe
I'm going to kite them so they come down
down maybe yeah are you on the second
floor too CeCe I'm on top of the roof oh
that'll do it here I'm pulling some of
these dudes
out hell all dipped
out oh my goodness so they're jumping
down okay one went back in and two
jumped
down okay okay and they I think they
took some fall damage from
that I'm going in take him see that guy
that guy's nothing he's nothing
oh there's a lot okay I went I got oh by
the way there's some more people coming
uh maybe like four zom zoms just oh just
kidding people as in zombies There's a
big one okay there's only one with me
upstairs right now so I'm going to just
loot everything yeah go for it take what
you can
take um I found a paper interesting oh
I'm dehydrated that's a big boy
yeah there's also two like right behind
me can I drink this water I will uh do
this technique called I found a medical
journal
nice nice and I found some vitamins
hello does anyone have locks not wait I
think I'm lagging oh I think the
server's lagging yeah I was going to say
they're dumb they're caught in the fence
F oh
whoa whoa whoa
hello all right he wants to sell
pancakes oh Yik I have no Stam sounds
like me when I'm hunging CU I'm
hungry I he a lot of zombie
sounds maybe that'll help me a little
bit here he's after me so you can
probably hit him during that cool that's
a good idea I can make I can make tea
with that flow power okay here we
go give him up wow I have I found a
reinforced chest and I will spend some
time on on on enforcing it enforcing it
in up up up enforcing it it looks clear
out here
now yeah there's only like two zombies
who take up a lot of hits
yeah I cck on the zombie
heads man he has so much health I'm
going to kill the a zombie that's
upstairs for you CC so you can come out
I'm
dehydrated I'm deated actually we need
to find water well there there's some
water here it's just too bad we can't
just eat the snow I know wouldn't that
be great if we could just eat snow eat
the yellow snow isn't it like the energy
you take to melt snow if you have a
human
body what if it's
lemonade sorry I'm not that into your
Jewel of emotions there no of
emotion I didn't I didn't mean I made
the yellow
snow I found an egg oh you're not sing
like a lemonade business with
it man my character's tired go away
zombie I can't okay time for me to drink
I don't have murky
water oh that's how you do it press W
just going to take some time to
heal
oh okay I'm at 3,400 out of 5,000 he's
finally dead it's fine he's not dead I
lied I got the Traer I finally got the
Traer oh my oh you're up here
hello I will help you oh now I have a
lot of skill points oopsies okay I'm
just going to leave this guy to you guys
hello I need help hello use use your
axxe oh my axe okay oh I I'm like too
weak in
general no you're strong to us you can
be like mentally strong even if you're
physically weak it's okay bro I'm tired
my character is
thirsty this guy is like too he's too
big in
health okay I'm leading him towards you
good
luck so uh what you do before the uh
zombie apocalypse
C uh I was an an interior designer
actually oh w
wow what did you design like like houses
like inside yeah mostly like yeah mostly
like for like you know rich people they
would hire me and then I would give them
like very high prices for very minimal
work uh but like but like lovingly and
um than God that guy would not leave me
alone I would focus on floral vintage
Aesthetics M ooh sounds fancy and then
uh I was pretty lonely fall while uh in
the zombie apocalypse but i' I've you
know I've found groups like this before
but they are never they never last they
never last um I see definely Will been
on my own for a while and you know I'm
ready I'm ready to Che on another group
I'm ready to open up GL you're
here thank you thank you I I feel very
welcome to be honest so I'm very happy
about that how about you what did you do
before
I I was a menace to society I was I
didn't I was unemployed I had no job I
Freel loaded so I'm kind of glad Society
fell during this zombie apocalypse so
everyone can start over and be equalized
because I was this like scum of the
earth you know scared me mhm would you
argue your life is better now than yeah
my life is better now cuz like everybody
everybody has nothing so we're all in
the same like playing field now yeah
it's great okay don't you think usually
you would want to push yourself up
instead of bringing other people down
well well now that now I can now I can
you know oh so you feel like you've got
second CH this this is this is my second
chance at life yeah and now you've
become like morally very positive and
supportive exactly before I was just
like you know not unemployed looking at
wow all those rich people with their um
switches and ps5s and I was really
jealous but now nobody has anything so
you're like a
vtuber no one has
PS5 what is a
PS5 what is it what is it but no I
understand that's good I'm happy that
you get to put on a night leave okay I'm
opening it oh oh that's that's you
scrapping for fun one first eight kit
pipe baton if anyone wants a baton a
baton Bandit armor plating mod um I'll
take the scrapping forun I'll just I'll
just oh no someone else can take it I'm
can I water from here please does
someone want to be a nerd I have
electrical traps magazine and a medical
journal a nerd I want a
medical not yet I don't want to be a
nerd I'm stupid yeah me too do you want
to pick this up
I'm scrapping for
fun banded armor oh pipon maybe I want
scrapping instead of medical
H I don't want to make thisis before we
talk to the others maybe they already
it's raining it's
raining rain re zombies Hallelujah
there's a house
there I'm going to keep uh looking
around I found some good
stuff oh God we still have not found
water yeah water's the big concern here
yeah I'm C
C think we have to oh okay I can take
the rest I'm not I'm just going to I'm
just going to put some seeds and flowers
I
don't okay I think there's like a way I
don't know how but I think there's a way
to craft like a
water rain oh yeah just a zombie I can
always get some more
St I'm trying to reset I don't want to
be trapped oh I just put some random
stuff in the chest
oh you have phone I want
that it's
raining that's weird why is it not me
it's
raining okay um how are we feeling what
time is it does anyone know what time it
is oh 2:00 p.m. only we can go we can
keep adventuring if we want to but we
are pretty in
cucumber maybe we should head back to
the farm just once to the farm uh not
the farm sorry our home okay okay okay
okay let's head back home put all our
stuff back oh if anybody wants extra
arrows I put it in here cuz I don't have
any room oh nice I need arrows okay nice
nice nice I'm going to arrow for where'
you put them bi boo in this chest okay
I'm going to grab it sorry you guys are
going to have to not see me for a minute
um as I'm resetting stuff oh nice
oh trash
pile
trash I do
think put the
plant oh I can still hear her
voice I'm
here come
here is
air okay I'll go back for now
okay oh there's a fireplace this house
is kind of nice
actually it is pretty good I'm not going
to lie it seems a little bit better well
but the other one has a pool table yeah
you're right sorry T and the and the and
the what is it called the TVs PCS yeah
the PC setups yeah it doesn't work but
it's still really cool yeah oh right we
didn't go underground oh she already is
here okay she proba everything
did you loot everything no I just looked
around and killed things okay let me Lo
yeah so the general rule is uh vc1 is
our home base and then all other ones
are different groups that are going out
on excursions together yeah cuz we don't
really know if proximity tat really
works in this game so this is just the
best the
best was really weird because it worked
the other day when we tested it didn't
it Kelly yeah it did we just is
extremely strange so wa maybe it's based
on if there's like less people so
smaller amounts of people could
work we were the same though we were
four earlier and we were four the other
day as well so yeah I I tried it earlier
during testing and no one could hear me
when I was out of the party it only
worked when I was in the
party yeah and even then it wasn't
proximity in the party it was just uh
General chat General yeah whatever like
you oh well it's okay I feel like this
is working especially when we're in a
little bit smaller
groups oh I think so too yeah oh I found
gasoline
oce oh he's beware of
dog I'm out of stamina in here like Che
I found pumpkins and I found eggs and so
much meat there's 30 raw meat bi boo
cook us something delicious pleas I will
let me
cook cook okay I'm back at the base so
I'll jump into the other I'm going to
I'm going to head back more Adventures
I'm down yeah we do one after we regroup
yeah okay
okay hold on I'm having to reinstall a
new camera you guys sorry about that
okay I will go I will hop over when I
get
[Music]
home time to cook some corn and some
meat and some St
stuff cannot hear me you can't hear me
say oh
nothing no I'm I'm in a bar with like
three things so I I'm trying to figure
out how to kill them here let me let me
come help you first and then we can head
back
together sure I was just looting this
place near your
farm wow my character's like so tired
I'm just too thirsty thirst I can't even
drink blue I didn't know you were wanted
me that bad
sh I can't help it I just look at you
and think like wow my beautiful yellow
snow which Barn are you in there's like
three
I just press um oh you're you're near it
just go okay I see I see I see
yeah it's just like if I do one thing I
lose like 20 stamina immediately that is
how tired I am I am I am not tired are
you downstairs oh be careful there's
like three crawling zoms
on I know aren't they kind of
cute wow I hear the music yeah me too
too all right guess I'll I'll try to
help
out uh thankfully they have very bad AI
oh they're dead they're dead one's dead
oh you're so quick okay I'm tired please
please carry on are you upstairs or
downstairs I'm still here I'm right
behind you oh okay okay there's two of
them here it's just hitting takes up so
much energy I'm so
tired I got a knife so me that's why it
doesn't take too much oh maybe it's cuz
I use a
spear maybe just
like die oh good God there's more I
think she wants my autograph oh she you
can jump okay I killed one I killed one
hold
on okay thank
you oh man I think my axe
broke live just kite oh there's more of
them seven days to kite sh okay I got
another one where are you
maybe there another one the P two people
the what the the H uh-huh over the what
over over the ponder over the ponderer I
thought you were like a
pondering no no no that's not me look at
you you shank so good for someone who
didn't do anything at pass sh really
well you're like a native Londoner I had
one skill I had one skill in my in my in
my past and that was shaking people to
survive so you know it carried over
wonderful my hero so you're the Sherer
I'm the Shanker she's the Shanker she's
a Shanker I'm the Shanker yes yeah okay
there's like literally not much
here uh there's clay okay we're good
this place sucks I I have come here to
beg you for food over oh okay over I'm
sorry we only have corn oh no I have
some food no we have like a bunch of
meat we have like 30 uncooked meat or
something oh well I'm surviving on corn
okay so let we want to go home so we can
cook the the corn and then I can give
everybody food oh yeah sure okay okay
over thank you see you see you there
over yeah
over so so what were you before the
apocalypse H I actually think I have
amnesia oh wow hit your head a little
I know probably got run over by another
freaking truck I could have sworn that
before all this I might have been in
this world that was all squares and
blocks and everyone was like really
really
crazy crazy a I was crazy once
yeah you were crazy what happened then
uh I was locked in a movie called The
Joker 2 and
flop wait I haven't I haven't seen that
but I've heard like the memes is it
really that bad I I heard it's bad you
heard it's
bad I heard it's bad that actually makes
me want to watch it
though oh there's my
axe was was the first one like really
good or something so the second first
one was actually I'm dying of
dehydration holy crap the first one was
actually decent I see I haven't seen
either the first one was like good I see
well uh you can watch both and then you
can uh proceed to enjoy one of them oh
it was meant to be a oneoff but they
made a sequel anyway according to the
voices in my head yes that is correct
I'm dying from dehydration beibs uh here
I'm going to drop you some juice here
got some juice come here
okay take my juice it's not
lemonade well even if it was I think I
have no choice but to drink it
oh thank you it's a musical for some
reason there's like so they so
characters just break off into
song yeah pretty much oh that's
cool yeah there's also some uh some very
kinky things I guess why is my running
in
place is she running in place for you or
is it just
me how do I put the cooking pot
down uh so at the right you see like
fuel right and then there's tools put
the the pot into like any of those tools
oh
okay yeah there's already fuel in there
oh oh okay I'm going
to turn on God we finally eat something
now I'm going to I'm going to make 31
cooked
corns oh blessed the corn
oh cooking grill required I can't oh I
can make boiled eggs though we we will
have to deal with the eggs then oh here
we actually have 15 eggs how about I
drop it for you and uh should we join
the other voice chat now here's the the
eggs okay oh I can make bacon and eggs
okay cool okay let's join the other
voice chat
yep hello
home silly okay oh welcome home I
have I
brought my cooking pot I have okay I
dropped like 30 meat on you I can make
bacon and eggs and I can make boiled
meat so I'm going to make oh thank God
blessed the heavens yes please okay hold
on to M let me cook we're so lucky that
we have eggs for
us can you make tea too B um let's see
with the golden
flowers oh I can oh I found a golden rod
flow oh I cured my a weapon or tool oh
you can make you can purify water as
well like oh oh please make we need that
yeah if you have
if you have murky water I can purify it
I have that too have some water that's
cool okay I'm going to bacon an exit up
okay we had two uh murky water I'll drop
it for you here go yay oh thank you
y how cute our natural murky for the
murkiest
reasons M it's a nice first house but we
definely want to get one closer to the
trader yeah actually it's
okay since we're near a river with our
empty bottles we could theoretically go
near it GA water and just like boil that
endlessly I hope wa you guys have
bottles I don't have
bottles infinite water trick what' you
guys get bottles open your mouth just
open your mouth look up you can't why
would they do
that what about glass how do I split a
stack I'm
blind right I'm just going to do a quest
no then
okay oh I figured it out okay thanks
have you seen the Traer yet K if anybody
has any more cooking books uh please
give them to me so I can yes I will give
them to you I do see I don't actually
know if it's like super important to be
honest I don't want to I don't want to
Railroad and be like oh we have to be
super careful when I have when I don't
know but this is just like my
inclination but maybe I'm wrong so just
be yes I am at the TR do have
flowers can you boil them so that I can
drink him okay let me try we can drink
him okay yeah thank you how I'll just
drop it okay and I'll also craft armor
so I'll read this I'll go for medic if
you want to give me the medic thingy
what's too expensive oh the medical
journals I put in the journal crate is
over here where the Jal crate so I need
I need one more level in cooking
if anybody has
any cooking magazines cuz I can't make
tea just yet somewhere else
okay the trader sells the tea that
you're making for 144
coins I don't even know where to get
coins Earth to we get coins that's crazy
that is crazy my diarrhea is going away
on own thank you sir any did I take the
GL I will just cook a bunch of meat
right now I found some acid if you think
that could help your stomach
problems it would help with the liquids
I
guess oh be do you want to put the the
cooked food in this one
the the right one and we should try to
figure out how to make a the one that
the one that you're looking at yeah okay
you are where I need to go for my fetch
Quest when did you take this Quest oh I
think you're sharing cuz we're in the
same party all right I'll put purified
water well how are you already there oh
I was just walking wait I don't think I
can do it for you doesn't let me okay
I'll wait so you coincidentally there
the moment I took it what oh you can
label the
boxes okay I'm on
M oh we can make we can make glue I can
eat glue no no no no
no not the idea I'm just grilling me at
the moment
okay awesome a b
sleepover yeah I love it you look like
the how do I in watch movies one item
instead of all the items guys I don't I
know rightside our door oh control right
water yeah control right click I'm sorry
I got to drink some that's okay I've
been dehydrated
water control go home water am I finally
like not as dehydrated okay one
two why can my skin not absorb the water
from from the skin why not cuz you're
dehydrated glass star just disappeared
that's
stupid you eat them why why would the
Glass St disappear after using them am I
just going to crap out glass like CS now
that
makesense ate the glass you glass
raining wo o how comy too bad we can't
drink it open your mouth can I open my
mouth just right now I'm opening your
mouth yeah you just have to look up at
the sky oh my God drank all the
water excuse me are you still are you
still at the quest oh yeah I think you
are please I'm so thirsty and so
unwet we do am I
drinking I can't tell if they were
kiding maybe no we're not you just you
have to wait it's very
incremental but I've already drink ohy
storm okay I'm going to start the what
should I do is there anything we can do
at night oh oh probably stick
around oh cry I love crying me too
supplies in here I hope the mushrooms
grow inside there golden rod seeds more
seeds
what there's zombies in here what
zombies what's wrong there's here okay
where all right is he stuck uh no I
think she's doing the
quest I'm on my way it's really scary
it's it's dark and rain
all it's very
scary oh maybe I can't Farm here
I probably
f a rotting
flash yeah we need a farm plot if we
want to
farm this might be all the man I can't
make my hops does anyone want to go to
the trainer for a quest if not totally
fine yeah oh no I didn't want to I
didn't run a rush I just thought if you
going to do something else can I not use
I got to go there anyway um the food is
going to take a couple minutes to cook
but I put I put food might be one stairs
it it keeps saying chart meat b i you
have no no no chartred meat is the food
it is the food oh really meat T meat is
is the food that youat very good at
cooking no that's what it says that's
the
option that's that's all I can make
right now I need one more book to make
make better stuff I don't want to take
both it's okay it's
okay I'll put one back Cheng no I
stabing in the you're going to eat my
Char meat and you're going to like it
where's the boiled egg O it's so nice
and dry okay I'll cook some eggs too I'm
cooking some eggs I'm dying you have
water wait why are you dying should I
not be here you should be here you
should be here what's happening don't
worry wait should we go into a VC the
quest yeah we can go okay yeah which one
two four
what okay Cecilia you wanted to go to
the Traer
right oh I want to go to the trailer too
okay I'm outside some wood Traer team
what VC should we hop into do you
think uh oh there's a bunch of now we
can take four let's take
four
jump hello yeah think I could eat a raw
egg is take place in America I'm making
I'm making boiled eggs if you wait like
a couple minutes oh cool I'll just go
put this egg back in the crate then we
can go oh it's no longer raining my free
water is gone what a shame I know they
hate me they just want to dehydrate my
butt so
evil some mky water the toilet oh good
give it to me and I can purify it
awesome that' be huge
B I'm going to put it in the food
actually here I'm going to drop it on
the ground I really need water actually
so how can I unlock this drop okay there
you
go that's huge that's a really big
deal always check toilets ladies toilets
are full of water that if you boil it
you can drink it okay it takes one
minute to cook let me cook I am
cooking okay and then we can definitely
we can go to the tra the Trader's pretty
far huh yeah it's an adventure sure I
mean it's already 9:00 p.m. we might die
but that is true well just prare your
spawn points you got your beds already
yeah that's true also you know we did it
last time it's fine it'll be fine have a
little water drink and then we can go
sorry if you guys is water still you
guys have enough water you guys have you
guys decent on water I'm starving and
dehydrated but it's okay maybe we'll
find hydrated but I am hungry oh there's
a c I see how cooking works there's a
cute is that why your meat is
charred Char me's pretty good
actually no it's
dry he was going to be serving us up
sirloin steaks pretty soon I know what
happened ooh I can't wait let's go my
Gordon Ramsay oh does it go into like
straight into the storage cases if I
take it
out it shouldn't that's going to strange
which
St
the I'm heading to the Traer now I hope
I don't die okay we'll go we will go as
well but if you want to goe Callie were
you thirsty I'm getting items too I am
okay hold
on before it hits
night okay here you go here's some water
all right ready to
go thank you so much B
let's run ladies let's run close the
door maybe let's go I'm just
walking just music now though repair my
C go my map got marked with a
Traer are they
sus we don't know yet we have to
actually the Traer is very hot hot as
like is on fire no like she's a
beautiful lady oh beautiful lady
wow yeah hey Chad how do iink won let us
live with her yeah I know what a shame
right I
know oh I hear them I'm on me way the
zombie me not car I wish I had a
car empty hands e all right hope you
guys catch up yeah me
too do you know where you're going I'm
just following you I have a Mark A a
marker on my thing it's not really
working but I'm also dancing with a
zombie right
[Music]
now that's never mind
is the marker for the Traer is for you
guys is it the uh the orange one it's
called White River citizen for me but
I'm might okay everybody at home died
what
happened uhoh huh they weren't at home
right I thought they were running I'm
just past the river Let Me swim to
you oh I'm
wet maybe it's because no I won't say to
make a do collection how to make a do
collector uhoh say it you
won't challenging her I
won't do you really think I would fall
for that trick yes how um oh oh oh hello
everyone guys I feel like it's important
for a social hierarchy to find out how
guy how old everyone is in the zombie
apocalypse
over oh that's not you guys that's
someone else you never ask a mustache
man his age
oh man I thought this one of you
over you first
over oh okay I'm
actually um
I'm okay are Ellie I said I've been in
the zombie apocalypse for 20 years that
was a lie it was a hyperbole it's just
my beard makes me look kind of old uh
I'm actually
only when when did the zombie apocalypse
start 30 minutes ago 30 minutes no but
like more like uh 2 hours ago actually
what
really yeah I found a wolf should I kill
it over can you take it over I don't
think I'm running away over oh shoot
that's a shame R the
away um I'm actually uh I'm
20 forever
22 but mentally I'm 38 I'm 38 guys I'm
38 okay I would like to that you should
do aot of things for us then I'm I'm 47
I'm I'm your
senior oh oh you younger than me no I'm
40 didn't you just say you're 30s I'm
47 40 oh yes I'm 4 older than me oh wow
Grandpa your age plus whatever that is
plus four what just so you
know am I a dog I'm older who
though I guess you I know guys I'm so
stupid I keep like taking my hand and
putting it on my ear like a phone oh I
keep getting
confused my hand isn't on my
mouse I'm stupid see hello oh oh hey
hello I just killed like so many things
on the way let's go where's the
traitor oh up here okay you can climb
this mountain yeah thought I did it we
got a Skyrim pretend you're a
goat anyone here ask or is it just wait
do goats go
back I I don't know but they do
now no more thirst issues did you know
that that there actually goats and sheep
hybrids and they're called
Jeep oh heard
CH Trader wrecked Trader
wrecked isn't the trader closing isn't
the tra Clos wa there's a time limit to
when it up yeah uhoh find drink the
water if you guys if sh if you look up
in the map I I found like a whole like
house area maybe that would be nice oh
do you want us to meet you there oh yeah
since I think the trade is closed okay
let's let's head toward the the CC Mark
then sure yep
yep go to The Cece maybe we could even
find a house there all you can eat for
only
$3.99 sorry you activated something
inside of me when you said
that 3.99 wear any commercials it's
pretty cheap oh I found some charred
meat oh this reminds me of B's
cooking like bi's cooking though no my
has a special
touch yeah she puts like hair in It
Special Touch what do you mean hair a
little bit
of hey just just because I shed a lot
doesn't
mean it gets in the
food that often shed a lot house well
well yeah I have a lot of hair she sheds
hair she's a wolf yeah I shed like a
dog
o okay we're here oh the gold I am here
go around I am in the in the garage the
garage hello I hear a bunch of zom zoms
yeah there's two at the
door everywhere why did do that to fast
ow maybe she wanted to
die I need to
heal wait why why is the door closed all
of a sudden I close it so that we don't
get ambushed from the other side I think
we might get get ambushed inside though
yeah but it's safe it's
okay all right um I need any more
bandages nice find those now I will
close the
door amount of
stamina
okay hey don't close
it we have less space
inside okay I'll open it yeah it's not a
good idea
definitely going to need to get prepared
before really trying to get in there huh
is that the house you guys are in
Residence we're in a Goldsmith house
right now the Goldsmith residence gotta
yeah y if we took over thisa we get
[Music]
our that be great we could each have our
own homes yeah that would be nice oh
sorry sorry I didn't mean
to here come in come in you know what
baby sorry I thought you I found a
hidden
basement o what's in there zombies oh I
hear
them hit him with my Bon stick I'm going
to make more bandages I cannot
make help you
okay big
Bonk good think my strength is unpress
nice yeah I found I found a door to oh
God a
uhoh that seems bad you okay I fell in a
hole you really gave you a shock huh all
right I
guess my leg is slained there's a lot of
people here but it's okay we keep hide
we keep
hi hard oh they're all really
fast she's very SL night time so I guess
it makes sense
okay we can drink oh crap oh crap
there's two of them on I'm going to die
guys I love
[Music]
[Applause]
you I should have put
a for
meit no I'm dead no there's two of them
in the garage as ah heads up dang it I
I'll watch over your
backpack your back but I found a really
cool
area what I'm bleeding that's cool ah I
died it's over
it's okay you found a really cool area
though I did find a really cool area I'm
cold and naked is it safe to get my
stuff in the G I think so are you guys
in a garage I'm in a oh my
God if you're in a hole my stuff is in
there I know I'm in the hole but there's
like three zombies in the hole so just
be careful they're coming take they're
following me up the
hole oh come on
hi
Callie I'm going to try my backpack my
stuff is you guys look a little
different oh
god wow the whole place is just trapped
completely yeah backpack
everything uhoh um well we just spawn
near a backpack so wor I'll kill him I
think it's fine unless there's
punishment I'm infected
I'm stuck I'm stuck between like five
zombies this is not the way to go I
don't like
it goodbye oh shoot oh trapped I'm
trapped actually I'm trapped it was a
good good call is
that
okay there is a way to get out y of a
cruel world oh hello ow can you hey can
oh is that a zombie
all right I like to spawn near my
backpack
again my dude is still a dream s get out
of my way some leave me alone oh jeez
wish could someone make me a spear
because my backpack is again I think
we're all dead um was everyone dead yeah
am I the only one in here uh I I
oh jeez however I think the tactic is to
oh shoot oh shoot why leave the
house leave the house this is
interesting it's over this is very
interesting okay I'm taking I'm taking
all your stuff and then I'm
running okay I'm out
okay thank you thank you Jo thank you
you're welcome you're welcome God oh
dear I will now have to get my items
down there there oh no because I took
the backpack I'm so Sor okay as long as
you guys put items I'll run I'll run
back over there I'll run
back what is happening holy sorry go
it'll be fine it'll be fine you're not
that far actually yeah I got to get my
items again um you guys just get your
items and get out then maybe we can come
back as a group yeah I can't my stuff
cuz it's cuz it's on the Upper Floor and
I okay I got my stuff I'm going to leave
never mind I'm totally dead no I don't
want to die now because I have CI stuff
all right I'll wait until she's
back and search I believe in you the
chat we already have a base we have a
base but we wanted to make one closer to
the traitor it's embarrassing I don't
want to that
s time does feel very long that is true
okay oh oh man this place sucks we got
this we got this yeah we'll be
fine this
is oh they broke the
ladder oh my God I don't know if I can
collect my stuff my stuff's in the Attic
I'm just going to kill everyone in
here if I have to die I will die again
and again and kill everyone and take
them down with me it could be morning
soon you
know all right I'm coming back for you
guys mark my
words hi okay I'll drop all your stuff
here okay thank you all of it yes thank
you so much for picking up my stuff no
I'm sorry for making you run but clearly
you're
good okay kite would you be able to make
me a spear then I can help a little bit
yeah k
k
oh
kite I don't actually know your I'm just
punching them all no okay let's see if I
can make you spear real quick
okay I got
out with my I'm punching all of them
okay here you go even through all the
pain all right I think they should at
least be out at least I hope they stay
that way nice I got a spear okay okay
I'm back put
your should all be outside hopefully can
one of you put me out of my misery okay
you want to be
killed thank
you always don't never hesitate to ask
guys we all support each other here it
Callie put your clothes on oh shoot
you're right I'm
naked they're after you they're after
you might want to run
actually that's your items after me does
anyone want to come after
them I got her arm busy are you still in
the house I was really fast oh is that
you oh that's you
yeah oh after you okay I'll try going
inside getting my backpack okay okay
just keep running short keep running I
think I might die in like 5 Seconds keep
running oh we got a lot of exp that's
pretty good must mean we' done something
good okay so you said they broke the
ladder oh yeah I got to go back there
though for my item oh no I mean the my
lad still
there I got my stuff nice I got my stuff
if you can get my items that's good too
it's at the bottom of the hole though
the bottom of the hole I am currently
like all the way
upstairs that's fine
oh I can't
see oh she's dead nice job
team I sacrificed myself for you live oh
sorry okay I'm going to try to get my
items okay they're kind of quick I got a
I found a sniper magazine like a sniper
stronger I could really use
G gun would be fun how am I suppos gun I
only found like a magazine for it all
right all my items are covered even if I
die I don't
care thank you for cting them all not
bad I mean thank you not bad Tech junkie
Tech Planet I'll take the sniper
magazine I kind of want to be a sniper
okay okay I'll give it to you you guys
find any shotgun mags please tell me you
can have they get out of
here it is morning time which means the
zombies should slow down no there's
still one after me if you guys want to
help I found medical journal oh there
you
go this house is just the floor sucks
right so we need to rebuild
it I don't know if it's a good idea
living here though unless we put all our
blocks down then it could be okay yeah
yeah maybe stop
spawning should we take this is way to
like crouch on the floor do you
sometimes see those like tiny holes do
you know if you can do something about
control but it's not much of a Crouch
yeah yeah it's very
pitiful we could also build our own home
near the trader but it's kind of
building is at the beginning is going to
be kind of difficult hard yeah I think
so I think it's best to like y house
okay do you guys want to go to the
trader then or do you want to stick
around here a bit longer sure let me go
there my two Health oh no take out of a
misery sh did we pick everything here
did we loot everything I don't think so
I still hear them in fact oh hi my hello
oh gosh the floor is lava certainly I
know do you guys go back inside oh you
guys are back inside yeah I got to get
my corn meal
ooh Rotting Flesh yummy yummy delicious
my favorite I
know I am a bit over encumbered if
anyone has space and would like to share
the burden I have no
space I don't really have space either I
have like one slot open I can't run
anymore it's over maybe you should eat
all your corn I don't have any
corn oh an archery
guide oo guess I'll use that I could use
it someone's cucumber
this eat my corn
meal stay nice and strong I know heal my
five Health
yeah I was going to say like oh I
haven't been hungry in a while it's just
because we've been in a death Loop yeah
maybe maybe it's a good tactic though
what's the punishment of death it might
be yeah shame that's about it that's not
I don't have that much it there are a
lot of houses around here right for the
picking though especially in the morning
yeah I mean if we can respawn near
backpacks I think it's worth doing it um
more you should put clothes on yeah
you're naked I accidentally have your
clothes I think when I picked up your
backpack it automatically put on your
clothes on me that's okay I'm just
making new ones no worries I can I can
come down I'm just getting some loot
real quick made it I'm good is there any
scam mail what do you think is in this
house oh Urban
combat who wants to learn oh this is for
stealth oh Urban combat's good for
everyone
actually Okay who wants to excel at
stealth I might go for archery oh I'm
doing agility so if you want to give me
steell stuff you
can okay I'm I'm not going for strength
or anything but I'm going for I want to
go for strength I'm going for speed and
Parkour
Speed that's like my aesthetic look at
you guys killing like an overworked
nurse I can't believe
you whatever hello all right uh uh beibs
I think I was call you something else
did you just call me I'm
bleeding almost
apparently now go collect your Urban
combat thank you I'll take your corn in
the
meantime I'm a bit probably someone in
the closet o what a nice your backpack
it's fine one sec I I'll be right back
one second that was very supplies in the
bathroom this is a
PG-13 stream oh my
God what going to do with paper there's
an option to turn off Friendly Fire yeah
we don't want to do that it's more fun
this way it's fun
oh man I have way too much
crap maybe we should really look for
another base closer to the trader huh
thank I'm back but I cannot walk so I
think I'm going to go back home because
like I can literally not walk okay I
might do that too do you guys want to do
that yeah we can go home let's let's
loot this house finish searching this
house and then we can go yeah yeah I I
have like two slots left so I can't like
I cannot physically I'm going to go be
uh in cucumber
uhoh yeah he's waking up someone I'll go
because I can't Sprint so I'm going to
be slower than you guys so I'll just go
home okay it's okay I'm going to be slow
too we're going to I'll be
slow yeah I'm cucumber now nice
yeah nice too my crotch shots don't work
on zombies what a
shame I don't think they can feel their
C was there nothing oopsie I can't feel
the love
tonight I'm playing a dangerous game
there I don't know what you're talking
about what a small house oh I got a
little achievement for you Char SI of
the house that you're welcome now who is
complaining about my
cooking did I complain or did I say it's
uh wonderful beautiful amazing uh
guys back me up isn't that what I said
didn't I keep praising her about her
great cooking and how much I love it oh
yes I I remember I remember that the 21
day of September no I don't remember
that anymore actually I have
amnesia but I don't have real Amnesia I
have plot Amnesia so it's okay when the
plot asks for it I don't know what's
going on apparently charred meat will
make you thirsty though so be careful
that makes sense
oh no you need you need something to
wash down your steak are you ready to
have back
sh yeah I'm just going to equip the
medical thing um I learned medicine just
now because I don't want to be in
cucumber okay when do you when do you
want to head back let's head back yeah
let's head back residence will be mine
though eventually just not right oh can
we invite Jo to the party so I can see
your marker better oh yeah you bet oh
I'm in a different party how do I leave
party there I sent you a a
request oh okay is this technically
cheating on my other party no you're
with us right now fine they'll
understand they'll understand is this
one oh wait how do I join your party how
do I leave a party
oh I guess I gotta got to kick people
out here I'll make GG leader see see you
guys there you
go excellent and then and how do I how
do I leave
party that's a good question oh here it
is okay okay I can join a party now you
might have to send me the thing again
okay let's see
[Music]
uh thank
you great now let's head back to home I
suppose I hope they don't think I'm a
home wrecker or technically you guys are
a home wrecker
I guess so that I mean have your
relationships in that party been family
your relationships already well well FAA
put her bed next to mine oh oh my God
any part of this I put like a candle in
the room I haven't had time to like
sleep next to her yet though cuz we
can't really
sleep that is messed up though I can't
believe you would do that to her oh I
didn't do anything well she you a home
record technically didn't like M yet
they didn't sleep next to each other
sleeping her on that's mess I didn't do
anything I think you guys are a home
recers look at you we didn't do anything
we didn't even know you were sleep next
to each other buddies you never asked
now you has to take
responsibility
respons not remove the guilt from your
life a bunch of squil it's okay
I'm morally flexible today more eggs for
bi to cook for me yeah I will cook eggs
oh yeah that's a good the killer cook oh
wow we did catch up to
you yeah I told you I'm really
slow oh you mat you're not slow you're
oh wait no that's Callie okay never mind
we'll catch up to you eventually you've
got cooking sniper and shotgun farmer I
do need to find a shotgun you're
actually closer to the home than I am I
think I'm really really really slow oh
Yik man I'm growing tired because you're
cucumber I am I am I am cucumber oh I
didn't even know that we could hold more
stuff than we have it just makes us slow
yeah it just makes you slower yeah I
didn't know that I mean depend on the
weight too
probably music is actually kind of nice
you have
music yeah I mean it's part of the
game in game music
yeah why don't we meet CeCe to help her
carry some stuff where let me find where
is she no it's okay I'm almost slow
she's not on my map she's the yellow one
oh oh
it's man I feel like a like a jaguar or
something running for
home yeah you're really bounding
bounding for it yeah you have those type
do those type of animals have homes I
don't think so I they just like sleep
wherever well I mean some animals have
dens but I don't
think those that big cat does have like
a den I think those are like more maybe
we should ask yeah we should
ask no do you think she just roams
around steals internet from people yeah
just like
beep can't believe it what oh my god oh
it's so you didn't say that you were
like a moocher in your past class didn't
you oh yeah I I was a street rat
yeah but it's but she's turned off a new
Leaf but it it really talks about how
much you've feel that you're openly
talking about it you know yeah
now don't know what and T did before so
you know they might be hiding
something they might be hiding
something something let me let me ask
you waa for the book uh or maybe they're
out on adventure
still they make gunpowder oh never mind
they're like really
far please let me
know all right we can eventually shoot
things I can't
wait yeah we definitely got to talk to
the trader though cuz that's going to be
a big a big Point turning point for us
so we better go to the trader soon yes
yeah in the next two hours or so cuz
that's about all we have right
yeah maybe we can make a little list in
the Discord of like magazines that
people want that might help okay I want
to be a farmer I want anything deck
built related and
cooking I want to be a med and maybe
something like I haven't decided like
Electronics or mechanic or something
maybe mechanic I'm just I'm not sure yet
oh I have a I have a tech junky
the you're back oh you're really huffing
oh you are panting I'm telling you okay
uh the sniper I don't remember who
wanted the sniper I'm putting it in here
oh I want it I'll give you I'll give you
this magazine it's a tech junkie that
might be good for
you yeah okay electrical traps is that
the one
or look a different I don't think this
base will hold out for like seven days
oh hey the trees screw up S days to die
yeah I see what you did did you end up
making new clothes way piercing ammo
okay I'll take
that all right should we head out soon
to the Traer so we have like plenty of
time to loot as well yes one sec I have
to like organize all my stuff since it's
morning time let me see if I can make a
better
Club you going to go
clubbing I wish
better not machine gun pipe pistol pipe
shotgun how do we make that oh glue
short I need four short iron pipes I
think we have that they're in this one
in the one I'm standing in front really
yeah one sec 9 mm what what do you say
is 9 mm how can you
tell like pistols
maybe also we should try and go after
air drops there should should be one
every uh hour but I don't know how to
track them oh they can leave as supplies
but they can't pick us up yeah sadly
it's messed up right yeah oh iron pipes
yay and then what was the last one glue
so much stuff I'm a little bit
overwhelmed
um put this in
here pipe
shotgun yay I'm making a pipe
pistol cuz I have bullets for it I
remain we have do we have a box for like
bullets that I can put it in no I don't
think so we can make one I'll just use
the one with the magazines then if you
have if you have 9 mm you can give it to
me I'll use it I put it in the Box okay
how do you name
boxes oh there's two of
them um hold e and then there should be
a rename option I think
oh here let me rename the food one
there you go
food how do you how is the Box what's
the name so I can make
some huh what is it called in the in the
in the in the building
menu oh to make a box a CRA hold up
building
block I think it's and then when you
place it down I think if you hold R was
it yeah hold R you can change into
different shapes
oh okay I also was able to do it using
the crate thingy I think is this the one
yeah okay thank you oh yeah yeah like
I'll just throw my stuff in here and
then if you have like a lot of items for
it you can upgrade the building blocks
oh cool iron building blocks at some
point yeah maybe we want to make we want
to really fortify our home for the first
rush so finding out IR how to make iron
blocks might be really
big we were we'll have to look for
it oh TR I'll put some here in my B in
my home you might want to make like
traps and stuff like that as well to put
around yeah that'll be
fun what's
wrong did you fall in your own Spike
trap what
happened what what happened what did you
doing was such a jump scare
h did the game glitch no no no no I I
one shot I one tapped you in the head
with my gun I just wanted
to criminal I didn't think you would
kill her like instantly I just thought
you think shoot someone in the
head you so messed up I can't
hum can't believe you murdered your
friends messed up
me you served me a meal a five course
meal a death a lot here I'll give you
I'll give you some meat as Sor take take
my cooking I accept your one charred
meat believe it UPS W your life is only
worth like one charred meat yeah that's
horrific I feel really sad about
that oh well I just had to test it one
time okay the intrusive thought took
over I didn't think it was going to kill
you and people thought I was bad
huh let's see where can we put spike
traps probably around the house maybe a
little distance though yeah just a bit
of distance I'm going to try to make a
balcony so we have like an Escape Route
or a place to shoot
from good
idea rotate it oh I can technically make
I still I can't really heal yet I need
one more Med kit medical and then I can
make first eight bandage oh nice that's
huge but I think I'll probably wait I
can't Wheels bicycle CH bicycle I five
medical okay I like how we just forgot
okay I'm ready whenever for you want to
go okay okay okay just don't get in my
way or I might accidentally shoot you
but of course wow
accidentally on on purpose oh these are
crossbow BS not
arrows I was recommended I scrap them
can I not do this yeah completed a
challenge
[Music]
oh yeah iron iron y okay we got to do
something with the iron though we got to
figure out how to cook it or something
like
that you can make a furnace at some
point O potato
I feel like we need to find a way to
like be able to get
regular water drinking water there must
be a way to mass produce water I think
that's like collecting like collecting
water you know like a rain collector
stuff like that ah oh my God the the
spikes but we also get water from the
trader when we do quests he gives you
like rewards and you can pick water I
think water every single time shells
there's only five shells all right is
everyone ready yep ready to go okay use
that enemy I must not let my blood lust
oh we can C we can craft a du collector
that's what it is you can craft a dle
need to craft one of those so yeah if we
do that that would be nice yeah it's we
need something called a polymer
something or another a workstation too
we have polymer oh yeah workstation uh
so a certain skill will unlock lock
being able to make the workstation is it
robotics oh we need like 100 scrap
polymer Advanced
engineering yeah I see let's head to the
Traer for now okay and then try and get
the advanced engineering skill under
intelligence you guys that'll help us
create Workshop or workbenches okay all
right why does why does someone put a
random door in
here Quest you're being a little
silly all right
time guys ready to run a kilometer
together yeah yeah this is a bonding
experience bonding should I sing a song
you guys want to sing a song please sing
a song I'll sing a song I'll sing a song
in German and then we all do it together
it go you know it's like there's 10
bottles on the
[Music]
door bottles the door and tonight will
be the night that I will fall for you
[Music]
yeah
again yes another door in
[Music]
here um and then
um I miss you where are you Miss where
are you and I'm so sorry
sorry I cannot sleep I cannot eat
tonight tonight will be the night that I
will don't waste your time make a song
that's like related to us okay so we
have the Shaker this a school trip this
is a school Tri we have to uh what's up
huh oh I just heard am I crazy I felt
like I just heard someone dur the voice
call never mind never mind
I'm voice maybe yeah it was like yeah I
thought so
too kill it um kill the rabbit kill the
rabbit killed what the what the rabbit
that's messed
up just want leave you but it's F I miss
you oh it's too fast for me to shoot
wait where is it where is it where'd it
go it's uh over Over
Yonder oh wait how do I how do I
release dang it is this really worth
it how do I cancel Maybe not maybe the
meat isn't that worth it may yeah I
don't think it's worth it to waste my
bullet time
buunny yeah that's not let's not do it
yeah dang it got away all right sorry
about that any
it's the Ping okay I missed because of
the
Ping it's fine it's don't worry believe
scroll wheel what I
tried I'm pressing
doubt this this server is not close to
me there is definite ping here but
people but people haven't you I mean the
Shakura haven't you learned about your
past experiences it's okay to admit
weakness sometimes it means
yes and I will admit weakness but it was
definitely the Ping of yes oh okay so
this you're admitting the weakness of
the server yes the server itself is weak
it's like a sideway step I I I get it
you know my dad told me when I tried to
play the bass in his band one time he
said you know my it's okay to admit when
you suck at something a
so know and
youat when you suck at but that's not
nice hey I I will admit my flaws like I
will definitely go for the beef and
fall oh understandable yeah yeah I've
seen I've seen your tweets so I believe
you hey with the traitors how do you get
in Traer wrecked wait wait this is not
the Traders never mind this is borb bar
Fields oh that's a little different yeah
whoops oh we can collect corn here
though oh I need corn I'm
hungry Carl wouldn't we go to Carl's
corn Carl Carl
Carl
Carl and
car is anything else
here we become one with a
corn corn they're
Corning Corner cor the corn is cornering
hey I found people it looks like they're
digging their
grave oh really are they NBC in like
real as W and crony are here digging
their grave that sounds like something
their own Graves that's a little yeah I
thought they were like real people
anyway I'm going to the
trader yeah I'm also I'm getting
distracted but I to the Traer as well
okay I wonder what they're digging maybe
they're getting items oh it says there's
a quest you think they're preparing
their
grave I'm at the board bar Bob's Bor
okay I have to get stop getting
distracted
am I supposed to go to the
barn you can avoid it if you want this
is a nice house though say we should it
is a nice this is a nice house nice
house oh I found man's
magazine it's really nice when Farm it's
not nice anymore they're keeping people
in
CED no that's that makes it even nicer
actually it's like a
holiday yeah they're like well fed and
taken care of
yeah it's like a spa experience I see
have you never wanted to be in a you
know just
like Grace a Cas bars I mean you've done
that no I I have I've been in jail
enough I do not want to be in jail again
can you believe bi Bo's been in jail
that's crazy to
me are you sure you can't do do you
really think that's crazy when I shot
you in the head Point Blank and killed
you I mean but that's in the game right
sure talk about in the game oh look at
the piggy wait aren we don't kill the
piggy I like the piggy ah never mind
kill the piggy kill the piggy uhoh
having some trouble with the bo piggy
just starts death
now the CH oh my God I'mma eat your body
tonight baby all right good job I'm
going skin this
pig okay you shank it she makes a good
point
yummy oh we got the wrong way I'll see
you guys at the
Traer oh what is this there's a pig in a
cage I leave this pig for now but you a
piggy i s like some Gordon ramsy recipe
picking a
cage Gordon Ramsey recipe I also might
die I'm
inors it's
Smokey why is it so Smokey okay I'm I
think if you guys follow Callie she's
like basically at the Traer right now
okay we're sorry we went in this house
we're doing some looting
first yeah I got distracted I found some
soup loots are shoots distracted again
oh they have oh wait there's another Pig
be prepare to kill this pig in case it's
mean but for now for now maybe it's okay
oh I think it's just
eing I heard there's a Beau for now but
I oh there a
zombie are you kidding me I got it I got
it
Traer eat my
wrecked okay now I got it there was a
hot girl in the in the the trailer not
the trailer the the beginner's course
video a hot girl who is this guy sorry
I'm only into like fictional that's just
an honest independent business owner
okay you have to stop being
so superficial he's got a lot of good
inventory but do he Havey what did you
think of
Leon oh he's oh oh it's here he's cute
he Al I don't know how to feel cuz like
he might have a thing for aah so I can't
trust a man who might have a thing for
someone else still Al I think that's the
old version yeah oh there's a cooking
grill oh oh we need that I can make corn
with it okay I got
it I'm probably going to let myself die
cuz I only have five Health anyway all
right I got a buried treasure Quest got
money all can you pass me the grill I'll
hold on to it yeah here I dropped it
thank you we can make corn
now n i can SCP money that is a big that
is a big thing
far actually that's crazy good finally
food yeah finally we have like a regular
food toys with the
grill are all the P I already made a
shovel
all right ready to dig wellow I don't
know what happened in this house but I
there's a story oh so they weren't
digging their own Graves they were
digging for for buried
treasure part of a
quest I like the idea of them uh digging
their own Graves though I have a I have
a weapon for you sh this one's better
probably here take it oh thank you oh I
actually have that too I just don't use
it I use
now oh that one's like not
broken okay what I what should I get rid
of sometimes a zombie might spawn though
if you dig
F care make candles look for that supply
Crate yeah Diggy Diggy Hole all right
are we done here sh maybe we should go
to the trailer now all right I'm coming
we're coming to you guys yeah
wow eat some a big hole here uh I I'm
outside of the farm I'll wait for you
though oh wait how do you how do you get
out what's the jump I jumped out the
window that's a good
idea I will M oh destroy my way out
actually give me give me five seconds
give me 10 minutes
girls
girls's I think I'm too sleepy I think I
got to go to bed okay I was going to ask
like you see yawning a bit
yeah I'll join again tomorrow
I thank
you see you tomorrow see you tomorrow
home
wer what's up oh yeah come
here
huh anyway I was going to go the other
way but now that you picked me up I must
now go with
you I had to leave in style you see I
had to leave my mark in this territory I
see oh treasure be
there okay let's go to the Traer I too
must eat my
dindon how how how long do are we going
for
tonight until we got another hour and
30ish minutes
hi I get
it I don't get
it is that it down there how am I
supposed to get out of the traitor can't
wait to go to Trader
Jes is she a hot lady Trader
wrecked that would be Trader Jill
then oh oh my character is tired
sandwich murky water Rotting Flesh
trador wrecked cuz I'm going to get
wrecked
wrecked wreck lucky me oh it's not a
cute girl what do you mean myy no was
yeah it's not a cute girl at all I know
I was lied to I was
[Music]
scammed I'm as disappointed as you guys
are there was a beautiful
girl
oh wooden shovel he's kind of mean too
but you know yeah he just said he's
going to cut my God bapon
throat can I shoot
him no I think we need him I really want
to shoot very guy he's got a lot of
custom you got to keep in the Bulls oh
but he has he has so much stuff I guess
I can't shoot him yeah you can't steal
stuff either I
guess man how long does it take for me
to feel
full why not
much girl see she's not here though can
I can we at least loot his
house no we need him I think you could
try well what he doesn't have to know I
don't want to use the can food that's
actually important compared to Corn what
is that button on his overalls block
oh guess I'll make that's better bunch
of
fragments what does that say I got a
stone shovel don't worry about
it there is stuff you can loot they say
do we really want to loot the trader
though I mean make himad looks like he
could kill us looks like he's got three
shot guns oh actually there's a bunch of
stuff oh can we take his
corn
vad oh I found his bedro oh no he has a
land he has a land claim block I think a
a fetch Quest I hear that sound when you
try to destroy
something all right are we going to dig
a hole or something yeah I guess we dig
a
hole all right what does he want us to
dig I guess by the exclamation play huh
I have no idea yeah yeah oh I wonder
what we should do buried supplies let's
go Quest okay let's
go am I too warm or something I got a
fetch Quest I think did you guys get the
buried treasure Quest yeah we're going
there right now okay go yeah do that not
that I was paying attention but
yes there here's the fetch Quest it's
way over here actually it looks like
youa and them we're doing
it tier one
fet oh bued supplies
is nearby okay we're I'm going to go to
the berri supplies first cuz that me too
yeah cuz I already marked it wonder if
they're going to do fet fetch
Quest too bad we can't just take like uh
credit for their hole they already dug
it
can we see our quests on
our thingy oh yeah I dug I dug the hole
already
oh but I still have the quest to do I
think oh thank you for the redirect
hello
CeCe good night
CeCe yeah good night CeCe put your
bedroom next to mine I thought I thought
you put it next to FL different location
oh no I didn't she did it she put the
moves on me yeah wow sure makes doing
quests together kind of difficult but oh
well we'll just have to work together
kind
of wait do you guys have the ber
supplies in this area near the farm oh
you have it a different
spot I guess so it's the near the place
of the pigs okay yeah then I guess we
all have to do it
individually yeah sadly that's okay we
can still you know talk to each other if
you want talk you want me to socialize
Yeah well yeah socialization is good
even in the zombie apocalypse we need
each other I'm talking to people how do
you do that what if the used to what if
there's an awkward silence your parents
used to what oh they used to force me to
socialize I didn't like it oh
really yeah yeah they may be join like
freaking clubs every Sunday made
you
yeah oh I see you want to join us I
guess we can
mer all right I'm digging I'm digging
too I'm hungry oh my God eat
corn get the corn they're normally all
can't believe you don't have same like
progress if they're nearby when you
interact with a big yellow exclamation
point why did she do that to her
maybe she need to get put out of her
misery quests are Auto shared with party
members that doesn't seem right oh does
it yeah yeah yeah I can see your fetch
Quest so if you wait for us at the fetch
Quest we can start it all at once
together okay so let me just finish the
digging one first and then we'll come
over we fetch oh this is going to be
such a long digging Quest and I'm like
tired my character oh this one gives
water I'll eat it
now it was not enough water I need
rain treasure I'll just chill around
here go around where the fetch Quest
is okay
I wonder if we should just help each
other with our uh digging to make faster
if I finish first I'll come to you and
then we can go to Cali together that's
different digging Quest yeah I thought
we would be in this we would have the
same ones we're in the same party oh
shoot I hear
them I hear them but I can't see
them time for a
swim you are wet I see them
now actually there's a question mark
near a Tre oh I found the
treasure nice good and then I will come
to you
after oh I see the very first Quest
cannot be shared but after that the
quest can be
shared okay I think I did
it yes okay okay I think I need to dig
at this hidden section I'm going to go
back and turn it in cuz I'm cucumber and
then I will come to you
going to drown don't be silly wait
what's this
E I just I just pressed e oh now I dig
okay oh wow you're
far I
know let's get a little wood on the
side when you get here I would
appreciate you cut down the tree so I
can see [\h__\h]
okay thank you you're welcome
wow just like on
Minecraft stop congratulations just lock
in
my
sucker oh I'm a go I'm a
goat I'll wait at the yellow exclamation
point for them am I just like digging
this entire area like how deep was yours
bebs it wasn't it was pretty deep I'm
getting close apparently if if it says
if it says you're getting close uh dig
side
sideways
in
perception fortitude the out okay I'm go
agility oh I'm tired
FY what I so since you since
you have the fetch Quest already you
already took it for us right
yep since we're in the same party
so all we got to do is gather at the
same area where the golden exclamation
point is okay cool and then I won't
start it until you guys are here all
right I'm going to help sori first and
then we will come
over it told me I was close near a
treasure but my character's just way too
tired and I can't even drink glue oh no
not even
glue yeah did you do the thing as a kid
where you like poured glue all of your
hands and then spent like an hour
peeling it off because it was fun not
because it was fun but because I had to
do it yeah oh you had to do
it well I mean yeah if I used a lot of
glue and it got on my hands I had to
peel it off but you never like put it
glue on your hands on purpose to peel it
off cuz it not on purpose but it's so
fun it was going to happen it was going
to happen in arts and crafts
anyway sure enough oh oh good God my
character is just so done toed and
tired dang you need stamina do I drink
this murky water I guess I
will damage is pretty good o
yummy any cardio for the gear but you
still owe us it's cardio like stamina
that's just from yeah cardio is like
running and jumping and sprinting and
hopping and so stamina yes I need big
all right I can't afford it anyway
actually oh yeah I want more bullets so
gun give
me is in the outline Circle this
one I thought this was just like the
circle uh getting stuck oh it's where
it's within the
circle yeah I'm pretty sure I'm with in
the circle maybe I need to like dig
deeper I'm
hungry all
right oh fancy looks like a zombie jar
way yo are you here yeah
yo
yo H I'm out of stamina it is so
horrible gosh darn I'm actually I might
be stuck
I think I'm stuck
hello please help me my Brave One my
character is just such a
princess and you sure it's not in your
inventory if you press tab you don't see
a box in your inventory or anything I
still see the outline Circle so I don't
think it's here actually I think I'm
going beyond the outskirts from there so
you might go this way which way this way
okay uh whatever I'm looking oh I see it
I see it look look look you see it it's
right below oh thank
God oh I oh nice you found it oh a
sandwich and murky water oh huh yummy
huh what was that oh I think I nicked
your leg with the
shovel oh I see okay how do we
uh all right now
sir ooh so heroic hated that walls may
be faster actually you're right Dam why
is so fast
oh he had
who you can have it Bes is it's a guns
and for steel brass I don't have
space uh okay I'll take
it I will drink my murky water let's go
give me my denter 12 oh we got forg
steel out of that that's cool I got
shotgun diar yummy he's helping me all
right I guess I got to go back to the
Traer yeah and then we'll go go me
Callie come on zombie we can do it all
right I'm going to head there besbes all
right I'm going to break my diarrhea
sets in I'm going to break these Pebbles
real fast and then all right o breaking
your own Pebbles get
broken oh I see him hey there buddy I
guess this is what Faun was feeling she
was not feeling
fun feeling fun
owie owie
owie getting kind of cheesy now I got
28% of
diarrhea wait you act you actually
diarrhea is actually a
thing yeah Haven
yet you think it was just a myth a
legend
beeps yes
diarrhea I've never heard of that
before
dang she joking oh a
disent disent I've heard
of she you won't know if it's fun until
you try it so let's go find you some
food to give you some diarrhea I
guess oh
hello I should lead the all TR
oh he trir here's your darn
Quest oh that's a lot of zombos actually
let me lead them
away uh I think I better take a pistol I
meant I meant diarrhea in the game by
the way
I having to clarify I have I feel like I
have to clarify because for some reason
people actually believe that I did know
what diarrhea was but
okay wa what silly people silly all
right I can go to the fetch Quest now
okay let's go to the fetch Quest I
started the quest after this I'm going
rest that's the easiest way
there my headphones hurt
I still see your tier one fetch Quest
cie so I'm going to head over okay maybe
it was a different quest for some weird
reason that's odd we all get different
Quest oh I think SII accepted a
different Quest that's why it popped up
oh cuz it it shows up for everybody to
clear the area Quest yeah oh yeah that's
a that's a new one I just
got I based it on what was
closest understandable but I'm going to
go do the fetch Quest yep we're coming
thank you even fetching I don't know not
sure
yet oh no now I have the DI rizle too oh
not hey welcome to the Riz Club I just
wanted the Sham
sandwich well you got shammed it was a
sham you got sham wowed I feel
silly where you know what would be like
funny what
if all this time um our Discord was
muted for one of
us that would be pretty
silly I know it's going to happen
[Music]
now I am not shio
silly it is getting kind of Darker out
here huh oh dang R just killed
crony why does she keep doing that do
you think um probably like past memories
of being married I got Casino oh I got
an actual pistol
oo nice nice oo I got Stu that sandwich
begins at 22 that's very frightening
I'll open that
later can zombies drown what if we hide
out in the water until daytime I was
thinking that might be a good idea well
can they down they don't have
want oh
true well yeah but they might be slowed
down by the water and then we can kill
him from afar maybe oh yeah there's an
idea I wonder what happens if your your
diarrhea percentage is like super high
does it affect you or something I wonder
mine's going down slowly so yeah mine
too like I don't know how it affected
me yeah maybe it just like makes you
hungry or something like that maybe you
just feel the shame feel funny you
know oh this about toast share some of
our shaming them bio no thank you I do
not want but you're the jewel of emotion
so you have to feel our emotion of
shame
that I I feel I'm I'm empathic for you I
feel bad for you but I don't want oh you
feel bad you feel bad well I want to
feel your emotion not your not your
physical ailment that's not how it
works yo myy how did you get there did
you just swim yeah I swam across
dang look at you my little buff buff
girl buff shoty shy Master shy oh God
feeling fear feeling fear oh they're
coming out oh they're all here can't
swim well it's night time well like very
poorly
actually but zombies can in fact
swim yeah oh crap I think I my
drown uh I'm
good you'll be okay I'm thirsty that my
growing my
Tommy your
tummy my tummy go
go wow I guess it makes sense that you
can uh fall in the water when you are
out of
stamina let's see I have enough O2
[Music]
get my
rewards ooh I think my character is
about to crap
themselves
yeah wait don't do it yet I want to
see F that's up to my body I can't
control that be I want I want to see and
laugh at
you you know as the gym of emotions then
I'll throw all the the results at you oh
never mindess up
sure I don't know we got no no I'm good
I changed my
mind how
sweet yeah you can you can join too I
guess more you and I are suffering the
same issues you know I'll pass I'm okay
yeah I
see away foul
Beast yo why can't I SL swimming
there you don't think they can swim
right well I'm slowly swimming towards
them
there you know maybe they can hope I
don't
drown I they can
swim just slows them down a little bit
oh God yeah what's wrong where's a bunch
of zombies I really hope they can't
swim
uh
yeah oh wow this is like a big area
yeah now he's doomed to live at the
bottom of the lake but he's coming oh my
god oh
man does this place
close let me
in oh you can you have to press e oh
door your stamina goes down as you're in
the water oh I I have a bad feeling am I
in the right place oh good
God wait am I not in the right place so
where am I oh
[Music]
no oh well I guess if I die it doesn't
really matter too
quiet o everything's going
dark yeah oh no all right time to go
back in there oh no now I have diarrhe
yeah it's a pretty common
thing the
diaria
diiz
I here we go oh I have to I went to the
wrong place I am near you though what is
this I'm not far enough away to sneak
yet have you guys seen the video of the
Japanese Rob big S is going I have a bad
case of diarrhea I have a bad case of
diarrhea are you seeing that I have I
have not seen that okay I'll send it to
you guys later no I I don't really know
if I'm interested no it's it's
cute why you think they were made to say
that they're they they teach they teach
you English words through aerobic dance
and one of the useful English the most
useful English words is I have a bad
case of die
I don't usually tell people that how
often would you use that number one
number two yeah this is like your
introduction to people bebs oh hey oh
hey is this you hey anyway I might bring
some here it it's useful it's useful to
like tell someone that before you know
it happens just to give them a warning
you know right you don't want to just do
that and without any warning so
say yeah it's it's a big it's a big meme
it's a famous I'm not with the times
okay well I'm going to have to send it
to you guys later say I need a bathroom
quick that works or like I'm just going
to the restroom I don't even give them
details you know yeah going to the
restroom wait why should should we take
this Quest now like what's going on
actually waiting for B I'm
coming she's swimming in the water
swimming like a fish okay this is a huge
map but I mean good you know there one
me I like where is this like if you're
about to talk to someone here's some
tips that you could talk about like
giving topics and then you kind of just
crack under the pressure and say I'm
going into labor
what yeah yeah that's what happens when
you panic talking to
someone but you can do a U-turn and you
still bring back the conversation to the
original topic if you bring up like box
manufacturing what it's a box
manufacturer how to make a
box how do you make the box is the
thing I don't know but you got to think
outside the box are you okay so do I
just make stuff up like talk out of my
ass like oh here's how box yeah that's
what I do all the time
yeah I don't
think maybe I'll try it next time okay
try it right now
so you know cardboard boxes are crazy
because what are they even made of like
I know paper's made of trees but like
like cardboard how do they even make
that stuff you
know uh
uh-huh
oh I'm here by the way oh she's here
okay okay well we're about to go into
labor oh yeah I think I to spawn out of
nowhere hey I love up let's go level
Ranger Station Delta shall we start the
mission there's a lot of zombies need to
start the quest I like how there just a
Giant floating exclamation mark all
members are out of range here we go oh
uhoh oh there they are now what now what
oh they're behind us
what I did have very little Health oh
they're very
fast yeah they're quick
yeah
thankfully can't be
helped oh no I
level nice
job you shooting them yeah I'm shooting
them oh oh there's too many of
them okay how about I fight them this
was maybe not the best
idea uhoh H Okay C not working
however we can do it through Brute Force
oh yeah we can I've been waiting to use
the oh you can't escape either the band
stop bleeding I'm dying
bro I got num
nom okay I'm about to get Nom nomed uhoh
I just hope there's something behind
me I got num nomed and infected oh no
the
failed it failed that's what it said for
me we can fail a
quest I guess if we all
die oh man that's harsh that is Harsh
okay I do need to get my backpack back
he has loot though oh he has loot I'm
taking
it oh
boy dang I ran out of I ran out of board
so quickly there's so many of them let
me lead them away okay I'm out
I guess we got to go back and retake the
quest huh that's a
lot do B are so
teleporters all right how do you get
back o at least this time we can go back
together
zombies yeah let's go back
together yeah let's head back okay maybe
we can do a different Quest that's
closer yeah are you swimming beibs what
are you going to do I'm for some some
swimming where where are you my let's
swim together yeah I'm going back to oh
whoops they found me I see you getting
chased I'm right next to you they'll
never get
me let's go never get
you uh Quest fails for players as soon
as they die
okay what a [\h__\h] that's a little hard to
survive
though yeah well for now I guess let's
just take quests that are you know easy
not too tough and not too far away I
thought that was supposed to be a fetch
Quest by the way there is nothing
fetching about
that we were supposed to grab something
I
think I'll be okay don't worry about out
of stamina in the water I'm
fine I can handle yeah we're like
mermaid I'm hey there's a
zombie cool kill
it cool murder it immediately can you
build a bicycle not yet I think we need
to do a few more quests
okay I'm hugging the
shore the more quests that you do I
think the better Vehicles you can make
eventually oh really sh that's like a
tricycle they found me that's
rough are you yeah okay I found Callie I
lost
you it's okay I'm making my way towards
the thing anyway I'm hugging the uh the
islands
okay yeah we can still pretty much see
each other on the map so
yeah D I do not have a lot of bullets
left only two shots but they do damage
do you have a shotgun yeah I have
shotgun bullets for you you do yes my
hero my her
Academia am I over encumbered no I'm not
I'll read one of these wait uh come here
and take them cuz I'm over cucumber over
cucumber okay let me see if I can find
you oh there you are you're a cool
looking and cucumber oh thank you maybe
I need to give this to someone else here
you go I've already read it
so thank you wow bullets bullets do you
have any 9 mm at all let me see I
might people under bullets yeah I do I'm
F my arrows I'll drop and then here this
is also for you you might want it it's a
armor magine I already read it so it
doesn't do me any good
well if you you you know you can there's
multiple levels of it right oh really
but I Ed
it oh it's okay when I used it before
cuz I tried to use it again and it just
disappeared from my inventory and
nothing happened
so weird well we're swimming together
[Music]
I can't wait to not be sick anymore what
is that infernal noise it's a zombie
it's probably where zom zoms sounds like
a pig to be honest oink oink dang
multiple volumes the the zombies
feelings this Lake Vibe is very
spooky spook the right
way I am it's the cleric Beast
[Music]
it has it has that clicker sound and
like
the ow what it was behind me this whole
time
ow oh no blast
them oh it's one of oh ah it's
jumpy it's just peace for me I did find
a house nice but I'll probably die on
the way
there nice there's another one there's
another one another
wait should we just like stay at a house
or something the camp guy is going to be
close isn't he probably isn't so bad but
Quest at night is probably a
noo yeah well just like stay out
area oh yikes I'm
getting you're supposed to save people
not destroy
them oh yeah the nurses it's pretty rude
huh oh oh my God
jeez these things do not die oh I'm dead
oh
no don't eat her no don't eat my body oh
I didn't see her hell dwindle away I
killed it I killed it that's okay thank
you B then let it ruin your
body I am at the
traitor I want to wait here and check
this he's Clos it's night time after all
but yeah I mean it's 2: a.m. or
something um this is where I'm going to
go and uh end it for me okay so I hope
you guys have fun yeah I'll see you
tomorrow or whenever I play next heck
yeah see you next
time good
[Music]
night bye-bye
did you get your stuff back you head
toward the trader huh oh I was waiting
for you for your stuff oh thanks I'm all
good I'm good to go let's go good to
girl let's run it maybe after we get
back to the tra we can head back home so
I can start cooking corn for everybody
okay I really hope we can find a place
that's closer to the trader might be a
good idea at least build a bike or
something
oh yeah cuz she already left I think the
the quest failed that's okay a next time
next
time youring has disconnected from the
car why am I leaning like this am I
leaning to the side right now you're
leaning it's kind of
weird cuz I'm going to fall over or
something the world is getting all
spinny is it a bug oh I think you might
have got bitten by the the jumper thing
cuz it makes you it makes you
dizzy oh it's getting worse oh
boy thank you very much for the rir
shield hope you guys had
fun oh goodness I'm very
dizzy my inner ear ah oh not the inner
ear people can see like this I'm seeing
different dimensions I'm I'm losing
it oh shoot that's a bad time for a
zombie to see me what a nice morning
yeah the morning looks good yeah we have
a little more time to
prepare um we got to really fortify our
home I feel oh we're actually close by
everybody if you look on the map like
everybody's kind of close by the
trader yeah everybody's doing Trader
stuff it would
seem no which is
good and do a barrel roll what's
happening I'm just waiting it out I'm
waiting for it to stop do you have a
timer on
it no no there is no timer maybe that's
just you're sick
forever that would be really terrible
honestly I'm also one more time oh yeah
are you are you seeing this if this
number gets to 100% does that turn me
into a zombie maybe that is what number
I don't know what number you're talking
about I have like a icon and a
percentage and it's at 1% right
now oh I don't
know I'm not sure
actually the numbers what do they mean
are we sure this isn't just a bug you
guys oh I am here I am at the
trader okay
me
too it's a bug this is a bug for sure oh
God it's a feature I can help you with
the bug oh yeah how would that would you
kill me thank
you Pi up speo thank you Sor I Don't
Want to Waste My
Bullets appreciate
it put me out of my Mis oh thank God it
flipped oh thank God that was killing me
now bi killed me thank you B you're
welcome big up she's the bug
squasher thank you so much for squashing
the bugs you're welcome put away your
weapon let's see where on Earth is my
backpack oh there is get a new start oh
his his stuff is
open how do you see how much money we
have oh yeah we completed a quest before
right so we must have a little bit
I want the shotgun Messiah magazine
before the rush but it might be tough to
get all that money oh it's it's these
coin thingies I only have 10 dang it wow
that's rough he really does not pay a
lot of money
huh let's see would you want to do like
a clear zombies
one I I just took one this oh you took
one okay
cool you said he's going to cut my
throat I have no money all right well
let's do
this what the
start let's do
it if we're together we can surely get
him and I got my
gun they're going down I can't this guy
has zero there we
go there's Beau
let's do it I hope I can find more
shotgun shells before the rush
tomorrow are we going to the oh we're
it's at both at the same place okay cool
let's go let's go let's go it's really
not that far thankfully we should do
these closer Quests for sure
yeah did I spend my skill points mhm
I've been spending them I might have
like one over try and spend it again
okay I have a question for you yeah can
you tell me the entire history of
Warhammer lore right now no since you've
watched all of it impossible oh give me
give me a 30 second
summary okay um the year is 40 is 40,000
uhhuh um and and before that even before
30,000 there was this dude he's the
emperor okay and he's like the savior of
all mankind and stuff like that um and
then they Ed the emperor's DNA to make
like a bunch of other dudes called
primarch and they're like the emperor's
sons and then those primarch DNA I think
the genan seed or whatever is used to
make the Space Marines and then and then
some of the primarchs though they they
turn bad they like go bad because uh one
of the prim marks named Horus he gets
all corrupted by like like these chaos
gods and the emperor goes yo what what
what the f what the beep is wrong with
you Horus you are my favorite child and
Horus is like f you Dad um and so then
they fight um and stuff like that and
Horus nearly kills the emperor um but
then uh the emperor kind of like
sacrifices like All Flesh and stuff like
that to put a stop to Horus and then
disintegrates his Spirit um and so then
Horus is like Gone Forever he's super
dead like he's the most super dead he's
the most dead ever okay yeah and then
they put the emperor on a throne on a
Golden Throne like barely alive because
they need him for space travel so they
put him on The Golden Throne and he's a
Skeleton Man and they're keeping him
barely alive oh
boy do you guys want to you zombies want
to hear about the war hore I think they
do pretty much I'm new here I still
don't know much about the Warhammer lore
but I'm I'm I'm trying so so so horse is
dead dead but the emperor is like semi
dead now yeah I mean he's he's still
alive he's just a skele man you know
deteriorating and here's the crazy thing
they have to sacrifice a thousand living
Souls a day to keep him alive because
you know my space travel and stuff like
that that's beeping messed up yeah it's
crazy right but you know space travel is
real important to
him yeah and then uh the there are four
chaos gods and they're they're insane
they're like super crazy dudes and there
are all these other is that
heresy yes yes anything that has to do
with with chaos Gods just don't mess
with them or else lest you become a
heretic
ah
yeah a thousand psychers yes it's the
psychers specifically it's the psychic
ones that have the brain power they big
brains oh wow I really I really can't
believe I missed that thank you why why
can't they just get a new emperor for
space travel why it seems like it seems
like a lot of high maintenance to kill a
thousand people a day he's
special he's special special
yes we love the emperor don't speak such
heresy no B that's
heresy he's also crazy powerful uh oh
here come more but he's dead isn't he no
he's not really dead he's he's alive but
just barely alive is the problem oh he's
like alive enough to do the space travel
and such wow really maybe if I hit him
in the head he could have
died are you kidding me I need help C
your aim this is why I hate shooting
zombies cuz they they move so
erratically you lead your
shots oh you got a shotgun all you got
to do is get close
all right I got one of them he's
dead get that guy yeah I think we're
really close I think it's in here oh we
did it we did it we're done just got to
parkour
oh ooh nice popping pills sealed
shipping crate well I got a medical
journal and painkillers and
Alam ooh I found hobo stew shotgun
Messiah Volume
7 here's the 9 M
mm hold up here's some shotgun shells
thank
you I'm going to read shotgun Messiah
can we break this
crate there might be stuff in
here yay
shotgun let's see
uh just watch you swing in that thing oh
search lab equipment oh it's just yucky
paper and Stu and such oh we need we
need the
pool oh is that the quest that's for uh
that's for the thing to collect water oh
true for the water catcher yeah all
right I guess we completed the quest we
can go back now okay how do we go out
maybe we just follow the oh that's a
really good question maybe we should
let's just go back where we came
okay I think that's going to be the best
Better Way all right par parkour
Hardcore Parkour okay continuing okay
Emperor is semi alive but they got to
keep him alive yeah he's a skelan so a
thousand psychers bioo a thousand and
those are people that are tapped into
the warp the warp is like this this it's
basically space hell it's kind of like
um an astral plane sort of where like
all these horrific wa what's demons
they're these they're psychic people
that like tap into the warp with their
powers and stuff I don't know details
but they're connected to the warp you
know they're they're super like cool
psychics and yeah they're connected to
space hell and their minds their brains
they connected to the space hell space
Wizards okay space Wizards yeah yeah
space Wizards and then they sacrifice a
thousand of them a day bi boo a thousand
did we not start the quest no we did I
got the quest is done for me oh maybe
maybe we have to start your class we can
do it again right yeah more money not
available until 852 oh okay let's turn
it in then 852 oh yeah you're right
let's let's just go back I don't want to
do that Quest again let's do some new
quests
yeah all right so War people 10,000 day
what happens when they run out of War
people cuz that's a lot of War people
they don't they don't run out of them
how they keep making them I don't know
de beats can you guys answer are they
like breeding psychers and Mass to
sacrifice to the the emperor cuz I feel
like that's something they do in the
Warhammer
Universe I feel like they would breed
psychers just to sacrifice to the
emperor that would be the smart thing to
do they have millions of plets of Pyers
there are trillions in the Galaxy but
but that's a lot of
day yeah mankind has a lot of people but
but that's a lot of hum millions of
Worlds bbo millions millions of Worlds
the Imperium of man humans are in the TR
trillion bajillion it's the year 40K
okay bajillion trillion people poor
people a day travel beo space travel you
have to travel in space but like what if
you're picked because then then you just
get how do they pick
them I'm not really sure how they picked
them but you know you should be honored
to serve the emperor in such a way
snipers are rare among the populist
though yeah see here's the thing though
bi the emperor dies no more warp travel
no more no more fast space travel and
you know what that means all the planets
that have that have people and different
like things and beings on them all
across the Galaxy gajillion trillion
light years away from each other they
get cut off from each other they become
barbarians so but that's still the price
of people oh look it's
crony I mean yeah but you sacrifice a
thousand of people a day so that
trillions upon trillions can continue
living every
day she's been fully indoctrinated look
I'm just I'm just telling the
facts can I get my reward please oh
choose one I'll take the crap
thing I don't really like any of these
rewards to be I'd rather get money do
you want to go say say hi to Cony and R
and see what they're up to maybe we can
all together yeah let's go hang with
them
okay oh wow that f word was real big
when he said that what let's GOP in
their VC
okay
hello hello hello are you CL
in yeah you want to CL together yeah
yeah yeah let
Co he says he doesn't have any any
quests right now though oh it it says
the same for me but then I joined uh
like in the crony's party shows the
quest in my list as well so maybe if we
make one
party oh you can share the quest I yeah
yeah yeah let's do it wo okay I'm going
to invite you
then
cool
[Music]
uh and
mor okay I send invites okay
okay
um I have to leave the party first uh
can you invite me one more time of
course oh God it's so
expensive okay I'm in Mar I think you
have to leave your party as well to to
leave it yeah yeah okay how do you
leave uh
so click on the party icon and try to
click on leave okay oh I have on players
oh no I'm not in a party right now oh
let me turn invite I'm make you an offer
you can't refuse well don't just stand
there I got I got a quest just now as
well oh yeah Quest started yeah Quest
started okay okay I see them now
[Music]
mhm yeah if you click on your quest list
you're going to see like everyone's
Quest
okay why won't he let me see his
inventory are you glitched again don't
even know why I open I don't know what's
going on that's fine let's make more
money together and then maybe I'll try
and buy something okay y we got about 30
minutes after all so let's do something
hi
gather
okay GA shall we we shall ladies ladies
let's go
uzoo guess we're going this
way is this a clear Mission we're going
to kill
zombies heck yeah I love that oh yeah I
finally found a cooking grill so I can
make grilled corn so what is this like
Tick Tock boom
effect I don't know what you're talking
about you hear something
strange wait uh myy can you kill me
first because I have very little health
and I'll do it I'll do it I'll do it all
right you sound oddly excited about that
she's a murderous type tell you oh can
you kill me actually I'm also low okay
yeah I'll do it thank
you awesome this is why Friendly Fire is
on
Friends very helpful sharing is caring
sharing is caring you don't need to kill
me though I'm good I'm good really yeah
I'm good although I could be at full
health think about
it yeah you know you could be at 100
HP yeah you know go ahead take me out
grony really what what's your what's
your health right now
68 okay yeah 69 thank
you ah my ladies I can always trust them
I can always count on
them I'm helping understand why you guys
were killing each other it all makes
sense
now yeah yeah we were doing it out of
Good Intentions oh wow sweet what a what
a kind world we live
in all righty on my way
back yay oh are you guys doing a little
handstands together making only human
tone it's very cool yeah join oh
maybe I can join it's a little difficult
with three
people but I bet it's possible oh to
jump on me and then you jump on people
yeah oh yeah oh okay here we go oh that
was an awesome idea now look we're
three can I can I jump with you guys on
can
you oh wait wait let let me try
Okay no no look at us effing around when
we have a
fre can't be helped can't be
helped also oh there's apparently an exp
debt from dying
actually oh what does that mean pretty
sure that you have to get a certain
amount of exp Before You Can level up
again but I don't know if they took that
off for our
server H I hope so we'll have to
see they might not have only after level
six okay yeah be careful after level six
you take a penalty okay it's okay you
lose X we level three yeah we'll be fine
wait how can I check my level uh if you
press Tab and go to your character oh
okay thank
you all right we're
here we're here clear yes to the mines
the mushroom Mining Company my gun ready
I'm is low for some
reason
okay oh we here oh yes ladies I'm ready
I'm ready oh yeah okay I'm
ready I too am ready let's
go let's
go let
go happen e it's like a blood big blood
bag firsty yeah it's like gushers wa
didn't we just do this one B yeah we did
just do this one but I guess it we F oh
be careful be
careful what's
up yeah killing zomie my favorite
SP yeah hell yeah be careful to don't
die because I think you're going to fail
the quest if you don't die don't Quest
is very bad ow oh nice one okay oh
there's still another one
nice yeah good job
ladies y teamwork yeah what the heck
where do we go next down
here bble knows the
way oh it's
crawling o
mushrooms oh my oh no I need to repair
my by Bon stick hold up I love
mushrooms ah
oh what oh
yikes good job
team lots of shies around
here can we
Harvest oh yeah
you uh oh here's another
boy another boy Mario actually doesn't
like mushrooms or saying
anyway wa what are you talking about oh
no nothing nothing
wait Mario is in Mario the guy doesn't
like mushrooms need
to back Mario doesn't like mushrooms oh
I mean I guess that makes sense because
he keeps like killing the people yeah it
says so in the Mario movie
yeah Mi
sense
ow oh Callie I'm going to drop some
shotgun parts for you you can have them
here you go really thank you booo
yeah man that was rude te we can help
each other with the things that we all
want to individually sell at you know
yeah oh I guess we can go up from
here wait what wait what where are you
guys there's a ladder there's a ladder
oh wait oh those mushrooms for our Roto
B
okay uh-oh
oh
sorry a little bit of Friendly Fire oh
got do we got to do it's okay my
vision's blurry oh I'm losing blood
alive wait what the heck I I sorry my my
knife makes people
[Music]
bleed get that I got an achievement for
killing 10
zombies nice yay goodies ladies wait
wait for me
a splint
o I don't think there oh we got to
destroy this one this one gives you
Goods you think so yeah this one you got
to break
it ni motor to
Parts pears oh there's a lot of shotgun
ammo here call if you want to look in
the boxes oh yes thank you what these do
armor parts I'll just keep collecting
them
thank you
y good job everybody we completed the
quest
nice ow oopsies hurt other
ladies I'm on my last leg oh
God it's okay we'll be fine there should
be no zombies on the way out it's not
night time yet or even close so we'll be
okay yay please I want to go down the
hole okay there we go nice job ladies
first okay wow I'm a
[Music]
lady that's
right just ignore my giant beard and
bald
head it's just a look right now you know
it's the highest fashion at this moment
for a high class
lady now let's go get some money let's
go get our Awards yeah I I want to get
the I want to I hope I can get the
magazin to learn the workbench work
station oh yeah that' be very
useful I'm looking for it maybe the
reason I can't accept any more quests is
because I already accepted this Quest
yeah you're on you're on a quest already
probably I don't know how to no I didn't
got a quest
either I don't know why well it says
return to traitor now yeah it says to go
to the Traer so let's go why is it still
exclamation mark yeah it's but I think
we did the the quest anyway let's go to
the Traer yeah let's just go back trust
the
process yeah yeah yeah
yeah it's cool it's cool place of
interest is on cool down oh top right
okay gotcha daily limits to Quest oh
a a I see can't have us getting too
strong too
fast guess it makes sense o look all the
wood we got to really fortify our base
tomorrow before the rush that's going to
be the biggest thing we got to do I
think the first thing I'm going to do
tomorrow is just cook a bunch of corn so
we just have a big supply of food oh
yeah do you have any recommendations of
what to do
tomorrow yeah so there's going to be a
rush I think that we need to stay at the
house that we've already established and
fortify it so try and protected as much
as we can gather as much ammo as
possible and pray we don't
die and tomorrow it starts an hour
earlier correct yes okay just make okay
okay thank you for letting me know
problem Oh an hour early I thought it
was an hour
later no it's an hour earlier so that uh
Kiwa and Cecilia can join a little
easier you can join whenever you want
it's just that's when the server will
open okie dokie okay okay I just
wiring wow it's really not a lot of
stuff in here tools digest what's
that got harvesting tool yeah I need
that do we
do I can't pick another quest with at
the clear zombie maybe or fetch what is
fetch I don't know we tried do fetch but
we died before we could figure out what
oh okay I do clear zombie now this is
all I canare water cooler ooh large
pipes Plumbing fixtures appliances oo a
real stove to cook on maybe
someday okay might be nice okay nice get
a
beer
okay I'm going to hold on to my
money there's nothing I want right now
already have all this stuffff take a
[\h__\h] look wow he cursed out yeah he's
really
mean you say that so
casually yeah he's just a mean
guy s off shotgun mod schematic that'd
be really
awesome well need a little more
money who wanted to be a farmer you want
to be a farmer cie yeah oh right here
I'm dropping this for you oh thank you
what's
that oh a farming book
oh yay I've unlocked tier one cotton we
can grow
cotton stone tools quality
too
oh three out of
20 yay oh
my C paint br
nice I got two points
available
lucky lter is
good okay I'll get this one
then o Harvest more crops that's
big this is also big pain
tolerance those
don't need them now this is also
big you hungry or
something pack mu n I'm just going to
make
pockets all right that's nice skills Yay
good job do we have time for another
quest uh what time what time is it close
and a little over 15 minutes I think we
can do it the we take too long yeah
yeah I just can't I can't collect any
more quests sadly oh I have another
Quest okay let's do
yours it's
uh to to
clear you want to follow me okay do okay
let's go let's go it's not too far right
no it's like 600 me away that's not bad
yeah all right let's do
it yes for survival
what kind of weapons are you guys using
I'm using the bow I like it oh do you
want bow crafting books I have yes if
you have it I like both I forgive I
forgive you for
being here you go very nice of you thank
you's got she's really Scavenging she's
got all the goodies yeah I'm picking I'm
picking the crafting books as
rewards so we can up our
skills smart
can someone kill me oh yes sure i' love
you're right I live B yeah no I'm
not I will give you an honorable death
oh wait a gun would be a waste of ammo
okay good
point nice sick thank
you I'd love to be able to punch zombies
in the face yeah yeah but I'm more of
like a club girl more of a shotgun
girl what's wrong with archers well when
you're far away and you're trying to
attack them and they shoot you with
arrows and then all their dudes fly
forward with big swords and there's a
freaking archer in the back it's like
you got to aim for the Archer first you
know I don't like I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm just really not an arer fan oh but B
look I like archers why yeah yeah you
play a game and an Archer is like do I
have Amo oh and they're in the way back
of the pack and they send all their
buddies forward with their swords you're
cool with
that yeah as long as I'm on you know
their side oh well yeah if we're on the
same side that's one thing
but isn't this the same one we just did
is it is
it yeah is it
oh or is it move further that
way out of range and we fail that's not
true they're all right here but let's go
toward the one the one the one the ra ra
ra has
uh is is a different place looks like on
M yeah follow me girls follow me okay
you think we can eliminate the stuff in
there could look at that cool
try goodies are in
there oh this would be a nice place
there's no nothing there's nothing here
wait wait for me I'm a little bit behind
it's okay I'm behind you ignore the
trailer the trailer doesn't matter I'm
also behind oh yeah it's here it's here
I think we're all behind right now I'm
over cucumber so I might be a little
slower that's okay we got to pocket wait
no the quest is actually over
here right yeah my quest is over here
exclamation point right it's over
there what
follow
me wait no I'm in the wrong group what
the
heck it's another ear oh yeah these are
different people yeah I was like yeah
they all look the same I was
confused oh I probably made it there I'm
going to wait here for you guys where
are you guys at time oh
uh over here this way this way yeah yeah
yeah
where is this
way who else is Kiara okay and is FAA
with them I
think I wait for you guys here yeah
we're just chilling here all good okay
they fell for the same group that's
really funny oh that's why they said
hies you got come to some with other
people so silly ah
that's
okay eye out for bird nest for Mass
producing arrows oh yeah if you like if
you like to shoot uh arrows as an Archer
just keep your eye open for for bird
nests cuz they've got all the fathers
yeah yeah I got all the Fe yeah yeah
yeah I will take any 9
mm bullet I will take all your shotgun
shells guy
oh this should be pretty easy The Smoke
House we got to smoke them out okay oh
yeah ready I'm get him in the head this
time I promise guys I promise let's
smoke them
yep oh yeah I think we're all here I
think yeah I'm I'm I'm waiting
here are you wait where are you oh there
you are we're up here there we go Quest
marks right here yes exactly do it
yay maybe we got to get him to get
angry by walking around getting all up
in their stuff up in their Turf
maybe
ooh stay within the area oh there we go
they they're the red points on the map
I'll take everything and show
you there's zombie Birds oh okay oh boy
hello
grandpa yeah head shot drank oh boy oh
not the birds we need to get the ammo
okay nice o what's
this o scary
nice there should be another yeah
there's there's one in the tent I
think oh this one maybe oh this one yeah
yeah this guy this guy ammo pile pipe
shot I found some 99 mm bullets people
give you thank you B which I uh sorry
which which weapons are you using I'm
using pistol so I need 9 mm okay if I
find I'll give you that's I have bullet
K casing biu I found home cooking weekly
oh that would be
useful ooh
is also a five shotgun here if you guys
want I already have one so I'm good but
thank you let me dump some
trash hobo St okay we're done with the
quest by the way yeah
vles throw that throw that oh hey B boo
where are you I'm behind you okay okay
right here so you don't get confused
with the other items this is for you uh
let's
see here's cooking thank you bones
cookie harvesting
more I can make I can make tea now we
can have a te yay te like Wasteland
Treasures volume
S I don't really know I think it's about
constructing things does anybody like
building
stuff building stuff
any Builders
here shot level two oh wait what is it a
better one oh we get honey from this
this is awesome a where by chance did
you find the shotgun from
before from the quest oh did you get it
as a reward yeah you get to choose which
weapon you get to have oh heck yeah
there is a pipe shotgun in
here oh where'd you find it Bab here in
the
tent yeah on this armor pile or yeah
ammo pile is it level two it is level
two oh that
then is
that
repair there we go wow I didn't know
there were different
levels interesting a okay well we'll
hold on the shotgun so we can give them
to maybe people that don't have weapons
tomorrow during the big ring yeah yeah a
good idea let's see if we can clear this
uh Quest back to the
trader yeah let's go back to the trader
okay good job team we did it we saved
jobob yay
[Applause]
yay
y find a more reliable way to get ammo
though for sure yipp yeah if we can
craft it that would be good oh there a
recip be
somewhere I think you can CRA you just
got to find the magazine for the
specific type of
[Music]
ammo y it' be nice to be able to have a
forge yeah yeah maybe we can build one
though there should be some time maybe
tomorrow oh apparently you make shotgun
ammo with paper so I guess cie collect
paper dang it I didn't know that I just
threw some paper out of my inventory
dang it
oh well we'll get him next
time oh we have some paper like at the
main base oh yeah yeah oh paper and what
else I wonder maybe we need the recipe
for
it
yeah I wonder like if there is a fastest
way to uh Craft um sorry to raise your
points for the skill tree like maybe
farming zombies is a good way that
that's to level up your stats stats but
like for like skills like
crafting um and unlocking crafting like
recipes that's
magazines yeah what about um the
challenges though the daily challenges
or not daily challenges not dailies but
if you press y all those challenges if
you complete them you also get exp for
your skill
trees well spamming spamming these
quests seem good too because these these
quests have uh magazines as
rewards
yeah quests are the best that's the
that's the thing to remember is quests
are the
best they very funny to do with friends
by the way like I think doing quests
with part is way easier and fun yeah way
easier fun way easier to level up I
think
gunpowder I'm finally here
yeah tra taking a
look what you got big hitters I could
use that for my club wielding I want
magazines they could give to me okay so
I got
gunpowder I got gunpowder I got we're
going to have paper eventually
corn he has
pets that be good nerd
outfit
yeah let's
see get the job
done interested in shotgun oh I'm level
four y does anybody here needs bullet
casing this definitely give you diarrhea
not yet but I feel like we'll need it if
we were to craft
ammo yeah I'm going to get some bandages
I got tomorrow cooking weekly cooking
magazine B Bo if you need oh
okay I drop it here see I wanted to give
him a
present you're going to give him a
present I know that guy sucks
I I met I met the other
Squad oh but I think they're a little
bit weary of me because I pointed guns
out though
understandable do you have
any I'm getting lots of lots of ammo
stuff I wonder when we can make ammo
though that's going to be big yeah
that'll change the game did you drop the
thing oh I see yeah I see here one of
them is just trash so don't take it
don't it I'll take bullet casing just in
case it can be used to make bullet oh
yeah yeah I have the inventory full
that's why I had to put it
there Place good job everyone today
yeah only four minutes left but good job
everybody
yeah so
good
woohoo sell that nice getting some good
money PGE PGE PGE PGE PGE very excited
to continue playing with you guys
yeah well I'll see I'll see I'll catch
you guys on the flip side then I got you
tomorrow see you guys tomorrow okay see
you guys tomorrow see you guys
tomorrow
everye
bye byebye
[Music]
all right hold on do I have a scene did
I I I didn't prepare a scene for
us
so do I have a
scene is this the correct scene let's
find
out ooh
[Music]
oh my gosh it worked you guys are gone
though okay come
back well that was
[Music]
fun welcome
hold on let me put the
game yeah that was a fun game fun with
friends
very lots of lots of violence but also
kind of laidback
sucessful ready for collab in 6 hours oh
yes so I have a collab with ra tonight
at
um
I 4 4: a.m.
sometime this morning I have a I have a
clab with
ra Monster Hunter yes we're Monster
Hunter I'm not going to have a POV
because it's just old Quest I'm just
helping her with her her Quest and
teaching her the ways of the monster
hunter so I'm not going to have a POV
I'm just going to be around oh but yeah
so you check out her stream I'll be
there we're we're training her with
training for a um Monster Hunter
mhm but yeah that was fun I guess I'll
be playing more again
tomorrow probably uh I'll probably be on
when
the server starts till like 5:00
p.m. mom
there's going to be a big what they say
hoard thing that happens like an event
or something like that so we got to
prepare for the hord when will you sleep
I will sleep between now well after
after we chat a little bit what you
don't want to talk with me you just want
me go straight bed you you don't want to
hang
out this week this week is going to be a
lot of collabs we we got a we got a
precious B
time here no go wait what what you want
me to go to sleep but wa you don't want
to you don't want to chill you don't
want to talk you don't want to talk
about my
bag I wanted to talk about my bag you
saw my you saw my bag today I wanted to
talk about it
we are to talk about
fashion and
stuff what's in your
[Music]
bag okay okay
wa wa wait where's the
bag okay so if you guys didn't know uh
Kiara Kiara I need to talk about the
tide po thing that's what I want to talk
about specifically the tide not tide pod
the Tide pen thing okay why is everyone
surprised that I carry around a Tide pen
huh oh if you didn't know Kiwa did does
a segment called Hollow bags and we send
her pictures of of our bags uh to her
right and so you saw my bag there hold
on I'm trying to find the picture that I
sent
I talk I need I need to talk about the
the
Ty cuz apparently that's weird what
what's weird about
having wanting your clothes to be clean
okay especially oh so what a Tide pen is
it's a little it's a little pen that if
you have a stain you can use the pen to
like you know take the stain out
and
um I like it
because if I you know
if I ever like go out to eat or
something like
that um I'm usually getting the spicy
food on the menu I'm not a Messy eater
what's wait what's wrong with having
something just in case you guys make it
seem like I'm using the Tide pen every
meal one it's just it's a just in case
sort of thing two haven't you ever like
had like a bowl of ramen and then plop
you know just a tiny tiny Speck of soup
gets on your clothing just because it
just happens sometimes you know it's
like a plop a tiny a tiny splash of
spice well maybe you're not eating spicy
food okay but that happens like a tiny
Speck like a tiny little plop of of
thingy of soup or broth or like hot
spicy oil gets on your sleeve or your
clothes how did that even happen okay if
you eat Chopsticks like if you're eating
like Ramen with chopsticks like there's
always a
splash
of sometimes like it can actually
accidentally Splash cuz you know you
it's just on the Chopstick or something
like that or even if like soup on a
spoon it's PL
right but anyway first of all I am
passionate about my fashion and I want
my fashion spotless it bothers me if I
have even a little speck on my on my
fashion okay so that's that's one thing
is you know I paid money for my cute
clothes and I like wearing cute clothes
so I am going to have a tie pen just in
case I get anything on my clothes cuz
yeah I can wait I can wait to go home to
clean it up but
it's going to be there the speck and I'm
going to be reminded of it also boom
here's the
oh that's
big okay here is my
bag I'll put it like right here for
now here's here's my bag okay right so
yes one I'm not using it for every meal
it's just a good thing to have in just
in case just like a a
Tide
pen just in case you have a stain on
your clothes okay like just in case and
it's not just for food too right like
what if I accidentally
trip and I get a little bit of dirt on
my clothes because I tripped that's a
POS
ability and and
uh
yeah also I started carrying the Tide
pen
specifically when I was in Japan I think
I was I think I said I was only going to
tell my pre chat this so I guess I won't
say who it is but I
specifically
carried the Tide pen in Japan not for
myself it was for somebody else that I
was hanging out with
in I won't say who it is because that
was for pre chat but
yeah yeah so I I didn't even start
caring it carrying the the tie the tie
pen I I keep trying to say tiod but tie
pen in my in my person in Japan in my
bag for me it was for someone else
because somebody else stains their
clothes way more than I do I I look over
and they're like
a stained again so okay
and it is true that I am kind of
clumsy cuz I
know someone saw me drop my ice cream
and stuff like that but I'm also very
clean as well my
clothes I spend money for my clothes I'm
going to keep them clean okay so there
is a tide tide pen explanation well I
don't know why you thought that I was
using it after every meal it's just a
nice thing to have just in case next
time you have a stain on your shirt and
you can't immediately take care of
it I'll laugh at you yeah just because
you're not prepared I'm prepared
okay I'm prepared
um
yeah and then wired oh yeah let me
explain the wired earbuds thing okay let
me let me expl explain the wir earbuds
thing I've never
owned airpods because I always
thought they were
for rich people and I never felt boozy
enough to be able to buy airpods so I'm
still on that wired ear blood
experience I always thought airpod do
something like
boozy
boozy you know High classy people owned
them so like I never felt like that so I
was like okay it's just me and these
wired earbuds the reason why I use the
Apple ones though is because this is the
only shape that like fits in my ear the
other earbuds like the ones with like
the suction thingy or or something they
fall out of my ears cuz my ears are too
small these are the only shape that will
stay in my ear yeah the other brands
they just poop pop out of my ear
yeah so that's why I use I use this
brand
uhhuh uh and then what
else um the
pens who knows when you need a pen
I love I love one I love mie pens I love
muchi pens um they're my they're my
favorite like I love myti pens so much
that's the brand of pens but they just
write so good and who knows when you
need when you need a pen for something
so I always carry a pen pens just in
case
uh-huh
um yeah to kill someone with who knows
but yeah I do I do really like mui brand
uh pant they're always
good so yeah who knows who knows
whenever you need to write something
what else do you need an explanation for
um well we'll just go through
them oh yeah my
phone
um see I didn't I didn't know when she
asked that I wasn't supposed to
like say
who or I wasn't supposed to be not
obvious at I didn't know it was a
guessing sort of thing I just thought
she was reviewing bags oh hi hi K we're
talking about my
bag I we're talking about my bag and
explaining Tide pen Tide pen is
good it's very handy it works very well
yes tight pant Ty pens I recommend them
just to have handy just in Cas neat yeah
they're very
neat all right anyway what was it say I
didn't know that that like I wasn't
supposed to be that obvious with um I
thought I just thought she was going to
reveal my bag but I was very excited I
was very very excited when uh Ki asked
about the bag thing cuz I'm like yes I'm
very proud of my
bag
because and stu oh wait what you say
it's okay yours was way less obvious
than some others except for the phone
he um well once you got to the DLC part
then it's pretty obvious I mean the the
Pokemon isn't as obvious because a lot
of people like Pokemon but then once you
see the DMC it's
like
yeah Android or
iPhone um I I used to be Android
but honestly iPhone so only cuz of V
tubic that's why I have an iPhone
because Hollow live
yeah all
so work related
mhm also the camera is pretty good on
the iPhone
but I used to be I used to be more of an
Android person though but I I uh I am
also the type of person who will use a
phone to its death like I do not get a
new phone every year I just am given a
phone and I will use it until it cannot
be usable anymore and then I will
finally upgrade yeah
that's that's what's been happening with
my iPad right now my iPad is on its last
legs where it'll just randomly
restart um and it's very very annoying
because I'll be in the middle of like
drawing or something and it'll just
randomly restart and then I'll have to
wait for it to restart and then I start
drawing again and then it restarts and
then I lose my progress and then it
restarts um and I should really get a
new iPad Pad but I'm just like waiting
for it to die die to get a new
one no it's not a charging problem it's
not a charging problem it's a I don't I
think it's like the battery of the
iPad's broken or something like
that
anyway uh what else oh so the little
gotta thing is a little gotta gotcha
that I got for Shi um and I was supposed
to give it to her during breaking
Dimensions but I forgot it so now I will
just keep it in my bag
forever
yeah if if you see in the bottom here
got the gift for
Seine holding until I see her cuz I was
supposed to give it to her during Bak
Dimensions but I
forgot so I will just keep it in my bag
forever until the next time I see her
maybe when we watch Sonic movie I'll be
able to I'll be able to get it
um oh no the source oh yeah there's my
card holder um I really like card
holders because I don't like go going in
my
bag okay I don't okay when you're buying
something I hate the awkward feeling of
like rumaging through your bag to like
get your wallet and your phone and stuff
so I like card holders because I will
just have it around my wrist at all
times um so I don't have to do
that so I have my phone on my wrist and
I have my card holder on my wrist
always instead of just having in my bag
so that way
um that way I don't have to have that
awkward moment where I'm screaming
through my
bag yeah scre SC rumaging through my bag
to like get the get the wall out cuz
that's
awkward yeah I I equipped my stuff so
well now if if I go back to Japan no I'm
probably going to get a new card holder
cuz it stays on My Wrist all the time so
then if anybody has seen this it's going
to be pretty obvious what is on my wrist
[Music]
uh but anyway yeah there's the dragon
this is the special limited
edition strawberry dragon that I got
that I was giving away to people this is
the special this is the secret um with
the strawberry cake on it they're coming
out with more they're coming out with
more colors and more versions of this
gotcha so I have to I have to either
like go back St or beg Dam tan to empty
out the machine for me but if if I can't
if I can't
yeah but card holder is nice because um
if you are in Japan you have a you have
a train card like a sua I have a sua
card so you can just put the sua card in
there and then looking at that gives me
so much memories yeah kind K saw saw
this stuff in person Hi
Kyla you you put the you put the sua
card in the card holder and you tap the
card holder to the the sensor and it'll
just go through it because the sensor is
powerful enough so you don't have to
take the card out so you can just keep
the the the train card in the in the
card holder it's nice
yeah B bum
it's very convenient so I really I like
card holders um for like cash and stuff
I put it in the in the v
pouch the the the V pouch the V pouch is
for I regret that I did yeah she was she
was she was looking at this she was
looking Kyla was looking at my my card
holder and she was like ah very
efficient law I need one law
ah very so so so
efficient why I want but then she never
bought one maybe we went to a we didn't
we go to a Pokmon Center but the line
was too long or something like that so
she didn't end up buying it yeah now you
regret it huh you should have just
bought one you should just now you
regret
it
dollar ly too long anyway oh so my
change my change and coins go in the v
Pou and then the stuff like uh the Tide
pen and the and the lip stuff and the
random pens they go in the Virgil Pou
yeah so I have two pouches to so the
miscellaneous stuff is in the viral
pouch and then the coin pouch is in the
v pouch yeah for money
uhhuh I got these at the at the Capcom
Cafe it says it right there but when
they were doing the the DMC
collab
um I was
like and then it I also bought this
microfiber cloth thing but I will never
I will
never I will never use it because it's
folded too nicely and I know if I open
it and use it I will never be able to
fold it
back
um I will never be able to fold it back
to the Perfection that it was folded in
so I just keep it in case I need it in
case of like a super emergency but I
don't think I'll ever use it
um and then lip
stuff no one wants dry lips Okay so the
the the bees the birs bees one is for is
for hydration the I forget what the
brand is I have to look at the back but
the the one on the right is for for a
cute collar and the one in the middle is
for strawberry
scent yeah so that's that's what so the
one on the left is is is for hydration
the one on the right is for nice col
color and the center one is to smell
like strawberries
mhm and then this Pokemon pocket mirror
cuz you know just in case you know
especially after you eat a meal you
don't want to be like oh you got a crumb
on your cheek or you know check
something like you got an eyelash in
your
eye got to make sure that you get it out
who knows when you need it I've never
actually even needed to use the pocket
mirror but I just keep it in there just
in case something like that
um yeah I'm more girly than you thought
huh
you what did you wait how come you don't
think I'm girly
huh I think I am a good combination
of girly and nerdy because I got the
cute girly stuff but I also got the
subtle nerdy stuff like the Pokemon and
the DMC so it's like a combination of
both subtle okay it's not that subtle
but you
know it the funny thing the funny thing
is to you should see my actual bag bag I
didn't show my actual bag bag because I
actually use my bag bag but my actual
bag bag is like very cutesy very very
pink
um it's very it's very cute it's a
little bit similar to to no's bag if you
saw no's bag
um we
have a similar looking
bag but it's cute but then it also has
like a the
The Virgil charm on
it I think I showed the the charm on T
the one that's me and Kyla are matching
with the one that me and Kyla I gave
Kyle and nuro and I have the first one
so it's just this cute pink
bag that's so cute and then boom there's
a Virgil charm on it that's so that's so
that is that is me and nutshell cute
girly but also nerd nerdy I guess I
think it en encompasses
me very well but I like fashion and
stuff so I really I like talking
about my bag and what's in it
and but yeah it's a combination It's a
combination but haha haha you didn't
what you didn't think I was is that
girly but I like girly stuff
too
yeah but you you expected it did you
guys expect it I know I saw a lot of
comments of people being surprised
though where's the katana it doesn't fit
doesn't fit in the bag unfortunately but
Katana is too big I have to wear it at
the hip you know I have to wear it at
the hip not not in my bag oh
well I have a feeling where how I talk
about how I dress yeah I dress very
cutely really
dresses totally my
thing my w don't my ward job is mainly
black though black black dresses with
white
accents is mostly I do have I do have
some pastel so I have some like pastel
pink pastel
blue and
uh I have some dark red black and red
black and purple purle black and
white yeah but my favorite my favorite
clothes
are majority black with white accents I
think they look the
cutest but I do I do have a balance of
both like I I do have white dresses with
accents um
but I said this in Prett chat but my
fashion sense will
change in these upcoming months because
now it
is oversized hoodie month and or months
and when it reaches oversized hoodie
months I will wear nothing but oversized
hoodies because that is my favorite
oversized hoodie weather
ideal yes giant sleeves no pants
oversized hoodie so that so there will
be a shift in beu fashion in these
upcoming months
mhm so normal
hoodies it is it
is uh it is oversized hoodie with
leggings sneakers and a beanie
season that is
that is the season for
that H
hairstyle
I I never put my hair
up
um because my hair is
too it's
too like
silky there we that's the word that's
the word that's silky that's how I
that's how Mom SEI always always
described my hair it's too silky so like
it will slip out of
ponytails and like stuff really quickly
like you have to tie it really really
tight for things like when when I was in
Japan there had to be times where I had
to tie my hair up for like dance
practice and stuff like that and I had
to like get the other girls to like tie
my hair up for me but it wouldn't stay
unless like you did like super super
super tight with
um with like pins and stuff because it's
just it just like you know slips like
right out that easy easily
yeah but it was cute
because
uh I love the moment I want to I want to
tie my hair up more because since I
don't really tie my hair up I didn't
know about this but like when when I tie
when you tie my hair up like really
really uh tightly and then leave it for
like hours at the end of the day when I
like unfurl my hair poof it's all like
wavy and Beautiful cuz it was like tied
up so it's like ah it's so wavy and and
nice I still like
that poof yeah so I want to I want to
learn how to tie my hair tightly more so
I can like do that where I just like
after I take a shower I tie my hair
really tightly go to sleep wake up the
next morning undo my hair tie poof and I
have really pretty wavy hair for like
the rest of the day I want to try that
yeah but yeah I never really ever tie my
hair up just because it's just a pain
cuz you have to tie it like really
really really really tight and
I also never really learned much because
again I said Mom SEI is kind of a tomboy
so I never really learned any girly
stuff from her
so like having my hair up in different
hairstyles is part of that I
guess and and Mom SEI is the opposite of
me where she'll usually go with for a
short
hairstyle uh where I am more of a long
hair style type of person
yeah so even then didn't really know
much write that down what that Mom ski
that's why that's why Drew mom SEI as
her design as short hair cuz Mom SEI has
short
hair
primarily would you consider getting
short hair yeah I consider I I think
short
hair is really cute but the only problem
with short hair
is it would make me look even
[Laughter]
younger even even more of a baby I
gu even more of a
kid 5 years old
because when when you have long hair it
kind
of I don't know I think people look
younger with short hair I don't know
what it is but I think people look just
younger with short hair in
general
yeah I like talking about about girly
things do you guys enjoy this talking
about girly stuff is does this interest
[Music]
you you're learning more about
me okay I'll talk about my fashion
then so my fashion right now outside of
winter seasons
is it's like a mix of d k Lolly it's not
like super formal Lolita because I don't
got time for that I don't have time to
like prepare full on Lolita
like two much time to get ready in the
morning I so I am more of like a
casual
Lita
or like frilly
di um I told preat this too but if you
search Liz
Lisa that is the type of clothing that I
wear but I don't really wear LZ Lisa too
much because there are other same style
clothing brands that I like more but if
you look that's basically the general
look but it's mostly that but black and
white yeah that's
my that's my main style of
fashion fashion yeah so Philly cute mly
dresses
mhm but I'm not very like high effort
about it yet like I'm not at the point
where like I
do like a specific pair of
shoes like one different pair of shoes a
day for this outfit
I only have like a handful of selection
of shoes so I do have cute shoes though
I do have that style of shoes but like
only one pair that I just like use and
then
um I don't use like the fancy frilly
socks either cuz that's too much High
effort and I already hate socks as it is
so like if you seen a lot of those like
things people will have like the fancy
socks to go with it I'm I'm not on that
step yet
because I hate socks
already not sock fat yeah feed prisons
too much
work not yet I will I don't know because
I'm on the I'm on the I'm very like I
like fashion but I also don't know how
people can spend 2 hours getting ready
in the morning
so I don't take long time with
accessories either I'll just put
like my Elden ring rings on and that's
it I I did collect more accessories
though same thing with like hair
accessories I haven't gotten to the
point of putting too many hair
accessories on my head yet same thing
with the the silky
hair um the silky
hair is issue is hair accessories also
don't stay on my head for very long
so I usually I am not on the step of
adding hair accessories just yet too
often
um but I'll put I'll put the oh so I
have I have my favorite rings are the
the the silver cat ring from Dark Souls
3 in the Life ring from also Dark Souls
3 and I will wear those to they're not
El ring they're from Dark Souls but yeah
so I'll wear I'll wear those two with
like every outfit that I have even if it
doesn't match I'll wear them cuz I like
them yeah the the life ring and then the
one that negates fall damage that one
but I have been I have been collecting
more like
minimalistic accessories like tiny
tiny like cute designs silver rings
and and like cute bracelets and stuff
like
that oh I got a really
fancy necklace before I left
um Japan and it's like super
fancy I wish I could show it off but
then then I wouldn't be able to wear it
out but it looks very it's like a very
fantasy like a very chunky fancy
necklace and now it's my favorite
accessory ever because it's like it's
like it's black and purple it's a black
and purple necklace I won't tell you
exactly what it is but it's a black and
purple necklace that was pretty darn
expensive and it it's like very it's
chunky and fancy and sparkly and it's
like my favorite accessory ever
um yeah and it goes well with my outfits
because my outfits are usually like
black and white he anyway so that's now
you know a little bit about B Bo fashion
I'm more girly than you think okay just
because I play
games and stream all the time doesn't
mean I don't have a girly side too
okay yeah I like talking about fashion
and outfit and stuff like that it makes
me happy anyway
[Music]
yeah pH phly clo really clo makes me
happy I I don't really wear earrings
because
again I don't have the
patience anything that will like
be that's like too too Troublesome to do
like I want to look cute but I don't
want to be too Troublesome so earrings
are like Troublesome for
[Music]
me since you get your nails done I did
get my nails done for the first time
recently and then I did not get them
removed by the time
I um by the time I came back to America
so I ripped them out of my nails I just
ripped them off it was very satisfying
it was a little painful some of some of
my nails
bled I bled the water Rock blood not
exactly Blood Cuz I don't bleed but like
bled in like the leaking rock water sort
of thing because you know the the the
stuff they use to attach the like the
the gel the gel is very very
um adhesive yes it's very adhesive thank
you so it took a lot for me to rip it
off and like the I didn't rip off my
nail I just ripped off the part that
like grows past your nail because that
part is weaker right so like the this
the the nail that grows past your your
nail thing is weaker cuz it's not
attached to the nail anymore so as I
ripped the the gel off it ripped the the
that part of the nail off and that
caused it to bleed because it was like
anyway but it's all gone now I did
it use warm water next time
oh I probably should
have but like I was stressed out it was
it was it was growing too long it was
going to start affecting my gaming and I
couldn't let it start affecting my
gaming
okay I couldn't let it start affecting
my gaming it's important okay I had to
take the nails
off
understandable but yeah I definitely I
definitely want to get my nails done
again someday cuz it was a very funny
experience and I couldn't stop looking
at them when I had them but I again I
don't know if I'm the type of girl to do
that often is the thing like I don't
want to have to go up go back to the
salon every month to get my nails done
and then I have to go get it done again
and again and again and again and again
it's too much
effort so I think I'm the type of person
who would get my nails done like once in
a special occasion or if like Iris
wanted to do it again I would go with
her and do it again but I don't think I
would just like go do it myself as a
tweet yeah as a tweet or something like
[Music]
that
uh anything else you want to know about
Be Fashion or be table girly things or
anything nice talk yeah nice
talk any
hats I don't really wear hats too
often because they fall off my head
Things fall off of
me very easily
[Laughter]
not
bald not bald it's the slippery hair
it's the S slippery hair problem
again
um maybe my I am just entirely slippery
because you know when oh you know when
like people especially like vtubers or H
Live members wear their jackets like
halfway I always think to myself do they
actually know what it's
like
to always have your jacket halfway like
that because I I have that I have like
my jacket halfway off of my shoulders
because it just falls off my shoulders
and it's uncomfortable because it's
always slipping down it's always
slipping off it's always slipping
down so I always wonder to myself
like is it do they is it a pain to to
hold those jackets up when you're
wearing it
halfway because I I I am constantly
having my jacket like halfway
off of my shoulders entirely off my
shoulders actually they they're hanging
on by my arms because it just
poof
yeah okay halfway like off shoulder like
a lot of like a lot of if you look at
like Hollow members or like just vob in
general and they have the art where like
they're like take Shori for sh is a good
example and she wears she wears her
jacket off her
shoulders
and it's for aesthetic yes but it's also
a pain in the
butt it's also a pain in the butt and I
know from experience how much of a pen
in the butt it is to wear it to have it
cuz mine my when I wear jackets it's
always off
shouldered yeah
[Music]
any perfume makeup I actually don't wear
perfume because like I said I'm like
half
girly so
like I don't I don't wear perfume but
I'm not stinky I Callie Callie and her I
was like listening to her to her stream
um about like how some people just don't
have the sweat stink Jean I don't have
the sweat stink Jean so I never really
felt the need to
wear perfume or
anything um and again it's just an extra
step of getting ready for the
day it it an extra step
okay that's an extra girly step I'm not
ready for those that step yet yeah so I
don't I don't wear perfume no not
really even deodorant I've never needed
deodorant
well I've never worn deodorant
before I I I don't need it so
like well okay it's not it's not lucky
Callie said this too they don't really
sell deodorant in Japan
because it's not really a thing they
don't sell deodorant or like super
strong deodorant in Japan because
because it's not
it's not
really common to need it for people to
need it
yeah yeah really really how you said
that I was listening to a stream
yesterday different different
culture it's it's definitely a us thing
[Music]
so they don't smell well so well the
people do smell like I I smelled some
smelly people still even while in Japan
it's not like they don't smell it's just
like different
jeans
yeah people still stink
[Music]
do you stink I've never been told that I
stink I've been told that I smell good
so I like to think that I smell
[Music]
good how we smell you
I actually I don't know what I smell
like because you you yourself are
desensitized to your own
smell so I can't I can't tell you what I
smell
like because because your own scent is
neutral to yourself right so like
I don't
[Music]
know anyway yes and all I don't really
wear perfume or deodorant I've never
really needed it but I've actually grown
more interested in perfume because I
keep seeing like how to smell like a
strawberry cake how to smell like a a
warm uh pancake on a on the Monday
morning how to how to smell like freshly
baked bread and then they have these
like combination of like perfumes of how
do you smell exactly like freshly baked
bread and then I'm like ooh that sounds
interesting but yeah like combine these
scents and you smell exactly like
freshly baked bread um right before the
bakery opens and the and the scent of of
cookies and
yes if I could smell like something I
would smell like strawberries because I
like strawberry smell but I don't think
that's surprising and that's probably
why I have the strawberry lip gloss
strawberry is my favorite
scent yes not
surprising so if you if you want me to
think you smell good make yourself smell
like
strawberries
yay I well I just I think perfume and
stuff is overwhelming I think I have a
sensitive nose my sense of smell is
pretty
good I think so
like perfume is kind of and clog is
overwhelming like man smell man man
smell is so intense like what does that
even smell like what is man smell like
how do you even describe
clog is this a bunch of weird chemicals
or something I've never smelled like
that naturally in nature before like guy
Colones like
broi I'm not into into perfumes and
clothes but
broi is into like clog and stuff because
broi is way more fashionable than I
am but yeah I don't understand it I
don't it's too intense for me no thank
you yeah braki is more fful than
me
drip sneaker
head but yeah I don't really I don't
really it just it smells too much it's
too intense it's too intense I don't I'm
not into that
anyway what are we talking about oh yeah
we're just like chatting now I was
supposed to like do super chats or
something but we're just kind of like
talking about fashion I kind of like it
though yappa yappa we've been like
yapping for an hour fast and
yapping do wear headbands
ever no I don't really wear anything on
my
head because that see I am the I am I am
girly but I take
shortcuts I am girly by take shortcuts
so the less steps it takes to look cute
the better so yeah so mostly it is just
cute
dress
bag cute
shoes and
then the only accessories I'll really
use is rings and then maybe a necklace
and maybe a bracelet but that's
it nothing really on my head nothing
really on the socks
Department
ah nothing that would take like too much
bonus
time
yeah no swords oh yeah and my Katana
tied to my waist ready for combat oh
yeah no no hair no hair really just
brush
hair that's
it but brush brush no I mean yes hair
just like keeping it down I don't really
put it up or anything I don't really
style it I just
yeah what no not that's not what I meant
like no hairstyle just
like
yeah but who knows while I continue on
my journey of girly maybe I'll continue
to add extra steps but right now too
much work
I'm not waking up any earlier to like
you know take away my sleep time I I'm
already taking away my sleep time
yeah no
makeup minimal like I don't do the thing
where
like like you know you have like
eyeliner and
and
uh
and like ey
Shadow and
stuff the only the only thing that I put
on my face is like okay I'll do the face
care thing Face Care is important I'll
do the face care thing but like makeup
wise I have a sunscreen that's
tinted so it's like it's not exactly
like Foundation or concealer it's just
tinted
sunscreen that like you know smoothens
out your like skin a little bit so
that's that's it
yeah
yeah I like putting blush on though I
like putting blush on though that's
that's something that that I guess is
make upy that I like cuz I like putting
blush and I like I like putting a lot of
blush on and and because it it's
cute so it's really it's really
just the the tinted
sunscreen and then blush and
then and then the Lippy the cute Lippy
stuff that I told you about and that's
pretty much it because again I don't
want to take that much time and again um
I'm not taking the time to do eyeliner
I'm
sorry my my eyes are sensitive they
twitch whenever things get too close I'm
not going to take the time to do
eyeliner sorry it's too scary
[Music]
yeah what about watches I don't really
own any
watches no I don't wear watches I I
think watches are cool though if I had
like a cute watch I would wear a watch
but I mean you have your phone for time
so I mean I feel like watches is a very
fancy people
thing so I don't I don't
really wear watches I don't feel fancy
enough to have a
watch BS on
heels
I don't really wear like fans see heels
but so many shoes in Japan are
platformed I guess it's to help all the
short people like me so I've started to
learn how
to walk on platform shoes now and also
the cute like Lolita shoes have like a
little bit of heel on them so I'm not
like super high like super thin heels
but like chunky heel chunky heel chunky
platform shoes
yeah but I do the thing I do the thing
all the time it I do the thing all the
time where like I step at an angle and
my my foot will go wee and like it'll
it'll it'll
like it'll like sideways it'll
sideways because yes and I that I do
that all the
time yeah I roll the ankle thing I
accidentally step oops ankle and I do
that all the time I do that I do that
all the time on accident
yeah
oopsies it was it was
funny um because I remember in Japan
when I would be with
someone when I would be with someone and
I was wearing my platform shoes or like
a heel um whenever I would go on the
stairs someone would be watching me like
go down the stairs like shy would watch
me on the stairs or like my manager
would watch
me go down the stairs or somebody
somebody would always watch me to make
sure I don't fall down the
stairs and I didn't ask for this I
didn't ask for them to like watch Me
While I went up or down the stairs they
just did that because they think I need
it or something like
that
yeah qu on people watch today are you
the most clumsy in Avent um
astronomically
yes te Heat
but I don't like that because every time
I think about clumsiness I'm always
reminded of like Twilight where Bella
Swan's
like I'm clumsy that's my whole
personality I fall down everywhere
oops I'm so clumsy I always need a
strong man to to help me and Edward
please I need your help and I don't like
that whenever
saw and that's why I don't make a big
deal of it like when when
um
when I just whoops okay moving
on whoops okay okay moving on you
know because I don't want to be be like
bis Swan my whole personality is that
I'm clumsy haha
no oh yeah whoops anyway moving on
that's just a thing
[Music]
because I cringe at myself cuz I'm
like be was being clumsy
again anyway
I guess that's
it I guess I should read super chat now
and then cuz I have a collab in four or
five hours anyway so let's read today's
super chats and then go nice
talk nice nice talk about random stuff
nice random
zatu yeah Monster Hunter soon
sorry answering a DM
okay who
w i just
confirming today
[Music]
I'll take a I'll take a a little bit of
an
apple all right I want to read super
chats for today's stream Warhammer Super
Chat I will read next time we play
Warhammer oh that was so fun yesterday I
need to start so so now I know there's a
there's a guy so so when whenever we
were staying for the emperor we're
talking about a half dead guy who's not
even doing anything he's just there to
enable space travel that's kind of lame
isn't
it you saved Humanity but people are
dying because of
him his mind is so important
bro literally fighting for chaos God
simultaneously more people will die
without
him apology streaming coming all I'm
going to start watching the videos to
get the lore I've see I got so many
recommendations on my last VOD so I'll
start watching the video the lore videos
okay so
I understand more
what you say is
heresy I am very curious about the Lord
because of them people can die but
aren't people dying because of him
anyway don't people die either
way less
people 10 times 10 times more with d
without well now I got to watch cuz I'm
curious
anyway today super
chats nice be hat thank you for the
super rock rock what cute seeing the
stuff in your bag on K stream good luck
surviving today thank thank you I was
really excited to show off my
bag cuz like whenever whenever girly
things are metioned like girly things
[Laughter]
well I said you did the bag in like 2
minutes it wasn't 2 minutes I had to you
know lay lay out my stuff neatly and
then take a nice picture and then also
write the cute little notes so it didn't
take 2
minutes more like
30 but I was just I was just so so
excited to just do it that
like yeah how are your earbuds not a
tangled mess they are a tangled
mess they are Tangled
F I have to untangle them again
I need like one of those cute like
earbud thingies that doesn't let it
tangle cuz I just pop it in my bag
[Music]
yeah use wireless on yeah I guess I
should evolve into airpod
the only reason I want airpods is
because airpod holders are so cute like
people make fashion out of airpod
holders and I think it's adorable and
that is literally the only reason I want
them to to get cute airpod
[Music]
holders yeah they're cute
they're totally worth it who owns
airpods you think they're worth
it I think I think I don't
use
wireless another reason why I don't use
wireless earbuds is like the same reason
why I don't use a wireless mouse is
because like I don't trust the
latency I don't trust it I want things
instant I don't want I don't trust the
latency of
of of of
Wireless I want things
instantly there is no latency okay I
believe
you anyway I keep getting distracted by
yapping but yap yap uh Super Chat nice
be hat thank you for the super rock rock
I read that one already Robert Panda
thank you for the super rock rock hi
people here's my tax loved how your bag
looked in K stream I left out of my
chair Mema and pointed when I saw yeah
and as soon as you saw DMC everyone was
like this can't be bees it's too girly
boom DMC it's bees it's B's bag it's B's
bag there's DMC on
[Music]
it I won't be able to watch the sadness
but have fun be thank you I have fun
today the Pokemon threw me off I am more
of a Pokemon fan than you guys think
just because I can't play it
but even my 3D debut
had like a Pokemon section so that might
hint you as uh how much I like
[Music]
Pokemon is the next Pokemon game is it a
next Pokmon game is supposed to be like
Legend
something Legend something I hope I
really hope we can play that one Legends
Legends
thingy
Legends Legends Z Legends
Legends people with weekly schedule this
week doesn't have a weekly schedule
because um the times are always sh
shifting for this event like even now it
was decided that we would start an hour
earlier tomorrow
so everything is not set in stone
he so I didn't want to do a schedule and
plus I feel like maybe there'll be a day
where I don't want to do seven days to
die and I want to play Warhammer instead
or something like that I want to
give I want to give uh this week the
availability to either if I need to take
a break I can take a break if I want to
play something else I'll play something
else or if I want to continue playing
seven days to die I can play seven days
to die I want to be flexible yeah that's
the word I want to be flexible this week
so that's why there's no weekly
[Music]
SK um Rob P thank for the super rock
rock another fun stream people thanks so
much for the streams for the emper for
the
[Music]
brothers the brothers the
brothers the
brothers oh wait that was that was for
Warhammer I read a Warhammer super
oops well thanks to the super Rock Rock
I zero thank you for the super rock rock
yay thank you for the super rock rock
tied pens for the apocalypse thank you
you know when you're in the apocalypse
your clothes are totally stained so
you'll need plenty of tie pens for the
apocalypse so you're welcome everyone's
going to ask me for a Tide pen and I'm
going to say why didn't you have them in
your bags already just in case h
literally so useful thank you thank
you thank you just because I care about
my
clothes doesn't me get to make fun of me
for
it
uh oh and yes thank you for getting pism
NOA to
200k yay H the English subs are gone for
the moment there is a paperwork issue
that was not my fault so I had literally
no control over the
subs being taken down or put up or
anything it was a paperwork issue that
wasn't my
issue
um and hopefully it will be up back as
soon as possible cuz the subs really
good so I'm kind of sad about it but I
was reassured that it will go back up as
soon as possible so let's just wait a
little bit I asked if we could at least
just leave the romanzi up
but no oh well
but for now thank you for your
pain
cuz I was I was like please make sure
that we have high quality Subs when the
that was like one of the things that was
important to me and that's also why I'm
kind of sad about it because I was like
please make sure we have high quality
Subs when the music video comes out so
that like people like know the meaning
behind the lyrics who don't understand
Japanese and stuff like that and people
can follow along so that so adding Subs
was supports me and it was important
that I had it in like both Japanese
English and and
ID as well so kind of sad that after all
making that sure that it got taken down
but it's okay we will wait
patiently it's not my
[Music]
fault AK could be thank you for the
super rock rock here's a super chat for
you people I won't be able to catch the
stream because I got to take my preal
test today have fun good luck with
preal good
luck math is
hard math is hard so good luck with I
hope you'll Ace your tat
[Music]
don't miss doing
math math is hard but it can be fun like
I feel really good memorizing
formulas like I just sound smart when I
say like X = B plus or minus the square
Ro T of b^ 2 - 4 a c / 4 a
like I feel I feel just like so good
saying
that yeah
yeah 2 a sorry 2 a no I forgot it no I'm
not smart
anymore
[Music]
no I was I was going to make myself look
so smart bang stupid now I'm stupid dang
it I always sounded smart I don't I'm
not smart anymore ruined
but math is good when I played when I
played the uh the card game I felt
really good speed running the change
like I was like look how fast I can give
you your change huh that felt good nice
J thank
you see give 89 pennies that was out of
spite black Ace thank you for that super
rock rock if the hurricane prevents me
from watching this collab today I'll
just have to watch the V later stay safe
the that one's pretty scary it's like
really really big and it's
like they said they're fine good good
good good good good stay safe there's a
it's going to hit like a lot of people
people and it's like immediately after
the one before too so stay safe stay
safe hope you have a great time bab I'll
try my best to watch this live if I can
yes but Safety First stay safe stay safe
safety first you can always catch the
VOD I would rather you be able to watch
my vods later than not be able to watch
it at all ever so yeah
[Music]
thank you for the super rock rock you're
not allowed to
play not allowed to I told you you can't
so you're not allowed
to car thank you for super rock
rock uh no for falling thank you for the
super rock rock bow bow oops wrong
channel oh
well rock rock now you're a pebble sorry
no no no escaping now now you're a
pebble Ruffian Diamond dog enjoyer
that's how it works be with
ti welcome welcome to your new
family thank you for your
limbs
enjoy
brother uh a cow that likes cookies
thank you for the super rock rock moo
I'm a cow and this is a banana flavored
Super Chat for the Rock Solid gamer are
you winning people I am
winning thank you I'm winning in all
aspects banana milk would sounds really
good right now I love some banana
milk kill my thank you for the super
rock
um a pimp name slick pack oh see that's
a song isn't
it slick back slick back oh the brain
Rod's getting to me again nice ju thank
you um
hello it's a Boondock
reference I am watch
that I don't
know I just know it from the meme and
you're going to hate me for it cuz it's
like oh bab not the brain rot again how
do you only know things from brain
rot sorry
uh yeah from the the the dance the air
walking dance song thing the when where
like you're walking backwards but it's
like you're flying or was it Forward
something something you're like flying
it looks like you're flying but it's
like a dance
move
anyway um hell be you I have a lot of
your songs on my workout playlist for a
while now love it make bury the cring
name of you but I need more power so I'm
going to add prison noo please do next
I'll take back the yam now it's
mine I paid a lot of money for
it uh if you want you'll have to take
it B
um yeah cute thank you for the super
Rock Ro the show is called Z King
English another line is spare me my life
oh I think I spare me my
life yes Z in English that's the one
with the with the aerobic girls and I
have a bad case of diarrhea I have a bad
case of diarrhea I have a bad case of
diarrhea D me my
life yes it's so funny look it up look
it
up Zin
English look it up I have a bad kisse of
diarhea
it's a
song it teaches to English
phrases I'll send it after the stream's
over thank you for super rock rock thank
you for super rock rock thanks for the
stream bald B buff see you later wa a
mon Hunter yeah
[Music]
C my S I need to remember it's okay if I
don't remember how to play right away
because we're doing like beginner Quest
anyway and I don't want to steam roll
through
everything
yeah uh I stand thank you for the super
rock rock glow in the- dark thank you
for the super Rock Rock thin thank you
for the super rock rock
epic night thank you for the super rock
rock why does the St princess have a pen
to remove stain H it's different kind of
stain
okay stain princess be will
also appreciate your clothes
okay they have to be
Immaculate uh e thank you for super rock
rock uh wired earphon Supremacy also if
you go back to Japan's orcades again and
try Rhythm games they have a wired
headphone jack for you to use so you can
focus and not get distracted yeah I
noticed that that's so
nice I played some new games new Rhythm
games in the in
the Japanese arcade they're so fun
there's so many there's so many
different
like arcade games it's amazing I I
wanted to spend more time playing in
Japanese arcade I like how they're just
like everywhere and you can just like go
in and then like waste so much
time what's my favorite I really like
the one with the box it's a square it's
a square rhythm game and you click the
squares in the correct time that one's
really
fun D beat yeah I like d
beats and then I obviously I like
classic DDR but I I really want to play
the one where it's not like just DDR
it's like you're sliding your
feet instead of and you're D like you're
dancing dancing instead of like the four
directions it's like a it's like a touch
pad for your feet I've never tried it
before but I really really want to try
it dance Rush stom is that always
called yeah I want the shuffling one
yeah the shuffling one I'll try that
one yeah yeah thank you for the super
rock rock also congrats on 200k on prism
naho thank you I've been looping it for
the day at bedtime to increase my luck
every day 10 10 it works it does work it
increases your Gad luck any luck did you
know if you listen to prism naho when
you're pulling things um it does luck
boost it's true I have um accurate
accounts of that happening
so can't confirm just
sing H are you fan Pebble thank you for
super rock
rock I just realized is have I been
saying your name wrong the entire time
have you just been Ru fan Pebble and not
are you are you rude instead of but I've
just been calling you are you the entire
time you send a
super yes I knew huh I'm sorry I'm sorry
that's just the Beil thing pronouncing
people's names wrong okay that's just a
Beil
thing I do it to
everybody it's okay I like it thank you
okay I'm going to keep calling you are
you oh I thank you for super Rock
today we learned B was truly the stain
princess as in the princess of getting
rid of stains no other meaning hope you
get some good eat before m h thank thank
you I'll take a
nap black a s you for super rock rock
I'm quite lucky the hurricane didn't
affect me too hard over here good I'm
glad wish the best of luck for those who
that did get hit hard though yes stay
safe I hope you have fun with monster
hunter playing with W thank thank
you K thank you for the super rock rock
monkey Rush thank you for the super rock
rock today's my birthday I send you
membership wish you all wish people we
will all get better and better happy
birthday to you pe happy birthday to you
I guess
whatever happy birthday dear
Pebble whatever happy birthday see you
happy birthday thank you for the Super
Chat I guess not like I care or
anything
huh okay enough yapping enough enough
the tangents let's take a little bit of
a break break let's take a little bit of
a break I'll see you in like 4
hours yes yeah I suppose it was a fun y
though fun y f times it's fun seven days
to die I had a lot of fun today thanks
everybody I'll see you in a few hours
and then again for day two of Seven Days
to Die
Tomorrow didn't know baby was so girly
well now you learned a little bit more
about me today I'm not just I'm not just
I'm not just a a a gamer girl okay I'm
not just a girl who plays the video
games I'm actually oh my God she's
actually a girl oh my
god oh
[Music]
man ew
grossa
ew
ew anyway bye see you in a bit wait
where's my ending screen there it is
[Music]