[Music]
byebye
I'm not
a I'm together
we
by today is the first day of the whole
life English Seven Days to Die Here We
Go are you ready to go
M let's spawn into the world then
[Music]
okay okay here we go oh
W oh my
gosh what just
[Music]
happened we'll wait a moment we'll wait
a moment wait a moment for it it's going
to Lord let it think yeah we so
close yeah you just have to let the game
[Music]
thinging
buing yes okay here we go here we go
again
there we go this time for
sure okay that was spooky that was
spooky take two here we
go what's that there's a l
there I love
rubbish oh iron iron that's good rubbish
iron yeah where where where where are we
spe let's go above this
why are you
screaming I was so
[Music]
scared f the scarest people
ever we got a friend ofite
too scary we have to wipe our tears
away it's so scary
[Music]
people I got a friend of my from
B do
I okay
ah how do I press the plus
[Music]
buttony I don't
know
hi let's
go this is
frightening I wish people had more
clothing I did too that's a little I
received a party
invite that's not that's not
uh this one
oh is that
it why do I feel small oh I can't I
can't hear you oh
oh cuz we're in a party
H can you hear
us oh I can hear the twins are you guys
around here we're in the party chat I
think
now
hello you scared us so bad we're using
party chat right now we're probably
going to use Discord pretty soon okay I
for
unfortunately unfortunately I'm
beautiful what
you nice beard okay you wish you came
running at us from behind we thought
you excent let us head in the direction
of the survivors yeah let's all go
together
do oh you
B yes I know I've been working out
let's apocalypse
huh oh yeah come to B to
B purple beard purple beard let's find
everybody looks buff I'm sure take a
look at the map I want ACH of
tre although this is too bu you would
want more FS but maybe they can't
because they don't find fool
would make sense sense
to
hello oh everybody clothes
huge is everybody
close is this maybe a we should probably
get to
[Music]
everybody we're just going to punch a
trail
together next I think there's some
eching us come to and
well we'll meet where we're
at okay we're going to stay here let's
punch the
grass
yeah this is good are we helping I think
we helping the rock let's not fall let's
not
fall let's stick together with just
going to continue punching the
tree watch in her punch the tree makes
me want to punch the tree let's punch
the tree yeah let's punch the tree
together
okay stop punching the tree huh are can
to make us do all the hardw yeah B
tree yeah take the anger out on the
tree first thing you do when your e gu
is punch the Tre already punching trees
I see that's good we're Gathering es
while you guys try to arrive also did
you punch
me what are you
doing I thought I fists were bloody from
the tree I thought we got all bloody
from punching the
tree
a this is how we survive this is how we
survive punch the
tree we swim
look maybe we could punch the other side
of the tree
swim little L
people sorry my my mic was yes you're
good I tried changing Pusher talk and it
didn't work for some
reason there's no like voice activation
I think it's just push yeah no no I
meant I tried changing my
Keye you guys were in voice chat already
actually we're using uh the party chat
but yeah probably move to Discord
afterward
okay minutes to
die did you die yeah I died like seven
minutes that's hilarious hello everyone
hello
I'll make a weapon got to
protect hello dear sir boing hello sir
nice
beard
nice nice
beard also very clean and nicely shaven
head I wonder how much time that takes
you every day let's down the
tree walk no I'm just naturally bald I
don't have on my head could it be that
the iname voice CH has a long
delay a long
delaying maybe maybe we should hop in
Discord stamina are you kidding me don't
take my down what the
hell not a
joke
sorry okay we go down the tree
I think we're moving to Discord voice
chat hello hello okay oh I think we're
good
[Music]
yay mic so low that's weird it's kind of
kind of
[Music]
quiet I think we're okay T volume tag
tag tag
hear me hear you okay thank you yay
we're figuring it out together
together why is it so quiet I'll turn up
maybe that'll help why is it so quiet
okay
[Music]
uhoh is there weight in this game too
like like um a maximum of how much you
can carry in in terms of weight nope
sorry guys sorry sorry sorry also you
can just carry as much as you want
that's great
it's it's there's inventory slots that
are
finite wait there's a house over here
can we have it yeah well the big goals
for today are to find a place to to
chill out in
together um a base even if it's
temporary um well yeah can we take over
this house this looks nice this is
actually a really nice house we did get
lucky wow this is like a Walking Dead
[Music]
house what
happening I don't think so we may have
to take out the enemies here though I'm
like
crouching what happens if we die oh my
God yes you crouching then we respawn
you may want to make a bed roll really
quick thank
you I thought we live in this house
there's a PC set up I can stream from
here
the
botom this bad sounds
huh zomes in the house so there's
there's baddies I didn't think of
[Music]
that yay zombie noises don't F
me to do you want to come with me to
them uh I'm already trying to make my
way way towards bi apparently that's
where we're
meeting so I'm I'm slowly making my way
there we are we are in a a big house
that could be our home base it could be
our home is it upstairs B do you want to
go upstairs with me we should go
upstairs first B okay what what are you
scared are you scared that why is a nice
house I call theed but I have a giant
hole here I don't know I don't know
about the Integrity of this house should
not sure need to fill the hole we'll be
fine but yeah you're
right yeah that's
true boy don't hurt my new
[Music]
friend that was close got
them they're still alive they're still
they're still alive but they're dead is
The Walking Dead right where' they
go you got a bit of reach on him it's
just Dark Souls just oh the downstairs
oh he fell I got the stones I mean oh
there's a lot of room in
here beds down
here I'll take the
couch is there a way to improve the
stamina somehow I might need level
up it's just stop being jump scared by
me SC yes
on the potatoed I'm going
to
Temporary need the CRA guys I'm going to
go on a little trip to find clothes I
will be back to this house temporary
base okay you you can craft clothes by
the way I have all ready to farm yeah we
don't have to stay naked forever and I'm
going to start cleaning the house cuz
you know you guys know I'm a clean freak
I'm sorry it can't be helped house is
very messy you
already I found your bedroom really you
guys can come check it out it's we
really lucky actually yeah come
downstairs downstairs yeah what do you
mean this is so
broken look it works it works now but
it's so broken we're going to have to
repair it so much you think we can find
can I show you look at this Callie
Callie look at this giant
yeah there is a pool table that a good
point that a good point playing pool
together yeah that would be really cool
I think you know what you won me over
you know a pool table pretty good that's
pretty good it's a fix upper as they say
put crates and stuff yeah yeah a lot of
blocks a lot of crates need to pick up
the there's snakes in this game snakes
snakes and they're not zombie snakes
they're just normal snakes oh my God
maybe I could blow it up like in and
make a balloon
oh oh I have
a that should be cool in the W does
anyone know how to get plant fiber uh
smack grass yeah just smack it oh
there's a water cooler bottle in here
down can we pick it up we could take it
to the water with us I think the one
thing I remember is that it's really
important for us to find water and not
to like save it like save it and not
drink it and figure out how to craft
like water reservoirs and water there's
a water cool bottle yeah mky water will
give you tummy egg probably but yeah it
has denter in it
oh back
upstairs go down here too but there's
nothing else up here down here what else
is oh gosh yeah I don't the toal mission
in the upper right
yeah to is
see look we can totally block this
hole challeng is
done basic survival we have no wood left
you see what where I'm getting right you
guys see what I'm getting at yeah I
think this is a oh I found $8 guys
anyone want to sell me something for
$8 I'll buy
you economy
uh can you can you can I buy
wood have no built it no I don't I need
can I have two go back okay for $8 I
need wait let me double check if it's
two really two yeah for $8 how do how do
I drop
something Cecilia and I'm still waiting
for you accept my friend request oh
sorry I don't we that out yet let's AC
everybody and got everybody
except how do I FL how do I
a thing oh like a stack but I this did I
do something wrong you craft more than
one how you split stackle yeah so I can
give you
two oh I found it you're totally going
to survive how do you do drop a okay
here you go I dropped it look what I did
I'm so smart I'm a builder
build oh W already you need a help this
is not safe with working environment I
do not I
don't she's already got
D so
many guess I can craft
multiple
okay I already forgot how to play this
game okay wood time see now the house is
well fortified cuz there's no hole
anymore nice nice
build this oh my gosh this is going to
be our streamer house going to stream
from here and it's like a dream come
true we going have one PC apocalypse
that we all have to share with there's
multiple PCS here multiple even okay
yeah kind all the off collaps for off
colls man off colls
forever I'm so hype let me move my bed
roll I mean even in the zombie
apocalypse didn't is important let's go
the be there where right there
okay you hit
me
choose no
never I
got make sure you guys do your
challenges by pressing
y did you find
let's make the stone axe team made it oh
we made
itone together more wonder if use my
face if we made a stone a we should use
it instead of the one weara and gig are
pretty far
away she's making her way downtown
walking fast face is past and she's home
now
[Music]
do I have to do
this
SP satisfying looking down the trees I
like the flowers we'll just work on
fortifying the base here more
flowers I need to GA PEB Pebbles give me
yourselves Pebbles where are you Salvage
this car you guys can salvage anything
by the
way how sorry I didn't listen how do you
salvage anything
just hit it oh just it inates I'm going
to put some crates in the house so we
can put stuff in there okay okay
okay doing it keep out
condemned
nothing
fin for the I mean we can do whatever we
want but for the mag I think it's
probably best to like keep them and then
see who wants to go into what because
otherwise there won't be enough like if
everyone just uses everything no one's
actually going to level any skill CU
they're really rare and you need like 10
of one type in order to get a level and
stuff sometimes so great let's have like
a magazine crate or something I person
going
for I
am death oh there's a Farm close by oh
nice want the big
we have a bunch of seeds yeah we have
coffee seeds potato seeds do I need my
first don't need any
Rock
Prim this is a good
spot
potato dinner time
baby we have
some wrong button we can make a bone
knife soon
too uhoh
if you find corpses on the ground hit
them ladies hit them I hit
them zombi kind of
cute a little further away kind of a
strong zombie I don't
[Music]
know
vampire how do
you fix infection cut off the arm oh
you're infected oh infected oh goodbye
goodbye bye goodbye nice KN you time to
put the cat down let's F hi where are
you where you at hi where you wait where
is she here I'm here I'm here where is
here where is here the hi I'll help you
with the infection go down
actually it might be worth at the
beginning she's wait where is she going
to respawn is she is she going to
respawn she might all
[Music]
beginning where where are you been I'll
just tear off that
limb we talk about
it no fting talk okay okay listen I want
to help I want to get matal I I want to
help you guys to fight zomes and oh
behind you behind you a
zombie oh KN oh we know where the
Outpost is now oh I can it's literally
right there don't want to sleep in the
bathroom hello oh okay but maybe you
guys are NPCs oh
k
out can hear me
he looks like a blueberry
[Music]
blueberry Health left he a
punch let take him
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm not sure I have to leave a party
that I'm in I am
hurting we should heal
somehow but I made a a bow and I got us
meat you guys I got us
meat I have a question how do you
actually wear the outfit uh you click on
the item and press
W look oh our house
the best house
ever freaking rocks figure out
right make sure we have more I'm not
Naked Anymore yeah don't be naked
naked's
dangerous we can make two dangerous
great this my bed now okay let's see
what other items and thanks can we
[Music]
to oh here we go all right I'm finally
where you guys are I think I I'm I'm
there welcome
home I see you she's here
welcome here for now right Y is it
yellow the papa residence yes the papa
that's a streamer
house welcome am I closed now but you
can check it out yourself too
scary though I can make more items wait
we have this s hello oh it's a brick
someone put that building block down
there and I accident maybe we picked it
up yeah it's just a block the okay I
don't know what this
is is a map I don't know this place is a
so we put our uh bed rolls in here
somewhere I think you go do that already
course
oh B right anywhere there's actual beds
in here there are
yeah did you build those beds or there
just
bunk for
us put your put your you have to craft a
bed roll and then put the bed roll where
you want to
SP I'm taking the master bedroom hey the
master bedroom
how do we does anyone know how to make
like chests or something yeah I just
made them they're in the living room
living room where oh there nice thank
you I wonder if I can put right I'll
just put all my garbage in here sure
just materials and
such on this couch you'll get to sleep
on this comfy bed
nice how do I put the bed roll down
[Music]
I think I got a building Cube from the
house maybe have to go on the
ground I'll I'll Rec click right click
how do you place a bed right click right
click but I don't know I don't know how
to turn
it you can't be on the top no oh oh I
guess I can't place it on the
bedy
water if you guys water you can uh you
can boil it in a pot over fire to clean
it I see network time M I got kicked
out did we all get kicked out no no it
said you disconnected okay I'm going to
sleep next to the PC
then we have eggs M no don't press the
stop that m
if we go upstairs there was like a fire
can we cook the eggs over the
fire was there a
fire I think so maybe I do want to burn
some I feel like if we started a fire
downstairs it would good there was a
thing we could do outside though oh like
right here there's a visitor at our
humble
abode yeah a good one
nice I don't know but they're not
talking is it just R NPC uh is it the
shieldy group
sh did you just attack
me I've claimed
land oh
nice
um we claimed this land with this
block uh what are you doing up my
beautiful girl
[Music]
[Laughter]
us we have someone
EV I have
nool look you look beautiful this is
this is my PC setup do you like it oh
nice garbage we need a cookie oh I can
sleep on top of it
actually or maybe I
cannot clean up our
house should I
SLE I mean yeah
yeah what happens if I take the sofa
apart
yeah sure I don't think we need it we
getting anything for me I don't know
does anyone want to come I want to go
try going to a f oh I'll go let's go got
just set up home here really quick let's
go
okay well then let's wait for sh did you
say you will come with us or let me my
bed roll okay okay we don't have any
healing items
though a second
there a tra here or you guys
Trader a Trader near this
house you found one yet we haven't done
anything take off my hat I like that
even in the apocalypse Trend thing and
we all wearing the same style I accident
cck way if you guys open the map you can
set a marker for where home is let do
that cuz we are going to get lost can
set
that's
nice
I I'm sorry every time back in I punch
someone that's what happened I don't
need it stay away from truth truth truth
please don't touch me you don't touch
me go
[Music]
leg this way I think was the farm Yep
this way wait wait who am I following
everyone looks the
same Cecilia
has the with spear I follow this the the
flow oh okay but I'm going to have ADH
on the that's okay at any point you
[Music]
want
dead so like dead corn and
green get the green coin get the forget
that forget that green
they're dead let's go there is real
corn there can we get can we get to
replant we have potato seeds already
those are still growing can I take from
those a tree apocalypse with corn that's
all I need I'll survive of the Corn are
dead
though can we just can't eat the the
people lot of
I mean they're just zombies they're not
people okay this one has this area has
three three skulls on it I don't know if
we're ready for that oh does that mean
like danger we're going to die yeah the
green one the probably really good but I
just
don't so I noticed that the green corns
actually contain
seeds oh they do
we set up a little farm our
home if we get rid of the Dead corn what
happens oh there's a house over here
too I
see this is be careful this is the three
School
area there zombies everywhere run run
run what are they going to
[Laughter]
do all right I hope the corn like
supplies maybe a farmer shows up and
take care of things
hopefully
fers I have so much I'm going back home
that sound going be useful too I don't
think it gives you anything can I eat
okay we can eat wait don't leave me
we just
need we found
[Music]
sand who wants to focus on getting food
maybe we should split
into gatherers this is just like
Gathering and
then I found a land claim block
destroyed this oh I think someone put
that down I just put that there for the
quest worry not oh I don't even know
where my land clim block is so if you
put a land clim box down
apparently um it applies a hardness
modifier to blocks so it protects it
protects damage on something
apparently so like safe in the zone I
guess or something like that or the
player who put it down is safe in the
zone it's like
now
house one of those I put one in the
living
room oh we're in the same uh Ally group
too so we should be good to
go it won't be harder for us to destroy
each other's things if we need to are we
all in the same party I have a question
um no Pary are is six oh how do you
level
up I think you got a kill experience
yeah if we find a Traer he gives Quest
and he gives a lot of exp from the quest
does anyone want to go with me on an
adventure to see if we can find the
Traer
really I have one on my map yeah
okay yeah
yeah this way point if he wants to trade
he should come to us that's right he
he's not going to do that I think
not going to be our face by the way or
he's going to stay here it's getting
hello I found
[Music]
people welcome hey you guys are all
wearing something aie where's your
hat there's a hat on yes put your
on you should probably like this is be
over there kill
it
look
will oh wait no I see a head oh thank
you yes put it on Oh
yay he's down down I think he's not
done oh he has a nice jacket
how to share
the
you I send the screenshot gloves I'm
missing gloves
pieces can we eat the corn just
[Music]
yet really me me me is this our our
we should probably do multiple campfires
what is this land plane
block our now with this basically
zombies will spawn around you see it I
put it in the channel of the map what if
we all put our land claim blocks like
around each other so they won't spawn
within a let's protect the
house I don't
have
so can't do anything right now
land oh I have a land CL block um I
don't know where to put it though uh it
won't let me put it
anywhere they already claimed This
Land Is there a maximum to can only one
person CL
cilia sorry how are you cooking oh this
is oh that's not me
that's maybe right there fig to put this
oh yeah can put the l oh yeah it's a
pretty it's a
PR I am dying of might
be I want to eat we need to unlock the
recipes take a look at our Quest
and
Riv maybe here oh we need cooking items
we need cooking skill I like the
placement of this fire
yeah you just put at the fireplace can't
believe
it we should probably try to find um
like a cooking pot and a water in the
inventory I found I found a cooking a
grill outside the house I don't
know we can drink some water we have
water in our inventory here free is
there a town
nearby oh there's a town far
away with some food that's the hill
that's food I think don't have to eat
scary
food night soon
everyone oh you guys have a nice vampire
out here wonderful we can more the idea
that I is that
vc1 is for the home and then all the
other ones are for like going out on
different excursions
together IDE think we're eating that
would be great we still hungry M I want
to eat
it
here River she's here don't know it's
about to
be I think I'm going to focus on finding
food yeah
going CH too if anyone wants to go on an
ex
stroll okay Excursion team
yeah night time stroll time yeah night
time
St time let's check
out that I am infected so if I die at
any moment do you have a bed roll yeah
okay then you should respawn at the
yeah yes indeed okay so yeah if you die
where you put your we're carrying a lot
right now we should probably should I
die here then and respond yeah okay I'll
kill you don't worry we'll help wa
should we put our inventory is there
like a box you can put it in
uhoh
noes you're welcome it's fine anytime
anytime you need for help we'll help you
don't worry no hes
wow is there a place that we can put our
stuffs in our inventory yeah there's a
box here in the living room oh okay we
can make one of those we just put our
stuff okay one moment we
go okay let's put it in there okay
should we check out the area East to
where we are it seems to have like a
little yeah I'm alive house or something
oh is that the farm your stuff is where
you di okay I'm going to pick it up yeah
that sounds bad
scary sounds all of a
sudden okay I'm ready give me five
seconds I'm just putting my stuff
away okay um should we try the one West
from us then scary
sound
okay zombie how could this happen to me
a zombie okay in the zombie game no
I hope this should we close the door
maybe let's close the
door she's in the house is
inside how do you get in
here somebody's on
fire I'm going to St back I think yeah
go down I don't
know
yeah do that sound good
no how much corn do I have to eat to not
be I think the corn just as it is just
heals one point so it's not worth eating
oh yeah we need to make we need to like
Grill it
probably
okay I have I have do oh I got some
chicken soup okay I'll just that there
is a lot of zombie sounds going
on sound sounds
sounds it calls
[Music]
me I got
some I don't think you can do anything
with eggs we need like a pan and stuff
yeah we need baby
what oh my gosh let's close the door so
no trees come
through were we were we heading out by
the way we would but then I we kind of
got scared a little right okay don't be
scared can someone make me a new um wood
um Stone ax thing oh we need a new one
is any can you make a wooden Stone ax
you can you can repair your oh we can
yes let's repair it
then I can't oh we don't I don't have
the material we don't have the materials
right now wait a second give me a moment
we put it all
away we need some rocks probably also if
we had a torch it' be a little bit
easier to see things I can make boiled
egg you should have one when you spawned
or is it a torch we have
one need play here oh gosh what is that
what is that help help help he's running
he's running oh no back we're going back
home we're going back
home it's the house the
house and lo it up Lo it up
okay
okay let's take some of the Rocko and
then fix our our weapon right now is it
that is it that I think so yes
thank you you saved
me you're
welcome not you
po you're
welcome we it y yeah we repaired it
okay
yay okay is everyone
here this
way is in the house we in the
house okay try going for the the the
area that is left of this down the
street okay oh
there we're going to be back up maybe
you should run run away from
that oh he got
me they fast what I feel like maybe it'
be better to run away from
them but it's the fast they can run
faster than
us nice does anybody have extra Pebbles
I want to make a speed oh we have small
st no we don't put them away put them
away we are very hungry our maximum
status is stamina is reduced we should
have some of our food M down but you
don't want to eat
it there goes our food
okay hungry still hungry I don't know
yeah I don't know the beginning is
really hard because there's just no food
so you're just going to be hungry I
don't know be H be hungry okay there
might be like a way to make food from
the very beginning but I don't know
so try finding stuff this b o cell tower
number one what what's this let's go on
in are you guys are you guys outside
right we're inside the
just if you're in the
party go towards the pink the pink
water triangle can I can I go past you
please oh sorry am I on the way thank
you it's
okay it's okay let's break stuff I think
I'm uhoh there's water empty water
nothing it's
empty it's empty water Co and not empty
water was
scratching it's okay you're you're
May going up maybe the game has like
Communications or
something I hear
sounds I want to climb on up oh I
can't I'm coming oh there we
go no how do I go up the the ladder how
do I go up the ladder you just go PR
W be careful there's a zombie up here
though watch out are going to get him
uhoh there's a lot of zombies I think he
ran off the cliff never mind oh so it's
safe up here yeah ah my leg is sprained
guys it's over I'm going to be dead from
now
on okay I I jump jump jump jump
jum jump jump
jump look jump jump oh my leg is broken
it's in the house in the house in the
house in the house this door is very
[Music]
strong the
door he in here oh my gosh my leg is
broken
we have 15 Health we're going to
die climb down I don't know you jump you
jump and you break your legs look down
is there outside I'm going to fight them
good luck wait will stay
here don't go down don't go
down in the we can't kill him in the
hole Yeah kill him in the hole on this
side
oh my go
[Music]
running my leg is broken for the next
two
[Music]
hours
eliminated that was from
before Oh I'll stay here let's break the
garbage 6 hp
back up no oh well I'm going to stay
inside the house let's break more stuff
okay right uhoh yummy we're not very
fast our stamina is really bad what's
the what's the little thing that says
eyesight
that's it's not healing very fast is the
one with the
shoe that one too I use a splint do we
have one
do we have a
[Music]
sp we make a spint uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh
here they come can we make a spint right
now can we I don't know how to do
that oh I got a
weapon take the weapon down take the
weapon let's use
ite me thank
you okay okay okay here we go here we go
here we go here we
go okay attack at the door attack at the
door attack at the door
look do I don't have ping
[Music]
anymore I really
need a lot
of on on my bed on my bed on my bed on
my bed I don't think we want to go
back come
on thank
you I don't have any
stuff we have a box to put down our
inventory is all in hi guys
hi I'm good I'm good
[Music]
SP take turns take turns take
turns where are you
guys this is one
very let's go get stuff from our
box we're not ready for this okay good
I'm going down
let I'm going
downstairs where is the self coming from
let's hide in bed watch
out that's craft in the meantime you
have anything to craft you got you got
the bock can we use the
rock why
you red eyes it's messed up what do that
because it's nice stronger
died oh they run away from us oh no mind
I'll try burning them he's burning he's
burning burn down burn
them's go if they come in here what are
we doing how are we escaping this little
tiny
room near it's okay it's okay
okay full moon oh oops The Rock
is almost
over the over I throw rocks they come
down the stairs I throw
rocks uh oh oh God okay okay okay maybe
this wasn't the
best what was that
explosion oh there is no door everybody
he's gone oh
door I don't know if they can get up
here let's take some I don't know we'll
see those are bad sounds those are bad
sounds those are bad
sounds there's
no okay
it's I it
again okay I say a PL change of plans
everyone go back home we
safe home is not safe right
now okay run home yeah run back home
pick up your backpack don't forget to
pick up your backpack I didn't we didn't
get our backpack it's gone does the
backpack Des spawn at some point I think
we need to craft some better weapons
before going in
adventure well it was still a nice
Adventure it was just
not was not a nice
Adventure there's blood everywhere no
it's it's nice
look
nice
okay is it interesting Sky coming up
Dawn upon
us okay we need a door is pink
outside did anyone find anything was
this like successful in any
way let's take it all press much it it's
all what did you find food that's good I
found we can make juice and some peas we
didn't find
anything what we not going to take
everything no I don't want to lose okay
I'm going back to the
other I'm home right now there's still
zombies out there let's make our own
wooden crate and put it downstairs in
our room and then nobody will get
confused
yeah
[Music]
uh-oh
arrows
arrows maybe range might be
nice
no
yeah and then we can put that
there put we should do them later maybe
maybe should do it sooner than later put
the stuff on it put the stuff on
it let's put the stuff on it quickly in
in what's going on behind me let's put
it in just put it in I don't know what's
going on over if if we're at home do you
guys want to go back to the main chat
the the where the main chat oh yeah the
main voice
chat went back okay that makes sense I
guess we do we'll do that in a second
quick did that work no no it didn't
work there go okay
okay broke through the
door the good news is I found
a oh really yes why did you get your
backpack why did you watch me
I or
something you just committing sex
no no I thought it was for the zombie oh
my God this guy has a lot of loot wow
done I don't have a me it was me was
composing I read your I read your
magazine you
read it's okay
I I find two more magazines I'll give
them to you I'll donate them no worries
no worries it's okay I have questions
yes how do
I
how I use an axe for
iron prob we have to find a rock and M
it
maybe beautiful is fine
junk I guess what are we looking
for do we have for
something cute frame oh I can make gr
for now I
got how can you make the grilled corn
baby I use a magazine to learn cooking
skill and now I have cooking skill
up I want to find a
magazine oh okay
I I need a cooking grill but if I if we
have a cooking grill I can cook the corn
I think there was a grill behind the
house leave the the cooking grill at the
fire so everyone can cook then yeah I
think the best way to go about the
magazines is probably to like share them
in the sense that like oh okay one
person does all the cooking one person
does this because otherwise you're not
actually going to level
anything I have I have two skill points
in cooking already so I guess I'll cook
she's going to be our cooker let
me I have coin I'll drop it give give me
your core and I will let's put them in a
chest the chest
people got the
coin I'm going to the farm if anyone
wants to come to the farm with me uh
come to vc2 I'm going to get materials
if someone wants to
come nothing oh okay where
was what's the
supposed to be punching corn do you
think yeah yeah punch the corn and then
you get it but but they have like not
dead corns for the green ones oh God
damn it yeah most of them are
dead that one looks alive oh thank God
did you say we had a cooking pot
somewhere no I didn't see it okay um
I'll leave my corn here although I am
hungry do we have to steal a cooking pot
or something yeah yeah it's necessary I
think we also need to find a source of
water and like to boil it with a
pot okay do you guys want to try going
to the oh my
God it turn out brand your magazines oh
really okay you can have them back here
I put them in this crate here are the
magazines something that anybody can
read or did they disappear afterwards
yeah they
disar I see thank I'm trying to survive
wait you know what [\h__\h] let's go in the
house I didn't mean to say
that I me oh
shoot you give it back this your
SM
together together the CL is better now
I'm
not okay I'll go with kie if anyone
wants to go Callie and I are going to
the
farm I'm not going to survive without
okay I'll go to the farm too oh my
goodness can you guys bring like food
and water I'm
dying let's make the stone and then
things will go faster food cornmeal you
can make
cornmeal is yeah and then you I have a
feeling we're going to lose all of the
resources around the
house how do
I how does one eat eat
show it's like you're learning how to be
human again
how does one get hungry where do I put
the
food I'm
learning looks important where
is what's up
here just let me know if you want to go
somewhere okay you see on the map I'm at
a gas I'm at a stiff tool
station who you're f
wow we should go to the trader and do
quest to though the trader gives a lot
of stuff oh you went
there yeah I went to the trader before
and he gave me a gun far one yeah it was
on the way on the
way I spawned quite South and that was
the trader it sent me to let's go back
to the house go there you think it's
safe to go alone to the Traer uh at
daytime it is after I explore this stiff
tool area I'll come to okay yeah I'll
join okay do we all have the Traer in
the same location though I think so
there okay okay should we go together
there's snowy
area I want my snowy area to be there's
a scary dog in there bright red alpha
eyes no do
ni all right I'm making sure our home is
up to base or up to code or whatever
thank you how do you repair
already you have to have enough wood
though do we have enough
doors oh nice we do have you can never
have enough doors
honestly I actually used doors to slow
them
down pretty pretty
good castle if
you
theow we can also make aor that would be
good for later see down down what do we
need for the torch yeah my bandages
thirsty I am also very hungry right now
yeah I'm surviving on corn I'm sick of
it I just don't know how not to be we're
sorry we commoners rep
how does one become hungry oh okay now
I'm very hungry I
guess you have learned a ways of the the
common folk ah yeah so this is how
hunger is yes
unfortunately don't
shovel
oh no I'm
hungry I am searching toilets don't
worry I'll find food can you find water
in there oh I found some water in the
toilet good oh no anything is
helpful you okay yeah we're trying to
get resources yeah we're trying to
help for the resources you can leave
them in a crate since we'll all be
sharing them okay if we get the cotton
plants then you can make them into
bandages and heal oh
F oh this is not good are you okay how
do you ever heal from an
infection
ohic just accept it do not get
infected you're dead now good to know
maybe you just have to have really good
hygiene and it goes away eventually I
don't
know some I have accepted this way of
Al I getting
yeah
okay I get all the
plants I don't know what they can be
used for but I have a feeling that
they're all
good maybe I can make more doors watch
out antibiotics and honey honey
honey
expensive do we have to kill them kill
the bees kill the Zombies yeah we have
to you a zombie
I know I feel like you
know that bad trying to the only answer
is
kill okay I'm going back home kill where
is home where is home where is home home
is on the map press I found
home thank
youi no problem when get scared Common
Sense CL of disappears
I hear
zombies let's go back in the house I'm
just killing one close the door it looks
like the weather is turning gloy oh oh
very yeah
okay a.m. or is it 7 half 700 p.m. in
the game I think 7 a.m. 7 a.m.
okay 24 hour clock okay
good e scary yeah know many of you guys
are SC that yeah they killed my family
how how can we make a farm that's so
unfortunate I I can make a bunch of SE a
magazine for that would be a better idea
yeah maybe the magazine you need to make
a farm plot block you need Rotting Flesh
for that how do I get rotting zombie
zombie yeah I so I think you have to get
the zombie and maybe if you destroy them
it's raining oh they're in another go
kill a zombie shouldn't be that hard to
find a zombie out in the rain like
this zombie
[Music]
zombie zombie zombie
zombie oh my character's
tired I thought you were a zombie
sh we almost got you just
[Music]
now
W zombie zom
there yeah be safe okay it's probably a
little bit scary right now down it is a
bit scary I am scared right now oh yeah
oh you guys can probably use a a spear
for the distance thank you did the
zombie tell us oh yeah oh yeah there you
go I think he's
still I was confused by the oh yeah SC
yeah I thought the zombie said oh yeah
oh yeah
there you go thank you let's get the
fles FL
FL no flesh FLH no flesh did I don't
think we got
FL how did I get FLH we got
hurt yeah do you get flesh from him
no maybe you got to maybe you got to
find it maybe you can't get it I'm not
sure how do I get FL we can go
Scavenging for it
this
way
zombies I think there's a town over here
I chest before destroying them we need
clay soil and R the flesh is
from dead bodies not zombies oh human
flesh deuses we need to find de
carcasses
is that our bag that must be our bag M
that's our bag from before let's go
should I get my bag we're close
0.1% what if there zombies let's just
grab it and go
great slow ah it's going I'm healing
myself with
honey how big nice honey works there's a
bunch of zombies inside if you guys get
Lon just look for um tree Stomps and
the get rid of the tree stomp get the
honey and then drink the honey
did what's that book is that a I don't
know why is this door so weird is there
any FL anywhere oh FL flush no get it
get it useless oh my gosh I I think we
got FL I think we got FL can you check
us this door I don't know I don't know
oh it's probably cuz it's this thing I
see
I think this is not the way to home yeah
there's the ho
really weird focus
on oh that was fun
yeah I need water I just Dr my the
[Music]
raining it's a beautiful day yay kind of
weak I guess I need to find fles let's
go find a deer carcass go along Let's
Travel towards the trader and then we
might be able to find a deer on the way
someone wants to come with me to the
trader oh go I'm going there right now H
where are you I'm at the
home we together okay let's put some
stuff I'm coming home I okay no I found
a
town I just make a put it all away and
then we'll take what we want
yeah I don't know what to do
here out the flush need to cook the
water Boozled they'll be like why is
there so
manys by the way there you
go
see I'll leave it here for now what's up
with the door why do we need it for
again for the land are we close I don't
think so
oh yeah stress crafting crafting Under
Pressure oh God
trees FL was for
planting okay okay we'll do that once we
get back we go with now okay we're going
to go out without I'm so close I'm so
close to home okay let's just F some
resources for now all right
oh this is a building
okay what are all these storage crates
are they all just like stuff that we can
call from other people probably yeah I
think everybody has their own little
storage crate for now okay I just put
the I put food in one storage crate
since we'll all be like
hungry so hungry we are starving
we should repair
our so
long seems like I can we have a lot of
rocks we can repair it right if you guys
go near the farm please collect more
corn
okay okay a pot yeah oh we can use
pot how are you cooking without a pot we
the crates let us know down down to do
you want to go
to V okay let's do it okay let's do
[Music]
it you're so big on my screen now very
cute where are
you I'm I'm um I'm I'm in the house
right now oh okay so where are you guys
we're just outside the house outside
okay I'm
coming outside we should have enough
time so I know where oh there we go
hello where you oh there you are oh
let's craft the spear yeah I'm going to
craft the spear oh okay I can also craft
Spears if you need okay can we craft
where is the spear Spears Spears a stone
spear Stone spear down down
down I don't have plant fibers I okay
give us 5 Seconds we got some take your
time to prepare don't
worry now
more in the me I'm going to put
missing oh I don't know oh there we
go okay mhm now we're ready okay good to
go give me
one
second
[Music]
MH should we put the on our map the way
point for the Traer and that way
hopefully we don't get lost okay I'm
ready is it the tra so the White River
citizen Trader yeah that person okay
let's go okay it's a little far away so
let's go let's go and
it's good it might be the other way
though let's just let's just try our
best I think it's a new advent yellow on
the
map it should take a little while but
yeah if we see a deer on the way that
would be helpful
too any sort of Rotting Flesh where' you
go there let stretch out zomies and if
it gets night I think we're going to be
okay but if it gets late or it starts to
rain we hide somewhere TR yeah yeah it's
not RK it if we notice any flesh let's
get flesh yeah oh yeah if you notice any
like cars to you check or some boxes
yeah let's get every materials we can
yeah oh yeah yeah also iron we're going
to need iron oh I I got a bunch of iron
earlier good job
yeah is important let's keep on moving
we're going to R out here it's okay
we'll plant don't worry don't
worries we have to keep moving oh
there's a car over there oh do we want
to head to the road let's go check it
out yeah oh there's a bunch of cars
there's water too we can we can go yeah
yeah it's okay I don't know if water is
glit
by should a whole house here
wow let's check out the other
cars I wish we could just use a car
right oh you found something yeah may we
got something from that we got some
flesh yeah yeah we got flesh yeah
awesome nice awesome okay we hear
some that sounds that sound sounds
zombie don't worry don't worry oh she
CWS just ignore it ignore it ignore it
yeah yeah yeah ignore it come come with
me it's better to run away from zombies
I think is smart yeah it's better to run
oh my gosh where did you go where' you
go I'm here I'm here I'm here you ninja
way yeah oh there you are okay yeah oh
my it's good it's it's
good I think it was so L it look very
impressive what is this oh wait there's
something cool here take take it take it
yeah let's hit
it oh do you do you want to attack this
too AIG is a
tiny I she has good stuffs we're getting
good stuffs I think where shiny it's
cool
yeah very good
to I never read a magazine I'm scared of
drowning you are
wet wet
dogs you when
you we're not really used to the water
too much we very fluffy and fuzzy so
it's not really the best we can barely
do a doggy
[Music]
paddle yeah you're probably better
suited for the water than us no no no I
don't like water you don't let's stick
to drinking water that house yeah
that'll be nice if we C there another
Farmhouse
corn
corn bodies on the road is there any
bodies on the road bodies on the road oh
oh oh that looks like a
garbage garbage bones bones bones should
be good what about the garbage next to
that is that no this is ground there are
two more cars here we can check it out
is there stuff in cars I never see stuff
in
cars this
where na
Forest where did go I'm here I'm here SK
without you I'm
[Music]
here oh that
was I'm here I'm here SC we thought we
heard
we found machete Parts machete parts and
electrical
traps that's cool electrical
trops and mushrooms boys
mushrooms I found a rotting fles yeah
fles is really helpful where are you
that oh I'm I'm right there let me find
you again okay we got split up a little
bit I think and I'm
scared let's check the car in the I come
to you
okay let's check the
car yeah
search Okay See's in the pickup truck
fuel fuel pumpkin
seeds take it take it take it take it
there's a Gun there's a Gun there's a
Gun there's a gun I got a
rifle awesome and now now is with us we
got a rifle yeah what can we do let's
go oh you got a gun A gun bullets though
so I'm going to save it for Emer my gosh
I think I have some mat for the
ammo wait where did you go I think D
likes to be in oh maybe it's just us no
maybe it's just us we just lose sight of
you we okay we can't wait really fast I
think I see some flesh on the road oh
yeah let good flesh oh it's just garbage
I think oh maybe if it's garbage well if
it's garbage it's garbage it's still
good oh it's garbage yeah oh there some
crushed sand CR H Parts okay
okay we're saying it's
helpful we're pretty close to where we
need to go yeah we're very close let's
keep on going where's let's go down down
there I think I think that was not not a
zombie okay good okay okay let's go over
the hill here let me get
this I need this feather for Fe for for
the arrows oh I see we have a bunch of
feathers oh yeah back at the house oh we
should all an arrow for you
then I just like I don't know what it's
for but feathers are cool I guess so oh
my God these Hills are steep they're
good at going up them yeah let's go
up we can see them maybe over the hill
here oh there's somebody on the
road oh yeah someone else is going to
broke my leg a that's not good there's
some other Shiny Rock over there
m i want to get back though I broke my
leg only we had a car or something what
is this this is another Co
walk stamina I'm going to continue on a
little bit of medication one second am I
bleeding
uhoh it's not a good sign with I didn't
mean to break my leg maybe the Traer
will have something for our
leg can we live at the Traders for a
little
[Music]
bit okay we're going to go on ahead a
little bit here cuz I'm worried I will
die before I get here yeah traitor I
feel safe here okay
is he kicks us out at night okay then we
better get in here my leg is broke a
your leg broke too broke leg
team me it here hello I that smirk off
your face one job we did he's in the
house here don't shovel let's complete
that I see
your my leg is
broken bued supplies yeah he has jobs
for us should we I guess we should take
them I don't
know my leg is still broken can can you
fix my leg for me he's a not a dog oh
here's stuff oh I have prob R he's can
of St a can of me have money will we
sell can we sell stuff to
him oh I guess we need money
huh oh I guess so w oh we have what we
have rocks we take
rocks okay so I got a quest did you get
a quest too a no not yet okay so if you
talk to them they're going to give you a
quest and we can do the quest together
okay that sounds good I knew you let's
get the quest the quest special job the
bued supplies I'm going make okay let's
accept it can't ref maybe give us
supplies okay that sounds good you're
going to need a shovel he gave us a
shovel thing
before let's make the shovel oh you're
right he did give
us okay we're ready to go now okay uh do
you have a shovel he gave us
one okay good it's raining outside
though I think oh yeah if it's raining
it's more dangerous so let's be careful
let's just close the door we could just
close the door interact with vending
machine vending machine has water oh my
gosh wait do we have money no
no what if we did that would be good
there so so much stuff
[Music]
here
a I don't know how can I fix my leg Yeah
I think we have to wait but I I noticed
it's an hour like 2 hours that we have
to wait right but it keeps on going back
up the more we use our
leg
so was was that right or wrong I think
was
by should we try digging outside his his
store yeah try to look around she right
door oh I don't
know try going outside M and digging a
little bit over there but here's
fine are we doing keep on diing out of
stamina keep on digging I'm
trying I unlocked something oh
really yeah I I think I
found like a magazine I think
really yeah but it was like it was like
an item that got um I got to use it I
don't know if it's one per player though
you can try
oh should go to one of those little
houses here and see if you can find it
too
okay let's see in a little hous is here
we still have skill points to unlock and
it wasn't a luggage it wasn't a um
yellow lugage houses let's see a yellow
luggage if you can find it then it was
one purle here
okay it was in here in the previous
house I don't know we didn't this one
one but if you cannot find if you cannot
see it then it was just one okay yeah
maybe it was just one then let's check
out our skill points and unlock
things it's not ring anymore good
nothing uh okay let's
see
[Music]
skills I really like cooking
being able to be a doctor would be a
good
[Music]
idea I would like to be able to
cook especially you know we both have
broken legs right now may we should try
[Music]
fortitude fortitude I think is measure
of your physical resilience healing
healing healing could be good
how many I have four
points let's do
that how do I get this do you have any
Glue
by no I've never seen glue I I got blue
glue but it's on my it's it's a home and
probably we can fix the legs if we use
the glue I see by crafting something
else we'll see you later yeah let's get
the C
[Music]
one second I want to see
stuff harvesting more crops that could
be good
too we want to we want to do crops right
it's coming fast it's good is there like
broken too it's broken okay so I think
we can what we can do is we wait two
hours our our sprting or jumping going
to heal cuz before it wasn't healing
like it heal a little bit and then it
get bad again but now I see it's only an
hour and 37 minutes for us and maybe
that's because we haven't been running
around as much yeah maybe you shouldn't
if you don't run
around show he it's a long
time I think we should get
card I wonder hours in game I think so
though is it takes a little while we
have two points still
available double the
harest we need to find a hours in real
life oh no oh two hours is 2 hours oh oh
no that's not
fair okay look walk slowly yeah
oh my yeah I'm watching our our tracker
might be good our bones and it does seem
to change with real time
passage that's not
nice w wow we need to make SPS
apparently and we need
glue if you can find glue
I like to kind of look around together
with as we head back I
think should we we need to finish the
quest first what is the quest again
[\h__\h] so it should be um can you see
your on the top of your screen there is
like an exclamation mark and it's yellow
you should go there okay
okay I'm trying to there's none
yeah we're digging there yeah I don't
know I thought that I could find
something here but maybe
[Music]
not okay I'm going for the Miss isn't
selected right now oh it's
not exclamation there's a bunch of stuff
do you see
it head to Rally
Point I don't see it on our map no oh
okay maybe 38
you got the quest right we got the quest
okay okay I don't see it in our map at
all okay let me check it out oh yeah um
can you try to uh press Tab and next
[Music]
to the cup there should be like a quest
mark which is an exclamation
mark we have that yeah it says
objectives head to the rally point it's
in the map let's check the map again
maybe we just really bad reading Maps
which is pretty
accurate I wonder if if we have
different quests what's our it was a
what was it called ah here it is oh it's
really far
away it's not as gray it's gray I don't
know why it's gray it's hard to see is
pretty close May
Tex okay well let's head over there then
I think it's the same Quest it's the
intro to
something my quest is um how to really
point oh uh oh let's see is that the
same intro bur yeah yeah the objective
is to head to the r point it's the same
let's head there together except it's
raining now it's raining we'll just have
to be careful maybe I come with you
don't worry yeah if we're together it
should be okay
I'm just right outside the Trader's
place oh I found some glue really yeah
but just one oh there you go can you see
me yeah W that's a big W it's 5:15 in
game oh it is it is it's 5:20 now oh is
it getting dark it's going to get late
soon so we should have back
or he's going to kick us out of this so
we can't stay in there so okay what we
can do is should we walk back go back
home let's go back home we can come back
in the daytime tomorrow go back home we
can do that in time yeah let's go yeah I
don't have much
stamina me neither so we go slowly let's
go a follow let me let me do theck Point
yeah let's go
okay one km away we're going to have to
do oured
uh okay if maybe I have a gun I wouldn't
use
it not on
me I don't I did kind of think about
that the moment we got it
what oh when um when we arrive home uh
we're going to we're going to build some
splints for for us for that sounds good
yeah is this the right way
yeah this is the
way where go no we're really bad at
Direction don't worry I'm
[Music]
the okay just be careful here yeah
falling was a mistake huh yeah set up
the
map I think we can do before night so be
careful here
be bad if we broke both
legs
no we're not making
a this is a really beautiful house here
yeah
actually invaded or something
maybe that' be nice I'm going to I'm
going to write this on the on the map on
the map so I come back to y yeah I think
it's a nice big home it looks like
there's a farm too it looks well kept
yeah yeah we should go back later maybe
right well we're going to have to finish
that Quest off right let's just make it
home time if you set up your map then
it'll be easier and if if we get
separated from that we'll still be able
to make it for home oh don't worry I can
find it don't worry okay okay it's 6:15
in
game when the sun set I don't know
is that our home no it's far it's far
it's still pretty far away like 800 M
away oh yeah oh 22 22 is night time oh
okay so we might be okay might not be
okay let's
see I like this car this car had the gun
in it yeah I think there's a lot good
items to be had around here yeah it's a
lot to explore right if we can go maybe
in the morning right when it's bright
out oh yeah we can go in the morning to
go complete the quest and in the
meantime we explore around right that's
a good
idea yeah I think we went little we need
to fix our our legs first yeah that
first and then make sure that we don't
break down
[Music]
likea is getting scared it's okay
don't worry M we we got this I going to
protect
you I think my leg is doing worse than
yours a yeah we get tired much faster
you okay worst case we can okay we can
kill each other and we're going to fix
the
S don't worry don't worry the zombie
ignore them okay ignore them I think
they might be faster than us with me got
this okay
halfway
okay we get tired quickly a quicker the
[Music]
hung go slowly it's
okay okay if we cannot fix the leg we
kill each other at home and that's a
good idea I don't want to drown
here let's cat your bre before we go in
the water
I'm let's
go out of
[Music]
stamina this is it for me this is it for
me I can't breathe here no you can't
come here come
okay water is scary water
dangerous got it is that a box oh box
box box Bo what's is something
trash I found a tape we can do the a
tape like a VHS tape yeah okay like a
duct duct tape is that better than
glue yeah like now we can make the um
stuff for your leg wait let me try to do
it now
okay um what was the name again
um one second ni we're
watching okay oh I can make it no wait I
need do you have cloth fragments oh yes
cloth fragments oh we did have cloth
fragment I can make we can make them yes
please okay one second it's taking me a
moment I need like four of them I have
more than four thank you do you want do
you need eight
yes okay we can
make okay we're good now oh no it's
getting really dark oh no it's raining
okay one second one second one second
okay yeah take your time take your time
I'll get you the items I'll drop them
okay rocket I dropped them dropped them
thank you and then if can make those and
we can patch ourselves up then we back W
I thought you said it gets dark at 22:00
it is not even 20 it's so
raining okay I made one you you the
first one oh thank you how do I get it
okay there we go okay use use
use
[Music]
use nice okay I'm going to make one for
me too
okay more CL fragment it's okay let's go
more we have more we have more we have
more I can make more you have more okay
I have 10 more 10 10 more yeah 10 more
okay okay you
want it take a little bit of time but
I'm making them wa oh thank you good
thing I picked up all the cotton you
know yeah I thought it were come in
handy thank you
for we can make it back okay now we have
okay I'm going to drop it okay we got we
got it thank you so much okay make it
okay
don't worry don't worry go home now okay
y
I'm let's go home okay nice
no let's make sure not to break any more
legs no more breaking
legs let's go I'm scared I make it
back very close we going to be home
before night time okay and if you see
zombie don't worry keep running okay
it's it's good if you have
stamina I usually like thunder but not
when there's zombies and thunder no not
a f we need to find some food when we go
home yeah
[Music]
before we go in the water let's get
stamina there's a river be careful can
you do that yeah I'm going to wait until
I have enough stamina across okay take
your time I wait for you okay let's go M
no no no I'm going to wait no let's go
let's go M
okay scary with the
Thunder 21 17
39 okay just meet
it I'm happy that we finally the
like that was lucky that it was in there
huh
right
ohina oh it's dangerous to swim in the
Thunder is it we're very close to
home Okay home
home I can't wait to make it through
those doors
careful should we put away this bear
what is this
us I can't
help soon okay follow the road and we
shall drive home okay okay yeah she
already asked us to get corn we didn't
get corn but we got a gun gun better
than corn better than
corn I got some flesh
too we want
yeah I can't remember why we wanted the
flesh anymore for farming for
farming
there's okay let let's go back to thec
with okay and and tomorrow we go explore
more yeah sounds good
[Music]
wa we're
back hey welcome
back has home been good
home has never been
better we almost didn't make it
back let's cook the eggs let's cook the
eggs we don't have our eggs let's go
cook our
eggs oh yeah do we have a cooking pop
now it seems like we
do yeah yeah nice and I have gas can
too treasure yeah we got a gun too
yeah let's put it all in
there water oh I guess we need can we
boil that the mky water maybe maybe we
should boil that yeah yeah do we have
any mky water oh what about that what
about that what about that with this no
that's water that's our water yeah
should we drink that we're
thirsty we have water should drink it
can you do you know how to cook the
spoiled
meat spoiled fles um if it's spoiled is
probably not a good idea hello no rotten
rotten flesh Maybe not maybe maybe not I
don't think so rot fles can only be used
for farming maybe I like oh farming yeah
we looking for it where did I put
the what should I do
I have
an okay I'll just put it right here we
need
[Music]
the can't make it yet can't make it yet
oh that's right I wanted to find the
cotton how do I
bam oh we need to Sweet the solent
farming
magazine
oh disappointment sick how do I find a
magazine why is there dubstep okay
what's going on
there can I find a
magazine mailboxes okay um I think it's
dark now it made a ominous sound yeah
it's night time now why I got to keep
dying I I he hising I I watch
hising I hear zies here are they outside
the
door hey can you guys boil some water
um maybe not right
now are they at the
door where are they no not yet I think
zomie we hear some very scary sounds
it's okay don't worry I the door now
they break it down the door think
no iak the door
down a
darn uhoh well I go fight them well too
late your best oh
go
up okay it's okay it's okay spe spe
probably
not I'm using my other don't have
stamina is safer I don't think so I
don't know if outside is safer it's not
safer it's not safer everybody they need
to be here to protect us fun I don't
have stamina for this we
[Music]
at
home beting
[Music]
my back spawn on my bed uh is let's do
on my bed and see what
happens on my bed oh maybe I shouldn't
have spawned on my
bed
bad look we have weapons in our
box take out the weapon spear spear
spear Stone axe you want the stone axe
what about the spear
uh
doesn't can we we have the item on I uh
I it's l
i I um I would help but I don't have
anything we just going to wa on top our
bed we're going to wait on top of our
bed and attack when they are here yeah
we have the upper ground yes we have to
top BP Advantage
yeah oh no use the spear not the axe oh
god oh no there's a spear spear go
timear I got the spear okay I think out
is safer now H bunk
Advantage it's bu is BU get off the top
get off the top but you not allow Ste
the bottom
B the bunk is open maybe a knife would
think he's done oh yeah I have a
KNE much better much better that's not
good our bed's getting all dirty we it
later oh no everybody's dying
oh come on that's all part of the
process I wanted to survive all the
seven days okay I I think it's time if
you want to come and Us in the bunk bed
oh he disappeared I thought he was
starting to move again the bunk is a
good place to
be oh we could put some like stones in
front of it I can't see where I'm going
oh think upstairs when did the zombies
go away
whoa 8 a.m. 8 a.m. dying is so much
better I hope this sh ends at 8 a.m.
yeah I feel like where is everybody else
they should have been protecting
home criticizing
everybody protecting the house you know
night time go back home protect the
[Music]
loser here we are was protecting the
base by hiding protecting the
hey
the from the top of the bunk from the
top of the
bunk what the
heck baby oh no ding now it is
dying just want to cook
[Music]
mys put more CL there still not here yet
I have one can i e
how it's quiet now oh now it's
not I didn't make it downstairs maybe
they're not very good at the stairs I
want my top bunk Advantage I do like it
top bunk plus be is a good combo yeah
rip other people
yeah yeah level
two let's spend the skill points while
everybody else is
there piano being played bad uhoh what's
bad the let's build the door M take out
our sticks let's take out our sticks and
build a door oh okay maybe I made the
door we have no sticks where did the
sticks go oh I think I carried them with
me you do
that oh it's upstairs okay the sticks
are on our
Bo oh oh I can like that that's
cool oh is friendly fire on can you
attack me yeah ow okay thank you can we
fix let's close the door I'm dying how I
fix it up how do I repair the door go go
into the actually no this is a good idea
ra come back
here can you kill me of course it's my
pleasure kill me ah yes
this one double door oh we don't need a
double door just a wood door
sorry no thank
you that way I can be completely cured I
did that mistake I'm placing the
door that's
okay is that how do work all right there
we go I don't know if that's the right
kind of door
huh oh I need to repair
my
axe that's kind of effective click with
the ax
on right click with the
ax just need one more
oh let's break the door oh I fixed
it what what what are we doing here no
no yes what what are youing you doing
I'm breaking this door oh cuz it's kind
of a funny door because I
[Music]
misplaced really
I I can't get in the house now I help
out
that
finally okay there go the door look at
that someh let's reinforce the other
doors
maybe we should try to make like let me
check if that is
like oh this door we can put a door this
door is that's a door yeah no that has a
door let's put doors everywhere door
going to fix everything I want to fix
everything now can we fix the windows
coffee
maker yummy we have coffee seeds so the
fact that we have a coffee maker means
that there's a possibility coffee could
be consumed at some point which is an
exciting thing to maybe I should just oh
I chill out for a bed office
tower well maybe our our door is okay
yeah think this is my
bed yeah yeah this is my
bed we should put a door there can we
put a door there I know that I'm
infected but uh oh you're infected do
you want me to kill you
no are you
sure it's okay you can just ask I can
kill you do you want to do you want to
kill me I'm
okay that's your only desire in your
life I can make it I don't have any
desires
well in that case I'll keep my life for
now okay let me know when you don't want
to live
anymore I'll tell you when my time
comes okay that's
good let me just take some of my stuff
okay oh it sounds bad yeah I think we
should probably get the door going there
m what door the door that you just
ruined because I wanted to put a door on
our room yeah I don't think we can yeah
we can you just put it wrong you sure
yeah I told you to spin it around you
can spin it around how spin it around
I'm not sure you can figure no it's
still not make a door you made a door
okay good good
good no no no no no no no now it's wrong
it was good for a second yeah yeah yeah
there you go that's a good door oh dead
oh
oh well it happens I guess everybody has
their
moment see and now we're even more
protected
yeah door let's put a more doors in
other places go done like a door over
there you know lots of hiding spots
doors
oh there's a door there too there's a
lot of doors that we didn't even know
about this is door this could be
repaired can you repair this door it's
dark how do I make it brighter in here
wow it's so dark at night if we had a
lamp
fire can we do anything with the fire
fuel fuel turn on turn
on do I have to give it wood put it into
the
yeah much
better uh I'm trying to level up M I
don't understand how that work
yeah let's go take a look at
our open the
door um which one's stronger a
sledgehammer or a spear Sledgehammer but
spear has distance but sled hmer if it's
a big one it has distance
[Music]
no
so I want the skill for
[Music]
seeds yeah I want to get better the
do what why am
I breaking things faster oh SL time is
very good
then let's use a torch it's really
scary are you are you
okay are you
okay I'm good now okay I'm glad you
your it's horrible outside it's raining
too
we haven't went upstairs M should we go
upstairs
theer do we not have any more
sticks Maybe not maybe not we can oh you
got to punch for more let's fix things I
want to fix
things should probably fix can I try
fixing it's not why is everyone dying
out of six I don't know maybe they're
fighting something check our inventory
kind of want to go to the snow area
but Castle there yeah there's a castle
there yeah maybe it would be a good
place to take over but I'm not sure if
it's worth
it I see
well maybe this is
where I go to bed for tonight and we'll
see you all tomorrow tomorrow
yeah we going to our for now oh
yeah hopefully P the door and hopefully
yeah everything work so cute
yeah oh good
[Music]
look hope you
survive yay I will see you tomorrow for
more s Days to
Die by
w wow it was really fun I really like
surviving together with everybody
hopefully we can find some more
magazines I want to make seeds why yeah
I want a farm yeah there's still lots of
unknowns a lot of skill points to gain
and spend and finish that Quest I want
to the farm yeah but I'm sure that we'll
come back tomorrow
and Tau a lot and learn want to I want
theity
yeah and it was really fun to
to thank you so
much looking forward to tomorrow
too wow is joining us in the archive
[Music]
today cold where it is bowow rot in FL
by thank you so much we see you
byee
[Music]