[Music]
a
I
[Music]
k k
KY
hello
[Music]
hello hello
hello uh excuse Mo I am not late you are
late or you are too early you you should
have F you should have you should have
known you should have uh what's the word
you should
have you should have not guessed what's
the word you should
have yes
M you yes you should have anticipated
exactly that I would come at this exact
time my cats have been zooming right now
they've been uh but they're I think
they're about to calm down H
[Laughter]
hello um um welcome to another week of
November uh it's yes it is November um
but it's still Halloween did you hear
that yes
movie go
D where are you where are you I heard
you behind me I don't see you where did
you go where did you go are you ah she's
on the top of my
bookshelf
meow
[Music]
nonstop is there a word that that's like
cuddling but that starts with N
nonstop ni nonstop ni November n nuzzle
really nonstop nuzzle the nickel
November nonstop nuzzle
nivember n n vember let's make it better
nuk is yes meow did you hear that she
keeps on meowing
I she already got uh her wet food today
and she already got um lots of cuddles
and she already got a a snack a a
slurpie snack you know the the the um
the liquid ones so yeah both chunkers
and smoothie yeah yeah so they're
excited right now
this song should be my intro
[Music]
song God no
please no God no
the only thing I can think of is um the
office when I when I hear someone write
something like that in
caps oh I can think of it was the
office love the office okay
we're going to play uh Alice today but
I'm not planning on finishing it today
we're just going to do like four hours
or something apparently see now it says
playtime 6 hours and 20 minutes with 37
completion that looks much better than
last time uh but uh official according
to Google the the play length of this
game recently I like looking these
things up is about 14 hours which is
pretty accurate that you guys told me I
have about 8 hours
left I think I'm not even that slow
because considering how how much time
I've been taking for these games I think
it's always been pretty accurate which
means I'm an average
gamer who takes up about as much time
for games as it is officially
anticipated yes yes yes yeah I'm a
gamer even though I mess up the controls
so much and around so
much yeah average gamer kiaha journalist
gamer
kiaha uh let me let me put this into a
position that looks good to me me oh
today we finally have enough time again
to chitchat and stuff if I don't rage
too
much you Tak Mya actually I made myself
like darker for like these kind of
Darker horror games and stuff but the
contrast of this game it's like overall
is still pretty bright so I guess it's
not even
necessary well anyway let's see no
[Music]
no Shadow
kiar oh welcome back oh my God what's
going on oh yeah this is where we
stopped it's like oh the world is
falling apart no problem I'll take a
break let's continue next
week this by the way seems to be a hint
because um I was like looking back on
the on the archive
um because I didn't know what to write
into my title so I tried to recall what
happened and uh
uh that that dude who was like giving us
a performance he was talking about uh
the caterpillar being able to help us
and the caterpillar what does the
caterpillar smoke guys do you guys
recall yes it is a what What's this
called again I forgot a hook
hookah a hookah yeah a hookah yeah so I
think this is a hint that next up is the
cat I mean it's not really a hint I
guess we already know at this point but
yeah caterpillar coming for
you what do I do they just want me to
jump into the
void no wait what's up there is that not
where I came
from from up
there wait what the
oh the bomb he did you just guys see
that my stream was dead for a moment I
find that interesting because we had the
same thing yesterday it calmed down
later
on there we go wait no I'm not ready for
that I missed something up here or wait
is this how where I continue
we're back we're back yeah yeah yeah
welcome back I don't know why but it
might happen again um Don't Run Away
guys wait I need I need to like I I lost
my sense of
orientation isn't this where we came
from or I guess
not I have to go up here so if if I
activate this thing here I don't
suddenly disappear
right again what you're back okay well
let's
see Journey Of A Thousand Miles begins
with a single step a single step off
London Bridge could end my journey as
your EP I'd hoped you were more
courageous what okay so me smoking the
hookah created is this even real is this
not just an my imagination it is real
apparently I mean what even is like
nothing of this is real of course but oh
hello H yeah
okay I want to get up
there wait a second we got to do really
good platforming hereit
wait I want to use that air uh stream in
order to get up there
them but how ah come
back how do I get up
there yes yes
yes
B yeah I knew I could do it I knew it
they didn't think I could do it but I
knew
it I know I can glide but I need my I
need the height when I Glide I lose
height and okay there he comes yep my
timing was just bad oh look at those
let's destroy them from
here game game froze for a
moment I have the giveaway winners by
the
way uh so I will let you know I guess in
a moment when everyone's
here are you guys all
here I will let everyone know on Twitter
as well afterwards
though smoke the
hookah so much for straight edge Idol
only appears as flimsy and in as your it
will oh okay nice nice hooka thank you
caterpillar
son did I ask you guys before who's your
favorite Alice character like Alis
so Alis in Wonderland who's your
favorite character did I ask you that I
feel like I did but I don't remember
answers why is the game so laggy
today jabber walkie cat the Mad header
mad header oh very very popular chest
cat yeah I love the chest shy cat too I
agree why are you missing Alice why are
you missing can I just not reach him
from here oh come
on sh cat Mad
Hatter the Red Queen ah she cray she
cray
cray you like crazy people is that why
you also like
me crazy ladies that are mad with power
H have seen that somewhere before
H okay I was supposed to go from here
obviously I I think that hurts yep I
shouldn't stand on that
oops I need those TW tee though thank
you I do love my crazy
tant I'm not even that crazy if you can
compare me to someone like I don't know
hatama right I mean I'm pretty tame I
would
say another lag why is it so laggy today
h
n you do you guys see that too or is it
just on my side the game just like
freezes for like a tiny moment is it
only on my
side you you guys see it too okay then
at least it's fair that um if I fail I
can I can say it's because of the
lag it's the Ping it's the
Ping not sure why it's freezing it it
did that in previous streams as well but
what is that that's kind of
sus but over here we have something too
but not as much as
today is my PC too weak is that what
you're telling
me it's the Ping oh oh the long table
where they have a
tea is that their version of it and is
this my new weapon what's go oh teapot
Cannon done you have just obtained The
Mad Hat manufacturing ink teapot Cannon
never seen before automatic steam
exhaust cap brand new clock face
pressure meter uh shoots devastating tea
grenades throw an instant tea party it
will be a blast ah
funny okay how to use this house is
different from the other stuffff the
teapot Cannon is highly effective
against groups of enemies oh even those
nice okay the longer a shot is
charge the larger the blast radius will
be oh
oh all the teapot Cannon can be used to
demolish weak
surfaces surfaces at range
oh but it seems like um am I wrong or
are there like the weapons are pretty
like um in inter
interchange was that the right word like
uh for example it just said that I can
use it to blow up some surfaces but that
also works with the with the normal um
uh bump the time ticking bump so you
don't you can just use whatever you like
the most I suppose yeah the only game
that the only thing that's uh really
like you need it
100% for certain things is like for
example the umbrella to block certain
things cuz there's nothing else to block
it
with for example I would
say those aren't
ranged this one has range as opposed
to well I mean these two for example
like I guess the teapot Cannon just
combines the bomb with the pepper
grinder somehow and switch between
pepper grind and teapot Cannon by using
Mouse scroll up left shift both or evil
one
let
uh wait a second wait what what what
what
what oh wait ah okay ignore ignore that
with the wow I love it I have
it ignore the uh scroll up that didn't
really work oh why you shoot so far far
oh nice
nice ski ski ski holy I'm going to
use that a lot I think
uh-oh
shoot does it lose focus every time I
shoot something no ow ha hey oh do I
need my stupid umbrella again oh I I
don't know how to use it oh there we go
shoot ow wa why did that not work why is
that not working why is that not
working n the Domino
no too early ow okay
the game
froze
no he's heing me let me out
damina
[Music]
I
oops oh my
God boom
boom he doesn't really care much about
the bump now stop stop stop stop stop
stop oh this battle is going pretty well
so
far even though it's just warm up
time
ow oh
oh I hit the last base I
[Music]
think flamethrower oh he must be
streaming Sparks every day oh my God
stop it stop it holy
oh oh nice nice I stopped
him okay when are you going to die it's
a
wow he's
tough no stop stop stop stop stop stop
please okay okay okay okay ah I get it I
get it whenever he does the flame ther
it needs me to stop him with the bomb or
something yo how defensive are
you okay
okay dead shinda okay
okay okay okay
wow
wow fun can I already upgrade it how
many do I have 170 that's nothing oh
damn I definitely want to upgrade this
one next I like using it
e
e a boom
boom half few blows hit his body not his
head
oh yeah I wonder if that did no damage
at
all well I'm focusing on him why I don't
know why if I focus on him it still only
hits his body then what else can I
do teapot is op hell yeah it freaking is
I love
[Music]
it okay
hit boxes are weird yeah yeah I agree
all right we got
uh oh yeah quite a bunch of people you
guys want to hear the names now of the
winners winner winner chicken
dinner want to hear
it yeah okay well uh it was R honestly I
I just really randomly selected the
names while also
um uh checking if if you guys uh
followed the rules and if you include
and everything like the URL and the love
dodo keyword and also uh I may or may
not have also paid attention to uh if
you literally just put love dodos at URL
or if you actually wrote and a text with
it and those might have had priority
soit one
second you were chosen and and
handpicked by my very precious hands
and I will let you uh guys also know on
Twitter separately but so far H winner
number one uh
azamor BG number two that's score lame
Boy AKA edifier number uh
two uh redout 27 uh aka the modular Matt
yeah yeah yeah uh number three BB braa
AKA braa and number I forgot the number
four five and that RWBY 736 AKA droy
number six7
Wonderland cat six AKA Chris and next up
is vpin fre AKA
warpin and next up is Kane
not
yt1 AKA Kane and then we have H ANB
live
aable AKA UMB one second is this wait a
second wait a second wait a second wait
a second one 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 yeah and
the last one is quic uh k w h e i n i c
congratulations sorry for everyone who
got who didn't get chosen but 10 10 is
actually quite a lot so H yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah thank you guys for
participating in the giveaway I'm glad
we could do it and honestly I want to do
another will give away of something
anything at some point um for you guys
especially because Christmas is coming
closer uh so yeah there were a lot of
participants indeed yes yes yes yes
thank
you I was glad that you guys were so
interested in it thank
[Music]
you so that was 10 people who will be
contact contacted by Al uh Alice by
American Magie um so please make sure to
follow him I think I saw uh um I checked
most of uh most of you guys's uh follow
follows uh a lot of you already followed
him so um just to make sure that you can
receive his DM uh follow him if you
don't do it if you're not following him
yet
okay no d m from me we'll get a DM from
Al Alex America Mickey and and
everything will be handled uh from their
side uh after after that okay
congratulations
yay h no no unfortunately Alice isn't
real let me eat a strawberry actually I
got berries with me I got uh blueberries
and strawberries with me a
snack what she isn't
what
M yum yum yum I love
berries I would eat berries like every
freaking day if they wouldn't like be so
how to
say E
sus if if they wouldn't be so fragile
you know they they go up so quickly
especially if they're just from some
shitty
Supermarket then the quality is always
so low what is
this can I
oops
uh oh see I didn't even try
to charge it
before Oh my God look at what that
does can I go lower does it
matter hey what is
this can I break
this I can only hit the top for some
reason no I don't think I can do
anything even though it's
uh I don't know seem to have some kind
of
effect hit him yeah
baby
yeah
nice EX explosion get that
hookah y yum kill enemy first I think
you need to defeat enemies uh-huh uh-huh
okay I'm devastated look what's become
of my beautiful Valley your beautiful
Val the fullness of time often not for
better I don't want to go up yet one
second I got some stuff to do
here
oh
Overkill and uh how do I open these
again with bombs or is my knife uh good
enough all oh yes it
was the more you charge it the higher
the Arc of the projectile
ah well oh that's so
cool oh I love it I love it P
got another freeze weird
was this one is Ah that's the same as
before right okay now that I killed the
enemies now it lets me through
oh okay recover May strike even
bestes of course one family's disaster
May
another and the same goes for a
surviving family one family disaster may
be a another family's
opportunity that sounds to me like some
some Desperate Housewives
[Laughter]
well maybe I'm just watching too
much of that wait I missed something
down there I miss something oh now I can
kill
you
why
why maybe more Game of Thrones ah true
as well yeah yeah that applies to that
too but it doesn't sound like something
that applies to real life only to those
kind of dramatic shows
oh
die who's shooting me who was that oh
big boy oh I mean slightly big
boy die eat this
bum here let's play catch what your dad
never played cats with you that's okay
I'm I'm your daddy now
ah or is this the guy that I have to
fight with uh umbrella usually can I do
it
without I feel like I got the upper hand
in this fight
dude oh if it weren't for
the
yes if it weren't for the freezes man
I was too cocky okay he's dead oh
remember guys how much trouble I had
with that enemy
before now it went much better
wow oh my God another thre should I
restart the
game weapon upgrades perhaps
I can't kill that now can
I what a battle music are you guys
hearing
this the battle music oh my God it's
like so intense right
now holy I love this
teapot yo
I love the
teapot SK SK kunuk
ski can I reach this did it drop
anything no what do I kill those for I
mean they're already dead but who whoa
what do I not sometimes drop
something explosives are awesome hell
yeah hell
yeah what the hell okay I'm going to
restart the game
but uh
when when's the last time i'
saved
uh
maybe
wait was there like a little icon coming
up on the screen whenever it saves I I
don't
remember it allo saves wait for the save
icon okay if you guys see it let me know
was it like bottom right
something restart doesn't help yeah who
knows it might it might you know do you
know those people who always say have
you tried restarting it have you tried
restarting it yet turning it off and on
again on and off again or whatever he
fell down hey come back I'm not done
with
you oh yeah
a oh
use the teot Canon at range to break the
wall which
wall behind me or
something 92% of tech support
yeah make them go
boom
M very nice so far today like I don't
know why but I'm feeling the controls
today even though it's been a while
usually when I didn't play a game for a
couple of days you guys know me I'm
usually crap at it oh freeze again can
I can I do something about
this everybody sick this month e cool
you
guys I'm fine I'm never sick for some
reason I don't know why my my immunity
system is that is that even what you
call it in English I'm too strong my
body is too
strong every stream is like experiencing
a game for the first time
exactly the flu season is above us upon
us oh
no I did I come from here cuz it wants
me to go that way but I didn't pick up
everything here yet
right wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait immune system yeah yeah yeah don't
jinx it no really like I'm too strong oh
wait from the other side yeah
in Japan they say if you don't ever
catch a flu or something like that you
are an
idiot I don't know what the logic behind
that is wouldn't that kind of make you
smarter for like staying away from sick
people and taking care of
yourself anime logic yeah
sick people are just too
salty I always get sick when going to
Japan oh that might be just because
you're not used to the uh oh my a what
to the surroundings okay how to F oh I
his shield explode nice oh my oh
oh wait I kind of wanted to fight the
teapot but oh well that's okay holy
combat let's go
time
War
there can't catch
me it's
eyeball that's a
delicacy lick AB
ball boom head
shot who's shooting me you're so far
away how did you even see me o no no no
no no I just arrive give me a moment
chill oh lag
lag
uh
W oh baby
yeah it's going too smoo
today black can't stop
me
yeah it was also a twice song that says
the title is can't stop me now I think I
love that song so many twice songs that
uh sum up my feelings I love it
yeah he did oh wow my gameplay is solid
today I don't know what's going on what
did I do to
kiaha what did I do to
kiaha oh yeah I sang it in kiok
before who am I oh
lag I don't know when it saves I want to
restart one time H but I don't want to
redo this battle
so o is that part of a train
station why song cover no that ain't
happening rights my friends rights
copyrights but on archived stream yes
yes yes yes is that me
looks like me okay um in the hopes that
I won't lose anything I will
restart wait restart restart in in this
manual means restarting the game I don't
believe it doesn't mean restarting this
level you were looking for ways to get
banned so here's
your not like that I don't want it to
happen like that okay wait main menu all
unsaved progress will be lost so then
let me save it
please oh
[Music]
well oh dear why are you showing
this okay no
problem
origin origin
sure very bright were you blinded guys
you were so blinded you couldn't see it
anyway right there was nothing that you
shouldn't be seeing anyway it's okay no
problem
G oh spicy
horse strawberry
[Music]
I'm so
happy that even in November I'm still
getting good strawberries these are from
Italy by the
way yeah thank you Italy a I love you
Italy
Italy thank you oh
[Music]
holy those are good why are these
so good it's often when you out of
season
it where am I
how far did that bring me
back looks like pretty
far no but I already have uh the
teapot one
puzzle oh
man well better be no lag now
now oh I was saying I was saying yeah
when when certain fruit or whatever are
out of
season chances are that if you buy them
anyway they're going to be
disgusting but these are so good yummy
also the blueberries as well and
blueberries hold up much longer than I
thought they would in the fridge
yummy I love fruit so much I love
berries which is maybe why I was such a
huge fan of Betty's cobal
no yeah that is just me and my wishful
thinking and my logic which is
non-existent I'm devastated what's
become of my beautiful Valley all things
change in the fullness of time often not
for
[Music]
better you and M should cover a very
strong for a moment I was like what do
you
mean do I know something that do you
guys know something that I don't that
she's a B's cobal and that would have
made my day but I guess you're just me
because m is always all about
berries
unfortunate would have been nice if I
had a fellow hello project fan but like
overseas no chance whole life Japan
members I feel like I can definitely
find hello project
fans for example of one dis I mean I
don't think K the Senai is such an
active and same goes hello project fan
anymore I also moved on but I just want
to you know
reminisce REM remin remin what what was
that remines about the good
old hell project terms I was a different
person back
then like in a lot of
ways no I was just I was so young
too uh of course still young am still
young I'm still
young you again okay uh will I this
fight up this
time
no okay maybe I will wait a second
[Music]
wait I want to kill him first he annoys
the hell out of me see I can even switch
Targets in the middle of a battle right
now what's
happening k is in
control
oh
oh I'm winning ow okay shut up shut up
do I need to stop your mouth
uh left or
right let me just get those
boxes unboxing live
unboxing what's the matter with you
but I think there's less freeze now than
before I felt one freeze uh a moment ago
but besides
that feels better than
before don't jinx it kihan don't jinx
it don't jinx
it oh I jinxed it
yeah well the freeze ain't got nothing
on
me give me
heart okay this is it is what it is
today that's okay it's manageable I
guess cuz I'm just that op today nothing
can stop me
ah
[Music]
nice
nice nice shot baby let
okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
okay don't fall
down any plans for vice shs unboxing no
no no no not planning on
it
actually I was pretty surprised
uh like I
don't really have any connection with
Vice rats uh except for it being a
German name
uh but my best friend she's a huge fan
like she plays Vice trats and I totally
forgot about that um so the vice trates
cards got revealed and cuz I forgot that
my best friend was a fan of it I forgot
to tell her and then eventually she
found it herself and she was like yo H
life got best R cards now and I'm like
oh yeah right yeah yeah yeah
yeah wait do Vice schwarts cards always
get released in English as well I wonder
if these whole live vs cards are
Japanese only
recently yes nope not at all usually
usually later oh I hope she can get
them but I mean there's no was there was
there even a whole live English card I
forgot I think even if they were like
the generic uh standing picture the
promotional picture one
taking care of two enemies at one
actually more than that
even y
y oh he's mad the one in the back is
mad dodging so many enemies at one
yo OU
who who who
wo okay now now it's not funny anymore
buddy no no no no no no no no no no no
no
you pay with your
teeth I haven't had a a pig snoot in a
while where are
they am I missing
something dentist
kiaha come to kiaha dentist
Tre I will take out all your teeth so
you don't have to worry about them
anymore do it for a good cause they will
be donated to the Chesire
Cat why are you guys looking like that
what's the problem okay this is where we
is this where we stopped where we
restarted the
game I think it is okay so we back on
track I think
oh then we there we have an auto
save now hold on I should have just uh
gone a little bit
further
oh oops oops should
focus take this
yeah so did you guys see the new
schedule you guys were quite excited
about
it seeing everyone's reactions was so
funny you guys went absolutely crazy
about the sponsorship of shin meami
tensei 5
I'm glad you guys are
happy I am really really excited for
receiving this
sponsorship
um however I will clear something up
right
now which will
maybe calm all of you down how do I get
up
there over side why am I stuck
oh
and the sponsorship is by
Sega not
[Laughter]
Atlas thank you
[Music]
Sega
yeah yes
yes Dad explains
it yeah I'm
excited how do I get up there
though how do I get
[Music]
there not missing anything no way I can
reach that no
way ah afterwards I don't know yet
maybe I don't know I can't tell
uh I I would like to I guess but it
would mean that that would be our next
jrpg I don't know yet I haven't discuss
it
yet nice I wasn't even
[Music]
focused oh
hello one and two
and a free you get another one oh and
another one you want another one
e how many do you
want there we
[Music]
go I still want to go over there I can't
forget about
it I I am just a assuming I'll get there
later in a
moment so I I I uh am glad that everyone
is so excited about the game I watched
the trailer in the Nintendo Direct
previously and uh yeah since then I mean
I've had my eye on it but I didn't
really plan on playing it anytime soon I
kind of lost sight of when it's going to
be released and all and then then I
received what the hey I was in the
flower since when can you be attacked in
the
flower
what oh wait oh oh oh oh
I received the what the IED the
yeah the sponsorship
offer it just makes me happy because
it's another jrpg and it looks really
good I mean wait is it a RPG it's a
Japanese game but this is an RPG I don't
know anything about the sh me got
me T say ser
oh
the holy I saved myself how did I
do that it froze and I still survive
it's turn based I need to look into the
battle system and stuff yeah I have no
idea how those games work um I only
heard that's a little bit
difficult Val
system uh
oh I totally forgot about the existence
of the
hammer I don't think I'm going to be
using this much
anymore uh oh
sh classic RPG series that started in
wow long time
ago Oh see now we can get
there it's more complicated RAB than
difficult
h you know I like my jpgs with the cute
pretty Graphics so it's like the
Aesthetics are totally up my alley I've
smoked a cigarette Alice no fun at all
oh one day I'll try a clay pipe clay
pipe oh what about clay
chicken oh what was that again clay
chicken what is that thing what was that
thing they told me about
wait a second need to move the
window clay pot chicken yeah that was a
thing right I learned about that
recently I want to go over there
too did I take the wrong route do I have
to go
back oh
Hello Kitty Cat stink a Sinister sound
what have you imagined
Alice I don't know she's kind of sick
perhaps oh oh there's a snot a secret
snoot I'll get you
here is it eating it up it did
oh oh
very
[Music]
interesting stop the freak where is it
stop it does this one not move okay so I
got to make this
jump
okay yes thank you okay we're done
here really smooth today going back
what oh
hello oh
it's a big boy guys it's a big
boy let's take care of him oh no don't
eat me I've had enough of that yesterday
with little nightmares man was freaky
freaky as hell
oh oh oh oh oh oh I don't know what I'm
doing right now I need to hit those
faces
shoot wait I Ted out
I want to kill the small ones
first nice oh double double hit wave the
the
faces
oh so is like
Shi related to Persona or what cuz I
like I mean it's m
but no time right now guys answer me
later no
no you leave me alone right
now oh
I got to be
careful I got to be
careful oh
[Music]
holy
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God yeah okay this is where you need to
hit him I was too far inside before when
we previously fought this
enemy okay are you going to die or what
yo
sh
nice ah that was a close
one that was pretty
close turn small to avoid getting caught
oh oh I didn't really think of using you
know that like getting small in a
battle
oh I don't think I can Implement that
into my fighting style right
now I'm already too used to the way I
play now so okay back to uh Persona is a
spin-off of smt oh really
yeah like I literally know nothing about
Persona and shin Mega like all of those
games I've never touched before it's not
I'm really curious look at the
destruction around you consider its
cause then join
okay kill me you will love the girls in
Persona great say got chose you then
well I think it's because you know I
play all those jrpgs
oh
oh we're getting there later um
yeah I have my reputation of playing
JP's and hey Sega sponsored our Yakuza
playthrough as well right the one from
like one year
ago and then we played we finished the
game afterwards maybe maybe that's what
they're hoping for secret
L who
knows
what you are familiar with the saying
that smoking stunts your growth adults
assault children with that adage usually
while they've got a pipe stuck in their
mouths I won't ask you to inhale Let the
Smoke envelop you
M
Small yeah the first yaka like a dragon
stream was a long time ago
oh
pretty mysterious
East look at the dress new dress oh it's
like
a Asian style
interesting wait one second let me
actually I think I'll make myself uh
I'll turn my filter
off wow I'm so bright have I always been
this bright
have I always been this Bright Now it
hurts my
[Laughter]
eyes is this because there's no uh no
Katakana and no uh hakana in I guess
this is
Chinese
oh that's how that's how you usually can
tell if you don't know much about like
these languages usually you can tell it
apart by looking whether or not there's
a h and Katakana in a
sentence if not then it's yeah most
likely not
Japanese no wait safe safe no
traditional Chinese oh I wonder what's
written
there music is kind of weird right now
but I think that's on
purpose should I not go over
there should I go there first was I even
able to go there
looked far away when I was closer to it
the
irony wait is that is that a ma maong uh
stone is it wait are all of those over
there
too wait that's so cool that's cool fish
fish why is that down there
fish
[Music]
fish I understand everything now but I'm
still going over there cuz there's a b
bottle f
[Music]
give me those teeth I got 460 I need to
go up to like 500 something something to
upgrade my beautiful
teapot
oh
s this skill platforming I have a future
in platforming I can feel
it I don't know why I would have ever
fought
differently I don't know something that
I have been trying to
forget something in my brain is telling
me woo
baby I want to go over there yeah yeah
thank you
okay okay
okay
change collect
bottle what is this instrument that's
playing it's probably some kind of like
traditional
flute you know how there's like for
examp of shamian like I wonder there
must be some kind of like similar
traditional FL loot as well I heard that
snoot just now I heard
it so peaceful where are the
enemies where are they and where is the
snoot where's the
snoot I hear it
oh is it there is it behind oh cracked
uh accidentally totally accidentally
so
close puzzle place oh I'm good with that
are those fishes
dangerous ah there you
[Music]
are season this notot season
it eat
blueberry
H oh
bump yeah bump yes whoever said true art
serves neither ornament nor use is
ignorant of the aesthetic of the
East
oh now hold on wise words from a wise
man
nice this so far it's kind of like all
over the place to be honest like it's
like where the hell do I
go um it's not very
obvious as it was in the previous levels
but I don't know I like it and I think
they did that on purpose give me those I
want I want
tee wouldn't call Red Cliff
wise oh wait why what did he do I forgot
what what are you for a moment you know
what for half a second of me seeing that
bug I thought about getting my net out
and catching it with my bug
net Animal Crossing brain
uh oh
man
beautiful beautiful level design also I
haven't had a lag in a while but I
jinxed it last time so I
guess uh-oh is there an enemy coming to
see me
soon no problem
I can take any
enemies but that's a Shinto shine uh
gate mixing again uh several countries
cultures
interesting what's up
there oh
oh so much for nice safe Jim
Tracy those strawberries are so good
sorry I'm I'm really enjoying them are
you guys snacking on something
[Music]
too
oh
wow drinking coffee some chocolate oh
yummy I would love to cover my my
strawberries in chocolate right
now oh oh this is where it gets
interesting
oh
oh I feel like I'm taking a a tour right
now like a like a tourist and I'm just
appreciating the beauty that I'm
surrounded
with instant noodles
M chocolate strawberries are fire hell
yeah nurse wi said was the
fire up like guy on no one knows how she
survived except Alice and she's St
remember what does that mean
St
oh M it's a
festival W it's too quiet though
sus no enemies nowhere to be
seen never
mind samai wasp
cusa
oh oh he's
fast he doesn't give a about my
Cannon oh I sliced you up though oh
there's another one
oh there's more and more I keep on
am I not going backwards why am I
picking up more and more enemies this
fight is too fast
already I can't get
him is there like a strategy for
this don't forget the horse ah wait uh
horse horse are
oh thank you that's right okay that
works that works very well okay I guess
the horse is being useful
[Music]
again very interesting where did I came
from I
completely forgot I think I came from
there yeah yeah yeah
okay okay okay oh those houses are so
cute
[Music]
berry berry
berry
M I love this I love looking at
this
wow that's gorgeous
what are we
doing okay will that give me some stairs
or something
outside time to upgrade the tee but ah
do I have enough teeth now let's check
it out I got 583 oh yes
yes okay I will upgrade the teapot
Cannon what what does it do now
what does it do
now is that poison it's a stinky teot
now more
op not really against the Wasps though
but that's okay
nice nice nice you're no mats for me
guys no match for takasi
kiaha oh
baby today is really fun I don't know
what's going
on I'm
gaming as a why shark said haha
stinky
ow die now maybe it might be worth
upgrading the hammer actually the The
Horse
Hammer who's that wise shark I was
watching her play Animal Crossing
yesterday she she was playing the
DLC and wow she was having a lot of fun
with it I don't know if I
would really enjoy the DLC right now
that much because like rather
than decorating other people's houses
currently I'm more focused on uh working
on my own Island yeah
yeah but uh I was also watching someone
else's
uh Animal Crossing stream
yesterday a certain Animal Crossing
YouTuber not actually not YouTube
actually not a
YouTuber certain smells are one off you
never mistake burning human flesh for
roasting a lamb chop and it was
interesting because
uh I I just like I like Animal Crossing
but I don't really see like
I
don't I don't enjoy the same way like
all those Animal Crossing Fanatics do I
wish I could like I need to learn from
them like what's the best way to enjoy
Animal Crossing H teach me
Senai yeah but uh I was uh saying not
YouTube because it's so Facebook
streamer can you imagine people stream
on Facebook
could I not have waited one more
[Laughter]
moment patience
girl
yeah Facebook yeah there are literally
like really active streamers on
Facebook like that girl has been
streaming on Facebook for years many
many years
now I just I don't just I wonder I was I
was just as confused as you guys like
where do you even find Facebook streams
right like where do they get shown you
have to I think you actively have to
already follow someone's like artist
page or something and that's the only
way you will be oops notified by their
streams is that working for her I was
thinking the same thing but apparently
it is she had like uh 500
viewers and and I'm like what
what this whole other world exists and I
don't really know anything about
[Music]
it yeah no 500 is pretty damn
good I didn't realize Facebook live
streaming had actually an existent
existing
audience yeah yeah yeah oh a it hello oh
okay
um yeah I don't know was but I don't
really I don't really I don't really
like the whole like layout and stuff for
Facebook
streaming definitely prefer YouTube or
even switch uh switch
twitch switch streaming now coming on
Nintendo
switch but you have to have an online
membership you got to pay for your
online membership in order to be able to
use
that
what don't start a fire
today sounds about
right it's it's just like I think maybe
it's just because we are all just so
Focus focused on on YouTube and and
maybe twitch um that we don't realize
that there's actually this whole
Community out there why do I get stuck
in this
for is shouldn't be on to there we go
the lag is weird today oh
again I can't
what the
hell okay this platforming is uh just
challenging surprised people still use
Facebook yeah I don't use it either
anymore there was a time when I was
addicted to it but no not anymore I
think that probably the same for a lot
of us here
huh we
sure come on come
down hi okay and
now and jump and wait a
moment and wait okay okay finally
finally finally
ohat she who saves a single soul saves
the universe remember oh deep stuff what
are you trying to tell me I saved the
universe because I saved a single
soul
myself I love those
[Music]
trees is that
bamboo pretty
trees just reminded me of
it reminded me of a YouTuber I watched
that was playing I think Animal
Crossing I think and that YouTuber saw
these kind of
trees like an animal crossing though
bamboo where it's obviously bamboo and
was like what are those trees what is
that does that really exist I've never
seen those trees
before I know it was really amusing to
me ah oh hello hello
like I I don't how have you as a grown
adult person never like
ever acknowledged the existence of
bamboo trees
before some people don't get okra I
can't believe them okra and but the
vegetable oh Dam clasp oh so
so
okay bunk bnk bunk FK I hate that
vegetable I hate
it oh he's good he's good he reads me
and plays me like a
fiddle oh
W get out of here get out of
here oh he got Stu or did I do
that bnk
bnk did he does he get poisoned when I
know that
it better do be doing some kind of
damage yeah okay oh he lost his
flag we're getting
there oh oh oh I'm I'm about to go
mad you don't want to make Alice mad oh
he got
scared whoa
oh wait this level design is so
cool so cool y I like it wait I got to
go there
first I hear snot
notnot it doesn't sound so close also
how would I get
there me
where is
you maybe I can get over there let me
give it a
try close but
no left side s left side from where
here
oh huh
wait oh right there in front of me it's
so dark I didn't see it oh wait uh
uh I guess you lost
orientation someone give this man an
award a medal whatever
oh yes
wonderful I need some HP back though can
we have a flower somewhere that I can
dive into for a
moment n okay uh by the way so anything
else that I wanted to talk about about
the schedule we're having tomorrow I
guess unarchived and archived K both of
it I don't know which one comes first
because um I I think I think we're going
to do unarchived first because let's say
that the endurance takes me forever I
would run out of songs uh in the
archived
C so as soon as I
reach uh the
Milestone am I going to fight you
guys as soon as I reach the wait that
reminds you of something me attacking
people who are just praying in the game
who are not actually about to attack me
anyway anyway I was saying You The
Chosen One yes our savior our benefactor
I'm the chosen one not the does that not
remind you of
something how they're like religiously
uh really focused on something and don't
notice what's happening around them
mhm uh I was saying I was saying
yes uh unarchived first and once we
reach the Milestone if we reach it we'll
have an archived one uh right after it
a and so look forward to that I didn't
really practice so tomorrow until the UN
I stream I'll be practicing a little
bit and M
yes it's going off I know I should have
gone there but I wanted to explore a
little bit more wait yes you really must
what about this place he even thinks
things
oh but there's like so many places to go
here right
now
M you can
like I hear snow and I see
BBA the M won't be archived then well
yeah but the celebration afterwards will
be
archived
celebration D come on love K yeah it's
been it's been a while since the last
one
and we are done okay where's this
not where is this notnot
where's
snot
huh oh there you
are uh
okay recently the snotes are becoming
invisible how
cheeky how snooty they are sneaky snoot
unbelievable
why do you want to hide from
me is it smart to go here
first or should I go that to that
elevator first let's go to the elevator
I
guess kind of weird that I can already
move on so far
though go back
okay I don't like elevators
anymore oh the memory just the one lamp
Alice as a nightlight but it stays in
The Upstairs Hall and only till you turn
12 oh
okay what's the deal with Shen bum I
don't like them that much but why did
you just come up with that a pel again
one of
those your Victory is in combat and
conundrum suggest your Fitness to
confront the challenges ahead mental
strength will confirm your worthiness or
declare your
defeat
never well first of all that one thank
you
Jesus yeah I thought it was going to be
um like kind of like a boring week but
turns out chin meami tensei got you guys
is so hyped
up so very very good there's never a
boring K Ki week is there
never yeah if we reach the M Stone I
think I think it will be automatically a
hyper week although I don't no currently
let's see how far are we away
currently I really hope we can make it
tomorrow if it seems too impossible I'm
just going to sing normally ah we are
currently uh 6,000
away
H it could be that until the stream
beginning we might uh if we're lucky we
might only be 5,000
away so m 5,000 Subs endurance K in the
past it was manageable it was easy in
the past but now I don't
[Music]
know I
so I will need your
help too too much of a gap
h i I will give it a try
yeah at one point I did like 8K
10K what where am I going ah
here oh
hello you weren't ready for me were
you oh that was too simple
buddy that was just too too
[Music]
easy yeah but back then it was also
still more hype like we were still
fairly new I think one more let's
do it
again that was a long time
ago I think they were just still a lot
of people
who didn't check me out yet oops
oh but now I think everyone already
checked me out why is there a turtle up
there oh it's not
real I know I know thank
you so
[Music]
I need one more of those bck
blocks where did I not
go I went up here right
yeah it or is this already
done y I need one more right behind the
waterfall
which waterful H in the room where I was
just in was it
here
really
nah did you just pull that out of your
ass or
what I just noticed the update schedule
congrats kiaha thank you yeah yeah yeah
yeah I'm playing s 10 five y I wonder if
I'm being the only one who's being
sponsored I think in Hol live English I
am but I wonder if maybe any Japanese
members are going to be
sponsored left of the gate ah I didn't
see
that
okayi W going strong today yeah it's
like I re
reincarnated this is me
now okay
yes time to do a riddle a
puzzle
[Music]
mm they didn't show me the original
though but I can already see where the
corner pieces are mhm that's a corner
piece and the right side corner piece I
guess is not
available okay
um oh wait how do I activate this again
it
how ah okay
uh this
app
tree uh maybe this here uhhuh this goes
here ah
easy first try sa us I'll open the
path why what do you need saving for huh
I cost a lot of
money I'm not going to just help anyone
for
free got to start a business as
Alice this feels like I'm walking
through someone's
guts oh oh she is certainly she imag
things and she has a
hero being unable to help apple I want
to I want to do a cooking stream where I
teach
myself uh where I teach myself how to
make this Austrian I think it's
Australian a desert desert dessert I
hate those two
words um H which is called app M vanilla
SA or Vanilla Ice it's so good it I
think I told you guys before about it
it's like apple rings that are um fried
in batter um apple ring slices and fried
and batter and then with vanilla sauce
or slash and uh with Vanilla Ice it's
like one of my favorite desserts ever
and I finally want to learn how to make
it m yeah yeah yeah
yeah especially cuz apples are so cheap
in my
country in Japan apples are so expensive
did you guys
know it's because I just want to eat it
but I don't know a place where to get
it I don't know a restaurant I mean I'm
sure there's many restaurants in
Australia that serve that but I can't
find them us and control the Peaks to
East and West need to eat it you must
defeat them to reach caterpillar's
Retreat I suppose I must go to the
Mountaintop as it won't come to me we
have faith that caterpillar the strange
and wondrous helps those in need one day
we'll have proof purity of heart is to
will one thing to approach his sacred
aie you must confront the Savage dios oh
you prevent our access to his power I'll
open the entrance to the sacred CES
where your Journey
Begins do you guys feel this too today I
feel like so chill and relaxed and
uh not stressed out I don't know why I
think the game currently is giving me
these relaxed Vibes and the audience
too you guys make me feel like today I
can take it
easy yeah
oh we're going into a different
world oh
what what is this Alice can move jump
shrink and use her float as
normal move carefully to avoid the
hazards depiction of domestic Harmony
and order the fruitful landscape
encouraged industry tolerance and
cooperation loving families flourished
happy children dear friends grateful for
their well-being lived for Generations I
can't attack though free but a sudden
onslaught of alien attacks broke their
fragile bodies and nearly crushed their
generous Spirits so the platformer let's
go right I I love how this game has so
many super like original like parts that
stand out so much from the rest of the
game game it doesn't fit in but it's
great oh
it's great anyway I love
it gives you a little bit of a
refreshing feeling I'm too
stupid training for
ory a little
bit good
okay oh God
okay let's do
this game setion yeah like the for
example the the ship
game o o oome
oome okay y
OAA no okay I I was wondering if I can
touch that I guess
not those leaves look like kiwi slices m
yummy what the is wrong with
you help
I really got used to saying yosa so much
thanks to living in Japan before Ora and
I think there was something else as
well something what else do I say I
think I say
as a reflex as
well like that
hurts ah I say e that's so true and that
feels so natural to me but
like in in in German language people
don't say that somehow it's weird what
like
[Music]
why I don't
know it's not like it it doesn't exist
but why why do
people normally don't not say that
like or like I guess when you just
listen to someone and and you're like
yeah interesting
interesting I I never when I have
conversations with my friends they never
say
that I got that in Japan as
[Music]
well if anything they say a so is or
something like that oh
VI okay this is really turning into aie
practice I know for sake
I can do it I can I can do it I can do
it
[Music]
yes he how much longer where am I going
here was that
it welcome to the
treetop oh wait I saw the peach there is
there a
peach I saw it though I'm going
back hi
hi hi
no
wa sh sh get that peach jump
Queen getting over with Alice mcky oh my
God I found this game
today that is very much kfp
themed uh and I'm going to play it
sometime maybe in December or something
if I got permission um it's another one
of those like oh finally another one of
those like getting over it slash uh egg
is broken hardest 2 style games um it's
again egg related which is perfect it's
made for me it's called
Yol look it
up it's an egg with
arms and a good game for like one of
those endurance streams or
whatever Yol yeah yeah some of you guys
know it huh it's new it's rather new it
released I think at the end of
October where are we going
here it doesn't continue there
apparently
[Music]
okay kiwi trees I think it might be on
purpose that it looks like uh
kiwi I think it's on purpose you only
love kiata every day #
yolked these platforms I hate
platform games just
kidding and where where are we going
from here n
[Music]
what up the tree
oh I thought I didn't oh but I didn't
have to go where am
I wait what this place is
new why did
I why did I spawn there what's with this
checkpoint
[Music]
oh that's not a new place that's an old
one but where am I now what are these
checkpoints what no
no what did I break the freaking game or
what's going on oh this is okay it sent
me another checkpoint back
[Music]
[Applause]
don't need you get out of
here okay are we at the tree now yes
okay well I guess I'll go up the tree
again I don't see where I need to go
from there I don't see it oh wait maybe
maybe
[Music]
uh red that a those KY ah ah ah okay
okay I saw it
[Music]
now to the right to the right but it
what point exactly I don't
know oh my God this is making me crazy
but I just
noticed these paches look like booby
pads even with the nipple hell yeah
let's jump on
Dad It Feels So bouncy and
fluffy I love jumping on booby
pets did you notice the
nipple I'm I'm not making this up
guys do we jump up one Higher I guess
so okay now stay
calm I guess I'll just go to the right
you so oh
finally only took me
a million
years yep take me there
oh what is
this I could go to the left that's like
the top of the other Mountain N I don't
care I'm going here yeah yeah
hello P
chain a
[Music]
why am I stuck in this weird world what
happened I turned into paper
Alice oh oh there we go we're
out back to the real fake
World
interesting so we came out of the same
spot though no or is this different
oh there is a
bridge okay okay and another
Bridge okay I guess it's a different
place hello only the foolish believe
suffering is just wages for being
different what what
what what is that supposed to tell me
isai into Wonderland and isai even
further into paper world yeah
it's
a
Inception Al Inception El
exception a beautiful honorable daughter
would commemorate her deceased family in
Marble I know A Gifted sculpter with
whom I might negotiate a commission what
he wants him turn my family into marble
o I mean why not I guess
it's I guess a nice way to look at that
face
to commemorate
them I don't think I would ever do that
oh I understand don't step on the fire
once that actually is the Kani for fire
even in
Japanese almost
oh Samurai wasp AR
arer okay you want to fight
easy yeah to close to the edge
Alice cherry blossom Cherry P cherry
blossom
paddles did I just hear
sh
yo ah reload reload
well they are like they the the the
Cherry no wait it's coming out of the
sky I thought it came from those enemies
but never mind it's just falling
randomly from the
sky what are we looking at
B well thank god there's no nipples
otherwise I would have to censor it and
it would be too late anyway how do I get
there
ah yeah get
respawn do please be nice to me here
okay oh wait wrong
way I was saying is cuz
someone someone just wrote in Japanese
that he couldn't sleep um so he came to
watch My Stream and I was like oh is it
like 2: a.m. 3:00 a.m. in Japan and then
I realized what that sounded
like
aha treason cut off her head
Tak take her head take her head
down with her head to the huge room with
her what is this part it's kind of sus
what if I jump into
it
hi it looked like you can enter Al
in baby why are you saying goodbye what
happened are you leaving me
forever just yesterday we were having a
talk about how you've been here for so
long and you stayed after dying
for
baby or he just wants to be alive now
maybe maybe baby decided to revive
himself goodbye to death oh
he never said a vas ever before W but
the baby's first words are Al
Vin we taught the baby
German rather than Japanese oh my God I
couldn't be more proud than I am right
now success
yes smart baby very smart baby give the
baby some candy yeah yeah or milk or
something give give baby oh I see a
secret
path are you saying I can't go up there
yet what
the I finished eating my berries by the
way
wow um
move
okay
smoo
hello wrong weapon
I she cut
me you'll pay for that with your life
okay we got another bottle
here and we got some more presents how
many teeth we got now 200 almost uh
300 and we pull the train chain CH you
are gaming today I am indeed gaming
wow like last time I played this game I
don't know why but I didn't
feel I didn't feel it that much last
time I think I because of like the level
maybe not being
quite
uh that kind to
me but today I know I'm really digging
[Music]
it and I'm just in a better condition I
think as
well oh
hello all that broken china oh no
Samurai ink wasp oh
what oh oh why did I
just wait what's going
on I'll take care of you first what what
who am I fighting left out to dodge what
what what what what what do you mean yes
I know I know why are you telling me now
you're confusing me with
that the
bees a
ow I
what leave me
alone okay okay that's it that's it
that's it that's it you make me
mad oh did that just kill all of them at
once oh that killed the stone
die
shoot what is it can I even catch them
yes I
can destroy all of these Stones
man oh we're done
y did you just his I don't know what
didn't notice M
cat oh by the way I was thinking on the
weekend to upload another M Something
Something video but I don't know what
animal I should do
next what should I become what's what's
a um an animal that is easy to
copy oh yeah I did want to do MB I kind
of wanted to do that or like M fly or M
wasp or something yeah that's right
maybe I'll do that
next uh koala no hell no that's not cute
oh no don't drop my precious
teeth how dare
you who am I fighting who am I
fighting okay those weird small wasps
wasp together with these Samurai wasps I
don't like that
combination but okay even more reason to
do an M wasp video or MB
video
yes
yes what do we have
here so beautiful like in the beginning
it was like these these houses these
paper houses and stuff now it's this
this blue
China in between we got those maong
stones look I love that I I used to I
think I used to watch my mom play maang
maang
maang but uh I have no idea how it's
being properly
played M
SL and
[Music]
look at that beautiful
tree and Alice Alice cute Alice really
cute in that dress pink suits you pink
and blue where are we going what what
opened a that
one
there you get inside and the other doors
open when the other one's
close I suppose
ah or it turns
around
oh
[Music]
yeah give me more teeth this is fun I
love these uh slides every time we get
them wow that's a beautiful slide is
that a phoenix is that a the Phoenix I'm
I'm seeing on the
pattern I never fell off
[Laughter]
before but I'm okay with that because
it's so much fun I want to slide
again it's at least it's a BB I can say
that
much slow paced right now and there we
go here comes the speed
oh no I'm really slow how am I how am I
being so slow right now I mean it's
easier to control
but who whoa whoa whoa w
i i couldn't jump anymore after that
last jump for some reason even though
supposedly it's supposed to be endless
Eternal jumps in this
game finally you know what this is all
just a technique for me to be able to
get all the
teeth that's why I kill myself sometimes
what if I jump down here
shortcut
gamer G
me that's not going to help
me intense
sliding did you guys hear the death
metal music I hear it
y I need help and
help no I missed one
no okay
okay see it's really only three times
though sometimes
where the hell are you spotting
me where are you spawning what's going
on how nice of you where am
I oh
oh that reminds me of yesterday so many
things remind me of yesterday little
[Music]
nightmares oh hello W no no I don't need
a welcome parade no unless you brought
fruit
cake oh that style oh God God oh God oh
God wait I only have one half of a row
oh I made it I didn't
die you want to fight
yeah
clutch good job gamer thank you thank
you
viewer
uh okay chill
chill I feel like we already made a
ton of progress
today don't you think don't you agree uh
is there something spawning here later
on to reach the beautiful lady here
because I can't reach it
SN
SN no why
here
o I deserve a more recent
checkpoint where was the snoot I was
looking the other direction when I fell
I
think
so it's
like where is it is it's underneath the
stone no
[Music]
wait maybe I'm not supposed to get it
right
now it was there ah there it is
ah
uh sorry brain is uh slow right now
now
oh ah I knew it I knew
it what does the lady have for me a
wonderful picnic basket oh isn't that a
nice picnic date with a half naked
gisha wow
I wouldn't mind of course you
wouldn't relatable so relatable yeah
totally oh uh sir no please
no oh God there's a lot of enemies here
oh YY ohmy this is not going to go well
ah I need to heal oh
unless I just don't take damage
good advice right from taka Niki this
time how about you just don't take any
damage ever thought of
that wow I'm actually doing
it I took a little bit though oh what oh
Str boy oh strong boy is here strong boy
oh can we make it can we make
it okay
oh come here come here don't be scared
now
ow give it to him give it to him as long
as you can he's dead he's dead he's
dead oh oh there's another one there's
another one wait wait wait
why does it not die oh there we
go
okay I think we're
clear why is the battle music still
happening are we not
clear ah okay okay
uh sending your present back please take
it come
on
okay
wow
W and that's all you give me back come
[Music]
on I need some more Health
please please
wonderful thank you for the Clapping I
deserve that yes yes we have to admit it
it is what it is I deserve the
claps what the hell
man oh by any chance am I supposed to
get up here and then shoot with my
teapot h no like that would be so
difficult to reach no that's not
it hey
hey just jump from where the pressure
plate is ah isn't that easy huh I guess
it is yeah a little bit more elevated
uh okay I'll keep that here
then and jump up
here there's another one there I guess
it opens the
drawer it does it
does oh I I thought I was waiting for
something
and and there we go simple it's as
simple as that take
it let me get comfy
here yeah a platform head had a
seizure oh did you guys see like I I saw
it by ego searching in Japanese but
apparently at least in for the Japanese
people right now my birthday merch has
been sent out
finally that freeze did you
see what why am I what am I doing here
was that not t
floor is that the picn picnic basket
lady but the stones weren't there before
were
they is this just a connection why
wrong way wait I got an email it'll be
around December before it's oh really
but but that means it it will be kind of
like a Christmas
present got to see it that way wait I'm
lost where am I supposed to go this
[Music]
way that's all Digos
almost which way do we go
first this way I need
healing very
desperately taka Santa Claus Zara that
is quite the reach the fuzzzy slippers
will be perfect for winter see I
anticipated that it will take that much
time for it to be sent out therefore the
slippers are made to be fluffy and warm
to heal up your little fies
chickens unfortunately all the emao said
for me was us won't be getting it soon
anyone oh oh they say something like
that so at least you got contacted
though at least it's not like you're in
the dark
forever Radcliffe asked me in just a
once very proud of his artifacts
he said impartial to to Goa Japan
doesn't
seem but perhaps that's
why English pronunciation of Japanese
words is something that triggers
me okay okay okay
okay uh
uhhuh triers you too
okay oh oh what is
that
oh okay I'll leave a bomb here but what
was there on the left nothing okay yeah
wait a nice
jck oopsie
Tri me as an English speaker just no
effort made pronounce it like an English
word yikes yeah I mean I mean they don't
know like I feel like you
can you would nail the pronunciation if
you like studied Japanese or you listen
to a lot of people oops speaking
Japanese so I understand that like you
don't automatically nail the
pronunciation if you don't have much
connection to that um that makes sense
sh night
night
yeah but I feel like for example for
movies and like let's
say uh
[Music]
English English translations for
animes oh that's where it really
triggers me though because if it's an
English translation for an anime
like it's English voice actors and they
can't even pronounce their own
characters names you know what I
mean that's just why like let's say okay
I don't even know if if that would be an
example because I have never watched an
English dub of har suia but let's just
say this as an
example uh the let's say the voice
actress of hadia would pronounce her own
name as
harui
suum or something like that suum Orum
Zoom that definitely happens so that's a
big no for
me yeah like Naruto as
well like is there no director that
tells them to get their pronunciation
right cuz no need to blame the voice
actors maybe they don't know better like
they are chosen for that role doesn't
mean that they are into Japanese culture
or
whatever yeah whoever is directing that
could you maybe tell them how to
pronounce it
suuk
SAS are we done with this level
[Music]
do we know
it yeah the director probably doesn't
know either exactly that's the problem
Oh Story
Time din saved my life I survived
because she showed me how to escape I
didn't leave the lamp in the library
that's why cats are superum the lamp and
Dina were upstairs when I went to bed
Dina was in the room with me when the
fire started
oh the third
key oh progress progress progress
[Music]
baby
wow
yeah okay but she's still wearing these
clothes yeah we're still in the Asian
Vibe uh
area was that a a peach
seed what are you
doing oh yeah right we didn't saved them
yet oh yeah yeah yeah no stop
it stop it they're just made on of
paper y can we act
faster wait wait wait wait let me just
open these
up I'm the one who said can we act
faster but
sorry let me hit one of them at least
come on no okay in that case you got a
special bking
service just like those uh Vena
schnitzel m going to make you flat and
then fry you in breading M then I'm
going to eat you in pral Bear
marada lingonberry
Jam actually that makes me think I don't
know what I'm eating for dinner today
h frozen pizza it is just kidding I
don't know maybe I should order terrible
oh great caterpillar why have you
abandoned us the door head is sealed
only by playing where the hell is the
caterpillar he got too high on his
hookah he forgot about his boys honor I
suspect are you ready no no I'm not is
this ribon game
again uh oh God
okay hi hi oh it's so laggy yeah
there Ted in my memory like Twinkle
Twinkle Little Bat I accidentally pushed
wish that I I didn't think there would
be such an option I thought it was a
redo well you can just skip it what do
you mean you can skip
it did I what do I lose when I skip it
is this just like
it get to the tree help our
brothers I've never seen it skipping it
yeah what the hell why was that even an
option journalist
mode no shut up
I wanted to do it
again that's kind of pointless you lose
the experience but I wasn't going to get
like any teeth or so out of it was
I ying and yang
cool fish fish make love M fish become
[Music]
one you again what a nice pleasant
surprise ow
ow
ow what's happening
oh get off of
me
[Music]
bastards
oh okay get out of
here no no no okay you know what I'm
killing
you right
now lag is there another one of those I
want to destroy it right now here
okay no no I will first take care of
those stones and then we can talk here's
another
one okay okay okay okay okay
buk why are you keep on losing focus
it's because of those stupid Beast oh
I'm getting mad oh you'll make me
mad
wait try me try me I was waiting for
that come
down
okay oh there was another one oh and
another one oh how
obnoxious uh let's switch to
oh wait that one doesn't work uh leave
me
alone I think now we're done
oh she's even throwing out Mega 10 memes
did I what was that that must have been
unconsciously because I have never
played a mega mega 10 game
before what did I say what was the
meme and another
one is that a mega 10
meme H what is that
what you just pointing over there what
what what I've been waiting for this
that's the meme
What DJ CI
oh I know that sound
[Music]
oh and once again we teleport are they
free now wait what why are we here in
the on the slide again it's a welcome
surprise let's try this again isn't this
the same
slide it feels like the same slide so
far time travel holy got to protect
myself
yby my HP
they just don't let me heal myself if I
get hit again I'm going to
die
sh I don't get T hysteria mod
really see now the yes was on the right
side why the hell would skip on the
right side
before
why I need some consistency
please wait but now I'm back to full HP
[Music]
right wait no I still have barely any
HP okay okay
careful
wait yeah really don't get no I see I do
get teeth what are you talking about no
okay I don't get teeth just for a moment
I was getting
teeth no I want the teeth
though oh I do get teeth just the small
ones not the big
[Music]
one okay okay what the
hell I need to be healed
it gets way too
faster I started with what half half a
rose right
now what if I say no I don't want to
continue what do you do then game what
you going to do kick me out where am I
supposed to heal
myself did I there's like no way to heal
myself at this point
the hit box
y hard mode is on so much for oh
yeah can I just jump over
there is that a place that I've been to
before maybe there's some healing over
there
use a shortcut yeah I I saw some
shortcuts
but jump over the
piles
excus
me
excuse me hey I was trying to
[Applause]
jump okay two hearts two hearts let's go
gave me two different tears after all
these years tears of your tears what did
you see that I didn't even touch
it cuz I hate
you cuz I love
you give me two I can't jump I tried
just now I cannot to
jump cuz I love you what if I say no
[Music]
I can't jump I told
you I press
space I think if I'm like on the on the
slide and I'm at a point where um like
the slide suddenly uh disappears and you
jump like autom teally if I'm already in
the jump then I can jump but when I'm
when I'm like here see now I'm pressing
space and I can't I can't I can't jump
okay okay okay okay
okay slow slow what you guys saw that
right I did not touch it I did 100% not
touch
it no no you can't tell me I touch that
no no
no wait what am I supposed to do here oh
I I jumped ah I jumped like outside this
was
inevitable okay I can't help it I have
to do this now the teeth because
otherwise I'm going to die now and I'm
not doing this
again oh now I'm super slow
sheat okay make use of it as long as I
can there we go
[Music]
what I did not touch it I did not oh
High Mark what what do that mean what's
that mean what does that mean what does
that meeme
mean no no no you don't make me restart
the slide don't you dare don't you oh my
God okay the real meme
Okay jump did you forget how to jump
Alice what going
on
okay I need some healing game
please I need some
healing heal
me
no no
no what is
this what if I make this go boom can I
do that
that China is
indestructible oh no you kidding me
you're going to make me fight
now okay well at least he gave me a
simple uh flower flower
flower
okay what is that weird camera
yeah I'll leave that
here cuz apparently we're going to have
a time pressure oh are we are they
staying
up I hope they
are okay looks like they're staying I
wouldn't be able to make it otherwise
any yes they are no wait they're going
down they're
sinking they're sinking
[Music]
Mears you guys with the emotes so
cute wait what the hell how how how
ah how am I supposed to reach that okay
reach
that re that sorry guys but I how was I
supposed to reach that
[Music]
anyway sure you
sure do you want me to pull that again
though no
okay wait wait wait oh no wait wait wait
[Music]
wait I was so
close this time thir time is the charm
oh nice I'm getting hungry guys the
berries didn't fill me up
much what do we have here some presents
some flowers thank you thank you I
desperately needed that you could would
have given that to me earlier but all
right thank you for the membership
welcome I saw that from the other
side food break no no not not yet no no
no even if I were to take a food break I
am not sure what I would eat I got
instant noodles like in terms of snack I
got uh chocolate rice uh uh
waffles I
got I got
Pokey oh I could snack on some Pokey M
Oreo shake run see I would love that
because I would love to get a crispy
chicken right
now that would be
lovely oh God they're attacking
they're
attacking
nice oh he
moved nice
K vegan yes yes of course
vegan you guys know
me totally totally vegan a vegan crispy
chicken oh crispy chicken I haven't
eaten one in a while the other day I
went to Burger King and I just got vegan
chicken
nuggets I actually was able to hold
myself back and just go for the
nuggies Yum Yum Yum Chicken Nugget Shin
nuggets
freeze you don't have to freeze the game
just because I'm so intimidating
free I am the kiaha
police what's
moving by the way I was going to talk
about the sports festival but I don't
even know what I would talk about right
now what what is there that I that I
could discuss
um well the ball tossing game let's talk
about the ball tossing game that was the
first challenge where I
participated on that day
what are we doing here
oh and um it was me S
andisa and I practiced that game a
couple of times
but in the practice it was going so well
and then in the
actual uh ball tosing real
match I up quite a lot like the
timing the Rhythm cuz it's really um the
rhythm is
important and the timing to step on the
pressure plate like normally if you run
normally if the moment you step on the
pressure plate it's like perfectly timed
you should be able to easily Reach the
the platform that elevates
you but I messed that up several
times I still have a think that I got in
quite a bunch of uh what it
Qui a bunch I think I have to go
back it's not going down now it's going
down ah quite a bunch of uh what did I
say quite a bunch of
balls oh
what and we ended up with quite the big
uh
difference to the red team like we had I
think something like
90 and the red team had what 40 50 which
ended up being a huge difference even
though I was feeling so bad about my own
performance
no people were saying uh s carried like
I had no uh idea like I couldn't notice
I couldn't pay attention to
that I think that is something we will
never know because no one knows how much
everyone each single person was able to
actually put in there but wow if she did
then thank you s for saving
it see the V oh is it so
obvious cuz in in my eyes from my
perspective it was it was just chaos it
was just running running running get the
balls get the balls get the balls you
start off with 10 balls and that is
really
nothing cuz that you're you're done with
those 10 balls after two jumps and then
you already have to go get
more it's pretty
difficult but you know what I'm happy
with the team because uh they practiced
I'm glad that my ball tossing team
actually practiced I'm very um grateful
for
that that way we didn't uh embarrass
ourselves thank
God yeah the the pressure is pretty
strong especially when you're the
[Music]
leader Yama
why is he
invisible is that a
bug he disappeared all r
not dude fell
down well fine with me bye-bye see you
later so yeah that was the ball tossing
game thankfully we did a great job and
Dad good team good
team and then after right after that was
the
elytra yeah and I was the last one to
fly because first it was team a white
and red and then Team B R and red and
then team C red and then me and everyone
got 55 points except pic she got the
maximum 60 points but still 55 is super
decent and easy actually if you can uh
if you practice so it's not a big
surprise cuz elytra was the solo the
single solo game so it was easy to
practice I guess because the other
things you would maybe need your
teammates to help you practice and stuff
yeah so I think everyone who everyone
who signed up for the elytra challenge
was totally ready to nail it no one
would sign up for that if you don't
actually have uh experience and and
confidence in nailing it
yeah so the elytra challenge was really
just people knowing what they're doing
and I didn't want to fly a second time
because it wasn't best IDE too and a
bridge will complete and 55 was all I
ever managed to get us to remove it in
practice as well I actually never landed
on the golden one before entr to the
next oh is super close next to
it so I
figured oh dear I figured I'm just going
to oh my God he's aggressive
help what if I just stay up here I'm I'm
hitting him I'm actually hitting him I
hear
it cheese Strat let's
go I hear
it I hear them
[Music]
dying okay I'm coming down
he's mad he's mad he's hitting his
friend because he's so mad
CA you hit him twice what the hell is
the matter with
you go back go
back
okay shoot
okay you can't hit me can't touch
this can't touch
this today's my day yo
oh is that me that's me that's me at the
top that's right where I belong at the
top
Bach we are saved our benefactor you're
free my friends wa there salt and pepper
uh thingies dispensers what
they just summoned one of the booby pads
thank
you oh oh I just thought it was a snoot
here secret snot no
no thank
[Music]
you now I hear the
SN wait
uh there you go salt dispenses yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah are they because they had
holes on their heads so anyway back to
topic um I actually have had uh three
games uh in a row because it was ball
tossing then it was elytra and then it
was red light green light and I must say
after the especially after the doie doie
of thank you I know that after the doy
doie of the elytra uh match um I was I
think at that point that's where I I
lost my energy I and perhaps my focus I
slept 4 hours or something by the way
which means I did manage to sleep quite
early I had to get up at
4:30 so I slept around like midnight or
even earlier but I woke up so many times
too so that kind of maybe explains
why um I
wasn't on on my best
uh
condition yeah
um yeah then red that green light uh not
only because I was already exhausted but
I think also really just we have to
absolutely blame the Ping that's we
didn't
anticipate that the Ping would be so bad
for Red Light Green Light holy it
was insane like the countdown would be
like 3 to one and then fade away and
it's kind of like at zero you stop even
though it doesn't show at
zero but we already had to stop at two
for some of us and then for others other
endlessly spawning for others it uh or
what the
I think it was earlier or later as
well there was no exact timing either
that we could figure out in that short
time yeah holy I think you guys saw
it though in Bale's VOD as well or maybe
not did ba have a a lot of ping issues
as
well I'm actually not sure why are do I
keep on spamming what
a why is that pot uh floating is that a
hint wait a second leave me
alone B hardcore Stu in front the Ping
oh
really well there you go
what are we doing here what are we
doing
die excuse me could you please
[Music]
die come on
mate okay
oh o o o why am I having so many
troubles
here I I think I need to hit their face
ow ow
ow what if I just ignore them am I
supposed to just ignore them cuz they're
getting on my nerves
now never mind I'll ignore
them they respond infinitely oh really
okay then I guess that's what I was
supposed to
do I felt challenged
I wanted to do it but now never mind ah
I knew those pots were
sus you
hey hey hey hey hey
hey sussy bucka sussy Buckle I'm
telling you
oh oh
no no oh now now they're sinking or
not give me one more try I wanted to
land on that one but then I gave up
Midway
through one more
trych ouch oh for
sake stop hitting me when I'm already on
the
[Music]
ground what is the session here
what the
hell well now they can't hit me at least
what the hell is that freeze no oh I
made
it oh my
God doie
dokie game mode off
mhm now I got my good moments I got my
good moments and I got my oh my God it
was so dark I couldn't
see oh my God
oh my God I made it thank God I
S
yo this is
a quite the platforming game thank you
Chad thank
you oh they're following me
[Music]
stalkers
no show me a
face coward he's flying is he flying
away from me there we
go okay now are we done or
what okay
hallelujah
oh it's a hack and slash well it's a
hack and slash forer
okay oh you're free get out of here get
out of here also there's no present here
are you for real no reward for me for
saving
you oh my
God okay so yeah uh then we had Red
Light Green Light overall I thought that
was so much fun if it wasn't for the
Ping and it would have been actually
quite the easy game and obstacle course
like a simple type of obstacle
course but yeah
uh oh my God interesting uh um command
thingy like when you die you turn into
the spectator mode apparently they
couldn't do anything about that it was
just like it had to
happen I never was in spectator mode
before G was robbed yeah apparently G
ran too early or so I didn't really
realize
that oh we freed
everyone me
the Greatful most often caner benefit to
the source of their
gratitude am I not the source of the
Gratitude what the hell why are they not
thanking
me what I should become as God not
whoever that
is okay I can heal
here good I was just doing what she saw
some of the Japan do she so she was
mhm yeah I don't know by watching them I
didn't see anything wrong with it like
after
they uh let us do it another time
apparently we still did it wrong and
then they explained to us like uh you're
doing something wrong and and and I
honestly didn't understand what part we
were doing
wrong maybe because I just always died
too early but I didn't quite grab as bit
which is why I couldn't quite explain it
either um
nice oh I see
you uh I where where did I go do I go
down I guess
so they did not account for the massive
ping yeah that's true as well can I go
up there where did
I so close
h i loved how everyone died in one
second yeah the first round was so funny
because you might think that we all just
died there immediately because we were
at the game but no it was really
just the Ping that was so
unfair oh it actually works from here oh
I thought it would be too far away okay
I'll take it she moved when red light is
fading not green light L well I I just
feel like well if it's if it doesn't
kill
you then shouldn't it be okay you know
what I mean because it was already so
strict that it would kill us if we moved
at um two for us or zero for the
Japanese
members
so why why is it not allowed to move
whenever it's okay to move you know what
I mean that would just be IL logical I
didn't understand but okay I still don't
up to this moment I don't
understand so I guess it's good that I
always died so early because I just
didn't
understand yeah then it was programmed
wrong that's what I'm saying if if we we
were not supposed to walk in that moment
then why did the the block not kill us
the Observer block whatever yeah can I
upgrade something I can
oh we are already maxed at the blade
what should we upgrade next guys all of
these are on
two didn't get the snoot reward what
okay I'm going to go
back
grinder
okay
sure
oh the final form is so cool oh wait
that's not even final but it already
looks so
cool can I go back to the snot what was
where did the reward go wait I don't
think I can even go back whatever I'm
not playing Collectibles
here oh we got a different reward
here so yeah and then and then that was
over and after that finally I got a
break because that was when PVP
started so so I uh went to warm up some
breakfast and
um uh yeah just after that I started
being more quiet because I was I just
didn't have energy and I as much as I
enjoyed the sports festival I I don't
know the the PVP uh part was as a
exhausted sleep lacking uh viewer uh of
me CU I wasn't actually playing it was
kind of uh tedious so uh yeah that that
really made me feel like I don't know
jelly what is
this oh H it it does work okay I didn't
see the wind
um but it was entertaining nonetheless
watching the girls I didn't watch all
the time um all of the matches I didn't
pay attention to all of it but it was
pretty exciting
anyway exciting and exhausting at the
same
time yeah I feel like I just moved on
without wanting to move on I I I missed
another part didn't I another section I
just went past it what the hell is this
so
green oh well oh oh this is like a Zelda
dungeon
yo
cat huh where are
you is that all you wanted
to is that all you wanted to tell me I
hope I didn't cut you up I didn't see
the fire
[Music]
coming I was just trying to
listen oh my God okay okay okay okay
okay oh my God okay uh where was I uh
yeah
PVP uh we lost I guess right we lost I
think did red team win all three
matches I don't remember definitely the
sea team lost no we
won oh yeah right at the end ba was like
steing oh I loved watching that moment I
saw her uh how she was um silently alone
stealing those diamonds and stuff and
then uh two of the red team ran out of
the
base and just didn't see Bae at all ran
past her and was already only a couple
seconds left you know one person passed
I was like okay that's funny but then
another person passed and I was like
what what's going on just don't see her
I thought they were going to kill her
now but no she completely got ignored
and then those two I I forgot who it was
but they they ran over to the white
teamc
base and they thought they could like
steal some stuff from us but no no
no no no no got it this is one of these
uh challenge battles isn't
it I think that's one of those portals
that lead leads me to a battle under
then I go back there's no time to waste
no time at all no time no time can you
survive the P passage passage of time of
course I
can wait wait wait wait wait I need to
get my weapons
ready I will survive
[Music]
how merciful how merciful thank you I
thought it was
over f f him to
hell those crabs
man go get him go get him go get him
yumy yummy yumy
com
shoot holy survive survive keep up
a
success that 100% felt like a success
indeed no it
[Music]
didn't am I really allowed to accept
this I'm getting the final heart which
is actually the only heart you get for
the game I think it looks like it it
looks like there won't be more huh
success really are you
[Laughter]
sure all right okay what the hell was I
talking about just now what why is there
oh fire Alice save yourself wake up
Lizzy Lizzy open the door the key Lizzy
unlock the door you'll
burn yes I was talking about Bale's MVP
moment yeah holy no that was
inspiring and so fun to watch if it
wasn't for bails at the moment I think
it it would have
definitely been
difficult what the
hell excuse
me oh another
one
oh so thank you babe um honestly through
out the whole match the the whole sports
festival from beginning to end I always
felt like the red team was dominating
most of the time but that somehow didn't
reflect in the point you know what I
mean we were always like pretty close
with
points with total points but somehow
watching those matches I always felt
like red was dominating and and and
doing better in general but somehow we
still didn't end up
losing we were almost about to win as
well in the end right like if it weren't
for me no just kidding I'm not even
blaming
myself um the problem at the end y the
problem at the end yummy ah of that race
uh was I'm going to tell you what the
problem was white team C and actually
red team c as well there were uh people
on both sides who did this
mistake we were all so excited that we
were following each uh racing member um
on the on the tracks sides of the track
running with
them trying to keep up with them to
watch them and then people forgot to
Simply eat
food and I was the last one and people
did that mistake before me so I actually
realized otherwise I would have done the
same mistake probably but uh so Callie
the reason the red team First lost uh
their lead was because cie forgot to eat
she ran out first and then later on S
from the white team did the same mistake
and I didn't notice the moment cie did
it but I noticed when sah did it uh and
that's when I told my teammates they
need to freaking eat otherwise we're
and bailes uh probably if if I
wouldn't have told her uh cuz she ate
after I told her um she she probably
would have had the same
issue holy so both teams made that
mistake oh are we going to play uh jump
rope over
there yeah yeah we would have we would
have lost anyway
um after bal's eight and I guess the red
team probably had a similar
experience it was uh the day was saved
however at the very end oh my God our
our lead was gone again
and MAA and me started running as the
last
Runners so close to one
another it was already close in the
beginning when we started running and it
was close super close until the very end
there were many moments when I was like
catching up to her and literally I was
like our characters were touching one
another and and I was like holy
holy holy I can make it I can
make it but then I didn't make it it was
so
close and my heart throughout the whole
relay was pounding so bad and my body I
was shaking it was crazy like I don't
know why but I got so into it oh I
should have gone there um I I was like
so immersed and I was so so like I don't
know pressured I felt like I needed to
win this y it y it y y I deserve this
yes I felt like I needed to R this it
was it was nerve-wracking yeah
absolutely I don't need to activate it
again do I no okay
oh that was that was quite
something don't burn me don't start a
fire today
okay thank
you it challenged your heart more than
Outlast yes I I I felt like drained
after so that absolutely my I I I felt
like all all my muscles in my body have
left me I felt like jelly and pounding
and shivering and everything holy I
was like I ran a real Marathon I'm
telling
you oh my God that was the adrenaline
yeah and oh my God oh my God holy
it's insane what what happened here what
what did I miss why is it not
[Music]
open do I have to smash
you
no what did I miss my heart ran a
marathon it did it did wrong place oh
there's another door there
yeah yep but I came from there yum
it yum it
it was the perfect ending with a draw in
the end yes for a moment when I didn't
get to be the first on the Finish Line I
felt guilty and I felt bad oh wait
that's where I came from I felt bad
about it for a moment but then I
realized wait this means we both win
both of our teams win and that's
actually the way more beautiful outcome
if you think about it h oh I was
supposed to go up there and I landed
here and now I get it
oh it it's like a circle and I I fell
down here but I was supposed to go to
the upper level oh okay
okay how did I make it through the first
time so easily oh wait can I not just
can I I can easy
[Music]
don't feel guilty K it was a team sport
everyone contributed their best yeah
yeah yeah I don't know but as a leader
it just feels like I failed for a moment
at least it felt like that but
it's it do be okay what the actual
I thought I was off the hook hey
come back down
please thank
[Music]
you how did that hit
right
okay don't get hit this
time okay okay okay can't get me
now yay oh we're going to play another
one of these paper
games I
guess Yep looks like
it yeah and and uh Kiana Muna rivalry
yeah without cause it kind of happened
because we were both the last ones in
the relay and we were both the elyra
fers world the assaulted could not
comprehend the masses brutality I didn't
want people to play it up too much
though which is why I didn't say
anything about
it I didn't want people to be like oh my
God they hate each other so they're
going to be killing it each other like
that yeah the only thing I said was
actually more something like positive
because it's funny that it's Sun versus
Moon
um but yeah uh oh my God excuse me
yeah I had a feeling the moment I saw
that MAA was going to be there elyra
flyer the moment I saw that I was like
ah going to see some annoying comments
perhaps that are trying
to stir something up you know what I
mean
close oh see oh see oh see
got
it excuse
me excuse me you didn't even show me
what was there and you expect me to see
[Music]
that oh that's that's evil
okay that was
[Music]
nice you know what I was relieved about
though is that you know because Cali
originally said that she wasn't going to
participate um but then once she said
she was able to participate after all
she was put into the red teamc as the
only whole life English a whole life
myth member and I was a bit worried you
know about about Callie's well-being I
didn't want her to feel like lonely or
um being left out but apparently she had
a great time in that team so all is well
when I saw her having fun it made me
happy white team C was kind of like
taking it easy but um um why am I doing
this
uh but uh it was good to see that CI
felt welome and had a great
time to be honest though when I saw that
eai uh wasn't going to participate when
that was announced like super gidy
[Music]
giddy W Who
whoo um it it was like 2 days before the
festival and I was about to say how
about cuz we're now missing one person
how about we bring C to our team but I
don't know it was so late that I thought
I didn't want to make any changes now I
guess if it if it doesn't come from C
herself then what the
hell I guess I guess this is uh where
she already feels comfortable so yeah so
we were missing one person but
yeah uh instead we got Mo Senai to help
us out a couple
times actually no it was a so Senai once
and Mi Senai ones super Senai joined our
team for the r red light green lights oh
my God and uh M Senai was the first
runner for our
relay I see I see I see what I see what
you want me to do but that's difficult
I'm trying to use the hover but it's
difficult to control right
[Music]
now don't M it can I float throughout
the whole thing without reactivating it
though oh I
can oh it runs off after a while
it's uh just stops after a
while o that's that's super difficult to
[Music]
time
wait
what it's not safe down there how was I
supposed to know
[Music]
that oh my God I made it I made it that
was very
tricky that was
[Music]
wait you missed Peach I got a peach just
now but how do I get over to the left
side what the hell later go back
down oh no I think I messed something up
just now cuz I wanted to go back down
and I already activated ah wait that's
how I go up though wait where's the
peach that you guys are talking about I
think I just soft locked myself
though where's a peach I did get a peach
there were two wait stop I don't want to
land on the
bbba
where I can't go anywhere from here
I only
die on the right
there what what are you talking
about I'm too stupid to jump on
there I I can't go through there
though I can that's like a
secret I thought I can't go through you
guys know the game too
well
hi hi hi hi
ah give me the power of the
BBA BBA elevation let's go
okay oh now a secret Peach and here it's
over it seems
[Music]
so all
right thank you what am I supposed to do
here
though am I soft locked
or will they activate thems will they
come
back it spawned me on the other side
y it spawned me on their side where I
wanted to go to
nice no don't shoot me no no no don't
shoot me no
no
no gosh these roofs man
oh oh wait
no babysit by the game not so very
difficult though
okay ride in my
heart right into my heart
man broo is Coco No Coco is broo I can
stand here
not for very
[Music]
long okay now I'm getting mad now I'm
getting a little bit
[Music]
langry no
no
[Music]
it ah lightning straight to my heart oh
oh oh uhoh twice fans uhoh uh-oh
lightning straight to my
[Music]
heart it go oh no never let it
go I'm getting mad for you this is
ridiculous are you saying you're getting
mad at me for being bad at
it then I say that that is
ridiculous I've been so good today okay
give me one one part where I can up
a little bit come
[Music]
on can I go oh oh no
I thought I couldn't stand there oh nice
spawn thank
you this is really
difficult what's
up what
up it's also not very clear sometimes
where you can stand and where you can't
cuz on that lowkey burning house I
cannot stand these this little um the
edges of the
roof are so
annoying W he shoots straight
[Music]
huh
n
n NY
I okay the moment I land on that roof I
have to quickly climb on the left roof
okay quick oh I can't make it I can't
make
it
[Music]
edges a
oh go go go
go too
[Music]
early what
you it's not fair that's not
fair you should have C me I head Bo what
the
oh my God what is this
[Music]
what is
this oh there's a peach
[Music]
there
hallelujah oh my God that section I
never want to see it ever again
or is that the
end oh it is oh
wow why are we here just to
suffer wow that was quite
something oh my god oh yeah oh yeah
battle
time uh no no no no no no no no sir
no ow ow ow
ow oh why did I switch weapon again no
no I want the other
one wait I'm I'm I'm really bad right
now I think I need a break from this
game
oh there you go this is what I
wanted yeah meat
Shields two ones from two different
directions oh no
no oh he's coming he's coming from
behind
oh
enter why is it not
entering oh now now it did what the hell
what was that what was that delay
there what was that what was
that stop it
oh do I have a rose somewhere lying
around
no and another
one coming in with the
clutch it
it stop it already
oh God ah
Hallelujah
yes okay this time I'll do better this
time I'll do
better you need umbrella I was trying to
activate it like two times but I had it
at the wrong
[Music]
timing uh
oh
sh kill
him what I I got you with that one don't
lie to
me oh he wants a slap me no no no
oh
am I too close y it ow holy
okay
okay Kwa is in control
again
uh oh my God where am I DOA
sorry I thought he was going to do
the the fire ball
thing I'll kill him while we're at it
and
nice what do you mean I didn't hit you
with
that I need to change the camera
angle so okay
okay you're going down I'm yelling
[Music]
to
okay a the doll arm broke up but
normally when you um pull out the
umbrella when they're shooting at you
then they stop shooting
after that normally like they shoot
three times if you don't block them but
if you do manage to block them on the
first try for example then they stop
shooting and they didn't so I'm confused
a vampire got to 500k really half a
million half a
million yo yo thank you guys for
listening to vampire I'm glad you guys
like it so
much thank you I'm hungry I'm so hungry
[Music]
oh another puzzle all right fine with
me once more the shadow dragon winds
along the path follow the dragon Alice
ah I see how it goes makes perfect sense
really at least now it
does it's the same puzzle how unoriginal
why couldn't you get a new one huh
huh go down
okay oh no more
[Music]
fighting slugs only no way ow who was
that who shoots at
me no it does look like slugs only so
far bleaches bleaches everywhere
is there like a spawn
point no I guess it's just to fight as
many leeches as you
can and then you'll be
free you guys need to put down more
torches in this
cave otherwise too many
enemies hey why is it
and there must been this feels like
endless but this is like I can't destroy
that it maybe a couple more ah
okay that was it okay okay okay
okay nope not infinite
aboral okay one Cube down
a couple more to
go anyway back to the topic of sports
festival I think mostly I said uh
everything I could say I don't know do
you guys have any questions regarding oh
regarding
something I just want to say that M and
Mi Senpai are absolutely amazing for
doing that me Miko Senai was doing so
many Minecraft streams leading up to
that
working hard on it so I really respect
that holy like what you can do with
Minecraft I was actually surprised about
it
h
no
and yeah very inspiring what did you
think of the rting what what was that
mean that question what am I supposed to
think a fleet interview hold talk when
oh ah this makes the move
perhaps H
yeah
uh yeah I was watching a little bit of
the Vault from their point of view
and I was looking at this screen where
me samai on the left side and mik S on
the right side commentating and stuff
and you know what I thought when I saw
that this could be me and
Amy I thought that it would be so
fitting if me and Amy did something like
that like not must it doesn't have to be
Minecraft it doesn't have to be a sports
festival or anything but I just totally
saw me and Amma in that position and I
wrote that to her too and she was like
yeah let's do something let's do
something cuz I feel like Amma is just
really good at both commentating and um
shoutcasting as she wanted to do it in
the Mario Kart Festival already and uh
just creating some some kind of big
project to begin with like planning it
out and all that and me I think I'm also
good at that like I can't do that VR
stuff and all that I'm not I don't have
much knowledge about it as she does but
still I think I have my own oh oh strong
suits and
yeah I just kind of wanted
um us to take that role because it's
literally only me and Amy who do these
kind of like big collapse inside of
whole life English who come up with
these project
so you two would be amazing for
that I agree thank you yeah I totally
can see the vision of it you
know I see
it I just don't know what because
obviously I don't want to just copy what
what M and mo Senai did I don't want to
just blatently copy
it and both me and Emma agreed to just
coming up with something anything but it
must be something big it has to be big
it has to be huge
yeah would be down for VR sports
festival we are going to die or at least
me I think H myth would
die oh wait no no no never mind maybe
Cel too because we I I keep on
forgetting that councel was on desktop
and that's why they were so
energetic what it was there two PPS I
don't like it oh I took the right one I
think um yeah I keep on looking back to
that big we collab the Halloween collab
and thinking oh I'm too old for this
council is so energetic but no no no no
it's because they were on desktop they
weren't doing VR it was just us hold
M that's why I felt like I couldn't keep
up with
them could do a game show or something
yeah I was thinking about stuff like
that
before yeah yeah yeah we'll find some
kind of original idea
what's up this lady holy it was it
was human faces before but now it's an
insect is it trying to tell me something
oh wait there's a button there I guess
that opens the door or something I
didn't even try to go for it but
okay chess tournament nah I want want it
to be something that is a little bit
more appealing to uh a wider
audience I mean yes chess is maybe
appealing to everyone but um I don't
know because everyone knows chess but I
wanted to be something more fun than
that oh look at me no no no no wait
no is it closing no why am I just stupid
to get up there fall
guys it's just not much variety then if
it were something like fall guys you
know with Minecraft you were able to put
so much stuff together oh I was supposed
to go
here you were able to put so much stuff
together it it had a lot of variety to
it and I don't think that will fall guys
it would be the
same okie dokie uh
uh how do I activate this again oh yeah
okay
um wait a
[Music]
second
huh why I want to move this
one why can I not move the bottom right
one
HH 20 second what the no wait
H I can only move those two
away the is going
on Corners are fixed now I can only move
the the left
ones or like select the left ones
on but wait I don't want to move that
anyway I want to no no that makes no
sense they in perfect
position I can't go to the other ones
before I was able to move the these two
now I can only do
these I'm selecting with the arrow keys
but it doesn't go right here it doesn't
go anywhere what the
hell is this
buged bu y
now I can go up but I don't need this to
be here and I can also I can't I can
only select these middle free so the
only thing I can really do right now is
keep on moving the same
one cuz that won't move
obviously this won't move obviously this
won't move I can't go right and I
[Music]
what what am I
but now it's
working no not
always wait a second I think I figured
out the yeah okay so with arrow keys I
can only go up and down but with W ASD I
can go in all
directions
uhhuh so right arrow key and left Arrow
key key doesn't work but the upper Arrow
key and the lower Arrow key works and I
was only using the arrow keys but it was
only going up and down what the
hell
H that's so weird Okay so anyway let's
get into this uh this
one needs to
[Music]
go uh this one goes here this one goes
here this one goes here
this one maybe goes there I just wanted
to bring this one here for now ah maybe
this is actually pretty good I'll go
here oh a I did it the gate is opened
now it appears that I can continue my
Ascent to the peak is your keyboard okay
no it should be fine see now it works
right arrow key left Arrow key but in
the puzzle it didn't
react
[Music]
okay you know what I haven't heard in a
while a snoot whereit where are the pig
snoots H kind of
sus
easy all right all right all right where
is this
not oh
yeah this whole level is long or is has
I has it been two levels by now like is
this the second one I've been doing
today
cuz the Asian Vibes are still on ongoing
and it's still the same wasps and all
that is this still the first level I
started
today I can't go for
here stop moving please stop
moving this one is just really long
huh no no no
yeah my outfit also didn't change yet
it's been this since like pretty much
the
beginning oh there's a not there
where H I can't see
it h
h no oh I do not see it do you guys see
it maybe I'll see it
later no
sure yeah same outfit so I suppose it's
just a Long Level
Sho Nice
Shot
uh um I don't know are we close to
finishing this level I I I think it
would would be good
to um end the stream or like end the
game play part when this level is done
but I hope it won't be much longer they
abuse and murder us they let their spawn
feed on our rotting C you should have
seen what they were doing to the Doos
okay that was much worse so stop
complaining you're actually still alive
so what the
hell the
doos unbel what they did to them I love
[Music]
those you should have seen what they did
to KF hey
motion what is it that uh you have seen
would you like to share it with me your
Superior your boss would you like to
share your
concerns what is it that you have seen
with your
eyes maybe the problem is not what you
have seen but the problem is your eyes
did you ever think about
that maybe we need to get rid of those
very
eyes lovers often exchange a lock of
hair to symbolize their vows human heart
is opened by a vast assortment of
keys
keys did I scare you guys it's all just
a joke J it's a
joke guys don't take me so
seriously it's
joke you know that don't
you ah these chickens always so scared
ah the last player
ow the bonking sound is so satisfying
holy
moly
wow are you guys going to be able to
come to the shin meami tensei stream by
the way it's pretty early as a streaming
time for me I hope the sea people are
happy I hope they're all going to come
it's a good time for sea but shitty time
for PST and early morning for EST I
think PST is 3:00 a.m. and then EST is 6
a.m. I can make it really you going to
stay up for me to 5:00 a.m. you don't
have to you can also watch the the um
archive if you want but I don't know I I
just I just because it's sponsored you
know close I canide Red Riding could
back work I know my multiplication TBL 2
11s I do not care frog
really pretty frog to remove the
obstruction wake the Frog and empty his
belly what's in his belly like that what
about it tongue and the prospect of
thank you Chad I watch The V thank you
boss you're the best thank you you're
the best it was done while I was
sleeping I'll check the Vault afterwards
thank you the thing is with um oh
dear what are
we oh
okay uh with sponsored streams I just
feel this pressure of having to deliver
and having to bring in a big
audience because I want them to feel
like it's worth it hiring me you
know understandable
right I want them to be like wow t
w w
have
it okay I'm I'm trying to
focus understandable thank you already
good
reputation I
wonder I mean I understand that for some
games yeah there's just not much
interest there I understand why are we
focusing on that right
now okay are we going to play the fire
game
now I know we would I know we would
that's
fun oh wait wait wait for
me spash slash slash slash slice slice
slice slice
M got to love my hacking
slashes oh here he comes
oh oh I stopped him
immediately yeah I think for smt it
doesn't seem to be too much of a reason
to worry because you guys are way more
excited about it than I thought you
were so um I I just wonder about the
time zone because I don't usually stream
that early
yeah but uh I'll be going on my little
trip on that day later on that day so
eh
let's uh start the day in a good way
what is this what what how how do I
empty his
belly by doing a good sponsorship stream
what what do you mean empty his belly
I love Persona so I like to see smtv
smtv SM
T5 understandable do I just kill
him I can't hit
him
what shoot the go ah at this thing
oh it doesn't do
anything I feel like I'm missing
something really simp oh a that thing up
there that's the and that makes so much
more sense I was like since when is that
thing called a Gong isn't that just like
a water
cooker looks like one of those
uh wait it doesn't work wait wait wait
wait that doesn't work either
what if I pepper this
thing no what are we
doing no
reaction aha well I found something
else which is I think not related to it
but
okay oh
the frog is just immune to my
charm
how try to get eaten by the Frog oh what
wait a second oh no this was related to
it after all
oh and fr W you did it good job are you
happy now what a cute
frog a it's like a god actually I think
it I think this is supposed to be some
kind of God with that rope T around it
and it being like a huge
frog
some did he open the door for me here
what a
gentleman thank you I love you froggo
wait no this is where it came from what
did he
do what did
he oh wait he he opened up this
hole
Tas
oo
o secret hole
oh oh dear I preferred them when they
were human looking I don't know about
this just I'm not really into that the
body looks good
though the big hole that is hard to miss
but you managed to
anyway I excel at that kind of stuff you
know it's my strong suit not seeing the
things that are the most obvious that's
what I'm good
at you know these nests have kind of
been freaking me out all this time like
it looks
like like a bees
one oh that's why the enemies
oh there's the connection I just
realized it
now
connection I got the feel for you
[Music]
never let it
go let it
[Music]
go never let it go I'm so addicted never
let go oh
oh I really don't like this shape by the
way I'm just
[Laughter]
saying f
oh no to
the I thought we were going to do one of
those fights
again I guess because there are no more
Hearts to give
away all right you know the good thing
about this kind of level is that there's
no fighting there's only platforming
[Music]
woo there might be enemies but the
choice is not whether or not to fight
them there is no
choice so was there anything else I want
to talk about
today bo bo a boing
bo bo bo no I think I
said pretty much everything
yeah and apparently though there going
to um copy the rest the rest of
the uh attractions from the sports
festival onto the uh Japanese sports
festival server which I think is really
cool because those are so much fun I can
I totally just want
to use it to play around with sometimes
I I can't get up
there n
[Music]
I can't get try the left one yeah maybe
maybe
maybe come on hello hello
hello oh oh oh okay okay okay that works
thank you for the message a raccoon so
cute don't worry about it College oh man
that sounds tough I haven't been to co
college so I respect
that oh I feel like that's going to come
down and kill me no oh no we're already
done that was a short one excellent
excellent with
GG we're still getting new
ones
really oh so maybe the maximum of hearts
that you can get is to in throughout the
game any VR plans in the future yeah
yeah I totally want to do more stuff but
but but I need to take the time um to
get Amit to explain it to me and also
for like K I kind of wanted to use a
model
that's wait a
second I kind of want to use a model
that's that has fingers but you know
what maybe I can get it to work
tomorrow the the normal Wy model maybe
the the vampire
one doesn't have fingers but oh well
it's still
cute uh I
think H but I would need to wear that
stupid helmet the whole time
right I think I think
so unless I get a different tracker from
my head but that's impossible until
tomorrow I'll see what I can
do but don't get your hopes
up
yeah W and it might not be very smart to
use that for uh for a marathon endurance
Marathon Maybe better to use
it wow didn't even need the hammer might
be better to use it when I'm just doing
a short Carefree C Oh I thought I was
having a sequence looking at you because
I didn't see
myself didn't it feel the same way to
you
guys I was like what am I looking at but
okay same right
okay by the way I've been really needing
to go to an idol meeting for quite some
time now but I didn't want to go cuz I I
know that whenever someone goes to take
an idol meeting there's always people
leaving the stream even if it only takes
2 minutes the people
leave and I don't want
that I really need to go those I've just
been hoping that the level is going to
end soon where the hell why am I stuck
oh no I'm not
stun we can wait I will stay r i don't
believe it I don't believe
it yes only the Savage regard the
endurance of pain as the measure of wor
this is so
long yeah pain and pain because I need
to go to an idol meeting and I'm just I
just won't let myself
I am an idol I will not use a gamer
bottle what the hell what no no I might
be a gamer as well but that doesn't mean
I will use that I will not go to such
lows wa I want to go back
up diapers no diapers are not okay
either
o why do you know that word you learn it
from Max and CH Sensei huh oh wait
wait wait wait I need to focus I need to
focus focus focus focus
focus a bunk a
bunk I have decided to switch over to
the sword after he stunned once because
that's automatically stronger
it my HP is kind of low though
help
die
yeah y yum
[Music]
yum okay okay uh wait
holy I'm getting really good at
dodging
yo
okay more more wait what the hell
what
what wait a second did my flower go away
I wasn't able to pick it up was I the
enemy is flower the the health bar
[Music]
thing you better drop some for
me they they are dropping
some okay what the hell give me give me
give
me there's just one flyer left I think
or or not
yes there we go
snot
snot snot snot
not careful
careful let's fill you
up all right right now idle meeting idle
meeting
time no I can't go I can't go people
will
leave a
ah it's really fascinating
though if you keep on streaming they
will they will stay but if you go for a
moment even if if it's just for two
minutes they're like no I guess now is
the time to
go now she disappears for 2 minutes now
is the time to
go
memor regrettably the creature has to
die image to be properly captured the
subjects of our Bonk that
booty
Bonk beautiful lady I am so sorry I
couldn't hold myself back you can bunk
my booty if you want in
exchange no no interest
okay you look better from behind right
now to be honest um
goodbye wait it doesn't continue There
does it
I don't think it
does
okay ow what
what stupid no
I'm going to go to an idol meeting
please
[Laughter]
stay please stay to
the I was gaming so good today and you
catch me at this this moment when I'm
basically
myself I want you to see the good side
of myself I was can the chat please
please confirmed that I was doing such a
good job in this game today like as if I
was a different person can you guys tell
her I'll be right
back get my reputation up
please
e e
I brought chunkers with me
a
Jun oh oh baby such
cutie
Cutie she was sleeping next to the idol
meeting uh
place in the corner she has a favorite
corner there because she thinks she's um
invisible there and and and the moment I
I walked past her when she realized I
was there she was like and then she ran
after me and and threw herself in front
of me and to get me to pet
her I just it's these simple things but
it's so cute I have to tell you guys
even though you guys don't really
understand so where is
everyone it
actually a few people left probably to
trigger me now that I said it so often
to not
leave you ch challenge me can I up
upgrade something no we're we're getting
closer
okay
quack I heard frog what we be wi do oh
yeah oh my
God I'm about to die
here did you guys notice recently G has
been coming to my streams more and more
often I think it's because I've been
playing all games that she likes she
said she really likes Alice madness
Returns and she also liked the little
nightmares and all that I'm glad I'm
glad I'm playing games that she
likes oh again we just came out of
one
M thank you Goa I guess you're not here
anymore but thank you
for checking Oh no you're still
here I like you to Oh you mean you're
not coming for the games coming for me
her could not suffering she began to
fight against the Savage murderers
abusers and defilers without quite
knowing why or who seek she truly fought
or how the struggle would
end titty look good there's a titty that
I I can jump on sorry I wanted to say
that because of
TI sorry good
sorry
GA sorry GAA oh my God I'm about to die
here oh I got no HP Help
me nice stomping though thank you for
killing the enemies I appreciate it and
push yes we're finally killing them all
no
mercy everything that is in the way must
be
destroyed and S
and smashed wait I want that peach
please give
me don't tell me I messed up okay I got
it
Peach yes sure and another one
oh
wow my head on a spike just how the
Queen of Hearts likes it
H doctor I got a a a huge piece of
bamboo stuck in my head do you think you
can help me with that perhaps I see a
peach there how do I get not here not
now no okay not now I
guess a splitting
headache what what could the cause be
Pro possibly is it is it because of this
piece that's stuck in my my
[Music]
brain oh oh Pro
Gamer oops oops I got too cocky
again uh wait where are we going I want
the teeth Toth aha there's some bansy
things down here too down there too oh
no hey Alice Focus
Focus get your together come
on thank you AC you acquired me Tel
finally free from the shackles of
Shadows Insanity what the fires of
Madness burn so
colorfully what are you talking
about thank you I don't understand
though what chuni is that what you call
a
chuni oh wait one more
please he spent too much time in the US
usual room what did I send him to the
usual room I don't recall
oh get small get
small Juni kiss your brother
no no that's not what I
mean chuno that's where the that word
comes from chuno is kind of like a uh uh
uh um Junior uh High School uh or
Elemental elementary elementary
school illness wait which one was it
Middle School syndrome okay that's
probably a better uh what the hell
better
explanation
yes Eighth Grade Syndrome and if that
doesn't tell you what we mean either uh
it's basically you know how uh those
middle schoolers or eighth graders
they're like they think they got some
special superpowers like dark flame
master and uh I don't know hiding one of
their eyes behind an eye
patch because they have to hold back the
power they must
not re unle we their full true
power
oh all according to
kako H yes I that was a lot of
references
toin I like that anime I liked it a lot
actually back when I watched
it and R's last name is the same as my
last name
Tak right because every time I look for
GI
gifts
on on twit
Twi uh when I can't find any more Ki
gift ships it shows
mea
uh maybe I should jump uh it shows me
Lia gibs and also some girl called uh I
think what was it again
Takahashi Takahashi
kiaha
so what the is
this okay Morty summer wait a second
wait a
second Mor sum wasn't that one of the
nicknames of one of the chibio
characters but what why is it so
so why is that so
fitting
I that that
way I got a similar name to R and then
cellie with
Mory both of our last names are in that
anime oh my God coincidence I think
not okay I think now I understand
this you don't need to jump you just got
to go to the other side
okay mon s was the tuni who stopped
being tuni oh yeah I think I kind of
recall something yeah we did
it brain expanding yeah it was meant to
be
perhaps oh my God you all play pretend
constantly we don't what do you
mean I'm Tak Phoenix part time waria oh
no of kfp is there anything you doubt
about that I have proof right here my
audience they're all working for me kfp
where you
at you guys are literally the proof tell
them that I'm not just
hallucinating tell them I feel like
we're getting to the end of this
level are we it looks like it it looks
uh dramatic
oh there he is and I came here with
basically no HP I hope I don't have to
fight
him I don't have to fight you do it but
why are you why are you uh made out of
iron or something like that can you
move caterpillar son all this way to
find a similar If I Had the Time i'
detail how often you prefer dealing with
Illusions rather than the real thing
problems you refuse to deal with don't
exist you deny reality that's not right
I know what's real no just just it's too
familiar with the conversation we were
just having I am real I don't deny
reality I'm real and you allow others to
tell you what isn't real now but that's
like telling Pinocchio he isn't real
right am I
Pinocchio coming
side a
it are we done with this level
now that's your nose grow perhaps I just
haven't ever lied before that's why we
haven't seen a grow in my nose before my
memories are shattered this wicked train
has ruined nearly all I can recall and
Wonderland will would you walk a bit
faster girl so much has changed I can't
help Wonderland if I can't help myself
much has changed but you've got it
backwards save Wonderland and you may
save yourself the carpenter was on to
something but he was hiding from the
real your goal is to accept it where
should I go then what should I do the
queen must be served Alice the queen and
all her guises must always be served the
queen look at my HP y wait who is
that that it oh is it is Shrek it's you
how can you stem this growing corruption
or resist myself what does she know that
I don't she is someone you once knew and
loved time changes us all not all change
is good remember that when you find the
thank you for this
it's falling
apart he got
wings fly like a
butterfly oh and there he goes leaves me
alone Shrek became a
butterfly
what we're done with the
level nice it did indeed take me 4 and 1
half hours
FR howling outside the old lady
muttering about a why am I in the prison
cell cursing insects on the national
railroad
in Min to herself but no danger to have
her surely she don't belong in jail to
True g a o l what send her back to Dr
Bambi he raised o l last time I kept her
overnight oh what happened is that the
way they say it in in the UK waste of
money Mother's Love was NAB all
spelling I was taking Alice down and two
coppers walking Jack to the cells he's
mad than the usual never wrong bloke
nonsense when he sees Alice that's a
what done it he she you miserable
C you L you maggot living off another's
labor etc etc I'm admiring her line of
inquiry suddenly she hits her head or
something and fats couldn't their own
could
I I guess bumby pitch a fit said he'd
had me jobbing me ass on a plate told
him he could have the former leave the
letter alone thank you very much good
night Al Can't you stop talking right
now I'm so sick of you're hearing your
voices for
sake Jesus Christ oh my God I'm
so sick of this thanks for letting me
out I was close to killing you with my
eyes yeah I can do a Bame a Bame a Bame
and then you die I'm better be careful
who's in
here when he s is up this fellow will
likely ask to go down to the cells his
fellow inmates don't want him sicking up
in the cells many of the homeless prefer
an overnight in the jail rather than
living rough on the street you like
British
kiaha oh I appreciate that thank you
chat thank you that's so sweet of
you bloody
helmate uh is this reality I don't even
know I've got a book too I just don't I
choose to not read it smart am I I know
I know I know this kid are you from my
house it's
Tuesday wait no it's Monday what what
are you
saying you stupid oh what oh cat
Cat come with
me I'm not that far off really my aent
approved a lot in you
really that's the real accomplishment
here why is this
tilted I'm back in the fake
world it's oh no it's a
jail touch hand check
event uh so which Idol should I line up
for
M you maybe I know who looks the
cutest I want the cute
one I'll become your fan I'll oi I'll oi
you or it's a heart
gate wow
oh oh it used to be hands but now
it's
tentacles T check event with the ancient
ones is K out there otherwise I don't
want to handshake it all yo live by the
terms of # woke # Yol you're doing it
right
mate nice only 5 hours of game left yeah
we're not doing it today that's for sure
[Music]
[Applause]
falling into the rabbit hole again oh
oh
oh new outfit let's go oh did we wear
this one before I think we did but is
this a card wait wait that reminds me of
the sand uh sandb bird
[Laughter]
level I'm still doie doie couldn't you
have healed my health back up come
on wait this is fun I like this too oh
now I got healed
than than you
[Music]
snoot snoy
boy I hear
you how come I don't see
you
SN where are
you now it's getting faint I I can't
miss
ah invisible snoot snoot snoot
son I am I hitting you
yeah what okay are you telling me to go
that way all
right o thank
you FL stolen his heart trifling with
his affections creepy sword touching me
my heart baby was that really the lyrics
never let it go oh oh never let it go oh
oh
oh I literally can't stop oh my God go
[Music]
back I feel like uh we should end it
somewh here huh but I'm having fun this
feels like freedom
oh
slide
oh did I miss something I hear another
snot another
[Laughter]
s let's get those
teeth wait where would that lead me I
could already enter the castle of those
cards but we go here instead is this
what it's giving me is that it
really but we're back to 500 tee boys
and
girls
oh
o and the music is so chill too you hear
that it's very quiet but very calm it
feels like it's healing me
[Music]
this is
nice this is very
nice thank
you how
polite what's
here it's like a
m yeah it's super bright oh is that like
a
keyhole light
light is useless if what it illuminates
causes pain and suffering better to cast
such things into the dark depths of leth
the river of forgetfulness I feel
insulted shut up
[Music]
idiot okay yes so perhaps
I should end it but I
can't I can't and this looks so pretty I
want
to no you know what there's too much to
look at right now I feel overwhelmed
already by not know knowing in which
direction I should go
first yeah all right and we're going to
read Super Chat those H I'll take a 2
minute break to get knackles and then
read the chados
yeah so feel free to join me in my
office after the shift ends because
officially the shift is never over I'll
see you in my office guys okay thank you
for watching today next Alice episode
will be the last one so make sure to
come to that one as well otherwise it's
like watching a Netflix show until the
very end and then just not watch the
last episode like what the hell why
would you do that I I mean I did that
with the handmaid's tail but just
because I'm a
coward but normally you shouldn't be
doing that okay okay
so calling myself out
exactly see you in a moment byebye don't
go don't leave
[Music]
n
I'm
[Music]
back wait
PA guys let's
[Music]
go guess we're playing fall guys just
kidding welcome back to my
office wait maybe in the office at least
I should put back on my
filter ta
okay I made a big cup of tea again a big
one my biggest
one k when is Christmas office oh I
don't know honestly yeah we considering
how fast uh shops put up Christmas
decorations uh if we compare it to real
life my office could already be a uh
yeah that actually no I actually got uh
see I don't even really know if Eden is
working on a Christmas Version so far
there was no talk about that however I
did get an updated version of the normal
office because uh the the vampire cover
was added into the
layout so
oh and wait what is that oh there's also
a picture from the Halloween stream in
there as well now yeah but uh I don't
want to change it right now I think
because uh it's all messed up over there
but I keep on pushing these kind of
things uh and pushing and pushing and
and I keep on saying I'll do it at some
point but I never get to it I always
forget what movie are we going to watch
that's a good question so right now I'm
considering Narnia cuz that was quite a
good suggestion because that can also
turn into a um a series we can watch all
I think there's free right free Narnia
movies and I've never watched them
before and it's isn't that isn't that
kind of like fantasy-ish as well so I
think it's actually
uh yeah something that would interest
me I've only watched the first one then
let's watch the first one together and
then the second and then the third as
well it is full fantasy well nice
haven't seen those in so long well there
we go that's good that's good if you
guys are up for it then we should watch
it
together I've never seen them I totally
ignored the existence of
[Laughter]
it I
[Music]
it's been years since the last time I
watched those movies yeah I I assume
that for most of you it's going to be a
long time which is good because then you
maybe don't remember the plot that
well I wonder how the CGI holds
up yeah I watched a little bit of a
trailer and it looked
good we need
but that's on when is the m stream
that's on
Wednesday no first thur day thur day
right Friday is when I'm leaving okay
okay yeah yeah yeah so tomorrow is the
endurance K and then on the day after we
have
Minecraft yeah wait let's look at the
schedule again here this week's schedule
ha I still had some really cute
Halloween fan art left over so I wanted
to use
it so we just ticked off Alice man's
returns from today tomorrow is K and
Minecraft and a members movie and then
Shin Mami
T that's new and
sponsorship yes I'll be playing it for
like approximately 2 hours hours I don't
know how strict they are because with
other sponsorships they were usually
like yeah play as long as you want as
long as you play at least the minimum
time but you're welcome to go over so I
wonder I wonder if I were to play a
little bit more if I were allowed to
play a little bit more
H I'll check up on that um it's just
like with jrpgs in in one or two hours
there's not really much that you can
show cuz jrpgs often start pretty slow
and they show
[Music]
meow and they show the story and all
that and introduce the characters and
all that hi
Chun don't worry it's not no no no I
said this already during the stream but
this is a sponsorship by Sega Sega
so I don't even think they would be that
strict but I'll check up on I'll ask if
they really wanted to cut off at exactly
2 hours but it's just like they they
don't know how far I will get in two
hours right like there's no way to
know
so yeah maybe they can let me go a
little bit further as long as I don't uh
cross a certain point in the story maybe
or something like that I don't know I
don't even know if I would like it cuz I
never played these games before M meow
yes yes yes you're excited too yeah I
got sponsored yeah yeah awesome right
junkers yeah
uh it was funny how everyone went so
crazy like I figured that at least some
people would be excited about this
sponsorship but I did not anticipate the
amount of craziness I think most people
just got crazy because they never fought
that it would be uh possible to play it
because of Atlas but
[Music]
bambooo bambooz I got
you
um however do you guys remember I think
uh I know there's no bgm on by the way
yet I'll put it on in a moment you guys
remember I think I think last
week someone here either in a super chat
or or in the comment mentioned I think
Shin meami T to
me and was like um I think I think you
were asking me if I would play it or not
you guys remember
that and I was I don't know I don't
remember my reply but I think I was
something saying something like oh yeah
I don't know looks interesting but I
don't know but at that point I already
knew I already knew but then the chat
was like I think oh no way that's Atlas
that could never work and I was like
yeah yeah sure of course yeah seems
pretty impossible don't get your hopes
up but I already knew I already
[Laughter]
knew well this time I I I was hiding it
well cuz you guys really didn't expect
it bambooo
so my tea is still too hot I
think I'm
Bo let me eat some
Pokey can't trust YouTubers these
days don't trust me
[Music]
yeah I think I'll leave this up on this
screen so that you guys if you haven't
seen it yet so you guys can see
[Music]
it
music oh these are so
good chocolate sticks
[Music]
oh you don't hear
that today it feels so comfy I don't
know what it is but I feel normally when
my streams get too comfy I feel worried
about it because I don't want that to be
my streaming
style but today I feel all right with it
it's
[Music]
weird and detective I think you should
be fired because you didn't anticipate
[Music]
that it's not that I don't want the
comfiness it's more like I feel like my
audience um likes me for being energetic
and giving them happiness and
stuff
um and and I my own streaming style I
see it more like similar to the Japanese
whole life members so when I get too
calm I feel like I'm not um uh
100% giving it my
[Music]
bestest but today I feel all
right thank you thank you you don't have
to be energetic we like
you I could watch you being sent for
hours T that's a little bit creepy
[Music]
I love you guys
mhm I love you
guys let me
see okay we are
now
um
5,900 Subs
away M can we get to 5,000 until the
stream begins tomorrow I hope so
[Music]
I don't want to fail at the challenge
though that would be so
[Music]
embarrassing here's
hoping
[Music]
yeah where uh where did we leave
off I think I just need to read uh
little nightmare super chats and two
days right I catch I caught up until
little nightmares I
think right yeah yeah yeah
okay again I feel like I can't breathe
well why why why why why does this
happen to me h
[Music]
little nightmar today okie dokie thank
you for the red super chat thank
you thank you so
[Music]
much okay
thumbnail
thumbnail didn't the thumbnail turn out
so
cute where is
it there so simple but I think that's
one of my best
thumbnails I like it I um I put that
little fan art on top of the actual
character and then I separated the logo
because it was too close together and it
I couldn't position it well without
actually separating the top part of the
logo with the bottom part of the
logo wait I just noticed something was
that wait let me label nightmares logo
oh no I just
realized I messed up something here cuz
I was separating it and you see those
little two dots above the little I
didn't
notice those are the feet that I cut up
from
the uh the character and the logo oh
but it it Blended in nicely I guess
it didn't stand out too
much didn't see it until now good I
didn't see it either I didn't notice
Oh I thought it was the perfect
thumbnail now I can't unsee that damn
[Music]
it okay there we
go I thought it was part of the logo
yeah it it it didn't stand out huh I
just noticed it now
loveely BM thank
you it's kind of not very loopy
[Music]
though that doesn't exist though
you know what I thought was funny
today me playing Alice today and an aqua
Senai announcing a concert with the
Alice theme
today m
did you guys
[Music]
see
mhm oh a bunch of you guys didn't
know let me show
you it's super cute
[Music]
ch
ch where is the image for that a
it that's not
[Music]
it did you not Retreat
that it must be on the whole live
account then H
live H live there we go oopsie it's so
cute the visual is so
adorable
T I don't know why I'm uh promoting this
right now but I don't know I thought it
was cute and January 28th Aqua Senai
second uh solo
concert look do you see that whole Alice
uh aesthetic the like the her cat is
like I don't know like uh uh dressed up
as those Knights and then also has the
clock
and her outfit has the the apron has
those card
signs it's super
cute and the merch looks so good
[Music]
too let me show you the merch
yeah I like the
t-shirt and and the towel I like those
M yes very
cute and then there's
um and there's this those
spoons how the does does the do spoons
have any significance in the Alice world
I don't remember but somehow it fits
really well
look at those spoons it's so cute with
her reir weird
[Music]
cat tapestry is oh I can't wait for my
own tapestry because you remember my
birthday tapestry the artwork for that
is so badass I want to see it I still
don't have it
and then there's this keychains cute
keychains and acry acry stand M wow I
like the pose I like the socks look at
those
socks on the side of the socks is this
pattern that's so
cute I don't know I felt like showing
you guys I thought the coincidence was
cute with the whole Alice thing
you got the email update last night on
did you hear qu where you here in the
beginning you're one of the winners did
you
know you're one of the giveaway
winners GJ just emailed me that it
arrived in the warehouse but seemingly
shipping to Germany is suspended
suspended suspended what do you mean
suspended
not you you mean delayed right is that a
translation
[Music]
mistake H DM DM from Al uh American
miy EMS is suspended Japan's postal
service has suspended almost all
international shipping what the
well it will come
eventually will come
eventually please wait a little bit
longer it's not that not that far off
anymore it's it can't be much
longer EMS is suspended but they emails
are outdated oh it has resumed oh there
you
go
M hold
[Music]
I'm so excited for you guys to get your
merchandise and then post it on Twitter
and be like look I'm wearing the apron
and my slippers in reality the reason
why I got you guys merchandise to wear
on your body was just so that I could
get pictures of all of my employees
[Music]
I hope my slippers fit yeah they're
probably going to be really big so that
they uh they fit most
people it's definitely like suitable for
men that's for
sure so unless you have a shoe size I
don't know
European 50 or something I think you
should be fine
creep chw excuse
me
bamboo oh yeah yeah yeah the employee
the employee ID that's a sticker yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah that's right that
that was also a thing for only only for
people who bought the full set I think
[Music]
yeah you can have pics of me anytime K
send that to your girlfriend
50 would be quite the soon you know what
they
say you should always write say so
comments guys because you never know
when I'm going to pick up your
comment normally I see like the moment
that like half a second before I read
out a comment I I like register it in my
brain only roughly with the words that I
say that without actually registering
the whole meaning of the sentence but I
can kind of already tell if it's okay to
read or not but you bamboozled
me you bum Boozled me there because it
started out with as a good sentence but
it ended up being
[Music]
y use your room
go you must
go you must go you must
pay chat reflects the streamer shut up
not in this
[Music]
case Okay I I said I would start
reading let's go let's read Super Chat
[Music]
guys looking for the top
H uh okay I already need my scale my my
Super Chat scale
got to put them on a scale see how much
they
weigh uh wait what did I
do p
Ln pln pln pln pln pln pln
PL there 250
aha uh oh that uh ends up being a pinky
I can do math wow wow
okay over half a year ago I found a job
and was worried that it will cause me to
miss some of your streams oh it isn't
that bad on morning shift I can watch
you after work and afternoon ones I can
watch you relative peace at work
recently I became a sampa and got an
indefinite contract oh your streams help
me relax after a hell day at work still
find it hilarious when I wake up for
work I can see you active on Twitter
well you are in a very close time zone
to mine so I think as long as I don't
stream early in the morning European
Time which will never happen I think uh
you will be dble you're uh one of the
winning kfp members
here yeah same p
z much love Tel sometimes I wish to
stream Sparks at work because of some
cause but that might be a little bad to
start the fire here help desk
pain
understandable very understandable able
but I'm sure you're doing a great
job thank you thank you for your support
and I'm glad you can still somehow
balance uh your time with work to still
watch my streams thank you Ace Crown D
pigeon d k you have showed up in my
dream 17 times just thought you should
know that wait why
17 is there a meaning behind that
[Music]
is there mean I'm probably reading too
much into it but the Pat is dreaming
about me
cute that's quite a lot yes that's
freaking me out
actually cir's anniversary D soon one
more month give him Freedom or give him
death H we're playing Minecraft on uh
Wednesday and I honestly don't really
have a clear plan on what to do we we're
probably going to finish the
tunnel um H not finish I guess uh
continue because I don't think I'll
finish it I don't know we will see how
long it takes me um but I guess we could
also try to save circles if we get done
early if we finish early maybe I'll go
check out
circles
but H I might forget again oops
see
maybe yep what if I go there and
then he's not there
anymore I circled him in a prison I
think to protect him but I can imagine
that the game by now for whatever reason
would have made him Escape because I had
that several times with like alpakas and
and stuff I don't
know and similar
things only one way to find out exactly
then he escaped and he's out for Revenge
Revenge why would he want revenge on me
I've tried to protect
him as long as the chugs are not loaded
she should be fine I don't trust
it I don't trust
it Donald irvy D
[Laughter]
great Hench hen oh great Hen of the CH
of the kfp what is your wisdom for
[Music]
today
wisdom my wisdom
[Music]
is why
one
two
five are the precious
numbers that you must
desire and
[Music]
Aspire not because of the Gooding or
whatever lottery ticket numbers no
because they're reaching 1.25 million
the next Milestone feels like it's been
a million million years since the last
Milestone it's really been a long time I
want to
[Music]
celebrate
yeah taii thank you for the red super
chat
regular what regular what you're a
regular see I was already wondering
about that last
time maybe he's
saying he wants a regular sized coffee
or something but you're the wrong place
sir or I guess does K sell coffee I
guess we
do maybe we do well thank you
taii Optimus
Prime
sad
monkey lion plan flights of fcy D motion
D flights of fcy d
ah talking about backing when we got
D patri Tony bz
d patri d Barack Obama D for the
pinky she really just did that amazing
oh thank you yes I did that oh my God
[Music]
unbelievable oh hi
oh my God Barack Obama reminds me
of
yesterday I got this really weird
recommendation in my YouTube
recommendations
yesterday
um right after my stream ended yesterday
I was a little bit late on tweeting out
because
because I opened this
recommendation which was basically
someone
explaining this stupid show you know
those reality TV dating shows like The
Bachelor or whatever and this show was
about
um I think the title was Marry Harry or
something like that or I Want to Marry
Harry or I don't know it was about
marrying the Prince
Harry and um this girl she was like
explaining the show and what was so
wrong with it because it was actually
not real hairy but they deceived how
many 10 American girls that participated
in that show um they deceived them from
beginning until the very end trying to
make them think that that is the real
Harry even though he doesn't even really
look like Harry and he never really like
was so obviously proving it like I mean
they were like playing it up by like
letting him show up in a helicopter and
stuff um which I guess was convincing
enough and him having a butler and all
that but I cannot
believe how this is even allowed
to it must have been that they already
knew about it but apparently they didn't
they were really deceived but how is
this all
a dating show where you're
being casted to uh try to date a guy
that I mean you only accept to join this
dating show because you already know
that you're supposed to flirt and date
Harry the prince they're putting this
idea in your head that you might become
a real
princess but think about it there's AB
absolutely no way
that the royal family would
participate in a freaking reality TV
Bachelor
show think about
it no way as
if that's the the first moment where you
should have been like something's not
wrong but not not right about this is
the moment you saw the whole idea the
whole concept of
this no way that the real Harry would be
doing
this that is so stupid like if you fell
for that I guess it's kind of your
fault if you fail for it then you have
no one to blame but yourself but I still
think it's an absolutely
ridiculous uh idea for a TV
show because that is basically a
scam what the
hell they all know about it but
somehow for this one apparently they
really didn't like some of the girls
figured it out throughout the program
throughout the show and were even um
like they were being kept from The
Producers to telling the other girls who
haven't figured it out
yet because they didn't want the other
girls to figure it out so whoever
figured it out uh was being constantly
monitored to not tell to tell the other
girls it's scripted that's what I would
usually think but that girl the way she
was explaining it sounded like they
really don't know I never watched the
actual
show but I am a tiny bit intrigued uh
because I want to
see which which type of stupid person
would fall for this
[Laughter]
stupidity there's no
way I'm not even from England and I know
that there's no way that the royal
family would do
that you just got to watch the crown on
Netflix but I guess back then that was
filmed in I think 2013 and back then the
crown on Netflix didn't exist yet okay
okay okay okay I'll give you that
[Music]
anyway that was something that I watched
yesterday I don't know I kind of like um
hearing people talk passionately um and
very
knowledgeably about things and shows and
websites and stuff that I have no idea
about just like the whole Club Penguin
thing like I had no idea what Club
Penguin was like but hearing someone who
was really into it talking about it it
it felt like um I I caught up on
it even if I'm not going to play Club
Penguin or even if I'm not going to
watch that stupid show it's still
interesting to hear them talk about
something I never got
into like when you when we listen to you
talk about Idols ah n
n imagine thinking reality TV is
actually real in 2021 well I don't watch
reality TV at all I think when I was a
teenager I maybe watched a little of it
like I guess I watched like Flavor
flame horrible show horrible
show but yeah in the past um let's say
10 years or so I haven't I don't think I
have watched any reality
[Music]
[Laughter]
TV yeah Flavor of Love oh my
[Music]
God okay let's read this um Miss
D wait there's a Korean Super Chat uh
Korean
[Music]
translat
thank apparently it's pronounced gome
and not
gnome gnome ghost d d for a pinky if
it's a steam game and controller does
not work try go into game library and
stream client right click on the game
choose properties choose controller tab
you will have option to choose override
choose enable stream input huh I did go
into I don't know if it was exactly the
same place but I did go into some kind
of settings with um the
controller but it was already set uh it
recognized the controller
supposedly but not when I went into the
game I don't know next time I'll try
that thank
you gome GH ghome
ghost
Bar D gnome with wings
thank all these GN of Dad thank
you if you connect before launching the
game yeah that's why I literally
restarted the game name during the
stream in the
beginning why not continue
mispronouncing no it's cute thank you
well yeah uh it's kind of a a habit I
think because in German it's pronounced
literally
[Music]
gnom you play too much Among Us
am am DM me with an
idea
[Music]
oh got to get back to her
way you don't hear her is am a muted I
hear her I hear her all the time
24/7 she lives rentree in my
[Music]
brain SAR have you seen the monogatari
prequel movies they did tell the events
of when anagi was a vampire and first
met shinobu and oino will you consider
it for a watch along sometime you don't
need to know series to enjoy it
uh I think I have I'm pretty sure I
watched
everything that is in video
form everything that I that exists so
far oh katar yeah yeah I watched all of
the kiz monogatari movies I think I even
watched them in Japan when they came out
first uh in the movies or at least one
of
them I think one of them I pronounce I
watched in
Japan yeah maybe the last
one yeah was very interesting I love
K the
scene one scene that will never leave my
memory is the one with adult
shinobu in the Train Station underground
uh let's just say missing some body
parts holy
man that is an image that is burnt into
my
brain wow crawling
oh yeah that happened oh no ah
D
boots ISAC of Cl rouder 1337 D you're
the best and oi D saus boots dun crab
cakes dun D Dylan chai than I was just
wondering if there was a chance of a h
life collab with Minecraft championships
especially after awesome after the
awesome Hol Sports Fest thank you so
much once again for all the awesome
streams wish you all the best thank you
I do not not know what that
is what is that also I want to change
the bgm I need something
[Music]
calm
yeah better much
[Music]
better thank you
tyy it's an awesome MC for fun event
uhhuh I don't really
know I don't know about
that J SW D Captain hum hum pants D
black d saus
boots boots please save the poor
sausages it's cute how you react to the
sausage part zire kitten d
and please play spal D boots boots
[Music]
D again thank
you ABC 97 D Randy RJ D fanfiction d as
a proud member of kfp I'm obligated to
donate money on my birthday to
you thank you for all the smells you
have brought to me and for the birthday
fights you are bringing this day oh
happy birthday was yesterday but still
happy
birthday
congratulations
yay I it does have a little bit of AC
Vibes yeah a tiny
bit sorry can I just bravee in and
bravee out for a moment
[Music]
it doesn't get
better
no it's so tight
[Music]
let me let me open the window for a
moment and breathe in fresh air I'll be
right back
[Music]
I'm you
a good baby
[Music]
I think it's a bit
better I
think I'm going give chunker some belly
ribs
yeah imagine it's you who's getting the
belly ribs Ching belly ribs okay byebye
chunkers byebye
oh I drink some more
[Music]
tea no I'm not calling you to day I'm
close to finishing these super chats
anyway I
think uh I mean somewhat close
[Music]
wait I need to reload the chat on my
side I think I need to talk quite like
calmer I put too much energy in my voice
in order to speak more clearly for you
guys because I feel like I don't speak
um English clear enough uh or at least I
I used to uh not speak clear enough and
I noticed that and then I tried to speak
clearer but it takes up a lot of my
energy to speak like
this you speak fine nobody like compared
to how I spoke back in the
day cat
hair
[Music]
okay
Mo Daisy monkey Randy RJ D tur Ferguson
D see if I read it like this I save much
more energy but I feel bad about not
reading your Super Chat
enthusiastically know what I
mean I don't want to sound like I don't
appreciate
[Music]
it outrun the
wind gnome ghost D muff muffins d l
frack
[Music]
not L thank you for the red super
chat let's go have unleash the
apocalypse was that around the
end cuz I was it definitely looked a
little bit like an apocalypse at the end
little nightmares was really
interesting I didn't
expect this kind of game like the whole
Meat part was so
weird actually my mom was watching the
stream too afterwards she um wrote to me
[Music]
something she told me let's see she gave
me another game recommendation let's see
what you guys say about this one she
said um I did a good job at little
nightmares you should try out um I I
think you could uh without any problems
play alien isolation it's a masterpiece
and I never heard of that
before alien
[Music]
isolation that's from
2014 so viral horror computer
game it's
terrifying scary oh you guys sound
terrified oh no you
can't my mom Believes In Me but you guys
don't you can't handle it kada that
might be a little rough for you are you
guys saying this is worse than Outlast
you won't handle
it Mama you hear this the chat is like
pretty United on saying I cannot do
it it's not a jump scare game it's worse
than outlas it's very much so Outlast
still scary in my opinion same te is
Outlet this game is 100 times worse than
LS oh so I guess it's it dark place
frequent jump scares oh but is it
relying Less on jump scares and it's
more like about being generally
scary is that is that
it mama don't recommend horror games to
me I don't want to play these horror
games you're not going to get far with
recommending this to me
[Music]
I think you could do it
no now that so many people you guys said
the same thing about Outlast to
me that I couldn't handle
it
hu is it like looking from the
screenshots it's a little bit hard to
tell like what do you do you just go
through like a spaceship do you shoot
them do you try to kill them or can you
only run like an
Outlast VR oh hell
no hell no I'm pretty sure that makes it
a million times worse only run you hide
from the alen you can
try AI it looks honestly from the looks
of it it looks better to me than
Outlast like from the how to say I feel
like Outlast is just it's just like
kind of I'm not sure how to describe it
but it's just so obvious um from like oh
Asylum oh people who look up but
this I don't know the Aesthetics of
alien isolation looking at these
screenshots look
already better to me do you know what I
mean it's just maybe what I'm looking
for is the word
tacky
H Maybe
it's just like when I think of a horror
game it's like oh yeah
well I don't know freaky people trying
to scare
you I a cliche yeah
maybe yeah yeah it's just yeah too on
the nose I guess so yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah you get it you get it
it's generic yeah it's
generic maybe maybe you get my point h
[Music]
I think like most horror games
are if you think about it they're all
pretty generic maybe that's why I don't
like them that much as
well maybe that's one my one my problem
with horror games is too cuz I really
enjoy having a proper
story proper characters and all that you
know that's what I like about games
that's why I love jrpgs they have a it
it just it just feels like it has so
much more meaning to playing a game like
that then to a generic game where the
mission is to run away from Monsters who
are trying to eat you whatever kill you
I don't
know I
mean all power to you guys who enjoy
that and I understand I mean Outlast and
hindsight I I I think I think it was fun
to play
but it would never be my first choice
because I feel like I get so much more
out of playing a
jrpg okay okay Resident Evil I give you
that that's definitely prob I assume I
never played it so I don't know but I'm
assuming from what I've heard that
Resident Evil has a proper story and all
that and uh that that I give to you I'm
sure that is uh you you get much more
out of playing that probably
yeah or Silent Hill I guess I don't I
don't know but I guess you guys are
saying that so I
agree yes yes yes but what did I get out
of Outlast
nothing maybe a fun time with GAA yes
but like the game itself it didn't teach
me
anything it didn't tell me a
story yeah okay you guys got content and
funny screams okay okay you guys got
something but I didn't get
anything I mean that doesn't always have
to be the the goal of it and that's fine
I'm just saying that uh this is why I
prioritize jrpgs and stuff and why I
like it better not saying that that's
why it's not worth being played or worth
being streamed totally I understand how
that makes like how that is interesting
uh you guys like these kind of games and
all that and it's funny to watch you
like watching girls being scared by jump
scares everyone has their own style
exactly that as
well yeah the RPG stories are generic as
hell usually oh yeah I get what you
mean um there is a pattern to jrpgs
which um I guess it's like kind of a
baseline oh also that applies to tales
off games uh they have on their own they
have another kind of like
pattern typical tails off pattern
but I mean still
[Music]
I yeah that but that's just that's also
another reason why I kind of uh
and last interest in anime because I
think anime most story lines are also I
mean for the for the maybe okay there's
a lot of non-generic ones as well of
course like back inat but back inat also
has some small parts about it that is
also
generic ah like
cliche there's I think yeah there's uh
uh a kind of cliche to everything
somehow
H it's okay to like and dislike things
exactly there are things that I dislike
games that I dislike and I don't really
want to play much um but I understand
that it has a charm to other
people um where was I going with this
though I was go I was trying to say with
this that the alien isolation
uh looks of it looks less cliche than
Outlast Point period end of
story anyway before I make too many
people mad let's
[Music]
continue JY cool
horror you know me you know
me you know me you know me good
music Jacob 47 soon Eden than soon G
soon thank you Jim Tracy D FAA thank you
for the red super chat T you make me doy
doy too I don't have the courage to play
this kind of game by myself mama's so
brave and smart thank you well little
nightmares was
really not that bad I thought the the
whole part with the long arm boy was the
worst
out of that whole game everything that
came after that was totally fine the
game seemed to be more forgiving
afterwards as well which is weird
because shouldn't it be the other way
around you adapt after a certain point
maybe maybe that's what
happened maybe I did maybe I did the
same thing that I did without last I was
too scared in the beginning and then
later on I got used to it
[Music]
no I think long arm boy was really scary
though the way he followed me oh my God
and the way he looked like oh my God and
what he was doing was way more scary
like the concept of what he was doing
was way more scary than for example the
cook like I don't know you know what I
mean cuz the long arm boy he was
like he was putting those
[Music]
bodies
um that was
freaky he was more proactive too yeah
and though honestly it was way easier to
run away from the cook than from the
long arm boy the long arm boy caught me
so many
times I don't think it was only that I
got better at the game no no no no no
way we're talking about takanasi kiala
here I don't get better at
games H his blindness made his mechanics
weird yeah he Hur me all the time
[Music]
man give yourself more credit well I
will say today I was hella
good thank you Fafa you can do it though
I mean you're welcome to watch my
streams instead of playing it yourself
you're totally welcome to do that but
feel free to play it maybe alongside
[Music]
me boots J
swet
[Music]
J
Lu it sounds like Louis vuon
Gucci happy B birthday oh it's your
birthday today's my birthday today I
will be so happy when you say happy
birthday to me did I sing I feel like I
reacted to this on stream because I was
trying to sing it in in
Korean uh
[Music]
a okay Dragon Spire thank you for the
pinky great J oh oh yeah okay great job
at the sports Fest team captain Ki you
flew like a The Majestic Phoenix you are
it was a great time for everyone thank
you I saw these screenshots that you
guys sent me on Twitter um I think it
was from from Bale's point of view where
uh I was flying right under the dragon
silhouette beautiful that was indeed
beautiful but um you should also watch
the I think I retweeted it anyway but
you should watch the
uh the point of view from mik because it
looked very beautiful on there as
well very symbolic
yeah I saw the pictures from K she she
was very busy as a photographer
huh Dragon by Danish Edie Danish for the
red super chat hello real life and time
zones made it hard for me to catch your
streams but recently I've been able to
and I missed it here so much oh
really you you came back thank you it's
been fun catching up by I just wanted to
show my appreciation for all your hard
work you are an inspiration thank
you thank you for not forgetting about
me thank you I appreciate that kiss kiss
[Music]
kiss I hope you're having a great time
here at kfp and don't leave again and if
you leave again you better come back but
don't leave don't leave
please okay p d you black FR than or
pyot black F thank you for the two
pinkies I actually too oh my God why
does my stomach hurt so
much it's
stinging
stinging now my whole body hurts it
hurts everything hurts my neck hurts my
shoulders hurt my spine hurts my stomach
hurts my uh my chest uh inside hurts oh
my God H sing hello I'm doing kind okay
tomorrow
wink hint
hint Tommy
H call it a day no
no
no was watching to call in Callie's jump
King stream and I noticed you said
something about wanting to expand your
vocabulary or are you going to teach
me through this I had a idea for you why
not do a stream where you and call go
each other I tried to teach you modern
lingo and hell even a bunch of Pop
Culture references so you can get all
the times and up to date my Boomer roshi
sounds like it can be a fun zdan esque
type idea side not you did amazing in
the sports festival proud of you H I
think I mentioned this before but um a
long time ago before
Deb I was asking
Gua that if we were to collab together
if she could teach me
um if she could teach me uh some memes
and stuff cuz cuz I got to know her know
her and uh my impression was that she
knows her memes and I guess I was
accurate uh with that right from the
getg
girl uh it never happened since then but
um I guess somehow on the way she still
automatically naturally teaches me
memes without even
[Music]
trying yeah big meme
girl like reverse streaming
lessons I wonder if she would do
something like that because these kind
of lesson type of streams require you to
actually prepare something like a
teacher
yeah h
[Music]
become as sensy can she do
that my stomach
hurts what about your price for playing
Alice oh yeah I haven't haven't uh
really discussed that with her
yet got to start looking into the whole
CA
thing I think if it will happen then it
will probably happen in December because
cuz I already feel too busy in
November I feel like November is um
going to be a weird month and it's going
to be over in an
instant I mean December probably as well
though uh and I I might uh the song
cover with
Ena I'm I don't want to uh stress out
the creators who helping me with it too
much uh so it might be actually the
first week of December or something it
might not really make it in November um
oh yeah and I'm also still working on
something for
hinotori which is coming up soon the one
year anniversary that's also in November
I think what was it the 22nd or 26th or
something like that Thanksgiving when's
Thanksgiving when was when was that
again
um actually um there is a m a lot of
people involved in what I'm preparing
for you guys and
currently uh I'm a bit worried if what
I'm preparing will really make it in
time because there has been a
delay uh but it has to be on time so we
got to make it work we got to make it
work
yeah it's it's pretty big guys
what's coming for Thanksgiving is pretty
big I it's like a huge Christmas pair
present to you
guys kind
[Music]
of turkey outfit no
new outfit oh I have to tell you guys
it's not happening in November I'm so
sorry it's not my
fault it's not happening in
[Music]
November remember when wait when did we
announce it
h one year anniversary September
September
um
I yeah
well it's it's coming
soon but not in
November I I kind of needed to tell you
because it's beginning of November and I
don't want you guys to keep on waiting
and waiting and waiting and hoping for
it to happen in November it's not
happening
happening um there's there are some
reasons for it that you will eventually
maybe understand but so far please just
wait and hold the line hold the
line yeah please
wait will it happen at all of course I
mean you guys have seen part of the
silhouette of course it's not like it's
just an illusion or like a something in
my imagination it
exists I I've been I've been waiting for
it guys sorry sorry soon soon look
forward to it but um yeah the thing for
hinotori is
unrelated to
that the new outfits are myth
H my new outfits are
my no don't say that you got to believe
in it like you got to believe in
Pinocchio why is this the second time
that I'm bringing up Pinocchio
[Music]
[Laughter]
today thank you for the
pink for
[Music]
for
black thank you for another pinky
actually I'm GNA give you a kiss cuz
that's like the F
pinky those people that say Dark Souls
is too hard are the same dummies that
say Outlet was too scary I believe in
your skills you got this kiaha oh but
isn't Dark Souls one of those games that
we don't get permission for that's the
one that uh uh Calli was asking for
right yes so probably not happy
happening so fluent and German wow well
it's my first
language it's my mother
tongue English is my second language I
learned it in
school o 3128
Halloween where did you
go
baby where are you
reer dark
t thank
you thank you for listening to vampire
Dusty D for the red super
chat hello my cute and Majestic tantel I
love this game and thank you for playing
it oh wait this is for Alice sorry it's
mixed
in uh are you here Dusty I'm reading
this early um I played this when I
bought my first PC and feel so nostalgic
oh what first got me interested where
the CG trailer take a look if you
haven't yet very creepy oh great gamepl
by the way love you thank you yes yes my
game play today was on point Thank you
for acknowledging it h
acknowledging um no I never watched
those CG trailers sounds interesting I
can
imagine though yeah might might want to
check it out
EG
knowledge you know what I've never tried
before eggnog eggnog eggnog sounds
disgusting to
me does it taste like egg like warmed up
egg juice or something like that that's
what I imagine when I think of it
but not at all yeah I guess
so what does it taste
like liquid ice
cream where where is the egg from then
why is there no egg in there it's like a
milkshake
milkshake it's alcohol ah oh so
milkshake with alcohol is that what
you're saying ew ew ew ew no more I
don't want it anymore no anyway Dusty
thank you I'm glad you were enjoying my
playthrough I'm really happy that so
many people enjoyed Alice I didn't
actually think that it would have such a
good um uh uh popularity with you guys I
appreciate that thank you for supporting
me with it than you soon we're finishing
it next episode so please come to that
uh episode next
week lagy couch d patri d m d not thank
you for another red Super Chat sorry he
I love you but even you couldn't give
get me to live in
France hey that's rude to the French
viewers that I have the few ones that I
can count on my hands on my
fingers not all EG nugget holic oh oh
there's non-alcoholic eggnog
oh well done scaring her away from
eggnog
needlessly you you seem really uh mad
about that with your caps lock okay okay
if I ever um stumble upon non-alcoholic
eggn I will give it a try don't worry
most French people feel the same way in
my experience you know you know what was
absolutely
horrible that Netflix show with that
Girl American Girl going to FR France
that was one of the worst shows I've
ever
[Music]
watched Emily I think it was Emily in
Paris horrible horrible
show and I think um French people were
also really annoyed with it because it
doesn't quite do a good job at
portraying uh France and Paris and
French people
and it was so tacky it was so stupid the
only good thing about it was Emily's
cute outfits I literally looked up the
outfits she was wearing in that show
several times and tried to get the same
ones but every single thing is sold out
wherever I look so it's
impossible but her fashion choices are
what what what do they always
say what do they
say not J I don't want to say
that and
uh
magn
yeah where am my French
people something
[Music]
with what am I thinking of what word am
I thinking
[Music]
of I don't
know CLA
[Music]
maybe that's what I was thinking of but
now it all just sounds like weird mumble
jumble to
me okay never
mind thank you not
LOM BL Dan not little Dan again for
Pinky uh to everyone saying it should be
hea yes you're right but I've mainly
heard that used as oh my now I I misread
that Super Chat the first time I read it
I thought he means boss and Mom together
but okay now I understand what you were
actually
saying okay so he is used to say Mom and
he is used to say boss okay well now I
finally understand I can watch your
stream it's been ages well hello it's
about to end when I'm done with the
super chats though but you're welcome to
watch the vot thank you
m thank you for coming by
but why do I think of something like jel
or something like that I hope I'm not
saying something
weird I can't help it I can't help but
think about it
je he feel a boss it's just a people
called the mom's boss of slang oh that's
funny
[Music]
that's so weird like like oh wait I
guess wait that's funny because you guys
do the same thing with
me I'm your mom and you guys call me
boss
too it is quite common is more common
than I thought it
[Music]
was you know what I imagine right now me
standing in front of that Conspiracy
Theory Board and being like it's all
connected guys it's all
connected you van very
what what the hell you guys are so
weird no the board always comes with me
I'm attached to the
[Music]
board Jacob 47 looking for
the for the red one I love
Tak thank you
D and that's it with the little
nightmare super
[Music]
chats let's
read the ones from
today thank
you thank you guys thank you
you see how Alice has this like smudged
emot eyeliner all around their eyes it's
so smudgy I remember back in the day
girls used to do that those emo girls
putting that eyeliner all around their
eyes and then inside like their eyelids
I could never do
that holy respect to the girls who
can put eyeliner on the inside of their
ey it guys you probably don't know what
I'm talking about I think that sounds
weird but yeah
um yeah I can't do that
ew I freak out when I try to do
[Music]
that yeah emo emo
eyeliner I can barely put on eyeliner
normally well I'm I'm good with eyeliner
normally but not on the inside of the
eyland
E it's near death experience every time
understandable yeah on the waterline
yeah yeah I'm just exaggerating with the
way I phrase it but yeah it's on the
waterline
[Music]
yeah okay let's do this
FR thank you for red Super
Chat there comes the apology
foro it's too late to
apologize it's too
late it's too late to
late please forgive me kiaha for sending
you super CH
sometimes I'll do my
for some words fall me English so I just
mix now you're just doing it on
purpose love you tent love you too thank
you no problem don't worry about it it's
okay I just I feel a bit embarrassed
when I have to read out something in
German but you're welcome to use German
it's
okay but but try try English when you
can you have to practice it here I force
you to practice it I am your
teacher it's a good opportunity to um
force yourself to practice more English
yes yes yes you will improve thanks to
me your German is cute oh thank
[Music]
you and thank you for from ah bye-bye
why am I saying
bye-bye I'm not leaving
yet Empire marry
P that is a red Super Chat thank you
m no is not going to the usual
room feels like I haven't super chated
Ki in a while and I won't be able to
catch the stream oh leaving a note here
so I don't forget to me when I check the
B please send a super cute a cute Super
Chat to Teno and thank her for all her
efforts don't let me down future
me but you but you already did
it this is like super chat message
reception no reception you're you're
calling yourself in the Super Chat to
tell me a cute Super Chat to send me a
cute super chat but you you but you
didn't
but but this is this is it
[Music]
though what
what but this is it so this is the it
already
[Music]
happened it's Shing our Super Chat
thank
you for
D that sounds like I said the word the
free word letter word but it's not it
says Z
[Music]
exx it says K can you pause the game I
have to
pee
no Andre dunon
thank
you oh congratulations on
recovering
Mo than pudding Chanel rookie 24 25 I
can't count rouder
[Music]
le as
life Alexander
you're not crazy like red green but ra
rather menacing what is indeed
attractive at least for
me me being menacing is attractive to
you especially when you change to your
serious ton of voice
ahuh
okay thank you she say than soon om FG
Blondie than soon
what I don't know what that
is Gator Vader D he doesn't know
D baby baby
[Music]
explain n NES Mario Bros please
Jessie
L
one WF than
[Music]
soon not a
h
interesting I will write that
down hold how would that isn't that
basically just a huge obstacle
Co Takeshi's
Castle someone said how about Takeshi's
Castle app clutch in Minecraft call it
takashi's
Castle isn't that basically just a huge
obstacle course
though isn't that just what it is
H that's just fall glass
H fall guys never gave me Taki CLE never
gave me takesi Castle Vibes though cuz
it's like I guess more colorful and
happy you put zombies and arrows to
shoot people as they try to make it
through
oh I will have to I feel like probably
already someone made something like that
probably but I'll look into
it if if it looks different from what
mik Mi did then maybe it's worth
thinking about it no one D Daisy D Petri
Dan Ultra D Maverick sign D Petri D
Tomahawk PV P WPT D and Daisy
D
[Music]
and oh
uh
[Music]
uh Daisy MF for oh these are flash CHS
oh I can skip them
nice no love B again with Hello I would
love to recreate
that like a no laughing
allow oh I would love to recreate
[Music]
that one of those oh my
God they're not not necessarily like
sell Library like um more like maybe
more like the the the
24hour and doing something something for
examp
you know the ones I told you about that
they always do at the end of the year um
on New Year's
Eve yeah yeah yeah um what would the
punishment be
eh I mean uh it would be the best if
they could all have a friend over who
would slap their booty every time they
laugh and we hear the
slaps oh no wait I have an idea instead
of the slap booies the booty slaps we
could have them um maybe that's fairly
easy to get like a like a you know how
the like these electrifying thingies
that uh maybe maybe um you know we can
Electrify the
electrocute those who give you like
electric
shocks holy
like not two tough ones aren't
there like like I don't know and I I've
seen them before in whole live official
streams uh where I think I've seen P
Senai do it too before like they or or
like for genen they did like a quiz in
3D in the 3D stream and there was like
an Electra shocking button and uh they
would push it and like if they say I
think they was something like they were
saying the wrong answer and then um they
cuz they were touching it they would get
an Electro shck from it and I was always
wondering if that was acting or if that
was real but they must have at least
gotten a tiny bit of a shock out of
[Music]
that Stream box
uh so so something like that get that
for everyone and then uh have us all
have a theme okay okay okay okay listen
listen have us all have a theme let's
say for example policeman so we all act
like we are uh police and uh we are not
allowed to ever get out of character and
then I'm not sure if we would do this in
Minecraft or anywhere else but let's say
it's taking place in Minecraft I'm brain
in right now um we built this whole we
built a uh a Minecraft police station
just like the the those uh 24 hours
downtown stuff thing
is um and and and and and uh in that
huge police like that kind of Acts a
little bit as a obstacle course but not
necessarily not 100% but anyway so what
would happen in these ah okay
listen okay I have I found a way wait
this could happen in VR chat actually it
could maybe but anyway listen listen no
matter where it happens so we would have
this huge police station and we would
act as policemen and then just like how
it happens in the actual comedy series
um in a comedy show the Japanese one we
would have like for example council
members come in like one by one like for
example let's say fauna comes uh into
the room or or we go into a room where
fauna is and she um does like a whole
comedy bit trying to get us to laugh and
if we laugh we get an Electra
shock name that a minut te would keep
going but doesn't it sound good
Yaki not Sky basically it it oh my God
and then and then uh yeah we we take a
little bit of time we do some challenges
in between just in the like in the gy
not Sky show like we do a challenge that
is kind of like related to the whole
theme like police or whatever and and oh
my God oh my God oh my God okay I'm so
inspired right now cuz I love that show
so much and I think they're not doing it
this year so wouldn't it be funny if we
tried to recreate it this year can we do
it until the end of the year oh my god
oh see see pH foone boy where are you
where are you where are you I need
you write it down write it down oh my
God holy holy holy holy
ho oh oh my God oh my God but
do you think that Iris and Council that
they could come up with some bits it
doesn't have to be a 24-hour thingy so
just 1 hour do they think they can come
up with enough comedic bits that they
could entertain us for one I think we
can fill an hour cuz it's not like
continuously like a full hour of chedic
bits it's just like in between there
going to be some fillers like these tiny
challenges like for example if if we
were police or if maybe if we act like
as detectives or whatever I don't know
we could be given the challenge of
solving a riddle or something like
that oh my God oh my God I have this
great idea what oh my god let's
go I think crony and Mum if you just put
them in a room they do their little
thing they're already funny just doing
their thing so if they try a little bit
harder they're definitely going to be
funny huh H I don't think we can do this
until the end of the year though we're
busy busy busy well maybe end of January
or something like that and we'll just
say there was a time
lag time difference time ping it's the
Ping we actually we're streaming this on
New Year's Eve but the Ping
[Music]
not next year no I don't want to RIT the
whole freaking year
no fits the
lore it requires a lot of setup but but
if you think about it the whole
Halloween thing was done in a fairly
short
time H well this could be my
project this time I fund it all and then
it happens on my channel I'mma just
going to help me a little bit with uh
with v are but I I I'm so into this
right
now oh my God oh my God
[Music]
oh I think they would like my idea too
and see I kind of wanted to do something
that's not Minecraft but still going to
be amazing so I think oh trying
to use VR chat for that again would be
great yeah
[Music]
I want to hear that I want to hear that
every time I laugh or or GAA or Ci or
Ina laughes you're going to hear a loud
voice oh we should have crony
recorded it should be
[Music]
like well that's too much
Echo out
oh my
God I can see it i a
t the Japanese Bros who are watching
right now oh they're reacting to because
they know it
[Music]
I'm so
inspired okay okay okay before I forget
this idea I don't know how I could ever
forget it let's finish these super chats
good
Eden salami D the game the whole stream
will be the Batu game salami d
salus beats Dan thank
you detective beats
Dan wait I'm
[Music]
getting
oh okay okay okay okay okay where was
that was the last name I just read I
think salber his Beats I
think where was that I refreshed here a
detective bigs and Dy thank you for the
red super chat hello my cute and
Majestic tantel I love this game and
thank you oh that's the one I already
read now it's here it worked itself up
Sky d p gaming d myal delire d m d g d s
d pet D Jessie link d t d I got to find
a way to explain to the girls what I'm
trying to make I need to find like a
clip that really uh well shows that show
um um maybe something sub something
short like a like a compilation or
something and show it to them and so
that so that they can imagine what I'm
trying to make you know you know you
know you know otherwise I don't think
they're going to understand but I'll
just have to say trust me on this one
trust me on this one girls it will be
amazing I'm
excited I'm
excited I'm so excited and I just can't
hide it well let me go on Amazon right
now Amazon
uh what do you call that
elect
shocker what what was that 500,000 Vol
no no not a taser I don't mean a taser
no no taser no no no like a joke maybe
uh it's joke maybe I write it's joke uh
prank prank
H you know those those those pen Electro
shck gadgets a pen like that that
shouldn't be too strong oh the chewing
[Music]
gum I remember that from my time as a
child but that's too weak no that's too
weak it need to be a bit
stronger but it needs to be something
that's available
worldwide kind of or at least a similar
device
ah ah this one this one like a wait let
me show you like a
screenshot something like
that here wait I mean I would prefer it
to be a bit more painful but
okay I mean they have to suffer
otherwise they're just going to laugh
and laugh and laugh and not hold
back it has to be bit more painful but
okay look at
this the M masochist inside of me is
coming out
uh okay so for example this is what I
have coming up this is like a hand size
shocker yeah yeah yeah uh it's like a
prank thing you know you you can't see
this right you something like this would
be good I think you could get that
everywhere somehow oh s both of it a joy
buzz
it oh those make uh car keys I saw one
of those
[Music]
too Revelation oh my God the huge one
from we can call it yeah we can call it
the the usual room challenge or
something like
that but that doesn't have to do
anything with the theme I want us to
have some kind of
[Music]
theme or or just the usual room
literally call the whole thing the usual
room and then we can do it more often
and every time we have different themes
but I'll have to have them make a whole
map and uh whole outfits for all of H
[Music]
myth because like if it's police and
everyone needs a police uniform and then
yeah the the rooms have to be police
famed and all that or I guess maybe
there's like already like finished rooms
but it would be nicer to have our own
thing you
know K you're scaring
me you can do it with Japan as well yeah
but I want to do it with all of English
so that you guys can enjoy
it but maybe I don't know maybe I can do
a Japanese version once one time
only I can't wait I need to
[Music]
okay I'm so excited I need to finish
these stupid super chats now my my mind
is occupied with something else h colel
[Music]
looking for
the thank you for the pinky d d to my
goddess I must apologize I have been
tempted by a very cute vampire girl ah
for a moment I was getting
mad you mean me okay I never knew kiaha
would discover my weakness but I promise
I'm loyal to you
JMA I hope my love reaches you before
the last of my blood is stolen I feel
[Music]
dizzy p d chip Skylock Don Jim Tracy D
pure Branch frer
[Music]
dun no way suspicious pear
Branch
poer uh
what why are you no way
suspicious
huh answer next oh
okay Ah that's
harine I mean the for some reason even
though it looks different it still looks
similar to his original profile
[Music]
picture my brain inside of my brain
there's a party going on right there I'm
a so I don't think you understand how
happiness and cuteness you're R radiant
when you're passionate about things are
inspired
by well okay that Super Chat reading so
I'm now going to leave you guys and
start planning my super
cool the usual room show
idea I think we got something amazing in
my brain right now and I need to let it
out I need to let it out okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay oh my God oh my God
oh my
God I'm a I'm I'm going to Rite it all
out yes yes yes yes yes it seems I have
been inspired I've been struck by
lightning I stream spars for too long
too intensely too
loud are you okay
no no
[Music]
I'll go work out the details the dets
and already start spamming JMA with who
we need to contact and who we need to
[Laughter]
commission yeah it would be even better
if we could do this as an as an off
collab uh you know what we can start it
out with VR chat and one day if we ever
gather together in Japan and have 3D one
day then we can actually get our butts
slapped by jenma
herself and uh yeah and that way uh we
can interact even better that will be a
special celebrational edition one day
but for now it works with VR chat if I
give them some torture devices to
torture themselves with uh by your
courtesy uh Tashi
Ki okay thank you guys for watching I
see you tomorrow for C okay H I need to
practice I guess oh well see you
tomorrow and enj
[Laughter]
Sal byebye thank you for watching I will
uh write another tweet uh with the
winners again uh tagging you guys so
make sure to uh take a look if you won
and I guess uh where if you didn't win
don't look at
it byee I in I in wait did I not say it
I said it right I did say it I think I
did h
h lable lable lable
[Music]