[Music]
so
cakey
this is this is so scuffed um welcome
everyone to
this scuff stream no it's not stuffed
you're just sick
i yes i'm sick i'm sick
um cali is in the background
hello kelly yeah i won't be here long
i'm going to the spa
yes kelly will go to the spa i
will try to play minecraft
we uh i wanted to play something else
today
but it's not working out so this is this
is uh
um this is minecraft hello cats
wait kevin grew up no
you were supposed to stay a baby kelly i
have a baby
i heard the word upon the street yes you
um
that you messed with my cat uh
yes i let no not me my cat messed with
your cat
okay how did that work out though was it
on purpose
it was pure love
you know somehow i just have a hard time
believing that
it's it's it's parallel and let me give
you something
yay okay guys it's like everything fine
like audio wise
and uh and
it's a stream like is it is it lagging
um i don't know if you guys know this
but when you get the cardboard disease
um your voice gets a little scratchy
almost as though you're using a poor
quality microphone
oh yeah that's another part of the
sickness
ah we have a i bought this like small
microphone what what did this
say
what the [\h__\h] the mic is higher quality
than debbie what the sorry that's right
now that's just that's just
no no no that's [\h__\h] because that is
not true
that is not true i saw it coming i had
to
scroll back up that's a pure line that's
impossible
[Laughter]
i tried to um do like a little test
uh recording before the stream to hear
how it sounds no game audio oh
that is impossible um
it sounds um not really good
but that's how it is wait oh no but then
we have double oh wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait no no no no i still have
this one oh my god
the scarf okay now this will this should
do this and then
we should probably have um minecraft
audio oops no
do you know how to check
wait a second
oh wait i feel like i do mine super
quiet do you guys hear any audio
no wait i don't i don't get that speaker
there's no minecraft
um
[Music]
whatever we don't need minecraft sounds
yes it's like this is
oh thank you are you a beatboxer now
kelly yeah
what does what does the torch say
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding ding ding
okay so um
playing playing minecraft today i'm
gonna get some
some diamond diamonds because diamonds
are good first random if you look here i
only have one diamond left what happened
here oh i was also gonna bring all my
[\h__\h] back
um are you guys okay with that
today was supposed to be animal crossing
i'm really sorry but we didn't we didn't
get the
switch to work unfortunately yeah we
were at it for like five hours
five hours hitchcock yeah i am free free
free
three two three let's say three hours
three and a half three and a half hours
yeah first we tried to fix
our cardboard disease but we couldn't
fix the cardboard disease we accepted
that we were okay with that but then we
tried to at least get the switch going
within the switch
we spent like two hours on that and that
didn't i mean the switch works but the
capturing doesn't work
so since both doesn't work we i'm going
for this now
um but that's okay
that is okay uh i'll play minecraft
for an hour and then later
cali is doing a solo stream as well
on her channel and then tomorrow we'll
get the collab started
is that okay is that okay guys
yeah we were waiting to eat our food
because we were
trying our best to fix this thing
uh well here we are
thank you guys for being so
understanding thank you
thank you um
wait one second one second
sorry i had a little talk with kelly
kelly is going to the spa um
without me because
she needs a little alone time
okay yes yes i gave her a goodbye kiss
yes
kelly you're still there yeah okay
do i have okay i need some stuff for my
we have a diamond pickaxe and we have
another normal pickaxe
and we have we don't we don't need any
of this but we're not gonna die right
guys
we're not gonna die so this is actually
okay but let me just put some [\h__\h] in
here
bye bye well she she did say yeah did
she
did you guys hear that i didn't even
realize that
hey and what am i doing
guys i'm all over the place because i
don't know what's going on
i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
i uh go uh let me explain in japanese so
there might be some japanese spirits
avatar is fresh but i freaking know
you think i don't know you think let's
get some of that efficiency hell yeah oh
yeah
let me get that efficiency now let's
freaking go
where are we gonna mine my friends
where i think uh we could use the watson
shaft
we could go for the watson shaft
let's see let's see
you know we we arrived oh my god hello
you were always here should we kill him
i feel sorry for him like he's always
just there
uh we arrived quite early today but
we spent like five hours of this stupid
technical [\h__\h] that we didn't do
anything and we had to order room
service even though we wanted to go out
you know
um but yeah
so today was uh kind of yeah
we couldn't do the things that we wanted
to do but tomorrow
tomorrow me and kelly will go around
whatever city we are in right now
and we will uh make some trouble
right double trouble right kelly you
will i won't
so yeah tomorrow tomorrow is exploration
day
i might that's my nice shaft
okay do you reckon what what's it what
what what up what up
what is it why'd you say it like that
what did i say
is that my i was just asking if that was
my shuffle come on
and diamonds are we wait
where did diamonds show up again nine
was it nine
do we have to go lower i feel like we
have to go lower
oh callie what i see you in the window
yeah getting naked go
i have a huge window in front of me i
see like the reflection
wait i need i need more torches okay we
have torches
you didn't see anything i didn't i
really didn't see much but
so where did the humans show up guys
where do diamonds show up
wait what the hell that breaks so quick
look look at that oh my god it's like
almost bye-bye time
what and nine to 12.
okay we're i think we're at 11. okay
this is um we're just gonna get some
diamonds
i hope i hope i really hope
oh my god it's broken probably breaks
easily yeah should i have stopped before
it breaks
i don't know uh probably i should have
stopped before it breaks
but we have another one this one is also
efficiency two
eleven is the diamond zone ah i might be
loving yes yes
yes yes it is all good all good
why do they whoa no i don't need that
give me diamonds take forward straight
free
dig fight what bgm and game volume stop
what the key yeah mine's in mine is
giving you electricity
where is my key you know what with those
things by the way in hotels
you think you need to put in your key
card but actually you can put in any
card
by the way yeah yeah that's it
uh okay wait let me turn it
yeah let me loop the bgm guys one second
loop there we go did you guys know that
that in hotels
you know where the slot when you have to
put in the
the cards you you don't actually have to
put in a card
uh you can put a room card you can put
in anything
yeah did you know oops oh it broke again
damn it
i wanted to stop this time before it
breaks but yeah
yeah there you go guys now you know the
more you know
sorry yes this is very scuffed you guys
do you guys like this
kind of stream should i just always
stream like this
is this how it's gonna be from now on
yes i love it yes yes no you guys are
not serious
you guys are not serious i don't like
that you guys just gotta be serious
i need my i need serious feedback from
you guys
also i don't have my shaders on i miss
my shade i was wearing my minecraft
shaders
but honestly like we tried so long with
uh
the switch um in the end i was like
kelly kelly is it okay do you think it's
okay if i just play minecraft
yep there we go oh that's also not what
i want
wait did i okay okay all good
we'll probably guys will probably be um
cardboard for until the trip is over
so i hope that's okay guys
why why nintendo in the description
because i didn't have time to change it
i didn't have everything's just too
scuffed
manchester united
yeah and i know now i'm at ten but it's
like between nine and
uh nine and eleven right
cali did you leave yeah she left
cali is gone kelly didn't say goodbye to
me
you know it's it feels so weird right
now
everything feels so weird why is there i
wonder also why there's no minecraft
audio
but sorry guys
just imagine that sound on your side
just
do it just do it
also i i ordered pizza by the way
oh guys i didn't tell i didn't tell you
what the what the happy
message is the happy news because i
in the pre-chat i i was like oh my god
right and you guys were wondering what
is she what
oh my god you guys are wondering what am
i so
wait wait one second guys okay
oh
[Applause]
i am back hello again
what yeah yeah kelly came back to me
because she missed me
no she needed she needed a
kick for the elevator wait was there
someone here before
or is it just is it just bright because
of the lava
i want to see what's going on there oh
so yeah
the happy message should i open that
there we go the happy message
is i got some game permissions that i've
been waiting for
forever
actually getting permissions from
something that i wanted
the very most why is it bright over
there
yes tails off not all the tails of games
but we got permission
[Music]
i wish you could see how happy i am
right now let me
let me i'm like i'm like this is how i
am okay
oh hey oh my god
namco namco finally came through love
you so much
i love you i love you
yes but only for uh certain ones for now
maybe more in the future oh my god so
dog help help
um for now i got like uh
three tales of actually two that are
already released but
we already got permission four tales of
rice which is not out yet but
but i'm waiting for it i'm waiting i'm
waiting i'm waiting i'm waiting
isn't that awesome so exciting
what's over there oh there's a torch
over there oh yes yes i've been here
before
okay that's connected now hold up
yeah i'm so excited i mean tents have
arrived i don't know when that will ever
be released
oh okay
what uh
[Music]
what i'm so confused this is is this
inception or
what what's
what's going on where am i
um but yeah uh the other games that i
got permission for
the other tales of games are games that
i
already played through before so i don't
know if i'm
what does the [\h__\h] say
[Music]
where did i come from where did i even
come from i don't even know
anymore where am i there's gold
so yeah the other games are games that i
already played before so i don't know
if we want to play that on my channel
uh yeah bursaria is one of them which i
i i enjoyed that so much i wouldn't mind
playing that again it's been a while and
yeah i wouldn't mind and the other one
is tales of persperia
uh the definitive edition which i also
played before
and i usually never replay the games
wait i still don't have a single diamond
when i need to i need to
step up my game we're at 11 okay let's
just randomly dig in here
yeah so we can even
wait for whenever tears of a rice comes
out
or okay nothing's here or
or play one of the ones that i already
played before but actually at the moment
i have like
enough gameplays going on anyway like
we're playing we're playing near right
now
near automata and
we're playing uh actually arizona as
well right now so what else do you want
right
i don't think we'll find any diamonds in
the stream
oh god near shouldn't take too long
are you sure about that are you sure
because i heard there's a lot of endings
and people insist on me playing all
endings
where'd we come from did we come from
now
i want to go back to my shaft
oh i remember that space too
what okay you know what i'm gonna go
over here but i'm gonna go down i don't
know where i am but
we'll find out eventually yeah i know
there's like five
actual endings and then there's x-rays
but
does it i thought it would take quite a
while if i play those five endings
the endings continue after one another i
see thank you for the membership
by the way guys today i will not be
reading super chat i'll be reading them
at the end of the week
and oh yeah for tomorrow oh yeah guys do
you want to like give me suggestions
because tomorrow
we planned on calli's channel to have a
collaboration of
51 clubhouse games but that is a switch
game
oh once again i have connected
damage damn it what let me at least get
out of here and take somewhere else
please
so yeah what else would you guys want us
to play i was thinking
maybe it could work
like uh you guys remember when i played
uh supermarket shriek
i wanna go back when i played
supermarket streak with gouda
what's here
oh let's go up just oh god am i gonna
die i'm gonna die where am i where is
this where is this oh my god
i'm gonna die i'm gonna die wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait where am i
i thought at some point you just don't
know anymore does it go up or does it go
down
um yeah yeah screaming i mean you don't
have to scream that loud
it will be fine go down
okay that's also not where i wanted to
go
what is this stream i don't know what
i'm doing
don't worry don't worry we're not gonna
get kicked out i wanna go all the way up
there is that possible is there anything
there anyway no
oh god oh god
i'm going to die
how do you go faster okay um
help i'm honestly lost
i don't know how to go back i don't know
where am i where the hell did i come
from
okay whatever just um just just
just um
because for a supermarket shriek
uh that game when i played with gooda
uh we had to like normally you can use
voice activation
but since we played it like um how do
you say that
we played it through steam remote play
we couldn't use that properly but since
me and callie are
in one place we could actually play the
game properly
when in doubt dig out and i'm scared
though
i don't want to leave this hole just yet
because
i am on a mission and i'm too high
i'm too high for that machine let's go
down
let's go down oh where am i am
where am i now damn it this this
shaft sucks i want to get out of here
but where did i come from
i i don't know
i don't know
i i always tried going through here
right wait actually
maybe i came from the other side yeah
maybe
did i does anyone know dig up
you think that's safe oh i
i can probably find my way home here
no wait i keep on going in a circle
what is his stream uh
i've been here before i've been here
before
ah hey no
[Music]
no where did i come from
okay digging up that's it let's see
where we get
do you think lava will suddenly drop on
top of me
is that is that gonna could that happen
yes how did i get lost here i've been
here before
what if i build up in stairs is that
okay
that's okay right i can build up in
stairs
but then we go back oh what's this
we go back with zero diamonds that's not
okay
what about just the usual just the usual
just ignore just go up nellis
today is not the day
okay
i can't see it
what what do you think of kelly's new
song oh i i listened to it um
i uh i have trouble understanding
what's going on i real i i did get the
feeling that the song is kind of savage
so i think that's correct
but other than that i don't know what's
going on in this song
i tried to listen to it while reading
the lyrics
but still i i have no idea
she's just rapping so quickly
ra rapping rapping so quickly
but i asked her what what the song is
about and yeah it's basically her being
savage
very nice that's how i like my cali
savage how did you guys like this song
she's a rapper yes yes yes
she's she's dissing yeah i like i like
that she's doing uh
actually before the stream we were um
saying that she should do a diss track
for what was that
she should do a diss track for a certain
uh
anti-virus program that got
uh installed against uh our
our wish i'm not gonna say which one but
she was like hell yeah let's do that
[\h__\h] that program [\h__\h] it
who needs that stupid the install that
[\h__\h]
we were really angry because we thought
we thought that that was stopping us
maybe that was the reason why
we have the the cardboard disease
but now we still didn't figure it out
although that was that was partially
affecting a lot of things stupid program
this stream is really special do you
guys realize that you're witnessing
history
i mean there's some correct names in the
chat but i'm not going to
name thank you for the membership i'm
not going to say
which one it is but there i see some
correct names in the chat
what's what's the best anti-virus
program anyway you know for a virtual
youtuber
it's very important to have a good
antivirus program
because obviously our bodies are
just you know virtual it's so dark
am i ever gonna get what's what's
normally what's like the
the number i want to be at normally
mostly what could it be 50 60
60 it's going to take a while with my
uh with my technique
oh god okay i should i should do this
properly wait okay
so i can do this better also i can
probably do this
nice no no i know i know 11 is for
diamonds but this shaft is [\h__\h] so i'm
just trying to get out of it now but
i got lost so i'm making my own stairs
back up even though we wanted to go down
but
yeah that's that's that's
i tried okay that's fine
i tried it i i i didn't try for long
but
sometimes you just have to accept the
fact that
oh water am i gonna drown
am i going to drown am i
is that is that a problem
i mean at least i can swim oh oh oh
hello
oh hello hello
moshimash
uh just gonna continue uh digging here
okay
never mind she's just gonna continue
it's so dark
that was close why was that dangerous
oh man it's so weird like to stream in a
different
environment that i'm used to also
usually i always have like some feedback
from
my mixer like i hear my own voice and
now i don't hear it so i don't know
everything's so weird different
microphone different
oh
should have brought a shovel
different oh
are we here am i ever gonna get out of
here
but wait wait can i not just escape
through that and get to the
to the top like i don't know wait
wait right there
wait i think i see the sunlight i think
i saw it
wait wait get rid of that [\h__\h] okay i'll
go go get it
we can do it your ears oh i'm so sorry
i'm gonna try to be quiet oops oh my god
get out here get up here get up here
no don't okay wait air air air
you can't no
no
that's not my tower that's wait i've
never saw it
i've never seen that before eno made
that right i never saw that one before
that looks amazing where the hell
am i
watching is that
oh is that oh is that the tower where
hatman killed herself
let's visit ina inna's little temple
very sad here oh very sad over there
what is that for
what what is that
fireworks where can you active is it
possible to activate them
do i have to bring fireworks
and place them here is that how it works
oh
is that it's empty
hey put her her shrine here uh tony
it's called tori in japanese it's so
pretty the gate
it's so pretty
damn okay but how do i get back home
how do i get back home oh don't fit
sweet
there's a lever behind me oh it's better
with shades oh yeah i can imagine
normally i can play with shaders but not
today
so i reckon that we oops we get back
home
by going here because i feel like that's
in us yeah that's home
okay wow what a success
what was that what a successful
diamond hunt
[Music]
what a successful diamond hunt was that
the creeper oh how did you know guys
i didn't hear anything there's no sound
in the game oh hi creeper
oh yeah that's a creeper that is a
creeper
very scuffed yes that's how we like it
would you be watching whole life if you
if you don't like
scuffed content no that's exactly what
you're here for
hello horsey hello
hello i'm back home today united
i didn't get anything from that because
that that shaft is
[\h__\h] that shaft is just [\h__\h] you know
what
we're gonna we still have some time
we can do something else
what else okay guys you decide on my
adventure
what do you want me to do this is your
adventure now
you tell me what to do let me sleep
first though
fishing are you for real
make a window more kitties
fishing what what fishing
why fishing for what what are we fishing
for
what are we fishing for
what are we fishing for for fish
what well that's just ridiculous
okay well you decided that tropical fish
wait how about how do i get it again how
did i get it back in there
wait i forgot how to fish
fish for the cats fishing for fishing
fishing for anthem oh yeah maybe we can
get one of those books
and how do i get it back how do i do
right click again
when when there's like bubbles on top of
it
like when something's coming there when
it sinks
oh oh it comes here it goes there we go
we got a fish but i want a book can i
get a book like anywhere
does it matter where i am
are we are we really fishing now
are we really there it goes there goes
wow riveting content
that's what i like to see you can get it
anywhere it's just rare okie dokie
wow this is amazing wow
what an amazing stream
wow wow wow
wow amazing wow so many fish too
wow there we go oh my god did you oh did
you see that did you see that
did you see how fast it zoomed over to
me oh my god
amazing but honestly guys
honestly guys i was close to just
canceling the stream
all together aren't you proud of me for
like trying to really get it to work for
five hours and then
instead of canceling it completely i
actually just said okay i'm gonna play
minecraft now
aren't you guys proud of me old kiara
would say [\h__\h] it i'm not streaming
today old kiana would say
i'm not streaming today all this sucks
i would say no thank you but here i am
cardboard kiana minecraft
shitty microphone but honestly the
microphone it looks so cute
it looks so cute though i got this
microphone just for
traveling purpose thank you
character character development exactly
i got the microphone for like just for
this purpose
i wanna oops that was too early
it's so cute it's do you know what um if
you it's a it's a it's a pink
raisin uh raisin saran
mini or something like that it's like
super small
and it's like uh like if it breaks
it's in the price range where i don't
give a [\h__\h]
so razor raisin raise rate on it
wait razor or raisin razor razor razor
say rin
mini what was that a bow you can get
bowls from fishing
i don't want balls
what i thought i got something exciting
sudden audio quality increase
where no way no eh
what
audio changed
what i got closer i just i don't know i
touched it for a second i don't know
what's happening
i didn't really get closer but
well hello actually
sounds cleaner oh interesting
[Music]
maybe it's the positioning hey
surprise asmr hey what's up guys do you
hear me
you guys hear me
[Music]
fishing asmr
do you like this i don't like it
oh fish
that's just [\h__\h] what the hell it
tickles
it's ridiculous i hate asmr
i i really asmr is the most awkward
thing to me ever
i don't understand i don't understand
i mean like if it's if it's like
erotic sounds then i understand what you
guys are doing
but if it sounds like eating eating or
like i don't know finger tapping sound
or
or cleaning your ear sound i don't know
how i'm
it why are you watching this stuff
stream what the hell
uh um yeah but what
what is it with this finger tapping i
don't get it or like i don't know any
any what's
what's it with this or like the sound
when you like
when you uh what where's my item
what about the sound when when
[Music]
german translation please german
translation
strokes your eye yeah like when someone
raffles
through your hair there i i've heard
asmr like that too
what what who is who is that for who
wants to hear that
i mean i guess some of you like it but
like why
just ruffle your own hair what the hell
trigger something in my back it tickles
oh interesting
what the what the hell no
no no no no no
county is a laptop is pretty cool though
she got a new laptop for streaming
did you hear that i don't know it's just
uh it's just uh
i don't i don't i didn't even read that
i think it wants to update some
system or something windows that that's
a windows noise that i never heard
before what was that
but honestly i'm surprised that we're
actually streaming uh
and the stream is not not even
like lagging or stopping like buffering
or anything
wow in that's that's hotel wi-fi right
now
i can't i can't promise that will be uh
stable
uh later on because we are switching
hotels later
i can't promise that it will be stable
stable uh
in the other hotel as well wait
[\h__\h] fish only guys okay decide what
i do next i don't want to
fish anymore what the hell this is
absolutely ridiculous
i don't want a fish anymore
next mission what's your next mission
farm okay now i i don't mind farming
because look at my farm and there has
some stuff has to be made here okay
[Music]
wait i don't have any space for those
seeds
diorite gravel
cobblestone cobblestone there you go
oopsie neat
build a hotel huh i don't have much time
left i mean we don't have to
stop exactly at one hour we can do it a
bit longer
until cali actually that kelly's stream
starts at
in uh 45 minutes or something like that
no
so we can stream until then in theory
oh man i still have a too many
i don't even need all these seats
i don't even need them all ah one hour
and 45 minutes in our stream oh
oh that's so much time that's so much
time
okay i have another idea then
maybe but actually i don't know if i
want to do that now
we could
you guys tell me what to do
she moved yeah she also moved her stream
a little bit
because i had to move mine and she
wants a little bit more spa time you
know because we were
we were trying so hard for hours on that
stupid technical [\h__\h] took away the
goddamn spa time i didn't go to the spa
that's okay because actually to be
honest um
i'm not i don't feel very comfortable
being naked
in these japanese spas not not
really not really my thing you know
not really my thing
i mean if callie was there
oh no no no no too embarrassing
no no no oopsie
oops
use okay we did the farming guys we did
the thing
get rid of that
i want my cobblestone again give me my
cobblestone back
nice we did it mission accomplished
hell yeah hell yeah let's go back
and make some bread build build a giant
kiara or
ah
what about not building a giant kiana
but building a giant chicken
what about that guys hmm
yes okay i don't have my reference down
oh so it will probably look horrible
but we can try we can try where did i
put my stone there we go
i cleaned up so nicely the other day i'm
so proud
i am so proud
put that there put that there put that
there
okay okay whatever i don't care about my
inventory
i don't care
okay so i have a lot of materials though
so we can use white wool
i would like more orange let's see uh
wait sleep
oh freestyle white chicken
i can try that we can we can get white
chicken
white chicken
just just ignore the description it will
be fixed later everything here is
scuffed hello
lonely chicken who survived that's only
red where's my orange
well yeah the orange chickens were he uh
orange orange sheeps were here for
[\h__\h] sake
are you know what wait oh wait enough
must have orange
i'll give her some i'll give her another
color instead
wait how do you when can i not run
am i running now am i running am i
dashing right now
is this how i'm running
no why why is it not running
it doesn't work ctrl doesn't work guys
it's not working
i am running really really wait do i
have to go wait
oh nice
nice okay uh what other color could we
use oh what does a dakuma
chicken look like trying to
imagine it in my head i feel like it had
some red in it
and probably
[Music]
channel channeling my inner takuma
chicken
what does the tacoma chicken look like
we'll try to make it out of our
imagination
replace shears what
no that's not how it looks like but okay
we can take that down the icon the
chicken icon we can take it as a
um wait wait wait wait wait wait i need
what are they called the things i want
to build on top of here oh no actually
let me build on top of that
what is that thing called to go on like
um scaffolding
scaffolding i think i have somewhere
uh here no here no here
no here here stand up stand up stand up
stand up sit
scaffolding
how do you make it scarf wait
how what's what's it called what is it
called
need bamboo oh [\h__\h]
i don't have bamboo okay i don't need
that
i don't need that i got my stones here
gran granny green each
or like let's let's go with die or right
sounds like diet coke or something like
that
need bamboo and string i don't i don't
wanna i don't wanna
i don't need scaffolding only people
think they're cool when they
use scaffolding who the [\h__\h] needs
scaffolding scaffolding i don't know i
don't even know what to say i don't give
a [\h__\h]
i don't care okay this is all i need
okay okay so we would want it to be
three-dimensional
it's gonna be interesting and we want it
to be three-dimensional
let me okay one second let me see um
that's not that's not exactly the
chicken that i'm imagining
those are white chickens i want an
orange chicken
sorry i was just looking at it for
inspiration
okay uh well first of all
uh i need actually i need yellow
i need wait let me look i'm at google
chicken
yeah hey thank you google that's perfect
oh god there's you know what also comes
up is uh
amez amis abe's version
of like you know the
you know you know the one where
i i don't even know how to explain it do
you know what i mean
the one that's like um
i i can't explain
yeah the fake one with the the butt
which looks like a rat which like uh
looks around its shoulders
oh my god okay so actually
uh i guess black let me go back again
i need ah
i have my shears
i i would like some black please
hello i haven't seen you guys in a while
uh uh-huh thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
thank you thank you wonderful let me get
the wool
[Music]
oh oh
there's a chick i saw a chicken in there
chicken this chicken is trying to be a
sheep
my friend that's impossible i know
exactly who you are but okay i will i
will let you believe that you are a
sheep
i see you're having an existential
crisis and i don't want to judge you
because of that some people sometimes
just have existential crises
gotta be supportive of my employees
right oopsie
i support my employees mental health
that's the most important thing
at kfp we take care of our employees
totally all right
okay so let's make a document chicken
we can do it i believe in myself okay so
feet uh let's make it uh i have no idea
i've never done something like this
before
okay feet oh my god it's
okay this is a one foot oh god
i don't i don't i don't know from which
perspective are we even gonna look at it
i don't
this is gonna be a monster um maybe like
that yeah
this is gonna be a monster i i don't
even know how to do this
it's gonna have some long legs actually
that could work do you guys see what i'm
trying to do
it's going to be huge though i need a
bit more space here
but you guys see what i'm trying to do
right uh
wait no that's kind of wrong wait how do
you
ah is it the shears do you do it with
the shears
oh no cut it
no oh yes okay
i mean wait what uh
what what yeah that's correct
okay okay okay legs complete
sexy legs oh hello
hello okay okay and then we just make a
really thick round chicken that's it but
like do we fill it inside
it's gonna take a lot of wool i guess we
could fill it with anything really but
okay um
let's make like a base that i can walk
around them
smart smart i know how to make a chicken
i know how to make a chicken okay okay
okay okay do i really do
oh wait that's uh actually i need some i
need some like um
i need some turquoise color
okay i don't know what i'm doing
yeah i don't know what i'm doing guys do
i ever know what i'm doing though
[Music]
oh yummy i don't know
it's just going to be a chicken ever
ever
okay that's uh that's probably looking
pretty good
i think it's probably looking good guys
trust me
trust me trust me white
chicken ouch okay let's look at that
i mean it will look good
at some point it will look good
eventually oops
this is yeah this is going to be
wonderful exactly
just believe in it believe
oh god damn it how do i i can't work
like this
i cannot work like this oh my god okay
so it gets thicker to the outside right
so
basically what we want is uh
uh here
i don't know how to build this ah
okay okay let's try to let's try to
build only the outside and not the
inside
uh
it gets it gets thicker at first and
then it gets
thinner again at the top mm-hmm
believe me
[Music]
is this vacation kia yes this is my
vacation
honestly it's so weird you guys gonna
you should you would have you would have
to see
um our hotel room it's like two laptops
next to each other
and like phones and and uh
like camera arms and
microphones a capture card
a switch everything like all together on
one table
it's like what what the hell did we come
here for
to stream what
something is wrong here
something is very wrong here the purpose
i i don't i don't know what our purpose
is anymore
what why are we here just to stream
exactly it's very confusing very
confusing i think the hotel staff is
also thinking what the hell did these
girls come here for
what why did they come here in the first
place
what is this did they come
did they not come for sightseeing no we
are here to work
uh free wi-fi i mean it's not exactly
free since the hotel
is uh not exactly on the on the cheap
side
it's not exactly the cheapest hotel
okay is this gonna work this is gonna
work right
yes yes yes yes
yes the only option is yes
ah freaking the chicken faking the
chicken
thicken the chicken even more hell yeah
thicken the chicken
faking the chicken faking the chicken
even more hell yeah
freaking the chicken faking the chicken
thicken the chicken even more
hell yeah freaking the chicken faking
the chicken
freaking the chicken even more hell yeah
faking the chicken
thicken the chicken freaking oh my god
you know what
as as a german speaking person
that makes me feel very uncomfortable
because i'm basically saying [\h__\h] the
chicken in german
um yes
i mean chicken is english yes but the
the thickening
uh thicken the chicken the first part in
german
yeah makes me feel very uncomfortable
maybe we shouldn't have told you guys
but i'm just trying to be honest here
okay
just trying to be honest
okay let's go down but if i go down will
i ever get back in here
i feel like no how thick
how thick does a chicken have to be
maybe we can do one layer maybe we can
start like uh
like we can do this now we can just
build up on the on the already existing
thickness of this beautiful chicken
i have this beautiful orange chicken
wait yup
we could have done this with pumpkins as
well honestly pumpkin chicken
mmm that sounds like a good dish
did someone ever cook something like
that before pumpkin chicken
doesn't that sound like for people who
like pumpkins that sounds amazing
honestly i like
i like pumpkin soup for example example
imagine like a pumpkin curry
pumpkin curry with a chicken in there
and i don't know sounds gross gross you
sound gross
i'm pretty sure that's gonna be amazing
that's not exactly what [\h__\h]
that's not exactly on hatama level it it
had
it needs some tarantulas and some
spiders and
stuff scorpions look at the chicken
three two one go i mean yeah actually
i can see it i can see it i see it
yeah wait
it actually looks actually that looks
good
oh my god
let's sleep hi chad i see you
it doesn't really wait did you say it
doesn't rain sand blows chicken it
definitely does resemble a chicken but
we need more orange though
i'm sorry inna i'll pay you back i swear
i i also i think she'll probably be fine
with it right let's bring some more
orange
also i um does she have like is it
possible to make like a turquoise
color like something in between green
and
and blue light blue is that possible
like not that
not that i mean worst case we're gonna
use that maybe
yes cyan really where does she have it
ah when that gets close enough but
that's not the one that you're talking
about guys right or is it
is that it
what can it get yeah that's it oh
cyan is lighter oh well how what what do
i have to mix together
also that could take ages to be honest
but i mean i could i could eventually
um just um change the parts later on
which i needs to be in uh turquoise we
can change it later
also by the way how does this like do
that
does this work with like sheers do they
ever get like
uh how does this work anyway
did i ever get replaced
inna's machine has stopped because the
cheeseburger oh so if i put in a sheer
like right here
do i put it in there
yeah okay cool oh
wonder how fast that's working
go do it do it do it but how do i turn
it back on
is it working now
cut it cut it cut this
ah shear first and then place it
oh it's naked
okay now
that's so embarrassing sorry sorry dude
sorry he's naked he's so slim now
okay i think it's probably working right
yay okay back to work oh wait that's the
color i want
i think
that's i think that's a is it
or is that just light blue wait is that
the same color as
what
that's a different color right is that a
different color
is that a different color or is that the
same
don't look at me like that i don't know
i don't know
same okay i'll try to
eventually get the right color uh
actually
no no no no no let me go back and for
now
i'm why am i not running i ask myself
but i need to eat something
for now me colorblind
shut up shut up
let me get the blue food one for now
and uh later
i'll get something uh else
uh later on but really is that
that's a different color yeah wait a
second
wait a second wait a second now
we can we can find out
wait a second
all right let me see this is a different
one
the moment of truth
okay everyone who said are you color
blind if you
that is a different color that is a
different color
hell yeah i need more of that scion i
need more of that
oh my god ina we have to capture that
one
we have to capture it how do i you know
i need your help i need your help enough
how did you do this
nice kiara thank you thank you i'm sorry
you it's okay it's okay i forgive you
when she had a special color there i
want that one
chad is colorblind with a leash
i want more of that one okay we'll get
to that eventually not today today is
not the day
but we can make the base of the chicken
that's the least we can do yes yes yes
yes yes
okay continuing
okay because i want to make the wings
i want to make the wings out of cyan and
some some
a little part of the breast of this sexy
chicken breast
[Music]
nice
how do i go back in there
okay this will be this will be fun to
get rid of
later on oh damn it damn it
damn it
okay all right nice
this how you're supposed to do it i
don't i don't need scaffolding
who needs that
not me it was
continuing to thicken the chicken faking
the chicken hell yeah thickening the
chicken
faking the chicken
thickening the chicken i don't want to
use scaffolding
over my dead body you sure
[Music]
oh okay
something's wrong here
oh well no
no chicken is perfect no chicken is
perfect
um that's okay
that's okay you're still beautiful
but how do we continue do we make um do
we make it even thicker
yes maybe maybe
no no no no no no okay one row
like this
you're giving thousands of people oc ocd
ticks right now kiara
you are welcome you're welcome my
friends
by the way should it maybe be like
should it have a little bit of a
of some you know some fluff here
oh no now that that gives me ocd too
oh cd sounds like some kind of
uh edgy rock band
don't you think so does that look weird
i wanna i don't wanna go back
i don't wanna go down to check it out
because that will just be very painful
to get back up
welcome to kfb little egg welcome to the
membership thank you for joining
yay normally my streams are not as
scuffed as this
everyone who's here i mean i don't think
there's anyone here for the first time
i would hope there's no one here for the
first time
because i don't want to see i don't want
the first thing you that you guys see
to beat a stream that's this scuffed
um let me just tell you normally my
streams are not
this horrible believe me
believe me
the one who triggers your ocdc
[Music]
beautiful i think this is about pretty
much what you guys look
like no i think it comes pretty close to
how beautiful you guys look like you you
guys look like this no
i think i i think some of you guys sent
me selfies before and you guys looked
exactly like that so
pretty accurate i would say i mean what
what else would you expect from me
huh i'm the chicken mama i know exactly
what you guys look like
what kind of mom would i be if i
wouldn't know okay you know what
we'll make another row on top of this
and then go down and see if we are ready
to
thin the chicken what's what's the
opposite of thickening the chicken
what's the opposite guys
i'm an owl i don't look like that but
you look pretty close
like that though deflating deflating the
chicken
thinning slimming the chicken thinning
thinning the chicken
but you know it's it's okay you can be
thick and beautiful but
this isn't a question of anatomy
at the top you just get thinner because
that's where you had this little chicken
so we're going down are we going down i
might die if i jump down here
i could try to jump right into that
water
i mean even if i die i can pick
everything up easily oh hi zombie
oh no
oh god what are you doing on my field
you little piece of
[\h__\h] i hope you die
do i have no i have a can i find him a
fishing round
okay i'm jumping i'm jumping three two
one go no no oh
that was so close that was so close
that was so close god damn it i was
gonna be like hell yeah look at me i did
it
wait wait let me let me first go to
sleep oh no why
why the door's open
stupid questions my door is always open
you're always welcome
to come into my office and tell me what
happened in your shift and complain or
do whatever
you're very welcome to do that oh no
okay and the thing is just i will listen
to you
but afterwards i will put you into the
usual room
that's okay with you that's okay right
oh
ah
i i will i will uh i will go back and
um thin in the chicken now
and then
we we must add some thickening here
we must thicken the chicken here but
then then it will look beautiful
believe me kiana do you know any swedish
no i do not
no i don't
i know a lot of german though because my
my that's
my most fluent language oh no
too stupid to get up there who needs who
needs scaffolding anyway
all right all right all right all right
are you guys enjoying this stream
are you you better
not enjoying it is not an option
it's not an option
yes very much
good i wouldn't have expected any other
answer
i'm gonna make some stairs now isn't
that amazing
wow look at that technique
absolutely professional
wow jules
wow wow
[Music]
wow okay going back
in how do we do this
um well first of all get rid of that one
i see what that did there i see
okay how do i place it
like that
okay okay nice
eat some food guys
10 out of 10 content no matter if you're
covered or not
thank you thank you
i that actually is a quite a really
thank you
thank you i'm very worried about this
but
as long as you guys are enjoying it
better than having no stream at all
right
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
what happens if i get rid of that one oh
no
no i got it i got it all good all good
guys
don't panic
okay we need some help here
and here okay okay
i might be enjoying this more than other
minecraft streams actually what
you mean other minecraft streams from
from me or oops no that's not the right
spot or minecraft streams in general
how is this more enjoyable than the
usual content
no that's just oops that is impossible
that's actually that would make me sad
because i put a lot of effort into the
usual content
you're sillier you are silly
how am i i mean at least we're finally
doing something that i always wanted to
do put a chicken
on the chicken house that's something
that was one of my life goals putting a
chicken on the chicken house hell you
life goal accomplished
we put a lot of effort into this one too
thank you
i mean yes i we did put a lot a lot of
effort into
however into this stream however
it uh it didn't uh
end up uh successful
we failed we have failed but we have
tried
it's always important to at least try
it's the microphone what what is the
micro you like the scuff that the
microphone
gives you oh yes
gotta love this stuff what's going on
here
what is this what's this what is this
huh
wait are you supposed to go inside
wait a second
no
okay okay okay
okay we are finishing the chickening
we are finishing the chickening
okay more thinning the chickening
thinning the chickening putting the
chicken in
the chicken well how do i make the hat
though
the head should be like somewhat round
and very flat
pretty flat because uh that's just the
beautiful
anatomy of the dakuma
chicken so i think after this layer we
can
yeah flatten it out quite drastically
diamond pickaxe to get rid of wool
what's your problem what's your problem
huh huh
huh no problem with that thank you for
the membership thank you
welcome welcome to the membership
does this hurt you
i don't have anything else i mean i have
a box
would that make you happier
okay i kind of want to go down and see
if it's okay to make the head now
um before we do that though
let me let me do something here let me
try
wait so there's the legs the legs are
like somewhere here so
[Music]
i don't know if the wings are going to
be difficult
wings are gonna be very difficult let's
see
thank you for the membership welcome
okay let's look at it let's look at it
fly little bird fly i don't think this
one can fly
oh
no no too early
too early should have gone up straight a
little bit more
[Music]
damn it it's difficult to make the
perfect chicken
i wonder when cali is gonna come back
from the spa
hope she's okay will she be okay
should i should i go and look for her
[Music]
oops
oh wait i have all the jumper nice
usually i would hate that
okay wait so wait wait wait wait i
wanted to add some fluff
here oh
thank you auto jump oh no no no no no no
um i know actually is that really where
i want to edit
no
is that where i want it
um actually we could just make the wings
here
oopsie wait
uh-huh
uh-huh that works oops no
can you guys imagine can you guys see
what i'm doing
[Music]
big chicken very nice
it's a chicken wing
okay ouch
that hurt quite a lot let's see
turn around uh
no no no no
what's up with the frozen turkey at the
bottom right i am
excuse me i am first of all i'm not a
turkey
second of all i'm i i have the cardboard
disease as kelly likes to say i'm
currently
with cali traveling um
and uh in the hotel
currently it is technically uh
not really possible to show you
my oops my moving self
unfortunately i'm very sorry about that
i will be back moving as per usual
soon in a few streams
it has to be like this for a couple of
streams i'm sorry
there's uh not much choice that we have
actually there's no choice at all this
is how it is
it do be like that sometimes
where are you i want to get up there
and switch from inside maybe yeah
um
[Music]
[\h__\h] i'm gonna die building this chicken
i'm going to die
if that keeps white kia out of the way
sounds good to me what's your problem
with white kiara
we love you for you not for your body
tangent really
i do i wouldn't i wouldn't judge you
if you would say you love my body
i wouldn't judge you i want that please
i don't know what i'm building right now
got it
is this how people usually build these
kind of things like it seems like very
um uh improvised to me
i do love your body scaffolding helps
[\h__\h] scaffolding they normally have
scaffold
[\h__\h] it who needs that
this is this shows real talent here my
friends
this is real talent
and so i wanted to get rid of some of
the top layers because it's not working
out
damn it i don't have any stones anymore
damn it
oh i love your body oh thank you
thank you that's very sweet
i like to hear that
ah okay so we'll get rid of that
you you
i fell down this is annoying this is why
i respect all the people who build
things like this especially if they
build it like
without a plan if they just build it
from scratch
like me that's that's that's i respect
you oh my god
also i mean 2d meals are fairly easy but
these 3d
stuff that's difficult oi
[Music]
now i want to get rid of that layer too
trap the burp she called us old
what i did not call you old how did i
call you guys old
you guys are
i don't know i mean i think there's so
some there might be some oldies but
there's nothing wrong with being old
that's totally fine everyone is welcome
old chickens young chickens medium
aged chickens thank you for the
membership
thank you welcome i welcome all kinds of
chickens on my stream
baby chickens yes baby chickens are also
welcome
we gotta you know you gotta welcome
everyone feels like a family
we are family
is 25 volts i would say no
i would think no
okay how much more do we want to
get rid of yeah we should get rid of
this whole layer that goes inside
turning fruity this month nice
i think i guess you i mean celebrate it
be happy about it celebrate
your experience in life
i'm 16 years old i'm baby no you're not
a baby you should at least
you should think that you're you should
think of yourself as an adult
to be an example
for how how
i don't know don't act like a baby if
you're 16 just don't act like a baby
you're not a baby
thank you for the membership welcome
well kelly has been gone for a long time
what the hell is she not like boiling
boiling to death like if i'm too long in
an
onsen i get like i feel like really
dizzy and stuff
like after five minutes
i will feel like super dizzy is she okay
is she okay
yeah she does it more often than me but
still
i want to check it just for health and
security reasons i want to check out if
she's okay you know
just for health and security reasons
no other reason
i wish this chicken would be more round
i wish it was rounder
maybe one day i'll just delete the whole
thing
and just do it all over
why are you doubting me
what's there to doubt guys
you guys don't trust me you want to work
for me but you don't trust me you have
to be able to trust your boss
oh sh
we need to do the second wing too
how would i do the second wing huh
okay okay
okay the question is more or
not i think maybe one row
one more row would be good and then
we're thinning the chicken ink
kiana's voice sounds so nice today
usually she is way too loud for me what
what do you mean eh huh
what i really wonder what what does that
mean
you mean my way of speaking normally is
too loud and now i'm quiet or do you
mean the microph is it the microphone
it's the cheap microphone effect and the
hotel acoustics
oh no we ran out of orange wool again
that's actually
a problem because
i mean there's a lot of rule here but
how am i gonna get back out again
um it's gonna be a problem because there
is no more orange room we have to stop
building but that's okay because uh cali
is
streaming soon anyway we have 18 more
that we can place
okay 18 more
english yoshi okay i'm gonna use
all all that we all that nature gives to
us
nature being you know
what was this stream originally it was
supposed to be an animal crossing stream
but i knew honestly i knew that
something would go wrong
i knew it
but i knew that one thing would go
strong a good ghost would go strong i
wish it would go strong
and i knew that one thing would go wrong
don't fall down
but more than one thing went wrong
i couldn't stream on my uh
with my switch unfortunately no switch
games during this holiday
that's it so yeah
but it's okay this it's not it's not
like a super long holiday
oh god i'm gonna die ah i can fall down
here oh wait before i fall down how
about i eat
yeah the 51 and clubhouse games will be
something else but we'll think about
it
[Music]
okay i'm ready to fall in
one two three
out okay
nice accomplishment
let's see all right let's sleep first
and then take a look and open
you could do browser board games you
know even for
such browser games we need permission
and
usually they don't answer that fast so i
don't think that's possible but
look at that whoa
[Music]
yeah i mean that's actually pretty close
it just needs to head it'll be like no
and then i need some wings here
and then it will be wonderful we'll be
working on that we will be working on
that in the future as well
not too bad
that's a chicken house actually recently
i slaughtered all the
chickens hi guys but
i already made new ones a lot of new
ones
give me your eggs thank you
[Music]
you have some new ones ouch sorry
you're running into me that's not not my
fault
yeah i just felt like i needed more meat
so i
just could you guys like go away that's
the door go away
bye bye babies oh it looks like it will
have room i will bring some seats wait
wait wait wait wait
they demand freedom well that's
uh i can't i can't do oh i had seats
i can't really help them with that
unfortunately i'll put that here for
later eventually
okay
chickens i got some food
babies hello oops
uh you here guys come
here they come come here come here
babies
no feeding time
everyone gets your food
grow big and strong and then i'll eat
you eventually no just kidding just
kidding just kidding
i will never eat you food
just focus on the food guys just focus
on the food
focus on the food and then you'll be
happy food equals happiness
new babies new babies yes yes ooh lots
of new babies
oh it lagged for a moment there i should
get out of here i should get out of here
okay okay bye bye bye bye
that's it no more food
actually i got some leftover eggs i
don't know where they come from
[Music]
bye bye oh hi
uh no one saw that you didn't see that
guys
what do you mean you saw that you wanna
go to the usual room huh
you wanna go to the usual room huh you
saw
nothing okay nothing
nothing
[\h__\h] where did i go [\h__\h] um
you saw nothing okay well cali is still
not back but
i feel like i did what i was what i
could do actually okay
okay you know what uh
how how do we
get more of that one sheep over there
[Music]
wait what do i eat again wheat if i give
that one sheep
wheat uh
it might make a baby and it might be the
same color as itself right
right
yes no yes no what why is the true
answers
check the last row i already did that's
light blue
for god's sake that's light blue
let me look at it again that's why when
i when i shared it
oh that's light blue that's not cyan
it even says light blue
nope nope nope nope nope nothing here
guys nothing here nothing here to see
but uh i want more i want i want to get
more of that sheep in a natural way
okay one second let's let's get um
let's make another shear
okay ah i have to die
another sheep cyan they don't just
when they recreate but don't they uh
recreate
in the color of either one of the
parents that
uh they were born from what do you what
do you need for cyan dying
but how do i make cyan die
die dude i don't have cyan dye
they mix it's a 50 50 well let's let's
just try it out
let's just try it out
[Music]
hi
okay but
um and wait wait wait wait wait wait
they eat wheat let's give them what they
want where did the shears go
wait did i put the shears in here
yes i did that's not what i wanted to do
and the lead ah so that i can bring it
to me
well i guess i could do that but how do
i make a lead
how do i make a lead guys thank you for
the super chat
threatens with you no i do care about
your mental health very much
believe me alicia
i don't get anything from that you can't
craft it oh my freaking god i don't have
one
no i don't have one i never got one
how how come i've unplugged hill now
never seen elite before
ina aina has sung she has one left over
uh
[Music]
wandering trainers have them oh you mean
if you kill their llamas
wait let me see maybe there's no way
that there's one in here huh
maybe no
no no
no no no
slime farm slime farm you mean the
the exp farm no wait where is the slime
farm take the slime
slime and string is elite what
string oh there we go i got the recipe
oh wait
what's with the people who just said
that lead is a leash is something that i
cannot make myself
what's here with the people who think
they know what they're talking about but
they don't
oh my god
unbelievable
okay i believed you
i believed you because you sounded so
confident when you said
uh a leash cannot be made in minecraft
you have to find it
so many of you said it i trusted you
i trusted you where did where was it
originally oh yeah
oh there's even more uh orange one not
money though
okay because you don't have slime
but they could have told me ah okay
wait wait wait wait so then i just bring
it back to me okay
well well well well well
so oh you guys are looking at me now so
feed you
make a baby come on make one make a baby
maybe i feed the others too
okay come on baby baby that's the right
color
oh my god we did it
we did it guys perfect
good night uh
but um so what if i take this one and
i'll leave another baby
can i can you come over here
no how do welcome back
i was worried about you
oh you did tune in yeah i was laying
down and i looked at my phone
oh and i went to your stream and you
were saying i wonder how cali is i
should go check on
ah that's why you get them out ah she
wanted to
what kelly no no you shouldn't say
something like that
are you feeling better a little bit oh
okay i'm basically i can stop streaming
anytime
it's what someone with an addiction says
[Music]
um
i don't know what i'm doing come back in
here okay okay close the gate close the
gate
okay close this one too okay give me the
lead
do i have the lid where did you go i
have it okay
now i want the cyan one
give it to me give it to did i get it oh
wait
come on come on come on here come on oh
wait i need maybe i need
oh no but then everyone comes no no no
no
i don't know how to do it damn it go
away
okay ff all of you leave me
wait where did my leash go there oh no
no
open why does it break though why does
it break
come on move okay
that's it okay it moved a little bit now
everyone can move back already go back
go back there's nothing to see here
[Music]
feed the sheep no
no they all want from something okay
what if we let everyone escape
what what will ena say if i let everyone
escape
damn it okay i i don't know you know
will have to help me with that
you know will have to help me with that
eventually i give up
for today i give up especially because
cali is back so now i'll
i'll leave i i will
wait did i close the gates
she would go muhammad
that all my sheeps escaped huh
honestly why why is this why is this so
difficult
how are they in the ballet i wonder if
you could do this for me i don't know
how to do this
huh welcome to the scuffed stream arena
one thing if you're ever in the
situation where you are as
scuffed as me as scuffed as this stream
is don't worry your viewers will love it
just just keep on streaming no problem
with uh streaming like this
i think okay ah
okay that's it that's it guys
i am i'll be here uh i'll be seeing you
guys
tomorrow on cali's channel and
um the day after tomorrow on this
channel
then the day after that on cali's
and then the day after that on my
channel again i think
just check my schedule if you don't
understand where
me and me and callie are currently on a
trip
and during this trip we are like one day
streaming on her channel one day
streaming on my channel one day stream
on her channel and then
we go back uh so yeah
i'll see you guys tomorrow i hope you
had fun
at least a little bit hopefully
we'll be enjoying our little honeymoon
and as much as we can tomorrow
and check out what's outside
and yeah i'll take some cute pictures
that we can show you
and at the end of our trip after
the trip is over
okay have fun on your honeymoon thank
you
thank you i will i will
thank you guys okay sorry for the
scuffness but i am glad you guys came
anyway
um in
i'll see you and bye bye thank you for
watching
and in german we say auf wiedersehen
[Music]
mavidasi
bye bye see you tomorrow
bye
[Music]
you